(Episode 53)
- Seo Rin.
- You're wrong.
I'm not Seo Rin. I'm Jang Mi.
Oh Jang Mi.
The same Oh Jang Mi you've been
trying so desperately to kill.
What did you say?
You killed my dad, didn't you?
Why did you kill him?
- Don't do this. Let me go.
- Tell me why you killed him.
Why did you have
my innocent father killed?
Manager Lee forced my father to drink
and then killed him.
That was on your orders, wasn't it?
Please, let me live.
Let go of me and talk.
Die!
You had my father killed,
so you deserve to die too.
You're going to die just like he did!
Please, don't kill me.
Is sending you to jail going
to bring my father back?
You're going to suffer the same way.
The exact same way!
Let go of me...
You monster!
You tried to kill me,
but you hurt Seo Rin instead, didn't you?
You knew that we were twins.
That's why you tried to get rid of me!
No, I swear...
You even barred me from the hotel
so I wouldn't run into Seo Rin.
You were afraid our secret about
being twins would get out.
You're pretty good at figuring things out,
aren't you?
That's right.
My dad must have run into Seo Rin.
And that's how he found out
that we were twins.
So to keep that a secret,
you had my father killed, right?
Bingo.
Why would you do that?
Why were you so desperate
to hide that we're twins?
Why?
Did stealing Seo Rin away
from my mother make you happy?
Are you having a blast
living as Grandpa's daughter-in-law now?
Is this why you stole Seo Rin from my mom
just to live like this?
Even going so far as to hurt my mother...
You're smarter than I gave you credit for.
Then again, if you're Seo Rin's twin,
I guess you'd be just as smart.
Seo Rin was clever too, you know.
"Was?"
Does that mean you know
what happened to Seo Rin?
I do.
She's fighting for her life in your place.
You're so lucky.
Shut up, you evil monster!
You raised her yourself for 30 years.
Seo Rin was your daughter.
And yet, she was hurt because of you.
How can you be such a monster?
How?
If you were in my shoes,
you'd do the same thing.
People aren't born evil.
Their circumstances make them that way.
You shameless monster!
You're a devil in disguise!
You're not blind,
so you saw what happened.
Because you took Seo Rin away
from my mother,
she's ended up like this!
How could you tear a child
from her mother...
and raise her as your own?
Why not? What was stopping me?
Do you think I'm just going
to let you get away with this?
For my mother's suffering
and for my father's life,
I'll make you pay for everything!
You just wait!
Did Baek Ho go to see Oh Jang Mi
first thing this morning?
Just let him be. I've given up on him.
Honestly, we should give Baek Ho an award
for his unwavering devotion.
That kid, I swear.
He got that from you, you know.
You never had eyes for anyone else.
Just loyal to one woman to a fault.
My goodness, he's your spitting image.
He acts the exact same way.
- Grandfather.
- Hey!
Come in, sweetheart.
Is there something you need?
You can tell me anything.
Grandfather, it's about my cell phone.
Mom clearly told me she threw it away
because it was broken,
but when she was on the phone
with someone,
I heard her ask when the phone was
going to be fixed.
I just thought that was a little strange.
What?
I'll have a word with your mother
about it.
It's not right for her to go through
her own kid's phone like that.
I know, right?
Grandfather, you're the best!
Thank you, Grandfather.
What could this be about?
Yes, Father.
Ma'am, we have a huge problem.
What are you talking about?
You took Seo Rin's phone
from the repair shop?
She may be your daughter,
but it's not right to snoop
through a grown woman's phone.
Snooping? No, I was just...
What did the doctor say?
He told you not to be so impatient.
Her memories will all come back
soon enough,
so stop pressuring Seo Rin.
Yes, Father.
(CEO Chae Hwa Young)
I was on my way out of the repair shop
with Director Ma's phone,
but Secretary Kim was waiting for me,
so I had no choice.
You're right. Refusing to hand it over
would've looked more suspicious.
But how did Father know
I was having Seo Rin's phone repaired?
Anyway, that sly old fox.
I can't let my guard down for one second.
If Director Ma really met Oh Jang Mi,
her phone is sure
to have Oh Jang Mi's contact information.
What if she finds it on the phone
and tries to contact Oh Jang Mi?
That's what I'm worried about.
If any of Oh Jang Mi's family
sees Seo Rin,
they'll find out
they're twins immediately.
That would be a disaster.
Before that happens,
we have to get rid of Oh Jang Mi's phone.
- We're out of time, so let's move fast.
- Understood.
(Oh Jang Mi)
If Chae Hwa Young had seen this,
it would've been a huge mess.
She almost found out that we met.
(Delete, Select Item)
(All Selected)
(Delete all calls?)
There might still be evidence
in a voice recording or in the cloud.
Jang Mi,
who in the world were you going to meet?
Tae Sook, listen.
Jang Mi's phone is completely dead.
I should take it to a repair center.
We don't even know when she'll wake up.
What's the point? Just leave it.
Don't worry. I'll drop it off on my way.
I'll be back tomorrow.
(Suk Hee's Side Dishes)
Oh, my.
Ma'am.
What brings you here?
Well... I heard Manager Lee...
ran into Tae Pyung at the hospital.
I heard Jang Mi was seriously injured.
Yes.
I'm so sorry to hear that.
So how is she doing?
The surgery went well,
but she hasn't woken up yet.
I'm sure she'll wake up.
Don't you worry, Tae Sook.
Thank you.
What excuse can I use to get inside?
Oh my gosh, are you okay?
I feel dizzy.
It must be my anemia.
I think I need to lie down for a minute.
Oh, dear, come inside.
Right this way.
Here, have some water.
I don't see Tae Pyung or Jang Mi's mother.
My mom wanted to see Jang Mi,
so they went to the hospital.
That's a relief.
I'm sorry?
I was worried that Jang Mi's mother
might have fallen ill from the shock.
I see.
How's your dizziness?
Are you feeling any better now?
I'll just rest for a bit before I go.
Tae Sook, you should get back
to your store.
I'm keeping you from your business.
This isn't right.
No, don't worry about it.
Go. Just get out of here!
No, really. I feel bad holding you up.
How about you pack up some side dishes
for me to take home?
Then I'll pack the usual for you.
Thanks.
That was Oh Jang Mi's room, right?
Darn it. Where is her phone?
Mom, you said you wanted to see Jang Mi,
so I brought you to see her.
So why are you going on
about Tok Hee again?
A burglar!
A burglar's here!
Wait, CEO Chae...
What are you doing here?
She's a burglar.
She's here to steal something!
She's a very bad burglar.
Mom, stop.
CEO Chae?
What do you mean, a burglar?
For goodness' sake.
I was just trying to call Manager Lee
to bring the car around,
but my battery died.
I was just trying to charge it,
but I've become a thief now.
I am so sorry.
My mother isn't well.
I apologize for her behavior.
Mom, that's enough.
Why are you treating her like this?
She's a burglar. She's a bad thief.
She's here to steal something!
- Mom.
- Mom, stop...
Yes, Father.
Yes.
Right. Today's the day
Seo Rin has her appointment.
I totally forgot.
I'll take her there right away.
I wish Baek Ho would move on
and meet another woman.
But the woman he loves
is lying in a hospital bed.
Do you really think
he would even consider it?
Remember that one lovely young woman
I keep telling you about?
The one who came by the office
the other day?
- Hello.
- Oh my, Hong Ju.
Oh, dear.
I think Baek Ho went
to the hospital to see her again.
I see.
It seems Lawyer Kang is never here
when I come to visit.
He's either at the hospital
or at her house.
He's such a mess.
I wonder how he gets any work done.
We've met at a meeting before, haven't we?
Yes, hello, Professor.
That's right.
You two must have met while working
on the Dream Hotel project.
Yes.
By any chance, do you know
which hospital Oh Jang Mi is in?
(General Surgeon Kim Jung In)
Good.
Her progress is looking very good.
Doctor, I was wondering...
if she could come to the office
and slowly get back to work.
I thought working with someone she likes
might help her get better.
"Someone she likes?"
As long as she doesn't overdo it,
working a little bit should be fine.
The stimulation from daily life
could be good for her.
(Name: Oh Jang Mi)
Oh Jang Mi.
Welcome.
No way.
Lawyer Kang is dating a woman like her?
Oh Jang Mi.
How can you be lying here like this?
You were so healthy.
They say,
"You never know what life has in store."
I guess that saying is spot on.
Well, it worked in my favor.
(Exam Room 1)
Mom, I'm just going to run
to the restroom.
Okay, sure. I'll wait here.
Seo Rin.
I'm here.
It's me, Oh Jang Mi.
Please open your eyes, okay?
How can you just keep
lying here like this?
Did you check Oh Jang Mi's hospital room?
How is she?
She is still the same,
with no signs of waking up.
But it seems the hospital bills
were becoming a problem.
They moved her from the ICU
to a regular room.
I figured as much.
By the way,
I just saw Kang Baek Ho leaving.
You should leave soon
so you don't run into him.
What? Kang Baek Ho was here?
Seo Rin just went to the restroom.
What if they run into each other?
I'll go find her right away.
Where did Baek Ho go?
His mother definitely said
he went to the hospital.
There he is.
It looks like fate wants
to bring Baek Ho and me together.
He's so incredibly handsome.
Oh, gosh.
Aren't you Lawyer Kang Baek Ho?
What are you doing here?
Fancy seeing you here.
It's a complete coincidence today.
Just a coincidence.
Since fate seems
to keep bringing us together,
please take my business card.
(Jin Hong Ju, Team Leader
of Food and Beverage, Dream Hotel)
So you work at Dream Hotel.
Yes.
Are you here to see someone?
I had some business here as well.
What a coincidence.
Well...
Being in a hospital really makes me
appreciate my health.
Oh, right.
You were at our hotel's reopening party,
right?
How did you know that?
For the renewal,
I worked with Professor Kang Nam Bong.
I was actually the one
who sent out the invitation.
And it turned out you were there
as Professor Kang's son.
Yes, that's right.
I recently heard the news...
about what happened to Professor Kang.
He must have been going through a lot.
- Well, he has.
- How is Professor Kang doing now?
I'd like to pay him a visit
and formally offer my condolences.
- But I'd be intruding, wouldn't I?
- That won't be necessary.
Gosh, he's completely shutting me down.
If we ever meet next time,
buy me a coffee.
How humiliating.
He doesn't give an inch, does he?
Then again, the woman he loves
is lying there in a vegetative state,
so it's not like he's going to be looking
at other women.
He wouldn't be charming
if he moved on that quickly.
One day, I'm going to make him mine.
Yes, ma'am.
Seo Rin is not
in Oh Jang Mi's hospital room.
I don't think
she'll run into Kang Baek Ho.
Baek Ho came here?
Don't worry about it.
I'm sure Seo Rin
couldn't have found out about that.
How could she know that we're the ones
who killed Oh Jang Mi's father?
Even if Seo Rin has met with Oh Jang Mi,
there's no way she could find out
about the Oh Bok Gil case.
Chae Hwa Young,
I'm sure you killed my father.
I swear I will tear you to shreds.
I miss Ok Hee and Tok Hee.
Jang Mi was here too.
Tok Hee is hurting.
Suk Hee's daughters, Ok Hee and Tok Hee.
I met Ok Hee and Tok Hee.
We're together!
Mom.
Why are you out here again?
If we lose you too,
we won't be able to go on.
Tok Hee is hurting.
Suk Hee is sad.
That's right, Mom.
Jang Mi is hurting right now.
But she's going to wake up soon.
Here, Mom. Have some of this.
With Jang Mi gone,
it's just too much to handle, Tae Pyung.
It's all thanks to Jang Mi...
that we've been able
to take care of Mom and get by.
It's okay.
Manager Lee, you can go. I'll drive.
Seo Rin.
I just want to see
if I'm okay to drive now.
I want to be alone with Mom at the park,
so please give us space, Manager Lee.
I'm okay.
Are you sure?
You're really okay to drive?
I'll take it slow.
You have a meeting at 3 p.m., ma'am.
The Chairman and the board of directors
will be there,
so you absolutely can't be late.
- Okay.
- Don't worry.
We're just going to pop over
to the place nearby.
I can finally breathe.
I felt so cooped up.
After being cooped up working,
it feels great to get some fresh air.
The air is so nice here.
Let's take a walk in the park.
Sure. Let me get my purse.
What? Why are you grabbing your purse?
I thought we'd walk light.
- My phone is in my bag.
- Come on, Mom.
Let's take a break from the tyranny
of our phones and just relax.
We came here to unwind.
Let's just clear our heads, okay?
I guess you're right.
The meeting is at 3 p.m.,
so we'll be fine if we leave around 2 p.m.
Until then, let's not take any calls
and just enjoy ourselves, okay?
Okay.
This feels good.
It's nice, isn't it?
That's right. Enjoy it while it lasts.
I'm going to run to the restroom.
Get some rest here.
Okay, go ahead.
Hello, I'd like to report
an illegally parked car.
The license plate number is...
I wonder what time it is.
What's taking Seo Rin so long?
She just went to the restroom.
Seo Rin?
Seo Rin.
She's not here either.
Where could she have gone?
I don't have my phone,
so I can't even call her.
This is so frustrating.
I have to be back at the office by 3 p.m.
Maybe she went back to the car.
What? No way!
Oh my gosh, what in the world is going on?
All my stuff is in that car.
My purse and phone...
What do I do? Hold on.
I need money to take a cab...
and a phone to call someone.
I'm losing my mind.
And I can't be late for that meeting.
What do I do?
What am I going to do?
Chae Hwa Young.
Let's see you squirm a little.
- Isn't Mom back yet?
- Your mom?
She went out with you.
That's strange.
I thought she came back ahead of me.
My legs hurt...
I feel so dizzy.
I can't believe Seo Rin left me.
Where did she go?
Excuse me.
Could I please borrow your phone?
I left mine behind.
No, I can't lend my phone to strangers.
I'm not looking to get scammed.
What? Do I look like a criminal?
I can't believe how heartless people are.
Excuse me, I'm not some weirdo,
but I forgot my phone,
so could I please borrow yours?
Where did Seo Rin go?
Ma Seo Rin!
Unbelievable. Gosh, my legs hurt.
Hey, what's going on?
You still can't get ahold of CEO Chae?
She's keeping
the whole board of directors waiting.
- Director Ma was driving her, so...
- Why are you blaming Seo Rin?
Is CEO Chae a child?
Can't she make it to a meeting on time
without Seo Rin?
- I'm sorry, sir. I'll try her again.
- Forget it! Call it off.
What's the point of having a meeting
without her?
The nerve of her.
Seriously.
Ma Seo Rin, you were supposed
to stick with me.
My legs...
I'm freezing.
Oh my gosh!
Mom!
What is wrong with you, Seo Rin?
Why did you put me through this?
What happened to you? You're a mess.
Mom, did you walk all the way here?
My legs...
My legs are killing me.
What on earth happened?
I went back to the bench,
and you weren't there,
so I just assumed you went to the meeting
and took a cab here.
Our car was gone. It must've been towed
for being illegally parked.
My phone and my purse were in that car!
Oh my gosh.
Really?
I just assumed you'd call Manager Lee
and handle everything.
For someone as capable as you,
that's a piece of cake.
You're good at everything, Mom.
(The First Man)
Two people with similar faces got
into a car accident at the same time?
Ma'am, I need to talk to Director Ma
to confirm something with her.
Could you please have her come in?
Compared to what you did
to my mom, dad, and Seo Rin,
this pain is nothing.
You need to suffer more.
You tried hard to destroy the evidence,
didn't you, Chae Hwa Young?
I have to hurry and find the evidence
Seo Rin hid.
That's the only way
I can finally take down Chae Hwa Young.
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)