Mom, we finally have a chance
to bring Chae Hwa Young down.
How?
I think Chae Hwa Young and Kang Jun Ho
are secretly looking for an investor.
- An investor?
- Yes.
So I came up with a little plan.
- Mom.
- Ma'am.
Come on.
- Mom!
- Ma'am.
Mom, it's me, Tae Pyung.
Tae Pyung.
Baek Ho, thank you so much, too.
I can't tell you how grateful I am...
for you loving and cherishing Jang Mi.
- Thank you. I appreciate it, ma'am.
- Mom,
do you only have eyes for Baek Ho?
I was really moved.
Of course, my dear Tae Pyung.
I feel like Seo Rin woke me up
for a reason.
It's like she's telling me to make
Chae Hwa Young suffer the way she did.
Mom, is that really you?
- It's strange hearing you talk like this.
- Tae Pyung.
Mom being okay has to be a secret
until we take down Chae Hwa Young.
- Don't tell Tae Sook either, okay?
- Of course not.
Baek Ho, you know I can keep a secret,
right?
(Suk Hee's Side Dishes)
Wait, so we're making a plan
to take down Chae Hwa Young?
Yes.
It seems she plans to acquire Hills Hotel
using a slush fund.
Acquire it with a slush fund?
Then it seems she'll create her own hotel
called Dream Hills.
So that's her scheme
to break off from Dream Group.
That's right. She'll acquire Hills Hotel
behind his back, expand it,
and then eventually partner
with Dream Group...
to completely take it over.
But does Chae Hwa Young
even have that kind of money?
She's not planning to buy the hotel
entirely with her own money.
I think she plans to find a major investor
to fund the acquisition.
- We have to stop her before that happens.
- So what we need to do now...
is bring in a big-shot investor
whom Chae Hwa Young can't resist.
Of course, the investor will be a fake.
But it has to be someone
who can fool Chae Hwa Young completely.
That's how we'll make her cough up
that slush fund she's been hiding.
I'd like to be the one to do it.
Is there a high-profile female investor
around my age?
Funny you should ask,
I've already found someone.
Back when I was working part-time
at a K-pop concert,
I happened to help someone out.
Turns out she was a major female investor
from India, Chairman Ali.
How suffocating.
How am I supposed to butter her up?
Who are you trying to butter up?
Chairman Ali understands
every word you're saying.
Let's just start with a slap.
My goodness!
How dare you hit me!
I'm a huge K-drama fan.
What you just said was about me, right?
No, wait, that's not what I meant.
The CEO of Dream Hotel is so classless.
Tommy, let's go to another hotel.
- Tommy, to the lobby.
- Yes, ma'am.
Chairman, I'm so sorry.
Please, you can't leave.
Chairman, please! Chairman Ali!
Chairman.
I am truly sorry.
But I wasn't referring to you earlier.
Please, don't misunderstand, Chairman Ali.
A classless hotel with classless service.
I'm offended.
Get out of the way.
Chairman Ali is furious.
Please, forgive me, just this once.
I'll do everything I can
to make your stay perfect.
Is this how you ask for forgiveness?
Don't you even watch K-Dramas?
- What?
- What are you doing?
Get on your knees, now!
You want me to kneel?
Tommy, this isn't working.
- Let's find another hotel.
- No, wait! Yes, I'll kneel.
No, please.
Chairman. I was truly wrong.
Please forgive me just this once.
Please, don't stay at another hotel.
Please stay at our hotel.
I'll ensure
you're treated with great respect.
What are your orders, Chairman?
I can't forgive you.
I wish I could just...
No. There's too much money at stake.
I have to land her for Dream Hills,
no matter what it takes.
Let's go, Tommy.
No, Chairman!
Excuse me, Chairman.
My apologies. I'm Director Ma Seo Rin.
Director Ma Seo Rin?
What do you mean you're leaving our hotel?
If you could tell me what happened,
I'll make sure we resolve the issue
to your satisfaction.
That woman is rude.
And now the Chairman is furious.
That woman is so vulgar.
She said she was going to cook and eat me.
She eats people? My goodness.
This is horror.
Ms. Chae Hwa Young, is that true?
- No, that's not what...
- We haven't trained our staff properly.
- Please forgive us.
- An employee?
Isn't she the CEO?
That woman's a liar.
Tommy, we're going to another hotel.
Why did you tell her you were the CEO?
Seriously.
Jin Hong Ju, don't mess with me right now.
She's not the CEO,
just a member of the staff.
She must have misspoken
when she introduced herself in English.
Please forgive her.
- It's our fault.
- Enough.
Tommy, let's find another hotel.
Wait, Chairman!
When we heard you were coming,
we prepared a special K-drama tour.
And some of your favorite actors
will be there.
We'll save you VIP seats.
- How does that sound?
- Goodness!
Tour service...
I like the sound of that, Director Ma.
Also, we'll have another concierge
assigned to you.
Or if you'd prefer,
I can personally attend to you.
That sly fox...
She thinks she can just swoop in
like that?
No way. I have to win that Chairman over,
whatever it takes.
Chairman Ali.
Please give me one more chance.
I promise I'll take excellent care of you.
Just one more chance, please.
Okay. If our job is to grant the wishes
of the living,
then we can grant the wishes of the dead,
can't we?
That's a line you hear in K-dramas
all the time, right?
Right?
The dead?
Again, I am so sorry
for earlier, Chairman.
Whatever you need, just ask.
I will provide you with service
that's guaranteed to satisfy.
Here, why don't you start
with a welcome drink?
- What? What's wrong now?
- Your welcome is a complete disaster.
That's why the Chairman is angry.
Hurry up and take off
Chairman Ali's shoes.
Excuse me?
- What is it now?
- Shoes.
Is there anything else I can do for you?
Our Dream Hotel...
- is the finest hotel in Korea...
- Tommy.
This place is a joke.
She refuses to do shoe duty?
My goodness, Tommy!
(Get lost!)
What in the world is she saying?
Alright.
"Atithi Devo Bhava..."
means to treat a guest
as if they were a deity...
and to purify and bless them.
So that's the meaning behind
the foot-washing ceremony, right?
Exactly. It's one of their traditions.
I've got a lot to learn.
I'll be sure to memorize it all.
"Rangoli."
These are designs used
to decorate the entrance.
Washing a guest's feet...
is a traditional custom in our country
for welcoming honored guests.
Really?
For supposedly the best hotel in Korea,
the service is awful.
Especially you. You're the worst.
Let's go, Tommy.
Wait. No, please. It was my fault.
Let me wash your feet.
Please have a seat. Please, just sit...
The service at this hotel is a disgrace.
How revolting.
Is this really how you
welcome your guests?
Please forgive me. I was unprofessional.
Please give me another chance.
Thank you, Chairman.
Then wash my feet, now.
She's doing a great job.
But what if Chae Hwa Young catches on?
I doubt it. She's too blinded by money.
She's desperate to secure this investment.
Mom. You're really going through a lot.
I'll send Team Leader Jin over soon.
See you later, Baek Ho.
See you.
Team Leader Jin.
Go and see if Chae Hwa Young is attending
to Chairman Ali properly...
and not making any mistakes.
And also check
if the Chairman needs anything.
Understood.
Just wait until I get this investment.
I won't let you off the hook.
No.
On your knees.
And use both hands, respectfully.
Yes.
Chairman Ali, is everything alright?
Hey, I've got this under control,
so you can leave, Team Leader Jin.
Oh, no!
What's wrong now?
I feel so disgusted.
How bad a person are you?
The moment your hands touched my feet,
my skin crawled.
I feel so filthy.
Get them away from me, now!
Tommy, the bell.
Yes.
Here you go, Chairman.
- Begone, evil spirit!
- Don't move!
- It's a purification ritual.
- Run, and you'll be cursed for life.
- Evil spirit, be gone!
Seriously! Please, stop it!
You wretched woman.
Be gone, evil spirit! Be gone, demon!
- You wicked woman.
- I told you to stop!
- Are you trying to drive me crazy?
- Be gone, evil spirit!
- Ali.
Don't you dare back out of the investment.
I'll get that investment money from you
even if it kills me.
Be gone, evil spirit!
What?
Chae Hwa Young washed Chairman Ali's feet?
Seriously?
Yes, on her knees, too.
Word has already spread among the staff.
On top of that, it seemed she upset
Chairman Ali while washing her feet...
because she was groveling at her feet,
begging for forgiveness.
- Is that really true?
- Instead of working,
are you all just wasting time gossiping?
No, I was just saying.
CEO Chae looked so pathetic
that it was embarrassing to watch.
But we have a professional concierge
for a reason.
I don't know why
she's bothering with this.
No one even asked her to.
Why she'd volunteer for such humiliation
is beyond me.
(General Manager Kang Jun Ho)
Chairman Ali...
I know she's an investor,
but this is just too much.
How can she make the CEO of a hotel
grovel like that?
That woman... Seriously...
Time for the final welcome.
What?
There's still more?
I'm going to lose my mind!
And why is that punk Tommy
so disrespectful to me?
He's obnoxious in so many ways.
Get on your knees...
and kiss Chairman Ali's feet
as if in worship.
What?
You want me to kiss her feet?
You don't want to?
- Let's go, Tommy.
- No, I'll do it!
I'll do it.
Hurry up. Quickly!
Again. Like you mean it!
Again. That was too short.
A sincere welcome, reverence.
Don't you get it?
- You know?
- Yes...
Are you taking pictures?
A memento.
What a spectacle.
My mom said she was always
in school plays when she was a kid.
I can't get used to seeing Mom like this.
It feels like I'm in a dream.
I know, right? I feel the same way.
To think that because of Chae Hwa Young,
she spent all those years
without ever getting to truly blossom...
- must be so infuriating for her.
- And that's not all.
She also lost Seo Rin.
And not only that, she lost Oh Bok Gil,
whom she adored like an older brother.
Can you imagine her
deep-seated resentment?
And after my mom regained her sanity,
her shock must have been even greater.
Compared to all that suffering,
making Chae Hwa Young suffer like this
is letting her off easy.
Anyway, I just hope
Mom doesn't get caught.
Right, Baek Ho.
We should get going to my grandfather's.
Right.
If we stop at the store for a gift,
we should get going.
Thank you for having me, Chairman.
Of course.
I should have had you over sooner.
Come on in.
My goodness, what's all this?
You're just visiting your future in-laws.
What did you bring?
It's nothing special.
It's just some ginseng
and traditional sweets.
Oh my, you shouldn't have.
Still, I felt awkward coming empty-handed.
(Ma)
What is this?
I have no idea what that crest is.
You see, because of my
high blood pressure,
I can't eat the ginseng chicken soup.
I feel bad eating it by myself.
I wish you could join me, Chairman.
Don't worry, we're having some too.
That's right, Lawyer Kang.
Don't worry, and just enjoy it.
Yes, go ahead and eat.
All right, everyone. Let's eat.
(Ma)
Is that the same crest on my golden spoon?
No, it can't be.
Jang Mi, it looks like you haven't changed
Seo Rin's room at all.
It's just as I remember it.
Grandfather told me to redecorate,
but I like it this way.
The truth is,
I keep feeling like Seo Rin...
is going to walk through
that door and say,
"What are you doing in my room? Shit."
Don't be so sad.
We will get to the bottom of this,
no matter what.
And we'll make sure Seo Rin
can finally rest in peace.
Of course. We have to.
But, Baek Ho, is something wrong?
No, nothing's wrong.
It's just, Jun Ho...
- Never mind.
- What? What is it?
What about Kang Jun Ho?
What did he say to you?
He was about to say something,
but I stopped him
and said I'd rather hear it from you.
Good call.
The thing is...
The thing is what?
Don't tell me, Baek Ho...
You don't have some weird disease, do you?
Or is it another woman?
That's ridiculous.
Who do you think I am?
I'm a one-woman man.
The truth is...
My mom and dad...
are not my birth parents.
They adopted me.
- Just like Kang Jun Ho.
- What?
Then...
They adopted me when I was a baby...
and adopted Kang Jun Ho later
when he was older.
This doesn't change how you feel about me,
does it?
That's ridiculous.
Why would I ever think less of you?
What do you take me for?
I'm a one-man woman.
We're about to get married,
so let's be completely honest
with no more secrets.
I'm sorry I didn't tell you sooner.
All that matters is that I know now.
But you don't happen to know
who your birth parents are, do you?
No. And I have no desire to find them.
As far as I'm concerned,
Lawyer Han Young Ja is my only mother.
If you ever want to look for them,
let's do it together.
I'll help you.
Right.
The crest.
(Ma)
I was right.
It was identical to this crest.
They said this was with me
when I first came to the orphanage.
Baek Ho, you're home.
Mom, you're still up?
You're so late.
Sounds like the Chairman treated you well.
The Chairman officially accepted me
as his son-in-law...
and even made me ginseng chicken soup.
Really?
He really rolled out the red carpet
for you.
But why do you have this out?
There's just something I needed to check.
By any chance,
did you hear anything
when you first brought me home?
About this golden toad or golden spoon.
I'm not sure.
Then...
could you give me
the orphanage director's phone number?
Actually, I thought of that
after we spoke the other day.
I tried to call her,
but I think her number has changed.
I couldn't get through.
Really?
I'll find out for you one way or another.
Okay, thanks. I'm counting on you.
Are you just leaving now?
Take this and go to a snack bar nearby
and buy some tteokbokki, sundae,
and some other things.
What? Tteokbokki at this hour?
She watched a drama and wants me to get it
from the place she saw on the show.
That's all the way over
by Gangnam Station.
That's a 90-minute round trip.
The tteokbokki will be
a soggy mess by then.
Besides, it's not like she'd know
the difference.
Just tell them to throw it
in a plastic bag.
I can't risk getting caught over this.
- It'll be a huge headache. Hurry.
- Yes, ma'am.
Try to get some rest while I'm gone.
Just you wait, Ali, you witch.
Never have I been so humiliated
on someone's power trip.
And to be utterly humiliated
in front of Team Leader Jin.
I'm so pissed off.
I've never had such a difficult day.
Yes, Chairman Ali. I'm on my way
to get the tteokbokki...
Hurry up. Get back here, right now.
But I'm already near Gangnam Station...
Shut up. I know you didn't go.
- What?
- Get back here now.
- Yes.
- Now.
How did she find out?
Ma'am, I'm back with the tteokbokki.
Ma'am, I bought this for you.
Are you out of your mind?
Why are you doing this to me?
I went all the way
to Gangnam Station to get this for you.
Why are you so angry with me?
You resort to violence
over every little thing.
You think you've been wronged?
Look at this.
Tommy took this picture for me.
It's so far,
so I had Tommy go check it out.
Where were you?
We must have just missed each other.
You're lying.
I'm not lying, Chairman.
Out!
You're a liar. You're out!
I'm checking out tomorrow.
You can have it.
Get out now!
Shit.
Unbelievable! Ali!
That crazy woman thinks
she can work me like a dog?
What a massive pain.
And now she's threatening
to leave the hotel again?
She's impossible!
Fine! This is too degrading.
Forget the investment!
Tell her the deal's off!
Hey, Jun Ho.
I heard what happened from the Director.
Are you holding up okay?
Oh, my son.
You called because you were
worried about me.
I've dealt with my fair share
of nightmare clients before,
but she really takes the cake.
Just drop the deal with Chairman Ali.
I hate seeing you swallow your pride
and bow down to her like that.
I'll find other investors,
so please, just stop.
No. It's not that easy to find an investor
of her caliber.
Who else would invest that much in us?
I don't have the energy
to talk to you right now.
What happened?
Chairman Ali called me,
and she was absolutely furious.
Let's talk about it tomorrow.
Chairman Ali said she's too exhausted,
so she's staying at our hotel tonight.
I'll find a way to win her over tomorrow,
so don't worry and just go.
First thing tomorrow morning,
you need to book a nail artist...
and send them to Chairman Ali's room
by 9:30 a.m.
And tell the staff to prepare
anything else she needs.
How am I supposed to find a nail artist
that early in the morning?
That's all up to you.
You said you could handle it.
Fine, I'll take care of it.
I've seen arrogance,
but this world-class arrogance is a first.
Take good care of her tomorrow.
No more mistakes.
Please.
Mom.
Jang Mi.
Mom, you had a really rough day,
didn't you?
Thanks to this,
I really had Chae Hwa Young fooled.
But I doubt she'll keep falling for it.
Either way, Chae Hwa Young is focused
on securing that investment right now,
so she won't suspect you.
I just need you for one more day, Mom.
It was satisfying to make
Chae Hwa Young suffer,
but it's nothing compared to
what she put me through.
I can't risk leaving it at home.
I need to hide it somewhere else.
What's this?
When I met Chairman Ma 30 years ago,
while pregnant with Dong Seok's child,
Chairman Ma gave it to me.
You remember, right?
Yes.
Of course, I remember.
Here's the key. Go on, open it.
This is...
I don't trust Oh Jang Mi,
so I brought it here.
That brat will get into my drawers
one way or another.
I want you to keep Seo Rin's baby clothes
and this necklace hidden for a while.
Yes.
I'm counting on you.
And don't get any ideas
about siding with Han Young Ja to test me.
By the way, something has been
bothering me for a long time.
When Father gave this to me,
there were two golden toads, right?
But back then, when I moved
into the Chairman's house with Seo Rin,
I didn't get a chance
to grab this until later.
I was so busy with Seo Rin and Chairman Ma
that I didn't check it until later.
But one of the golden toads was missing,
and I couldn't find it anywhere.
(The First Man)
Bring Kang Jun Ho to the lobby right now.
Take off those leather shoes, now.
Have you no respect for our traditions?
Chae Hwa Young, your 30 years
in this business really show.
- Is that supposed to be sarcasm?
- It is.
- What did you say?
- Chae Hwa Young. You need to suffer more.
What's wrong?
I think Chairman Ali is Jung Suk Hee!
She must have gotten her memory back.
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)