(Episode 62)
(Lawyer Kang Baek Ho)
I hope this isn't a dream.
This really isn't a dream, is it?
It's not a dream, Baek Ho.
It's really you, isn't it, Jang Mi?
I can't believe it.
I still can't believe it.
You can believe it.
It's me. It's Jang Mi.
I'm the same Oh Jang Mi who loves you.
Thank you, Jang Mi.
Thank you so much, Jang Mi.
About General Manager Kang...
Why would he go out of his way
to reveal that he was adopted?
He probably figured that
if I found out he was adopted,
I wouldn't accept him as my son-in-law.
That's how he wants to stop this.
General Manager Kang...
looks like he had
a very painful childhood.
He looked so troubled.
It's long overdue,
but I'm going to make it all up to him.
I'm going to give my son
everything I have.
You can head home.
And one more thing about Jin Hong Ju.
- Yes.
- Clear out her desk.
How dare she stab me in the back
and pull a stunt like that?
Impersonating Professor Kang,
sending a bouquet with a note.
There's a limit to how much
she can mess with me.
Does she really think
she can get away with that?
But I don't think...
Team Leader Jin was the one
who wrote the note.
Besides, Team Leader Jin never even came
to your office that day.
Then who on earth would pull
a clever stunt like that?
Who? Could it have been Seo Rin?
Did Seo Rin do that
knowing about Professor Kang and me?
Is that why she's refusing
to marry General Manager Kang?
I have so much to tell you, Baek Ho.
It's okay. Tell me everything.
Tell me exactly what happened.
I don't know where to start.
Seo Rin and I...
are twins.
That explains it. So you're twins.
Yes.
But there's something even more shocking.
The person who hit Seo Rin and me
with that truck...
was a henchman sent by Chae Hwa Young.
What?
You're saying CEO Chae did that?
I know it's hard to believe.
You don't know the first thing
about Chae Hwa Young.
My mom's accident, my dad's death,
and the reason Seo Rin and I
were separated despite being twins...
Chae Hwa Young was...
behind all of it.
Then CEO Chae must have been the one
trying to kill you all along.
Yes. If it got out that we're twins,
Chairman Ma would find out
that she'd kidnapped Seo Rin.
She couldn't risk being exposed
as a child kidnapper,
so she was determined
to get rid of me, no matter what.
She wanted me gone from this world.
That's unbelievable.
And that's how Director Ma
ended up taking your place.
Seriously, how could she do
something so despicable?
It wasn't enough that she kidnapped
your twin, Seo Rin.
She put the very child she raised
for 30 years into a coma.
Chae Hwa Young isn't even human.
I'll never forgive her.
So, after you learned the truth,
you decided to take Director Ma's place
in that house.
To get your revenge on Chae Hwa Young.
Yes.
To make Chae Hwa Young pay for her crimes,
I need conclusive evidence.
And to find that evidence,
I had no choice
but to impersonate Ma Seo Rin.
You must have been so anxious
and scared all this time.
Footage of Chae Hwa Young
harming your father...
would be the smoking gun.
We have to find it, no matter what.
Yes. And proof of what
she did to my mother, too.
Looks like we have
a lot of work ahead of us.
No. This is something I have to do alone.
The reason I stayed away
from you until now...
is that I didn't want to
drag you into this mess.
How could you say that?
Finding evidence for what happened
to your father is my fight too.
Baek Ho, are you still here?
I'm so sorry.
I didn't realize you had company.
Hello.
Mom, you were home just a while ago.
What are you doing here?
I forgot some files for tomorrow's trial.
Is Seo Rin home yet?
- Not yet.
- But her car is parked outside.
Where could she have gone without driving?
The Chairman said he wanted to see you
as soon as you got in.
Father did?
But...
what brings you here so late at night?
Oh, right.
Hello, I'm Ma Seo Rin.
I'm here for some legal advice
from Lawyer Kang.
Hey, you said you had a trial tomorrow.
You should get going.
Sorry about that.
What do you mean,
General Manager Kang Jun Ho is...
out of the question?
I'm saying he is not a suitable match
for our Seo Rin.
Absolutely not.
Of all the men in the world,
you pick one of our employees for her?
Father, I've put in a lot of thought
about this.
You thought a lot about this?
Who do you think you are
to decide who Seo Rin marries?
I'll find a suitable husband for Seo Rin.
You stay out of it.
Father, I know Seo Rin best.
I'm her mother.
Who could know her better than I do?
So?
Are you saying that I, her grandfather,
don't know a thing about her?
That's not what I meant.
Seo Rin is in love
with General Manager Kang.
She's just throwing a tantrum...
and taking it out on him
due to the accident.
If you don't let her marry
General Manager Kang,
she won't want to stay in Korea.
Seo Rin isn't a child.
Let's give it some time
and see what happens.
Honey, while you're looking for
a match for Seo Rin,
could you please find one
for our Hong Ju, too?
- I should get going.
- Jang Mi.
Don't do anything dangerous on your own.
Let me handle it.
You need to go back to your old life.
You'll be found out in no time,
living in Chairman Ma's house.
No.
I can't go back to my old life
until I see this through...
with Chae Hwa Young.
If you're caught, you could get hurt!
I'll be careful.
Don't worry about me.
Ma Seo Rin, you're finally home.
Were you out with Jun Ho?
But is something wrong?
What's this?
You were a drunken mess earlier,
but now you're fine?
You couldn't even stand up
and had to be carried in by a guy.
You saw that?
You saw my Baek Ho?
Isn't he gorgeous?
He's cute, I guess.
What's all the fuss about?
Listen to you. "Cute, I guess?"
Open your eyes. He looks like he jumped
right off the page of a comic book.
A man straight out of a comic book.
Beauty is in the eye of the beholder.
But why are you so desperate?
Did you really have to pretend
to be that drunk and stick to him?
I get it now.
He's not falling for you,
so you had to resort to a sly trick
like that, right?
Ma Seo Rin.
Come to think of it,
I bet you look upset...
because of Jun Ho, right?
Why? Is it not working out
with Jun Ho these days?
Mind your own business.
And stop making such a fool of yourself.
What's with her?
She's back to her usual bratty self.
Is her memory starting to come back?
Thank goodness.
I'm so glad Jang Mi is safe.
Wait, so the person I've been visiting,
holding hands and talking with daily,
was Director Ma Seo Rin this whole time?
Jang Mi, I'm right here.
You can hear my voice, right?
Every time I wanted to see
Director Ma Seo Rin,
something always got in the way.
It was because of CEO Chae.
I don't know who you are,
but why did you send me a photo
of CEO Chae and Professor Kang...
and tell me not to trust CEO Chae?
Can we meet and talk in person?
First, I'll meet with Baek Ho tomorrow.
Then I need to see Tae Pyung.
The common enemy
we must defeat together...
is now Chae Hwa Young.
I'll be in touch.
We'll be able to meet soon.
A common enemy?
CEO Chae is our common enemy?
That's ridiculous.
What in the world is this mystery?
Hey, Baek Ho.
Hey, Tae Pyung.
Jang Mi is doing fine
at the hospital, right?
What are you talking about?
Of course she is.
I was just checking, just in case.
Sorry to call so late. Get some sleep.
That was so random of Baek Ho.
Anyway, his love for her is so pure.
I should probably tell
Tae Pyung the truth.
But I should probably leave that
up to Jang Mi, right?
By the way, where did you go
with your car parked...
in front of the house?
Do I have to report my every move
to you at my age?
- Why are you being so suffocating?
- Ma Seo Rin.
You only play the adult
when it's convenient for you, don't you?
From the look on your face,
you didn't sleep well again.
Try not to rely on sleeping pills.
Here, drink this. It's freshly made.
Just leave it there.
I'll drink it after I wash up.
You honestly...
don't remember
General Manager Kang Jun Ho?
Am I supposed to?
You're the one who begged me to marry him,
saying he was the only one.
So I gave in
and began to seriously consider...
Director Kang Jun Ho for you.
So if you say that you don't remember now,
- where does that leave me?
- I don't know.
What do you want me to do
if I can't remember?
You can forget everything else,
but you have to remember Kang Jun Ho.
This just won't do.
I'm going to have to call Dr. Kim.
Actually,
- I remember.
- You do?
I knew you did.
Then why were you pretending you didn't?
Because I've lost interest.
- What?
- People change.
Did you expect me
to stay devoted to him forever?
If I'm not interested,
I'm not getting married.
But Mom,
why are you so set on me
marrying General Manager Kang Jun Ho?
That's...
That's because you liked Kang Jun Ho...
and you begged me to let you marry him.
Like I said, I don't like him anymore.
- And that's why I'm not marrying him.
- And that's what's so strange.
Why are you suddenly acting
like a completely different person?
No way.
She lost interest in Jun Ho,
so she's not going to marry him?
Jun Ho, you're working
with Director Ma, right?
Yes.
- Why?
- Why did...
Director Ma come to see you
so late last night?
Was it really for some legal advice?
Director Ma came to see you?
- Yes, something like that.
- And?
What happened?
You've been dying to meet
Director Ma, haven't you?
You did?
It'll be a problem
if you become interested in her, Baek Ho.
Especially since CEO Chae is trying
to set her up with Jun Ho for marriage.
What's this about a marriage?
That's absolute nonsense!
Goodness.
It will only happen
if Jun Ho actually wants...
to marry CEO Chae's daughter,
but is that any reason to get so angry?
What's gotten into you?
I mean, Jun Ho isn't interested.
Why do you keep pushing him
to be with Director Ma?
That's why I'm so upset.
You never know with these things.
Besides, I hear they're working together.
And from what I saw yesterday,
Ma Seo Rin...
seemed so graceful and polite.
- She seemed like a good catch.
- Graceful?
And you think she's polite?
Hey, can I talk to you for a second?
You're not really thinking about
marrying Director Ma, are you?
You're not interested in her, right?
Why do I have to tell you that?
What's that supposed to mean?
Are you saying
you've had a change of heart?
Who knows.
Why do you care if things work out
between Director Ma and me?
I'm just...
- curious.
- And why would you be curious?
You were all for me
marrying Director Ma before.
Don't tell me...
you've developed feelings for her...
after meeting her once.
What? That's ridiculous.
I was just curious, that's all.
What is going on here?
Who got rid of Team Leader Jin's desk?
Director Ma, did you do this?
Why would I waste my energy
on something so petty?
- Then...
- So this is...
the desk disappearing act
I've heard about.
You're really in the hot seat now,
Team Leader Jin.
CEO Chae, are you really doing this to me?
Just as I thought.
Chae Hwa Young suspected
Hong Ju and decided to lower the boom.
Ma'am, my desk is gone,
and I just don't understand why.
All I've done is work my hardest.
Your desk? Your desk is gone?
I guess you can't work today, then.
Ma'am...
A lot of companies are hot-desking now.
People just find a spot with their laptop.
Just grab your laptop and work at a table.
How could I...
Everyone else has their own desk.
How could I be the only one?
It's humiliating.
Team Leader Jin, this is a company.
Crying and throwing a fit
won't change a thing.
You must have done something
to deserve it.
Don't you think?
Now, get out.
If you don't want to work,
feel free to go home.
That won't be necessary.
I can't quit this job.
I'll write a formal apology
for my wrongdoing. So please...
That's enough.
Didn't you hear me? I said to get out.
(CEO Chae Hwa Young)
What?
Hwa Young took away your desk?
Yes.
What am I going to do now?
What did you do to make that witch
get personal revenge on you like this?
I sent that bouquet and pretended
it was from Professor Kang.
- She found out, so this is her revenge.
- So?
Why is she being so petty
over something so insignificant?
And to my precious daughter,
of all people.
That Chae Hwa Young. I ought to...
- I'm so furious.
- What are you so furious about?
Hong Ju, let me call you back.
Honey. I mean, Mr. Chairman.
Have you ever heard of anything so unfair?
What is it now?
CEO Chae took away Hong Ju's desk.
What else could this be
but a threat to make her quit?
So how can I not be furious?
They took her desk away at work?
Why would CEO Chae do that?
- There must have been a reason.
- It's because of the bouquet...
What?
Nothing.
From now on, don't bother me
with these petty issues.
I've already got enough
on my plate with work.
Tae Sook, you're always great at work.
You'll do great with your own business.
We've gotten so many more customers
since you've been here.
Thank you for saying so, sir.
The contract's signed.
I'll make sure there are no delays...
on the final payment
as per the date on the contract.
Please do.
(Director Ma Seo Rin)
Hello?
Baek Ho.
It's me.
Yes, Jang Mi.
- Did you get home okay yesterday?
- Yes.
It's been a while since we've talked
on the phone like this.
It really has.
I still can't believe it.
I couldn't sleep a wink last night.
Just thinking about you fighting all alone
in that strange, dangerous house.
Where are you?
I'm at the side dish shop.
There was some paperwork
I needed to file with the city.
Thank you.
Don't you worry about
things here, Jang Mi.
I'm here every day, clocking in
and looking after your mom.
Jang Mi?
- Tae Pyung?
- Hey, Kang Baek Ho.
Who are you on the phone with?
Are you really...
my sister, Jang Mi?
Are you really Oh Jang Mi?
Yes, Tae Pyung.
It's me. Your sister, Jang Mi.
You...
You little brat...
When did you wake up?
You should have called me
the second you woke up!
I'm sorry, Tae Pyung.
Do you have any idea how worried I was?
I thought you might never wake up.
I was so...
Tae Pyung.
Tae Pyung, I'm so sorry.
But the person lying
in that hospital bed right now...
isn't me.
What are you talking about?
The person lying in that hospital bed...
isn't me.
It's Ma Seo Rin.
She's my twin sister.
My little sister.
A twin?
What kind of crazy talk is this?
She's telling the truth, Tae Pyung.
So that's the kind of person
CEO Chae really is?
She pretended to help our family,
but she's the one who did that to our dad?
Hey. I get how you feel,
but you need to calm down first.
Baek Ho. I'm sorry about back then.
I honestly thought it was
Professor Kang...
Wait a minute.
Professor Kang and CEO Chae...
Tae Pyung.
Wait, what is it?
Am I the only one who's out of the loop?
No, it's not like that.
Seriously, what nonsense is this?
Don't tell anyone
I'm posing as Ma Seo Rin.
Until I make Chae Hwa Young pay,
nobody can know who I really am.
Of course. It would be too dangerous
for you, Jang Mi.
Alright, I get it. My lips are sealed.
Chae Hwa Young, that woman...
I won't let her get away with this.
See? This is exactly why
I couldn't tell anyone.
Don't worry.
But...
Don't you miss Mom?
Of course I do.
How's she doing?
She must be asking for me a lot, right?
She's doing a lot better
than she was at first, though.
Bo Ra loves rolled omelets.
It's yummy. Bo Ra loves rolled omelets.
Bo Ra loves Grandma.
I like Bo Ra. Bo Ra is pretty.
I miss Jang Mi.
(Ian Daily News)
(Restructuring on Three Pillars,
Tourism and Lifestyle...)
(The Female Leader
Women Most Aspire to Be...)
(is CEO Chae Hwa Young of Dream Hotel)
(With K-culture's spread,
evolving into a K-culture destination...)
("K-culture" and "Polarization")
(Chae Hwa Young)
(Copying one item
from Desktop to New Folder...)
(General Manager Kang Jun Ho)
Kang Jun Ho.
You couldn't stand Director Ma,
thinking she was a stalker.
So why are you so upset
now that she says she dislikes you?
Hello, this is Kang Jun Ho.
General Manager Kang.
I'd like to formally invite you
to my home.
- What do you say?
- What's the occasion?
Let's say it's to wish
the Dream Project success?
Sounds like you sent the invitation first
and are making up the reason now.
And what if I did?
This is all for your sake.
Stop it. You're making him uncomfortable.
I accept. How about sometime this weekend?
First the father, now the son?
Doesn't that seem a little strange?
I don't know about this.
Mom, why are you so set on inviting him?
(CEO Chae Hwa Young)
(Suk Hee's Side Dishes)
I should get going.
Aren't you leaving, Director Ma?
You go ahead.
I have something to discuss with my mom.
All right, then.
I thought you were done talking
when I saw the General Manager leaving.
(CEO Chae Hwa Young)
You're pretty slick.
You used to just throw yourself at him,
but now you know how to pull back
and let him come to you.
I know what I'm doing, Mom.
Who sent this?
Gosh, why won't this open?
Who is this?
(The First Man)
I don't know who it is,
but I think CEO Chae is being blackmailed.
- Blackmailed?
- We have to find that USB.
It could be the crucial evidence
from my dad's accident.
I'll find it no matter what
and make her pay.
CEO Chae Hwa Young,
I trust you received the gift I sent.
Who are you?
How dare you pull a stunt like this?
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)