None of this is adding up.
I have to go to the accident scene
first thing tomorrow.
Don't go alone. Let's go together.
And about that composite sketch,
when my mom saw the sketch,
she screamed that he looked terrifying.
After seeing the sketch?
Yes. It happened at our store,
and also at the funeral home
when she saw Manager Lee.
What if...
the sketch is of Manager Lee?
Manager Lee?
If your mother was scared of Manager Lee,
we need to look into it right away.
But wouldn't that be rude?
What if it's just a misunderstanding?
Either way, I have to confront him.
Besides, I have things to ask him
about the Dream Hotel CCTV footage.
Hello, Manager Lee. It's Kang Baek Ho.
I heard the police came by
to ask for your alibi.
That's right.
Why do you ask?
I'm just curious.
I just can't stand not knowing things.
What could you possibly be
so curious about now?
The police were just here poking around.
It's about the CCTV.
It just doesn't make any sense to me.
How can the CCTV in a hotel this large
be down due to a malfunction?
Well...
You mean how it was off for a few hours
in the parking garage?
Things like that happen all the time.
I suppose you wouldn't know.
It happens all the time?
Aren't you being a little too casual
about this?
All right. I understand.
Thanks for the coffee.
Next time, it will be on me.
Hey, who does this look like to you?
I told you,
I can't tell who it is from this.
Why did you even get this sketch made?
Are you doing this just to prove
Kang Baek Ho's father is innocent?
That's not it.
Then why do you keep shoving this sketch
in my face?
Mom screamed when she saw this sketch
and said it was terrifying.
Just like the last time
she saw Manager Lee.
Manager Lee?
Don't you think it kind of looks
like Manager Lee?
I guess it does, a little.
No way.
Think about how good CEO Chae
has been to us.
Why would Manager Lee get Dad drunk?
That's ridiculous.
You're right.
He must just be a look-alike.
I really don't want to go see Mom.
Ma Seo Rin, be careful.
You can't go in there
and start nitpicking for answers.
I hope Mom is not the one
trying to kill Oh Jang Mi.
Jun Ho!
Jun Ho...
It's not Jun Ho.
It's General Manager Kang Jun Ho.
Were you upset I didn't use your title?
Okay. General Manager Kang.
You just made my heart skip a beat.
How about we hug just one more time?
There you go again.
You realize this is almost harassment?
No.
I'm feeling down today.
Let's go get a drink.
- My treat. Okay?
- No, thank you.
Where to, General Manager Kang?
I'm on my way to see CEO Chae. Why?
Okay, then have a good meeting.
Yes?
Come on in, General Manager Kang.
I heard your interview went well.
Have a seat.
I called for Seo Rin, too.
I wanted to talk when you were both here.
I just ran into her out front.
She didn't seem
to be heading this way, though.
Is that so?
I wonder what she's up to.
Is something wrong?
No, it's nothing.
Anyway, the reason I asked to see you...
was to check if the meeting preparations
were coming along...
and if there was anything
I could do to help.
Just get to the point.
All right. I won't beat around the bush.
How would you feel
if Team Leader Jin became your boss?
Team Leader Jin Hong Ju?
The Chairman has declared
that he's taking Jin Hong Ju's mother...
to be his wife.
Of course, on the condition
that it won't be a legal marriage.
But do you think Team Leader Jin
and her mother will settle for that?
Now that they're becoming family,
Team Leader Jin's status will change.
So, with that said...
General Manager Kang.
Can I consider you to be on my side now?
What do you say to marrying Seo Rin...
and taking over Dream for yourself?
You want me...
to marry Director Ma?
That's right.
Seo Rin grew up without a father
or any siblings.
All she's ever known is
Chairman Ma's doting affection.
You know how it is.
A grandfather just can't help
but spoil his granddaughter.
Seo Rin might be acting childish
on purpose...
to hide how lonely she is.
Hiding it?
That's not how it looks to me at all.
Don't you think it's just that
she's bad at expressing her feelings?
I think...
you could really soothe Seo Rin's heart.
- What do you say?
- I must be hearing things.
This is absurd.
You were so dead set against me,
so what's with the sudden change of heart?
Me? Marry Director Ma?
Like I said,
Seo Rin and I absolutely need you.
Join us, General Manager Kang.
Why me, of all people?
I need you because you're competent
and a great asset to this company.
If you join forces with me
and marry my Seo Rin,
you will achieve everything
you've ever wanted.
Do you even know what my dream is?
I think I have an idea.
To climb to the very top.
To a position where
everyone has to look up to you.
Am I wrong?
Seo Rin. Are you just getting home?
Yes, Grandpa.
Jin Hong Ju.
You used to be my gofer, carrying my bags.
Now that you've moved up in the world,
do you think you're untouchable?
What? Why are you being like this
all of a sudden?
Seo Rin, Hong Ju is your aunt now.
So you'd better watch your mouth. Got it?
You've got to be kidding me.
Hong Ju, you don't have to speak formally
to Seo Rin anymore.
You're her superior now. Got it?
Okay.
Father, that's all right with you,
isn't it?
Of course.
You heard him.
Grandpa, people who come from nothing...
can't handle it
when they suddenly come into money.
If you give our shares to those beggars,
I swear I'll disown you.
Don't give them a single cent.
I've made myself clear.
My word. Goodness, I feel faint.
She called us beggars!
How am I going to crush
that tramp, Ma Seo Rin?
There's no need to get upset.
All we have to do is hold the ceremony.
No matter how much they kick and scream,
half of the Chairman's shares
are destined to be ours.
You're right, Mom.
No matter how much Ma Seo Rin struggles,
that ship has already sailed.
That's right.
I'm Chairman Ma's daughter now.
I should buy myself some nice clothes.
Of course.
You need to look the part.
Let's go shopping tomorrow.
By the way,
why haven't I heard from Madam Kim?
I told her to find
the best possible husband for you.
What about a lawyer for a husband?
You know, his mom's a lawyer,
and his dad's a professor.
Do you think the Chairman would approve
of a husband like that?
You need to marry the son of a tycoon
who can help our Dream Group.
Why are you being so shortsighted?
Don't tell me...
Are you talking about that punk,
Lawyer Kang Baek Ho?
- Why would you call Baek Ho a punk?
- Hey, Jin Hong Ju!
Come on, get a grip!
In the first trial,
stress the victim's pedestrian negligence.
You got the hospital's consent
to check the blood sample taken...
during Oh Bok Gil's surgery, right?
Yes, here.
I confirmed it with the police's consent.
A blood alcohol content of 0.12 percent
means he was heavily intoxicated.
It's key evidence for proving
the victim's negligence,
so make sure it's on the initial list
of evidence with the forensics report.
I can't believe
I have to go up against Jang Mi.
I know that for a fact
her father isn't the kind of man...
who would be on the road, dead drunk.
Dad, by any chance,
have you seen this person before?
What?
Who is this?
He bought soju near the scene
of Jang Mi's father's accident,
and something about him
seems suspicious to me.
What's so suspicious about him?
I feel like he's somehow connected
to the accident.
- He might even be the culprit.
- Kang Baek Ho.
Are you suggesting that this man...
pried open Oh Jang Mi's father's mouth
and forced soju down his throat?
What could possibly be so suspicious?
So what if he bought soju?
Don't people live in that neighborhood?
Does that make
everyone who buys soju a criminal?
I looked up the serial number
of the soju bottle found at the scene,
and it was from a batch sold nearby.
This is the closest store
to the accident scene.
He most likely bought the soju here.
And since this store is so remote,
I was told that almost no one
but the local residents shops there.
The only person who bought soju
at that store that day...
(Case Summary, Yeongseo Police Chief)
was this man.
- Really?
- I will prove that Dad's accident...
wasn't what ultimately killed...
Jang Mi's father.
That's the only way Jang Mi's father
can rest in peace,
and you can clear your name, Dad.
Your father never lost his honor
in the first place.
How can he lose his honor
when he's innocent?
Your father is completely innocent.
Mom, come on.
By the way, Kang Hyuk.
What did you do with the wrench?
I buried it on a nearby mountain.
On a mountain?
He buried it on a mountain?
A mountain?
Even if I knew which one,
how could I search an entire mountain?
I can't even stand getting my shoes dirty.
Gosh, I don't know.
No.
But...
that wrench seems like it could be
the crucial piece of evidence.
Bok Gil is gone.
Jang Mi.
Let's go see Bok Gil at the hospital.
Mom, Dad said he was really tired.
He needs to get some sleep,
so let's go see him later. Okay?
Jang Mi, take a look at this.
Okay. What are these plane tickets for?
So this is it.
This is why Dad wanted to meet CEO Chae.
He knew I’d refuse to go abroad to study
if he was the one sending me.
He was going to ask her to say
that she was sponsoring me instead.
That's why he went to see her.
Because all these dangerous things
kept happening to you,
he must have thought
sending you away would be safer.
What do I do? Tae Pyung, I think
I'm the one who caused Dad's death.
I miss Bok Gil.
Bok Gil, please hurry back.
I miss him so much, Bok Gil.
Bok Gil.
(Suk Hee's Side Dishes)
Mom.
What are we going to do now?
You're going to keep crying
and asking for Dad.
What am I supposed to do
every time that happens?
Dad treasured all these memories.
I'm so sorry, Dad.
I'm so sorry.
I'm so very sorry.
I will find out why you had to die,
no matter what.
And the person you were always
searching for,
the one who did this to Mom.
I'll find them.
I'll do it so you can finally
rest in peace.
I love you, Dad.
Mrs. Yang.
- Where's Seo Rin?
- She left for work early this morning.
She went to work early this morning?
Is something wrong with Seo Rin?
- What?
- It's just that...
she rushed in here yesterday afternoon,
all worked up,
grabbed something,
and then left again right away.
Seo Rin hasn't been herself lately...
and seems out of her mind. It's strange.
She's causing trouble again.
Where in the world did she go?
By the way,
where are you getting the money
to dress up like this?
What's that supposed to mean?
Like mother, like daughter, I see.
Are you trying to treat us like beggars,
just like Seo Rin did?
- Isn't all that money from Dream Group?
- No, it's not!
I used the credit card my husband gave me.
Don't play dumb.
You're using Father's card.
Anyway, it must be nice
being such an airhead.
I am your mother-in-law.
I told you to show me some respect.
How could you forget so quickly?
The test results are in.
I'll give you a moment.
(Ma Seo Rin and Chae Hwa Young
are not biologically related.)
Shit. I'm not my mother's daughter?
Then who am I?
(Genos Gene Examination Center)
(Ma Seo Rin and Oh Jang Mi
are 99.998 percent biologically related.)
I'm related to Oh Jang Mi?
That must mean we're twins.
No way. How could this have happened?
How can I not be my mother's daughter?
Then who is my real mother,
the one who gave birth to me?
(Suk Hee's Side Dishes)
You're not Jang Mi.
You're pretending to be Jang Mi.
- You're not Jang Mi.
- What's with this woman?
That woman is my mother?
No, this is all a huge mistake.
- Mom.
- Hey, Jang Mi.
- What's this?
- A package came for you.
- Jang Mi...
- Oh Jang Mi, who looks exactly like me,
just called that woman "Mom."
There's no way a woman like that
is my mother.
Aren't you cold? Maybe I should've
put another jacket around you.
It's okay.
Something is completely wrong here.
It's all a big mistake!
(Suk Hee's Side Dishes)
Mom, you had a bad cold,
but you got better right away
after taking your medicine, didn't you?
(Suk Hee's Side Dishes)
Mom, you need to make sure you bundle up
so you don't get sick again, okay?
Jang Mi, you're so pretty.
Jang Mi is Suk Hee's daughter.
That's right. I'm your daughter, Mom.
My beautiful Mom.
I must have had it wrong from the start.
She's just some girl who looks like me.
That's it. A doppelganger.
- Suk Hee...
- She has to be a doppelganger.
- listens well.
- Shit.
Suk Hee isn't sick anymore.
(Mom)
- Mom, let's go get some ice cream.
- Oh, you're here!
- Go on, you two.
- We'll be back!
(Suk Hee's Side Dishes)
- What?
- Seo Rin, you left early. Where are you?
Why do you always have to be so nosy?
Shit.
Is a mother checking on her daughter
considered nosy?
I only called
because I barely get to see you.
How can I face you after all this, Mom?
Hello? Are you there?
Did you have something to say to me?
I spoke with General Manager Kang
yesterday.
I told him to marry you.
- Are you serious?
- Of course I am.
So, start showing up
at the office regularly...
and attending the meetings.
No more distractions.
Fine.
(Suk Hee's Side Dishes)
- It's time for the meeting.
- All right.
Today will be...
our Jun Ho's first major presentation
in front of the Chairman.
I wonder if he'll do okay.
Ma'am, in front of others,
you need to be careful
about saying "our Jun Ho."
Oh, right.
- Okay.
- Shall we?
It includes the hotel's signature
red wine reduction sauce.
Next.
The Ocean Jewel Box.
Sauces include a spicy chili vinaigrette,
mignonette, and aioli,
making up our signature trio of sauces.
That concludes my introduction
of our new signature dishes.
- Now, for the next item...
- All right, that's enough.
We can just read the handouts
for the rest.
General Manager Kang, in your opinion,
why do you think we hired you?
I started from the very bottom
and worked my way up in the kitchen.
My strengths are...
reading people's tastes and emotions,
as well as quickly reading the room.
I believe I have more hands-on,
practical experience than anyone else.
Is that so?
In that case,
what's the biggest problem...
with Dream Hotel's
Food and Beverage Department?
Instead of focusing on
customer satisfaction,
I believe too much energy is spent
on procedures and reports.
To innovate, you have to focus
on the people.
Both our guests and our staff.
You talk a good game.
So, what, specifically,
are you going to change?
First, I will establish
a new menu development team.
We'll create a channel for on-site staff
to share their diverse ideas.
Second, I plan to redesign the hall layout
based on customer flow.
Third, I'll conduct
a transparent review...
of our price agreements
with current vendors.
That's Jun Ho for you.
Alright.
I expect you to back up...
everything you've said with results.
Yes, Chairman.
What's going on?
Why did my mom suddenly give Jun Ho
that look of affection?
Why's she suddenly pushing for my marriage
to Jun Ho?
I wonder what Mom was thinking,
raising me as her daughter.
Wait, we're twins.
Why was I the only one
she ended up raising?
I said that you don't have to do this.
Come on, let me help.
I just really want to help you,
even if it's just this.
You doing this
isn't going to change anything.
You need onions peeled, right?
I used to be a cook in the army.
I'm an expert at peeling onions.
Hold on.
Here.
That's enough. Just go.
Let me just finish this, and then I'll go.
What excuse should I use
to give this to Manager Lee?
I have to find out everything
about my mother with this.
If we're twins,
why am I the daughter of a woman
I'm not even related to,
and why was I separated from Oh Jang Mi?
What about Oh Jang Mi's father's death?
And what's the wrench?
I'm going to find out everything
with this bug.
Mister.
"Mister?"
It’s been a while
since you last called me that.
You've been parked for a while,
so I came to check on you.
Is something wrong?
What's that?
I was going to give it to Jun Ho.
But then Mom gave Jun Ho a watch,
which totally spoiled it.
Do you want it?
Come to think of it,
you were the only one
who looked out for me when I was little,
and I've been so awful to you, haven't I?
What are you talking about?
Not at all.
You were adorable when you were little.
You're saying I'm not adorable anymore.
I'd say you're more charismatic
than adorable.
You get it from CEO Chae.
And here I thought
I took after my grandfather,
but I guess you see my mother in me.
Well, anyway...
It's a gift.
You're...
- giving this to me?
- It was supposed to be a gift for Jun Ho,
so I guess it's a little weird?
If you don't like it, just toss it.
I was going to throw it out anyway.
Seo Rin gave this to me.
She said that it was for Jun Ho,
but you got him one first.
Did she?
That's sweet of her.
Seo Rin was always fond of you,
calling you "Mister" and following you.
Keep up your good relationship
with Seo Rin.
Yes, I understand.
We still need to get rid of
Oh Jang Mi quickly, though.
First, I'll make sure she's too busy
making ends meet.
Then I'll find a way.
It seems she's very behind
on her shop's rent.
All right.
Especially with her father dead,
we need to make her so busy
just putting food on the table...
that she can't think about anything else.
She's going to get rid
of Oh Jang Mi quickly?
- What about the police?
- The investigation's been closed.
So the chief pulled some strings.
All right, that's settled then.
Now we just have to keep a close eye
on Seo Rin.
"Keep a close eye on me?"
Yes. I'll make sure there are no slip-ups.
Where has Seo Rin been running off to?
I haven't seen any sign of her lately.
And what's all this nonsense
about a twin all of a sudden?
She should be grateful
I stole her and not Oh Jang Mi.
I'm the one
who lets her live like a princess.
If I had taken Oh Jang Mi instead of her,
she'd be the one suffering...
as Jung Suk Hee's daughter
right now, right?
I'm the one who changed her fate.
And she repays me by running wild
with no sense of gratitude.
She really gets on my nerves.
(The First Man)
Are you out of your mind?
You want to make your father a murderer?
Jun Ho!
I just want to find the truth.
This is my insurance policy, just in case.
So, Mom wants to keep an eye on me?
Fine. I'll be the one controlling her.
You're giving CEO Chae a thank-you gift?
Nothing I do makes me feel any better.
How can she look exactly like me?
What in the world is going on?
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)