(Episode 83)
It's true that...
I was the one
who was prescribed sleeping medication.
Even though I saw my mother suffering
from insomnia,
I shouldn't have done that.
So please, blame me. But as for my mother,
please find it in your hearts
to forgive her.
Are you saying CEO Chae Hwa Young...
had sleeping medication
prescribed in your name...
and then took the injections herself?
CEO Chae, is that true?
- Is your daughter being truthful?
- Any comment?
- CEO, is it really true?
- We need a comment!
Chae Hwa Young. An eye for an eye.
I'm just paying you back
for the despicable trick you pulled.
You wicked witch!
(CEO Chae Hwa Young)
You nasty, insolent brat!
How dare you pull such a sly stunt
in front of my Jun Ho!
What's going on, CEO Chae?
Stop that interview
Seo Rin is giving right now.
Don't let it be published as an article,
and above all, keep it off social media.
Stop it now!
Yes, ma'am.
You don't believe me either?
That brat, Ma Seo Rin, got the shots
for her insomnia, and she took them.
That's odd.
You two are mother and daughter.
Why do you act like you're mortal enemies?
Because she's trying to pin it all on me,
that's why!
That sly little witch.
Enough.
Have you set a date
for our families to meet?
Do you really love Oh Jang...
- Are you in love with Seo Rin?
- How many times must I say it? I am.
- And...
- And?
I owe a debt to my parents now...
for saving my life and adopting me
after I was disowned for having leukemia,
I have to make them proud.
No. I will make them proud.
This is absurd. A sense of obligation?
Fine, of course you do. They raised you.
But for you to side with me,
your mother, because of them?
It's just so disheartening.
It's just basic human decency.
Do you think I wanted to abandon you?
Right. So Seo Rin solved this problem
all by herself?
I knew she had it in her.
By the way, Secretary Kim.
That business with Seo Rin's medication
that we paid to bury.
Who had the nerve to dig it up again?
Darn that brat! Darn her!
Please, calm down.
At this rate, I'm worried
you'll make yourself sick, CEO Chae.
You haven't been
out of the detention center for very long.
Exactly.
The minute I get out, that Oh Jang Mi brat
tries to screw me over. I'm furious!
I need to get rid of that little witch,
and fast.
I'm so upset, I'm going to lose my mind.
And my own daughter, Seo Rin, is in a coma
because she was hurt instead.
I'm worried about
what happened to Seo Rin too.
She has to wake up safe and sound...
so she can help me achieve my dream.
It's Lawyer Han Young Ja.
I bet she's calling about
Jun Ho's wedding.
- Hello, this is Chae Hwa Young.
- CEO Chae, is now a good time to talk?
Yes. The reason I'm calling
is about our Jun Ho.
He says he's determined
to marry Director Ma,
and he's asked me to help
move things along.
- I see.
- I know you must be very busy.
I was hoping we could meet to discuss
the children's wedding when you're free.
- When would be a good time for you?
- Anytime is fine with me.
In that case, how about
this weekend evening?
I'm not a great cook, but our housekeeper
makes some delicious dishes.
Why don't we have dinner at our place
and discuss it then?
Yes, that sounds lovely.
Baek Ho, I should get going now.
- Okay.
- Yes.
Wait, hold on!
You're just going to leave like that?
- Aren't you forgetting something?
- I am?
What did I forget?
You have to give me my stamp right here.
How could you forget something so crucial?
Not this again. You're impossible.
- Let's just keep this professional.
- But I like it this way. See?
That's it for today.
- See you tomorrow.
- All right, get home safe.
- What is it?
- I need to talk to you.
If you have something to say, spit it out.
Baek Ho, you've known this whole time...
that Director Ma
and Oh Jang Mi were twins.
Why are you keeping it a secret
from everyone?
- I'm not hiding anything.
- Then have you told the Chairman...
and Director Ma about Oh Jang Mi?
See? You are hiding something.
What are you getting at?
My mother and I...
get that Director Ma
and Oh Jang Mi are twins.
- And?
- But why?
I don't understand how
CEO Chae could give birth to twins...
but only raise one of them.
And why would Oh Jang Mi
report CEO Chae, her own mother,
as the suspect in her father's murder?
You know, don't you, Baek Ho?
Please, just tell me what you know.
And why should I tell you anything,
Team Leader Jin?
You know where Oh Jang Mi is.
Let Director Ma and Oh Jang Mi meet
so we can get to the bottom of this.
Chae Hwa Young!
- What do you think you're doing?
- You insolent little brat.
You're the one who started this.
On the surface, you and I are
mother and daughter.
So why would a mother
turn in her own daughter like that?
Who do you think is the reason
Seo Rin's in pain?
With a mother like you,
is it any wonder Seo Rin has insomnia?
I was utterly humiliated because of you.
Oh Jang Mi,
does that make you feel better?
You're throwing a fit over
a little bit of humiliation?
You killed my father
and drove Seo Rin to this.
And that's not all.
You also murdered Ssangkal.
A murderer talking about being humiliated?
Don't make me laugh.
- You're being ridiculous.
- Why you...
My goodness. What is going on?
What the heck do you think you're doing?
This is my grandfather's house,
so it's my house and the Ma family home.
And you have the nerve to slap me in here?
- What right do you have? Know your place.
- You little witch, are you done talking?
Without Grandfather,
I'm the rightful heir to the Ma family.
This is all mine.
- So how dare you lay a hand on me?
- What gives you the right to push me?
I've never met such a vile,
despicable brat!
Hey, stop it, both of you!
Goodness, calm down!
- Get out of my way.
- Oh! Goodness!
Oh, dear. My goodness.
Real nice.
Treating Grandfather's wife
with such disrespect.
Seo Rin.
You have no manners.
You don't respect your elders, do you?
You don't even know your own place.
Who are you to lecture anyone?
What's all this commotion?
Grandfather! Mom...
Mom hit me.
Seo Rin!
CEO Chae!
I want a word with you. Now!
You...
Have you lost your mind?
After everything I did to get you
out of that awful mess,
you dare lay a hand on Seo Rin?
Father.
I'm truly grateful that you pulled strings
with your connections for me.
I was already preparing something
to show my gratitude...
But why would you take it out
on poor Seo Rin and slap her?
Are you doing this because
Seo Rin threw you under the bus...
over that injection incident?
She was just trying to save
her own skin by blaming you.
You're her mother.
You couldn't even take the fall for her?
How can you even call yourself her mother?
Father.
Seo Rin lied at the press conference
without even talking to me,
so of course I was upset.
I barely just got out
of the detention center,
- and I can barely face the employees.
- What about you?
Did you even look into why that drug story
came out in the first place?
That's a case
we already buried once before,
so why is it suddenly resurfacing?
Who dared to leak this to the press
and stir up all this trouble?
If you want to protect your own daughter,
shouldn't you be investigating that first?
Is this old geezer on my case
because he knows I'm the leaker?
And like I told you before,
I'm not letting this slide.
Your one percent stake.
Sign it over to Seo Rin.
- I can't do that, Father.
- Did you forget the promise you made me?
Should I make you pay for all the damages
our company suffered...
while you were in jail?
This is insane! I'm so sick of this.
So sick of it!
I'm so sick and tired of this!
You monster, Chae Hwa Young.
Don't you dare whine about your suffering.
You haven't seen anything yet.
Compared to the pain my family suffered...
and what Seo Rin and I have endured,
what you're feeling now
is just a drop in the bucket.
There you are.
Did you ask Lawyer Kang
where Oh Jang Mi is?
If he were the type to talk,
he would've given her up already.
So he's keeping his mouth shut, then?
- Yes.
- Gosh, when are we going to solve this?
By the way, Hong Ju,
something's off with Seo Rin and CEO Chae.
What do you mean?
They're a mother and daughter,
but they act like mortal enemies.
- Really?
- Yes.
I wonder why.
You think Seo Rin found out
that her mom abandoned Oh Jang Mi?
Professor Kang.
Did you come here knowing I'd be here?
No.
I just came for a drink
because I was upset about something,
and you just happened to be here.
You and I...
I guess we're fated
to keep running into each other.
Even when we try not to, we keep running
into each other like this.
Or maybe you came here on purpose,
not by chance.
I don't trust you anymore, CEO Chae.
What's this? Why are you crying?
Is this your new strategy?
Trying to win me over with tears?
No. I'm not appealing for anything.
It's not like that at all.
Then why are you crying?
I'm sorry.
I can't help it.
The tears just keep coming.
It feels like the one person I believed
was always on my side...
is walking away, and I'm just watching
his back disappear,
leaving me all alone
in a vast, empty field.
My heart aches,
and I feel so lonely and desolate.
Professor Kang.
Do you hate me that much?
I haven't done anything wrong to you.
- I don't want to hear it. Just stop.
- No.
I'm going to say everything now.
I can't stay silent
when this is so unfair.
You're misunderstanding me.
I'm the one being wronged here.
What exactly do you think I did wrong?
Why did the person
who took the fall for you die in prison?
You ordered the hit, didn't you?
In the end, you murdered Oh Bok Gil,
and then you framed me for it.
Do I really have to spell it out for you?
Answer me!
This is so absurd.
I'm at a loss for words.
Nam Bong, so this whole time,
you’ve been dating me
thinking I was that kind of woman?
That's insane.
How could you even think
something so horrible?
- So you're saying you didn't do it?
- Of course not! Absolutely not.
My goodness! Me?
How could I ever do something like that?
How could I hire someone
to murder another person?
And someone in jail, no less?
How could I have done that?
Does that even make any sense?
After I lost Seo Rin's father,
I didn't date anyone for 30 years.
I just lived under Chairman Ma's wing,
shuttling between the hotel and home,
as a woman who lived only for her work.
But then, for the very first time,
when I met you, Nam Bong,
my heart fluttered with excitement.
For the first time,
I felt like a woman again.
I wondered why I hadn't met you sooner.
I even imagined starting
a family with you,
and for the first time,
I found happiness outside of work.
I was happy just being myself,
Chae Hwa Young, not CEO Chae.
All because I was in love with you.
After feeling all of that,
how could I turn around and frame you?
Isn't that a horrifying thing
to even imagine?
For me to kill someone,
when I feel this way about you?
How is that even possible?
I don't know anymore.
One person tells me one thing,
and it sounds true.
Then you tell me your side, Hwa Young,
and I feel like I've had it all wrong.
Nam Bong, I really didn't do it.
I'm being completely wronged.
Most of all,
I can't bear the thought
of you misunderstanding me.
It really wasn't me. Please believe me.
They let me go because I'm innocent.
Is our country's justice system
that incompetent? Of course not.
I'm truly innocent.
If I misunderstood you...
I'm sorry, Hwa Young.
Nam Bong.
You'll believe me, won't you?
- Right?
- Don't worry.
Nam Bong, I love you.
Please, stop whining.
It's hard for me, too.
Jang Mi, I'm putting Mom on.
Try to talk some sense into her.
- What's going on?
- Mom keeps whining about seeing Tok Hee.
I think her Chae Hwa Young's men
are posted outside watching us,
so we can't risk going to visit Seo Rin.
Okay. Put Mom on, Tae Pyung.
- Mom.
- Jang Mi.
I'm going to see Tok Hee.
Suk Hee wants to play with Tok Hee.
- I miss Tok Hee.
- You miss Tok Hee?
Tok Hee is sick.
Suk Hee has to sing her a lullaby.
Let's just get through tonight
and go tomorrow, okay?
So just hang in there a little longer.
"Hang in there a little longer?"
Who were you talking to?
It's none of your business.
"Let's just get through tonight
and go tomorrow."
"So just hang in there
for a little longer." What?
Who was she talking to?
Jang Mi?
Jang Mi's gone. She hung up.
- Grandma, let me see.
- Okay.
She really did hang up.
She must've been in a bad spot to talk.
- Mom, you heard what Jang Mi said, right?
- Yes.
But still...
I'm worried about Tok Hee.
Grandma, take this bunny plush instead,
and you can rock it to sleep.
Ma'am.
- It's Baek Ho! You're here.
- I am.
You're so sweet, Baek Ho.
I brought your favorite ice cream,
- and Bo Ra's favorite snacks.
- Thank you.
- Bo Ra, let's go eat these.
- Okay.
Hey, little bunny.
Let's go.
You must be busy.
You didn't have to stop by.
I was afraid I'd forget your face.
Hey, Baek Ho.
But seriously,
is Jang Mi really marrying Jun Ho?
- So what's the deal?
- That's not going to happen.
He can't exactly marry himself, can he?
Jang Mi is never going to marry
my brother, so don't you worry.
You're the one who should be worried, man.
You better step it up so Jun Ho
doesn't steal her from you, you hear?
Jang Mi, are you asleep?
No, not yet.
I don't think I'll be able to sleep
until I hear it from you.
- Hear what?
- That you love me.
Do you love me?
- I'm asking, do you love me?
- For goodness' sake. No, I don't.
- There. Happy? I'm hanging up.
- Hey, that's not fair.
That's what you get for asking
such a cliche question.
I'm dying to know,
and you call it a cliche?
What's there to be so worked up about?
You can't get a confession for free.
Show me you mean it.
Then I'll tell you I love you.
Fine, I'll sing you a song.
Get all cozy in bed,
ready to sleep, and listen.
I promise it'll help you
drift right off to sleep.
I'm getting ready.
Okay, commence operation.
Begin.
If you were to ask me what love is
It's more than the initial butterflies
It's cherishing the comfort of familiarity
Even when things don't go your way
It's never giving up
Jang Mi. You were right
about the hotel supply company.
For years, they've just been
faking the bidding process.
And it turns out most of the people
involved are connected to CEO Chae.
I bet they're lowballing the prices to
ridiculous levels to build a slush fund.
She probably used that fund for bribes
in politics and business to pull strings.
I'll have to look into it.
By the way, you know Grandfather took
one percent of Chae Hwa Young's shares...
and gave them to me, right?
Of course. I just met with CEO Chae
and handled the paperwork myself.
CEO Chae is probably about to
blow a gasket right about now.
Be careful.
My patience has its limits.
That piece of trash.
I can't let her get away with this.
What are you going to do?
I'll have to teach her what happens
when you mess with Chae Hwa Young.
I can't stand watching her strut around
as if she's Ma Seo Rin.
Is this the new uniform?
Yes, that's right.
(4. Main Design Option Three)
(5. Designs by Job Position)
(CEO Chae Hwa Young)
Not bad.
Did you say the concierge uniforms
arrived today?
Yes, I was told they'll be ready
for inspection in 30 minutes.
Would you like to go yourself?
No.
This right here...
(Director Ma Seo Rin)
Oh Jang Mi, that insolent little brat.
Then again, what can you expect
when her mother's a half-wit?
What brings you here, CEO Chae?
I heard the resort's concierge uniforms
arrived today.
I was hoping Director Ma could
go inspect them in person.
Director Ma.
- Me?
- Of course. Who else would go but you?
We agreed that the Dream Project
would handle the Dream Resort...
from start to finish, didn't we?
Fine, I'll do it.
Sure. I'll go see just what a mess
the design you picked is.
Keep up the good work, everyone.
Manager Lee,
you have our people ready, right?
Yes.
Jang Mi is on her way there now.
Make sure there are no mistakes this time.
Show that arrogant witch exactly
what happens when she crosses me.
Yes, I understand.
Jang Mi. You were right
about the hotel supply company.
For years, they've just been
faking the bidding process.
Chae Hwa Young.
I will find out how you're
building your slush fund,
and I'll make you pay big time.
Just you wait.
You'll catch a cold.
- What's this for?
- You've never been in the laundry room?
The laundry room is way more
dangerous than the kitchen.
Plus, the detergents are incredibly harsh.
Just folding the restaurant tablecloths
for a day will make your hands raw.
I thought you were only a good chef,
but you know your way around
the laundry room too?
Don't go thinking I'm falling for you
just because of that. Dream on.
The fact that you'd even say that
means I'm on your mind.
Am I wrong?
My gosh...
Of course not!
(Caution: High-temperature Steam)
Alright, just stick close to me.
Please. I'm fine.
Director Ma. This way, please.
Right, okay.
(Caution: High-temperature Steam)
Darn it!
Jun Ho!
Jun Ho! Are you okay?
Here! Over here! Hurry!
Someone call an ambulance! Hurry!
- Seo Rin...
- What?
Oh no. Jun Ho! What do I do?
Jun Ho!
Somebody call an ambulance!
Hurry!
(The First Man)
So, you've finally grasped the situation.
I'll give you one week. Exactly one week.
Find Oh Jang Mi by then. Got it?
That's right.
I'm going to be honest with my feelings.
I don't want to live like this anymore.
Oh my, what's this?
Chae Hwa Young!
So Jun Ho is your most precious person.
Losing him
or having him stolen from you would be...
the most painful revenge, wouldn't it?
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)