She should be grateful
I stole her and not Oh Jang Mi.
I'm the one
who lets her live like a princess.
If I had taken Oh Jang Mi instead of her,
she'd be the one suffering...
as Jung Suk Hee's daughter
right now, right?
I'm the one who changed her fate.
And she repays me by running wild
with no sense of gratitude.
She really gets on my nerves.
And Jung Suk Hee...
jumped off a cliff like a fool
to save Oh Jang Mi,
and now she's not all there.
What was the point of even surviving?
She's just a lifelong burden
on Oh Jang Mi.
So that woman, Suk Hee,
really is my birth mother.
Wait, she took me from a set of twins?
That's kidnapping. Shit! She's crazy!
Seo Rin should be on her knees
thanking me.
Otherwise, she'd struggle like Oh Jang Mi.
What other life would she have had?
I'll keep a close eye on Seo Rin as well.
Seo Rin is sharper than she looks.
She could catch on quickly.
Be careful.
Understood. I'll watch her discreetly.
So I was the twin she took
to bring to this house.
"Be grateful?"
She kidnapped me from my own birth mother.
How can she say that?
I'm a daughter of that woman,
Jung Suk Hee?
No. I hate that.
I don't want to be that fool's daughter!
Why does it have to be her?
Shit... This is infuriating.
But how on earth...
did Mom end up stealing me?
What did she do,
and how could something
like this even happen?
This is unbelievable!
Shit!
Mom, I'm heading out.
Tae Pyung is so pretty.
Tae Pyung's making money.
Tae Pyung's going to work.
That new sparkly outfit
looks amazing on you.
You got that on a payment plan,
so work hard singing to pay it off.
Don't you worry about a thing.
- All right, I'm off!
- Bye.
- Break a leg!
- Let's do this!
Was my mom really such a monster?
You're not that kind of person,
Mom, right?
Tell me you're not.
The woman who gave birth to me...
(Suk Hee's Side Dishes)
Mom, you had a bad cold,
but you got better right away
after taking your medicine, didn't you?
Mom, you need to make sure you bundle up
so you don't get sick again, okay?
Jang Mi, you're so pretty.
Jang Mi is Suk Hee's daughter.
That's right. I'm your daughter, Mom.
Shit. This is so annoying.
How can a woman like that
be my real mother?
I'm going to lose my mind.
It's true that clothes make the man.
Putting on a proper stage costume
really changes my whole mindset.
- Okay.
- Hey, Tae Pyung.
You're not up next.
What?
Go on, break a leg.
Sir, I'm supposed to be next.
I need a word with you.
What? CEO Chae cut me off?
Right. You're a complete amateur,
so what could I possibly do
with someone as unknown as you?
You're not even a proper rookie.
So all this time, you only kept me on
because of CEO Chae?
Don't make me repeat myself.
Either way, we're done as of today.
Don't come back.
Sir, but you can't just spring this on me.
What, you want a preview
before I fire you?
Sir.
Please, just help me out here.
I know I can do a great job.
I even got a new costume.
I've got a whole new attitude.
Sir, just give me one more chance.
Please?
Hey, that's enough.
I said we're done here.
Sir...
Please.
Look, I'm paying...
for this outfit in installments.
Just let me work until I can pay it off.
- Sir.
- What is with you?
Sir!
What do you think you're doing here?
No, this can't be happening.
Director Ma!
Get a hold of yourself, will you?
Who are you?
What are you doing here?
What's wrong?
Look, you've had too much to drink.
I'll call you a cab so you can get home.
Mind your business!
I said, stay out of it!
So you're a crier when you're drunk.
Fine, cry your heart out then.
Fine! Mind your own business!
Nobody tells me what to do!
Goodness! Where has she been drinking?
Did you two drink together?
No.
Oh, my, she reeks of alcohol!
General Manager Kang.
- How could you let her get this drunk?
- Excuse me?
Yeom San Wol, stay out of this. Go inside.
Who are you to be scolding him?
He's my employee!
This way. Hurry.
- General Manager Kang...
- This way.
Why is Hwa Young
looking out for him like that?
(Suk Hee's Side Dishes)
I'm so sorry.
I'll be sure to pay this month's rent
on time.
I couldn't run the shop
because of my father's passing.
I'm truly sorry.
Okay. Have a good day.
Tae Pyung, when are you getting paid
from the lounge bar?
Even if you get paid,
you have to make
the payments on your costume.
Until you make it big, don't think about
bringing money home.
Just focus on your singing.
Jang Mi, you sound like his mother.
You think I'm nagging Tae Pyung
because I don't know any better?
Just stop it.
I'm sorry,
but I got fired.
- What?
- Tae Pyung.
This is killing me too.
Our whole family is a mess,
and now I can't even make a living.
But you're a great singer.
Why would you get fired?
That boss clearly doesn't know talent
when he hears it.
Yes, Tae Pyung is a good singer.
Tae Pyung is wonderful.
I don't think I was fired
because I'm a bad singer.
It's because I couldn't get to the bar
with Dad in the hospital and his funeral.
They replaced me with another singer
while I was gone.
Can't you keep your face
out of my sight, Mrs. Yang?
Day in and day out,
you show up with that beaten-up face.
It's ruining my appetite.
I'm sorry.
It's hangover soup.
Eat up, and it will make you feel better.
Seo Rin, my dear.
Did something happen yesterday?
You'll ruin your stomach.
You need to think about your health.
How could a young lady
who will get married soon...
come home completely wasted?
What will people think?
Can't you figure out
why Seo Rin was drinking?
It's because of you.
What? Me?
Of course, Seo Rin would be upset.
Her one and only grandfather
is getting remarried.
Are you saying Director Ma got drunk
just because my mom is getting married?
Enough of this nonsense. Just eat.
Seo Rin, you should eat up
and feel better.
I wonder what my Baek Ho is doing.
I need to at least get something going
with Baek Ho...
so I can try to make him jealous
or something.
This is ridiculous.
I haven't even been able to meet him yet.
My dear daughter,
you've been through so much.
Now that you're the chairman's daughter,
it's all smooth sailing from here.
I'll start looking for a good match
for you first thing tomorrow.
You need to marry smart, just like me.
Got it?
I don't care.
Right now, I'm only thinking
of Lawyer Kang Baek Ho.
What do you mean?
Did you hear a word I said?
(DNA Test Result Report)
(Ma Seo Rin, Chae Hwa Young)
(Probability of maternal relationship
is determined to be 0.000054 percent.)
(DNA Test Result Report)
(Copying to USB)
(100 percent complete)
(DNA Test Result Report,
Conversation Recording Files)
This is my insurance policy, just in case.
Insurance for just in case.
So, Mom wants to keep an eye on me?
Don't make me laugh.
I'll be the one controlling her.
I'm sorry, what?
You're saying the investigation is closed?
This is absurd, Detective.
What is it, Lawyer Kang?
The case involving your father is closed.
Shouldn't you be relieved?
Of course, as his son, I'm relieved.
But you even said yourself
that something felt off about it.
Then you need to investigate this further.
That's what the police are supposed to do.
Mom.
Why would you just hang up my phone
like that?
What do you think you're doing?
What do you mean, "something felt off?"
Are you suggesting your father
murdered Oh Jang Mi's father on purpose?
- No, that's not what I meant. I just...
- Then what?
The case is already closed.
But you said
there should be a further investigation.
What could that mean?
You're a lawyer, for crying out loud.
Whose side are you on, anyway?
What would your father...
possibly gain
by killing Oh Jang Mi's father?
That's true.
If it were a murder,
- it would mean someone had a motive.
- "Murder?"
Did you say, "Murder?"
Are you out of your mind?
Are you calling your father a murderer?
That's not it, Mom.
I trust Dad.
I know he wouldn't do something like that,
better than anyone.
Then why bring up murder?
Don't you dare say something like that.
You're not making any sense right now.
There's a mystery here
that I can't figure out,
and I don't know what it is.
It makes no sense that
Dad could be involved in this case.
I'm just...
I'm just so frustrated, Mom.
Hey.
I don't care
how crazy you are about some girl,
but how dare you suspect our father?
Are you saying Dad did it on purpose
to kill Oh Jang Mi's father? Is that it?
I'm not suspecting Dad.
The whole situation is just weird.
Even the police said things don't add up.
Shut up.
Oh, no.
Jun Ho, what do you think you're doing?
Baek Ho, are you okay?
What am I going to do?
Why would you hit your brother?
Use your words.
Baek Ho, are you okay?
Even when one son tries to paint
his father as a murderer,
you still coddle him
and take his side in the end.
I'm a lawyer before I'm anyone's son!
Everyone's equal before the law,
and no one should suffer an injustice!
That's what you taught me, Mom.
And I'm sorry, Dad,
but I just want to find the truth.
Baek Ho, I swear to you.
I'm not hiding anything from you.
I believe you, Dad.
It's not that I don't trust you.
I can't believe this kid...
(Suk Hee's Side Dishes)
What did you say?
They closed the case?
Yes, the order came from the higher-ups
to close it.
Detective Kim was disappointed too.
I'll try talking
to the detective again tomorrow.
What power does he have?
His superiors ordered him to close it.
Anyway, thank you.
I'll find who bought the drinks.
I'll go with you.
It's better than going alone.
Just wait here for a minute.
Don't even think about going by yourself.
A great opportunity just came up.
Is that right? How big are we talking?
It had better be a big payout.
Don't worry.
We're looking at a return of
at least ten times the investment.
In that case, let's get things moving.
Now that Oh Jang Mi's father's case
is closed,
I should focus on setting up
Seo Rin with Jun Ho.
- Yes.
- Right.
Still no word on Choi Ha Joon,
the son of Choi Myung Chul?
If we're going to take over Dream,
we're going to need his shares.
I'm still looking for him.
Jang Mi, let's go see Bok Gil.
Bok Gil isn't here.
I miss him.
Mom.
Mom, why are you being like this?
Dad's gone. He's gone for good.
- You saw him die, Mom. You were there.
- Tae Sook!
What? Our dad is never coming back.
We can never see him again.
Our dad spent his whole youth
taking care of you...
and had a lifetime of hardship,
before he just died so meaninglessly.
He's never coming back!
No...
- No.
- Do you have to be so cruel?
Why are you trying to shock Mom like this?
I'm furious he suffered his whole life
because of you and Mom.
Why did Dad have to clean up Mom's messes
only to die like that?
Why?
That's enough.
What's that going to solve?
Do you really think
Dad would be happy to see this?
You sounded like you were a perfect son
to him when he was alive.
You gave him the most grief, Oh Tae Pyung.
Always running off to be a singer
and getting scammed.
Do you have any idea how much he suffered
cleaning up your messes?
You're not one to be saying that.
Dad begged and pleaded with you
not to marry Bo Ra's father.
You stole Jang Mi's tuition money
to elope!
Dad got so furious
and said he never wanted to see you again.
Frankly, I never wanted to see you again
after that either.
What? You can't just talk like that.
Stop it, both of you!
He's gone. Bok Gil is gone.
Bring him back. Now.
Bok Gil...
Mom. It's okay.
Dad...
is just gone on a picnic.
A picnic?
Tok Hee too?
You mean, this bunny?
Yes.
Suk Hee is going too.
Suk Hee is going on the picnic too.
With Tok Hee and Bok Gil...
This is so frustrating.
I'm the one who wants to cry.
What am I going to do about my poor dad?
Who knew he'd pass away so soon?
Dad.
Seeing that Seo Rin came home that drunk,
something must have changed.
Did she really meet Oh Jang Mi?
Could that be why?
Right. I'd better find out if Seo Rin...
really did meet Oh Jang Mi.
(CEO Chae Hwa Young)
Ma'am.
How have you been doing?
I was worried about you, so I called.
I'm managing, thank you for your concern.
I was thinking of stopping by your shop
to see you.
Okay.
Oh Jang Mi is my twin sister.
The one who gave birth to me...
No.
The one who gave birth to the twins
is Jung Suk Hee.
(Suk Hee's Side Dishes)
Mom, you had a bad cold,
but you got better right away
after taking your medicine, didn't you?
Mom, you need to make sure you bundle up
so you don't get sick again, okay?
Jang Mi, you're so pretty.
Jang Mi is Suk Hee's daughter.
That's right. I'm your daughter, Mom.
The woman was injured
while saving Oh Jang Mi,
and it left her half out of her mind.
And I have a mother too, Chae Hwa Young.
(Dream Hotel Reopening Ceremony)
(Dream Hotel)
Good evening, esteemed guests.
(Genos Gene Examination Center)
(Probability of maternal relationship
is determined to be 0.000054 percent.)
(Ma Seo Rin and Chae Hwa Young do not
have a mother-daughter relationship.)
But Chae Hwa Young isn't my birth mother.
She's a kidnapper
who took me from Jung Suk Hee,
and she's trying to kill Oh Jang Mi.
How can something like this even happen?
I don't know.
Go on, try it on.
Let me see if I chose well.
- Ma'am, why are you doing this for me?
- What do you mean, why?
You've been so down
since losing your father,
so I wanted to do something
to cheer you up.
You need to shake off
this sadness quickly...
and get back to being
your old, cheerful self.
Your father would want that for you, too.
Ma'am.
What your father would have wanted...
is for you to get your bright smile back.
So, cheer up.
Thank you, ma'am,
but I already feel like
I'm always indebted to you.
Here.
Go on.
Are you going to leave me
hanging like this?
Don't feel pressured.
It's nothing expensive.
Then I'll gratefully accept it.
Let me put it on for you.
She's just like my Seo Rin in every way.
Except she doesn't have the mole
behind her ear.
Anyway, judging by her expression,
she definitely hasn't met Seo Rin.
By the way,
have you settled
with the person responsible...
for your father’s accident?
No.
I don't think I'll ever be able to settle.
Even if they claim it wasn't intentional
and it happened late at night,
from our point of view,
we suddenly lost our dad.
It just feels so unjust.
The case was full of suspicious things,
but the police just closed it suddenly.
- Really?
- They said a higher-up gave the order.
Someone powerful must be involved.
Otherwise, why would the detective
just drop a case with so many loose ends?
Oh my.
- Is that what the detective told you?
- Yes.
He said that it was odd
my dad suddenly went...
from the Dream Hotel way out there.
Oh dear. That's true.
That is a bit strange.
On top of that, my dad's cell phone
just vanished without a trace.
So how can the police just close the case
when nothing adds up?
His phone is missing too?
Yes. I had just spoken with him on it.
That was the last time
I ever spoke to him.
That's truly heartbreaking, Jang Mi.
I can't just let this go.
I'm going back to the accident scene...
to try and find my dad's phone again.
(CEO Chae Hwa Young)
Oh Jang Mi.
Don't dig your own grave.
Just stay out of it.
You won't find anything there anyway.
Because Oh Bok Gil's phone
is right here with me.
Dad.
This place really is
in the middle of nowhere,
even the road getting here.
If someone wanted to harm your father,
a place like this with no CCTV is perfect.
You're right.
I thought there were CCTVs everywhere
in this country.
And with no houses nearby,
it'll be impossible
to find any witnesses.
I was the last person my dad spoke to,
so it's just so strange
that his phone hasn't been found.
I'm going to search
every inch of this place again.
I already searched the whole area,
hoping to find something,
but there was nothing.
Thank you, Baek Ho.
What are you doing?
I don't know exactly what happened here.
But if your father's spirit
is watching over us,
I'm making an offering
to ask for his help.
Don't pour out too much.
I know, Jang Mi.
Half a bottle of rice wine
was his limit, wasn't it?
Father, it's Baek Ho.
Jang Mi and I...
will see this through
and get you the justice you deserve.
Please, don't you worry!
(Suk Hee's Side Dishes)
Baek Ho.
I didn't get a chance
to thank you properly earlier.
I never expected you to bring
my dad's favorite rice wine...
to the scene of the accident.
I just wanted to pay my respects.
He was a wonderful man to me, too.
With everything we've been going through
since my dad's death,
my family has been too hard on you, right?
Though you were always there for us.
Jang Mi.
I know it would be shameless of me...
to ask you to be with me at this moment,
but I am absolutely not giving up on you.
But after getting tangled up
with your father in such an awful way,
how could we possibly be together?
Just please don't push me away, Jang Mi.
Just like I promised your father earlier,
I swear I'll be the one to solve...
the truth behind this case.
What? You're getting a thank-you gift
for CEO Chae?
Yes. She went out of her way to visit
and gave me this lovely gift.
So I feel I should get her
something in return.
But I don't know what to get her.
How about a nice designer scarf?
It’s a thoughtful gesture,
but not so expensive
that it would feel awkward.
You think so?
Thank you, come again.
I'm in such a foul mood.
Nothing seems to make me feel better.
Shit, this is so frustrating!
(The First Man)
Just think about it, Mom.
I'm Ok Hee, and my sister is Tok Hee?
So is that why you called us
Ok Hee and Tok Hee?
Why are the police investigating CEO Chae?
Because Professor Kang caused an accident.
Professor Kang?
Mom can never know I met Oh Jang Mi.
I’m going to find out how Mom took me.
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)