(Episode 31)
Hello, this is Chae Hwa Young.
Ma'am.
Please, get Director Ma out of my sight.
Who?
Kang Jun Ho?
How rude.
I think the rude one is Director Ma,
sitting here gawking at me.
She's a distraction.
Please, just come and get her.
That's all.
That insolent brat!
But did you really have to call my mom
over it?
Okay, message received.
It'll just be a scene if my mom shows up,
so I'll get out of your hair for today.
See you.
Kang Jun Ho!
Who do you think you are,
telling me what to do with my daughter?
Just because you're the CEO,
does that mean you can lay your hands
on an employee?
This is a blatant abuse of power.
Should I report you?
Fine, do it. Go ahead and report me.
What on earth did I do wrong
to make you so upset?
Who do you think you are telling me
to get rid of my daughter?
How arrogant.
- Your daughter just didn't get the hint!
- What did you say?
I've put up with a lot from you,
but what did you just say?
She didn't get the hint?
I made it clear
that I'm not interested in her.
But she's so clingy. If she keeps this up,
I'll have to report her for stalking.
Clingy? A stalker?
Make this very clear to Director Ma.
If she keeps this up,
I will report her for stalking.
You're her mother.
You can keep her in line, can't you?
Do you realize
you're crossing a line right now?
You're trying to get a rise out of me,
aren't you?
You're testing my patience,
you arrogant punk!
Let go of me.
This is assault.
And this isn't the first time.
Do you have any idea
how much I've put up with you?
How dare you dislike my daughter?
Why do you dislike her so much?
This is an insult and a challenge to me.
Are you laughing?
You should be throwing yourself
at my daughter's feet,
what makes you so special?
How dare you dislike my daughter?
Who do you think you are to turn her down?
Calling her clingy? And a stalker?
- How dare you!
- If you're the CEO, then act like one.
Have some dignity.
Don't go around hitting your employees.
If I report this for abuse of power,
your position as CEO will be in jeopardy.
- Is that what you want?
- Go ahead and report me.
And you think you'll get away unscathed?
You'll be blacklisted forever
as the employee who reported his boss.
Do you think you'll ever find work again?
Your career will be over.
That's just your wishful thinking.
I won't let that happen.
I'm so bored.
Maybe I should take up pottery.
I'm warning you.
Watch yourself.
Don't cross the line again.
Please leave now.
"199005."
What's that?
Is that a date of birth?
What are you doing?
That tattoo on your neck.
- What do those numbers mean?
- Why the sudden interest?
Just answer the question.
I see.
So now you're going to use my tattoo
as an excuse to fire me?
How dare you talk back to me like that?
Just tell me if it's a birthdate
or if it has some special meaning.
That's it.
I give up.
As you wish,
I will give serious thought to resigning.
I need to think about
whether I should keep working under you...
or if I should just quit.
Hey! I'm not finished talking to you!
(Public Release of Suspect Information,
Name: Park Soon Sun)
So you're saying this is the gangster
you were looking for when you got hurt?
Ssangkal must have lured Jang Mi.
This was clearly premeditated.
I don't care what gang he's in.
I'll find that punk and make him pay.
- Darn it.
- But every crime has a motive,
- but I just don't know what it is.
- You mentioned it before, Baek Ho.
That maybe the banner revealed
that my mom was alive,
and you thought that might be
how they found out about me.
Right. But that doesn't add up either.
I can't figure out why anyone
would want to hurt you, Jang Mi.
There was the time
she almost got hit by a car,
and the time
a sign almost fell on her head,
and this time, she was almost kidnapped.
These aren't just
a series of coincidences.
So you're saying
someone's trying to kill Jang Mi?
But why on earth
would they target Jang Mi?
No, that can't be it. Why would anyone
try to kill a nobody like me?
Baek Ho, I don't think that's it.
It has to be a coincidence.
Even so, you have to be careful.
It's just that my Jang Mi...
"My" Jang Mi?
- Kang Baek Ho, punk. What's with "my?"
- What about "my?"
My dear Tae Pyung.
Our dear Father.
"Our dear father?"
You little punk! What did you just say?
- What do you mean, "our dear father?"
- Hey, stop it.
Chairman.
Chairman, you saw how CEO Chae...
bullied and abused her power
over me and my daughter, right?
When are you going to go public
with our relationship, Chairman?
I don't know how much longer
I have to live in this limbo.
Mrs. Yeom, time heals all wounds.
So just be a little more patient.
Come on, look at Seo Rin.
She doesn't lash out at you anymore,
and we're getting along
like one big family.
Exactly.
That's why...
it's the perfect time for you to decide,
Chairman.
I already told you that I need more time.
I've just barely managed
to pacify Seo Rin,
and she'll come around eventually.
Seo Rin isn't the problem.
It's CEO Chae. I'm telling you.
She's making life miserable
for me and Hong Ju.
(CEO Chae Hwa Young)
About Chef Kang Jun Ho,
have you ever seen the tattoo on his neck?
Sorry?
Yes, ma'am.
It looks like
it has some strange numbers on it.
I wonder what they could mean.
Why would someone get a tattoo like that?
He said it's his date of birth.
Why do you ask, ma'am?
It's nothing.
(Professor Kang)
Professor Kang.
I was just thinking about you, actually.
Are you free today?
(Bomdama)
- Hello.
Please have a seat over here.
This place is so big and clean.
I'll sit on the inside.
- Go on in.
- Welcome.
Lawyer Kang, why are you
treating us at a place like this?
Mr. Oh, does this mean
you'll finally accept me as family?
- What?
- Dad, just stop talking and eat.
- Okay.
- What's gotten into him?
It looks like a buffet
where we can pick what we want.
They say it's all-you-can-eat
with fresh ingredients.
- Thank you, Lawyer Kang.
- Not at all. Please, help yourself.
Awesome.
This is really delicious!
- Mom, I want some meat.
- Okay, sweetie.
- Dad, I want some meat too.
- It's delicious. It really is.
They have so many different broths.
Even Bo Ra, who hates spice, enjoys it.
- You're right.
- It's good, isn't it, Bo Ra?
It's yummy, right?
The meat is so delicious.
Suk Hee is going to eat a lot.
Please, eat a lot.
Mom, you're really eating well today.
Here it goes!
Okay, here we go.
Are you kidding me?
Seriously, did you get your law degree
from a claw machine or something?
- How have you not missed a single one?
- I have my own little trick to it.
No way!
- Oh my goodness!
- Here, this one's for Bo Ra.
And this one's for you, Jang Mi.
- This little thing? What is it?
- It's a lucky hippo.
In Northern Europe, a hippo doll
means good luck and prosperity.
Give it to me.
You're always misplacing things,
so I'll attach it to your bag for you.
- What did you say? I misplace things?
- It was a joke.
Think of me...
whenever you look at it.
What are you talking about?
Thank you.
I'm home.
What's this?
Jun Ho, is something wrong?
This is not like you at all.
- You're home?
- Yes.
Jun Ho, what's the matter?
You never even touch alcohol.
What's going on?
It's nothing.
I think I might have to quit my job
at the hotel because of CEO Chae.
- I've just been worried about it.
- No way. You can't just quit.
What is it with CEO Chae?
Why does that woman
give you such a hard time?
My poor son. This must be so hard on you.
Hwa Young, you seem a bit down today.
There's an insufferably arrogant employee
who's really getting under my skin.
An employee?
There's just something about him
that rubs me the wrong way.
He's so insolent about every little thing.
You should fire an employee
like that on the spot.
If someone's upsetting you,
I'll go have a word with them myself.
Who is it, anyway?
Knowing you're completely on my side,
it really warms my heart.
I suppose a husband and wife,
through all the bad times
and the hard times,
are supposed to stick together
and face everything as a team, right?
That's not always the case.
You know how they say you can be lonely
even when you're with someone?
There's a reason for that.
I've never experienced that...
in my life.
I've always felt empty...
and lived feeling
like there's a gaping hole in my heart.
I...
I'll make sure you're never lonely again,
Hwa Young.
Professor Kang.
I'm always on your side, Hwa Young.
We're...
on the same team now, all right?
Would you look at him?
Didn't he come home last night?
I wonder if something happened.
What if he was in an accident?
"199005."
What's that?
Is that a date of birth?
Why do I feel so anxious?
I should've checked
whether it was a date of birth.
I need to see Kang Jun Ho
first thing in the morning.
(Wife)
(Child Welfare Card, Kim Young Ho)
(Date of Birth: May 29, 1990)
That's him. That's my son.
The date of birth is the same.
Who is this boy?
This is definitely a photo
of my Ha Neul as a child.
But why does Professor Kang
have this photo?
You're still up?
I think you got a call from home.
- It can wait.
- No, you should call her back.
She must be worried, waiting up for you.
I'm just going to use the restroom.
It has to be my Ha Neul.
I'm sure it's my Ha Neul.
So how can this be?
Why would Professor Kang have this photo?
Honey, what's going on?
Where are you right now?
What? You fell asleep
working on your thesis?
You need to take care of yourself.
You didn't come home,
so I got so scared, thinking you
might have been in an accident.
An accident? Don't be silly.
Don't worry, I'll...
I'm managing just fine.
Why does Professor Kang
have a photo of my Ha Neul?
Go on to bed. I'll be home soon.
Don't worry about me.
Okay.
Thanks for being so understanding.
Looks like my wife was waiting up for me.
And she waited up
even though she has a cold.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to look,
but I was getting your phone when I saw
your wallet had fallen on the floor.
But...
do you have two sons?
Yes, I have two sons.
And you have only one daughter,
Director Ma, right?
I thought your only son was Kang Baek Ho,
the lawyer.
So then,
what does your other son do?
Well, the thing is...
(Manager Lee)
Hwa Young, your phone's ringing.
You should get that.
Yes, it's me.
CEO Chae, I'm coming in.
Oh my.
What's going on?
So Chae Hwa Young spent the night out?
Oh my.
Chairman! CEO Chae didn't come home
last night.
This is definitely proof
that she's seeing a man.
- She stayed out all night?
- Yes.
Chairman, it looks like
we'll have to marry off CEO Chae soon.
I don't know whether
this is a good or a bad thing,
but in the prime of her life,
how many years has she spent all alone
as a faithful widow?
You just have to turn a blind eye...
and let CEO Chae leave this house.
What other choice is there?
Mrs. Yeom.
I didn't realize you were so indiscreet.
- What?
- You aren't sure of anything yet,
- so why must you be such a gossip?
- Oh my goodness.
I'm sorry.
- I only thought it was for the best...
- Shut up.
You've got some nerve
slandering my mother.
You think I don't know what you're up to?
You want to kick my mom out of this house,
so you and Hong Ju
can take over this house and Dream Group.
How could you...
Director Ma, that's a baseless accusation.
How could you say such terrible things?
I swear on my life
I've never even considered such a thing.
Seo Rin, that's enough.
That's no way to speak to your elders.
Grandfather,
this woman is saying my mom...
was out all night with a man.
She's just running her mouth!
So you're telling me to just let it slide
when she's slandering my mom?
Oh my goodness.
This is so unfair.
It's so unfair I can't stand it.
Slandering? Who is slandering anyone?
So I'm not even allowed to say
CEO Chae didn't come home last night?
Unbelievable.
Seriously.
Just you wait.
I'm sure of it.
Chae Hwa Young is seeing a man.
One way or another, I'll find proof
and get her kicked out of this house.
I hope things work out between my Hong Ju
and the youngest son of Jinan Chemicals.
I wonder if she had a chance
to talk to him by the Han River.
It's about time
for Lawyer Kang Baek Ho to show up.
I'm sure it was around this time.
Yes, there he is.
It's Lawyer Kang Baek Ho.
Oh my goodness!
Don't you recognize me?
Last time when I fell,
you put a bandage on me,
and you even hailed a cab for me.
Remember?
I did? No, I never put a bandage on you.
Right. You didn't put it on,
but you gave it to me.
The bandage.
And the taxi.
Right. Yes.
What a coincidence, running into you here.
I guess you usually run around this time.
Sometimes, when I'm not too busy.
My bike broke down,
so I was just jogging and...
Are you all right?
Be careful.
What the heck?
He didn't even try to catch me.
He just left.
Unbelievable.
I told the Chairman
that you were in meetings all night...
about the Dream Resort project.
Okay, got it.
Were you...
with Professor Kang?
What are you going to do
if the Chairman finds out?
Kang Hyuk.
Yes. What is it?
I've kept Ha Neul a secret all this time,
but is now the right time to tell him?
What's wrong, Hwa Young?
Have them bring up the documents
for my approval.
Are you actually thinking of
remarrying Professor Kang?
Are you just going to throw away Dream
you've worked for all this time?
All for some man?
- Don't be dramatic. It's not like that.
- Then what is it?
You were with Professor Kang yesterday.
I'm tired. Get out.
And cancel all my afternoon appointments.
- Didn't you hear me? I said get out.
- Hwa Young...
I said get out!
Why have you been hiding
so many things from me lately?
Since when do we have
so many secrets between us?
Lee Kang Hyuk.
I told you not to cross the line.
Who do you think you are to me?
- Where do you get off being so arrogant?
- Chae Hwa Young.
So you're really not going to tell me?
Just because Kang Jun Ho
looks down on me and acts so arrogant,
does that mean I'm a joke to you, too?
Is that it?
You know that's not true.
It's just that you won't confide in me...
and it's starting to hurt.
Don't be late for the meeting.
(CEO Chae Hwa Young)
I'm sure CEO Chae is seeing a man.
Are you serious?
Mom, that's great news for us then!
Absolutely. Of course it is.
But that little brat Seo Rin
was making a huge fuss,
telling the Chairman that we're trying
to take over Dream and all that.
- And she was right on the money.
- Seriously?
- She's sharp as a tack.
- The way she ran her mouth scared me.
Ma Seo Rin is a sneaky little fox.
She was onto us the whole time.
She's always one step ahead.
Anyway, we have to be extra careful.
By the way, you're at the company,
so see if Chae Hwa Young is dating...
or where she's meeting this guy.
Keep a close watch on her.
Come on, you don't really think
she'd bring him into the company, do you?
You never know.
Love affairs usually start
when you see each other every day,
and things happen with someone
right under your nose.
Got it.
Chae Hwa Young, you're finished.
The day you get caught seeing a man,
it's over for you.
So much for that holier-than-thou act.
- I'm here.
- Hey.
What?
- What is all this?
- It's nothing.
Hey, my arm's about to fall off.
Mr. Oh, after that shock,
Jang Mi needs to eat well for a while.
Otherwise,
she could develop a chronic condition.
What?
Well, you're right.
Baek Ho, can I talk to you for a second?
What is it?
What do you think you're doing?
What? What do you mean?
I already feel so indebted to you,
so why are you making this
so uncomfortable for me?
Are you trying to bury me in debt
or something?
Come on, why would you even say that?
Since you went through
such a shocking experience,
I thought you should eat well
and get back on your feet quickly...
Did you ever stop to think
how much pressure this puts on me?
- Jang Mi.
- You bought my family dinner yesterday.
Why am I always on the receiving end?
Relationships are about give and take.
I have nothing to give you in return
except for some side dishes,
so why do you keep making me the taker?
Who says you have nothing to give?
You have plenty to give me too.
What are you talking about?
Think about it carefully.
Think about what you can offer me.
I mean it, think hard.
You don't have to come up with it
right away.
Take your time and think it over.
You'll figure it out eventually.
You seem very busy these days.
Yes, things at the company
have been hectic.
Especially with the Dream Resort project.
Mom, did you see
Chef Kang Jun Ho's tattoo?
Even his tattoo is so cool.
I saw he had some strange date tattooed
on the back of his neck.
I wondered if it had some special meaning,
but apparently it's his own birthday.
I guess Chef Kang is pretty narcissistic,
seeing he tattooed his own birthday
on himself.
I heard he got it to cover up some moles.
He has three moles in a row on his neck
that he thought were ugly.
What?
CEO Chae, is that really so surprising?
(The First Man)
Tell Chef Kang Jun Ho
to come to my office.
Hey, stop. I'm expecting someone.
You two seem to know each other.
Go on the blind date.
She'll be better than that trashy girl.
- Okay, I will.
- What?
Honey, could you really leave me
for another woman?
Are you kidding me?
Excuse me.
This man is mine.
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)