December 12, 1996, at 3:15 am.
It's a baby boy.
They're here! Run!
Doctor, please take my baby and run!
Mom, have you ever thought
that you imagined it?
I trusted them once.
I believed everything they said.
That I had lost my son
and that the stress had affected my mind
and created hallucinations.
But believe me, Valentine,
it was all lies.
The government lied and controlled us.
Your brother must live on The Farm…
NICKNAME: ALMOND
ALMOND EIGHT YEARS OLD
…with no chance to choose his own life.
ALMOND 28 YEARS OLD
Mom…
I found him.
♪ All you ladies
Are you looking for love? ♪
♪ Tired of waiting for what you deserve ♪
♪ Hidden treasure
They don't come so easy ♪
♪ Let this love take you
To where you can be ♪
♪ Ladies and Gentlemen ♪
♪ Are you ready for the show? ♪
♪ Five, four, three, two ♪
♪ Ready, Set, Love ♪
♪ Ladies, you ready ♪
♪ This is the day you've waited for ♪
♪ All that you need ♪
♪ Are better love and brighter days ♪
♪ Ladies, you ready ♪
♪ Don't let this chance get away ♪
♪ Are you ready for love? ♪
What are you doing here?
Answer me.
It's all right.
She was looking
for a new shooting location,
so I said I'd show her around.
I see.
Well then, remind her
that this is a restricted area.
Of course.
Thank you. Good night, Mr. Almond.
Good night.
Come on.
I remember you now.
What?
You conducted our interviews, right?
Yeah.
Try to be more careful next time.
The Farm has a lot of restricted areas.
Even The Gentlemen can't go in there.
Got it.
Thanks a lot, Almond.
You got it.
I should get going.
Almond, wait.
Well…
Well, I…
Are you available for more footage?
Attention, ladies.
There will be no shoot for the show today.
Please enjoy your time off.
That's crazy.
Son's got the same kind of necklace.
It isn't identical.
But it is one of those ones
that fits together.
Someone told me that…
you have a necklace like this?
You finally remembered.
I…
It's…
You're really tall.
It really is you, isn't it?
Mm.
Son… it's really you.
Hey, it's a bit tight.
Oh!
Oh, gosh. Sorry! I got a bit excited.
Um…
So…
why'd it take you so long
to remember me?
Hey, you didn't remember me.
And you accused me of being a stalker
and you tried
to get me out of this competition.
And who'd have thought…
What?
That…
Meow Meow was
a boy.
Go on in.
Welcome to my secret base, May Day.
You hungry?
Which one?
How come you can't talk?
You can live here now.
I'll call you Meow Meow.
I've always wanted a cat, you know.
There's a playground nearby
and shops with desserts.
If you like,
we can go and see them tomorrow.
Do you know my mommy?
Oh, you can talk.
My dad said he would take me to my mommy.
Can you bring her to me?
Hm. There are lots of moms around.
Which one is your mom?
Before my mommy went to heaven,
she told me to keep this
and that it will protect whoever wears it.
Here. It'll help you
to find whoever you're looking for.
Hello, Meow Meow! Let's go out!
Meow Meow.
Oh!
Meow Meow?
And after that
you were brought back here?
Mm.
They wouldn't let me go that easily.
And your father came back as well?
Dad.
Keep going!
-Get away from here.
-Dad!
As for me…
I'm no different
from the fish in this tank.
I get it now.
Why you looked so upset
when I said I wanted to stay here.
I always wondered
would we recognize each other
if we met some day?
I wondered
what you'd look like as an adult.
Mm.
Here.
I give this back to you.
And let this necklace…
protect you always.
Uh… Mm.
I… Wait here.
I gotta pee, okay?
Yeah.
Oh, wait a second.
It's our day off today.
We don't have a shoot
for Ready, Set, Love, right?
Hm.
Then…
let's go out.
What do you say?
And to finish up today,
I'll be playing our most requested song.
Thanks for listening, everyone.
This is Beyond The Wall.
♪ They will not force us again ♪
♪ They will not cause us any pain ♪
♪ We will refuse ♪
♪ When the sun starts shining
Feel the light ♪
♪ Yes, we may not survive
But we really… ♪
♪ …have to try… ♪
Hey, what are you doing?
♪ Beyond the wall where tears… ♪
What are the chances?
I was just fixing my radio
and your song came on.
What? So Chun replied?
-And you talked all night?
-Mm.
But he's never replied to anyone.
So? What did he say?
Uh… Hey!
I want to know more about you.
Tell me about the world outside.
The music you listen to.
What books you read.
If you want to know that much,
how about we meet up?
I can't.
The Farm has strict rules.
I'm on a fixed schedule
and there are staff that follow me around.
Doesn't that bore you?
Don't you want to be free?
Hm…
I don't know.
I've lived here my whole life.
I've never known anything else.
It's like asking a fish
if they'd like to fly
like a bird in the sky.
They wouldn't be able to imagine it.
But you're not a fish.
So why not come outside
and fly with the birds?
What?
Oh, my God.
I'm blushing listening to this.
It sounds like a confession.
It does?
So…
how are you feeling?
Mm.
Don't know really.
I really like Chun.
And I like you too, Bovy.
I don't know.
I don't know what I want.
How about we test it?
How?
What do you think?
Ah, you're just like me.
I mean, I've kissed a lot of women
in dramas,
but I thought kissing a man
would feel different.
I guess
it'll just have to be only Max.
Um, hey, I remember that you told me once
that no woman
has ever made your heart beat faster.
What about with a man?
Well, what were you doing there?
I want a straight answer.
Well, it was an accident.
I was trying
to find some really nice locations.
I just got lost.
Stop lying!
Do you understand what you did
was a serious violation of the rules?
I have every right
to send you to The Farm,
and I promise you don't want that.
My brother is here!
My mom wants to meet him.
She said he was brought here
without her consent.
And she was confined,
tortured and drugged.
All she wanted was to be with her son
and to watch him grow.
How did we become the ones
who were considered criminals?
There are reasons
why those rules are in place.
If you follow them, you're rewarded.
And punished if you don't.
If you can't understand
something so basic,
you don't deserve to be here.
Now get back to work.
Hey?
We never had this conversation.
But if you do this again,
I'll send you to The Farm immediately.
Understand?
Why is God never on our side?
Despite all our efforts,
you're always made to suffer.
Look at this as sending our son
to boarding school… or summer camp.
And when he's of age, then we can see him.
The Farm is not a summer camp.
And you know that.
You know, I heard that there's a group
who can help people like you and I.
They're called City Ground.
Stop this.
You, of all people, know
how hard I worked to get to this point.
I'm not going to sacrifice it all
for the sake of a child.
Yes, but that child will be our child.
But we can try again
as many times as it takes.
I'm good with that.
And when our son has reached legal age,
we'll go and visit him.
That doesn't sound like a life.
In the morning,
I'll inform the authorities.
I'm the doctor.
I think it's my responsibility.
I'll take care of it.
Oh, you look so pretty, little sister.
You're definitely slaying it, Queen.
So you're saying
I could be one of The Ladies?
Come on.
Uh… Oh, hey!
This way.
-What are you doing?
-Shh!
This is dangerous.
So many guards patrolling
and cameras everywhere.
Are we gonna make it?
When the guards come back,
those cameras will point the other way.
-Right. Follow me.
-Okay.
-Come on. They're coming back.
-Oh!
Oof!
Sorry, sorry.
Hang on. How did you know
which way the cameras would face
and when the guards
were going to come back?
I've always had this plan…
but never the courage to do it.
Think of it
as a challenge in the competition.
Ah!
And now we're doing
a special game called Hide and Seek.
Hey, you have to see this.
Oh, my God, they're so cute.
They're gone. Come on.
Oh, hold on!
Just give me a minute.
Are you okay?
-Oh, quick.
-Oh!
Huh? What? You okay?
Tired. So tired.
We got through the hard part.
Now it's just the forest.
Okay, you ready? Great.
Control yourself.
Hey, wait for me.
Oh!
Blessed one! Blessed one! Blessed one!
Hey, it's me. What are you doing here?
Paper?!
What the hell?
Son, I followed your plan. It worked.
I was like a shadow. Nobody saw me.
Like you said.
What on earth is this?
Go back to your room.
Oh, and what is that?
You don't get to tell me off.
Also… why are you two together?
Do you like her now?
I'm coming with.
I don't want to hear
another word about it.
You can't.
Huh? Why not?
Just let me tag along.
I'm going to get out anyway.
You heard me. Now go back.
-I'm not going back!
-No, you're going back.
-No!
-Both of you, be quiet.
Stop arguing or we'll get caught, okay?
Hey, it's that way, right?
Yeah.
-Come on, hurry up.
-Let's go!
♪ Ladies, you ready ♪
♪ This is the day you've waited for ♪
♪ All that you need ♪
♪ Are better love and brighter days ♪
♪ Ladies, you ready ♪
♪ Don't let this chance get away ♪
♪ Are you ready for love? ♪
Hey, Son, look.
It's the car from that ad we shot.
Gosh, why are you so excited?
Anytime, day or night…
…car rentals you can trust.
Eve Car Rental!
Gosh, they're like nerds
skipping school for the very first time.
-This time we get to drive it.
-Where should we go?
Hey, gentlemen, are we going? Hm?
How long are you gonna fanboy over it?
Sorry for calling you so late.
When I can't sleep, I like to cook.
And you had said
you wanted more footage of me,
so I thought I'd call you.
Oh, that's okay.
Mm.
It says on your profile that…
your mother gave you to The Farm
with no intention of contacting you again.
Yep.
Well…
have you thought about your family?
Nah.
You must have heard that…
family, it's more
than just blood and DNA, yeah?
Huh?
Even though my mom abandoned me,
I understand.
I know she had her reasons.
But I grew up with those guys.
It was great.
My brothers and I,
we've got it pretty good here, you know?
For me,
The Gentlemen are my family and…
The Farm is my home.
And what if your biological family
hadn't intended to give you up?
Had been trying to find you?
I'd prefer that they didn't.
Because if they did contact me,
they'd be breaking the law.
I wouldn't want them getting into trouble.
I'm happy here.
Stop here.
Okay, take care, Paper.
-We'll see you later.
-Mm. Mm.
-Hey.
-Mm?
You guys… are you on a date together?
Anyway, at least you're not being followed
by a camera team.
Oh, come on.
Are you nuts? We're not on a date.
This would be, uh…
two friends on a cool getaway.
Yeah. Isn't that right, huh?
Okay. All right then.
See you later.
See you.
Bye.
♪ We are delighted
To welcome our passengers ♪
♪ To the airport of love ♪
♪ They say that eyes don't lie ♪
♪ They say the eyes are the only way
To say what your heart feels ♪
♪ I've had my eyes on you
For a long time ♪
♪ But I wouldn't dare ♪
♪ Looking you in the eyes ♪
♪ In fear of one day ♪
♪ You might know ♪
♪ The truth I hide from you ♪
♪ The love that I keep inside ♪
That's enough.
♪ Haven't told a soul ♪
♪ But I can no longer hold it ♪
Just go with it.
♪ The closer I get to you ♪
♪ The more I want to reveal my feelings ♪
♪ My heart is racing
Whenever our eyes meet ♪
♪ It's so hard to keep this love inside ♪
Hey, um…
Listen up.
This is a kidnapping.
Chun?
Here you go.
Okay!
Ah!
Hello again.
VISIT LADY LOTTO'S FAVORITE RESTAURANT
Looks like her.
Oh, excuse me.
Mm!
Mm.
You sound like
you've never had one of these.
Ooh!
Mm… Of course not.
Look at this lean body.
And the perfect skin.
Of course, I've never had this stuff.
Is this who he really is?
It's fizzy.
Oh!
I live by a schedule.
I eat what my dietitian says,
exercise with a trainer,
and my teachers are PhD qualified.
If I get sick,
a team of doctors looks after me.
Yep, my life.
Ooh, what's that? Mussels?
What's this?
You know, I think we should be leaving.
Mm-hm.
-We've gotta go. Just leave it. Come on.
-What?
Where should we go next?
Hold on, let me think.
So good-looking.
Huh?
Are you really right in front of me?
Wow, you're beautiful.
We finally meet.
Whoa!
Whoa.
Oh, it's incredible.
Where am I?
This is my place.
And the headquarters of City Ground.
Sorry for blindfolding you.
This is a secret location.
A secret place.
You're part of City Ground?
Can I get you a beer?
Oh!
That's right.
You don't drink.
Give it here.
Do you want a soda or something?
I'm old enough to drink.
So tell me about yourself.
And City Ground.
I want to know the truth.
Then let's start…
with what you know already.
TOFU CUPCAKE
Tofu Cupcake.
Here you go, Son. Some water.
Oh, thanks very much.
Hm, I've never met someone famous.
Uh, I'm sorry that my house is messy.
I heard you're a fan of mine, so thanks.
Uh, yeah, I've changed.
I was a fan of yours.
But now I'm a fan of Day's.
Oh, I see.
Um…
Is this your cat?
Not really.
I just feed
some of the neighborhood feral cats
because Day told me she once had a cat…
called Meow Meow.
And one day it disappeared.
She told me she cried so hard
and she spent months trying to find it.
She loved it very much.
Meow Meow, Meow Meow, where are you?
And so since then
we just… have never had a cat.
Day said she's too scared
of losing something like that again.
My sister always likes to look
like she's the toughest.
Except, actually, she's not at all,
you know.
She's really soft-hearted.
What's going on here?
May, were you guys gossiping about me?
Of course we were.
Well, what were you saying?
Mm-mm.
So what do you think?
He's here? You satisfied?
Hm, you're blushing a little.
You know…
I've worked out where I'd like to go.
Actually, you look good
with a wig on.
Really?
-Son?
-Hm?
What if I came first on Ready, Set, Love
and I picked you in the end?
What would you say?
Impossible.
Hey, wait a minute.
What do you mean by that?
You mean I can't?
You think I'm not capable?
-Oh, that's not it at all.
-Oh, right.
So you're worried I might pick you
because maybe…
you have your eye on somebody else?
Wait. Hey.
What would you say
if I told you that…
Ready, Set, Love is just a fancy advert
and that all the games and results,
the whole thing is fixed?
What?
There's no way.
What it means is…
no matter how you and I feel
or how hard we try to be together…
in the end…
something will be put in place
that won't let us win.
Well, it is, you know,
the entertainment industry.
I suppose, of course,
reality TV is all scripted.
Yeah, and I guess…
that means you know
who you'll end up with, right?
Do you even realize
that everything I do is for you?
You will not fail again. Am I clear?
Hey, you.
I've been watching you swim.
Training for the Olympics?
I thought I'd been really clear.
Why does it have to be Son?
I guess
I only like things that are the best.
-Oh!
-Is that funny?
All right.
Tell you what.
Let's keep this polite.
Then if you really don't like me,
I'll leave you alone.
Come on, that's more than fair.
-Hey.
-Hm?
-Do you come back here very often?
-Yeah.
MAY
DAY
This place is where I come
to get away from it all.
It's the same.
Here.
That night, Son's face was all swollen.
-Really?
-Mm. He'd had some teeth out.
And I thought it would be so funny
to draw on his face, take a picture
and then put it on socials.
I was kind of a troll.
I remember that.
The photo went viral
with the hashtag #sonthecutierabbit
It did. It trended globally.
I was mad. So mad
I didn't sleep the next three nights.
With Son, it doesn't matter.
He's always the star.
And for me, no matter how hard I try,
I am just the backup.
Life can be so unfair.
It's exhausting, isn't it?
Trying so hard
but no matter what you do,
never being good enough.
You're cute.
I can't look away.
Cheers.
I guess I'll have to keep trying.
Cheers again.
You sure… you should have that much?
Um, Well, it's sweet. I like it.
Oh.
To your health.
Uh…
Um…
I know that City Ground
was a group that resisted The Farm
and took on the government until…
they were purged.
Hm.
The truth is,
our families were taken away.
Our rights had been taken.
And we're fighting to get them back.
13 years ago…
we'd made a plan
to save a group from The Farm.
And when it failed,
the men were taken back to The Farm.
Only a few made it out
and City Ground was purged.
We've been underground since then.
They said it was to protect us
from human trafficking.
They lied.
Because it's really a system,
a system that keeps men as property
for the wealthy elite.
Ready, Set, Love is just propaganda
designed to make us think we're free.
And equal.
But all the past Ladies,
their families paid huge bribes.
This new lotto system
was just introduced…
to try and hide the corruption.
So are the other Gentlemen, you know,
aware that the results are fixed?
I hope not.
If I didn't visit Chanel's house so often,
I wouldn't know either.
And…
the reason I didn't tell anyone…
I didn't want my friends
to feel this hopeless.
The mothers who resisted
were jailed and forcibly sedated?
They were either re-educated
or we never saw them again.
No way. I don't believe it.
I've lived my life on The Farm,
why have I never heard anything?
I've lived my life with City Ground.
These things really do happen.
It's not a story.
What about me?
My mom gave me over to The Farm
of her own free will.
I've heard enough. I don't believe you.
Did she?
What do you think?
How many mothers
would give away their children?
You're from The Farm.
You never had a mom,
but I did.
Some mothers, they got pressured.
Some were paid for their children.
But my mother…
and the moms of City Ground…
sacrificed everything…
so that we could…
be free.
Okay.
What are you saying?
Are you trying to tell me…
my mom is in jail right now?
Or even worse?
Listening to this, I feel… I don't know.
I'm so depressed and sad.
It's like…
If everyone knew about it,
imagine what they'd think.
These things take time.
You grew up in that place.
Okay, that's enough.
Hey, give it a rest, will you?
I'm a grown man. I can do what I want!
Oh, yeah?
You are a man.
So I guess…
you can do whatever you want.
♪ They will not force us again ♪
♪ They will not cause us any pain ♪
♪ We will refuse ♪
♪ When the sun starts shining
Feel the light ♪
♪ Yes, we may not survive ♪
♪ But we really have to try ♪
♪ Beyond the wall ♪
♪ Where tears no longer fall ♪
♪ Where we can smile ♪
♪ Where fish can fly ♪
♪ And the birds from the sky… ♪
A while ago,
when I realized my fate,
I was weak
and I accepted it.
But I think
I want more now.
What?
Why are they letting off fireworks?
Dad!
Keep going!
Son?
What's the matter?
Can you hear me? Hey!
Oh.
♪ Beyond the wall ♪
♪ Where tears no longer fall ♪
♪ Where we can smile ♪
♪ Where fish can fly ♪
♪ And the birds from the sky ♪
♪ Are down in the blue ♪
♪ We'll cut the stars from the sky ♪
♪ And wear them as our prize ♪
♪ We will sing our songs again ♪
♪ From our tears we will refrain ♪
♪ We'll rise again ♪
♪ When the echoes of hope
Runs through you ♪
♪ It's now our time to thrive ♪
♪ Together side by side ♪
♪ Beyond the wall ♪
♪ Where tears no longer fall ♪
♪ Where we can smile ♪
♪ Where fish can fly ♪
♪ And the birds from the sky ♪
♪ Are down in the blue ♪
♪ We'll cut the stars from the sky ♪
♪ And wear them as our prize ♪