-I have to go.
-Will I see you again?
Well…
Say you'll come back.
Promise me.
Mm.
Well,
goodbye, then.
Wait.
Forget something?
Oh, um…
Thank you.
Well, what do we do now?
Run away?
It's crazy.
For us to get away,
we have to go back in.
-Really?
-Yeah.
If we run to save ourselves,
then the system doesn't change.
That's right.
I wanna help my friends.
They should know the truth about The Farm.
Hey.
Chun told me about City Ground.
He said they have an operative
working on the show.
Hm.
Are you sure?
Mm.
Do you know who?
Let me think.
Christmas?
Or New Year?
Halloween…
Valentine!
You met Chun,
and now you want to help City Ground.
And you!
You know that the competition is rigged,
and you're close
to the owner of Eve Capital
because you've been
in her house a few times.
We've got the spies.
Now we just need evidence.
It shouldn't be hard at all,
now that you guys are all in.
Yes!
I get it.
Yeah, so that's the reason
you wanted to work here.
Mm, yeah.
I'm doing it for City Ground.
No other reason.
Val, you should have told me
right at the start.
Then I could have helped you with this.
Day, I'm sorry.
You know you're my best friend.
The thing is,
the fewer people who know this,
the safer it is.
For you as well.
We're on the same side now.
If you need anything, I'm here.
Mm, okay.
I can deal with a show
that gets people hooked.
Except when they take away children
from their mothers,
that's criminal.
So just you wait.
Whatever they're hiding,
I'm gonna find all of it.
Ha!
All in?
Yeah!
♪ All you ladies
Are you looking for love? ♪
♪ Tired of waiting for what you deserve ♪
♪ Hidden treasure
They don't come so easy ♪
♪ Let this love take you
To where you can be ♪
Ladies and Gentlemen,
are you ready for the show?
Five, four, three, two… Ready, Set, Love.
♪ Ladies, stay ready ♪
♪ This is the day you've waited for ♪
♪ All that chimney ♪
♪ Are better-loving, brighter days ♪
♪ Ladies, stay ready ♪
♪ Don't let this chance get away ♪
♪ Are you ready for love? ♪
Hansel and Gretel
lived happily on the cheery farmland,
until one day,
Witches invaded their village.
They began eating the Villagers
and pretended to be them.
They even kidnapped Hansel.
On moonless nights,
there are Witches hiding among us.
And if we can't figure out
who the disguised Witches are,
all of the Villagers will be eaten.
Hello, and welcome back to…
Ready, Set, Love.
I'm excited to tell you about
this week's game, Hansel and Gretel.
Some of the players are Witches,
and the rest of them are Villagers.
The Villagers' team
need to complete six minigames
to collect the items they need
to defeat the Witches
and figure out
who the disguised Witches are.
As for the Witches,
they'll need to keep
their identities hidden
as they attempt to eat the Villagers
without being caught.
The Villagers' team will win
if they can complete the minigames
and catch all the disguised Witches.
The Witches' team will win if they manage
to grab and eat all the Villagers,
or complete their counter-mission.
Hearing the rules, the Villagers' team
have a hard time ahead.
Complete the minigames,
be careful not to get eaten,
and figure out who each Witch is.
But the Witches have a hard time too.
They've got to take the Villagers
out of the game,
but nobody can see them.
It's essential they cover up
what they're doing.
The more I think about it,
I wouldn't make a good Witch, you know,
because I couldn't
keep the lies up.
Contestants,
please check your assigned roles.
All right.
Everyone has been given
their assigned roles.
There are three Witches among them.
All the Witches know
who the other Witches are,
but the Villagers' team have no idea.
This is something I apply to my own life.
You have to do away with negative people,
just like these Witches.
There's a special reward
for this challenge.
The Lady who comes first
can bring their Gentleman home
to Mom and Dad.
Oh! Meeting the parents
is an important step.
Eve Capital's boss
wants Chanel and Son to be together,
and the show's rigged
according to what she wants.
We need to prove it
and release it on socials.
The whole country
will be talking about it.
The next challenge could help us,
if Chanel wins.
Think you can do that?
Yeah.
We'll make sure Chanel wins.
Let the game begin.
Twelve Ladies have made it
this far in the competition,
but three will be going home
after this game.
Let's see what happens.
Day, Day.
Are we all Villagers?
-Yeah.
-Mm.
Now what?
How do we know which people are Witches?
Ooh, watch out.
They didn't waste any time.
It's already begun.
-Hey.
-Mm?
You think we'll be able to pull this off?
Not sure.
I think it could be a big deal,
what we're doing right now.
It feels like
we're saving the world, right?
-Really?
-Mm.
Not for me.
For my part,
I just want us to be together.
Why don't you get a room, hm?
Eavesdropping is rude.
I wasn't eavesdropping. I'm right here.
-Yes, you were. You're a big liar!
-What do you mean?
That's not true. You're a liar!
The rules state
if a player finds a body,
they can call a meeting.
Khaopoon found Joy's body.
A meeting has been called.
The Villager who's caught and eaten
must be silent
and not move until somebody finds them.
Seriously?
Oh.
Now let's see if our Villagers
are able to figure out who the Witch is.
Um, I think I saw
someone sneaking toward Joy.
-Who was it?
-Oh!
Um, it was…
um… um, maybe a man.
It was dark. I couldn't see.
So, one of you two could be a Witch.
Hey, it isn't me.
It's not me.
Kaew did it.
Now she's trying
to point the finger at us.
Villagers, who is the Witch?
Please cast your votes.
Hmm.
This game could benefit
from another level of deception,
like a new character.
I wonder what team Chanel will be on?
I think they're going to set up Chanel
to have an advantage,
something that will set her apart
as special.
She will be Gretel.
That's right.
One of the players
has been assigned Gretel,
and knows the identities
of all the Witches,
except the Invisible Witch.
Gretel can give hints
to the other Villagers,
but they've got to be careful,
because the Invisible Witch
is allowed to guess who Gretel is.
If the guess is correct,
the Witches' team win the game.
Time's up.
Kaew has been voted off.
Please exit the game.
Kaew is a Villager.
What? I was wrong.
Okay, then it was Max.
-Hey, hey, hey. Why do you say that?
-Ooh, you all saw him lay hands.
-You're a Witch.
-You are!
-You are! You are!
-You're the Witch!
I was nearly able
to get myself a real husband.
Then it has to be Almond, Max, or Jin.
Which one do you think is the Witch?
I can't tell,
but we should stay away from them, hm?
Recommencing the game.
Come on, Chal, let's go.
-What are you doing?
-What about you?
You might, uh, be a Witch.
Come on, Chal.
Uh, okay. Wait, wait, wait.
Now, why don't we all just go together?
Hm?
Minigame.
The group presses the button
for 10 seconds.
Hm. It's easy. We just need four of us.
Then let's get started.
Let's get started.
Huh?
But I said it first.
-You ready?
-I'm ready.
-One, two--
-Wait.
All right.
One, two, three.
Ten, nine, eight,
seven, six, five,
four, three, two, one.
The Villagers
have cleared the first minigame.
You have received
the Witch-Defeating Sword.
The Witches are brewing poison.
The Villagers need to clear
the Shock Coil Challenge minigame
to stop them.
-Day, are you okay?
-Uh, yeah, I'm okay.
Go check on Chanel. Hurry.
Okay.
Come with me.
-Who's there? Who's there?
-Huh?
Hey!
-Who? What?
-Hey!
-Hey, who is that? Hey--
-Huh?
-Day?
-Uh, Almond.
Oh, uh, how's it going?
Glad I found you.
-We should get out of here. Come on.
-Uh, uh…
Uh…
Hey, we're here. Come on.
"To extinguish the poison cauldron,
you must guide the ring
without touching the electrified core."
Okay, let's start.
You good? All right.
So the plan is for Chanel to win?
Huh?
It's all right.
I can help.
Let's start over.
Oh, okay.
Oh, we made it, Chal.
It's okay. It's me.
What are you doing here?
The Villagers have cleared
the Shock Coil Challenge minigame.
The poison cauldron has been extinguished.
I thought you were Son.
Just relax.
We should stick together.
I'll keep you safe. Trust me.
Hey!
Have you considered that…
I might be a Witch?
Maybe I don't care.
But if you are a Witch, then…
…come and get me.
Come on. Let's go.
Hi there, Max!
-Hey, Almond.
-Hm?
Um, how did you know about our plan?
Once we finish the game,
I'll explain.
Okay. Right now,
Son and Paper are with Chanel.
With you on board,
we might even come out on top after all.
Mm.
Hey, watch it!
Stop kicking me!
It hurts, okay?
Venus, I'm sorry.
I didn't see you there.
I'm not sure
that was an accident from our Lotto Girl.
I'll call it.
Now the Villagers have their chance.
They need to figure out
which of the players are hunting them.
A simple deduction.
-It was none other than…
-Sherlock Holmes's dumb, cousin.
…Day.
Hey, it's not me.
It's not, Mr. Holmes.
I'm not a Witch.
Oh, I see now.
You killed her
and then called the meeting.
What? Clearly you're no critical thinker.
It isn't Day. I know that. Can confirm.
Hm!
Wait. You did it.
The Gentleman who's a Witch.
You thought you could fool me.
That's right, that's right!
Paper is the Witch.
Uh, there's no way that I am.
Damn it, Max!
If you don't truly know,
then don't talk such nonsense.
Yeah, listen to him.
-What are you saying?
-You're swaying people.
No, I'm not.
You're swaying people's thoughts.
-It's obvious.
-How is it obvious?
-He did it.
-You're imagining things.
This all seems
just like brotherly bickering.
-Am I wrong?
-No! No, no, no.
-Yeah.
Day didn't do it.
I'm sure of that.
I think it's Jin.
You scratch your nose
when you lie, don't you?
You're right, Almond. He does.
Whoa! You got him, Al.
Oh, it was Jin. You're such a liar.
Uh…
You deceived me,
but I'm too smart to be fooled for long.
You thought it was me.
Admit that you're the Witch.
Admit it.
Jin has been voted off.
Please exit the game.
Why, God?
-What did he say?
-Don't know.
Jin is a Witch.
Oh, good job, Almond! Congratulations!
-Bye, Sherlock Holmes.
-Bye-bye.
Hey, Chal. Do you think
only one of the Witches was a guy?
Nina is dead.
-Why?
-Opal has been voted off.
-Opal is a Villager.
-Hey, why hasn't Gretel helped out?
How about dropping some hints to the team?
Well, if it were me,
I'd do all that I can to stop
the Invisible Witch from finding out,
or it's game over for the team.
But if they continue to keep losing people
the way it's been going,
then it's game over for the team anyway.
Orn has been voted off.
Orn is a Witch.
Ooh.
Oh no. Almond died in the minigame.
And Max, Bovy, and Chanel
were the only ones there.
No! I'm dead.
Who is the Witch?
Yes! Demonstrate your will.
Blessed Illuminati, protect the Witch!
Mm!
Chanel has called a meeting.
You were the only one there.
Who was it, Chal?
I told you already.
I'm not a Witch, Chanel.
Neither am I.
I don't care about the game.
I wanna be with you.
Chal, how long have we been friends?
You can see into my heart.
I never could lie to you.
Time's up. Cast your votes.
I think…
Max is the Witch.
Max has been voted off.
Max is a Villager.
And now Max is out of the game.
Oh! So Bovy is the Invisible Witch.
Chanel's best friend is now her enemy.
Bovy wants Max, but Max only wants Chanel.
Even the closest friendships
can be torn apart when love is involved.
You're cute.
I can't look away.
Cheers!
Recommencing the game.
-Hey, Son?
-Yeah?
Bovy's here now!
Get out of here.
We'll keep the Witch away.
I'm counting on you.
Okay.
-I'm ready.
-Okay.
Day, Mako, and Khaopoon
have cleared the Ring Toss minigame
and received
the Witch-Defeating Spell Book.
Only one minigame remains.
Yes!
Oh! Hm.
Paper.
Huh?
Just needed one.
One body. Now we can call a meeting.
What?
Oh, mine looks like it's a bit sluggish.
We both might have
to power up a little first.
Shit.
Killed by Bovy.
You betrayed me.
Dude, please forgive me.
What are you doing, Lotto? Move.
Die, then.
Lotto, hands off me!
I thought you were friends with Chanel.
More like a frenemy.
She knows that I'm into Max,
and now she's getting cozy with him.
I wanna kick her into that wall!
Bovy, calm down,
or take your anger out on me instead.
She's dead.
Bovy, think about
all the good things
your friend has done for you.
Anything come to mind?
Now, think carefully.
Okay, relax, yeah?
Think of the things
Chanel has done for you.
Ping-pong!
Her bitchiness, and even her bossiness,
I can handle.
Except when it comes to guys,
I will give it all that I've got.
-Take that!
-Oh no!
Watch out, Chanel!
She's coming!
When you clear this challenge,
you'll win, huh?
Yes.
And didn't you say that you'd help?
I already helped you a lot.
I thought you knew my situation
better than that.
You know me and Max.
It's something that can never happen.
No matter how I feel.
The Villagers
have cleared the final minigame
and rescued Hansel.
That's enough!
The Invisible Witch
now has a chance to guess who Gretel is.
Who do you think is Gretel?
-It's gotta be Chanel, right?
-Mm.
Because she guessed all of the Witches,
except Bovy.
Hm.
-I mean, it makes sense. I'm with you.
-Mm. Mm-hmm.
Looks like a win for the Witches' team.
You got this, Bovy.
I'm sure that Mako is Gretel.
Bovy answered incorrectly.
Chanel is Gretel.
The Villagers win the game.
We won!
Hey!
Aww. That's such a shame.
The search for love is very important,
as all women know,
so it's sad to see.
But also, Bovy is… she's bonkers.
I mean, she might have just messed it up.
What kind of game are you playing at?
Explain yourself.
I've only been into Max
for a couple of years.
But you've been in my life forever.
Chal…
it's time you were true to your heart.
I just want you to be happy, Chal.
Oh my God. Stop hugging me.
You let everybody take advantage.
You're so simple-minded.
That's why I'm always stuck with you,
never able to get away.
I know that.
You're the greatest.
It's time to choose your dates.
Mako stole Venus's points
from the last round.
Tallying the scores from this game,
last round, and popular votes,
The Ladies eliminated are Opal…
…Khaopoon…
…and Joy.
Oh.
Even though Day was killed,
she still has a higher score
than Bovy does
because she was on the winning team,
and she's always been further ahead
on the popular vote.
The Lady who's in the lead
gets to choose her Gentleman first.
And The Gentleman in the lead
gets to pick the trip date first.
I'm interested to see
who Chanel's date is tonight
because she's already been on dates
with Son and with Max, as well.
And with each, she had a good time.
Chanel, please step forward
and choose your date.
Hey, what is she doing?
Sorry that I didn't trust you.
Let's go out, unless you're tired of me.
The Lady in first place
gets a special reward.
She may bring The Gentleman
to meet her family.
-Hey.
-What?
Shh. I'm returning it.
-We did it.
-Great, thanks.
-I have to go. Someone's coming.
-Okay, I'll see you later.
What's up, Lotto Girl?
You went all out today.
Yeah.
Of course you'd do your best
with your sister's life at stake.
It must be difficult growing up
without all the opportunities
that The Farm offers.
I understand that.
So seize every opportunity,
and give it your all.
Focus on the things you want.
And give it your best shot.
I should never
have gotten you involved.
I'm all right.
Just focus on your mission.
I can handle looking after me.
Don't worry, okay?
Day, you're in a bit of a mess now.
You could have just sat back,
always winning the public vote,
ending up with one of The Gentlemen
and living happily on The Farm.
Oh yeah.
That's right.
What did you mean
when you said that you're one of us now?
I meant exactly what I said.
The other night,
I heard everything.
I heard the whole plan.
So you're joining us?
Yeah. You guys are my brothers.
I'm here to help.
He's on the team!
Hey, Al.
You know, outside isn't comfortable
like The Farm is.
Are you sure about this?
I can't let you go out by yourselves.
I'd be too worried.
All right.
We should probably head back
before anyone figures out
that we're missing.
Here.
This is for you. Try a bit.
Mmm!
-What do you think?
-It's really good, actually.
Awesome! Really?
-Mm.
-Yeah!
I've never seen you make Thai desserts.
Well, people can change, can't they?
You should know that, right?
I'm sorry, man.
I should have told you everything
from the start.
Ah, forget it.
So your necklace matches Day's?
Hm.
So she was the kid you met
the time you escaped.
I'm excited for you.
I just want you to know
I'm happy you found her.
Hey, don't worry.
We're all right.
Well, that's just like Almond,
isn't it?
But you haven't known him very long.
He's the kind of guy who's really strict
when it comes to the rules.
I'm not sure he's with us.
Mm-hmm.
Usually, he'd be the guy
who was trying to stop us,
and not the one encouraging us.
Mmm!
Hey, you.
We have a reliable big brother
joining our gang.
Can't you say it's a good thing? Huh?
I guess.
Hm!
-Wake up.
-Hm?
Yes?
Bovy likes you. Do you know that?
I know.
Even on Mars, they know.
-Listen.
-Mm?
Bovy's really cute and nice.
You two would really
get along well together.
And you?
You and I get along together.
I like you, Chanel.
Oh…
And you like me too.
Okay.
Who is it that likes whom here?
Are all The Gentlemen
so full of themselves?
Listen.
Everyone can see it.
Even on Mars,
they know.
You just stop overthinking it,
okay, Meow Meow?
Okay, you've convinced me.
Meow!
Oh, if your many fans
could see you now as Meow Meow,
I wonder what they'd think.
They would think
that your cat is back with his owner,
and this time…
Meow Meow's staying forever.
Meow!
So, how am I supposed to get over someone
when they're this cute?
Easy.
Control yourself, and stay away from me.
Wait a minute.
You're the one who came to talk to me.
Oh, I get it. You're crazy, huh?
I don't understand
what holds you back.
With Son, I'm okay with losing.
But when it comes to you,
I'll never back down.
And you know it.
What a cutie.
Son, do try this tea.
It's been specially imported.
Thank you.
What lovely weather.
Yes, it is. It's very nice.
Oh, Son.
Chanel isn't eating that stuff.
She's on a diet.
Well, they are teenagers.
Such high metabolisms.
They can eat pretty much anything.
Right.
Of course.
I see…
someone's lost in thought today.
It's just that, um…
I guess it's just that
I'm not used to having you in the house.
But I like it very much.
Then…
how about I come and live here?
Excellent.
Would you look at that? Our queen bee.
You know, she just gave a lesson
on turning on the charm.
Oh, and Son's doing well.
He used to be such an Ice Prince,
but now he's like a delicious snow cone.
It's very moving to see.
Can someone get me a water?
How's it going?
And Chanel's parents
seem very impressed with Son too.
The most popular of The Gentlemen
with the heiress of Eve Capital.
It's a match made in heaven.
Ugh! Son, you're a rotten cheat.
Now I am switching my favorite.
Oh, don't be like that.
Chanel and Son are so nice together.
But Son's in love with Day.
You just haven't seen
the way he looks at her.
Oh, May, you say that
like you've seen him in person.
Oh, look at that.
Why don't you go open the door?
It's obviously Son coming to visit.
He really has been here, you know.
May I see
some childhood pictures of Chanel?
Good idea. Please.
I really hope this plan comes together.
After everything I've learned…
I can't stay here.
The kids on The Farm,
do they ever meet their real mothers?
We were raised on The Farm.
We've had no contact with the outside.
We never even knew
our biological families.
Some mothers chose to give away
their children to The Farm.
Then there's people like Max,
who were born into The Family.
Don't you feel like maybe that's weird?
What isn't weird these days?
People are just trying to survive.
I can understand that.
But not everyone… agrees.
I've been here
many times in the past,
and I'd like to apologize
for, um, for the way I acted.
It's just I never quite got
how things work,
but I understand better now why I am here.
I'm glad you're able to see that.
Eve Capital always must have the best,
and I can assure you, Son,
you'll be a treasured addition
to our family, dear.
Thank you, Mrs. Kwan.
But I have to confess that now…
I'm worried because I want Chal to…
win the competition, or…
we won't get to be together.
We are the main sponsor of the show.
I need Chanel to win.
I will do whatever it takes.
Don't worry.
It's all been arranged.
I'm so happy to hear that.
Your words mean a lot.
It's so great!
That's more than enough.
Once this information is public knowledge,
it's over.
I'm sorry, Chanel.
Never again
will I judge someone so quickly.
Ms. Kwan, you have a call from Ms. Jenny.
Jenny.
Excuse me for a moment.
While you're gone,
I'll look at photographs.
What a good idea.
Hello?
What is it?
Files converted.
-Let's upload.
-Yay!
-And enter.
-Yeah.
Huh? Oh no.
Come on, internet.
Is there no signal?
Hang on. I'll try hotspotting you.
-Hm?
-No.
What?
Mine doesn't have signal either.
-What's happening?
-I'll check again.
-It's not working.
-What's going on?
You're coming with us.
You maintain a quiet and bored facade,
and yet, you're quite something,
aren't you?
You should all be grateful
that I'm the one who found you out.
Otherwise, it would have been bad.
But, as I'm the producer
of Ready, Set, Love,
you're all my problem.
So then, I've decided
to offer you a way out.
If you all agree
to play the game as I instruct,
and I mean you all,
this will go no further.
Okay?
Win-win.
You don't know how unpleasant
The Farm can get.
Or Eve Capital's power.
There are secrets in this place
that you'll never know.
And you should leave them alone.
So you're saying
you knew about all of this?
You're just a kid, and so you're naive.
You couldn't possibly think
that if you just play the game,
you'd get everything you want.
You knew all of this, and ignored it.
I know you have a heart,
but I suppose it's okay
as long as it's someone else's child.
Someone else's life, right?
Who do you think you are?
Did you all really think that you
are the first to discover these things?
To think that you'll change it?
The world won't be that easy on you.
And you.
You just won't give up.
Why would you do it again,
after I told you what would happen?
Did you really think
I wouldn't keep an eye on you?
What kind of stupid idiot
do you think you're dealing with?
You brought all of this on yourself.
You and City Ground.
You just said you'd let us go
if we played the game your way.
Yeah.
The thing is, pumpkins,
she's not on the show.
She's not special, like you are.
Please, will you tell me
where we're going?
Excuse me.
Excuse me?
Please? Please?
Where are you taking me?
Please.
Why is it like this?
We only want what everybody else has.
Why can't we be free?
It's all right.
Don't cry, Paper.
It's for you.
Come along now.
How come the lady looks so sad?
But I suppose it's okay
as long as it's someone else's child,
someone else's life.
She was right.
I am just a naive kid.
Who am I to change anything?
You're amazing.
Don't worry.
We're not out of hope yet, you know.
So we stick to the plan, but in secret?
Exactly.
Just like the competition.
It's here.
Only this time, it's real.
We need to work out…
who the Invisible Witches are among us.
It's here.
My God.
Hey! What are you doing?
Requesting back-up.
We have an intruder.
Just a normal day.
♪ Just a normal day ♪
♪ Look at the sky ♪
♪ The way the clouds are moving ♪
♪ No place to hide ♪
♪ Another day, though it brings ♪
♪ And don't you know
Extraordinary things could happen ♪
♪ Usual, normal days
I will take it gladly ♪
♪ No problem ♪
♪ Just a normal day ♪
Just a normal day.
♪ Things never change ♪
♪ Just a normal day ♪
♪ Same faces, they're walking ♪
♪ Not finished yet ♪
♪ Just a normal day ♪
♪ I know what everyone's thinking ♪
♪ Day after day, and every day ♪
♪ And don't you know
Extraordinary things could happen ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Usual, normal days
I will take it gladly ♪
♪ No problem ♪
♪ Just a normal day, yeah ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
Just a normal day.
♪ Just a normal day ♪
♪ Just a normal day, yeah ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪