[Unbreakable Ⅱ]
[Episode 5]
You wanted to use him to get rid of He Ming
and then have Xu Jianshe sent back to prison,
but unexpectedly
He Ming caught wind of it and ran off,
ruining your plan.
Am I right?
You two are overthinking this.
I'm not that capable.
Besides,
if Xu Jianshe does end up in prison,
you can't expect me to live like a widow forever.
Ms. Ma,
let's not dodge the real issue, okay?
He Ming has already fled,
and as long as Xu Jianshe isn't caught,
He Ming won't dare come back.
Your plan to use others to eliminate him won't work.
Do you know what's going on with Xu Jianshe now?
He's a fugitive wanted by the police,
and who knows what he might be up to
while in hiding.
Harboring him is already a crime.
If he commits another crime,
you'll be his accomplice,
and the punishment will be even harsher.
You should think for yourself now.
The smartest choice
is to turn him in voluntarily.
Let's not even talk about anything else;
your personal safety
would at least be guaranteed, right?
I'll take that as true.
Xu Jianshe has been on the run for quite a few days now.
If I were to hand him over to the police now,
wouldn't that count as harboring a fugitive?
I mean if,
I'm just saying, not that it's true.
But if you willingly hand him over,
we are willing to represent you as your lawyers.
Harboring him earlier was definitely a crime.
However, if you voluntarily hand him over and show remorse,
we will do everything we can to
help reduce your sentence.
I knew you two were waiting for this.
You still haven't given me back
the money you pocketed from me before.
Let me ask you,
if I hand this case over to you two,
can you guarantee that my assets will be protected?
Ma Lili,
are those really your assets?
If Xu Jianshe is actually caught at your place,
the matter of you illegally transferring his assets
will come back to light.
When he finds out what role you played in all this,
do you think he'll still let you
manage his money?
Besides,
you've already made plenty off of him.
Be satisfied.
What's more, what could be more important than life?
Let me think.
I'll let you know once I've made up my mind.
Hurry up, life is more important.
[Jingbei Municipal Public Security Bureau - Wanted Notice]
I don't need this.
Our law firm has been in the business for 20 years.
-You can rest assured.
-Thank you.
And our law firm is nearby.
Thank you, young man.
Auntie, please reconsider, okay?
Okay, thank you.
Hello, do you need a lawyer?
Take a look at our Yinghua Law Firm.
No need.
Thank you, young lady.
Thank you.
Sir, do you need a lawyer?
Please take a look at our law firm.
Young lady, how long has your law firm been established?
Not long ago.
But we are all professional.
You can't take my case.
Please take another look.
Follow my work plan for this.
On the first day, we'll go and handle these...
Excuse me.
Is this your law firm?
Sorry, I'm working.
How about this? You can go over there and ask.
I'm sorry.
Do you need us as your agent?
I'll think about it.
Are you a lawyer?
Thank you.
The business card I just gave you
has the phone number, address, and other information.
Feel free to contact me anytime if needed.
Okay.
Got it. I'll contact you anytime if I need to.
Okay, thank you.
Young lady.
Are you a lawyer?
Yes, Auntie.
Then is this card yours?
Yes.
Yinghua Law Firm is ours.
Auntie, do you need a lawyer?
I have a case.
I'd like to hire a lawyer as my representative.
Auntie, my surname is Xia.
Just call me Xia.
What's your surname?
My surname is Song.
Auntie Song,
what cases did you mention earlier?
Someone owes me money,
but I can't get it back now,
so I'd like to hire a lawyer as my representative.
How much does she owe you?
Auntie, here's the thing.
I need to remind you that
filing a lawsuit comes with costs.
It's not worth it if it's too small.
She owes me over three million.
Over three million?
Including the part without evidence,
it's close to five million.
That much?
You just said you have evidence.
The evidence means the other party's IOU,
bank statements, or something similar.
Do you have those?
Yes, I do.
Here.
You brought them?
Let me see.
Are all these real?
Could they possibly be forged by me?
No, I didn't mean that.
The amount involved in your case is significant.
I'll need to go back and inform my two partners first.
Then I'll set up a time to meet with you. Okay?
Sure.
See you next time. Bye-bye.
See you next time.
I've brought the money. Wait for me in the warehouse.
I'll be right there.
If you don't want to die,
don't shout.
Got it?
Don't play tricks.
Boss, you...
What do you want?
I haven't offended you, have I?
Call Ms. Luo and Ms. Qiu
here.
No way.
Listen to me.
Now,
the police all over the city are looking for you.
You're bound to be caught sooner or later.
Once you're arrested, it's the end for you.
Now,
only Ms. Luo and Ms. Qiu
can help save your life.
Get those two
to No. 3 Warehouse,
at No. 3 Plastic Factory. Do you remember?
Give me the password.
0694.
It was we who got your case
sent back for retrial,
not we who caused your trouble.
I've got a worthless life;
don't force me.
You know what to say.
[Xia Shu]
Who is it? Answer it for me.
Xia Shu?
Hello, Xia Shu. What's wrong?
Luo.
Where are you and Qiu?
Wait, what's wrong with your voice?
What happened?
I...
I was driving
out to handle a case
and got hit by someone.
He
ran away,
and I'm injured.
My phone's dead too.
Can you
come pick me up?
Xia Shu, you're injured?
Is it serious?
Hurry and send us your address,
we'll come get you right now.
I'm
at the No. 3 Warehouse, the No. 3 Plastic Factory
on Pingling Road.
What case is she handling at the plastic factory?
Xia Shu's car was sold long ago.
She couldn't have crashed.
Something must have happened to her.
Could it be Xu Jianshe?
Boss.
I'm begging you.
You're seeking revenge
on the wrong person.
We've always wanted to help you.
The two of them have been looking for you,
wanting you to turn yourself in
so you can get a reduced sentence.
It's Ma Lili
who has been lying to you.
She is together with another man now.
Go on;
keep talking.
It was her who caused all of this.
She gave us 300,000
at the time,
and then she wanted it back.
We barely managed to get your case sent back for retrial,
and then she replaced us.
She never had any intention of getting you out.
Keep making up stories.
Let me tell you,
in all the time I've been in prison,
only Lili came to see me.
She even took care of my mother for me.
Your mother
has been dead for a long time.
It's true.
What are you talking about?
Say it again!
It's true.
I swear.
Your mother passed away
while we were handling your case.
Ma Lili has been lying to you all along.
She wants to control you.
She wants to keep you in check.
She wants your property.
It's true.
She's dating
a lawyer named He Ming now.
They're living in your house,
and spending your money.
If you don't believe me,
you can call to confirm.
You can call to confirm.
I'm not lying.
Fine.
Sister.
It's me,
Jianshe.
I'm here, Jianshe.
I've brought the money for you, Jianshe.
Jian...
Rui.
What should we do?
Go outside and call for backup.
Walk quietly.
Jianshe.
Jianshe, what are you doing?
Jianshe, I'm here to give you money.
Jianshe.
Take the money and run.
Money?
Yes.
Jianshe, what are you doing?
Jianshe.
You want my money, right?
My mother died,
right?
No, Jianshe.
I'm taking good care of her.
Who told you that?
She.
You bitch!
Jianshe,
don't listen to these lawyers.
None of them is good.
The three of them have cheated us out of so much money!
Jianshe.
Do you still...
Let me ask you,
where were you
when my mother died?
Jianshe.
She's fine, Jianshe.
Jianshe, I was wrong.
Stop beating me, Jianshe.
How dare you spend my money
while sleeping with another man?
No.
How dare you lie to me about my mother's death.
It wasn't me, Jianshe.
It wasn't me; it's He Ming.
Let me explain.
It's He Ming.
He Ming knew that I transferred the money.
He wanted to send me to jail, Jianshe!
If I went to jail, how could I save you, Jianshe?
Jianshe!
Go die!
Don't move!
I'm a cop.
Don't come here!
Xu Jianshe,
if you're still a man,
don't take your anger out on women when things go wrong.
Put the knife down and you still have a chance.
My life's worthless.
I'll die anyway.
Officer,
you have only two choices right now:
One,
we all die here.
Two,
you bring Luo Yingzi and Qiu Hua here;
I have something to ask them.
Call them here!
Captain Zhang.
Shang, what's going on inside?
The wanted criminal Xu Jianshe has taken two hostages.
The floor is covered with gasoline.
Captain Wang is inside trying to calm him down,
but he's still very agitated.
Ms. Luo.
You can't go in there.
Is Xia Shu kidnapped by Xu Jianshe?
Is Xia Shu injured?
Rui is taking care of it inside.
Reinforcements have arrived.
You all should listen to me
and wait in the car.
Officer Shang, Xu Jianshe taking Xia Shu hostage
is definitely because he's looking for us.
We must go in.
Besides, Officer Wang is inside.
As long as we don't get close to Xu Jianshe,
we won't be in danger.
Please let us in.
We're on a mission.
-Hello, Officer Wang.
-Follow my instructions.
Go back to the car.
We're at the entrance of the warehouse.
But they won't let us in now.
Okay.
It's Officer Wang's call.
Hello, Rui.
Shang.
Bring them in.
Get up!
Calm down.
They'll be here soon.
Jianshe.
Ms. Luo.
Ms. Luo, Ms. Qiu.
The entire underground is filled with gasoline,
and he still has a lighter in his hand.
We can't shoot easily.
Xu Jianshe wants to talk to you.
Don't irritate him.
Xu Jianshe.
The people you want to see are here.
Can you release the hostages?
I want to ask them
why didn't you tell me
about my mother's death?
Jianshe, it's all my fault.
Shut up!
Xu Jianshe.
We didn't know that
you were unaware of this matter as well at the time.
Ma Lili never told us
whether she had mentioned it to you.
During our interactions with you,
we felt that you had violent tendencies.
So,
we thought bringing up this matter
would trigger you
and affect the subsequent handling of the case,
which is why we didn't mention it to you.
You know Ma Lili lied to me, right?
We only found out
after we were replaced.
At that time, Ma Lili
repeatedly asked us to meet with you,
bringing along the power of attorney for you to sign
in order to handle your property.
We felt something was off,
and later we found out
she wanted to take your assets for herself.
Jianshe,
the two lawyers have deceived us out of so much money;
do you still believe them?
Shut up!
Why should I believe you two?
You used to tell me that my case
would receive a light sentence,
but in the end,
it turned out to be a heavy sentence with no possibility of parole.
Because your case lacked evidence,
there was room for discretion in the trial.
Ms. Luo and I focused on that point
and communicated with the court at the time.
As long as you actively cooperated with
the victim's family's compensation request,
the court also believed it could reduce your sentence,
but later…
Later,
it was replaced by He Ming, right?
Did they two get together?
No, Jianshe, he forced me.
He Ming forced me, Jianshe.
Jianshe, He Ming forced me to do it. It's true.
You deserve to die!
Xu Jianshe!
Xu Jianshe.
It's true.
He Ming did
help Ma Lili
transfer your property; that's true.
But He Ming also secretly hid evidence,
and he used that evidence to blackmail Ma Lili.
That's how he later became the vice president of Ma Lili's company.
Xu Jianshe,
I'm telling you,
it's meaningless to talk about this now.
What's most important now
is that you need to understand one thing:
Ma Lili is definitely guilty.
She will face legal judgment.
But if you make your own crimes worse
because of her,
it will not be worth it.
Now, put down the knife,
put down the lighter,
and let the two hostages go.
You still have a chance.
My mother died.
Nothing matters anymore.
Who would give a prisoner a chance?
Xu Jianshe, there will be a chance.
As long as you surrender,
you can still seek leniency, Xu Jianshe.
I...
Both Ms. Qiu
and I
can become your attorney agents.
But if you really
intend to harm Ma Lili,
the punishment you'll face will also be greatly increased.
My mother died.
Xu Jianshe!
Xu Jianshe, think about your mother.
If she saw you like this now,
how heartbroken would she be?
You...
Don't you want to go to your mother's grave
and pay your respects?
She would definitely want you to live well.
Xu Jianshe.
Think about it.
Think about your mother.
Think about what the two lawyers said.
Your mother doesn't want to see you like this.
You deserve to die!
Xu Jianshe!
I'll turn myself in.
Handcuffs! Hurry!
I have...
I have evidence proving Jianshe's guilt.
Xia Shu.
There's an ambulance outside.
It's alright now.
Let go of me!
I'm innocent. Let go of me!
I can provide evidence against Xu Jianshe.
Goodbye.
Okay.
See you.
Thank you.
Hello?
I'm calling to ask you
if there's any progress with Xu Jianshe's matter.
Has he been arrested?
You called at the right time.
Xu Jianshe was arrested just now.
He has been arrested?
That's good.
I'm relieved.
I've been waiting downstairs at Luo Yingzi's place all afternoon,
I didn't eat.
I'm tired and hungry.
I'll head back now to eat.
Don't hang up.
Ms. Luo, Ms. Xia,
and Ms. Qiu were all at the scene earlier.
Was Luo Yingzi there too?
She was tricked into coming by Xu Jianshe.
Didn't anything happen?
They had a confrontation for a while.
She has gone to the hospital.
I have something to do. I have to hang up.
What are you doing?
Who are you looking for?
I'm looking for someone.
Excuse me.
Is there a patient named Luo Yingzi?
This is the observation room.
There's no such person.
You can go check the emergency room next door.
This way?
Yes, check over there.
Can... Can I pass through?
Sure.
Okay, thank you.
[Emergency]
Officer,
we'll be done soon.
Please wait here.
Will giving the statement later
take long?
No, it won't take long.
Okay, thank you.
Luo.
Qiu.
I caused trouble again.
I just wanted to remind you,
but Xu Jianshe hung up the phone.
Okay, Xia Shu, you've made progress;
at least you're reflecting on it now.
Xia Shu, in today's society,
I don't believe that
if someone says they'd rather diethan yield
even with a knife at their throat.
Most likely, they're just a hypocrite.
In such extreme situations,
none of this is your fault,
so don't take it to heart.
Just make sure the wound doesn't get wet
and remember to change the dressing on time, okay?
Thank you.
Why are you crying again?
It's okay.
Everything is fine.
There, there.
What's wrong?
Or do you want to wipe it yourself?
Sis, you better help me wipe it.
My whole body hurts.
Are you addicted to being a spoiled princess again?
Fine.
Just for today, I'll care for you like a mother.
But only this once.
Sis.
I'm thirsty.
Okay, my lady, I'll go buy some.
Remember to buy hot water.
There's no hot water.
How about I warm it up for you under my armpit when I get back?
Okay?
Okay.
Then just make do with drinking the cold one.
I've been looking all over; where is she?
Luo Yingzi.
Why are you here?
I heard you were in the hospital, so I came.
Where did you get hurt?
No.
Let me see.
Wait, stop touching randomly.
I'm fine.
I just have ticklish spots.
Why are you so stubborn?
Who do you think you are?
How dare you confront a murderer?
Didn't I tell you
to move out earlier?
But you wouldn't listen. You stayed at home.
Do you think you were lucky yesterday, lucky today,
and will be lucky tomorrow?
That you'll be lucky every day from now on?
Do you think you're a cat
which has nine lifes?
I know you hate me.
But you don't have to do this.
You just took your safety so lightly.
Are you done talking?
No.
You won't listen to me until you've suffered, right?
You don't know what's good for you.
I know Xu Jianshe wanted to hurt you,
so I've been hanging around downstairs at your place these past couple of days,
just in case he tries something.
It's true that the onlooker is more worried than the player.
Where are you hurt? Let me see.
I really didn't get hurt anywhere.
I'm fine.
Wang Rui said you were injured.
But the one who's injured isn't me.
Here comes the injured one.
Mr. Chen,
you are so well-informed.
You arrived so quickly.
Ms. Xia is injured.
How can you say that?
Anyone who got injured is not good.
Earlier, he was adamant that I was hurt.
Ms. Xia was kidnapped.
It's just an external injury, a couple of days of rest, and she'll be fine.
We'll wait for you in the car.
Here.
Okay.
See?
However,
I was careless this time.
I admit
your concern this time is right.
Yeah, just say it like this.
Just be obedient.
Are you treating me like a puppy, petting me?
Alright.
Hearing you say that,
I know you're fine.
I'm relieved.
Okay, I'm leaving.
I still need to stay with Xia Shu to take her statement.
I'm leaving.
I'll go with you. I'm familiar with Wang Rui.
You don't need to go.
What if they end up treating you as a suspect
and arresting you?
I can't bear that.
I know you're injured, and I rushed over,
and now you're leaving?
But Chen Shuo,
you did a great job this time.
I'll give you a thumbs up.
Exactly.
Keep a safe distance.
What are you doing?
I'm leaving.
Okay, I'm relieved that you're fine.
Xia Shu.
Here, drink this cup of milk,
and you can sleep well.
What are you looking at?
Luo,
there's a layer of milk skin on top of the milk you heated.
Yes.
That's how boiled milk always is.
You've never boiled milk before?
No.
I actually love this layer of milk skin.
When I was in middle school,
my mother would heat a cup of milk for me
every night before bed.
She said
only milk heated in a small pot would have milk skin,
not in the microwave.
It never stopped for all 365 days a year.
If you like it,
I'll make it for you more often.
It's not that I love it,
I just...
I found something interesting.
When people
encounter something,
the first person they think of is always their mother.
Have you noticed that?
Like, when you're scared or shocked,
the first thing you shout is "mother!"
And after it passes,
you're still thinking about your mother.
Not only you,
but actually Qiu Hua and I were shocked.
But I found
you are quite lucky.
You can always get out of danger.
It's all in the past.
Just consider it done,
and don't be scared anymore.
Qiu Hua and I are with you.
Thank you, Luo,
and Qiu.
But Xia Shu,
you have to learn from this.
In the future, be more careful
when you go out.
I was just going to get a facial;
I didn't expect he'd block me at the door.
I hand out business cards at the courthouse every day,
and my face has even gotten sunspots.
But it's all worth it.
You got kidnapped, and you still think it was worth it?
Of course.
I got a case.
And it's a big one.
How big?
This case involves an amount of 3 million.
I met a client at the courthouse,
Auntie Song.
She lent out 5 million,
and 3 million of that
is backed by IOUs and bank statements.
I've read it. It should be true.
She even reached out to me herself,
wanting us to help her with the lawsuit.
You met her by handing out business cards?
Why do I feel so unreliable?
How about I meet with her tomorrow and talk it through.
Whether it's reliable or not, we'll know after the conversation.
Okay.
Drink the milk.
It'll help you sleep well.
I'll call Qiu Hua
and tell her about this.
Okay.
Morning.
Morning, Ms Qiu.
I brought breakfast;
have it while it's still hot.
Thank you.
Xia Shu,
there's some for you too. Come over and have some.
Thank you, Qiu, but I'll skip.
I've got an appointment with Auntie Song,
and I need to go pick her up.
I'm leaving.
See you at the cafe at 9:30.
You got hurt yesterday;
aren't you taking a day off today?
I'm fine. It's just a scratch.
I'm leaving.
Tough as nails.
There's no case. Don't need to rush.
Take your time.
Here, this is Qiu's kind gesture.
-Have it on the way, okay?
-Okay.
Okay, I'm leaving.
Bye-bye.
She has made progress.
[Madam Mei]
Madam Mei is calling.
Madam Mei, why are you calling so early? Is something wrong?
Yingzi,
I've decided
to give up on that case; I'm not going to investigate it anymore.
Why?
I work in law,
so I understand the finality of judicial decisions.
It's over.
There's no need for me to cling to it
because of my own obsession.
Madam Mei.
are you really just going to give up like this,
even though Mr. Yu's death is so unclear?
There's nothing unclear about it.
He died of a stroke.
Alright, let's not talk about it anymore.
I've made up my mind.
I'm sorry that
this cost you your job,
but if you ever need my help in the future,
I'll be there without hesitation.
Madam Mei, you see...
Hello.
She hung up.
Wait, so
we've been going all out to help her,
and yet she's backed out when it mattered.
Yingzi, didn't you notice?
Notice what?
Madam Mei has already figured it out that
Liangcheng Law Firm fired all three of us
because of this case,
which means Liangcheng Law Firm's involvement in this
is far from ordinary.
So you're suggesting that
more than one person is behind framing her?
Could it be a coordinated effort?
Is that possible?
Do you think Fang Lihong is also involved?
It's hard to say.
Since Madam Mei doesn't want us to keep investigating,
there's probably a reason for it.
Maybe
she wants to handle it herself,
or maybe she thinks
continuing the investigation
could end up being worse for us.
If she doesn't want to commission it, fine.
I'll investigate on my own, no one can stop me.
But we've already been fired,
and we have no idea
what's going on inside Liangcheng Law Firm. How are we supposed to investigate?
I should have planted an undercover agent
within the Liangcheng Law Firm.
Speaking of undercover agents, there actually is one.
And he's the best.
I know who you're talking about.
Well.
You think that guy is the best in your heart?
He's not bad.
Let me tell you,
even if the whole world were gone,
I still wouldn't turn to him.
I'm serious.
Chen Shuo likes you so much,
so he'd definitely be willing to go undercover for you.
I know,
but there's no way we could be together.
Why not?
I just don't like that type.
So, what's your type then?
You like men of Liu Ming's type, right?
That guy's the one who screwed you over.
Is there really no one else in this world
besides Chen Shuo and Liu Ming?
Are these the only two men left?
Anyway, I can't stand his arrogant, slick attitude.
He changes girlfriends more often than he changes clothes.
That's true.
You didn't see it, did you?
Actually, I need security too.
Wasn't I screwed over enough by Liu Ming?
If I have a boyfriend,
I have to constantly worry about
which girl he's flirting with.
Who can stand it?
I can't stand it anyway.
Forget about him.
I'm going to apply lipstick.
Then let's go to see the old lady.
Wait.
Aren't you going to eat the breakfast I bought for you?
I'll eat on the way.
You drive, and I'll eat beside you.
Once I'm done, I'll touch up my lipstick.
Don't worry.
You go ahead.
Is there any meaning to an eyelid twitch?
My right eyelid has been twitching all morning.
Oh no.
Left eyelid twitching means good luck, right eyelid twitching means bad luck.
Forget what you said.
Go in first.
I'll call them back.
Hurry up.
Okay.
Ms. Qiu.
Hello, Ms. Qiu.
Mr. Chen, you mentioned before that
I should let you know
if I remembered anything
related to Madam Mei's case.
Today, we contacted Madam Mei,
and now I'm certain that
the reason we were all fired by Liangcheng Law Firm
is connected to the rape case from back then.
There's nothing else.
I just wanted to let you know.
That's all. Bye.
Why didn't you go in?
Look at Xia Shu;
she's daydreaming again.
This is the old lady who lent someone 3 million?
Plus another 2 million with no proof?
Qiu Hua, don't blame her.
You put too much pressure on Xia Shu.
It's my fault?
Well, let's not go in.
We have to go in.
Before Xia Shu's condition gets worse,
we have to stop her.
We can't let her cause any major trouble for us.
We've just opened,
so let's not set the bar too high
for consultation fees.
Ten yuan an hour should be fine.
Ten yuan?
Is that even enough to cover the water in front of her?
Xia Shu.
Luo. Qiu.
This is Auntie Song.
Auntie Song, this is Ms. Luo,
and this is Ms. Qiu.
-Hello.
-Nice to meet you.
Hello.
Sorry for the trouble.
I'll go get some drinks.
Xia Shu, we don't drink anything.
It's fine to sit for a while.
Auntie, I heard from Xia Shu that you want to file a lawsuit.
It's good that you have strong legal awareness.
But I need to talk to you a bit more
about the lawsuit.
For a typical civil dispute,
the litigation route is something you resort to
when there's no room left for negotiation,
a last resort.
In other words,
it means you and the other party are beyond reconciliation,
things have reached a point where it's impossible to make up.
Litigation relies on evidence.
Once it's in court,
reasoning and emotional appeals won't be very useful.
So in the end,
if you don't get the outcome you want,
not only
will it waste judicial resources,
but
it will also waste your own financial resources, energy,
and time.
I can tell you're a reasonable person, Auntie,
so...
But she owes me over 3 million.
Auntie Song has evidence.
I just looked at those IOUs
and the bank statements again;
they're all real.
They're all here.
[Transfer Voucher]
Auntie Song,
these two lawyers
are very capable.
They previously got a murder case
reopened for retrial.
Don't worry.
Xia Shu.
How about you order an Americano for me?
Qiu Hua, what would you like?
I just want lemon water.
Okay.
Hello.
Hello, what would you like?
You're Auntie Song, right?
Judging from these IOUs
and bank transfer records,
it seems
you lent over 3 million to someone named He Qiaohui.
Why did you lend her so much money?
It's a long story.
I'm afraid it might take up too much of your time.
No.
We've just opened,
so we're not charging for
legal consultations.
If you're over 60, it's free.
Go ahead.