[Unbreakable Ⅱ]
[Episode 17]
Mr. Xu, what's up?
Ms. Luo,
are you at Yinghua Law Firm?
Yeah, I'm working overtime.
I'm reviewing the debt claims of Dingxin and Wanhe.
Have you eaten?
How late are you planning to stay?
Well, I can't say for sure how late I'll be working.
I've prepared some food.
Do you need something?
How about a cup of coffee to refresh yourself?
Coffee?
Where would I even get coffee at this hour?
Who is it?
Delivery.
Is that Mr. Xu?
It‘s really you.
Your delivery is here.
You even brought coffee.
Please come in.
I asked my assistant
to prepare the latest materials
on Dingxin and Wanhe's debt claims
for you as a supplement.
-Thank you.
-I've never been here;
so I thought I'd drop by and take a look.
It's pretty shabby here.
We just moved in.
Look, there are still a bunch of cardboard boxes over there,
but it'll definitely get renovated later.
Is this what you prepared to eat?
I'll just grab a quick bite.
By the way, Mr. Xu, have you eaten?
I haven't either.
Let me cook you a bowl of noodles.
Thank you.
Which one is your office?
That one.
How many people are there in your firm?
Three.
Our case is huge;
aren't you planning to hire more people?
You know that
one person on our team
can handle the work of ten.
The circuit tripped.
This building is too old.
The wiring is outdated and keeps failing.
Mr. Xu, please wait a moment.
I'll go check the circuit breaker.
Let me go.
You go? Do you know where the breaker is?
I know.
The power is too high, so it's prone to short circuits.
How did you know where the circuit breaker is?
The first office of Zhuoyue Law Firm
was quite similar to yours,
actually not as nice as yours.
I didn't even call it Zhuoyue Law Firm,
I called it the Pavilion.
Pavilion? Why?
When Zhuoyue Law Firm was just established,
it was right after my second time out of detention.
Because I had been detained,
case sources were scarce.
Taking on pro bono cases doesn't make money
and it's easy to offend people.
Anyway,
we were dirt poor,
stretching a pack of instant noodles into two meals.
That winter,
we won a fraud case
for a group of deaf-mute people,
and as a result, the opposing side trashed our law firm.
They cut the electrical wires,
and in the dead of winter,
we were left in the dark,
with drafts coming in from all sides.
It was a miracle they didn't tear the roof off.
That's why I call it the Pavilion.
Compared to that,
at least we've got what you could call a "tent."
Mr. Xu,
you know how we always complain about
how tough our work is?
But hearing your story
really makes us seem overly dramatic.
What I mean is,
no matter how simple or fancy your law firm is,
whether it's packed or not,
it doesn't change your abilities
nor
how I see you all.
But I did want to replace you last time.
It was you who wanted to replace us?
We all thought it was the partners' decision.
It was my decision.
I believe in your abilities,
and Madam Mei believes too.
But your firm
can't vouch for Zhuoyue Law Firm,
and you don't have the qualifications of administrator.
You're also not very familiar with bankruptcy projects,
so you're not the best choice.
So, the reason you decided to choose us in the end
was because we managed to uncover
Wanhe's hidden assets?
Is this the only bowl?
What about yours?
I have bread
and the coffee you brought.
Do you know?
This is exactly what makes you valuable.
Without you,
I wouldn't have been able to secure the deal with Dingxin.
Mr. Xu, thank you for your honesty.
Actually, I've been looking into
bankruptcy reorganization cases recently.
Have you heard of a case
called the Zhucheng Case?
That case was handled by me.
At that time, Zhuoyue Law Firm
had no staff, no money, and no cases.
We even hired disabled people.
Luckily, Madam Mei helped us secure
a commercial case.
But Ms. Luo,
how did you know about this case?
Apart from the court and Liangcheng Law Firm,
the case files aren't accessible.
Actually, you don't know that
we were fired by Liangcheng Law Firm,
so I have a bit of a vendetta against it.
The reason I fought so hard for the Wanhe case
is also related to the Liangcheng Law Firm.
But here's a secret I'll share with you:
I have an insider at Liangcheng Law Firm.
So, it was incredibly satisfying for me
to sabotage their bid.
So Liangcheng Law Firm should be regretting it now.
It's their loss
to fire you.
Mr. Xu,
did Zhuoyue Law Firm's reputation
take off
after the Zhucheng case?
Not exactly.
Later, the Zhucheng Case was handed over to Tao Zheng and his team.
We did make some money.
At least we can afford the rent,
and finally stop using duct tape on the windows.
Well, if you put it that way,
the Zhucheng Case still holds reference value for us,
and you have experience too.
More than experience,
I believe in you
and Ms. Qiu.
Thank you.
You all are much stronger now
than I was back then.
I hope we can have a pleasant collaboration.
Absolutely, it will definitely be a pleasant collaboration.
Cheers.
You're back.
Go wash your hands and eat.
You eat. I'm not hungry.
What's wrong? Did you eat outside?
I just have no appetite.
Then keep me company and eat a little.
Why do you have no appetite?
I don't know, maybe
I've just been too tired lately.
I don't feel like eating.
No appetite recently?
Do you feel like
throwing up at all?
Occasionally, what's wrong?
Well,
does that mean I'm going to
be a dad?
What are you thinking about?
I'm still on my period
and having cramps.
Don't jump to conclusions.
Then you just have a poor appetite.
Have some yogurt
to whet your appetite.
I can't help but laugh at your absent-mindedness.
I just told you I'm on my period,
and you fetch me an ice-cold yogurt from the fridge.
I forgot; let me warm it up for you.
Just leave it there; I'll drink it when it's warmer.
Alright, I'll leave it here.
You can drink it when it's warm.
But you still need to eat something.
Take care of yourself.
After all, we're going to have a baby.
Quanquan,
I might not be ready to have a child yet.
You know that
my law firm has just been established,
and there's so much to do.
When we got married,
we didn't go back to our hometown for the wedding.
My mom and dad
still feel like they've lost face
in front of relatives and friends.
Now that Mom has retired,
she wants us to have a child sooner
so she has the energy
to devote herself to taking care of our baby.
This way, she won't feel so empty inside.
She'll have something to focus on;
isn't that good?
Quanquan,
I really can't
consider having a child right now.
You know, if I were to have a baby,
I wouldn't be able to do anything else for at least three years.
The focus of my life and our family
would have to shift entirely to the child.
I can't afford that kind of sacrifice at the moment.
Even if you weren't doing anything right now,
we'd still be fine, wouldn't we?
And Mom said that
women with too much career ambition
have a hard time.
Besides, my job is stable now,
and we can still rely on our families;
isn't that great?
But I can't rely on the family, on you,
on your dad, on your mom forever.
Why not?
We are a family.
You're my wife.
You're the daughter-in-law of my parents.
Quanquan,
our values don't align
on this issue.
Yes, I am the daughter-in-law of your parents,
but I am also an independent person.
I could never rely on others for my entire life.
I can only rely on myself.
I can't let you
or your family support me.
Let's discuss the issue of having a child in a few years.
I'm tired; I'm going to take a shower.
When you're done eating, just leave the plates and bowls
in the sink.
I'll wash them after resting a while.
By the way,
I also skimmed through the administrator's work records
of the Zhucheng Case that Chen Shuo brought over.
Didn't Madam Mei and her husband
handle it at the beginning?
Later, after something happened to them,
most of the partners, led by Lawyer Tao Zheng,
got involved.
There's no problem,
but the only thing that seems a bit odd
is why Fang Lihong didn't participate.
I noticed that too.
When something happened to Madam Mei and her husband,
Liangcheng Law Firm
must have been in complete chaos.
She was Madam Mei's disciple
and the only remaining founding partner at the firm.
She was busy handling Madam Mei's case,
so it makes sense that
she didn't participate.
What I find strange is that
Han didn't get involved.
Not strange at all.
Lift your feet.
Few people at Liangcheng Law Firm
think highly of Han,
so it's normal that he didn't get involved.
There's another thing
that I find quite strange as well.
Xu Zhuo is also in this team,
and the administrator fees of Zhucheng are over ten million.
Logically speaking,
since Madam Mei and her husband
are the founding partners of Liangcheng Law Firm,
such a lucrative job
should have been given to their own people.
How could they let such a lucrative opportunity go to an outsider?
Madam Mei always said that
she particularly recognized Mr. Xu.
Perhaps she just wanted to nurture the younger generation.
But I think
if someone were to frame Madam Mei and her husband
because of the huge interests
behind the Zhucheng Case,
that person should still be from within the Liangcheng Law Firm.
Who do you think
could have the heart to do such a thing?
I have no idea.
How about we go ask Madam Mei?
Okay.
Madam Mei,
you mean
back when you were handling the Zhucheng Case,
you also took on
the Wei Cheng rape case at the same time?
And later, you got into trouble because of the rape case,
so the Zhucheng Case was handed over to
Tao Zheng, right?
To be precise, after we ran into trouble,
the Liangcheng Law Firm
was assigned by the court to handle the Zhucheng Case.
Tao Zheng was the lead attorney,
but Fang Lihong, as the head of the firm,
was also involved in it.
How did you know about the Zhucheng Case?
Why do you care about this again?
I never said I wasn't going to investigate.
I just said I'd take a different approach.
Fine, I can't convince you.
After you called me today,
I tried really hard to recall the details,
but no matter how much I think about it,
I still don't see anything suspicious
about the Zhucheng Case.
Madam Mei,
could you tell us
about the situation back then?
Zhucheng was a large privately-owned casting enterprise
specializing in pipe production.
Due to poor management, it was on the verge of bankruptcy.
Yu and I were appointed by the court
as the bankruptcy administrators for Zhucheng.
We successfully drafted
a bankruptcy reorganization plan,
which was approved by the court.
However, the challenging part was that
our plan had to be passed
by the creditors' meeting.
I remember we held
three creditors' meetings for this case.
Before the third meeting,
Yu and I were forced to step down
due to the rape case allegations.
Later, the Liangcheng Law Firm took over
and still used our plan,
successfully achieving the bankruptcy reorganization.
That's the whole story.
The one who benefited will be the prime suspect.
In this case,
the biggest beneficiary was the Liangcheng Law Firm,
so they did have a motive
to frame you.
I've thought about it,
but then I felt like I might be overthinking it.
The Zhucheng Case was the biggest case
Liangcheng Law Firm took on at the time,
and there was no room for any mistakes.
When we got into trouble because of the rape case,
Liangcheng Law Firm had to take over.
Actually, the firm didn't treat us unfairly.
Fang Lihong insisted that
since we had done the groundwork,
we still received nearly 30%
of the administrator fees
in the end.
Maybe they did that
just to ease their own conscience.
Madam Mei, is it possible that
Liangcheng Law Firm, or someone from the firm,
framed you
to take the Zhucheng Case
away from you?
An ordinary lawyer
wouldn't be able to take the case
even if he brought us down—
unless he was a partner.
But all the partners at Liangcheng Law Firm
were former students of mine and Yu.
The students framed the teachers,
and went all out to ruin them...
What do you think?
I have another question.
Xu Zhuo was also part of the administrator team at the time,
right?
Yes.
But Xu Zhuo
wasn't a lawyer at the Liangcheng Law Firm back then.
There were over 100 lawyers in Liangcheng Law Firm.
Why didn't you use someone from your own firm
and instead bring in Xu Zhuo?
He was detained twice.
You know that, right?
Yes.
And it seems like he had a really tough time
when he was starting out—
much worse than the situation Qiu Hua and I are in now.
When we were handling this case,
he had just been released from detention for the second time.
Then he established Zhuoyue Law Firm.
Because of his criminal record,
it was hard for him to get cases.
We admired him,
and wanted to give him a hand,
so we brought him onto the administrator team.
When dealing with this case,
Xu Zhuo actually contributed a lot.
That means
the Zhucheng Case was what established Zhuoyue Law Firm,
and Xu Zhuo's first big break
came from this case, right?
You could say that,
but he didn't gain much
from this case.
After we ran into trouble,
the others at Liangcheng Law Firm weren't particularly close to him,
so when it came to the final distribution,
he didn't get a larger share.
Fang Lihong, Tao Zheng,
Fan Yiqing, Zhang Zhi.
Why didn't Han
get involved in the Zhucheng Case back then?
If he had been involved,
he'd be my first suspect.
"If I can't have it,
neither can you"—
that totally fits Han's personality.
Maybe he did it.
No, it doesn't fit him.
"If I went through all that strenghth to ruin you
and take the benefits,
I'd definitely
want a piece of the pie."—
that's more like Han.
Yes.
You've worked with him longer,
so you know him better.
But why did you keep bringing up Xu Zhuo
back at Madam Mei's place?
What do you mean?
Nothing.
I was just checking the facts.
Okay.
Don't tell Xu Zhuo
about the Zhucheng Case for now.
Why not?
He was involved back then.
We've just joined his team.
I know he appreciates you,
but trust hasn't been fully established yet.
What if he knows something about
what happened back then?
Who knows which side he was really on?
He must've been on Madam Mei's side.
Back then, Madam Mei and her husband
didn't even use their own people
but they chose him, an outsider.
He was the biggest beneficiary.
He had to be on Madam Mei's side.
Not necessarily.
It's been so many years,
and Xu Zhuo hasn't developed a closer relationship
with Madam Mei.
Besides, when Madam Mei
wanted to uncover the truth this time,
she didn't reach out to Xu Zhuo.
There must be some reason
that we don't know about.
If we bring it up
before we fully understand the situation,
wouldn't Xu Zhuo think
we're investigating him?
I don't think Xu Zhuo would take it that way.
I still think it's better to be cautious.
A little impatience can ruin a big plan.
Let's wait until we've made progress on the case before saying anything.
You can drop me off up ahead.
What are you going to do?
Quanquan's sinusitis is acting up again.
I've been telling him to go to the hospital, but he won't listen.
I'm going to the pharmacy to get him some medicine.
Doesn't he have his own phone?
Why do you have to go buy it for him?
Can't he just order it online?
There's a difference between what I buy and what he buys.
Ugh, you're so cloying.
Okay, I'll find a place to stop for you.
Stop talking.
Thank you.
Bye bye.
Take care.
Okay.
[Unscrupulous Chen]
Righteous Luo.
Unscrupulous Chen.
Yes, what's up?
Let's meet at the usual spot.
You want to meet me?
If you're willing to admit
it's a date, then I'll go.
Cut the nonsense. Are you coming or not?
Yes.
I'll be there in 20 minutes.
Okay, bye bye.
Fang Rui, I'm going out.
Are you going on a date with Ms. Luo?
None of your business.
Mentor,
honestly, I think you and Ms. Luo are a great match.
She said she's a famous lady,
and I'm a notorious hooligan.
How does that match?
That's exactly why it's a match.
You're right.
Black and white, good and bad, ladies and hooligans—
that's how the world balances out.
Stop focusing on me all the time.
Learn from Yuguo.
Look at him—he went after what he likes.
You've changed your style.
You're dressed up nicely.
Well, I'm the boss now.
A famous lady keeps dating a famous hooligan?
What do you mean?
Do you like me?
Cut the crap.
Let me ask you,
you specifically brought up the Zhucheng Case.
How did you get involved in this?
I heard you're looking into Madam Mei's case.
If someone framed Mei Daliang,
that person must still be at Liangcheng Law Firm.
And the root of it
definitely has nothing to do with the rape case.
Based on my analysis, it's all about the Zhucheng Case.
Chen Shuo, let me remind you kindly.
The three of us lost our jobs
because of this.
Aren't you afraid of getting dragged into it?
If the three of you can start your own businesses,
do you really think I can't?
Can the three of us be like you?
Don't you even know
how you made all that money?
You're always pushing the boundaries of the law.
The Zhucheng Case is complicated.
Aren't you afraid someone might catch you slipping
and take you down
like they did to Madam Mei back then?
Don't worry.
I'm meticulous.
To investigate this case,
I've reviewed all the cases
handled by the partners from two years
before and after the rape case.
They probably have no idea what I'm looking into.
You reviewed all the cases from two whole years?
And why
are you being this meticulous?
For you.
I'm doing this for you.
Stop talking nonsense.
Let me tell you,
I came here specifically today just to tell you—
stay out of this.
Mind your own business.
Okay. Stop dawdling. Got it.
I heard you officially started working at the Zhuoyue Law Firm?
We've officially joined Xu Zhuo's team now.
We're handling
the biggest creditor of Wanhe—Dingxin—alongside him.
The moment we stepped in,
we crushed Liangcheng Law Firm's dream of
becoming the bankruptcy administrator.
We...
Who exactly do you mean by "we"?
Our firm and Mr. Xu's team.
Come on, what's so great about Xu Zhuo?
He just loves showing off;
he's always on TV,
or making videos to post online,
like he's afraid people won't know who he is.
Our firm is newly established,
and working with a team like Mr. Xu's
is a great learning opportunity.
Plus,
this case is going to
make us a pretty nice chunk of money.
How does him being on TV and making videos bother you?
Why don't you talk about
how he's been helping disadvantaged groups consistently for over a decade?
Just that alone
puts him miles ahead of a lot of people.
By "a lot of people," you mean me, don't you?
I never said that.
Wait, Luo Yingzi,
do you know Xu Zhuo?
You just mentioned pushing the boundaries of the law—
well, let me tell you,
Xu Zhuo
is an expert at that.
You probably don't know this,
but back in the day,
he hired disabled individuals
to issue fake invoices for tax evasion.
He registered several companies,
with all the legal person and financial officers
being disabled people.
But the salaries he paid them
and the social security contributions he made didn't match up at all.
In the end, those disabled employees
sued him for unpaid wages.
You told me you could learn from him;
so what exactly have you learned?
Who's exactly the one pushing the boundaries of the law?
It takes a long process
to build a sound legal system.
Back then, the laws
had plenty of gray areas.
Besides,
do you have any idea how hard it was
to start Zhuoyue Law Firm in those early days?
Do you know?
I don't. As long as you do, that's all that matters.
You've only known him for a few days.
What do you even know about him?
Go on, enlighten me.
Of course I know.
Our firm just established,
and we've already run into all sorts of challenges.
Getting the chance to work with Xu Zhuo
is already a huge stroke of luck.
Without him, we'd probably still be struggling to make ends meet.
Okay.
Luo Yingzi, I've noticed that
ever since you started contacting with Xu Zhuo,
everything about you
has changed—
your way of speaking,
your whole vibe—
honestly, it's not like
the Luo Yingzi I used to know.
You asked me to come today.
Since we've cleared everything up
between us,
I'm telling you now, I'm leaving.
What's going on?
Are you okay?
I'm trying to talk to you nicely here,
and you're acting all sarcastic.
Mr. Liu, happy cooperation.
Happy cooperation.
As for the remaining 30%,
it'll be paid in full once the payment for the goods comes through on your end.
You and I...
If you break the contract,
it's all laid out clearly in the agreement.
See, everything was going great,
but then you had to go and say something that just killed the mood.
No problem.
Alright, it's settled. I'll treat.
Let's go have a drink.
Don't, brother. You're not local.
Since this is my turf,
let me treat, okay?
-Let me treat.
-Don't try to steal my turn to treat.
Let's go.
Shall we go?
Yes.
Good thing you called me out,
tutoring kids every day is exhausting.
Eat up, or the food will get overcooked.
Xue,
am I really worse than Xu Zhuo?
He did a bit of charity work,
and it left Luo Yingzi completely smitten.
It's too strange.
You're way worse.
He's gentle, caring, understands women;
how else could he have gotten married three times?
Who wouldn't fall for that?
Who's falling for that?
What's there to be falling for that?
He has been divorced three times.
Statistically speaking,
tell me, what kind of good man is he?
Three divorces isn't that bad,
I've got a buddy who's been divorced five times.
Do you want to compete with this?
Luo Yingzi was divorced too.
Are you done?
I'm treating you to a meal, and you're just here to pick on me.
You're treating me to food,
and you're only ordering a couple of cheap dishes?
How can I not pick on you?
You can order whatever you want,
just say something I wanna hear.
I'm not ordering anymore.
Did Luo Yingzi tell you
she likes Xu Zhuo?
No.
Then what are you complaining about?
She didn't say she likes me.
She just treats me as her friend.
I'm a man,
why would I go out of my way
just to be this girl's buddy?
Why are you so stubborn?
Going from buddies to lovers
and finally ending up together
is a long process.
Your sister-in-law and I were like this.
You've gotta let the girls
drop their guard completely
before you can make a move.
I just feel like Luo Yingzi...
Anyway, whenever she teams up with Xu Zhuo
and praises him, it just doesn't sit right with me,
and makes me uncomfortable.
She can admire anyone;
why she admires someone so fake and put on a front?
Don't worry.
Someone will definitely help you teach Luo Yingzi a lesson.
Who?
The one who puts on a front.
You don't get it, do you?
Xu Zhuo is not a good man.
Acting all high and mighty every day.
The stuff he's done
might not get him a sentence,
but it's still illegal, right?
He's a lawyer.
A lawyer
who's always working on the edge of the law to make money
and then showing off how miserable he is.
Wait.
Let me tell you,
in today's society,
the ones who are elevated to high status
are often the ones who end up falling the hardest.
Just wait and see.
Well said.
Something will happen to him sooner or later,
-right?
-Well said.
But
it's not really a bad thing.
Luo Yingzi is too idealistic.
Someone like Xu Zhuo really
needs to step in and teach her a lesson.
She needs to be taught a lesson.
She deserves it.
A good sword remains always sharp.
I believe you. Come on.
Just say what you need to say, but no swearing.
Hello.
What?
Okay.
Okay, I'll get it.
I'm leaving.
Are you leaving?
Let me tell you,
the trial notice for the Mingshan case
I'm handling is about to be sent out.
When I walk out of here today,
I'm still poor.
But when I come back,
I'll be rich.
One case makes me financially free right away.
Awesome.
Chen Shuo,
you should think the thing I just said over carefully.
The ones who are elevated to high status are often the ones who end up falling the hardest.
Be careful.
Okay.
Get a designated driver.
You drunk.
Okay, you'll pay the bill.
Look at how impressive Ms. Xia is.
She's got such a commanding presence.
I haven't seen a woman
like her
for so many years.
She's impressive, right?
A heroine.
She's bold. I'll toast to you.
I must drink liquor.
Applause!
She's impressive.
Applause.
A heroine.
Brothers,
you all can back me up on this.
Mr. Liu has already paid Mr.  Hao
4.2 million yuan.
The agency fee should be 840,000 yuan.
And don't forget the travel expenses—
it wasn't easy for me to gett here.
Totally, it's 1,300...
Fine.
Why the rush? Let's go back and calculate.
Look. Okay.
You're not too drunk, are you?
Yes.
Awesome, right?
My sister's law firm has these three elites.
They're all amazing.
Good looks and sharp skills.
You're in for a challenge going forward.
Mr. Hao,
you didn't pay Ms. Xia enough.
Ms. Xia, how about this?
Come work for me,
and you can name your price.
You're poaching her right here?
Mr. Liu,
now that you've said that,
I have to toast you.
Bottoms up.
You're good at drinking.
The atmosphere is in place.
The atmosphere is in place. Sit down.
Mr. Liu, you really have an eye for talent.
Indeed.
But I'm indeed a talent.
Of course.
Once I'm done with Mr. Hao's business
and make the money I need to,
I'll come represent you.
I'll wait for you on behalf of our company.
Deal!
She has got another business opportunity.
Brother, let's drink.
Come on. Let's drink.
Let's drink.
Come on.
You know why...
I didn't expect that...
Today...
Mr. Hao.
I'll toast you after I finish this.
I've paid you. Where are you going?
Brother, let's drink this first.
Come on.
Okay.
Luo, don't worry.
I'm heading back to Jingbei tomorrow.
I've got all the money back.
I'm drinking with them.
Don't drink too much. Mix it with some water if you need to.
I've told you before, keep your guard up when you're out there.
Don't force yourself with those men.
I know.
Luo, let me ask you,
are you convinced
when I get the money back this time?
Yes, I am.
Not just me, even Qiu's convinced.
Really?
Don't lie to me.
Don't treat me like a child.
Wait, why would I lie to you?
This is collecting the debt.
We're already in awe of you;
just waiting for you to come back so we can celebrate.
You're in for a big surprise.
I'll wait for your surprise.
Alright.
I'm hanging up, Luo.
I'm going in.
Bye bye.
Ms. Xia, you're so impressive;
why are you crying?
Mr. Hao.
You promised inside that
you'd reimburse my travel expenses.
Let me go over the details for you.
The most expensive one is the car rental fee,
then the accommodation and train tickets.
When I was eating ramen on the side of the road,
I even asked the vendor for a receipt.
I've taken pictures of everything.
Let me show you.
Wait, you don't need to be so serious.
Why not?
Let me make it clear.
The money doesn't include
the costs for Mr. Zhou bringing people to protect me.
The law firm will need to pay
that favor back.
Mr. Hao,
when will you transfer the money to me?
You're impressive.
You've got everything clear and straight.
Of course.
Ms. Xia,
I heard from Zhang Lan that
you were abroad before.
When did you come back?
It's been three years.
I heard
something happened to your dad.
Yes.
I really admire you.
It's true.
You're such a young girl,
pretty,
and looking all fragile,
yet you dared to crawl under someone's car
and take down
those rough guys in no time.
It's all for you, Mr. Hao.
It's all for getting salary from you.
The total is 843,250 yuan.
840,000 yuan is the fee,
♫Clouds♫
and 3,250 yuan is for travel expenses,
mostly the car rental, right?
♫Why are your eyes squinting?♫
Good memory, Mr. Hao.
I've worked so hard to help you collect this debt;
you better treat me right.
♫Awaiting a breeze♫
Of course.
Out of all the lawyers I've met,
I think you are the best.
♫To wake her up♫
I admire you the most.
And I understand you.
I feel like we're pretty alike.
♫The sun on my shoulders♫
♫And the weight of the rain♫
When I was abroad,
♫She never mentioned it♫
I was just drifting through each day.
When my dad died,
I felt like
I was kicked down from the sky straight into the mud.
♫Clouds♫
And now, I have no choice but to come back and clean up
♫Floating aimlessly, leaving no trace♫
the mess he left behind.
♫Between the sunshine and rain♫
We're nothing alike.
The "mess" you're talking about
♫She comes and goes without a word♫
is a billion-yuan business.
If you recover this debt,
♫The tranquility I’ve grown used to♫
it's a business,
a livelihood,
♫Is the invisible cloud♫
and many people's livelihoods—
enough to support many people.
♫Giving me shade♫
What about you?
What did you take over?
♫That piece of pure, soft cloud♫
What I took over is a mess.
♫Supporting the wind and rain♫
♫The tales of sun and rain♫
♫Going back and forth in the darkness♫
But I've accepted it.
♫Silently weaving through♫
Something happened to my dad.
♫A glimmer of light can make it break through♫
I can't count on my mom.
♫That piece of reassuring, heavy cloud♫
But it's okay. I'm fine.
If I can go through the wheel for the first time,
♫Will accept it♫
I can do it twice.
♫The bitterness and mistakes of the world♫
I'm happy
that I can earn money on my own.
♫She understands all my clumsiness and persistence♫
♫In our sky♫
♫She will always wait for me♫
Thank you.
Your company is here?
Which floor?
Top floor.
Here, Boss.
Thank you.
Let me help you bring your luggage upstairs.
It's okay. Give it to me.
Just drop it off here, I'm leaving.
Ms. Xia,
thank you.
Thank you for your hard work these days.
It's okay.
Remember to transfer the money to me.
Luo, I just got back to the office.
You're both not here?
You're both at work?
You're back already?
I came to Mr. Zhou's place;
I have something to take care of.
Alright, you go home first.
I've left some food in the fridge for you.
What about Qiu?
Are we still having dinner together tonight?
Luo, you promised yesterday that
you'd throw me a celebration dinner.
How about I book a restaurant first?
Qiu Hua went to meet with the representative.
How about this: once we're done with work in a couple of days,
we'll celebrate for you.
Okay.
Luo,
let me report my work to you again.
The case with Hao Lei that our firm took on
can earn us over 800,000 yuan, 840,000 yuan to be exact.
I knew you could do it.
Has the money been received?
It doesn't count before it's paid.
I haven't received the money yet,
but we've made the contract.
I'll follow up in a couple of days.
Okay, follow up on payment.
I can't talk to you right now.
Mr. Zhou will be here soon. Bye bye.
Okay. Go back to work.
Sister.
Mr. Zhou.
What's the matter again?
I'm here
not to trouble you today;
I'm here to thank you.
If you pull something like this again, I'm gonna be upset.
You've done me such a huge favor, and I can't just let it go.
If I don't repay you,
I won't even know how to face you next time.
I'm here today
to offer you a hand.
Let's sit down and talk.
Sit down.
Mr. Zhou,
your business
has stayed safe
because you know
where the legal lines are, right?
But the legal system
is constantly evolving and improving.
Being safe today
and yesterday
doesn't mean
you'll stay safe forever.
I know there are a lot of things
you don't want others to find out about.
I don't want to know either.
Yes.
After all, I used to
want to keep my distance from you
to some extent.
No.
But now, you've done me
two huge favors.
If I were to distance myself from you now,
that would be my fault.
Since we're being straight with each other,
whatever you say, I'm listening.
That's why I'm here today.
I'm currently handling a case
for an economic chain store.
This chain
has around 40-50 stores
in Jingbei and several major cities,
and its assets are really solid.
But due to its rapid expansion,
the cash flow broke down.
To pay off the debts,
they're forced to sell at a low price.
Mr. Zhou, have you ever thought about changing industries?
If you are considering it,
I think this could be a really good opportunity.