[Unbreakable Ⅱ]
[Episode 33]
Go ahead, I'm listening.
What's wrong with Wei?
I'm asking you.
Tell me, what's wrong with Wei?
She
doesn't understand anything.
I have to teach her everything from scratch.
I don't get what's up with
college grads these days.
I mean, she couldn't even write a simple speech.
You know, today,
she wrote a speech for our division chief.
It was sent back with a scolding.
She was crying her eyes out.
So I had no choice but to fix it for her,
tweaking every little detail.
I had to explain everything to her step by step—
that's why I'm still stuck here.
Oh, Wei is a woman?
Since when
did you become such a mentor?
Well, that makes sense.
Back at our workplace,
I used to call everyone teacher.
Now it's different.
I've become a teacher too.
That's nice.
Here, you can have this piece.
I'm going to take a shower.
I have some here.
I'm too tired.
Dear creditors,
there are three colored ballots: green, red, and yellow,
in front of you.
If you agree with the reorganization plan,
please cast a green ballot.
If you oppose it, please cast a red ballot.
If you choose to abstain, please cast a yellow ballot.
[Voting box]
It definitely got approved this time.
Ladies and gentlemen,
after rigorous selection and negotiations,
the review panel, composed of the administrator,
creditors' committee, and relevant department representatives,
finalized
Qiwu Group as the winning bidder.
and it will become the largest shareholder of Wanhe Group.
All creditors
will be compensated
according to the debt repayment plan outlined in the reorganization proposal.
Now, let's welcome
President Li of Qiwu Group to the stage!
Mr. Liu,
small creditors like us
have no choice but to accept our losses
and take whatever we can get.
Are you really just giving in like this?
With a 32.3% recovery rate,
how much can you actually get back?
I invested a total of one billion,
yet I'm only getting a little over three hundred million back.
Wanhe alone has dragged me down.
Then why didn't you bid?
[The Second Creditors' Meeting of the Bankruptcy Reorganization Case of Wanhe Group]
Wanhe is only worth 1.8 billion now.
It's a great investment opportunity.
I have the will but not the means.
Colleagues of Wanhe Group,
dear creditors,
the management team,
and the audit team,
it is an honor for me
to speak on behalf of Qiwu Group today
and share this moment with you all.
Mr. Xu, are you heading back to the firm?
The story is over;
I'm going back.
Negotiate with Dingxin
and have them pay the remaining agency fees.
How much is still outstanding?
Thirty percent—over three million.
We made over 10 million from this case.
Liangcheng Law Firm made more than 50 million.
Well, they put their entire firm's resources into it,
while it
relied almost entirely on you.
I'm not Fang Lihong—
no way I'm exhausting myself
over a single case.
Mr. Xu, as expected of you.
This game is over.
Next, we need to focus all our efforts
on the criminal prosecution.
We must make sure that Chen Shuo
ends up in prison.
[Xia Shu]
Why is she calling me?
Who?
Xia Shu from Yinghua Law Firm.
Xia Shu?
She really admires you.
There are plenty of people like that.
Ms. Xia.
Hello, Mr. Xu.
I wasn't sure if I should call you,
or if you'd even answer.
Ms. Xia,
although our collaboration has ended,
I still cherish
the days we worked together.
Really, Mr. Xu?
I also often miss
working by your side.
Mr. Xu,
can I see you in person?
There's something I think you should know.
What is it?
I'd still like to tell you in person.
How about this? I'm heading back to the office anyway.
Why don't you come meet me at my office?
Thank you, Mr. Xu.
See you later. Goodbye.
See you later.
This naive and innocent girl.
I wonder what she wants from me.
I have no idea.
Actually, I quite like her.
Being with her feels effortless,
and I don't have to put up any defenses.
I like her too.
She's clear and straightforward, nothing hidden.
Let's see what she wants.
[Jingbei Zhuoyue Law Firm]
Come in.
Mr. Xu.
Ms. Xia.
You're writing calligraphy?
Your handwriting is excellent.
So you're also interested in calligraphy?
Mr. Xu,
can you give me a piece of your calligraphy?
If you like it,
I'll give you this one once I'm done.
Okay.
Do your two other partners know
you came to see me?
They don't know.
I came privately.
Well then, what's on your mind?
I mentioned to you before that
I have a university classmate
who works at a large foreign consulting firm.
But at the time, you didn't seem to take it seriously.
Nevertheless, I still asked my classmate
to investigate the assets
of Mr. Wan's daughter for me.
Mr. Xu,
I see you have many philosophy books.
So how's the investigation going now?
She said that
Mr. Wan has hidden a large amount of assets
overseas.
Some time ago, his daughter
purchased a shipload of precious metals,
which was being transported to China.
But now that Wanhe is suddenly going bankrupt,
the shipment has been halted
and is currently drifting in international waters.
Your study is really nice.
Precious metals?
What kind of precious metals?
I'm not sure about the specifics,
but it's not gold.
My classmate said
it's worth much more than gold.
It's used for high-end military-industrial products—
an entire shipload worth
300 million.
300 million?
And that's in US dollars.
My classmate said that
now that Wanhe's bankruptcy reorganization has been settled,
the ship should be docking soon.
The only question is whether it'll be brought back to China
or sent elsewhere.
Mr. Xu,
does this information
mean anything to you?
Mr. Xu?
Xia Shu, please have a seat.
Xia Shu,
are you sure all this information
is accurate?
Of course, it is.
Mr. Xu, I wouldn't lie to you.
Have some water.
Thank you.
This information is very helpful to me.
I have an appointment with a client downstairs.
I'll be right back. Please wait for me.
Mr. Xu, then I'll take my leave now.
I came here just to tell you...
Xia Shu, listen to me. Please sit down first.
Xia Shu,
actually,
I've always wanted to have a good talk with you.
I think you're very talented
and have great potential.
Previously, Luo Yingzi made the decision on your behalf
to decline my invitation,
but I still really hope
you can join our team
and work with me.
Really, Mr. Xu?
When Luo rejected your offer,
I was quite disappointed.
Of course it's true.
How about this?
Wait for me to come back,
I'll finish writing that piece and give it to you,
then we can have a proper discussion
about the possibility of working together.
Okay.
Then wait for me.
[The Second Creditors' Meeting of the Bankruptcy Reorganization Case of Wanhe Group]
Next, let's give a warm round of applause as we invite
the employee representative, the creditor representative,
Mr. Wan from Wanhe Group,
government representative Director Xu,
and the administrator team representatives,
Ms. Fang and Mr. Tao to take the stage.
[Xu Zhuo]
Zhang.
Mr. Xu.
Xia Shu is upstairs in my office.
Go up and stay with her.
No matter what method you use,
don't let her leave my office.
Don't let her make any phone calls.
What's wrong?
Don't ask.
Remember, before I come back,
don't let her leave
or contact the outside world.
Xia Shu?
When did you arrive?
I just got here.
How long is Mr. Xu going to be with the client?
If it's going to take a while,
I'll go make a call to the office.
Wait a moment.
Are you in a hurry?
No.
Then why are you making a call?
Besides, it's been so long since we last met.
Mr. Xu is just handling a contract—
he'll be back soon.
I've got a bunch of gossip to tell you.
Might as well order some milk tea.
It's buy one, get one half off today.
What would you like to drink?
Taro boba milk tea.
Aren't you afraid of gaining weight?
With 30% sugar.
Alright.
I hereby declare
the signing ceremony officially begins.
[Fang Lihong]
[Xu Zhuo]
You're already at the brink of disaster,
yet you still won't answer the phone.
[Luo Yingzi]
[Xu Zhuo]
It seems Xia Shu's message got through.
Are you answering or not?
No.
The signing ceremony probably hasn't ended yet, right?
Whether he can stop it or not is up to him now.
He's calling again. He's so persistent.
You still don't get him?
He's arrogant,
and extremely goal-oriented.
Hello.
Has the signing ceremony ended?
The meeting is over. They've gone to the second floor.
Thank you very much.
The main credit goes to Ms. Fang and Mr. Tao.
No, no, it's what we should do.
It's what we should do.
Here, let's celebrate.
Congratulations.
Thank you, Director Xu.
Where did you go?
Why didn't you answer your phone?
I was just on stage signing the contract.
I didn't have my phone with me.
Here, let me introduce you.
Let me make an introduction.
This is our behind-the-scenes hero—
Lawyer Xu Zhuo.
Thanks to Mr. Xu,
he convinced Dingxin Group
to change their vote in favor of our proposal
at the most critical moment.
So, our proposal
was able to pass successfully.
Once again, a big thank you to Xu Zhuo.
Thank you very much.
Congratulations.
Let's have a drink.
Mr. Xu.
Thank you.
Congratulations.
[Jingbei Zhuoyue Law Firm]
Look at that photo in the middle—
that's Mr. Xu's first wife.
What a perfect match of talent and beauty.
On the left is his second wife,
and on the right is his third.
Each of the three is more beautiful,
more capable,
and even younger than the last.
But it also indirectly shows that
Mr. Xu is truly exceptional—
otherwise, how could all three of them
be so devoted to him?
Indeed.
Mr. Xu has said that
he will absolutely never forget
any woman
who has appeared in his life.
Why hasn't Mr. Xu come back yet?
Maybe I should leave first.
-So soon?
-Ms. Xia.
Mr. Xu.
What are you talking about?
I was just chatting with Ms. Xia.
Alright, you can go ahead with your work.
I'll be going now.
Ms. Xia, please have a seat.
Mr. Xu, I was just chatting with Ms. Zhang
about you and your wives' love stories.
Ms. Xia,
about what you mentioned earlier—
a ship full of precious metals
worth 300 million dollars…
Could it be a rumor
or fake news?
Your classmate wouldn't lie to you, would they?
Why would my classmate lie to me?
Mr. Xu,
my classmate works for a large consulting firm
called Gallud in the U.S.
You must have heard of it, right?
That's their specialty.
During the U.S. financial crisis,
they helped several major short sellers
make a fortune.
Besides,
Besides, our firm signed a contract with their company.
Who signed a contract with whom?
Our firm and their company.
Foreigners are meticulous in their work.
The due diligence report they sent over alone was dozens of pages long.
It took me several days to translate it all.
When did you receive the report?
Let me think...
It was the night
after Luo signed the termination agreement
with you.
Was it before or after
the termination agreement was signed?
It was after.
Look,
the email has a timestamp.
It clearly shows it was after the termination agreement was signed.
Mr. Xu, what should I do now?
Xia Shu,
you're also a lawyer.
You understand the weight of this matter.
If this leaks,
it would be bad for us,
for me,
and for your firm as well, right?
I know.
That's why I rushed to tell you.
However, Mr. Xu,
we've already terminated the agreement with you.
This matter no longer concerns us.
But it's indeed unfavorable for you.
You're the representative of Dingxin, right?
How does this relate to me?
I just heard about it from you.
I reminded you before,
but you didn't take it seriously.
Xia Shu,
don't say things carelessly.
I'm not. I recorded it.
Mr. Xu,
I heard that Mr. Wan's daughter
graduated from UC Berkeley.
I have a classmate who also graduated from there.
Do you need me to ask her
to look into her?
Investigate his daughter?
That's not necessary.
If we look into it,
we can get a better grasp of Wanhe's assets.
But it will cost a bit.
How much?
Not too much.
It won't bankrupt Zhuoyue Law Firm.
It's not needed for now.
Why were you recording this?
I have a bad memory. I always forget things,
so I record every meeting.
Mr. Xu, I've already told you
about this.
Think it over carefully.
I really have to go now.
My boyfriend is waiting for me downstairs.
Goodbye, Mr. Xu.
Mr. Xu, Xia Shu is leaving?
You told me she is a naive and silly girl?
That's right.
Look at her—
isn't she just naive and silly?
You're the naive and silly one!
Mr. Xu, I...
Get out.
Ms. Zhang
gave me a detailed rundown
of how outstanding each of his three ex-wives was.
Why does he
keep their photos on his desk?
To remind himself he's been divorced three times?
No.
To remind himself he's split his assets three times.
When I hit 40,
I'm going to plaster
a whole wall with pictures of my ex-boyfriends—
just to remind myself
how popular I used to be.
Come on, Xia Shu.
Let me record
that last part you just said.
I'll send it to Mr. Hao.
That would be his honor.
Luo,
what do we do about our report?
It's like an atomic bomb.
You know its weight too, right?
Of course.
Why else would we spend so much money on it?
If this gets out,
it won't just throw Zhuoyue Law Firm into chaos,
but it'll drag Liangcheng Law Firm down with it.
Luo,
you're not still attached to Liangcheng Law Firm, are you?
What about you?
They did treat me well back then,
but that was because of my dad.
After he got into trouble,
they cut ties without hesitation.
Comrades,
the court has issued a hearing notice.
Chen Shuo's case is going to trial.
Alright, I'll call Chen Shuo
and Mr. Xue
to have them come over.
Okay, I've already bought the food.
We don't need to worry too much
about the joint account issue, right?
With your abilities,
it should be easy to win.
Indeed,
but it might leave a bad impression on the judge.
It's human nature.
if he can't even understand that,
how should I put it...
Moral perfectionism?
Exactly.
But what worries me is Xu Zhuo.
He's become so unscrupulous lately
that he's capable of anything.
So I think
we still need to be fully prepared.
If I were Xu Zhuo,
there's no way I'd admit in court
that Mingshan just wants to evade payment.
That's right.
They'll argue that the agency fees should be paid by Party A,
according to the agreement,
so the money
should first go into Party A's account
before being allocated.
They'll make a big deal out of this point.
So if we want to win,
we have to prove that
Party A intended to cheat the lawyers from the very beginning.
But right now, we lack concrete evidence for that.
[Xu Zhuo]
Why is he calling me now?
Hello, Mr. Xu.
Yingzi.
Are you available?
I'd like to talk to you.
Is there really anything left for us to discuss?
I'm right downstairs from your office.
I want to talk about Chen Shuo's case.
Downstairs?
What should I do?
Go ahead.
See what he's up to.
Okay, I'm coming down.
I'll go put on a coat.
He just won't go away.
He's so annoying.
Thank you.
I know
you don't want to see me.
Just get to the point.
I'm busy.
A lot has happened
lately,
and there have been some misunderstandings between us.
I wanted to clear things up in person.
There's nothing to clear up.
You came to talk about the case, didn't you?
Mingshan is determined to sue Chen Shuo.
As their legal representative,
I have to act according to my client's wishes.
I hope you can understand that.
We're going to court tomorrow.
Don't you think it's a little ridiculous
to bring this up now?
I don't want to be your enemy.
I can talk to
Mingshan Group
and persuade them to withdraw the lawsuit tomorrow morning.
But in return, I hope you won't make things difficult
for me in other matters.
Can you do that?
Are you talking about Wanhe?
I never expected
you to go behind your current client's back
and secretly negotiate with the opposing counsel
over another case.
Does Mingshan Group
know you're doing this?
Yingzi,
you know once those things are exposed,
many people will be implicated.
How about this?
You name your terms.
Whether it's withdrawing the lawsuit
or asking for agency fees,
as long as it's within my power,
you can ask for anything.
I know
you're a kind person.
Yes, I am a kind person,
But I'm also someone with principles,
so not everything
can be negotiated.
Mr. Xu,
I find it pathetic on your behalf.
You have absolutely no bottom line.
As for today,
I'll pretend you were never here.
Yingzi.
Hello?
Mr. Han.
This way, please.
Mr. Han, Lawyer Xu Zhuo is here.
Mr. Han.
You can go ahead.
Okay.
Mr. Han.
Mr. Xu,
I can't believe you actually came to see me.
Here, please have a seat.
Mr. Han,
I'll get straight to the point.
My lawsuit against Chen Shuo
on behalf of Mingshan Group
is solely about his personal actions
and is by no means intended as an offense to you.
You can rest assured about that.
I'm not worried.
You don't need to
offend me.
Mr. Han,
the current situation
is not what my client, Mr. Sun,
wants to see.
He never intended to
withhold your agency fees.
This was entirely Chen Shuo stirring up trouble,
which ended up implicating you.
Here,
on behalf of Mr. Sun, I want to make it clear that
the portion of the agency fees that rightfully belongs to you
will be transferred to your account as soon as possible.
That's great!
Thank you so much.
Well...
But...
there's no such thing as a free lunch, is there?
Things can't be this easy.
What's the catch?
Mr. Han, you truly are a veteran.
I've already submitted a request to the court
for a witness to testify;
I'd like you to appear as a witness.
No, well...
Asking me to testify isn't...
The agency agreement
was signed by both of you.
The contract only states that
you're authorized to collect the enforcement funds,
but it does not grant you the right to distribute them.
Tomorrow in court,
all you need to do is truthfully tell
the judge what happened.
Mr. Han,
you're a law-abiding and ethical lawyer;
otherwise, you wouldn't have returned the money,
right?
Alright, I won't bother you any longer.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Goodbye.
Let... Let me see you out.
No need.
Why are you looking at me?
Why are you so quiet today?
Normally, you're like a magpie,
chattering nonstop.
Maybe I'm just tired from all the meetings.
You're worried about Chen Shuo, aren't you?
We've already analyzed
his case thoroughly.
There's some risk,
but we have expert endorsement.
and the evidence is solid.
Xu Zhuo is unlikely to win.
I'm just afraid Xu Zhuo
might get desperate and pull some dirty tricks.
You know
he's out to ruin Chen Shuo.
You used to tell me to be more optimistic.
How come you're the pessimistic one now?
Don't worry, trust me.
It'll be fine, Yingzi.
I hope so.
What's going on with Quanquan?
I haven't seen him pick you up lately.
He's been busy with work recently.
That's not an excuse.
Next time I see him,
I'll have a word with him.
Why do you want to talk to him?
This is fine.
We're both busy with our own things.
It also lessens my guilt a bit.
I really admire you two.
This isn't a marriage;
it's just a partnership.
We're really doing fine.
Don't worry about us.
You'd better focus on tomorrow's case.
If we end up with a
strict judge,
there's still some risk.
Who is it? Can you check for me?
[Han Zhitong]
Han?
Why is he calling me at this hour?
Should I pick up?
Yes, hold on. Let me get my earphones.
Hello, Director Han.
It's so late. What's the matter?
I heard Chen Shuo's case
is going to court tomorrow. Is that right?
Yes, it is.
You two were both representing the same case,
yet tomorrow he's
going to court alone,
possibly facing criminal charges,
while you walk away clean.
Director Han,
you must be feeling pretty pleased with yourself right now?
Pleased?
Well, if that's how you see it...
I...
Why don't you come over to my office?
I'm in the office.
Director Han, you're quite something,
still working overtime at this hour,
so dedicated.
I'm worried.
My partner is caught up in a criminal case.
How can I not be concerned?
If you're so worried, go find Chen Shuo.
Let him appreciate your kindness.
Why are you calling me?
I'm calling you...
Aren't you Chen Shuo's agent lawyer?
Right?
I'm calling you... Who else should I call?
I have something to discuss with you.
It's up to you whether you come or not.
Is he asking me to go there now?
What do you think he's up to?
We know much about him.
But why does he insist on me going over there?
To show concern for Chen Shuo, I guess.
Forget it.
I don't want to deal with him.
My head hurts.
Just ignore him.
This court is now in session
for the case of the private prosecutor,
Mingshan Mining Group,
accusing the defendant, Chen Shuo, of the crime of embezzlement.
First,
I ask the court
to allow me to express my respect for the defendant,
as he is a lawyer and a fellow professional.
That being said,
why are we filing a criminal private prosecution against him
and demanding that he bear criminal responsibility?
As lawyers,
our mission
is to use our knowledge
to uphold the justice of the law,
not to act like the defendant in this case, Chen Shuo,
who knowingly violated the law
and brazenly committed a crime
for enormous personal gain.
This is a blatant trampling of legal justice
and a disgrace to the legal profession.
Chen Shuo not only personally shouldered
the enormous risks stipulated in the contract
but also secured a victory for Mingshan with the final judgment
serving as valid proof of debt
and enabling the partial realization of certain claims.
The defendant, Chen Shuo, displayed extreme malice
and arrogance.
Despite knowing he had no right
to dispose of Mingshan Group's assets—
let alone withdraw funds from the joint account—
he brazenly transferred and misappropriated them for personal gain,
even after Mingshan Group
repeatedly proposed amicable negotiations.
The private prosecutor, Mingshan Group, violated the contractual agreement
by unilaterally signing a settlement with Minghai Group.
Such conduct
has already constituted a breach of contract,
and the conditions
for full payment of agency  fees
to Liangcheng Law Firm
and Chen Shuo have been met.
If even such actions
cannot be regulated under the crime of misappropriation,
then what is the purpose of this criminal offense?
What is the purpose of
criminal law in punishing offenders and protecting the people?
Mingshan Group's actions
are not only an act of betrayal and opportunism
but also a complete disregard for contractual integrity.
Despite the public security authorities having already dropped the case,
they insist on filing a private criminal prosecution,
attempting to use public power for personal gain.
They are exploiting criminal litigation
to retaliate against a cooperative partner
who provided significant assistance during their time of great difficulty.
This conduct not only violates the most fundamental principles of goodwill
and shared values.
Their claims clearly should not receive the court's support.
Your Honor,
the core of this dispute
revolves around the agency fees.
I would like to specifically draw the court's attention to the fact that
whether the agency fees are in dispute
must not be used as a justification to deny
the illegality of Chen Shuo's possession of the funds in question.
Your Honor,
if not for Mingshan's prior breach of contract,
which caused the defendant significant distress,
he would not have resorted to self-help under urgent circumstances
to safeguard his legitimate interests.
Why else would Chen Shuo
retain the disputed funds?
No matter how the other party tries to argue,
Chen Shuo's unauthorized transfer and disposal
of the disputed funds from the joint account
is already an illegal act.
I have also contacted the other attorney
named in the agency agreement, Lawyer Han Zhitong,
and I request Mr. Han to testify in court.
Your Honor, members of the court,
I am Han Zhitong,
a lawyer from Liangcheng Law Firm
and one of the representatives named in the agency agreement.
Mr. Han,
we all know that
Chen Shuo transferred 5.6 million
from the joint account,
of which 20% was paid to you.
Why did you later
return this sum
to Mingshan Group?
Because I am a law-abiding lawyer.
The agreement did stipulate that
we could receive
and transfer the executed debt payments,
but it did not authorize us to withdraw or distribute the funds at our own discretion.
When Mr. Chen distributed the money to me,
I felt there was a risk involved.
So I took the initiative to return the money.
I even advised Mr. Chen to refund the money,
or if not possible, to negotiate with Mingshan
and sign a supplementary agreement.
But Mr. Chen disagreed.
In my opinion, Mr. Chen is just too young
and inexperienced.
Your Honor,
Mr. Han has made it very clear.
Chen Shuo knowingly violated the law and the contract,
and despite the dissuasion from another representative,
he still proceeded with the intention of illegal possession
to withdraw and distribute
the large sum of money belonging to Mingshan Group.
His subjective malicious intent is severe,
clearly meeting the criteria for the crime of embezzlement.
Mr. Han,
were you aware of
how the defendant, Chen Shuo,
withdrew and allocated the payments from the joint account?
Were you aware of
this process?
I was not aware at first.
After receiving the money, I was puzzled.
Wasn't it supposed to be a joint account?
And the other party clearly didn't want to pay.
So how did the funds get withdrawn?
I only found out after asking about it.
That being said,
I understand that Mingshan is indeed facing difficulties.
If they wanted to reduce the agency fees,
that could have been negotiable.
Mr. Han,
please be responsible for your statements in court.
The private prosecutor, Mingshan Group,
has never had any intention of maliciously breaching the contract.
We have also actively communicated with the defendant
in an effort to reach a mutual agreement.
Your Honor,
I would like to respond to the private prosecutor.
First,
we have never denied that
the defendant, Chen Shuo, had certain irregularities
in handling the joint account.
However, as the witness Mr. Han stated,
all of this occurred under the premise that
the private prosecutor, Mingshan Group, had openly breached the contract first.
My client, Chen Shuo,
had no choice
but to take action to protect his own interests.
Moreover, both parties have not
reached a new agreement
regarding the settlement of agency fees.
According to the contract,
the 5.6 million yuan
withdrawn by Lawyer Chen Shuo from the joint account
is far from the agreed payment amount.
Given that the conditions for payment have already been met,
this 5.6 million yuan
cannot be simply classified as
funds belonging to Mingshan Group.
Your Honor,
we happen to have
a very important audio recording here.
The person in this recording
is none other than Mr. Sun Mingshan,
the legal representative of the plaintiff.
This recording proves that
our client, Lawyer Chen Shuo,
resorted to self-help measures
to withhold the funds
only because the opposing party had breached the contract first
and had explicitly stated that
they would not pay the agency fees as agreed.
Objection!
The opposing party is engaging in trial by ambush.
Representative for the opposing party,
you just requested Mr. Han to testify in court—
does that not also constitute trial by ambush?
Your Honor,
why did my client, Lawyer Chen Shuo,
take such a significant risk
to withhold the disputed funds in advance?
The answer lies within this recording.
We formally request
permission to play this recording in court.
Please grant permission, Your Honor.
Permission granted.