[Unbreakable Ⅱ]
[Episode 25]
I've made up my mind.
I'm going to pursue this lawsuit.
Okay.
I'm going to sue.
But suing...
I might lose, right?
But I don't care anymore.
I've been hesitating,
especially since that day when the lawyer mentioned that
Liu Jianming is living in hardship.
I was thinking,
since I'm living better than him,
is it too much for me
to sue him instead?
But I never expected
them to resort to such despicable means
to evade responsibility.
So, I'm going to sue them.
Ms. Luo,
don't overthink it.
You haven't done anything wrong.
No, Ms. Xiao.
This is indeed my responsibility.
I am truly happy
to see you so brave,
but when you mustered your courage,
I missed
such a good opportunity.
I really feel like
I cannot forgive myself.
Ms. Xiao,
going to court
is both mentally and physically exhausting.
Given the current situation of this case,
the possibility of losing is very high.
We might end up
spending time and money
only to suffer another round of hurt.
What's the point of that?
For myself.
Until this morning,
all the decisions I made
were influenced by Yang Shu.
I was always afraid, always blaming myself,
thinking that it was my fault that led to all of this.
But now I understand
it wasn't me—it was them.
They are the ones who committed wrongdoing,
and even after all these years,
they show no awareness or remorse,
acting as if what happened
was justified.
Cowardice and fear in the face of evil
are tantamount to enabling it.
That's why I want to sue them.
Winning isn't the most important thing;
what matters is standing
in court
and telling everyone what they did to me
and the harm I suffered from
what others might dismiss
as minor wrongs.
For me, that is enough.
I'm back.
You're back.
Why are you so late?
-I just got off work.
-Let's go.
Where are we going?
To the Division Chief's house.
Didn't we agree that
Chief Hou has been so supportive of my work,
so we should go and visit.
I was too busy and forgot.
Alright, let's go.
Maybe you should change your clothes.
What's wrong with these clothes?
It's just... I feel like
our outfits don't really match.
They do.
You're in professional attire,
and so am I.
That's exactly the problem—it's too formal.
It's too late.
Honey, change into something else.
Wait,
we're just going to Chief Hou's house, not a banquet.
No need to change. That's it.
Let's go.
Aren't you in a hurry?
I'm not changing.
-Let's go quickly.
-Okay.
Here.
Hello.
You are...
Are you Ms. Wang?
I'm Hou Chief Hou's subordinate, Zhang Quanquan.
This is my wife, Qiu Hua.
Hello. Hello.
We came specifically to visit Chief Hou.
Sorry,
but you came at a bad time.
Hou hasn't returned yet—
he's at a meeting at the bureau.
Quanquan, maybe
we should visit another day.
This is my fault for not confirming the time.
How about we wait downstairs for a while?
He told me he won't be back until very late.
How about you reschedule for another day.
It's okay.
We'll wait downstairs.
Go inside.
It's okay.
We can wait downstairs.
It's okay. Come in.
I'll contact Hou
to see what's going on.
Come in.
Well, then, sorry to trouble you.
It's okay. Come in.
Sorry.
It's okay.
Have a seat.
Do we need to change shoes?
No, no.
Fei, hurry up. I need to entertain guests.
Go inside and play with your sister.
I don't want to; the cartoon just started.
Be good; the guests are waiting.
Be good.
Hurry up.
Go.
Are you disobedient?
I'll tell your dad when he comes back. Go.
I'm not afraid even if you tell him.
I just want to watch.
Ms. Wang.
Just let him watch.
We're going to wait anyway.
I'm sorry.
This is the time
he watches cartoons every day;
so it's become a habit, you see.
We came too suddenly
and disrupted your normal routine.
We're really sorry.
It's nothing; have a seat.
I'll make you some tea.
Don't bother.
What's your name?
Mom.
I'm busy now.
I'll call you later.
How busy can you be?
What if your mom has something important?
A couple of days ago,
my dad was sentenced
to 10 years.
My mom has been feeling really down lately
and keeps calling me.
I don't know what to do.
Wait,
how come you didn't tell us about something
as big as your dad's sentencing?
The more I talk about it, the sadder I get.
I'll just get through it.
Luo, aren't you the same?
How can we be the same?
You're still so young.
I just grew up overnight.
I wanted to go back in the last trial,
but my mom wouldn't let me.
She said we could visit him together
after he's eligible for visits.
Besides,
with the mess that Han
left us in Xiao Nannan's case,
I couldn't just run away
and leave you two to clean up the mess.
Anyway, Xia Shu, just remember this:
whether it's money or manpower you need,
as long as I can be of use,
you just tell me.
Thank you, Luo.
By the way, Qiu Hua has been going through the accounts these days
and mentioned that the second debt repayment
hasn't been settled by Hao Lei yet.
What's going on?
He's currently canvassing for votes
to become the president,
planning to buy equity,
and has a pile of unpaid workers' wages.
What do you mean?
Are you going to give up the profit
and let go of the money?
How could that be?
Right now, I'm
helping him win over shareholders
so that once he becomes the president,
he'll give me all the legal business for the year.
That way, our law firm will have its income secured.
Anyway, Xia Shu, as I've told you before,
the money is only real when it's in your own hands.
Hao Lei is indeed having a tough time,
but you're also in a difficult position now,
so take care of yourself first.
I understand.
Luo, I've gone through the legal codes over and over,
and this time Han
has really blocked our path.
It's all my fault for being careless.
What should we do?
Just keep
exploring new ideas,
see if there's any good strategy left.
You think about it, and I'll think about it too.
Super Wings, transform, fight monsters.
Quanquan, shall we go now?
Wait a bit; the episode just finished.
Thank you.
Here, have some fruit.
Sit down.
Sit properly!
Why are you being so inconsiderate?
I just called Chief Hou,
but he didn't answer.
I guess the meeting hasn't ended yet.
Chief Hou is usually very busy, right?
Yes.
It's just a matter of timing.
As you know,
there are always a lot of personnel changes at work,
so Hou is especially busy.
Yes.
Of course.
How about
I try calling again?
I'll try calling again.
Thank you so much.
It's okay.
Quanquan, I really think
we shouldn't bother them anymore.
I feel like we're overstepping.
Let's wait a little longer,
or else this trip would've been for nothing.
You're already disrupting their personal life;
it's so awkward.
Don't you feel embarrassed?
Keep your voice down.
Xia Shu,
come look at this.
Check out the last post—
look at this comment.
Well...
Do you notice anything?
Compare the date on this one with the previous one.
I'll call Qiu Hua.
Okay.
This is funny, right?
[Luo Yingzi]
Sorry.
Yingzi, I'm out handling something.
What's wrong?
Where are you?
Can you come to the office right away?
What's going on?
Come quickly.
We can't wait for tomorrow.
Come here now.
Okay, I'll be there later.
Quanquan, it's getting late.
Let's go.
Go?
I'm so sorry.
Hou isn't answering his phone.
What if something important gets delayed?
No, no.
I'm sure the Chief Hou is just busy with more urgent matters.
He probably won't be available for a while.
We really shouldn't
have disturbed you today;
sorry for the trouble.
Oh, don't say that, it's nothing.
It's nothing.
We're leaving now.
Okay.
Sorry.
Well, my wife and I
will come to visit Chief Hou another time.
Alright, you two can come by again later.
Okay.
No need to see us out.
It's nothing.
We'll visit you next time. Goodbye, Ms. Wang.
Okay.
Okay, come again.
Sorry to bother you.
He's so cute.
Bye.
It's okay. Bye.
Sorry to bother you.
My law firm has an emergency.
You can just drop me off
at the entrance of the firm later.
Okay.
No wonder
you were going to leave after just half an hour.
Turns out you've got something to deal with.
It's a pity that
today's trip was for nothing.
Even if our firm didn't have an emergency,
I would have asked you to leave.
Don't you feel awkward
sitting in someone else's house?
It's so awkward,
even Ms. Wang felt awkward.
Why should it be awkward?
It's normal for subordinates to wait for their superiors.
Last time I went to the airport to pick up a leader,
the flight was delayed,
and I waited from morning till night.
It's quite normal.
I just think it's meaningless.
You once said that
a division chief
is the most basic level of an official in a state organ.
He can't determine your fate.
Besides,
how we live our lives
depends on us.
Why are you trying to curry favor with some division chief?
He supported my work,
and I just wanted to thank him.
How does that turn into currying favor?
Qiu Hua, I realize you really
don't want me to advance.
But advancing also requires the right methods, doesn't it?
If you look down on me,
why did you marry me in the first place?
When did I ever say I look down on you?
We don't have a foundation
in Jingbei.
If we're not going to build a good relationship with the leaders and colleagues,
how are we supposed to get by?
I just want to rely on my own ability.
Maybe we're not doing as well as others right now,
but I'll feel at peace
knowing that I'm making a living with my own skills.
Okay.
[Yinghua Law Firm]
You're finally back.
Well,
do you remember that
website from Xiao Nannan's university days,
the one where Liu Jianming posted
Rich Girl's Sayings?
I remember.
But that was 5 years ago,
hasn't that post been buried by now?
Yes, I think so too.
But it's suddenly active again.
The post has resurfaced.
Take a look.
Qiu, come and take a look.
Fox posted a reply below,
and Liu Jianming even
responded to him.
He's still attacking Xiao Nannan.
Look at the timing.
Since the post is active again,
it's still relevant.
Yes.
The defamation is still ongoing.
Who is this Fox?
Where did he come from?
I was thinking about who this person could
be on my way here.
Then I figured
it's probably that guy.
Chen Shuo?
How did you figure out that it's Chen Shuo?
He's so sneaky,
always pulling these shady tricks.
Actually, I haven't heard from him recently,
so I'll give him a call and check in on him.
Is there any other post?
No.
It's page 10.
His phone is off.
Even Unscrupulous Chen has his offline moments.
Well,
didn't I tell you before that
there might be a turning point?
Have you changed your mind?
Yes.
You called me over this late
just to make me realize my mistake?
No, it's because of this.
Okay, I'll go home and reflect
on my mistakes.
You're so petty.
Quanquan is still waiting for me.
I'm leaving.
I'm leaving too.
Okay.
It's so late. Who's there?
Hello, who are you looking for?
Hello.
Is this Yinghua Law Firm?
I'm Hao Lei. I'm here to find Xia Shu.
Xia Shu.
Xia Shu, someone is looking for you.
Hao Lei?
Why are you here?
Mr. Hao,
you brought all this food
for Xia Shu, didn't you?
I saw Xia Shu posting on her Moments that
she's still working overtime.
I wasn't sure what she likes to eat,
so I bought a bit of everything for her to choose from.
What are you doing, making such a big fuss?
You must be up to no good if you're looking for me.
Xia Shu, Mr. Hao's intentions are good.
He's so considerate,
right, Qiu Hua?
Mr. Hao, since you're here,
I have something to say.
You still haven't paid
the second debt payment
for Xia Shu's reclaiming debt for you.
How do you plan to handle that?
Actually, I'm here today
to discuss this matter.
Okay.
I'll leave it to Xia Shu then.
You can discuss it then.
Xia Shu, Xia Shu, I'll leave this to you.
You must make it clear.
Okay.
We're leaving now.
You can enjoy your late-night snack,
but the accounts still need to be settled.
Your two lawyers are quite funny.
Come in.
Come and have some.
I have no appetite.
Let me ask you,
can't you really gather the money
Zhang Lan is asking for
in this agreement?
I'm already figuring out how to gather the money,
but ever since you two talked last time,
she's disappeared again.
I can't talk to her about the price.
Well, maybe that's not such a bad thing.
At least for now, no one can get her shares.
Not such a bad thing?
If you can't give the money to Zhang Lan,
you won't be able to become the president.
That would mean your promise to me
is just an empty one.
Do you expect me to do this for free?
I'm already thinking of a way.
To raise the money,
I've even sold my house.
I'm in a tough spot too.
Can we maybe tweak the agreement a bit?
That way, we can lower the price,
but Zhang Lan will still feel like she's made a profit.
No, take it away.
Put that look away.
Just now, Ms. Qiu already said that
the money you owe us is a temporary extension.
Don't try to back out.
If you can't pay the big amount,
can't you at least pay the smaller ones?
So,
we should find a way through the contract.
If we can squeeze out some money through the contract,
I'll have enough to pay you.
But how can we squeeze it?
Xia Shu,
your sofa here is pretty comfortable.
Tell me, do you think
I might have post-traumatic stress disorder?
Every day when I enter the company,
all I can think about is my uncle coming to force a showdown
and the shareholders going crazy.
What's wrong with me?
You clearly haven't worked before.
Don't you know that
sleeping at work
is always better than sleeping at home?
Sleeping on the office sofa
is way deeper than sleeping in your own bed.
So, when you're working for me,
is this how you slack off too?
Of course.
If Mr. Hao is not satisfied,
find another lawyer.
I'll change right away.
You'd better find someone rich
who can pay Zhang Lan
all at once.
Then I guess I can only look for one in my dreams.
I've almost finished reviewing Zhang Lan's contract;
let's go over it together.
Hao Lei.
Weren't you saying you had post-traumatic stress disorder?
It looks like you're sleeping pretty soundly now.
What is it?
Tell them to wait.
I'll ask someone to pick them up.
Okay.
The boss of Mingshan Group is here.
They still have the nerve to come?
Any news about Chen Shuo?
Don't mention it.
He said he would turn off his phone on vacation.
I thought he was joking,
but it turns out he really did.
It's been so many days,
and he hasn't even made a call.
He made money for himself,
but he leaves us to clean up his mess.
Hello, Han.
She's up there.
Mr. Fang, they are here.
Let me introduce you.
This is Mr. Sun Mingshan,
the CEO of Mingshan Group.
Mr. Sun, this is Ms. Fang,
the founding partner of Liangcheng Law Firm.
Hello, Mr. Sun,  I'm Fang Lihong.
Hello, Ms. Fang. It's an honor to meet you.
These are our company's two legal counsels,
Mr. Gao and Mr Jia.
Welcome.
Hello.
Please come in.
Mr. Fang, your firm
has transferred 5.6 million
from the joint account
without our permission.
This action is not only malicious in nature
but also involves a significant amount of money.
We are formally demanding that
your firm return the full amount of the illegally transferred funds
to the joint account within five days.
Otherwise, we will file charges
against your firm and the individuals involved.
You're Mr. Gao, right?
I believe you're mistaken.
Our firm withdrew the funds
based on the terms of the contract we both agreed to.
Is there an issue with that?
Mr. Han,
we're all in the legal profession,
so let's not avoid the core issue.
The issue at hand is that
your side bypassed the other party of the joint account
and withdrew funds from it without authorization.
This violates both the agreement and the law.
I don't know
about the details.
Because this case
has been handled by Mr. Chen.
He's currently on vacation,
and his phone is off.
We don't know when he'll be back.
How about this?
Once he returns to the firm,
we'll gather all the details
and get back to you.
There's one more thing, Mr. Sun.
Before Mr. Chen
left,
he expressed some concerns about your company.
According to him,
your company has been negotiating with Minghai Group
behind the lawyer's back.
This behavior
blatantly violates our mutual agreement.
You have nothing to do here.
Wait for me outside.
Mr. Fang. Mr. Han.
I don't want to escalate things.
Yes, I have been negotiating with Minghai Group,
but we have no choice.
How the money was taken out,
you need to figure out how to get it back for me.
We can negotiate the agency fee.
Once we resolve our issues,
we'll entrust all of our company's legal matters
to your firm.
Wouldn't that be perfect?
But if the money isn't returned,
that's a different story.
Mr. Sun, are you threatening us?
If that's the case,
then I don't think there's any point in
continuing this discussion.
We are in the legal field,
and we only recognize the law.
Mr. Sun, whenever you have time,
I'd like to visit you
and sit down to discuss this matter.
I understand that
you might be in a difficult position,
but if you don't honor the agreement
and end up using the lawyer only to turn against them,
it could damage your reputation
once it's spread.
I believe we should prioritize harmony.
Let me know when you're available,
and I'll arrange a visit.
Mr. Han, if only Mr. Chen
could be as reasonable as you,
this would be much easier to resolve.
Fine.
I'll ask my secretary to contact you when I get back.
Okay.
I'm leaving.
Be careful.
Watch the steps.
Bye.
[Righteous Luo]
Hello.
Unscrupulous Chen, what do you mean?
Did you already scam them enough
with the last case,
or have you suddenly grown a conscience,
decided to stop doing bad things,
and turned over a new leaf?
What do you mean?
Don't you know what I mean?
You've got a chance to make money,
why run off to play?
You even turned off your phone.
Come on, tell me, where did you go?
Who did you take with you?
You're not talking, are you?
Is it because I guessed right?
There's no need to stay quiet if I'm right,
no need to act shy.
Hello.
What are you doing?
I'm fine. What's up?
Let's talk in person.
Let's meet at the usual place.
Mr. Sun, Chen Shuo and I
have invested nearly 1.4 million
in costs for the case.
You'll have to cover that;
you can't expect us to work for you
out of our own pockets, can you?
Alright,
as long as there are invoices, we'll acknowledge them.
Okay.
The 5.6 million previously withdrawn
doesn't even cover 50% of the agency fee,
so we won't be returning that.
Additionally, if you pay us another million,
we'll consider this matter settled.
Mr. Han,
your demands are way too much.
That's absolutely out of the question.
According to the agreement,
you owe us over 13 million.
I've already said that
we can't carry out that contract.
Then what do you propose?
Return the 5.6 million you took first.
We'll reimburse any documented costs
with invoices
and pay you another million.
If that's the case,
then there's nothing to negotiate.
Mr. Han,
aren't you afraid of going to court?
I'm a lawyer;
why would I be afraid of going to court?
Besides, if we do end up in court,
we're the ones upholding the contract
while you're the ones breaking it.
Who do you think the court will side with?
How about this?
I'll go back to the board
and get the approval for the 5.6 million.
As for costs, like I said,
we'll reimburse anything with valid invoices.
The agreement ends here. Is that acceptable?
No.
You need to add another million, just like I said.
Mr. Han,
the deal we reached with Minghai Group—
aside from the 20 million we already paid—
they've only agreed to pay another 10 million.
Think about it.
I have to cover your costs
and give you an extra million.
That means nearly 30% of what I manage to recover
goes straight to you.
How am I supposed to go through with this agreement?
Fine.
Then 5.6 million is approved
and the costs will be reimbursed; is that what you mean?
I still need to get board approval for this.
Unscrupulous Chen.
Where have you been these days?
Your phone's been off.
Nice haircut.
Did you break up?
Yeah.
Really? With whom?
It's none of your business.
Didn't you say you had something to discuss?
Just get to the point.
Okay.
You're Fox, right?
You saw it?
Knew it was you.
Unscrupulous Chen, aren't you on vacation?
Where'd you find the time to mess around like this?
I wasn't messing around.
I just set a reminder
on my phone.
That day was the statute of limitations deadline,
so I just replied to the post.
I just realized now
when we went to see Liu Jianming that time,
he was scheming to
get information about Xiao Nannan from us,
and you even chimed in with him.
Did you already foresee today's outcome?
That day,
I was thinking that Liu Jianming's
life must be quite mundane.
If he found out that
someone he used to bully
is now doing better than him,
he would definitely feel unbalanced.
In that case,
he might do something drastic.
Later, I found out that Han is his representative.
I thought the trap I set earlier
was about to spring,
so I replied to the post
and mentioned him.
Well, you're quite the schemer, Fox Chen.
Thank you, Fox Chen.
Thanks to your help this time.
I sent you three videos.
Take a look.
Good, Unscrupulous Chen.
That day, I was arguing
fiercely, red-faced and heated,
while you were quietly recording videos behind my back.
How are you going to use these three videos?
I sent them to you;
shouldn't you be the one deciding how to use them?
You've got two options.
One, you can post them online
and let public opinion put pressure on him.
When the case goes to court,
the judge will definitely take that into account.
That's vigilante justice.
Using public opinion to influence a court ruling.
I can't agree with that.
What's the second option?
What a righteous lawyer.
The second option is simple—
just hand the videos over to the judge.
Whatever decision they make
is out of our hands.
But if I were you,
I'd go with the first one.
I need to think this through,
but I really can't accept the first option.
Suit yourself.
The videos are with you now—it's up to you.
Anything else?
Why are you acting so weird, Unscrupulous Chen?
Are you sick?
No.
I've got work to do at the office. I'll head back first.
So weird…
Luo Yingzi,
if I ask you something,
can you give me an honest answer?
Go ahead. I'll tell you the truth.
Are you in love with Xu Zhuo?
Why are you so stunned?
You heard me clearly.
Are you in love with Xu Zhuo?
Are you all right,
Qiu Hua and you?
I'm a career-driven woman.
Why do you assume I'm all about romance?
Right?
You look obsessed with romance.
Besides,
who I like or don't like
is nobody else's business.
Does it have anything to do with you?
Yes.
We've known each other for years, haven't we?
If we're friends,
I should at least give you a heads-up.
A heads-up about what?
If my guess is right,
you should be extra careful
when dealing with him.
Careful about what?
He has something to do with Mei Daliang's case.
What are you talking about?
What do you mean, "What am I talking about?"
Didn't you hear me clearly?
Unscrupulous Chen, are you jealous of him?
Why would I be jealous of him?
We are peers.
You're hopeless.
Silly girl.
Just admit it—
you like Chen Shuo.
Wait, what's going on with you and Chen Shuo?
You guys keep trying to match me up.
Maybe you should just switch careers
and become matchmakers instead.
You don't like him?
Then why did you say he was jealous?
How many times do I have to tell you?
It's just professional rivalry.
That's not just professional rivalry—
he's jealous like a love rival.
Don't tell me you haven't noticed.
Why is it so hard for me
to just focus on my career?
Can we please stop dragging everything back to romance?
I'm begging you.
A career woman is like a brick—
she gets placed wherever she's needed.
Fine, I'll stop talking.
As long as you know
what's going on in your own heart.
I know exactly what's going on.
As long as you do.
By the way,
you just said Chen Shuo suspects
Xu Zhuo might be connected to
what happened back then.
But I feel like he's always had a bias against Xu Zhuo,
so his judgment might not be entirely objective.
Not necessarily.
Xu Zhuo was part of Madam Mei's team back then—
he was directly involved.
It's entirely possible.
Qiu Hua, don't start thinking like Chen Shuo,
always assuming the worst in people.
Yes, we assume the worst,
but you just have terrible taste.
What do you mean?
I can't be bothered to explain.
What do you think Han would do
if he found out that
Liu Jianming had made a new post?
With Han's temper,
he'd probably smash his calculator so hard it sparks
and then throw it in Liu Jianming's face.
They deserve it.
Let's wait and see.
Director Han, we're here today
to inform you that
the infringement has been ongoing.
We've already filed a criminal private prosecution,
and the court has accepted the case.
Your client
will soon receive a court summons.
The notarized document I have here
is the latest piece of evidence.
Who knows if your evidence is even legitimate?
Director Han,
we've given you chances.
If you think it's fake,
we'll verify it in court.
[That rich girl is doing great now, and she's back to stirring up trouble.]
Uncle,
I'm busy here.
I'll call you later.
Busy…
You won't be busy for long.
You'll be too busy in prison, you know that?
What?
Are you out of your mind?
You run a tiny business, yet you still have time
to stir up trouble online?
What possessed you
to post insults about her?
She's found the evidence
and has already sued you.
Just wait to serve jail time.
You're absolutely hopeless.
I should've never helped you.
How did you put up this screen protector? This is messed up.
I'm not paying for this.
I'll redo it in a bit.
Uncle, listen to me.
I was just bored.
Do we have any other way?
What else can we do?
Go to court!
This is really good.
Mr. Chen, Ms. Fang asked you to see her
as soon as you get back.
Which Ms. Fang? He?
Fang Lihong.
Mentor, you are finally back.
I called you so many times, and you didn't answer.
I even left you messages.
Maybe you're the only one who cares.
I just gave you 10%,
but you bought so much stuff?
Consumerism is a trap.
Ms. Luo didn't reach out to you?
Can you not mention her?
Fine.
Let me get down to business.
I went to Jingxiang Nursing Home;
I figured I should give them the money in person.
I didn't know you're pretty famous there
until I got there.
You're amazing, Mentor.
What's so great about it?
I just donated some money;
I didn't actually do anything.
Is there anything else?
By the way, Mentor, there's one more thing.
Mingshan Group
asked us to return the 5.6 million,
but my aunt stepped in.
She's adamant—we won't give it back.
Is that so?
Then I should thank your aunt.
What should we do next?
We'll take it one step at a time.
Your aunt asked me to come to her, anyway. I'll head up first.
I'll go up first.
Okay.
Chen Shuo, you've been away for more than 10 days.
Your phone was off,
and you didn't contact the firm.
How could you do that?
Have some water.
No need, Ms. Fang, just get to the point.
Here is the thing.
While you were away,
Mingshan Group came to the firm several times.
They want to terminate the agreement
and have the transferred funds returned.
From what I've gathered,
Mingshan Group and Minghai Group
must have negotiated privately.
Are they close to reaching a settlement?
That's why they don't need us anymore.
So now that they don't need us, they want to terminate the agreement?
Then why did they sign it
in the first place, Ms. Fang?
Besides, they betrayed us first.
They betrayed us—
why should we be the ones to back out?
So, sorry,
but I don't agree.
I'm sure you remember
when they first put out the public bidding,
why did no one dare to take it?
Because everyone saw
this coming.
Mingshan Group treated their lawyers
as disposable from the start.
The moment a situation like this arose,
they already had a plan for how to deal with us.
So,
there's no need for us to fight this head-on.
Why shouldn't we?
They're the ones who breached the contract first.
Chen Shuo, now is not the time to be angry
or impulsive.
You don't fully understand what's at stake here.
Some things
just aren't worth insisting on.
If we refuse to compromise,
there's no telling
what might happen next.
So, take my advice—
let's take a step back
and talk to them.
We'll negotiate for
the best possible outcome.
Okay, Ms. Fang.
I'll give you some face.
We can talk, but I won't back down,
unless they give me enough reasons.
Fine.
I'll arrange the negotiation time, okay?
No problem. Just let me know when it's done.
Mr. Chen,
I've always thought you were someone
who knew how to be flexible.
I just hope you won't be too stubborn
about this.
You don't know me very well.
There are things I can be flexible about,
but I'll stand my ground
on some things.
You're finally done talking.
Come here.
What are you doing?
Good news.
We need to talk.
Hurry up.
I put in an enormous amount of effort—
talking until my mouth was dry—
to get this result.
So, what do you think? Can you accept it?
Mr. Han,
this case was originally mine, wasn't it?
You were just assigned by the firm to assist me.
So why did you negotiate with the other party behind my back?
Why?
You weren't home,
your phone was off,
and the people from Mingshan Group came several times.
Plus, Fang Lihong kept coming to me.
What was I supposed to do?
Fine.
All right.
Well...
I admit it was wrong of me
to negotiate
without your approval.
I apologize.
Do you accept the outcome I negotiated?
No.