[Unbreakable Ⅱ]
[Episode 24]
It costs tens of millions for a case's agency fee.
Which company would agree?
It's better to negotiate with Mingshan before the two sides
reach an agreement,
and lower our expectations.
Make as much money as we can.
You can't say that.
The price Mingshan offered initially
was much higher than what we signed,
but still, no one was willing to take it, right?
Without us,
they wouldn't even get the 20 million.
Okay, Mr. Han.
I have to go back to the firm.
Okay.
Mr. Wang,
I owe you one, thank you.
70% is 50 million.
50 million times 8%,
minus the firm's share,
that will be 640,000.
It's not much.
Something is better than nothing.
Don't worry.
We're good partners.
Don't worry, no problem.
Okay.
Come in.
Mr. Sun, Mr. Chen is here.
I have a guest here.
Talk to you later.
Sorry to bother you.
Not at all.
Did you come now because you knew
I'm having crabs in the canteen today?
Don't leave later.
Have a meal here.
My chef is from a five-star
hotel,
with top-notch cooking.
No, Mr. Sun.
Eating is not important.
We just came to bring some good news.
The first installment of the execution payment
has arrived in the joint account.
Really?
The court should have notified you, right?
Did they?
Well, maybe they didn't tell me yet.
I don't know.
They definitely notified.
It's arrived.
Sit down.
The information we provided
was extremely accurate,
so the execution went smoothly.
Also, the court said,
Minghai will
pay the remaining debt as soon as possible.
Great. Great.
So, Mr. Sun,
according to our agreement,
shall we take out the first
installment of our agency fee soon?
Why are you in such a hurry?
This is just the first installment, right?
Isn't that what the agreement says?
It's supposed to be withdrawn in batches.
Mr. Chen,
our company
has really been dragged down
by this debt.
How about this?
About your legal fee,
don't worry, absolutely no problem,
but transfer the first
installment to me first,
so I can arrange normal production.
So many workers
are waiting to be paid.
[Jingbei Zhuoyue Law Firm]
This one,
this one and this one.
These are all from 2015, right?
Yes, they're all from 2015.
Alright, let me see.
These three are my ex-wives.
That day, Qiu Hua and I
saw them and chatted privately,
saying they all look very beautiful.
You have such good taste.
Thank you.
Mr. Xu, can I gossip a bit?
Aren't you gossiping right now?
What?
Do you want to gossip about why we got divorced,
or
why I have three ex-wives?
I want to ask about both.
Actually,
there's nothing strange about it.
Two of them married me when I was
still a public interest lawyer,
with no money, no future.
And it just so happened that I went to the detention center twice.
They suffered a lot with me,
so we got divorced before I even
left the detention center.
Didn't you stay in the detention center
for long back then?
So they wanted to get divorced so quickly?
That's normal.
Every woman in a marriage
is an independent individual.
A wife has no obligation to wait for her husband.
You can understand that, right?
Absolutely right.
Rather than suffer with me,
I hope they can live well.
And at that time, they didn't know
I would be acquitted either.
But to be honest, Mr. Xu,
I always thought a big part of the reason
you were acquitted
was luck.
So I don't really understand,
why were you so daring to refuse to plead guilty back then?
The risk was just
too great, wasn't it?
When I was in the detention center,
there weren't many good books to read.
Just this collection of Petőfi's poems
was barely readable.
That overused line,
"Liberty, love!
These two I need.
For my love I will sacrifice life,
For liberty I will sacrifice my love."
At that time,
I suddenly understood it.
Everyone advised me to plead guilty,
saying that if I did, I'd get at most three years.
Minus the detention time,
I'd probably only serve a year.
Even my wife at the time advised me to plead guilty.
Compared to prison,
these people's words were more like a cage.
I am a lawyer.
Not guilty is not guilty.
I absolutely cannot sell out the law for freedom.
The law is the truth, freedom is not.
But
at that time, you were already inside,
you didn't know
what the future would be like.
In that case,
did you still think the law
was worth maintaining at all costs?
China has a long way to go from
an ancient clan-based society
to a rule-of-law society,
and many sacrifices will have to be made.
If needed,
I don't mind being one more sacrifice.
[Unscrupulous Chen]
Mr. Xu, I need to take a call.
Hello, Unscrupulous Chen.
What's up? Go ahead.
Righteous Luo.
I feel a bit down inside.
I want to talk to you.
You're already financially free,
living it up every night,
and you're still feeling down?
How are we, the working stiffs, supposed to live?
Let me tell you,
I'm working hard now.
Don't rub it in.
Working yourself to the bone for Xu Zhuo again?
He doesn't even let you rest?
You said I'm working myself to the bone.
How can I still have time to rest?
I'm hanging up if there's nothing else.
Mr. Xu is giving me a lecture right now.
We're talking about Petőfi.
Impressive.
You're so pretentious even after working with him for two days.
Let's meet at the usual place
at eight tonight, okay?
I've got something that needs your advice.
Then you're buying.
My treat.
Okay, bye.
Qiu Hua.
I find that
Mr. Xu is
no ordinary person.
How so?
I just asked him about
his time in the detention center.
This guy is really tough.
He'd rather sit in jail
than plead guilty.
That's what you call sticking to legal principles.
Unlike us,
who at best earn a few bucks
and be money-grabbers.
Come on.
Is he working pro bono now?
He seemed pretty calculating when we were
discussing the contract.
He's holding onto the money.
I don't see him giving us any.
I meant that
he practiced what he preached,
sticking to his principles.
I've seen those two cases of his,
and I don't think it's like that.
What do you think it is then?
Those two cases of his
are actually
in the legal gray area.
I suspect it's because he knows the law so well
that he exploited the loopholes.
Forget it.
Since we're in the legal profession,
let's respect the legal judgment.
What a job.
I thought we were joining his team,
but it turned out we're just doing the work for him.
What does the client write here?
Can't read it clearly.
Just like him, no ice.
How much did you drink?
Are you okay? Drunk already?
I'm fine.
I'm in trouble.
A lawyer who throws around millions like that...
Thank you.
A great lawyer
can still have trouble?
You're just being sarcastic.
They're planning to welsh on the payment.
Your client?
Yes, them.
This case, initially, was about
the Mingshan Group, which I was representing, suing Minghai.
They wanted to collect a debt.
The contract amount is huge.
So I went all in.
I even mortgaged my house
and put everything into this case.
We won the first trial.
But the Mingshan Group
was really underhanded.
They violated the contract
and secretly negotiated with Minghai behind my back.
And I found out that
not only did they welsh on the payment,
but their whole purpose of suing
was to use me, the lawyer,
to pressure Minghai
into negotiating.
So, I, Chen Shuo,
am just a pawn being dangled.
I get it.
This huge sum of money
is like the carrot in front of a donkey's head.
You can see it but can't eat it. It's frustrating.
I'm desperate.
So,
I'm asking you to help me think of something.
Use your wit.
The two options I can think of are,
one, to confront Mingshan head-on
and get the full payment.
But that means a fight to the death.
The second option
is to negotiate.
You might get back about a million.
Admit defeat.
Only one million?
Which should I choose?
Logically,
you should get what the contract says.
But then again,
a million isn't enough for you to spend?
Moreover, neither of these
companies seems simple.
It's not worth it to go head-to-head.
It's not your style either.
What's my style?
Money-minded.
You're not a person to argue with reason.
Besides,
you're not the type to stick to principles.
So you earn more than others.
Luo Yingzi,
don't you know
the case that made Chen Shuo famous?
A client once tried to welsh on me.
I sued him.
The contract amount was one yuan.
You know why?
It wasn't about the money, but the principle.
Of course I know.
Fang Lihong has told both me and Qiu Hua.
But come on,
can their backgrounds
and contract amounts be the same?
One person, one group,
what's the difference?
Stubborn.
I'm giving you advice here,
and you won't even thank me?
Luo Yingzi, do you know...
why I asked you here today?
You're confused
and want to ask for my opinion.
That day going to Wanxian,
I was just a quiet driver.
I was like a persistent dog,
sticking to you,
While you just
kept chatting with Xu Zhuo
non-stop,
completely ignoring me.
What do you mean today?
You actually agreed to have a drink with me.
Now
you're blaming me?
I'm drinking with you,
not with Mr. Xu, right?
Understand me, will you?
This Dingxin case is our firm's
first big job.
I'm under a lot of pressure.
Moreover,
I have to work with an expert
like Mr. Xu.
I'm afraid of making a fool of myself.
I want to do everything perfectly.
You haven't seen much of the world.
Is Xu Zhuo really an expert?
Is he?
I think,
if Mr. Xu were to face this,
if someone tried to welsh on him,
given his unwavering
commitment to the law and principles,
♫Why are your eyes squinting?♫
even if he were jailed,
he'd still want to get to the truth.
Learn from Mr. Xu.
For the sake of the law,
♫Awaiting a breeze♫
he'd forsake everything.
Okay?
No.
Why should I learn from him?
♫To wake her up♫
Is he constantly brainwashing you
with Petőfi's poems?
Packaging himself
into a national hero
♫The sun on her shoulders♫
to gild his lily.
This narcissist.
♫And the weight of the rain♫
But he has been consistently supporting
the disabled in the judiciary for over a decade.
♫She never mentioned it♫
Isn't that a fact?
Stop, stop.
Listen, don't talk about Xu Zhuo anymore.
You keep talking about
♫Clouds♫
him
all the time.
What?
You can't talk about anything else but him?
Stop talking about him to me, okay?
♫Floating aimlessly, leaving no trace♫
Luo Yingzi, let me tell you,
it's fine for you to work together,
♫Between the sunshine and rain♫
but in life,
emotionally,
♫She comes and goes without a word♫
if you're going to collaborate with him,
keep some distance.
If you really need to find a man,
you can
♫The tranquility I've grown used to♫
consider me.
♫Is the invisible cloud♫
♫Giving me shade♫
♫That piece of pure, soft cloud♫
Are you even listening to me?
♫Supporting the wind and rain♫
♫The tales of sun and rain♫
♫Going back and forth in the darkness♫
Chen Shuo.
♫Silently weaving through♫
♫A glimmer of light can make it break through♫
Why do I have to collaborate
♫That piece of reassuring, heavy cloud♫
with someone?
Can't I just do it on my own in life?
Why do I have to...
♫Will accept it♫
rely on someone to prove myself,
♫The bitterness and mistakes of the world♫
on a man?
I'm a...
♫She understands all my clumsiness and persistence♫
career-oriented woman.
Besides,
if I really wanted to find someone,
♫In our sky♫
I'd look for someone
♫She will always wait for me♫
refined,
steady,
and
reliable.
Hello?
You're here?
Alright, wait for me downstairs.
I'll be down in two minutes.
Designated driver.
I'm leaving.
Just go.
One million.
It's enough. Just accept it.
♫Floating aimlessly, leaving no trace♫
Donkey head.
♫Between the sunshine and rain♫
Bye.
♫She comes and goes without a word♫
You like Petőfi, huh?
♫The tranquility I've grown used to♫
I'll give you some Petőfi.
♫Is the invisible cloud♫
♫Giving me shade♫
♫That piece of pure, soft cloud♫
♫Supporting the wind and rain♫
♫The tales of sun and rain♫
♫Going back and forth in the darkness♫
♫Silently weaving through♫
♫A glimmer of light can make it break through♫
♫That piece of reassuring, heavy cloud♫
♫Will accept it♫
♫The bitterness and mistakes of the world♫
♫She understands all my clumsiness and persistence♫
♫In our sky♫
♫She will always wait for me♫
Miss, look.
Hold the bow like this,
place it under your chin,
close your left eye, open your right eye,
and then shoot.
It's actually quite easy. Practice it yourself.
Okay.
You seem off.
How much did you drink yesterday?
Sober up.
About Luo Yingzi?
I misjudged her.
Since I was young, my view on relationships has always
been to pass through a hundred flowers without a single leaf sticking to me.
I never give my true feelings to anyone.
But after meeting Luo Yingzi,
I knew I was done for.
I was losing my mind.
But I don't regret it.
I'm willing to.
But after going through all these things,
I'm disappointed in her.
All she cares about now is
the empty fame and halo of being a success.
No matter what I do,
I want her to see my existence,
but she can't see it.
I've figured it out.
I'll stay single from now on.
I won't give my feelings
to anyone anymore.
I won't be infatuated or suffer anymore.
How can you be so sure that she has no feelings for you?
I'm very sure.
She's now completely obsessed
with that fame-seeking hypocrite.
Well,
it's common
for a woman to be confused
sometimes.
Luo Yingzi may seem smart,
but she can't escape this rule either.
We have to give her time
to let her wake up.
Wake up?
What about me before she wakes up?
I have to turn into a stone there,
always waving at her.
I'm here. I'm waiting for you.
Am I that bored?
Anyway, from now on,
if I ever get jealous, infatuated, or silly again,
you should kick me. Kick me awake.
I want to kick you right now.
Aren't you being jealous right now?
No, I think it's good.
I've said everything
I wanted to say,
I'm happy.
From now on, I'll just be a money-grabber.
Earning money is my top priority.
That's right.
Well...
I've transferred 200,000 to you.
Check it.
And
tell me how much the information
you provided today is worth.
Let's drop it for today.
If you insist on giving,
the more, the better.
Profit talk, true mates.
Bye.
Shuo,
well,
don't confront Mingshan
head-on about that matter.
Get what you deserve,
and take as much of the remaining money as you can.
If you can't earn the money this time,
you can earn it next time.
The key is
not to hurt yourself.
I'm not the same Chen Shuo as before.
Now I can only fight.
Thanks for your concern.
Bye.
Take care.
Call me.
Won't even open the door.
Sir, who are you looking for?
I'm Chen Shuo, a lawyer from Liangcheng Law Firm.
I'm here to see Mr. Sun.
Sorry, you can't go in.
I was allowed in last time.
We haven't received any instructions.
You need instructions?
Ms. Liu, it's Chen Shuo.
I'm here to see Mr. Sun.
The security downstairs won't let me in.
Mr. Chen.
Ms. Liu, sorry to trouble you.
What brings you here?
I'm here for something.
I was allowed in last time.
Why not this time?
It's to guard against me?
Mr. Chen, you must be joking.
What brings you here today?
Well,
I'm heading back to the firm
and send you a letter on behalf of
Liangcheng Law Firm,
requesting to withdraw our first installment
of the retainer fee from the joint account.
Is there any problem on your side?
Wait, Mr. Chen.
Didn't Mr. Sun already
talk to you about the execution payment?
You need to transfer the 20 million to us first
so that the factory can arrange production.
Once we get our business back on track,
you'll get your pay.
No, no, no.
That's not how it works, Ms. Liu.
We're not bargaining here like buying vegetables.
Like if I buy 1 kg of eggplants
you'll give me some free green onion.
We need to follow the contract.
You can't make the decision.
I'll go see Mr. Sun.
Mr. Chen,
Mr. Sun is in a meeting
and won't see anyone today.
In a meeting
with Minghai?
So you're violating the contract.
I have to see him even more.
Mr. Chen. Security, security.
No, you're violating the contract.
Sir, sir, sir.
Mr. Chen, you really can't go in today.
How about we reschedule?
Come on,
is Mr. Sun afraid of seeing me?
Or do you never intend to pay the money?
You can talk to Mr. Sun about the money later.
I'm sorry.
Mentor, how's Mingshan doing now?
They must have reconciled with Minghai behind our backs.
I just went to Mingshan,
but the security guard stopped me.
I didn't even get to see Sun Mingshan.
These people are really treacherous.
Fang Rui,
draft a letter right away and send it to them,
demanding they fulfill the contract
and transfer the first installment of the money to us quickly.
I calculated, it should be more than five million.
5.62474 million.
Alright, no need to be so precise.
Ignore the decimal points.
Just get them to transfer the money to us quickly.
After the letter is drafted,
have me review it.
If there's no problem,
stamp it and send it to them.
I'll notify them right now.
Mentor, one more thing.
Mingshan Group sent a notice of demand.
Take a look.
It says to transfer the 20 million execution payment
from the joint account to them.
This notice was sent directly to our law firm.
What's going on?
The debtor is more anxious than the debt collector.
Chen Shuo,
come to my office.
I'd like to discuss something with you.
Alright, I'm on my way.
Didn't I just say
to draft a letter right away?
Why are you just standing there?
I know about this.
After all, I have more experience than you.
I've thought of
these things early on.
The more the situation is like this,
the less we should rush.
Don't go head-on.
The execution payment
has already arrived in the joint account.
I think
we should withdraw it.
Withdraw as much as we should.
This is to show them
we're not pushovers.
We have ways to deal with them.
But after withdrawing,
we need to negotiate with them immediately.
Draft a supplementary agreement,
and discuss a price acceptable to both parties.
No.
Mingshan is not an ordinary private enterprise.
They have connections.
We can't confront them head-on.
It's enough for us to withdraw the money from
the joint account.
We are lawyers.
How do lawyers make money?
By time.
You're wasting a lot of time
on this case.
With this time,
you could have earned this money
from somewhere else.
Mr. Han.
I really appreciate you
telling me all this sincerely.
But I'm in charge of
this case.
I have the final say.
Now I'm telling you my attitude.
I will fight against Mingshan.
I will get
every penny they owe me.
As for your share, don't worry.
Once the money arrives,
I will transfer it to your account.
Alright, I'm leaving.
Did Mingshan disagree?
They didn't say so,
but they're just playing dumb.
I went to see Sun Mingshan,
but the security guard wouldn't let me in.
Later, the secretary came down,
but whatever I asked her, she was evasive,
saying she couldn't make the decision.
Anyway, I made it clear.
I said I would send them a letter,
demanding they pay our first installment
of the agency fee as per the agreement.
But they didn't listen.
Today, they sent another notice of demand,
asking us to cooperate
and transfer the 20 million execution
payment to them.
So, what are you thinking?
I was thinking,
Ms. Fang, how about this?
The firm gives me authorization,
and I go to the bank and suspend that U-Shield
in their possession.
I'm a lawyer.
Everything I do
is to protect the firm's
and my own best interests.
Alright, then you go to Zhang Zhi and get one.
Fang Rui, I'm going out.
Mentor, I'll do the errand.
This time, keep that U-Shield safe.
Okay.
I'm your assistant.
We should take the responsibility together.
Give me the letter. I...
Don't.
Don't worry. Thank you.
You're welcome.
Keep it well.
Bye. Take care.
I'll keep it well.
I don't know
what will happen next.
I don't want to get you involved.
Be good.
Mr. Chen,
after deducting the firm's share,
there's still 4.48 million.
After taxes,
shall I transfer it all to your account?
Transfer 20%
to Mr. Han Zhitong's account.
Besides,
I'm going on vacation
tomorrow.
If it's convenient for you,
please notify Mingshan that
we've withdrawn our share
as per the agreement,
and the rest is their money
which can be transferred to their account at any time.
Well,
Chen Shuo said he's already sent a letter to Mingshan,
demanding distribution as per the agreement.
Are you aware of this?
He told me.
But Mingshan ignored him.
This case was handled by the two of you.
What are you going to do?
Mr. Chen, come here.
What's up?
I'm here to report on the work.
Is it okay?
I've withdrawn 5.6 million
proportionally of Mingshan's money
and transferred to our firm's account.
According to the agreement I signed with the firm,
I'm supposed to get 80%,
which should be 4.48 million.
Can I...
withdraw the money?
Sure.
Leave the taxes and take the rest.
Mr. Han.
Although we've divided 4.48 million,
all the cost at the beginning is over one million.
Now you've changed your face.
Don't worry. I won't deduct the money this time.
Your 20% has been
transferred to your account.
Check it yourself.
Okay.
No. Well...
It's not right
not to deduct for the costs.
In that case, I'll transfer back 300,000 to you.
Consider it as the cost.
There's no need.
You've done a lot in the early stage, Mr. Han.
Thank you.
If you really want to be do it,
next time, okay?
One more thing, Ms. Fang.
I want to take a vacation.
No problem.
Just make sure everything at the firm is sorted out.
I've already arranged everything at the firm.
Also, there are just a few loose ends
with the execution.
I've spoken to the court.
They said it's fine.
Okay.
I'm leaving.
Sorry to disturb you all.
Besides,
Ms. Fang, I won't be answering my phone
during the vacation.
Just for this one case,
he's made a few million.
That's just the first installment.
Right.
Why?
How much do we earn from the cases we handle?
His case only had one court session, right?
The profit-sharing ratio was agreed upon by the firm.
We're all in the legal field.
Can we have some contractual spirit here?
Han, you...
If you're envious,
you can do the same.
I have to go. See you.
Mr. Xu, I'll follow your car.
It's okay. You can take my car.
Does it bother you
how we talk?
You're with Mr. Xu.
Who is with you?
Are you ever going to stop?
So annoying.
Now Mingshan and Minghai
♫Shoulders covered in morning dew♫
negotiated secretly.
Mingshan is playing a delaying tactic.
♫Facing the sunrise, with the crowd at my back♫
They tricked you.
Mingshan is not an ordinary private enterprise.
They have connections.
♫Hearing the baby crying♫
We can't confront them head-on.
A million isn't enough for you to spend?
♫Suddenly recalling the very start♫
It's not worth it to go head-to-head.
It's not your style either.
What's my style?
♫Floating between black and white♫
Money-minded.
You're not a person to argue with reason.
♫The lantern-bearer fears not the storm or fog♫
Besides, you're not
the type to stick to principles.
♫The seeker of light in the distance♫
So you earn more than others.
♫Wishes to light your way♫
All she cares about now is
the empty fame and halo of being a success.
No matter what I do,
♫No need to ask♫
I want her to see my existence,
♫Whether right or wrong, rise or fall♫
but she can't see it.
I'd look for someone
♫The path of chasing the wind alone♫
refined,
steady,
♫Our solitary and brave journeys♫
and reliable.
♫There will always be a beam of light♫
♫No longer asking♫
♫Where to go, where to head♫
♫On this endless long road♫
♫It embraces and listens to♫
Sir.
Hello, my name is Chen Shuo.
I've booked the courses online.
♫My dreams and my destination♫
Hello.
I'll take you to the dorm to clean up.
You know the phone needs to be handed over, right?
No problem, here you go.
No hurry.
♫No need to ask♫
When you're done,
let's have some vegetarian food first.
♫Whether right or wrong, rise or fall♫
Let's go.
Thank you.
♫The path of chasing the wind alone♫
♫Our solitary and brave journeys♫
♫There will always be a beam of light♫
♫No longer asking♫
♫Where to go, where to head♫
♫On this endless long road♫
♫It embraces and listens to♫
♫My dreams and my destination♫
Xia Shu.
There's still no news from Han?
I called him last weekend and he said
he hadn't come back yet.
Really?
How could it take a week to get evidence?
He said there was a minor mishap,
and asked for another week.
This old fox isn't playing tricks on us, is he?
No way.
Liu Jianming doesn't want to go to court, right?
If he doesn't want to go to court,
he'll have to negotiate with us.
He won't do anything else, will he?
Alright, I'm leaving.
The work at Zhuoyue Law Firm isn't finished yet.
Okay.
Bye.
Qiu Hua, I'm heading to Zhuoyue Law Firm.
Something's wrong.
Hello, Luo.
Xia Shu, check the time
of the last post Liu Jianming made online,
and see if it's been more than five years.
Okay.
2013?
Luo, come back.
We've been tricked.
Luo,
come and see.
When Xiao Nannan was a junior in college,
Liu Jianming posted a new
"Rich Girl's Sayings" on her school's website.
Look at this date,
March 1st, 2013.
It was this act that completely broke Xiao Nannan.
The next month, she dropped out of school.
Today is March 2nd.
The maximum sentence for defamation is less than three years.
For crimes with a maximum sentence
of less than five years,
after five years, prosecution no longer takes place.
Today it's already expired.
We've been tricked by that old fox.
He must have calculated the statute of limitations.
At that time, it was less than half a month left.
He kept finding all sorts of excuses to delay.
Now he's finally dragged it past.
Xia Shu, come with me.
Let's go find him.
What's the point of going to find him now?
We have to find him.
We can't just let it go.
Let's go.
Ms. Luo, Ms. Xia, what's the matter?
Looking for Han.
No.
What's going on?
I'm sorry.
Mr. Han said he's busy with a case.
Please make an appointment with him.
Okay, tell Director Han
I'm going to the parking lot to see if his car is there.
If the car's there and he still doesn't show up,
then don't blame me.
Luo, what are you doing here?
Tell Han
I’ll give him one minute.
What are you doing?
Open it for me.
Luo, it's my fault.
You and Qiu have been busy with Zhuoyue Law Firm.
I should have thought of this.
Stop it.
Our car is over there.
I know.
Hello.
I'm at the parking lot
of Liangcheng Law Firm's building.
One of the cars got into my car.
The license plate number is Bei A03088.
Can you notify the owner and ask him to come down
to discuss compensation with me? Okay?
I'll wait by his car.
Wait here.
He will come down soon.
What...
Stop looking.
Director Han,
do you think this is appropriate?
Yingzi, I think you're so cute now.
It's like two people in the ring.
You tell me which punch is okay, which one isn't.
This case has passed
the statutory prosecution period.
To be exact, there's no case anymore.
What you should do now
is follow our advice
and help the parties become friends.
My hopeless nephew
is having a divorce with his wife.
If Ms. Xiao doesn't mind,
I think they...
What are you talking about?
What do you mean by that?
Are you speaking human language?
I may not speak human language,
but I don't do inhumane things.
You're doing criminal private prosecution
over something trivial,
and you didn't even notice the statute of limitations passed.
Do you call that human behavior?
And you still dare come here
and kick my car?
I'm telling you,
if you really damage it,
I'll charge you with intentional property damage.
Let’s go.
Luo, don’t be angry. It’s all my fault.
I don’t deserve to be a lawyer.
How could I overlook something as sensitive as
the statute of limitations,
and lose to someone like Han?
Back already?
No results, right?
Qiu Hua, I don't want this year's
year-end bonus.
I'm just a big fool.
Don't worry.
It's not hopeless.
As for defamation, many opinions
say the limitation period
can start from the end of the act.
I just checked.
Liu Jianming hasn't posted anything new,
but the old posts
are still online.
You can still search them today.
So, his harm to Xiao Nannan
is ongoing.
In this sense,
the statute of limitations hasn't expired.
I know. I thought about it on the way.
But who knows
how the judge will rule?
They will definitely argue
that the harm ended five years ago.
Then let's give it a shot.
We'll try our best.
But if Xiao Nannan goes to court
and loses,
isn't that just more harm to her?
The more I think about it, the more I feel I can't forgive myself.
Criminal private prosecution is already hard to win,
and then this Han set me up.
We should honestly
tell Xiao Nannan about the situation
and let her decide.
I'll call Xiao Nannan.
I'm really sorry.
It was my oversight.
I apologize to both of you.
I see.
Ms. Xiao, Mr. Yang,
about your case,
the three of us discuss it together often.
I'm also often criticized by these two.
But today, I want to
express my opinion again.
Even if the case could be filed,
the chances of the judge ruling the harm is still ongoing
are small.
That is to say, Ms. Xiao might
face the awkward situation
of not getting legal relief
and being
harmed again.
So,
I still stick to my opinion.
Ms. Xiao,
rather than asking the world for help,
it's better to rely on yourself.
Force yourself to become stronger in the face of harm.
I've decided.
I'm going to fight this lawsuit.