[English subtitles are available]
[Under the Microscope]
[Episode 4]
Assistant Magistrate Ren.
How are you feeling?
Much better.
Thank you, Prefect Huang.
You may rise.
I found a good physician in the city
especially for you.
You can
join the discussion now.
Let's continue to discuss
the Silk Poll Tax.
All of you are busy
with the affairs of your respective counties.
Let's finish the discussion quickly
so you can head back as soon as possible.
Yesterday,
Shuai Jiamo filed a plaint
and requested that the eight counties of Jin'an
open their Archives
so he can check the original records.
What do you think?
I'm against it.
Magistrate Mao.
You must have a reason for it.
What reason do I need?
He's just a commoner.
How can we open the Archives to him?
It will damage the government's authority.
Besides,
if everyone
follows his lead,
our county offices
will never hear the end of it!
Don't make a scene here, Magistrate Mao.
This is no longer
merely a plaint from a commoner.
This is something
Jin'an Prefecture must investigate carefully.
The Silk Poll Tax
has been around for over 100 years.
If we don't open the Archives and check the original records,
how can we get to the root of the problem?
How can we rectify it?
I suddenly remembered
that the Houhu Yellow Register Archives in Nanjing
reported a case
five years ago,
about a father and son who sneaked into Houhu
and tried to tamper with the record
of their ancestral home,
and were arrested for it.
I remember it very clearly.
They were sentenced to strangulation.
It shows that the Archives are a place of importance
and must not be treated lightly.
There are rules to be followed.
Although our Archives
are not very grand,
special guards are appointed to stand guard outside.
Even I have to report and register my name
when I go in.
Magistrate Fang.
When you found out that
he had trespassed into the Archives,
why did you let him off so lightly,
with only a flogging?
Are you disregarding
the safety of our country's records?
Magistrate Mao.
Don't say that.
How could I have known
he wanted to raise an uproar
in Jin'an Prefecture?
However,
I passed an order immediately,
prohibiting him from entering the Archives again.
It was no match
for his tricks, though.
We are talking about
the Silk Poll Tax,
not
Shuai Jiamo's sentence.
Prefect Huang,
that's not right.
Shuai Jiamo was ill-intentioned
from the beginning.
If we sit here
talking about the silk tax,
wouldn't we be letting him get the better of us?
You always talk about getting to the root of problems.
We must
get to the root of this.
What are Shuai Jiamo's
ulterior motives?
Why is he creating dispute
around the Silk Poll Tax?
That's right!
Jin'an Prefecture was doing perfectly fine.
Then, he suddenly appeared
and tried to create an uproar.
This is too strange.
When things are strange,
something deeper must be at play.
Shuai Jiamo is an orphan and a bachelor,
he's the only one in his household.
Even if I voided
the Silk Poll Tax for Renhua County,
what would Shuai Jiamo
get out of it?
That's even stranger.
Why would he do this
if he can't get anything out of it?
Magistrate Deng, look at him.
He's just an arithmetic nut.
What ulterior motives could he have?
I see!
You mean
someone is instructing him!
Everyone.
We are talking about
how to deal with the Silk Poll Tax,
not how to settle old scores with Shuai Jiamo,
nor how to appraise his character.
If someone is diligent for no reason, he must be up to no good.
Think about it.
He's working so hard on something
that doesn't even benefit him.
There must be a greater conspiracy
behind this!
If we ignore
these details
and allow him to lead us on
in discussing the Silk Poll Tax,
we would be missing the point
in a very grave manner.
What exactly do you want?
We want Shuai Jiamo
to make clear
what his true purpose is
in raising the matter of the Silk Poll Tax.
If he cannot make himself clear,
we should follow the example set by the
yellow register tampering case in Houhu, Nanjing:
punish him severely
as a warning to others.
Shuai Jiamo.
Tell us.
Why did you go
to the Archives?
Yes.
When I helped people
measure their land,
I found that the numbers didn't tally
with those in the fish-scale map registers.
I get a headache
whenever I find anomalies in numbers,
so I went to the Archives to look it up.
At first, I was checking the fish-scale map registers.
Later, it led me to the tax registers.
The numbers
are all related.
Each implicates the others.
Later, I followed the lead
and found
there was a problem
with the Silk Poll Tax.
Enough!
Prefect Huang.
Listen to him.
What nonsense
is he spouting?
Shuai Jiamo!
Be serious.
I am serious.
Looks like
it's up to us
to reveal the truth.
Tell me your name.
I'm a student from Lanxi County,
Cheng Renqing.
How do you know
why Shuai Jiamo went to the Archives?
All the affairs of the world can be boiled down to six words:
common sense, human sentiment, justice, and public-mindedness.
I infer based on common sense,
judge based on human sentiment,
argue based on justice,
and defend based on public-mindedness—
Stop that.
Hurry up and tell us.
We need to trace this back to
20 years ago,
during the 38th year of the Jiajing reign,
when a tragedy happened in Renhua County.
A home caught on fire,
killing a couple
and leaving behind their orphan.
The husband in this couple
was called Shuai Duncheng
and the wife was called Liu Yue'e.
This Shuai Duncheng
was a copyist
in Renhua County's Revenue Office.
He was well-known for being a master of arithmetic.
Cheng Renqing.
Don't talk about irrelevant matters.
Assistant Prefect Song, calm down.
Let him finish.
In the 38th year of the Jiajing reign,
there was a corruption case in Jin'an Prefecture.
It involved a shockingly huge
sum of money.
The Grand Coordinator and Regional Inspector were alerted of this
and their offices issued orders
for a thorough investigation.
After investigating the case,
only one culprit was found.
It was Shuai Duncheng.
Let's set aside the matter of what Shuai Duncheng did
and how he was discovered
for today.
After the incident,
it just so happened that
Shuai Duncheng and Liu Yue'e's house
caught on fire.
Both of them died.
Rumor has it that
they committed suicide to escape punishment.
Only one pitiable orphan
grew up on the charity of his neighbors.
How did you know about this?
Fortunately,
only 20 years has passed since the incident.
Many people should still remember this.
Assistant Magistrate Ren,
am I right?
Yes.
I was in Renhua then.
It was a tragedy.
It's truly lamentable.
Old Mister Ren.
In your opinion,
was there anything suspicious
about Shuai Duncheng's case?
It's hard to say, after such a long time.
However,
the money involved
was probably not pocketed
by Shuai Duncheng alone.
In other words,
something was off with the case.
Yes, but not much more.
It's all in the past.
It has nothing to do with the topic of today's discussion.
No.
Old Mister Ren,
may I know
what kind of case
Shuai Duncheng's case was?
A corruption case.
Shuai Duncheng embezzled 3,530 taels
of the Silk Poll Tax.
He self-immolated to escape punishment.
Although there was something odd about the case,
it wasn't enough to reverse the verdict.
But it was certainly enough
to sow seeds of hatred
in a child's heart.
To think that
Shuai Jiamo is Shuai Duncheng's son.
How unexpected.
How unexpected indeed.
I see.
Both father and son
are involved with the Silk Poll Tax.
A seven-year-old boy
watched his parents
die tragically.
How could he forget?
As he got older,
he understood more about the world,
and so began to question
why his parents
had killed themselves in that fire.
Were they really the culprits
of the corruption case?
His curiosity about the case intensified
as time went by,
and his hatred towards Jin'an Prefecture
deepened!
But even though Shuai Jiamo wanted revenge,
he had no family to rely on,
was not qualified to take the imperial examinations,
and did not have brute strength.
What then?
The only thing he had
was the arithmetic
he had inherited from his father.
He could only use
what he was good at
to take revenge
on the whole of Jin'an Prefecture.
[3,530]
Jiamo.
Remember this number.
What's going on?
Assistant Prefect Song,
Shuai Jiamo is fine.
He just has some repressed emotions in him
that he's unable to vent.
He just needs to drink some sour date water
and get some rest.
Prepare it, quickly.
Okay.
Jiamo, how are you?
I saw my parents.
My father was holding a book.
Jiamo.
Cheng Renqing will stop at nothing
to win.
He will strike you
where you are the most vulnerable.
You mustn't take it to heart.
Yes.
I still have to investigate
the silk tax case.
Wait.
You're still thinking about this?
Prefect Huang is still discussing it
with the county magistrates
in the hall.
I haven't explained
the origin of silk tax yet.
What do they have to discuss?
They're not discussing the
silk tax.
They're discussing you.
Everyone.
You're hell-bent
on punishing Shuai Jiamo.
Is there really something wrong
with the Silk Poll Tax?
Prefect Huang.
I want to show you
something.
Take a seat,
all of you.
Prefect Huang.
Assistant Magistrate Ren
is a truly respectable official.
Here.
Yes.
Prepare a pair of new boots
for Assistant Magistrate Ren.
Yes.
Prefect Huang,
I've worn these boots for many years.
I've travelled through mountains and rivers in them,
and I don't know how many times I've mended them.
I didn't mean to make a show of my frugality.
It's just that money is tight.
You know that Wancheng is known for being
seven parts mountain, two parts water, and one part arable land.
But the people not only have to bear
regular taxes during summer and autumn
and apportioned corvée,
there are many other types of miscellaneous corvée work.
A family of three
working nonstop through the year,
sowing in spring and harvesting in autumn,
earns perhaps less than
half a tael of silver.
It's not even enough for a loan
to buy seeds the following year.
Even if I wanted to be corrupt,
it would be like trying to carve flesh
from a mosquito's legs.
The policies are harsh,
and the commoners find it hard to make a living.
That is why no one wants
the position of County Magistrate of Wancheng.
That's how my boots get worn out and
need repeated mending.
I dare not speak about
the Silk Poll Tax.
But I can tell you
what will happen in Wancheng
if a new tax appears all of a sudden.
Those farmers
will have to liquidate
their savings and livestock
in order to pay up.
But they are poor,
and can only borrow money from loan sharks.
They will have to either sell their land
and become métayers,
abandon their land and escape,
or
kill me and the taxmen
and join the bandits.
Every time taxes are raised,
these things happen.
Whether the silk tax is real or not,
I dare not agree
on behalf of my people.
It’s the same for Lanxi County.
If disputes due to a tax increase
cause delay in the transportation of main taxes,
the court will hold me responsible.
When that happens,
I will be forced to resign.
You...
Prefect Huang.
This tax has existed
since before I was born.
It has been around for over a hundred years.
Even if it were unjust,
it has become the status quo.
We should not be too meticulous about matters of the past.
If you insist on
pursuing the matter,
what if there is something wrong
with the other taxes?
If we open the floodgates,
the controversy will be endless.
I, Prefect Huang, have made a decision
[Jin'an Prefectural Office]
on the silk tax case.
Shuai Jiamo spread false rumors
in an attempt to seek revenge.
He has been detained and will be handed
to the Office of Justice to be sentenced.
People of Renhua,
you are not to talk about this issue
nor spread rumors.
Offenders
will be held accountable.
Go in!
[Honourable and Just]
Buying ham?
Do you want me to show you around?
I'm here to see your brother.
You found out we won the lawsuit
and came to congratulate us, right?
What a coincidence.
He might have been stopped by the people
on his way back.
Your brother
lost the lawsuit.
Your brother is fine for now,
he'll be back soon.
As for Shuai Jiamo,
he wasn't
that lucky.
He was reported
for holding a grudge
because of his parents
and trying to take revenge on the entire Jin'an Prefecture.
His parents
burned to death.
Who said that?
Me.
You?
I have to thank Ms. Feng
for telling me
about Shuai Jiamo's background,
which led me
to discover this piece of information.
Listen to my advice.
Taxes, money, and grains
are of paramount importance
to officials, and to the court.
You're seeking doom
if you interfere in these matters.
You're the one seeking your doom.
I have a second piece of advice.
Interfering with someone making their fortune is akin to killing their parents.
This has been the case since ancient times.
Competing for profit is the gravest type of enmity.
If you want to threaten
the interests of the other seven counties,
do you know how much trouble you will make?
What trouble?
I came to your branch in Tongyang today
to check if the pork you're using
comes from diseased pigs.
I’ll go to your branch in Wancheng tomorrow
to check if there are problems
with your account books.
The day after tomorrow,
Jin'an will send you a note
nominating you for an imperial commission
to send 3,000 jin of
top quality-ham hocks
to the capital for free.
You can abandon your business,
but
do you want to save...
that playboy brother
of yours?
You...
Tell your brother when he comes back
that I've finished writing
a confession for him.
He was deceived by an evil person and couldn't tell truth from falsehood.
He only raised the joint plaint
because he could not turn a friend down.
Now he has repented
and is willing to testify
that Shuai Jiamo was indeed trying to take revenge
by deceiving the public.
[Shuai Jiamo wanted to take revenge]
[Yufeng Bridge]
Sir,
you seem to be in a good mood
after leaving the ham shop.
Do you really like her?
She gave me half a string of cash,
that’s all.
Mr. Cheng!
Sir,
should we wait for him?
No need. Go on.
Mr. Cheng!
Mr. Cheng.
Have you signed the confession?
I want you
to clear Shuai's name.
Clear his name?
That comes at a price.
Mr. Cheng!
According to The Great Ming Code,
Shuai Jiamo's crime
will get him flogged 30 times
and exiled 3,000 li away at most.
It's not heavy.
Shuai is a dummy except for his arithmetic skills,
he won't make it
if he gets exiled 3,000 li away!
Mr. Cheng.
I beg of you.
Find a way
to clear his name.
It's easy.
Take your confession and tear it up.
Turn yourself in at the government office,
and tell them
you were behind the whole thing.
He'll be fine then.
Wait.
Shuai Jiamo's sentence
depends on Prefect Huang.
I'll be off now.
[Prison]
Guards!
Help!
-Come here. -What are you doing?
Help! Help!
Why aren't you sleeping?
We need to change cells.
What's wrong with you?
Changing cells in the middle of the night.
This- This cell...
I- can't stay here anymore.
The new guy...
So what if he's new?
Is he sick
or did he see a ghost?
We wanted to intimidate him.
But he...
He...
He kept mumbling
and even drew sigils on the ground.
And I saw
a wisp of black smoke
floating in through that window
with my own eyes.
Could he be
possessed?
It's possible!
I can't live here anymore,
it's too scary.
Yes.
I'll confess everything I did.
Let us go somewhere else.
Hurry up.
Open the door.
Come on.
Here.
Wait.
-Let's go. -Look at this.
Ghost!
Master Fan.
Fortunately, I did not let you down.
Alright. You may go.
Magistrate Deng, Old Mister Ren,
farewell.
-See you. -See you.
Looks like
you have a trump card.
Hurry up.
You're too slow.
I'll hurry.
[Renhua]
It's fresh out of the oven.
You scared me!
Don't say that.
We saw a spirit
last night.
Spirit?
There are spirits
in a prison as lame as this?
Keep your voice down.
Yes.
There really was a cat spirit.
We saw it last night.
I think
the cat spirit that eats straw mats
possessed him.
Possessed who?
The one from yesterday.
He-
The one who just came in yesterday.
He's called...
Shuai Jiamo.
Him?
This is the prison.
What are you doing here?
Greetings, Sirs.
I want to visit someone.
Do you have a document from the Office of Justice
or a letter from the Prefect?
Who are you visiting?
Shuai Jiamo. He just came yesterday.
Tell him
the two of us
are on orders to stand guard here.
We have no grudge against him.
Tell him to spare us
from his hoodoo.
Please come in.
Yes, this way.
Shuai.
Are you okay?
You came at the right time.
I found
a new way to prove it—
That's not important anymore.
Why not?
I found a new way
to prove the relationship
between the Silk Poll Tax
and the provisions supplement.
As long as I get the original registers,
I can calculate it.
Shuai!
I have to get something clear
today
because it concerns
many important things.
Go ahead.
Was
what Cheng Renqing said yesterday
true?
What?
He said
you're making use of the Silk Poll Tax
to cause trouble in Jin'an Prefecture
in order to avenge your parents.
Is that true?
No.
I can't remember anything
about my parents.
I know you don't lie.
But after listening to
Cheng Renqing's story,
you responded really strangely
and then passed out.
I've never seen that from you before!
I had a splitting headache.
Many things from the past
swept into my mind
like a gust of wind.
But they were all jumbled up.
I couldn't tell
which ones were real
and which ones were fake.
Did you really
have no memory of them
before this?
I wish I could remember.
But I can't even remember
what my parents looked like.
In the past,
even if someone scolded me,
saying my father did something wrong,
I could never get angry.
Because I didn't know
what he did.
But you remember
the arithmetic your father taught you.
Because arithmetic
is the only thing
I care about in this world.
You don't understand.
It's like how I could never understand
why you think
brothels and gambling houses
are so fun.
You will also never understand
how interesting arithmetic is.
Interesting?
Numbers are simple by nature.
Arithmetic is the most honest thing
in the world.
One plus one is always two.
Five times four is always twenty.
And the square of 12
is always 144.
People are unpredictable and hard to figure out,
but numbers are simple and never deceive us.
The relationships between numbers
are like the constellations in the sky,
they don't ever change.
As long as you understand
the principles of their workings and the methods of calculation,
you can find out
anything you wish to know!
This is what I pursue!
Even if there are infinitely many numbers,
even if the sums are complex,
fundamental principles allow me to command them!
Perhaps to you,
this is just
a room filled with
tattered official newspapers.
But to me,
this is the way to the abode of the Immortals!
Here, my spirit wanders
up into the heavens and down into the netherworld!
Countless sceneries appear
in a blink of an eye!
What is this, if not true freedom?
What's the difference between this
and becoming an Immortal?
[3,530]
Well said...
What- What does that mean?
I didn't understand either.
But it doesn't matter anymore.
Shuai,
wait for me here.
It's time to change the straw mat.
We'll change it.
-Right away. -Right now.
[Office of Justice]
No.
This is an official document.
A few days ago, Magistrate Fang
handed an official document over to me,
saying he wanted to try
the silk tax case.
Since we reached a conclusion yesterday,
according to standard procedure,
I should write an official document to Magistrate Fang
in return, right?
Ask Renhua County to execute my orders.
You mean I should
turn this official document into a bulletin
in Renhua County's name
to announce the judgement?
This incident caused a ruckus
in Renhua.
Don't we owe the public
an explanation?
If this judgement is announced,
and the people find out
they have to continue
paying this Silk Poll Tax,
I'm afraid
they will object.
How could they?
They will only praise Magistrate Fang
for being considerate of the people.
Prefect Huang,
that makes sense,
but did you know that
even though the people of Renhua
are simple and honest,
there is no lack of scoundrels either.
Shouldn't we
be more aware of their feelings?
You're new here.
If there is a disturbance
in Jin'an Prefecture,
it will be bad for your reputation.
I really don't mind.
Anyway, my orders
are only effective
within this Prefectural Office.
The ones doing the real work
are the county magistrates.
Prefect—
I have made copies
of this official document
for the county magistrates
of Lanxi, Wancheng, and Tongyang.
I believe
they will publicize it soon.
Go back and handle it according to the rules.
Prefect- Prefect Huang—
See him out!
Are you here to submit the confession?
Come back with me.
No, Sister!
I thought of a way to save Dummy.
You-
What could you think of?
[Flog 40 times, Exile 3,000 li away]
Do you want to save Shuai Jiamo
or kill him?
Look at
what you wrote.
You want them
to punish him severely?
Slow down.
This is why it's brilliant.
Brilliant?
It's worth my effort
spending the whole night working on it.
Get to the point!
The ones who want to punish Shuai
are the four county magistrates.
Prefect Huang still supports us.
Why did he order Shuai's arrest then?
He was forced to by the circumstances.
But when he gave the order,
he said
he was detaining Shuai Jiamo
for the Office of Justice to sentence him.
Hush.
If Prefect Huang
really wanted to punish Shuai,
he would have given the order himself!
He's letting the
Office of Justice handle it
to hint that
he wants to wash his hands of the matter.
It's up to them now.
So,
I came here in a hurry
to speak to the Clerk at the Office of Justice.
So you mean
Prefect Huang has already hinted at his intentions,
so the Office of Justice
must find him innocent
no matter what?
No!
If he is acquitted,
the other county magistrates
will protest.
So my solution
is to do the opposite!
We'll suggest a harsh sentence.
The heavier the crime,
the more absurd it is.
The more absurd it is,
the easier it will be for Prefect Huang
to throw it out.
We'll make submissions and get them thrown out,
until the outsiders can't find any flaws.
Then, Shuai will be acquitted.
I see.
Recently,
an insolent resident of Renhua, Shuai Jiamo,
spread rumors and stirred up trouble
[Tongyang]
regarding matters of taxation.
He attempted to profit from it and throw the community into disorder.
[Wancheng]
I, the Prefect, argued logically
on the implications of the matter
such that the people will not have to suffer
[Lanxi]
an increased tax burden.
Now, the criminal has been detained.
People of our Prefecture, do not be alarmed,
all is well now.
[Renhua]
I happened to catch a cold,
and am unfit for work.
All official matters shall be postponed.
What's going on?
He's cowering
at a time like this?
He can't do anything.
This is outrageous!
[Jin'an Prefectural Office]
Deceiving the people with falsehoods
and indulging in barratry.
He should be exiled 3,000 li away.
They came up with this verdict.
The Clerk at the Office of Justice
is a long-serving functionary.
Naturally, he can read between the lines
and knows how to act sensibly.
Did you teach him that?
The people in Jin'an Prefecture are in harmony with one another.
That's my wish.
Not at all.
Am I being unreasonable?
They are the ones who were being aggressive.
Yes.
Guards!
This sentence is too harsh. Overruled.
Ask the Office of Justice to review it.
Yes.
In this way,
we all get what we want,
and the matter will be settled.
Not necessarily.
[Official Newspaper]
The Prefect's document reads:
[Ticket]
This criminal deceived the people with falsehoods
and indulged in barratry.
However, the mitigating circumstances
are pitiable.
Considering this was his first offence, he will be given a warning
and released from prison.
-Release him! -Release him!
Any recidivism
will be a serious offense
and punished harshly.
Hurry up.
-Come on. -Come on.
Turn over a new leaf after you get out!
Turn over a new leaf!
-Don't come back! -Don't come back!
Shut up!
-You should go. -Go, quickly.
Get rid of the bad luck.
You did quite well in prison.
Everyone is afraid of you.
They are afraid of me
because they think
I was possessed by a spirit.
What a coincidence.
Baoyu was possessed by a spirit too.
Then you have to get rid of the bad luck for me.
Come here.
No.
Don't...
Sister.
This...
This is good.
Shuai Jiamo,
Feng Baoyu.
Prefect Huang.
Shuai Jiamo.
This is your plaint.
Take it back.
I came up with
a new way to prove it while I was in prison.
As long as we add it into the memorandum,
we can prove—
It's useless to file this plaint
in Jin'an Prefecture.
But the Silk Poll Tax—
Didn't you understand what I said?
It's useless to file this plaint
in Jin'an Prefecture.
Understand?
Prefect Huang, take care.
The memorandum was well-written.
It's just that Shuai Jiamo
entrusted it to the wrong person.
Let me see.
[This has been the case over several reigns, but it shouldn't be so.]
Is Prefect Huang
revising your memorandum?
Let me see.
Look.
There are so many emendations.
Is Prefect Huang trying to
become your schoolteacher, Dummy?
What is this?
This is an official newspaper.
What is an an official newspaper?
You don't know, do you?
Official newspapers
report on
officials who were promoted or demoted
in a given month,
countries that sent tribute,
or decrees issued by the court.
Things like that are all in there.
It's for the reference of
the officials in the provinces.
Shouldn't we return it
to Prefect Huang then?
Right.
Let's go.
Prefect Huang.
Prefect Huang said
we shouldn't file the plaint in Jin'an.
Yes.
What if we do it
somewhere other than Jin'an?
I understand now.
Did Prefect Huang mean to say
we should go somewhere
a level higher than Jin'an Prefecture
to file the plaint?
Look.
The spirit has possessed him again.