"While You Were Sleeping"
The brain dead patient will barely
survive a week and die soon.
Then, proceed with the autopsy
and deal with it afterwards.
Sir, can I proceed with
the organ transplant...
...and autopsy at the same time?
Amazing.
Prosecutor Jung's brain dead patient
will proceed with both organ transplant...
...and autopsy at the same time.
That's too reckless. That's a rare case...
But that rare case is
very similar to this case.
All the victims from this case
are injured at the brain area...
...and not the organs.
According to the results,
we found blood near the neck.
Without autopsy on the organs...
...we can conduct it on the neck and
the brain to reveal the cause of death.
He said he'll reveal
the truth no matter what.
What's wrong with Prosecutor Jung?
What makes him so confident?
Nothing.
What?
Don't you know Prosecutor Jung by now?
His role model is a mayfly.
He likes to start on something
without thinking of the next move.
Isn't this too much, though?
I bet you he's somewhere pulling
his hair regretting his words.
"Episode 12"
This darn mouth...
This mouth is making my body suffer...
This mouth of mine.
Why did I say such things if
I don't know what I'm going to do?
What do I do when
I didn't even win a lotto?
Who's calling? I don't feel like talking
on the phone right now.
"Little Pup"
What's up?
I was curious to what you decided on.
Same choice as you.
That's a tough choice. Are you sure?
Of course, that's why I chose it.
I don't believe it.
Aren't you some place
sitting down pulling your hair?
Did you see that in your dream?
Nope, I followed your ringtone.
Hongjoo.
-Rat, rat...
-Goodness!
Where?
My leg is cramping.
Oh, that...
Are you that not confident?
No, it feels like I just learned to speak
and now I have to take the SATs.
I feel like a turtle trying
to catch two rabbits.
Gosh.
Don't worry.
It may be hard to get it done
but you'll catch them all.
What?
I had a dream.
The organ transplant will go well...
...and you'll win the trial,
putting the culprit in the jail.
Really?
Yes.
After you catch both rabbits,
let's go to the beach.
The beach near that bus stop.
That's a relief.
Why would you tell me that dream now?
I just thought you would be careless.
Don't worry, I won't.
It's good, you should go to work now.
Okay.
I forgot my stuff...
MY goodness.
Thanks for telling me about the dream.
Human lie detector my foot...
I think you should
go back to the hospital.
Why?
Prosecutor Jung got an approval
on the organ transplant.
What?
Prosecutor Jung.
There was something
I left in Hwan's hand...
...when I was sending him
to the operation room.
I think it was when he was sixteen...
I gave it to him for his birthday...
...and he made up his mind
when he got that.
He said he wanted to become a writer...
I...
...could never forgive the person...
...who ruined his dream.
Don't worry.
I'll make sure he's pronounced guilty
in the trial.
I'll work on the main artery now.
The time of death is June 2nd, 5:17 PM.
We'll begin the organ transplant.
We'll begin the transplant.
Forceps.
We'll control the bleeding.
"Knocking on Heaven's Door"
"There's only one title in heaven,
it's the sea."
Hongjoo.
Wootak.
Are you on your way to work?
Yes.
Get on. I'll give you a ride.
It's okay. I'll get there pretty soon
by bus, too.
Get in, it'll be even faster.
Although I declined...
...but I was hoping you wouldn't leave.
Can I charge my portable charger?
Do you have the cable?
Yes, here.
Wootak, did you have
any dreams about this trial?
No, I didn't.
I thought you said you had a dream
where Jaechan won the trial?
I didn't. It was a lie.
What?
Why did you lie about that?
He looked so discouraged,
so I wanted to encourage him.
Perhaps I went overboard.
He'll get mad if he finds out, right?
I told you, if you can cover it up
until the end then it's not a lie.
If I become a murderer then I'll
reveal all your secrets to the police.
Have you lied like this before?
A lie that you covered until the end?
Nope. Never.
You don't have to wear
that for the trial tomorrow.
I already told the detention center.
That's a relief.
Because of Lee Hwan, that crazy jerk...
You have such foul-mouth
for Korea's representative write.
I'm being accused as a murderer
because of that jerk...
Well...
You do deserve to be called a murderer.
After you strangled
your teaching assistant...
...you pushed that poor, unconscious guy
down the elevator...
...with the intent to kill him.
"Charge: Murder"
That's why you're charged with murder.
And you are a murderer.
You said you'll make me innocent.
I will.
But, don't forget what kind
of crime you've committed.
That way it'll be worth
the expensive fee of hiring me.
Is it really possible to make me innocent?
It could've been difficult if
you were charged with homicide...
...but thanks to the prosecutor,
he charged you with murder.
It's easier to set you free when
you've been charged with murder.
He can get out of it if you
charge him with murder.
I charged him with murder
because he killed a person.
What else should I charge him with?
Sir, you also agreed with that.
It's very difficult to prove
a murder charge in trial.
We haven't even done much preparation...
...and if he was found guilty
it can become a big issue...
...so maybe it's safer
to change the charge.
Charge him for injury or assault.
I can't. This is clearly a murder.
Why are you so reckless?
Do you have something to back that up?
Yes, I do.
What if he gets reckless
because of my dream?
He won't be unreasonable
because of that, right?
No way.
What are you looking for?
I don't see my portable charger.
Maybe it fell under my seat.
Wait. I'll look for it.
It's okay.
I have another one so you can
give it to me later if you find it.
It's a red one this big.
Okay.
Bye.
Hongjoo.
Don't worry too much about Jaechan.
I've been investigated by him before.
He's very trustworthy and careful.
I know that he's careful.
Mr. Jung, you're too careless.
It's like you're on the express way
without wearing a seat belt.
You should wear your seat belt first.
Charge him with murder,
but put assault as preliminary charge.
That's too pathetic.
Preliminary charges are known as
a charge that the prosecutor...
...is letting the judge know that
he's not confident with the case.
I'm going to charge him
with murder no matter what.
Prosecutor Jung will definitely
charge you for murder.
Why is a murder charge
easier to set me free?
The difference between a murder
and homicide is simple.
It's a murder if you pushed him
thinking that the person would die.
And if you thought that
he might not die...
...then it's not a murder.
It's much harder to prove
a murder charge than homicide.
If he can't prove that,
then you'll be set free.
Whether or not Prosecutor Jung
can prove your murder...
...I'm also curious.
The accused, Moon Taemin,
is a professor at Myungwon University.
The victim, Lee Hwan,
worked as Moon's assistant.
The accused made his assistants,
including the victim...
...do his personal work
such as tutoring his children...
...washing his car,
helping him on his moving day...
...or even running his personal errands.
He even assaulted his assistants...
...when he didn't like their
attitudes towards their work.
On 2016, May 30th at 4 PM...
...the accused assaulted the assistant
at his publication event...
...because he was holding a grudge
against the assistant...
...who reported him for assault...
...and exploitation of labor and called
him separately and assaulted him.
The victim, Lee Hwan...
...revealed the accused's picture
without his permission that day.
The accused claims that his
assault is a justifiable act.
In the process of assault...
...the accused strangled the victim
and made him unconscious.
This fact led the accused
to murder the victim...
...thinking when people found out...
...about what happened
he would lose everything.
I agree that there was minor
bickering and physical fights.
But, the victim was too drunk...
...to have a proper conversation
on the day of the incident.
That is why the accused
left the scene right after.
The accused pushed the victim
who was unconscious...
...through the gap on the bottom of
the elevator and the victim...
...fell from about 20 meters.
Three days after the incident,
on 2016, June 2nd at 5:17 PM...
...the accused has led the victim to die.
After the accused left the scene,
the victim couldn't hold his anger...
...and kicked the elevator
door and made a scene.
And this made him fall between
the elevator door on his own.
I hereby charge him with murder...
...according to
Criminal Article 250 of Section 1.
The accused not only doesn't
have any motive to kill the victim...
...but there isn't any direct
proof to prove that...
...the accused killed the victim.
So, I hereby deny the charge.
"Criminal facts subject to judgement"
Attorney, please go
through all the evidence.
"To inspect evidence
submitted by prosecutor for trial"
Evidence number 34, disagree.
Evidence number 43, disagree.
Evidence 43 is a testimony by
a witness, and yet you disagree?
Yes, I disagree.
He's the only witness to this case...
...but he's only
a 4 years and 9 months old kid.
It's very doubtful that this
kid could testify logically.
So, there is a need for us
to hear from the witness.
You're not going home?
You should go first...
There's something I need to take care of.
Okay, then.
-Bye.
-Goodbye.
Can a five years old kid
testify in a trial?
Gosh. This is a problem since
he'll be scared to even talk.
That kid has a lot of fears.
He even cried and peed his
pants when I rescued him.
That kid is the only witness, right?
Wouldn't the accused be free
if there's no testimony from the witness?
I have to get his
testimony no matter what.
You said you heard from the kid
at the patrol yourself, right?
Yes, I did.
How?
Wasn't the kid scared
at the patrol as well?
I spoke to him by putting myself
in his shoes...
...and approached him by
communing with his emotions.
Then, he testified.
Communing with emotions...
How do you do that? Can you teach me?
Why were you scared of that guy?
If you tell me, I'll punish him for you.
Talking like a kid...
Can you ask the witness
like that at the court?
Why would I do that?
I can just call his guardian
or the child's psychologist.
My gosh.
Mother, where should I put this?
Mother? Just call me as you used to.
That's enough. You should all go to work.
Hurry up and go.
-Okay.
-Thank you for the food.
Go ahead, I'm going to sew a button on
before I leave.
Mom, have you seen the sewing basket?
Why is this...
Hongjoo, Prosecutor Jung forgot his phone.
Mom, why is this here?
Did you hide this on purpose?
Yes.
But... Why?
By the way, the kid
really likes Santa Claus.
He testified well when I told
him that I'm Santa's friend.
Santa Claus?
No, not Santa Clause, but Santa Grandpa.
I'm more like an anchor style.
I actually can't make sounds like that.
Why can't you?
My Robin, did you poo? Did it feel good?
I can do it... Did you eat?
Was it good?
Seungwon is good. You can't do this?
Yes, not at all.
My phone.
I think you left it inside.
I'm seriously out of it.
He can do it.
Really?
He can perfectly do it.
Tell me.
Why are you so mean to
Jaechan these days?
What did he do wrong
that you're so cold to him?
You said you met him at
the funeral 13 years ago.
Are you okay when you see him?
I'm not.
I'm trying to forget about your dad...
...but whenever I see Prosecutor Jung,
he reminds me of that incident.
I'm like this, but are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
No, you're not fine.
What did you say last time
when Prosecutor Jung passed out?
You said you
couldn't change anything...
...and was crying your eyes out in case
the same thing happened to him like Dad.
Others may not know, but I know.
I can tell what you're thinking of.
Your dad passing away and
Prosecutor Jung's accident...
You're blaming yourself
and suffering from it.
You're going to continue
to blame yourself and suffer...
And get hurt again...
That's what you'll most probably do.
Mom.
I'm afraid that you'll get hurt
meeting Prosecutor Jung again...
I'm worried.
So...
Mom.
I'm really fine.
I feel good thanks to him.
I'm happy thanks to him.
So, please don't do this.
Please like him like how I do.
Please be nice to him.
Hongjoo, have you seen my phone?
Yes, here.
You must be really out of it.
13 years ago, to me...
...you're a scar...
...and a wound to me.
I thought it'd be fine
if I just ignored it.
But I guess I'm not fine
seeing how hurt I am.
Wow, the beach is so pretty here.
I wonder if it'll look like
this if I took a picture.
What's wrong?
Are you worried about the trial today?
No, I have a witness and autopsy results.
The witness is a five years old kid...
...and the autopsy result isn't clear
because of the organ transplant.
True, but I have your
dream I can depend on.
You should still not be so careless.
Don't worry. I won't be.
You shouldn't.
If you do...
...I'm going to punish you.
"Trial in process"
We'll ask the witness.
Hello, Lim Seyong.
Can you hear me?
Yes.
A cop rescued you before, right?
Can you tell us what you told him
the other day?
No.
He's so young.
How can he testify like that?
Lim Seyong, you have to tell us...
Mom.
It looks like it'll be difficult
to get his testimony...
We can try again after
he calms down a bit.
We'll get back to the defense
attorney for the cross-examination.
No, I think I can question now
since it's not regarding the accident.
Really?
Can the defense attorney
start the cross-examination?
Sure.
It's really scary here, right?
You must be wanting to go home.
Yes.
What did you take to come here today?
The bus.
Which bus?
I don't remember.
You can go home if you can
tell me which bus you took...
You still don't remember?
I remember.
It was bus number 6.
Can Seyong's mother answer as well?
Did you take bus number 6 today?
No, we took number 433.
Seyong, did you just lie?
I don't know.
How can the kid testify
when he's only five years old?
That's all for me.
How can the kid testify?
He's made the kid into a liar in seconds.
He's our only witness...
...but it's over if we impeach
the testimony like that.
Prosecutor, will you do
any additional interrogation?
Yes.
Your Honor, for communing with
the witness with his emotions...
...I'll have to proceed without
having to use any law terms.
Sure, go ahead.
Lim Seyong!
I'm a friend of Santa Grandpa.
You know Santa Claus, right?
Yes, but are you really his friend?
This uniform is for Santa's friends...
...and I can fly wearing this
uniform during Christmas.
What is he doing?
Oh my gosh...
Wow.
You would never lie to
Santa Claus, would you?
No.
Then, you wouldn't lie to me
since I'm Santa's friend...
...and tell the truth, right?
Yes.
You drew this picture
before for the cop, right?
Yes.
Wow. You did such a great job.
Do you remember what
this man told this guy?
Yes, I remember.
Before I interrogate,
let's all hear from evidence number 67...
...which was recorded on the victim's
phone and compare it to the testimony.
Your Honor, if we hear the evidence now...
...the child may repeat it.
No, maybe he already heard it.
We'll listen to the kid testifying first
and then listen to the evidence.
And this recorded file was found
during the prosecutor's investigation...
...and it'll be Seyong's
first time hearing this.
You may continue with interrogation.
Now, Seyong...
What did this man say to this guy?
He pushed him and
asked him if he was drunk.
Are you drunk?
Your drunk behaviors cannot be forgiven!
Then, what did this guy say?
He said he didn't need something.
And he said he learned
how to clean his shoes.
I don't need to debut as a writer.
I haven't learned anything besides
cleaning your shoes and cars.
So what's the point of debuting?
It's similar.
Now we have the witness's testimony...
Now, the evidence on murder.
We're almost done.
What happened to these two after that?
The man in gray grabbed the other
guy's neck and pushed him.
It made a loud noise and pushed him.
How was the guy in the white?
He suddenly fell asleep.
He fell asleep?
So what did the man in gray do to
the guy in white who fell asleep?
He pushed him down the elevator.
He purposely pushed him down...
That's done.
That's all.
Santa's friend.
So embarrassing.
Walk slowly.
You may actually end up flying.
What is it?
How did you pull of Santa Grandpa
with that personality of yours?
You're trying really hard.
Of course.
The accused is trying to get away...
So, being Santa isn't a big deal.
I can do more.
What more?
Can I see it next time?
Of course...
It's rare to have an autopsy and
organ transplant at the same time.
There's a lot if you search for it.
Did you search everywhere?
I did.
I'm looking forward to it.
Yes, go ahead.
Welcome.
Hey, Jung Seungwon.
Myung Daegoo...
You work here?
You live around here?
Yes.
Can I have 10ml trash bags
and food recycling bags in 2L?
10 pieces each.
Are you running errands for your mom?
No, my parents passed away...
...and I take care of the house since
my brother is the house destroyer.
Charge me for this as well.
Does your brother come here often?
If a tall and normal-looking guy
who acts like a kid comes by...
...that's my brother.
Be careful.
Hey, Seungwon...
Yes?
Can you ask your brother
to meet with my father?
Your father?
You should get closer to Seungwon.
His brother is a prosecutor.
Who knows?
His brother may get your
father out of the prison.
Oh, about that...
He's going through a lot because
of an important trial right now.
I see.
Then, just pretend you didn't
hear anything from me.
I said something I shouldn't have.
I'm home.
You're home?
What's with the stool?
I was putting it away since I thought
I wouldn't need this anymore.
Then, we won't have enough
chairs for tomorrow's breakfast.
Tell everyone to eat at their own homes.
Why?
I'm tired.
It's uncomfortable seeing Prosecutor Jung.
Mom.
Mother, Mother, I peed on my own.
The pee just came out.
Really?
Good job.
I'm so proud of you, my prince.
Grandma will be here in 30 minutes.
Can you stay here by yourself?
Yes.
Chanho, there's so many
people we need to be thankful for.
There's so many people
that we're indebted to.
Yes, we should hurry and repay
them back for their generosity.
I'm fine now.
Hey, it's me...
Where are you?
I'm on my way to your
house for breakfast.
I'm sorry, but I think we'll
have to skip breakfast today.
Why?
My mom said it'll be difficult due to
her restaurant work for the time being.
Okay.
By the way, I found your portable charger.
What?
The portable charger that
you left in my car last time.
The red one.
Oh, that...
I'll give it to you next time I see you.
They said it's going to rain today,
so don't forget your umbrella.
Okay.
What are you doing here?
Were you waiting for us?
I felt like having brunch outside today.
Let's go.
I just want to eat at your place.
I don't like brunches.
You do like brunches.
Let's just eat brunch.
Let's go eat brunch.
What time's the trial today?
2 PM. Why?
Are you going to come and watch?
Of course. It's the final trial.
I have to watch and see if the slow
turtle can catch the rabbits.
Let's go.
Did you bring your umbrella?
It's going to rain today.
Of course.
Can you let go of this?
Attorney Lee disagreed to
the autopsy results, right?
Yes, so I have to interrogate
the doctor who conducted the autopsy.
I've never seen anyone
disagree to the autopsy results.
It looks like he's going to
point out the fault...
...for conducting the autopsy
after the organ transplant.
Yoobum is playing it so dirty.
Prosecutor Jung, let's go
to the trial together today.
I'll question the autopsy doctor myself.
Why?
I can't stand him playing it dirty.
Would that be okay?
Yes, I will feel so much
better if you joined me.
Thank you.
No, I'm thankful.
Why?
I'm so grateful for you these days too.
You're so good.
Did you write the autopsy
results yourself?
Yes.
According to the autopsy results,
what was the cause of death?
The cause of death is the exterior
shock on the brain of the victim...
...that led to excessive bleeding
on the arachnoid membrane.
The autopsy was conducted
right after the organ transplant.
How was that possible?
When the victim arrived at
the hospital right after the accident...
...he didn't have any other injuries
except for a cerebral hemorrhage...
...and several fractures.
And when we put him
through the CT and MRI scan...
...before the organ transplant,
the other organs looked perfectly fine.
So we excluded organ damage
as the cause of death...
...and conducted the autopsy right
after the organ transplant.
By any chance, is it possible...
...for the autopsy results to have changed
due to the organ transplant?
No, that's impossible.
Her strategy is good.
She wants to lead the game...
...by asking the same questions
before the attorney does.
According to the autopsy results...
...the right thyroid cartilage
was fractured.
What does this mean?
Thyroid cartilage is what
covers up the vocal cords like this...
...and can get fractured when
someone strangles another.
What if it got fractured because
the person fell by himself?
Like a person gets drunk and falls down.
It's rare for the thyroid cartilage
cannot get fractured from a simple fall.
But what if we assume that
the victim's thyroid cartilage...
...got fractured from the fall,
like the attorney's argument?
If that's the case...
...the fracture should've
occurred around the jaw...
...and cervical spine as well,
but it wasn't the case.
The most important part is that
we found blood stains...
...around the thyroid cartilage...
This means the stains only appear
when it's pressured by two hands.
This is also cleared.
Then, the autopsy results tell us
that the victim passed away...
...because someone strangled
his neck and was unconscious...
...and he fell down the elevator
door in that condition.
And this led to his death from
the exterior shock and bleeding.
Is this correct?
Yes, that's correct.
That'll be all.
Defense attorney,
please start the cross-examination.
Okay.
Now.
When was the victim
diagnosed with brain death?
It was on 2016, June 2nd at 8:30 AM.
Then, when did his heart actually stop?
It was on 2016, June 2nd at 5:17 PM.
There's about 9 hour difference.
Then, how did you decide
on his time of death?
When we were trying do
his heart transplant...
...we just recorded that
as his final hour.
Then, that hour must be the final hour
recorded on this arraignment, right?
Yes, that's right.
That'll be all.
What? He disagreed to
the evidence just to ask that?
I know...
What's he planning?
The victim's previous life...
...was meaninglessly taken by
a professor who he once admired.
But from the day of
the incident until today's trial...
...the accused denied the charge
and frequently changed his statement...
...in order to cover up his crime and
does not show any form of remorse.
According to
Section 1 of Criminal Law Article 250...
...I hereby request for a sentence of
10 years for the accused due to murder.
Next, defense attorney,
please deliver your closing argument.
The trial is almost over.
A testimony from a five year old,
autopsy after an organ transplant...
All of these are still inadequate
to prove that a murder occurred.
Watching this unstable reasoning...
...there's a question that I've
constantly wanted to ask.
Can we actually charge
the accused for murder?
What nonsense is he saying
with that much confidence?
According to the doctor's
statement of the autopsy...
...the victim died
on 2016, June 2nd at 8:30 AM.
And after 9 hours, at 5:17 PM...
...his heart stopped after
the organ transplant.
As we all know,
brain death is not considered...
...as an actual death
according to the criminal law.
The criminal law only recognizes
death when the heart stops beating.
The same applies for
the organ transplant laws as well.
We refer to the family of patient
who died of brain death as a family.
We call them a bereaved family...
...only after the organ transplant
has been completed.
No way...
If the victim damaged his brain and
died only after some time has passed...
...then, we can charge
the accused for murder.
But when the victim's brain died,
but his heart hasn't stopped beating.
During his organ transplant surgery,
his heart has stopped beating.
No.
The accused was not the one
who stopped his heart from beating.
We'll work on the main artery.
It's the doctor who stopped his heart...
...when he started
to work on the main artery.
So, the death recognized
by the criminal law was...
...not caused by the accused...
...but the doctor
who conducted the surgery.
No way.
Therefore, by the criminal law...
...the victim didn't die
because of the accused.
He died because of the organ transplant.
He really has the devil's tongue.
Therefore, we can't charge
the accused for the victim's death...
...and the accused...
...is pleading innocence for murder.
This can't be!
Wait... Who killed my son?
Sir, please calm down.
Wait, are they saying that
the doctor killed my son?
And not that man? Let me go!
No, that's all nonsense, so don't worry.
I'll escort him out.
Sir, please come with me.
Don't worry about this.
That prosecutor will tell them
that he's talking nonsense.
Please leave quietly.
He has to understand, so he can leave.
Imagine how he must be feeling.
Why can't we charge him?
If that guy didn't hit his son,
he would be perfectly alive.
The doctor didn't have to do the surgery.
Isn't that right?
Please leave.
She's really brave.
She says whatever she needs to say.
I'm sorry.
Prosecutor, are there any additional
statements you would like to make?
Shall I go?
No, I'll go.
Yes, I do.
Is the law really like this? Is it?
Does it make him innocent
because of the organ transplant?
No.
The law is not that loose.
There will be justice.
I shouldn't have agreed
to the organ transplant...
Because of me... Gosh.
Sir, this is not your fault at all.
After hearing the attorney's defense...
...the victim's father must be
blaming himself right now.
Goodness.
"Because I agreed
to the organ transplant..."
"...the person who killed
my son can't be punished."
"I did something good and
yet it turned out to be bad."
"The law is on the criminal's side."
I'm sure that's what he's thinking about.
The law cannot be like this.
Of course... Of course...
The victim suffered from brain
death because of the accused.
And as the attorney said,
after suffering from brain death...
...if days passed without
going through organ transplant...
...his heart would've stopped
and he would've died.
All brain dead patients end up that way.
But just because the organ transplant
jumped in between his death...
...can the accused be innocent?
It doesn't make sense.
Your son would've died even without
the organ transplant in few days.
He would've died even without the doctor.
But imagine if the incident where
Mr. Moon hasn't hit your son.
If this incident never happened,
would the victim have died?
It's quite simple to figure
who caused the death.
You can start by removing
the causes that led to the death.
Even if we remove
the doctor out of the equation...
...the victim would've died anyway.
But, the story becomes different
if we remove the accused here.
If the accused did not do what he did...
...the victim wouldn't have died
and have continued to live his life.
Your son's death was not
caused by the organ transplant.
And it's also not because of you.
The person who took away
your son's life is Mr. Moon.
You cannot confuse that fact.
The law shouldn't get confused by that.
The law has to clearly and fairly judge
who is responsible for the crime.
Just because the time of
the death applies new rules to the case...
...doesn't mean we can say that
the accused is innocent for his crimes.
Or else, that means we can
also say that there is no justice.
Also, for the sake of victim who gave
new lives to seven others...
...and the bereaved family members
who all agreed to the organ transplant.
...we can't let this trial go
in favor of the accused.
That's also not justice.
Please...
It is my sincere hope...
...that the justice and righteousness...
...of the courtroom...
...will be reflected
in this trial as well.
"Trial in process"
Prosecutor Jung.
Thank you so much for today.
No...
I'm the one who's thankful.
Thanks to you...
...I think I'll be able
to sleep comfortably.
Thanks.
Thank you so much.
Yes... Well...
Thank you, too.
Thank you.
Is it out of paper towel?
Yes.
Do you want to use my handkerchief?
It's okay.
I'm home.
Hongjoo, I got all your
blankets from your room.
I don't think that's all going
to fit in the washing machine.
I'm going to get it done
at the laundry place.
Mom.
Should I tell them not to come
tomorrow morning for breakfast again?
Yes.
Mom, I went to Jaechan's trial today.
After seeing the trial...
...I realized I've been
confused all this time.
About what?
Like you said, I thought
Dad died because of me.
Jaechan was also
shot because of me...
So, I was having a hard
time because of that...
But I realized I was wrong
after watching that trial.
I realized why I've been confused
all this time.
Dad died because of
the soldier who ran away.
Jaechan got shot because
Sookyung's father shot him.
Those things would've happened in
those moments even if I wasn't there.
Right?
Yes.
It was someone else's fault all along,
but I didn't know about it.
I was confused for a long time.
So...
...do you feel better now?
You don't blame yourself?
No, I don't.
Goodness. So much laundry to do.
Mother.
I mean, madam.
Hi.
You're doing laundry?
Yes.
Others may not know, but I know.
Your Dad's death and
Prosecutor Jung getting shot...
You're struggling because
you're blaming yourself for it.
You're going to continue to
blame yourself, suffer...
...and hurt yourself again and again.
That's what you'll probably do.
Madam.
There's something I'd like to say.
It's not Hongjoo's
fault that I got hurt.
Someone else shot me.
Hongjoo knows that's the truth, too.
-So, she won't be confused about it.
-And she won't be confused about it?
And that she won't blame herself?
How did you know?
Did you guys plan this together?
Did you hear from Hongjoo
that I'd be here and followed me?
No, not at all.
I just came here to do laundry
and happen to see you here...
Don't talk nonsense.
You don't do any chores and...
...yet you brought laundry here.
It's not natural at all.
I do a lot of chores, Mother.
No, madam.
I'm sorry for telling you to do
it this way and the other way...
But you can just call me Mother.
I'm sorry for being cold.
I know I shouldn't be doing this...
...but a person's heart can
be such a fickle thing.
To protect my kid,
I'm hurting someone else's kid.
I'm sorry for behaving
such a way as an adult.
I'm really sorry.
No, it's totally fine.
Then, will you forgive me?
Yes, Mother.
Thanks for being so good
to her and taking care of her...
No, I'm more thankful, Mother-in...
No, Madam...
Mother.
Come here.
It's a red car.
Whose car is this?
That scared me.
Prosecutor Jung, what are
you doing in front of my car?
Is this your car?
Yes, it's my car.
Wow, this is my dream car, red car...
Tell me anytime. I'll let you borrow it.
Really?
Yes.
Why?
I just checked and
Moon Taemin is charged.
Guilty of murder!
Seven years in prison!
He deserved
the maximum sentence of 10 years.
Seven years is quite a lot.
Good work. And...
...thanks.
You too?
Why is everyone thanking me?
Is a prosecutor doing his job
something to be thankful for?
Of course it is. But I'm just so thankful.
Yes. You said you'd let me
borrow it anytime, right?
Yes, why?
Then, now!
Now?
Wow.
-Wow.
-Wow!
The keys.
Can you take your day off?
If we leave now, we can see the ocean
for about an hour and come back.
It's the ocean!
Wow, it's the ocean!
It looks the same.
How did you find it?
I searched everywhere.
How is it?
Is it the same as the ocean
you saw in your dream?
Yes, it's the same.
Lies.
No, seriously.
It's the same.
It's prettier than in my dream.
You didn't have any dream.
I know you were lying.
How did you know?
I told you, right?
I'm a human lie detector.
And I can tell you were lying.
You kept telling me not to be careless
and you even came to see the trial.
Your face made it obvious
that you were lying.
Why didn't you say anything
even though you knew?
Why did we come here?
I knew you wanted to.
I can tell that you want me
to win the trial...
...and come to see the ocean.
I worked a bit for it.
Actually, I worked a lot for it.
Thanks for working really hard.
You don't want to go in?
It's too early.
I just want to watch.
Okay.
What a relief.
It's not that cold.
Why don't you come?
Stop lying.
Your lips have turned purple
because you're cold.
No.
This picture is seriously
worth your profile picture.
Really? Send it to me.
Wow...
How is this possible?
Really? How did it come out?
Let me see. Did it come out great?
This is so fake.
Wait.
No! No!
Stop!
It's a blessing to know what's
going to happen in the future...
That's what I used to think.
But this blessing takes away
the feeling of butterflies in our stomach.
It kills the will to challenge oneself.
"My death, a rainy day, green umbrella,
SBC Blue Team Uniform"
It puts out embers of hope.
Today around 5 AM, a 52 year old man...
...named Mr. Myung tied up
the underwear he was wearing...
...and hung himself while serving
in Seoul Goomin Prison.
A future I can't change.
"A rainy day, green umbrella"
A future that's been predestined.
Father...
In May 2015, Mr. Myung...
...was pointed as the culprit of
a serial killing using injections...
...that caused a stir and
was sentenced to life.
That's another form of despair...
...and makes me lose everything
by giving up...
...and repeating every day in vain.
Mr. Myung left a suicide note...
...saying he was falsely accused
and that the truth must be revealed.
Lieutenant Han,
is the walkie-talkie fully charged?
It's...
When did you start charging them?
What?
It's green. They're fully charged.
Okay.
I wish I gave her some time to
relax by bringing her to the ocean...
...and that this can be a shelter
from those days that are in vain.
I hope...
you had an exciting day.
"While You Were Sleeping"
Are you saying that the cop may
also be dreaming of us as well?
The person who killed himself...
...in the prison is the same person
as the injection murderer.
I'm going to interview
you guys starting today.
Us?
Can't you tell that they're lies?
I'm just saying I'll check it myself.
Hey, Prosecutor.
There's something huge in there.
-Victim...
-Victim?
The injection murder case...
That case...
Answer me!
He might be the accomplice
or the real culprit.
The dream started.
I see dreams of the person I saved.
"While You Were Sleeping"