"While You Were Sleeping"
"Lee Jongseok"
"Bae Suzy"
"Episode 6"
"Kang Chohee"
He's not picking up.
He must've sensed that we're after him.
Track all his calls
and credit card records.
Put him on the suspect
list if that doesn't work.
What do you mean, suspect list?
What wrong has my brother done?
Attorney Lee, you have
a guest waiting for you.
Who?
I'm not expecting any guests.
A new guest who came
in for the first time.
He came to see you.
I see.
I'm sorry, can you give me a moment?
Is this pro Bono?
No.
Or have I already fallen behind?
Just because I lost in
Park Junmo's case?
I don't think so.
Then, why do I get such a client?
You should talk to him first.
There must be a reason why he's here.
Okay.
Hello, I'm attorney Lee Yoobum.
What's your name?
I'm Kang Daehee.
They sent me here when I requested a
lawyer who also was a prosecutor before.
Yes, that's correct.
Have a seat.
I don't accept just any cases
because I meet with them.
I'll listen to your case and
decide if I can work on it or not...
Pardon...
I'll give you as much money you want.
I don't place my bets
after looking at the pot.
I look at my chances
before I place my bets.
Talk to me.
How can I help you?
It's so unfair.
I got into a big car
accidentally recently by mistake.
And I lost by younger
brother in that accident...
The police accused me of
faking it all for his insurance...
...and even issued a warrant
to arrest me...
Did the warranty state that
you killed him on purpose?
No...
I haven't seen the warrant yet.
I left right before the police arrived.
Then, you ran away when you don't
even know what the warrant says?
No, it's not that...
Well...
If I was still a persecutor,
it means you made a big mistake...
But don't worry.
I'm an attorney now
and to keep the ethics...
...I can't say a word about
what you just said.
If you want to live,
you have to lie to a prosecutor...
...but to me you have to tell
me honestly what you want.
What you are doing to me now is
like shoveling sand against the tide.
I mean...
...you have to be honest with me so
that I can fix whatever is going on.
Isn't that right?
Did you kill your brother?
Yes.
Um... what I want from you...
...is to make me innocent...
...during the trial.
The criminal who killed his brother
going after his insurance money...
When are you up?
It's coming up.
Reporter Nam Hongjoo reports.
Seoul Han River District Prosecutor's
Office sentenced life imprisonment...
...to Mr. Kang, 37 years old,
for murder and fraud in the final trial.
Mr. Kang has intentionally killed
his younger brother and sister...
...for accidental death benefits that
were put since June 2015...
...and was imprisoned and
prosecuted for the murders.
This is Nam Hongjoo
from SBC news.
Seoul Han River District
Prosecutor's Office didn't do it.
It was Prosecutor Jung who prosecuted him.
So, is it unfair?
Well, no...
Not that it's unfair,
but you just left out a word.
Really?
I was going to comfort you
if you thought it was unfair...
Now that I think about it,
I think it's a bit unfair...
Tell me.
What's so unfair?
What the heck!
What the...
Why are you on my bed?
I came in to wake you up and
you're the one who pulled me.
You were saying that it was
unfair and pulled my arm...
You should've turned on the lights.
You're such an easy man.
Gross.
What am I saying?
Right?
You don't even know what you're saying.
That's because you're the one
who's wrong and you're ashamed.
Be quiet.
Cereal for breakfast?
Or should I make ramyeon?
I wonder why you want to
suddenly make breakfast for me...
I don't know if I may owe you again.
If something bad happens,
please protect my daughter.
Never mind.
I'm going to have breakfast
next door from now on.
From now on?
Every day?
The lady next door wants
to make breakfast for us.
Her breakfast is so good.
You talk as if you've had it before.
Of course I did.
Without me?
When?
Yea, last time without you.
I don't like you for many
different reasons today.
Stop.
Wolverine.
Seriously, stop.
I don't like it...
Mom.
Where's the razor?
Mom, why do I have so much leg hair?
It grows so much within a day.
The growing speed of
my hair is like the speed of light.
And my armpit hair...
Okay...
Hongjoo, say hi.
We're going to have
breakfast together from now on.
And the armpits...
I mean, the razor is next to the shampoo.
So, you can look for it there.
Okay.
Welcome.
Hongjoo, you're quite moisturized.
My eyebrows are gone,
half gone, like Mona Lisa.
Half of these should've
been on my eyebrows.
Wow, enjoy.
Hongjoo has such a neat and
tidy personality...
...that she won't
allow one strand of hair on her leg.
I see.
You have breakfast like this every day?
Jaechan, this is just a regular course.
Last time, she made five-spice
sliced steamed pork.
The shabu shabu you made
last time was seriously the best.
Nice.
Then, I'll make it again next time.
Welcome.
Mom. You should've told me
we were having guests over.
I did.
You must've not heard me
since you had the music so loud.
It's okay.
Everyone's like that at home, right?
No, not to that extent.
Stop lying.
My brother doesn't look
like a human being at home.
I know how your
brother looks like at home.
-You saw him?
-How do you know?
I've seen your house
in my dream many times.
You go to work without washing
your hair for many days, right?
That's right.
I'm scared something
will come out from his hair.
You take your clothes off everywhere...
...and never put
them in the washing machine, right?
Why do you use the bathroom
with the door open?
That's right.
What's worst is that after he's done...
-He doesn't even flush.
Wow, seriously amazing...
How do you know
everything through your dream?
I've been having a lot of
dreams of your brother lately.
I don't mean to but end up
looking inside your house a lot.
Who's going to clean this up!
A prosecutor is beating me up.
It's a scene nobody should miss,
so stop being so coy.
I haven't said a word about other things
to keep your dignity...
...but should I say some more?
Hey, Nam Hongjoo.
What!
I admit.
Let's stop.
Let's eat.
Eat.
I've already seen everything,
so just behave as you were.
Don't pretend to be neat...
Your brother will talk trash about you.
Are you upset?
What are you doing? That's your bus.
Aren't you getting on?
No, I'm not.
Why not?
I have to drop you off at your work first.
Cling onto me, ask me to take
you around and protect you.
I'll try to do it.
Well... if it makes you relieved,
I'll give it a try.
That was real.
It's for real.
I told you it's for real.
It's here, let's go.
What are you doing?
You're going to be late.
"City of the Blinds"
Two boxes of business cards?
All the people in the prosecutor's
offices were changed while you were gone.
Two boxes may not be enough
if you're going to visit them one by one.
Okay.
It's starting for real now.
I'm going to watch what
kind of items you bring in.
Police, prosecutor, firemen, and patrols.
What they are investigating
and what's their top list.
You must be aware
of every little detail, okay?
Even the patrols?
You don't want to?
No, I love it.
I feel like I've gone back to
being a freshman and feel young.
Shall I report to you every
two hours like I'm a freshman?
Sounds good.
Wow, I give up.
This mouth of mine...
Welcome.
Hello, we're here again.
Hongjoo isn't here.
It's fine, we didn't come for Hongjoo.
We came for pork belly.
I haven't had breakfast, so I should
eat some pork to keep me going.
And we don't need any cash receipts.
A tough man won't ask
for a bill or a coupon stamp...
We don't ask for such things.
We're done with those.
What's wrong with
asking for cash receipts?
It's a fair trade that
a police officer should be aware of.
Hey, what should we do?
Did I make another mistake?
Please...
Han Wootak.
I mean, Lieutenant Han,
nice to see you here.
What are you doing here?
You two know each other?
You got hired?
No, I got my old job back.
I can't be pretty all my life,
I have to work.
SBC reporter?
You were a reporter?
Wow, I'm sorry I didn't know.
How do they know each other?
I don't think they do...
What?
Do they know each other very well?
Hey, don't you have anything
on the top list in your office?
I have to report to my senior,
but I have nothing to report.
Oh my...
I need something to report.
Yes, it's Nam Hongjoo.
I'm here at the third patrol.
Something to report?
We have a case of a street cat
that was murdered.
Yes, a street cat was killed.
-It's a serial murder case.
-Yes, it's a serial murder case.
The number of cats
that's been killed so far...
Around 100...
100?
Over 100 cats.
Yes, sir.
Okay, sir.
I'm here, sir.
Welcome.
Hello.
I don't see Prosecutor Shin.
She went to monitor
the death benefit fraud case.
Death benefit fraud case?
Yes, it's relevant to you as well.
With me?
Yes, I was here during
your duty last time.
There was a car accident then,
so I went to examine it.
Yes, I know.
But, it wasn't a simple car accident.
Shall I conduct an autopsy?
No, no autopsy.
The brother was against autopsy,
so I had no other choice...
...but to give an order to pass
the deceased one to his family.
But after I investigated it,...
...the guy put 2.7 billion won
on the deceased's insurance.
I had the creeps after hearing that.
He cried so hard for the dead.
But he killed them and
pretended to cry like that.
He probably gave it all on
his acting for the 2.7 billion.
Still, how could he
kill a person for money?
His brother at that.
Mr. Kang has registered his
younger brother and sister under...
...a big death benefit insurance
and faked a car accident...
Is the accused's last name, Kang?
Yes, how do you know that?
That's right, it's Kang Daehee.
Is the case where he killed both
his younger brother and sister?
No, just his brother. His sister is alive.
His sister is alive?
Yes.
But how do you know
that he has a younger sister?
You saw his file?
No, I may have been
confused with another case.
Do you think there's a chance for
him to be innocent for this case?
No way.
He already confessed that he
killed him while we were investing.
Not a denial but a confession.
So, why did you conduct
another direct investigation then?
His attorney is Lee Yoobum.
Hi, Prosecutor Shin. Hi, Pilsoon.
Hi.
You must've prepared a lot for the trial.
Of course I did.
You should politely say
no at this moment.
It's only polite to prepare a lot
when I have to go against you.
Today's trial is a bit unique.
Pick one.
Yes, a female jury and all
the panels are women as well.
It's the first time for me to see
two women juries to be in a trial.
It doesn't feel quite right.
But it should all be fair, right?
What doesn't feel so right?
Pardon?
What's wrong with female juries?
By any chance...
...are you the Assistant Chief Jury,
Kim Jooyoung?
It's nice to meet you.
No, it's not that it doesn't feel
quite right but it's rather unique.
I'm used to seeing male juries...
Exactly.
When all jury were men,
you didn't say anything about fairness.
So, why mention about
fairness when they're all women?
Aren't male jury more likely
to be unfair than female jury?
I don't really understand what you said.
That's true.
If all the jury were men...
...being fair should not
only apply to women...
I'm sorry.
It seems like she
already doesn't like you.
Yes. I may lose to Prosecutor Shin today.
That has nothing to do with
what just happened.
"Trial in progress"
You said you place bets after
seeing the chances, right?
Yes.
What are the odds?
99 to 1?
We're one?
All rise.
Straighten your shoulders.
We're the 99.
The chance of being
guilty is 99 percent, of course.
I deducted 1 percent since
Yoobum is the attorney.
In fact, it's 100 percent guilty.
Do you really think there's no
chance for him to be innocent?
What's wrong with you?
Is there something you know?
We just have to be careful
with every single thing...
You're not being careful,
but you're stepping all over my heart...
...so you can walk over me.
Hey. I'm in big trouble if he's innocent.
I feel uneasy especially since I haven't
even dissected the deceased's body.
Stop sighing...
We can do it.
Prosecutor, please state
your point to the charge.
Sure.
The accused Kang Daehee,
registered his siblings as insurant
since June 2015 and set himself,
as the beneficiary for over 31
life insurances and has been paying over,
...4 million per month for insurances.
His income source had gone wrong
when his stocks investments...
...went wrong and to get the death
benefits from the insurances...
...he decided to falsify a car accident in
which his brother ended up being killed.
On March 28 at 9 PM...
...the accused was on his way
to send his brother home ...
...and killed his brother by intentionally
driving into the entrance of the tunnel.
Also, the accused has reported false
information on the fake car accident...
...to seven insurance companies
and claimed total of 2.7 billion.
The accused, based on Criminal Law
Article 250, is charged with murder.
Criminal Law Article 337-1 adds...
...fraud to his crimes and shall
be prosecuted based on these.
Attorney Lee, do you admit to the charges?
No, I plead not guilty
to the entire charges.
The accused...
...claims innocence to all charges.
Kang Daehee is claiming
innocence to all his charges?
Yes, I was worried that he'd
beg for mercy but I'm glad.
It's easier to prosecute now.
Yoobum is being
reckless this time.
It's a confession case,
so why bother flipping it around?
Well...
Don't you think Attorney Lee
made him confess for a reason?
They tend to investigate less
when a confession is made.
Prosecutor Jung, what's wrong with you?
You said something
like this last time as well.
Well...
It sounds quite reasonable this time.
Confession could've been a strategy.
They investigate less and
can prove better in the trial.
You think that way, too?
Put your heart down.
Chief Park.
Why are you praying alone?
Let's all pray separately from now on.
Prosecutor Shin, don't ignore his advice.
Yes, sir.
Prosecutor Jung.
Thank you for your advice.
I thought those advice can only be made...
...by those who have
over 20 years of experience.
But it's only been few months for you.
So, how could you possibly
give such experienced advice?
I really want to learn.
That was a compliment, right?
What compliment?
She said that to make me look bad.
Why do you twist her words around?
Maybe she really wants to learn.
She meant that I crossed
the line and should stop.
How do you not understand?
What's your score in literature?
Why are you getting mad at me?
My goodness.
I dream a lot about
your brother these days.
So I get to see a lot of things
that are happening in your house.
Yes, I shouldn't get mad at you.
What's wrong with you suddenly?
Is someone here?
Lift up your feet.
I need to vacuum there.
What's with your hair?
Your hair's messy at home.
You put on BB cream as well?
I didn't.
No.
You did.
Why would you put BB cream at home?
Is it because Hongjoo's dream?
Be quiet, you little punk.
I'm right.
That's why you're cleaning and...
...wearing clothes that you
usually don't wear at home.
You're really putting on quite the show.
This little punk.
I've already seen everything,
so just behave as you usually do.
Don't pretend to be neat and have
your brother talk trash about you.
She dreamed about this already...
She's like a human surveillance camera.
This is crazy.
I'm seriously getting dizzy.
Okay.
What's happening to the Sangbu-dong
street cat serial killing?
Any update?
After investigating, it was only
one to two cats few months ago.
But now it's gotten much more.
And now there's over
100 cats that's been killed.
Who's the perpetrator?
None of the cats have external
bruises but all died of poison.
Police thinks there's one suspect.
Keep reporting on that
until the suspect is caught.
Do I have to follow such a case?
It's something like the TV show
Animal Farm should show.
Really?
I think there's
possibility of a story here.
It's like a pre-warning before
the serial killing and...
...one of the typical signs
is animal abuse.
It's like a rehearsal before
the actual serial killing on people.
He's someone who killed over 100 cats.
Am I the only one who's curious
who the suspect is and...
...what kind of traits he has?
That's right, I'm also curious.
He has a point.
What's wrong with everyone?
I also want to cover humans and not cats.
Jaechan...
If you've seen this
moment in your dream...
Why is...
...Kang Daehee...
A guy named Kang Daehee
attacked me in your dream?
What case are you're covering these days?
Anything dangerous or something
that may lead to grudges?
Anything relevant to
death benefit insurances?
Not at all.
Not human, but I'm covering street cats.
Street cats?
Yes, someone killed the cats with
potassium and they told me to cover that.
That's a relief.
That's not a relief.
They treat me like a complete freshman
because I just got back to work.
It's still better than
something dangerous.
What's with your reaction?
Aren't you worried that I had
a dream of you dying as a reporter?
This could be the dream.
At least it's not this dream.
Was that place...
...in the mountain?
No.
By any chance,
did you see a green umbrella?
No.
See?
It's not that.
It's okay as long as it's not that dream.
And I let go of my worries and fears...
...when I crossed the road
holding your hand.
Otherwise, I can't be a reporter.
You've changed.
Thanks to you.
Kang Daehee is in trial right...
...and a smart prosecutor named
Shin Heemin is in charge of it.
So, he won't be free.
No need to worry.
However, you have to
promise me one thing.
Promise?
So annoying...
I hear it's bad news when records
are spilled before the trial...
It could've been worse.
This is all because of Prosecutor Jung.
Him and his big mouth...
Jeez. I'm sorry for my big mouth.
What?
You want to see the record and criticize?
I know you'll do well today,
but please do your best.
Are you teasing me or what?
How ridiculous.
I'm sincerely cheering you on.
You have to make sure
that Kang Daehee is acquitted as guilty.
Okay.
Gosh. Are you okay?
You did that on purpose, right?
No, I didn't do it on purpose.
I'll help.
Go.
Are you okay?
No, I'm not.
Prosecutor Lee, what are you doing here?
I had some free time...
You came because you were nervous
about him not being charged, right?
What do you mean?
I believe in Prosecutor Shin.
On the day his brother died,
accused Kang Daehee...
...has searched the following
things on his phone.
We can tell his motives...
...on why he killed and his paths
when we link all his search words.
He has intentionally gone to Domun Tunnel
for the accident to kill his brother...
...and has looked for any
witnesses at the crime scene after that.
And he was scared that
his motive will be revealed...
...if the body goes under autopsy,
so he researched on how to avoid it.
He hurried with cremating
the dead body and has searched...
...for how to claim insurance for
the deceased during the funeral.
And finally...
...he has claimed 2.7 billion in the price
of his dead brother.
What a trash.
It becomes a crime scenario
if you assume that he killed him...
...and link all these key words.
However, if he didn't kill him
and we look again at these search words...
...it will paint a different story.
The accused didn't want to ruin...
...the dead body and wanted to pay
respect to his beloved brother.
That's why he searched
how not to go through autopsy...
Due to financial reasons...
...he couldn't hold the funeral for long,
so he had to shorten the funeral...
...as it costs less and searched
for how to cremate the body.
Although he was sad
due to his brother's passing...
...he was having a hard time
trying to survive without money...
...and came to think of
the insurance money.
He thought of the insurance...
...as the last gift from his brother.
Thus, the reason why he searched
for all these keywords.
This also makes sense, right?
That makes no sense.
His difficult financial status has won
over his sadness of losing his brother.
So, how could he pay 4 million monthly
for the insurance?
The accused has often paid
penalties for not wearing seat belts.
But on the day of the accident...
...he was the only one who
wore his seat belt...
...and his brother wasn't wearing it.
Could this have been a coincidence?
After paying many penalties for it,
he has worn it that day.
Then, how do you explain how he still
paid penalties even after the accident?
That's right.
I'm sorry.
Sleepy?
Yes, I'm going to get some sleep.
I had a lot of work today,
so I'm a bit tired.
Yes, get some sleep.
I'll wake you up when we get there.
As you can see...
...the dashcam in the car was moved
to face the sky instead of forward.
What was it that he didn't want to record?
If he didn't want to record it,
he should've removed it.
As you can hear form the recording,
the brothers were in a good relationship.
There's one thing that's strange.
Why didn't you want an autopsy?
There's no special reason...
...to skip out on the autopsy
if it was a car accident.
There is...
...a reason.
What is it?
He didn't die from the accident.
You were the first to arrive at
the scene of the accident, right?
Can you describe how
it was during the rescue?
The driver's seat was okay.
But the passenger's seat
was completely destroyed...
...because it ran into
the entrance of the tunnel.
So I couldn't really tell the condition.
The driver, the accused who's sitting
over there. Was he conscious?
Yes.
Did he ask to save his brother
who was at the passenger's seat?
No.
That's all.
I have read the medical record
and it said he didn't bleed much.
The accident was big
enough to completely destroy...
...the passenger's seat and
yet he didn't bleed...
Doesn't that sound odd?
The accident is big and
yet he didn't bleed much.
What do you think it means to
have big scars but not much blood?
That's possible when the scar
is made after the death.
Your honor.
The attorney is asking questions
based on hypothetical statements.
I'm only making a point that the victim
did not die from the car accident.
The victim didn't die
from the car accident?
The claim by the prosecutor...
...that the victim died in a car
accident sounds more like...
...a hypothetical statement
than the truth.
Then, please provide
evidence to your claim.
The victim's body temperature
right after the accident was 35C.
Isn't this too low to be considered
as a temperature right after death?
Yes.
It usually drops 1 degree per hour
after death...
This means that the differences
were more than 1.5 Celsius.
Which means that it has been more
than one hour since his death, right?
Yes.
It was recorded that
his oxygen level was 0.
Is it a normal reading right after death?
No, not usually.
It should take more than
an hour to reach zero.
All the records here prove that...
... the victim died
before the car accident.
This is not a hypothetical statement.
"According to Attorney Lee, the victim
didn't die from the accident."
"He died before the accident."
Attorney Lee is claiming that...
...the victim didn't die
from the accident.
That he died before the accident.
Really?
Yes, didn't you go to examine as well?
Yes.
You said it was a simple car accident.
It was a simple car accident,
but the victim didn't bleed much.
He's holding on to that.
Whether he died from
the accident or not...
...the victim was killed for
the benefit insurances, right?
No, if that's the case,
everything changes.
My gosh.
Look, the prosecutor...
...already prosecuted him for killing
in the car accident, right?
If this was not a car accident
that killed the victim...
...no matter how the victim died,
this trial will state an acquittal.
Let's just say that the victim
died of something else.
The victim was in the car...
...before and after the accident and
it was only them in the car.
Then, there's only one person
that is likely to have killed him.
So how could that plead innocence?
He could've died of a heart attack.
On the day of the incident, the victim
had a tough day delivering mails.
And while sleeping in the car, the
victim could've died of a heart attack.
And after his death,
the car accident probably happened.
-It doesn't make sense.
-Not completely.
I personally would like to know how
the victim died in this case as well.
It really is a pity.
If only we went through an autopsy...
...either of us will have
a solid evidence by now.
However, neither of us
have a solid evidence...
...so any indirect evidences
should not have any contradiction.
However, the victim's body temperature...
...oxygen saturation level, and
statement from the emergency personnel...
...all contradict to what
the prosecutor said.
Of course, the incident...
...may give a thought that
accused killed his brother.
However, even if there is
a 99 percent of confidence hes guilty...
...and there is even 1 percent chance of
a victim's death by heart attack...
...the accused
needs to be deemed innocent.
If it wasn't the car accident,
then how did you kill him?
Potassium cyanide.
At first, the street cats
were making so much noise...
...so I fed it to the cats to kill them.
And the results were immediate.
100 percent success rate.
Why would you do that to your brother?
The car accident is not a guarantee.
I'll be in trouble if he
regains consciousness...
That's why I used
potassium cyanide poison.
I'll feel better
if it's completely guaranteed.
The police don't know this?
Yes.
Of course not.
I cremated the body before autopsy.
It's obvious that Kang Daehee
killed his brother.
But do we have to
accept that he's innocent?
We prosecuted him wrong,
so what can we do?
If it's not the car accident,
then what is it?
I know it doesn't matter now.
But why didn't you do an autopsy?
This is all because you didn't do that.
That's because...
All the doctors and police
said it was a car accident.
The deceased's family
was crying in sadness.
So how could we ask to dissect...
...the naked corpse when it was
a difficult thing to ask the family?
Everybody will find it hard
to make that request.
Can't we issue another warrant
on the day of his release?
He'll commit a bigger crime
if he's released like this.
What can we issue a warrant for
when we don't know how he died?
-Sir.
I don't want to release
the suspect either.
That doesn't mean we can...
...ignore all the laws and issue
a warrant on nothing and arrest him.
This is bad.
The suspect will be innocent if we
don't know how the victim died.
Han River District Court,
Criminal Investigation Department 2...
...will now announce the verdict.
2016, case number 2029,
to this murder case...
...the accused Kang Daehee...
... is  claiming that he didn't falsify
the car accident killing.
But is claiming that the victim
was dead before the accident...
...and he's denying on the charge
of murdering the victim.
According to the evidence that
the prosecutor has submitted...
...the accused has put a huge amount
of insurances under the victim.
Despite his difficult financial status...
...he has put in a tremendous
amount for insurance every month...
...and has maintained this
unreasonable amount of insurances.
He has also claimed...
...the death benefits during
his own brother's funeral...
...and facts subject to judgment
do exist in indirect presumptions.
However, in this case...
...we are unsure if the victim
was killed in the car accident...
...and we are also uncertain if
the motive of the accused is clear.
We still have many questions remaining
on this case.
With the above indirect presumptions...
...the charge does not have
enough evidence.
There is no direct
evidence to prove the case.
The charge to this case only applies to...
...when the crime has no other evidence.
By the later part of
Criminal Law Article 325...
...I hereby pronounce the accused
as innocent from those charges.
That dirty jerk.
I had to shake hands with such jerk...
You've gotten old, Lee Yoobum.
Yoobum.
What is it?
You followed me?
Kang Daehee is innocent of all charges.
The case is done so please tell me.
How did he die if the car
accident didn't kill him?
You know, right?
Please.
Tell me how he killed him.
I have to know that so that
I can issue a new warrant.
Why are you asking me that?
You have to find the answers.
Why are you asking me?
Yoobum.
It's over.
You're begging me...
...to give you the answer
when you've already gotten it wrong.
Kang Daehee, that jerk...
...put so much insurances
under his sister's name.
He would even kill her
if we let her go right now.
It's your fault if he goes out
like that and kills more people.
My fault?
Why is that my fault?
Even if he does kill more people,
that can't be my fault.
It's the prosecutor's fault who
couldn't give enough evidence!
So who told you guys to presume
it before you have the proof?
You should've had
the evidence to find him guilty!
I have done my part as an attorney
and if something were to happen...
...that's not my fault, but yours.
So, you guys handle it.
Why is he so obsessed
with Prosecutor Shin's case?
I shouldn't be saying this now.
But does Prosecutor Jung
like Prosecutor Shin?
It's something you really
shouldn't be saying now.
"Little Pup"
"Youngduk Crab"
Oh my, Prosecutor Jung, what's up?
You usually don't call.
Where are you right now?
I'm at the third Patrol Station
investigating street cats.
Everything's okay, right?
I wish it wasn't so that I have
something to report at least.
If something happens,
you have to call me right away, okay?
Okay.
Sorry, I kept you for long.
No, let's go.
I'll take you home.
I'm sorry but it's been
really quiet these days.
So there's not much to tell you.
Have you asked around?
Yea, according to kids...
...they saw some guy giving
chicken to the cats...
...but we couldn't conclude
that to a specific person.
Chicken?
I've also seen a man
feeding chicken to cats before.
Really? Do you know the guy?
Yes.
Why in the world would
Kang Daehee attack Hongjoo?
They have nothing in common...
All these records here prove...
...that the victim had died
before the car accident.
Someone killed the cats with potassium
and they wanted me to cover that.
No way...
-Mr. Choi.
-Yes.
I wasn't texting.
I was reading some spam texts.
For Kang Daehee's case,
when you examined the victim's body...
...was there a chance
that he was poisoned?
I don't know. It never crossed my mind...
What? You're scaring me.
Something crossed my mind
now that you mention poison.
The color of the blood.
The color of the blood?
Yes, usually the color
of the blood is blueish red.
But the victim's blood was
pinkish and closer to orange.
What does that mean?
That's the symptom for those
who are infected with that...
That thing...
The one used to
kill people in the past...
-Potassium cyanide?
-That's right, yes, potassium cyanide.
If they die from eating that,
the blood is pinkish!
Prosecutor Jung, where are you going?
Prosecutor Jung.
Chohee, you were here.
You must've been worried for me.
Chohee.
I was on your side.
It didn't matter
what the prosecutor said...
You know that I said you would
never do such a thing.
Right?
Of course, I do.
I came out safely thanks to you.
I went to your trial.
Why?
I told you not to come.
The voice from your dash cam...
That wasn't his voice.
Both voices were yours.
Sleepy?
Yes, I'm going to get some sleep...
I worked a lot today, so I'm a bit tired.
Okay, get some sleep.
I'll wake you up when we're there.
Daehee, did you really kill him?
Is this the place?
Yes.
I saw the owner from this place giving
pieces of chicken to the cats every day.
Really?
You stay here.
Call the police if something happens.
What?
Anyone here?
Sir, what's going on?
Excuse me... Are you okay?
Sir.
Wootak.
Run.
Hurry.
Do you have a phone?
No, it's at the store.
What should we do?
Hello, you can speak.
Where are you?
I told you to just go.
This is driving me crazy.
Promise me something.
Promise?
If something dangerous
were to happen to you...
...I can see it in my dream prior to it.
Jaechan...
If you happen to see
this moment in your dream...
Tell me so I can go find you...
...if you ever get stuck
in a dangerous moment.
Please...
Don't forget and come.
Tell me the time and the place,
so I know it in my dream.
Promise me that.
The rooftop of Soojo Building
at Sanggu-dong.
Today is April 11...
...10:12 PM.
Jung Jaechan!
Mr. Kang Daehee!
You are under arrest for poisoning
your brother to death.
You are under arrest for falsifying
a car accident to cover it up....
...and claimed false insurances.
"While You Were Sleeping"
Don't count on it.
My today could become your tomorrow.
Do you think it's your fault
that Wootak got injured?
If it wasn't for me...
...you wouldn't be
blaming yourself, right?
Crying and blaming myself briefly.
The daughter of archery gold medalist
Lee Sookyung, Go Hakyung...
...will be on the public wanted list.
Why are you here?
Help me.
I feel like I'm on the same team as
Prosecutor Jung this time around.
-Do you feel like you owe me a debt?
-Yes.
Can I be considered an exception?
Can't you stop thinking of repaying me
and be fine with everything?
Let's just say you repaid
all your debt with this.
What?
"While You Were Sleeping"