"While You Were Sleeping"
"Episode 14"
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
The ambulance is almost here.
Are you okay?
You look like you hurt your hand badly.
-That's not important.
-Gosh!
Why in the world did you
come to a place like this alone?
Why didn't you call me?
Well...
It was after your work hours,
so I felt bad to call you...
You should've called
even if you felt bad.
What would you do if something went wrong
when you ignored all our procedures...
...by coming out here all alone?
What did I tell you when
you executed the warrant?
What's the most important
thing in places like this?
My safety.
If you know that...
Why did you go alone?
You could've died...
...if I didn't show up today.
It didn't cross his mind that
it would be dangerous here...
Stay out of this.
Taking his side won't help.
I'm sorry.
It's the same for you too.
Why would you come here...
...when you don't know
who's going to be here?
Right, without any fears.
The ambulance is here.
Who do I need to go with
when there's two people.
Please take care of him.
He inhaled a lot of
gas trying to save me.
No, please take care of her.
Her hands were shaking
a lot earlier as well.
It's not shaking. It's fine now.
His internal injury is
probably worse than mine.
Hey, you're not okay.
No, I'm fine but you're not.
Are you okay?
What should I do?
Over here.
When you ignore the assistant
chief prosecutor's orders...
...and went to the site without
your inspector, you can become the victim.
You're destroying the neutrality
of the whole investigation.
Do you understand?
Yes.
How did you know I was here?
That's not the problem right now.
Just be quiet and keep this on.
This is there for you to breathe, but
it's also there so that you don't talk.
I'm glad. I'm so glad.
What a relief...
I'm so glad that you're both alive.
Thank you.
If you're thankful, then please listen.
Stop making me worry...
Hongjoo, we're going to
go over for breakfast in a bit.
I know, but there's a favor I need to ask.
A favor? What is it?
I inhaled so much smoke yesterday that...
It keeps coming out no
matter how much I blow my nose.
I can write something with my snot...
Well, Jaechan...
Hongjoo is here because
she wanted to ask for a favor.
Really?
Wait up.
Write with my snot...
Can I come back from this?
So disgusting...
Jeez...
I think he has a trumpet on his nose.
I don't need an alarm.
I wake up to that sound in the morning.
You're not shocked, are you?
You said you see him all messy
all the time in your dream, right?
Yes, it's fine.
I have ash coming out of my nose as well.
And your brother...
He's sexier when he's wet
coming out of the shower...
...and it makes my heart flutter.
I see.
You being this blind by love
could even be a disease...
My gosh.
Seungwon, you're going to be late.
Hurry up and wash up.
What favor do you need to ask?
I briefly told my mom...
...about the accident yesterday because
I don't want her to worry.
What did you tell her?
I just happen to see a fire when
I was passing by, so I called 911.
So when we eat later,
try to go along with it.
All right.
Shall we go then?
You can't be like that to me.
What do you mean?
You can't lie to me because
you don't want me to worry.
Whether it's bad things or a bad dream...
...you have to tell me
the truth and not lie.
Okay.
You still have that dream
you told me about?
The dream about
the green umbrella on a rainy day.
I don't.
It's been a while since
I last had that dream.
Really? You're not lying, are you?
I'm serious.
I'll tell you first if I have
that dream, so don't worry.
All right, then.
So, inside the phone were photos of
victims of the IV drip serial murder case.
Is this right?
Yes.
Then, is he related to Myung Yiseok?
Like an accomplice?
Could be.
I could find out if
I investigate a bit more...
...but he could be the real criminal.
The real criminal?
What evidence do you have to say that?
Other than the 11 photos of the victims...
...there were eight extra photos
in his phone.
What are you talking about?
Then, what happened to those eight people?
They're all dead.
-What?
Why weren't those
eight victims listed in that case?
They were not part of the same
hospital room with the case.
They weren't included because
they died after Myung Yiseok's arrest.
They died after he got arrested?
Then, he can be
the real criminal or an accomplice.
This means that the real killer
is still out there in the world.
There's also a threat that he
may commit another crime.
Are you sure that the man who
died in the fire wasn't the killer?
The person who died from the fire
wasn't the owner of the phone.
But he was just there
to get it for someone else.
But when the police
approached the person...
...who was looking for the phone,
someone else killed him with fire?
That means that it's a high probability
that the phone belongs to the arsonist.
And it's highly likely for
him to be the serial killer.
We can't make any assumptions.
This is a reinvestigation,
so let's be cautious.
Did you get the personal
information of the phone owner?
It's not easy to find the owner
due to it being a burner phone.
Hongjoo.
Weren't you in charge
of the case last year?
Yes.
Now, I want you two to step down
from the line and focus on this case.
Doohyun, go to the hospital and
find out more about the eight patients.
Hongjoo,
stick with the police and prosecution
to find out the phone's owner,
and if there were any problems
with the old investigation.
-Yes.
-Yes, sir.
Did you give the phone's backup
data to the digital forensic team?
Yes, it's here.
By the way, how did you know
so much about the case?
It's not your own case.
Well, I was the first to
recognize this as a case...
You're the victim of the arson case.
How can the victim investigate?
You'll be excluded if I were the judge.
Yes, I know.
Prosecutor Jung, stay out of this...
...and Ms. Son and
Prosecutor Shin should lead this case.
-Yes.
-Yes, sir.
Also...
...you and Prosecutor Lee should work
on reinvestigating the serial killer case.
Yes, sir.
But, if you do not follow my command
and run out to the crime scene again...
...I'll remove you from this team.
I understand.
All right.
We have two cases but only one suspect.
We'll work on it with two tracks...
...and have both teams have
a meeting every day and cooperate.
First, I'll contact the Yeonju office
to get the records of the case...
...and request to investigate
on the confiscated goods.
Okay.
Prosecutor Jung.
Are you going to be fine?
What do you mean?
Reinvestigating a closed case...
...means something in the previous
investigation had gone wrong.
Yes, I know.
You have to investigate Attorney Lee
who was the prosecutor for this case...
...and Mr. Choi who was the inspector.
I'm sure nothing went wrong.
But if we find a problem with
the previous investigation...
...Mr. Choi may face disciplinary actions.
Best case, dereliction of duty.
But in the worst case,
he may have to go through a trial.
It's hard to do it myself
since it's my right hand...
Thanks.
I'm really nice, right?
Yes.
Since I'm so nice...
...I wish someone like
Lieutenant Han fall from the sky for me.
Han Wootak also lived a good life.
I'm sorry.
Can you investigate this case...
...when it may put Mr. Choi in trouble?
"Catch Me If You Can"
There's so much record.
It's going to take several
days to look through all of this.
There's a lot because 11 people died.
Watch it.
Why would you close it so hard?
You could've just pushed a button.
Prosecutor Jung,
I've been watching from before...
...but let's be more careful
not to ruin the leather.
This color...
I should've asked for a separate car...
Get in.
You should get in as well. We'll be late.
Whose car is this?
It's my car that's kind
of like mine and not.
What?
I wish I was in the same team as you...
I miss you.
We're going to put all
the confiscated goods...
...and the trial records
in your office, right?
I'll put the investigation records
in my office.
That won't work.
Mr. Choi is in your office.
Put all of them in my office.
You're going to leave Mr. Choi
out of this investigation?
Of course.
We'll send him to the arson case team
and ask for another investigator.
I'm going to investigate
this case with Mr. Choi.
Mr. Choi has nothing to do
with the people who are involved...
...so he shouldn't be exempted
just because of our assumptions.
I said no.
Put these in my office.
Sir.
Mr. Choi is the one who thoroughly
investigated this case with Yoobum.
If any false records are found,
he could turn out to be a criminal.
Can we talk about that later?
What do you mean, later?
What if he wanted honor and
manipulated the case to his benefit?
-Sir!
-What? What about me?
I also don't want to suspect
Mr. Choi of any wrong doing.
But what can I do?
It's my duty as a prosecutor
to suspect everything.
It's our job to suspect even those
who we don't want to suspect.
You're right.
Right? Mr. Choi!
What I meant was I'm not saying
that you made a mistake or anything...
I know.
I shouldn't be on this case...
...and it's only right to leave these
in Prosecutor Lee's office.
What?
Mr. Choi also said that I'm right.
Prosecutor Lee is going overboard.
How can he do that to his partner?
So cold-hearted.
I know.
It may hurt his feelings...
But it's right to do that from
investigation perspective.
Are you siding with Prosecutor Lee?
She's not siding with anyone,
but just saying it's right to do that.
It's possible that a real
criminal could be out there.
Then, that means the old
investigation went wrong and Mr. Choi...
I know Mr. Choi very well.
And he would never...
That he would never do such a thing?
How can you be certain?
This is how you said it last time
during Hakyoung's case.
How is this the same as last time?
There's not much difference.
I thought what you said to me
back then was right.
I know that Mr. Choi is a great guy...
...but it's also true that there are many
suspicious things about the case.
-First...
-Let's talk about it later.
I don't want to hear it since
it'll make me lose my appetite.
Did Mr. Choi explain
how he knew about the arson...
...and came to the place?
No, but there are many ways to know.
What many other ways?
He could've followed me...
Then, he would've
stopped it before the arson.
Or he could've been walking by...
It was far from his usual path.
He could've seen the fire
from far away and came.
He came before the fire started.
Do you remember what Mr. Choi told me?
It's the same for you as well.
Why would you come to this place
alone not knowing who could be here?
He knew that you and I went separately.
He came before the fire started...
...but isn't it weird that he waited
to rescue you after the fire started.
So, what is it that you want to say?
Are you saying that Mr. Choi
started the fire with the arsonist?
He's not saying that.
Don't get suspicious
and just ask him directly...
Mr. Choi saved us by risking his own life.
How can I ask how he got there and
why he waited to save us after the fire?
You still have to ask.
You can't make assumptions and not ask
because you don't want to be rude.
That's even worse.
Are you mad?
What Wootak meant...
I know.
I know that he's right and I'm wrong.
I've contradicted myself and I know
that I'm not being a good prosecutor.
I know why you and Wootak
are being suspicious of Mr. Choi...
I know it in my head, but my heart...
I can't get my heart to do it.
I just don't like myself right now
and feel disgraceful.
I'm embarrassed that you
have to see this side of me.
Did we just have a fight?
Do you want to be alone?
Okay then, I think it's best
that I go alone today as well.
I'm leaving.
What?
I said I wanted to go alone.
Me too.
So let's just go alone together.
That doesn't make sense.
Where's the sentencing of Myung Yiseok?
Here it is.
You're here.
Where's Mr. Choi?
He went to the arson team.
What?
I'll go through the confiscations first.
Why are you telling me that?
He's throwing a tantrum towards me.
Just ignore him.
I don't think that Mr. Choi...
...is a person who would manipulate
a case for a promotion.
I see.
Prosecutor Lee.
Prosecutor Son wants
you in the video investigation room.
Me? Why?
She's currently lining up arson suspects
and needs a sidekick.
Lift up your face,
so we can see your faces.
Witness?
Yes, someone saw a man running
away on a bicycle from the scene.
I gathered whoever spoke to
Jo Inpyo that day and...
...has similar foot sizes of
the footprints from the scene.
It's that guy.
The guy in the far right
that's showing his teeth.
I'm certain.
I saw his teeth yesterday.
It was bright even in the dark.
You said the culprit was wearing a mask.
How did you see his teeth?
I said that?
That second guy...
Second guy?
Wait, is it the third guy?
What in the world...
Contrary to prior belief,
it's quite hard to purchase gasoline.
If consumers buy it from a container...
...we must record their
personal information.
Was there anyone who purchased
it on June 22nd or before then?
No.
How many gas stations do we
have around here within 5km?
It's over 40...
40...
Hello, Attorney Lee Yoobum.
It looks like you enjoy hot
coffee even during the summer.
It makes sense since
the air conditioner here is so strong...
...so you probably have to drink it hot.
Who is this jerk?
Welcome...
You guys sell Icy Hot patches here?
Yes, it's right next to
the toothbrush and toothpastes.
Thank you.
How do you feel right now?
Do you have anything to
say to the family of 11 victims?
Do you have anything to say to your son?
Please say something.
Please say something to your son.
How do you feel right now?
Please say something.
How much is it?
Are you reporter
Nam Hongjoo from SBC?
Oh? How do you know?
Did you see me on TV?
No, I've seen you in person.
"How do you feel right now?"
"Do you have anything to
say to the family of 11 victims?"
"Do you have anything to say to your son?"
I'm the serial killer, Myung Yiseok's son.
You stood out amongst all those reporters.
You were so persistent...
Hey, look...
Do you know that my father passed away?
She does, she also knows
that he felt wrongly accused.
You're Myung Daegoo, right?
You're Seungwon's friend.
We're reinvestigating your father's case.
Reinvestigation?
Yes. To see if the previous
investigation went wrong...
...or if he was wrongly accused...
We're going to go through
all the evidence again.
If anything unfair happened
in the previous investigation...
...or you have any evidence that
proves your father's innocence...
...then give me a call here.
I'll listen to everything.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Why the patch? Are you hurt?
Mom's shoulder muscles are aching.
Are you still mad?
Are you okay about feeling embarrassed?
Somewhat.
When will you stop being mad?
Soon.
Bye.
Thanks.
For what?
Earlier... That kid was really scary.
What's so scary about him?
He's only a high school student.
You know...
I was really scared, but now I'm okay.
Thanks to someone.
You were so cool earlier.
No need to feel embarrassed.
So hurry up and stop being mad at me.
It's uncomfortable.
Okay.
I'll stop being angry.
I'm not mad anymore. I'm fine.
I'm fine.
I'm sorry for being
suspicious of Mr. Choi.
I didn't want to suspect him either,
so I wanted you to ask him.
My suspicion only grows
if we don't do anything.
We don't need to be suspicious
if we heard it directly from him...
I wanted to believe in Mr. Choi,
that's why.
I know.
You had a driver?
You look like my age...
I envy you for having a driver.
Isn't that all thanks to me?
Who in the world is this crazy jerk?
You're the one who manipulated the
confiscations for Myung Yiseok's case.
Didn't you?
Attorney Lee.
You have a guest.
Who?
I thought it was someone else.
What brings you here?
There's something
I want to ask you for a bit.
Gosh. I should time it.
My time is quite expensive.
I just need three minutes.
Tell me. What is it?
"Lee Yoobum"
What is this about?
I know a suspect who is getting
investigated by a prosecutor...
...and the prosecutor keeps giving
out tips on the results to the media.
That's not right.
Who's the prosecutor?
The investigation result
is strictly confidential.
Even a suspect has his rights
and full rights to protection.
Does that suspect have his own
attorney who can stand up for him?
Why would the prosecutor keep
leaking information about the case?
It's obvious.
Either he doesn't have enough evidence
or he's not sure about something.
If he charges the suspect,
he may get acquitted...
...so he's probably
asking the media for help.
Like that Coke bubble from last time?
Yes.
You must've leaked information...
...during Myung Yiseok's case
for that same reason, right?
I thought you gave that information to
me because you had feelings for me...
But I guess you had that planned out.
Did you not have enough
evidence back then and...
...wasn't sure about something as well?
Why...
...would you suddenly bring up
a case that's been closed?
We received information that
the real criminal...
...other than Myung Yiseok is out there.
Our reporting department has made
a new task force to start covering it.
It's been three minutes.
I'll listen to both the attorney
and the prosecutor...
...for Myung Yiseok's case and
fairly release articles...
...so give me a call if you
would like to say something.
I'll come by any time.
You know my number, right?
Of course.
I'll be going.
Thanks for the tea.
Good bye.
Excuse me.
Who are you here to see?
I had something for Attorney Lee.
He forgot it last time.
Among all the confiscated items...
...the bottle with poison turned out to
be the finalizing evidence for the case.
And Myung Yiseok pleaded
innocent until the end.
What did he say about the bottle himself?
He said it doesn't make sense and
that the prosecutor manipulated this.
Manipulated?
We can manipulate your report card.
Yoobum, my father is a cop.
You can raise it a little
bit so that it's subtle.
Do you think a prosecutor
or an inspector...
...can manipulate confiscated goods?
That's really horrible.
Is such fabrication even possible?
Prosecutors can do it if he wants to.
Who went for the confiscations?
It's Mr. Choi.
If it was manipulated,
it's either Mr. Choi or Attorney Lee.
It's probably Attorney Lee
if it was manipulated.
Mr. Choi would never do that.
We're still investigating,
so we don't know that for certain.
Minyoung.
Yes?
Please contact general affairs...
...and get Mr. Choi's personnel
records and make copies of it.
If I get caught, I have to tell
the prosecutors about your manipulation.
Would you be okay with that?
Let's meet. Where should we meet?
9PM tonight, at your office.
You're here?
How's the investigation going?
Yes, it's going somewhere, I guess.
How about you?
Any updates on the arsonist?
This is harder than I thought.
You didn't see the arsonist that time?
I couldn't see since
I came after the fire started.
Do you remember what Mr. Choi said to me?
He knew that you and I went separately.
If you came after the fire started...
...how did you know that
Hongjoo and I went separately?
That...
I was just guessing.
How did you know that
we were going to be there?
That too, I just happened to pass by.
Mr. Choi.
It's just... How should I say this.
It's like I just received a telepathic
message that you were in danger.
I have such super power.
Perhaps it's because I went
to school near Miari Ridge.
What are you doing here at this hour?
I wanted to ask you something
about the arson incident.
Before that, here.
I've been trying to give it
to you but kept forgetting.
I found your portable charger.
The red one that you forgot in my car.
What?
Is this red one not yours?
It's mine. Red one.
Thanks.
What is it that you need to ask?
Didn't you say that you arrest
the guy who got killed by the arsonist?
Yes.
How many gas stations
have we visited so far?
36 gas stations.
Hello.
Aren't you going home?
I have a consultation with my client.
You can go home first.
Okay.
The prosecutors and police have
been looking for the arsonist for days...
...but they haven't caught him yet.
I've been digging as well,
but haven't found anything.
I came hoping for something at least.
Was there anything that stood out
when you arrested Jo Inpyo?
I'm not sure...
His clothes didn't look nice at all
for someone who had 10 million won.
Anything else?
And the bag that had cash...
What about the bag?
It's here on the 22nd
for 10 liter of gasoline.
He bought the entire bottle.
Yes!
I'm saved.
Did he buy it with cash or with card?
He bought it with cash.
Do you recall what he looked
like or what he was wearing?
I'm here.
Wow, your office is nice.
You should treat me out.
If I get caught, does that
mean you'll lose all of these?
Those who have a lot...
...can lose a lot...
That bag...
...looked like a woman's bag.
Woman's bag?
It wasn't a man.
It was a woman who came on a bicycle.
-A woman?
You sent those texts?
Yes.
You look surprised.
It's nice here...
I found out that we're the same age.
I can talk to you comfortably, right?
You have many awards too.
Let's sit and talk.
Shall we?
What's with the text?
Why were you looking for me?
Weren't you expecting it?
You're supposed to be smart.
No!
I have no idea.
You're not curious,
but you want to make sure.
It's just as I texted.
I've killed close to 20 people.
But thanks to you, I'm not in prison
and have been living a nice life.
I'm...
...really grateful for you.
If the real criminal is a woman,
then it must be her.
Ha Joohan, 34 years old.
Who is she?
She was a long-term patient at
the ward where the incident occurred.
A patient with Crohn's disease.
But she was also admitted in
the same room as the other eight victims.
So she wasn't on the list of
suspects because she was a patient?
That's right.
When all the patients were killed off,
Ha Joohan was also ill...
...and was categorized
as one of the victims.
But why would a patient
kill off other patients?
Because it's so unfair.
I had to remove my intestines...
...and stomach and had gone through so
many operations for so many years...
...but I didn't get any better,
but others did.
Plus, they got discharged
only in few days.
And they said they felt sorry for me...
You'll get better soon.
Cheer up.
They were all talking nonsense.
So you killed all those people?
Do you think that justifies what you did?
How can that justify what I did?
So I gave up everything and thought...
...if I get caught, I'll get caught.
If I get punished, I'll get punished...
That's what I thought...
But wait!
The prosecutor put someone else in jail.
And that was me?
Then, this crossed my mind.
This is the first time...
...I found hope in my life.
The person who gave me that
hope is you, Lee Yoobum.
And I hope...
...you can continue...
...to be that hope for me
until the very end.
So have you to put that
Ha Joohan on the wanted list?
Yes, but she hasn't come home
in a long time and has been...
...switching from burner phones
to burner phones...
...so it's been hard to trace her.
All her records of credit and
transportation cards,
are gone after the arson.
It means that she'll try to
run away until the very end.
She can try to run but that won't
last very long in today's world.
She's been on the run for over a year
in today's world after murder.
I'm sure she thinks it'll work this
time since it worked last time.
So Attorney Lee, make another
miracle happen like you did last time.
Give me hope. Okay?
I can't listen to this any longer.
When did I ever become
hope for a trash like you?
Why am I a trash?
Because you've killed people!
I can't do anything about that...
...since it's already in the past.
Of course....
...it's a sad thing.
But those who are living
need to continue their life.
In reality, who would benefit from
knowing that I'm the real culprit?
To the family of the victims,
Myung Yiseok is the jerk.
And that jerk already died...
...and that somewhat was a consolation
to them. But what if I suddenly appear?
It'll break their hearts.
And what about Myung Yiseok's son?
He'll go insane knowing
that his father is innocent.
And you...
What are you going to do?
Be quiet.
I...
...was really shocked
after hearing the news.
That the bottle of medication was
found in Myung Yiseok's office.
You were probably anxious.
It was obvious that
Myung Yiseok was the culprit.
But no direct evidence came out.
The media kept questioning
the prosecutor's competence...
...so you probably manipulated
the confiscated bottles...
...as Myung Yiseok's, right?
The bottles were already there!
Then, why are you calling me a killer?
If the bottles were found there
then Myung Yiseok is the killer.
So, why call me a piece of trash?
Tell me.
You understand now, right?
If I go down...
...you're going down with me.
Don't worry.
The only people in the world
that knows that you've manipulated it...
...is just you and me.
It was three of us until recently,
but I got rid of him.
You got rid of him?
You saw the news on
the container arson, right?
That was your doing?
Someone who knew all
about our story was living there.
He's not the type to talk...
...but unfortunately he got
involved with the police...
You were here?
Yes.
The door was open.
Aren't the gloves too much when it's hot?
It's better to be hot
than being in danger.
Yes.
I took care of your phone.
I threw it deep in Han River and
didn't say anything to the police.
So don't worry.
Inpyo.
Thanks.
I took care of all the dirty deeds...
...so you take care of the rest.
Family of the victims,
Myung Yiseok's son, you and me...
Let us all be in peace.
You know the meaning of conceal, right?
Now you understand, right?
If I go down, you're going down with me.
I received information that
the real culprit is not Myung Yiseok.
Don't worry.
The only people in the world
that knows that you've manipulated it...
...is just you and me.
Our reporting department has made
a new task for on Myung Yiseok's.
You know the meaning of conceal, right?
I have to figure something out.
"Notification on Electricity Maintenance"
"Starts at 9 PM on June 28th
until 6 AM on June 29th"
You were thinking for a long time.
What do you say?
Will you take on my case?
Before that...
...there's something that you missed.
What is it?
There are three people that know
about the manipulation aside from us.
Who else knows?
Would you like something?
You're the only one who
truly thinks about me.
You're so nice.
A lot of meat.
Right?
I'm so pretty and nice like this.
And yet why can't I get
a man like Lieutenant Han?
Don't be like that.
It's a punishment for
someone like Lieutenant Han.
So, Prosecutor Lee and
Prosecutor Jung think that...
...the IV serial killer case
was really manipulated?
Yes.
That case was investigated
by Attorney Lee and Mr. Choi...
Does that mean they both manipulated it?
Prosecutor Lee thinks that way...
...but Prosecutor Jung keeps denying
that Mr. Choi would do such a thing.
It's a case where over 10 people died...
...so if it comes out as manipulated then
many people will get be in trouble.
I think that's why Prosecutor Jung is
working even harder to protect Mr. Choi.
Do you have an interview?
Yes, I have an interview
with the victims' families.
You said you'll write fairly, right?
Can I have an interview
at my office tonight at 8 PM?
So many interviews.
Attorney Lee wants an interview.
He's the prosecutor in charge of the IV
serial killer case at that time, right?
Yes.
If there was a real culprit...
...that means there was
a mistake on the investigation.
-Go find out.
-Yes, sir.
Is it going to rain today?
No. The possibility of rain
is only five percent.
Ok, I'll be back.
Prosecutor Lee, here are
Mr. Choi's personnel records...
What about that?
Where's Prosecutor Lee?
Did Prosecutor Lee ask
you to make copies of that?
Yes.
He's seriously going overboard.
Can he find out if it's been
manipulated looking at this?
What? What is it?
You sure can.
"Ilyoo Police Station"
Mr. Choi used to be a cop?
Yes. That's why he's good
with crime scenes.
Ilyoo Police Station...
Why?
Do you know that place?
My father used to work here.
Did they work together?
Yes, they did.
Such coincidence.
No way...
Mr. Choi.
He's not here. He quit.
What do you mean he quit?
After lunch, he suddenly turned
in his resignation letter and left.
I tried to stop him saying
he should say bye to you at least...
...but he just left saying that
it'll be hard to leave if he sees you.
Prosecutor Jung,
I didn't manipulate anything.
Attorney Lee will probably
say the same thing.
It's obvious that both of us
will deny manipulating anything...
...so our plead won't mean anything.
So, don't worry about me or anyone else...
...and just focus on
reinvestigating this case fairly.
I'll also prove my innocence my own way.
Thank you for everything.
"From Choi Damdong"
This is too much.
How could he just quit like this?
What are we going to do?
"Prosecutor Jung Jaechan"
Is it Jaechan?
I'm sure he called
because of the investigation.
Is he bothering you over the IV case?
Probably since I'm being suspected.
It'll be hard for you to handle it on
your own when investigation gets serious.
My law firm will help you.
That makes me feel better.
Hyangmi, don't tell anyone about
him quitting. He didn't quit, okay?
No one at home is picking up either.
I'll visit his house.
Okay. Give me a call if you see him.
Hold him so that he
doesn't go anywhere else.
Okay.
"Mr. Choi, please call me."
Thank you for the food.
Take care.
Yes.
-I'll be going now. Keep in touch.
-Sure.
"12 missed calls"
"Nam Hongjoo"
Hello, Hongjoo. I'm in my office.
I told the front desk,
so you can just come up.
"Notification on Electricity Maintenance"
You're here.
Yes, what are you doing?
I was working on
the investigation for IV case.
It's hard to remember
since it was a year ago...
...so I thought it'd be helpful
to organize it into a file.
Please wait a bit.
Sure.
Are you going to give me
a copy of that file as well?
Of course.
I'm making it for you.
Is it for press release?
Are you sharing it with others as well?
No.
You're the first one.
I haven't contacted anywhere else.
I can't promise that I'll write nicely
even if I'm the first one to get it.
Of course.
Excuse me. We'll be conducting maintenance
soon, so all powers will be out.
I have a meeting with Attorney Lee.
I'll be right out.
It'll be brief.
No!
After she takes this,
she won't be able to breath...
...and die after 5 minutes
as if she's falling asleep.
Jaechan...
Did you hear everything?
Please...
Hongjoo, please...
Please pick up.
"Youngdeok Crab"
Is she the other one that knows about it?
Yes.
Hello?
I just had a dream of
Hongjoo getting kidnapped.
-Kidnapped?
What do you mean? Who?
That dream.
The green umbrella on a rainy day.
When is it?
10:30 PM, in 15 minutes.
Where is it? A mountain?
It's not a mountain.
It's the roof of Haekwang Law Firm.
"While You Were Sleeping"
There's a death that's been blessed.
Do you want to become a killer?
I just want to get rid
of a piece of trash.
Please hang in there.
There'll be a fair argument.
Why did you left me
alone at a time like this?
I want to take responsibility as well.
My carelessness is not illegal.
Don't just make assumptions.
Think towards what makes sense.
I think what I'm making more sense.
I'm curious.
I wonder whose words
will make sense this time.
"While You Were Sleeping"