"While You Were Sleeping"
"Episode 2"
Who is the owner of that white car?
That's me.
What about this silver car?
You can come to the station later.
You should go to the hospital first.
Yes.
Are you okay?
You should just look forward
since we're okay.
Excuse me?
Yes.
I believe in you.
Because it's me...
...I can believe in you.
How can you believe in me?
Excuse me?
What do you mean?
About what I said earlier...
When I said that you and your
mother will die because of Yoobum...
I don't think I'd
believe you if I was you.
I think I'd get angry also.
I'm not angry.
I sincerely believe that you saved me.
Why do you believe me?
But I'm not saying that I lied...
You had a dream, didn't you?
And that dream kept coming true...
Isn't that right?
How did you...
I have dreams like that too.
And those dreams always come true.
Like yours.
Are you okay?
You're sweating so much.
I guess she's feeling hot.
You're okay, aren't you, honey?
Yes.
You keep having those kinds of dreams?
Yes. I have many dreams like that.
Was that your first time for you?
Yes.
How much of the future...
So how much further into
the future do you see?
Ah!
I'm not asking you because I believe you.
There's isn't a set time.
Sometimes it's few months
into the future...
.. and sometimes
it's just couple of days later...
It can be just few minutes later too.
Has your dream ever been wrong?
No. Never.
There are dreams that
haven't happened yet...
...but they're never been wrong.
And you've never tried to change them?
That's why you're amazing.
Did I really save someone?
Yes.
Then what happens now?
I'm not saying that I believe you,
but if I did change the future earlier...
If we say that I changed the future,
what will happen?
I'm not sure.
When you stop the water
from flowing one direction...
...it will flow to a different direction.
Now that you stopped
an event that was to happen...
...the time will flow
to a different direction.
I really have to lose more weight.
Why were you so late today?
Don't even ask.
I almost died today.
I'm going to die if
I don't lose weight too.
Yes. I try to work on
my conditioning usually.
I practiced very hard.
Yes. Miss Park Soyun.
You are the first Korean to make it to the
finals of an International Competition.
Please tell us how you feel.
Many people were cheering for me.
I hope I can do my best so
that I don't disappoint them...
Mom.
Honey.
Madam.
Hey. Call 911. Right now!
-Honey.
-Mom!
What is this?
I didn't do this.
Is this the police?
I'm calling from Ivana Art Hall.
I'd like to report
a domestic violence case.
I said I didn't do this!
Mom. Please wake up.
Mom.
If the time flows
to a different direction...
...which way will it flow?
To a better direction or worse direction?
I don't know because I've never
changed the future before.
But what I'm certain is that...
...it won't look that much different from
the original future which was set.
Don't you think the differences
from both events...
...will be greater as more time passes by?
Do you know who I am?
Soyun.
Are you okay?
How did you get here?
Well.
I was just passing by.
You...
Don't say anything to our friends
about what happened today.
You didn't see anything.
Do you understand?
Okay.
I won't say anything.
Never.
Okay...
Thanks.
I'm certain that the time will flow to
a different direction from now on.
For better or for worse.
I guess so.
Now it's my turn to ask you.
Why did you come to save me?
It must've been just a dream to you.
Why did you go so far
as to destroying a car...
...in order to save me?
I'm not sure.
I guess you're not sure.
I think I get it right away.
What do you mean?
When did you start falling for me?
Excuse me?
I fell for someone? Who?
Me? I fell for you?
Bingo.
I think you have a misunderstanding.
You fell for me when I hugged you, right?
That's why you hugged me too.
That's because you hugged me...
...so I just hugged you
without any feelings...
You held me for such a long time for
someone who has no feelings for me.
You patted me too.
Do you usually hug women
who mean nothing to you?
No.
Then I'm not just any woman to you.
What is it?
What's so special about me?
What about me that attracted you?
Why...
Why does it have to mean that way?
That might not be it.
You hugged me after you came to save me,
so you must've fallen for me before that.
Then perhaps at the bus stop?
If not, maybe when you
brought me the rice cake?
Oh my goodness...
I'm right.
But you fell for me just
by hearing my voice?
That's amazing.
Wait...
Did you move across from my house
because of me?
This is driving me crazy.
"A good person"
Which police station?
Yes.
What's the charge and suspicion?
"A bad person"
Wow. I got goose bumps.
You moved across the street from my house
on purpose because of me, didn't you?
"A weird person"
"A good person, a bad person,
a weird person"
Are you okay?
Wake up, Jaechan.
You're late. You're late.
You're late.
Hey! Jeez!
You jerk...
What time is it?
Hey. Make me a bowl too.
You should make one yourself.
I'm troubled also.
You're acting mysterious.
Do you have senioritis or something?
Jaechan, it's...
Don't say anything to our friends
about what happened today.
It's nothing.
What is it? Now you're into
mysticism or something?
Anyway, what's going on with you
and the woman across the street?
Are you dating her?
You want to die, don't you?
You're bored with living, aren't you?
Why? You were so worried about her before.
You even destroyed your car to save her.
Mom. I think that man is
head over heels for me.
Which man?
The young and handsome guys
who moved in across the street?
My gosh.
Then what about that lawyer, Yoobum?
Mom. Don't even talk about that jerk.
He would've framed me
so that he could live.
So you're going to break up with him?
Then how can I keep seeing him?
He could've let you and I die.
Then you're going to start liking the man
across the street from now on?
No.
I'm just saying that
I'm going to do what's right.
Do what's right?
What do you mean?
Jaechan saved your life and mine.
I have to consider it as repaying him back
for his kindness for the rest of my life.
Isn't that the right thing to do?
How are you going to repay him
for his kindness?
I can tell by looking at him that
he can't make a move on women.
What can I do?
I'll have to accept him.
Don't you think so?
You should think carefully.
You might be repaying him with
vengeance rather than kindness...
Vengeance?
That's nice too.
Just like Romeo and Juliet...
That's exciting.
That woman is crazy.
She said that I fell for her.
She's delusional and snobby.
A person like that has to go see a doctor.
The have to make a law that a person like
that has to wear flowers in her hair.
That way people can
avoid people like that.
It was so unfortunate
to meet someone like that.
You said so.
She looked so sad in your dream.
I'm not sad for her.
No. I'm scared of her.
I think I saved her because I was scared.
No. I didn't save her.
The dream was nonsense,
so don't even bring it up anymore.
People will say that I'm crazy.
Yes.
Yes...
Who could it be at his hour?
Oh?
It's the woman from across the street.
What?
I'm Nam Hongjoo who
lives across the street.
Yes. What is it?
Oh my...
I wonder who has such a nice voice.
Let me see your face. I'm curious.
-What's wrong with her?
-See? She's not in her right mind.
She has to put flowers in her hair.
I can hear everything.
I made someone rice balls.
I wanted to share some with you.
Hello. Miss Nam Hongjoo.
Yes.
I can't believe the story
about the dreams.
So I didn't save you,
so there's no need for you to repay me.
I'm going to turn down the rice balls too.
She should've understood, right?
You can't believe it?
I totally get it.
"Flower"
Hello.
Sparrows are chirping.
Chicks are cheeping.
A tall man with long
arms will get it out for you.
His name is Jung Jaechan.
Thank you. Mr. Jung Jaechan.
Welcome.
In three minutes, a tall man
with long arms will be here.
He's wearing a beige color coat.
When he comes...
-I'd like...
-Your order is an Americano...
...with double shot
of hazelnut syrup, right?
Yes. That's right.
I'll charge your card.
"Kiyoung Station"
Do you know each other?
-No.
-Yes.
Should I change seats with you?
-No. That's okay.
-Thank you.
It's me, Nam Hongjoo.
I live across the street from you.
I know.
You have a lot of questions
right now, don't you?
You must be wondering if I followed you...
...but I was on the train before you.
So you don't think so.
It's too strange for
it to be a coincidence.
Am I right?
Do you know how to read minds too?
I did follow you.
Because I saw you going
to work in my dream.
I saw the balloon
getting caught in a tree.
I saw you order coffee.
I also saw you riding
the train to work today.
I even saw which platform you
were going to take the train from.
I see the future in my dreams.
It's not nonsense.
So, you did save me and
I am indebted to you.
Right?
"This train is for Jang am"
Why aren't you answering me?
I came all the way here
to hear your answer.
That's right.
You'll need this later.
I don't believe in what you said.
You said you dreamt about me.
Why can't you believe me now?
It's not that I can't believe you.
I won't believe you.
Excuse me?
I won't believe it because
I don't want to believe it.
Even if I have another dream
like that I'll never believe it.
I don't care if someone dies in my dream.
Why not?
If I believe in it,
I'll have to save that person.
If I don't do it,
I'll be responsible for it.
I'll have to blame myself to no end.
How can I handle something like that?
Can you handle something like that?
No.
If you can't handle it,
you should ignore it.
Just consider it as bad dreams.
That would be better
for your mental health.
If you really want to change the future...
...you should look for
someone else other than me.
You're the only one I found.
I don't know why it has to be you.
You should look longer.
If there are two,
there might be three or four our there.
There's aren't anyone else.
It's just you.
Father.
I had a strange dream yesterday.
What dream was it?
One, two, three...
I dreamt that you died.
How did I die?
Did I bleed a lot?
I had to bleed a lot
for it to be a good dream?
Put more snap on your wrist.
One more time.
Your bus exploded in my dream.
It exploded?
How?
A soldier got on your bus,
but he had a gun and a grenade.
You brat. Do you think this is America?
That's not realistic at all.
I mean it.
He set off the grenade in
the bus so everyone died.
That was what happened.
Father.
Can you not go to work today?
That dream felt so real.
Is that right?
Then...
...I'll consider it if
you grant me my wish.
What wish?
My gosh!
I don't want to. I'll never do it.
It's not that big of a wish.
Why won't you do it?
You'll need this later.
Darn it.
The weather forecast is never right.
Good morning, sir.
Look who it is.
It's our newest prosecutor.
Yes. Did you bring an umbrella?
.
No. I'll go and get an umbrella from
the convenience store right away.
Sir.
Prosecutor Shin.
Where's your car?
My car isn't allowed to be
driven today under the law.
Did you bring an umbrella today?
-Of course.
-My gosh.
I'll take you all the way
to the office safely.
Yes. That'd be great.
Prosecutor Jung. What can I do?
I don't think I can take all three of us.
I'm fine, so you can just escort him.
Okay. Excuse me.
Let's go, sir.
Yes.
By the way, why is the newest
prosecutor speaking informally to you?
I think it's because
I was his junior in school.
What happened at
school doesn't matter here.
He needs to respect
the order in our office.
I don't think he understands things.
I know.
Our newest prosecutor
has a long way to go.
I'm sorry.
I'm a little late, aren't I?
It started raining suddenly.
You went too far this time.
I looked at your wife's examination record
and saw that you broke six of her ribs.
Our colleagues went through
a lot to get rid of the CCTV footage.
I know that they went through a lot.
That's why I paid them each with
a watch for their time spent.
It will be complicated if it
becomes a charge of injury.
So, I'll speak with the hospital and
bring down to a charge of assault.
You should write a letter of apology
according to the date just in case.
You know what you need to do once
you're charged with assault, right?
You need to have your wife sign a letter
saying that she won't press charges.
Only then...
Then, I won't be prosecuted
because she's not pressing charges.
I know. This isn't the first time.
Your wife should write a letter
of refusal to press charges, right?
If she doesn't, it will mean that
she's going to make me a criminal.
Don't worry.
She'll never make her daughter
into a criminal's daughter.
Yes. From Yoobum's perspective,
it could be embarrassing for him.
He got criticized for something he
didn't do and I hugged another man.
It's natural for him to be angry.
I should stay calm and use common sense.
I need to end things rationally.
You're here.
What coffee would you like?
No thanks.
This will only take a minute.
I wanted to see you because I
wanted to hear many things from you.
For example, an apology.
I know very well that
you were very disappointed...
...with my behavior...
...at the time of incident.
I'm glad that you know.
I know that I'm acting out of
my mind and I know that...
...you didn't do anything wrong.
But I think I have to end things
with you for me to sleep well.
Excuse me...
Nam Hongjoo.
So let's end things here.
You can say that I was struck by
lightening or that I'm crazy wench.
I have no excuses.
I'm sorry.
Is this an apology?
Yes. My voice gets
louder the more I feel sorry.
I'm sorry about everything.
I've done a terrible thing to you.
I sincerely apologize.
Yes. Welcome.
The floor is slippery.
Please be careful.
Why didn't you go to school?
Why are you getting on this bus?
I was just worried because of that dream.
Gosh. You'll have to drop out of school
if you have another dream.
Father. That's the soldier
I saw in my dream.
It's just a coincidence.
Father. I think he has a gun in that bag.
This is breaking news.
An army private first class
soldier deserted from his post...
...with loaded rifle and a grenade
in Anjin-gu, Gangwon-do.
The soldier shot a policeman in
a convenience store in...
...Seoul and ran away.
The police and the army are pursuing him.
The policeman who
was shot died at the scene.
The detailed news...
Why is it raining all of a sudden?
Are you coming back from
seeing your mother at the hospital?
What?
Yes.
How is she?
Is she okay?
I told you, didn't I?
I told you not to act
like you know anything.
I'm asking you because I was worried.
I'd never acted like
I know in front of other kids.
You...
What's your name?
Don't you know my name?
I was in the same class with you
last year.
Do I have to know your name
if I'm in the same class with you?
Of course you should.
That's the responsibility
and duty of being a classmate.
I didn't know I had
that kind of responsibility.
I shouldn't have given her my coat.
Are all those cases assigned to me?
Then do you think they're assigned to me?
Wait a minute.
There's no space.
How about borrowing Prosecutor
Shin Heemin's cabinet?
She works so fast that she
hardly has any unfinished cases.
She has a lot of cabinet spaces also.
I work fast also.
Did you make reservation
for today's lunch yet?
You're the lunch manager.
I'm going to do it now.
Which restaurant?
Is that important?
It's important.
There's even rumor that
the evaluation of...
...a new prosecutor depends upon
upon how good of a lunch manager he is...
...than the actual case he works on.
You have to choose
the restaurant carefully.
I'm going to ask Prosecutor Shin
and choose one carefully.
Do you think she'll teach you?
Of course.
She's my junior back in school,
so we're very close.
Heemin.
Hey. Shin Heemin.
Hey. Miss Shin.
Miss Shin.
Does she have bad ears?
You should've called her Prosecutor Shin.
Heemin. Shin Heemin. Miss Shin. You can't
call her like that. It's prosecutor Shin.
Even if she was your junior in school...
...if she has seniority over you at work,
you should call her respectfully.
So why were you calling
her so desperately?
I heard that she was
the lunch manager before I got hired.
I was going to ask her how to do it.
You should memorize this, you brat.
Senior Prosecutor here
doesn't like meat in soup...
...so don't choose seollongtang
or shabu shabu restaurant.
The Chief Prosecutor doesn't
like raw meat so avoid sashimi.
The assistant prosecutor
doesn't like foot odor...
...so he doesn't like restaurants that
you have to take your shoes off.
Prosecutor Shin doesn't like
Italian food so keep that in mind.
Why are you teaching him such
valuable information for free?
I know. I should get paid for
teaching him this information.
You brat.
Pay me the tutoring fee...
I'm going to go inside.
What's wrong with him?
I think he has hard feelings against you.
I was his tutor before.
I think he must've thought that
I'm treating like my student.
But still... He made you feel foolish...
That's okay. I should've been carefully.
It's my mistake.
I think he's the runaway solder.
What do we do, father?
What if we all die like in my dream?
Don't worry.
No one is going to die today.
I'm going to say
that the bus broke down...
...and tell all the passengers
to get off the bus.
Then I want you to...
I'm sorry. There's a problem
with the tires on the bus.
It needs repairs.
I'm sorry, but please use the next bus.
I'm sorry.
Next bus will be here soon.
Why did the tires
causing me trouble today?
I'm sorry.
Why is it raining so much?
Sir.
Please hurry.
Hurry up and go.
I think it will be difficult to
change the tires all by myself.
Would you please help me?
Father!
"Seungwon will become
a murderer because of me."
Who is Seungwon?
Who is he going to kill?
And who is his brother?
Ignore it if you can't handle it.
Just think that you had a bad dream.
I want to talk to you.
I think they're flirting.
Follow me.
I told you not to act
like you know anything.
I told you not to open your mouth!
I saw you what you searched
on the internet earlier.
Why did you search about
the sentence for committing patricide?
Why did you search how to
purchase potassium cyanide...
...and how much antifreeze
is enough to kill?
What are you thinking?
Are you thinking...
...of killing your father?
I'm trying to save my mom.
Dad has to disappear...
...for my mom to live.
Why do you have to do that?
He was reported to the police.
The prosecutor should be
prosecuting him by now.
Your father will be
tried and go to prison.
That should be fine so why...
Why if the prosecutor
can't prosecute him?
Why not? He committed a crime.
He can't.
My dad will never be tried.
Because...
The prosecutor is an idiot and
the defense attorney is shrewd.
Attorney Lee is here.
I came today as the defense
attorney for Park Junmo.
Park Junmo?
The man who is being sent
for assaulting his wife?
Yes. He's a regular customer of mine.
You know that piano
prodigy Park Soyun?
It's her father.
Yes.
I thought it's a typical
domestic violence case.
Did you already review the records?
Yes.
He kicked his wife Do Geumseok
while wearing his dress shoes...
...and fractured six of her ribs.
So, it should be assault
with bodily injury.
It's not with bodily injury.
It's just assault.
That shrewd attorney will make it...
...into assault without bodily
injury no matter what.
What's the difference between
assault and assault with bodily injury?
If she didn't get hurt, it's just assault.
But if she was hurt,
it's assault with bodily injury.
You said your mother was
injured and she has broken ribs.
Isn't that obviously
assault with bodily injury?
I said its assault.
This is medical report of Do Geumseok.
Multiple fractures of
the ribs and contusions...
This is the medical report,
so how can it be just assault.
It's assault with bodily injury.
Hey. You should look
at the date. The date.
The incident took place on February 14th.
The medical report was given
4 days before on February 10th.
Then are you saying that her
ribs weren't broken...
...because she was hit
by Mr. Park Junmo?
That's right.
Then how did that happen to her?
This is Do Geumseok's
credit card statement.
If you look at the usage
report on February 10th...
...it shows that she was at Chungin Resort
and rented ski equipment.
Therefore, those ribs weren't broken
because Park Junmo assaulted her.
She had them broken while she was skiing.
If there isn't any change,
that shrewd attorney...
...will succeed in turning assault
with bodily injury to just assault.
Let's say that it turns into
just assault like you said.
But what is the problem?
Assault is a crime too.
That's right.
It's a crime, but it's a strange crime.
It's a crime that can only be punished
if the victim presses charges.
So if the victim doesn't
want to press charges...
...there's nothing
a foolish prosecutor can do.
And that crime will just go away.
Hey. Then you need to tell your mother
to press charges no matter what.
No. Mr. Prosecutor.
I don't want to press charges.
I was injured while skiing.
It has nothing to do with my husband.
As usual, my mom will say that
she doesn't want to press charges.
Yes.
Why not?
My mom is...
I'm sorry for troubling you.
My mom is more scared
of my father than the law.
So this is how you do it.
I've been curious since a while ago.
What about?
You said it earlier that...
...Mr. Park Junmo was
your regular customer.
What kind of trouble is he in
that he's become a regular customer...
...of an attorney who quit
being a prosecutor not even a year?
Seeing how you dress and what you drive...
...I can tell you're an attorney
that works for high legal fee.
Why did you take a case like this?
.
I was quite curious about it,
but now I understand.
What are you trying to say?
You must've been this way all this time.
You used few documents to turn assault
with bodily injury into just assault.
You threaten victims not to press charges
and throw out the indictment.
You get rid of crimes for him and
made him into a regular customer.
How many times do you have to do this
to make him into your regular customer?
Shouldn't we stop him?
Prosecutor Jung.
I think you're going too far.
I was wondering, but you're still
the same just as I worried you'd be.
I know that you have a grudge
for what happened 13 years ago.
Fine. Let's say that
I can understand that.
But you should let it end with me.
So why are you getting your
revenge on my innocent client?
Revenge?
Then try to explain that...
...what you've done to me for the past
few days are not revenge.
I just can't understand that it
can be anything, but revenge.
First,
Why did you harass my girlfriend
to break up with me?
No way.
Second, why did you crash into
my car when I just driving carefully?
He crashed into him?
Third.
"Prosecutor Jung crashed into
Attorney Lee's car..."
You can tell just by looking at the
documents of this case what the answer is.
So why are you trying
to pick a fight about it?
Don't put them together forcefully.
The case and those things are not related.
Well.
I can only explain those three things.
It's revenge.
That's crazy.
No way.
Prosecutor Jung crashed into
Attorney Lee's car intentionally.
Why?
I don't know.
He's saying something about him
taking his revenge on the suspect.
So I think there's something
going on between them.
There's something between them?
What is it?
I heard that Prosecutor Jung
stole Attorney Lee's girlfriend.
Don't you think its blind passion?
Blind Passion?
That's so disorderly. Disorderly.
I'm not asking you do something
impossible just because I know you.
I'm not asking you to get rid of
a crime that's been committed.
I'm just asking you to do it by the law
that you learned at law school.
Get it approved by the Senior Prosecutor
by today...
...and take care of it as
there's no right for arraignment.
Don't get revenge on my stern client.
By the law.
I'm going to go.
Hey. And please don't act like a child.
You acting like this make you
look like a drunk 16 year old.
I'm going.
- I'm going.
- Goodbye.
That foolish prosecutor will
not be able to save my mom.
It's been that way all this time.
There has to be a way.
There has to be another way.
The old sayings are never wrong.
Where drums beat...
...the laws...
...are silent.
Miss Shin. Here.
Miss Shin. Over here.
Hey. Over here. Miss Shin.
Do you think she's acting like that
because she doesn't hear you?
Just call her Prosecutor Shin.
Hey. Miss Shin!
Miss Shin!
Miss Shin. Over here.
There you are.
I'm sorry.
I was lost because
the restaurant sign was so small.
What's your religion?
I don't have a religion.
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
We share the same religion...
...so we take turns praying for the meal.
Don't worry about us and eat first.
- Yes, Sir.
- Shall we pray?
Then you why don't
you start praying first?
Yes.
Gracious God who
gives us our daily bread.
Please show kindness
to an unbelieving lamb.
Please have the lunch manager
choose a family restaurant...
...with big signs so that
there are no lost souls.
I work for an organization that
has clear order and system.
Please help the lost lamb
to understand that order...
...and system is more important age.
Unsolved cases are increasing.
Please help him become a prosecutor
who takes care of unsolved cases...
...quickly in order to ease
the sadness of victims.
Also, please help the soul
who disgraces the position...
...of prosecutor by
wearing inappropriate attire...
...and give him wisdom to wear
clothing worthy of a prosecutor.
This world is full of jealousy and anger.
There are times that people get
caught up in their personal feelings...
...from their past and
lose sight of the cases.
That's because...
A prosecutor must see cases rationally...
...even when he's caught up
in anxiousness and anger.
Please help him not to
deviate from being a prosecutor.
In the name of Jesus we pray, Amen.
-Amen.
Let's eat.
Why aren't you eating yet?
Yes. I'm eating.
Here. Take this.
Let's eat.
Yes.
What are you doing?
What do you think I'm doing?
I'm taking out the cases I'm
going to take care of today.
Don't you think that's too much for today?
I'm going to finish all of them
even if I have to stay up all night.
I can empty out that cabinet in one day.
It's Park Junmo's case.
There's a medical report and
the victim is not pressing charges.
I just have to sign off that
this case can't be prosecuted.
It will only take five minutes.
Just five minutes.
Suspect Park Junmo.
Crime is assault.
The victim expressed that she
doesn't want to press charges.
Therefore, the case can't be prosecuted.
The end.
Wow! It didn't even take five minutes.
If it's like this, there's no need
for me to stay up all night. All right.
Next case is regarding unlicensed...
This will only take three minutes.
Unlicensed.
Why is he acting like
that all of a sudden?
Did he drink at lunch?
He's totally drunk.
Will we get off work on time today?
I'm here at the funeral of
Inspector Jung Ilsong and the bus driver...
...Nam Chuldoo who saved the citizens
from the armed runaway soldier.
They stopped the tragedy by
sacrificing themselves bravely.
The politicians requested for
National Merit to be awarded to both men.
Where's his son?
I heard he was on
the bus with his father.
We have to interview him.
I know. I heard that he
evacuated all the passengers.
Where is he?
The assemblyman would like to
give him the words of comfort.
Mr. Kim. Did you take a picture of the
Assemblyman paying his condolences?
Yes. We took it.
Did you take it?
Let's go.
Mr. Choi.
He's out.
I thought he was working too fast.
No!
Oh my goodness.
My heart stopped.
Did you have a bad dream?
No. I wasn't sleeping.
It seemed like you were crying just now.
No, I wasn't.
Wait a minute.
Jaechan. Jaechan.
Get me out.
I didn't do it. I didn't do it.
Hello.
Where are you right now?
At school.
You're okay, right?
You're not sick or hurt, are you?
No.
Why do you ask?
Never mind. It's fine if you're okay.
What time are you coming home?
I'm not sure. Around 10 PM maybe?
Don't go anywhere else
and come straight home.
Do you understand?
Do you think I'm a fool?
Where else would I go?
Okay.
I'm trying to save my mom.
Dad has to disappear...
...in order for my mom to live.
Yes. It's just a dream.
It's nothing.
Let me go!
We can't.
I asked you to believe me.
We could've changed it
if you believed me.
Seriously.
I want you to make sure that
all the passengers get off.
Once they get off, make sure that they
go as far away from the bus as possible.
Let's not do that.
Let's just run away.
It's exactly like my dream right now.
I'm responsible for this bus.
So, how can I just runaway to save myself.
Father, please...
You brat.
If a catch doesn't catch
the ball and runs away...
...the umpire will get hit by the ball.
Then it will be a mess.
I'll grow out my hair.
You said it's your wish
to see me with long hair.
I'll grow out my hair.
So let's get off.
Really?
Okay.
I'll see it later for sure.
So get off the bus first.
By the way, it wasn't
a son but a daughter?
I heard that the child on the bus
wasn't a son but a daughter.
-Is that right?
-Yes.
Madam. Where's your
daughter right now?
Hongjoo isn't here right now.
Oh my goodness.
What are you doing here at this hour?
I didn't come here
because I changed my mind.
I wanted to explain why
I won't believe you.
Go ahead.
I'm a prosecutor.
My job is to punish the culprit
after the crime took place.
It's not to stop the crime.
I'm saying that there's nothing
I can do...
...no matter how many times
you tell me your dream.
It's not my business
no matter who dies in our dreams.
And I don't need to be responsible
for them.
But...
You feel like you've
become a catcher, don't you?
There's a ball coming at 160km per hour.
It's scary catch it.
But if you avoid it,
you'll mess up the game.
It's like that, isn't it?
That's right.
Now even if I don't want to
believe it, I can't ignore it.
Because I'm dreaming
those darn dreams too.
Why did I start having those dreams too?
Why me?
I don't know why it had to be you either.
I don't even know why I started
having these dreams either.
So how would I know that?
I don't know what it is,
but there must be a reason.
A reason that you and I are
having those dreams...
I don't know!
But what are you going
to do if there's a reason?
You can't stop them because
you're a prosecutor...
...and you don't want to believe me.
But you're saying that it's all my fault?
Did you come here to tell me that?
I need your help.
You were in my dream.
You blamed me for not listening to you...
...and Seungwon got into a police car
or an ambulance and left.
I just don't know what
that dream is about...
Seungwon...
Who is Seungwon?
He's my younger brother.
Why?
In my dream...
...the guy named Seungwon...
...killed someone.
Excuse me?
"4 season antifreeze."
Seungwon.
Look at that.
You memorized my name.
Then he said it's
because of his brother...
He said that he became
a murderer because of his brother.
Then his older brother is you, Jaechan?
Did you follow me?
Yes. Let's go together.
I'll take you home.
"Nam Chuldoo"
"While You Were Sleeping"
Is it connected to
Park Junmo's case?
It's because you
released Park Junmo...
It's because of you.
Do you have contact lenses?
Do I look different without my glasses?
Are you falling for me again?
Isn't the case closed?
I brought it back.
I plan to dig into the case to the end.
Why is it so hard for you to hear
that I'm looking forward to it?
You're saying that you'll be
disappointed if I can't do it.
But why is it me?
Why don't you want to
disappoint me specifically?
What do you do, Nam Hongjoo?
Are you interested in me now?
Are you saying that you
want to start dating me?
"While You Were Sleeping"