"While You Were Sleeping"
"Lee Jongseok"
"Bae Suzy"
"Lee Sangyeob"
"Go Seonghee"
"Jeong Haein"
"While You Were Sleeping"
It's happening again.
It's that dream again.
It hasn't happened yet...
...but the dream makes
me feel like I'm there already.
That dream makes me feel like I'm still
dreaming even when I woke up from it.
That nightmare makes me feel
like the morning will never come.
"Episode 5"
There's a sound that wakes
me up from that nightmare.
It comforts me by telling me that...
...the night is gone and the dream
has disappeared into the future.
It calms me down and says,
"Morning has come. It's okay."
My mom is the morning
that wakes the night to me.
My goodness. This is killing me.
I can't believe I gave birth to you.
Is this really a person's room?
This is a pigpen.
This is why I can't eat pork.
Because it reminds me of my daughter.
Mom...
Let's sleep for
just another five more minutes.
What's wrong with you?
It's gross.
Did you have that dream again?
Crazy jerk...
Why are you leaving so early today?
Are you meeting someone?
No.
I'm leaving early so that
I don't have to see someone.
Who are you talking about?
Who is it?
Yes. Thank you.
The neighbor across
the street brought us mackerel.
Go and get it.
Hey. You go and get it.
Just go and get it.
I have to go to the bathroom.
No. If I go out like this,
she'll misunderstand.
You look clean cut. That's good!
That's what I mean.
The problem is that I look clean cut.
I look too cool to be receiving mackerel.
She'll think that I'm trying too hard.
She's going to misunderstand me.
I just don't want to have that kind
of misunderstanding anymore.
Why are you being ridiculous?
-Hey.
-Let me go.
I have to go and poop.
Seungwon. You brat.
It's you, Mrs. Moon.
Your brother said that you
don't eat that much breakfast.
That's not good for men.
You won't have enough energy.
I wrapped it individually,
so put them in the fridge.
Grill them when you want to eat it.
It's already seasoned,
so you just need to grill them.
This is even easier to make
as compared to ramyeon.
Yes. Thank you.
You must like mackerel.
I should've brought it to you sooner.
You've been coming earlier lately.
Yes. I'll have Americano
with double shot of...
Extra hazelnut was already ordered...
...by the woman
with the short hair just now.
She went to the bathroom a moment ago.
She'll be back soon.
She's already here?
At this hour?
Yes.
It seems like the two of you have been
missing each other for the past few days.
I told her that she'll be able to
see you if she comes a little earlier.
I did a good thing, didn't I?
You didn't need to do that...
She's coming...
Gosh...
Americano with double shot of hazelnut.
Yours, right?
Are you a stalker?
Don't you have anything to do?
No. I don't.
By the way, have you been
working out in the morning lately?
I didn't know that you've been
going to work so early lately.
I missed you for several days.
You said you've been
taking time off from work.
Aren't you going back to work?
If I go back to work, it will
be hard for you to see me.
Do you want that?
Yes. I want that desperately.
Oh no.
I like seeing your face more
than going back to work.
Gosh.
Are you sure you just don't
want to go back to work?
It's not that I don't
want to go back to work...
Should I go back to work or not?
Why are you asking me that?
It's because I really
don't know what to decide.
It's exactly 50 to 50.
Half of me wants to go back
to work and half of me doesn't.
"Reinstated employee"
That's why I want you to decide for me.
I'll do what you tell me to do.
Should I or shouldn't I go back to work?
Is it difficult to be a reporter?
Do you really hate it that
much to go back to work?
No.
It's because I want to go back to work.
Because I really want to.
You look great.
I was born with it.
Are you dating?
Of course I'm dating.
Are you really dating?
Yes. I'm involved with my cases.
With your cases.
-Good morning.
Close the door.
Get in.
I'll get on the next one.
He says he's getting on the next one.
Get in. We still have lots of space here.
Please move along.
Get in.
I have to go to the restroom.
He has to go to the restroom.
Hurry up and get in.
Did you make any progress?
I was pretty fast.
In one month, I was already...
That's enough.
There are a lot of people here.
I won the Excellence Prosecutor
award in one month.
Is that something I shouldn't say
just because there are people here?
No.
You were thinking about
a different progress, weren't you?
Was it about Nam Hongjoo?
I'll see you later.
Bye.
Hey. I progressed faster
than you with that.
You should do better.
What progress?
The progress that you
and I are thinking about?
That rumor must be true.
The rumor that he stole
Attorney Lee's girlfriend...
Really?
I can hear everything.
Well, since you heard us...
...you should tell us
your side of the story.
If you let a rumor like that spread,
it will just get bigger.
A rumor like that spreads more
if you try to make excuses.
Who is...
...Nam Hongjoo?
I don't know her very well either.
Nam Hongjoo?
Nam Hongjoo from
Hongjoo Samgyeopsal?
That one that makes great kimchi stew?
That's right.
We'll be able to see her if we go there.
-Have you been there?
-Not yet.
But according to the rumor,
she's very pretty and intelligent too.
She's pretty and intelligent?
What is she like?
Is she like Prosecutor Shin?
Not at all.
There wouldn't be a rumor like
that about Prosecutor Shin.
That's what I'm saying.
Prosecutor Shin is only
attractive among average people.
I heard that Nam Hongjoo
is on a different level.
I don't think we can
even compete with her.
Attorney Lee said that she's
really hard to get type.
She's a total femme fatale.
Excuse me? What did you say?
Femme, what?
You know...
She captures men's hearts with
her beauty and intelligence.
But she'll never give her heart away.
Femme Fatale.
You completely picked the bones clean.
What was missing this time?
There was a leg missing.
It's the most important part of
the chicken along with the wings.
I'm not a machine.
A piece can fall into
a different box while I'm packing.
I'll be careful next time.
I've ordered 26 chickens
from this restaurant.
If a piece can fall into a different
box from time to time...
...then there must've been times
that I received extra pieces.
Right?
That's right.
But there was never a time
that there were extra pieces.
The name of the menu
is one whole chicken...
...but why do you think that I've
never had a whole chicken before.
Where do you think missing pieces went?
Are you sure you're not making...
...another whole chicken
with those missing pieces?
What's wrong with you?
Are you one of those black consumers?
You complain without any
evidence and take money...
If I report you, you'll be punished.
Evidence?
I have evidence.
I have a video that I took from
the moment I received the chicken.
According to the video...
I sent you to grocery shopping.
What are you doing here?
You really are terrible.
Even though I gave birth to her,
I just can't understand her.
Never mind. Sorry...
-Yes.
-...seems to be the hardest word .
-Sir. I'll be back.
-Come with me.
I'm going to keep watching you.
What are you going to watch?
-My goodness.
-Mother. Mother.
"Don't trust that woman"
What's wrong with you?
Why weren't you grocery shopping?
Why were you causing
a scene at someone's business?
Right?
It just looked like I was
causing a scene to you, right?
I used to do reports
from Prosecutor's Office...
...police stations and congress.
But now I'm only digging up corruption
of a fried chicken restaurant.
This really is a waste of talent.
A waste of talent.
Is that why you're
trying to get reinstated?
Did you see it?
Of course I did.
You put in on top of your desk,
so I'd see it.
Why aren't you answering me?
Are you going to go back to work?
Yes.
You said you saw yourself die
as a reporter in your dream.
You said you can't be a reporter
anymore because you're scared.
You said you were going to
work with me at this restaurant.
Why did you have a change of heart? Why?
I didn't have a change of heart.
The future might be changed.
You said the future can't be changed.
You said that we can't change the future
even if we know what will happen.
It can be changed.
Look at Jaechan.
He saved you and me.
So you're going to go back to work?
Did he say that he's going to save you?
Is he going to protect you?
Well...
It's not quite like that...
Frankly speaking,
he was able to change it.
Why can't I change it?
You can't change it.
You'll never change it.
Why not?
What can he do better than me?
There are many things.
There are so many things.
Mom.
I'm your daughter.
Why can't you believe
in me more than him?
I can't.
To me, you're not as
reliable or strong as him.
I'm more worried about you.
Much more...
You're more precious to me than him.
You're the only one
I have in this world also.
So don't leave me alone.
Okay?
Okay.
That's my daughter.
We're here to have some pork belly.
Hello.
Again?
I skipped breakfast today,
so I'm so hungry.
43007, 43008, 43009...
What is he doing right now?
You know the protest at
Ganghwamun yesterday?
He's going to see if the count...
...by the police or the organizers is
right by counting each one himself...
He's got too much time on his hands.
Hey. Bong Doohyun.
Nam Hongjoo is returning
to work next week, right?
What did she say?
Is she going to return to work?
43019...
Why are you asking me?
43020.
We're getting new uniforms...
...so I have to let them
know how many we need.
You're her supervisor.
You need to take care of these things.
Do I have to do these things?
43024...
-4...
-9...
Captain. I lost count
because of you.
You're my supervisor.
I don't even expect
you to take care of me.
But at least you
shouldn't ruin things for me.
Other people will think that
you're my supervisor or something.
What are you going to do?
Do you want me to count her or not?
-One, two, three, four...
-Look at that...
Gosh.
He must be losing his mind.
Let's finish our meeting here.
Lunch Manager.
Where are we eating today?
-Today, we're eating at...
-Sir.
Why didn't you approve the DUI
hit and run case I submitted?
I stated the reason as lack of evidence.
Indicting the passenger for aiding
and abetting DUI is too harsh.
You know that even if
we indict someone like this...
...he'll just go free at the court.
Someone from last month was
found innocent last month also.
-Where are we eating today?
-Today, we're eating at...
There were similar cases
in Gwangju and Daejeon...
...that sentenced
the offenders to probation.
In Japan, the same case involving
this kind of passenger is indicted...
...with two years in prison.
That's right. I saw that file too.
Is your case similar to that one?
Yes. No. It's more serious.
He got drunk together with the driver
and even got the keys from the valet.
He told him that he knows how to avoid the
police and asked him to drive him home.
It's aiding and abetting
if he goes that far.
"Aiding and abetting to crime is
advising someone to commit a crime"
Because of him, a nine years old child
lost his parents.
Now he has to wear colostomy
bag for the rest of his life.
If he tried to stop the driver,
this wouldn't have happened.
I went easy on him by indicting
him for aiding and abetting.
It's not harsh.
It isn't nearly enough.
He didn't drive the car.
You can't do that to him just
because he gave him the keys.
You shouldn't turn someone into a criminal
just because you're a prosecutor.
Sir.
Ms. Son.
Let's eat lunch first.
We can't solve cases that
can be solves if we're hungry.
Mr. Jung. Where are
we having lunch at?
Yes. I decided on a pork katsu restaurant
nearby.
Chunha Pork Katsu.
Mr. Jung. Were you inside
my stomach just now?
I was craving pork katsu.
Chunha Pork Katsu is good.
But Chief Park drank last night, so he'll
need to eat something for his hangover.
I heard that kimchi stew in at
Hongjoo Samgyeopsal is amazing.
That's too far,
so we should go somewhere closer.
There's a...
Yes. There are a lot of
kimchi stew places nearby.
Then...
Let's go to Hongjoo Samgyeopsal.
Weather is nice,
so we should walk as an exercise.
Let's go.
The weather is nice these days.
I get off the bus one stop earlier,
so I can walk to work.
Let's go.
I analyzed the dreams that
the three of us have been having.
You've been dreaming
about random people, right?
And you've been having
dreams about Jaechan lately.
Yes.
I think Jaechan
is having dreams about you...
...and I usually have dreams
about Jaechan.
Is that right?
That's amazing.
There must be some rules to this.
You're the one who
started having dreams first.
Then the next person is Jaechan.
And I'm the last one to have the dreams.
If we think of this as a virus,
you're the first person who got infected.
But it wasn't contracted
through air or contact.
If not, there would be a lot
more people who are infected.
Hey. Do you think I'm a patient
with an infectious disease?
I'm just putting it simply.
Do you hate having these dreams?
Yes. I feel like I betrayed my country
in my previous life or something.
I feel like I'm being punished for it.
No. You must've saved
a country in your previous life.
Once we figure out
the rules of your dream.
We'll be able to stop variety
of crimes and disasters.
What if you have dreams
about a war or terrorism?
Hongjoo.
We should each
master a foreign language.
That way we can communicate
internationally to stop crimes.
I can speak a little German.
Lieutenant Han has such great manners.
He's handsome and
he has an American style.
It's because he takes after me.
He looks exactly like me too.
People tell me that I raised a good
younger brother all the time.
Can I pay with cash receipt?
Of course.
Thank you.
You're so excited.
Do you like having these dreams?
Of course I like it.
What if you dream about you dying?
What are you talking about?
That's ominous.
You're a police officer.
What if you dream about you dying
while working on a dangerous case?
Are you going to quit
being a police officer?
Are you crazy?
Do you know what it took for
me to become a police officer?
But you might die if
you stay as a police officer.
I can just change the future.
I just have to change it.
I can change it.
Really?
Do you really think that way?
Get out!
What's wrong, mother?
Who are you calling your mother?
Get out right now.
Mom.
But Mother...
Who is your mother?
Stop talking nonsense and get out.
Get out right now!
Why is she acting like that
all of a sudden?
Did I say something wrong?
No.
I don't think it was because of you.
I think it's my fault.
I asked for her if I can
pay with cash receipt.
Why did you do that, sir?
It wasn't that much.
-She even gave us free rice.
-Jeez.
Han Wootak?
"Prosecutor - 2
Police -  X"
-Welcome.
You can sit anywhere you like.
Oh my...
Prosecutor Jung is here too.
Jaechan. You must be
close to the owner here.
Of course. He's a regular customer.
Then are you guys
dating just like the rumor?
No. We're not like that.
If Prosecutor Jung is a regular customer,
will you give us free sodas?
People who ask for free
sodas at a place like this...
...and free wontons at Chinese
restaurants seem so cheap.
It seems like they rip people off.
It's not like that.
Of course we should give free sodas.
Please wait a moment.
That must be Nam Hongjoo.
She's so pretty.
She seems intelligent.
Like a femme fatale?
Is she?
Femme...
Lord Jesus, you allow us to have
grace and wisdom even in difficulties.
Please grant us your wisdom
to all the prosecutors at our office...
...so that we would be fair
in prosecuting offenders.
A child became an orphan
because of a mishap...
...and he's going to be handicapped
for the rest of his life.
The person who didn't stop
the accident is a sinner along with...
...the one who caused
the accident before this tragedy.
Please punish the one who didn't stop
accident with your sword of justice...
The driver didn't commit a deliberate
offense but a negligent one.
There can't be aiding and
abetting on unexpected mistake.
Therefore he can't be
charged with a crime...
Drunk driving can cause accidents,
so you can expect it...
It can be expected.
That's right.
Lord. It's obvious that the person who
ignored expected crime should be punished.
It's an obvious logic...
If we live by that logic,
everybody who ignore the poor children...
...dying of starvation
should be punished as well...
Please save us from foolish people
who forcefully cloud the issue...
We live in a country
who believes in the elders.
Let us respect our elders...
Why are you bringing up
about the elders first ethics...
...when we're praying to our Lord?
That's Confucianism.
If the doctrine is the same,
we can bring it up.
Don't you know anything
about religious reconciliation?
Let's not do this.
Why don't we just decide by majority?
On the basis of democracy...
Miss. We'd like our free sodas please.
It's not free.
Please add it to our bill.
Yes.
Fine.
Let's decide it by majority vote.
A passenger who didn't try to stop
the drunk driver should be punished.
Raise your hand.
He shouldn't be punished.
What's wrong, Mr. Jung?
Why didn't you raise your hand?
I can see that both sides
have elements of truth.
I think I'll have to think about
it more to give you an answer.
Don't mind the others
and give your opinion.
It's cowardly not to vote
at a time like this.
Don't you think so?
Why are you asking me that?
I was curious if I'm the only one
who thinks that's cowardly...
I don't know.
First of all,
praying like this is a behavior...
...that goes against the
public officials' religious neutrality.
No. All four of us are Christians.
No way.
Excuse me?
At most, only 20 percent of Korea's
population are Christians.
Then the possibility of all four
of you being Christians...
...is 0.2 to the power of 4 which
comes out to be 0.0016.
It has a lower possibility that seeing...
...a double rainbow which you
might see once in your life.
It means that it's impossible.
It clearly means that one of you is hiding
your religion because of your superior.
It also means that the person who
refuses to pray in an organization...
...has quite a conviction.
I don't think this person is
minding others or being cowardly.
I'm sure he's thinking
about it with his conviction.
More carefully than anyone else.
Does that give you an answer?
Wow.
Who is she? She knows how to argue.
That tone of voice...
I've heard it somewhere before.
-Nam Hongjoo!
-Oh my goodness...
You scared me.
That girl from
the restaurant is a reporter.
Reporter Nam Hongjoo.
She was a reporter at SBC.
I didn't recognize her
because she cut her hair.
No wonder...
What kind of a reporter was she?
My gosh. She was really tough.
She was so talented in picking...
...the best spot when
the suspects are summoned.
She'd stay close to the suspect and pour
on her questions.
She always yelled
at the top of her lungs...
Please give us a statement.
A chief prosecutor is causing
a controversy after sexually harassing...
...female prosecutors at a team dinner.
Was it two years ago?
She exposed the case on
sexual harassment...
...of the chief prosecutor at
Yeonju District Prosecutors' Office.
It was that reporter who made him quit.
It was revealed that he fondled
some body parts of female prosecutors...
...and committed
other sexual harassment.
Then she disappeared suddenly.
I thought she was sent as
a correspondent somewhere.
Why is a successful reporter
working at a restaurant now?
I wonder, too.
I'm curious about that too.
She's not someone who
would quit being a reporter.
I should ask around.
The organizers announced that
70,000 people participated in the protest.
However, the number of participants
that the police announced is...
...15,000 which is far less than
what was reported by the organizers.
So, the difference between
the organizers and the police...
...was caused by the method
and the timing of counting.
If you consider everything,
you'll have to arrest everyone.
What are we going to do
if don't arrest everyone?
Let's go back to
the beginning and think it over.
Alright.
He's responsible for
providing that opportunity.
That's why it's a car accident.
However, when I counted
the total number of participants...
...there were 37 thousand
participants at 6 PM.
Did you hurt yourself?
Let me see.
You should've been careful.
Leave it.
I'll do the rest.
Are you crying?
Does it hurt a lot?
Should I take you to the hospital?
Mom. I don't think
these are fresh onions.
They are so spicy.
Taeseob.
Yes.
This is the last delivery.
Yes. I'll be back.
What is this?
Did he steal the chicken for that?
Okay, I won't do it.
That's not my business.
I am so tired now.
What if you dream about you dying?
I can just change the future.
I can change it.
"Myungwon University
Candle Light Event 2016, March 28, 8 PM"
"Myungwon University"
What are you doing?
I'm a father too.
I cried after I found out
that child became an orphan.
But I'm not the one who drove.
I only got in the passenger seat.
That's my only sin.
I didn't kill them.
You didn't just get in the car.
You gave him the car keys and even
told him where to avoid the police.
Is it a sin to have
given him the car keys?
If I didn't give him the keys,
someone else would have.
He would've driven
even if tried to stop him.
Frankly speaking, did I grab
his throat and make him drive?
Did I beat him up?
Just because I did this...
Just because I told him to drive...
...do I have to be treated like
a criminal because of that?
That frustrating guy...
It's not only this...
Ms. Son is so stubborn.
Since Chief Park didn't approve it,
she shouldn't indict him.
Why did she call him for questioning?
Why did you come here?
Did you decide if you
would indict him or not?
I have a favor to ask of you.
I have to question a suspect.
Bye.
Bye...
Okay. Okay.
What is it?
I have an urgent matter later tonight.
Could I ask you to take my shift tonight?
My goodness...
There's a scary curse here at
Han River District Prosecutors' Office.
If you take someone else's shift,
big problem will occur...
Then...
I'll take your weekend shift for you.
I took someone's shift before and an
explosion at a karaoke bar took place...
I'll take your extra holidays shift.
There were many deaths and there were so
much work with autopsy and examination.
I took someone's shift unfortunately
and ended up doing so much work.
I'll introduce you to a woman.
What?
It's your shift tonight, right?
Yes.
Thank you so much, Mr. Jung.
Jaechan!
-Did you fall asleep?
-I didn't fall asleep.
Aren't you hungry?
There's a cart bar that sells
amazing stir-fried blood sausage.
Should we eat some?
Instead of that, what do you think of...
...patrolling around Myungwon University?
Okay. Then let's eat
stir-fried blood sausage quickly...
...and go patrol
around Myungwon University.
I'll drive.
So let's go on the patrol first.
Maybe, you're right.
Let's do it.
Hey. Where are you
going at this hour?
Mom. I might be late today.
Don't wait up.
Where are you going?
What is this?
I'm going to save someone.
Someone got hurt in my dream.
Mom. Promise me one thing.
If I change my dream this time...
...and save that person...
...I want you to reconsider
my return to work.
What are you doing?
That's so annoying.
Chohee. Chohee.
I'm so glad.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
You might not believe it,
but I just stopped a big accident.
What are you talking about right now?
This took so long to prepare.
Do you know what I went
through to prepare this?
What are you doing?
Hey. Stop there!
Hey. Where did she go?
What are you doing here, Jaechan?
Hush.
It's alright.
In my dream, a female student got burned
because of the Candle Light Event.
So I put the fire out with
the fire extinguisher.
But once I saved her I realized that...
...it was that woman from
the cafe that we go to everyday.
Isn't that amazing?
Did you come because
you dreamt about me too?
Recently Wootak said that you
dream about me often these days.
I wonder why?
Is because opposites attract?
Are you nervous for no reason?
Is it fate?
I'm sorry about back then.
And thank you.
Back then?
When are you talking about?
When you took my side
at your restaurant...
Back then...
I didn't take your side.
I just told the truth.
Then I take it back.
By the way, did you make up your mind?
Would you indict that person who aided
and abetted that drunk driver or not?
I'd indict him.
Why?
It's not like he caused the accident.
You're going to indict him
for only giving him the keys?
It's a crime because it was
only giving him the keys for him.
If he only gave him the keys, he could've
only not given him the keys also.
He aided and abetted him to
drive drunk with a single word.
Then he could've stopped
him with a single word also.
If he didn't say that to him,
he could've saved them.
Since he ignored it, he's a criminal.
Because he only did that, it's a crime.
You changed.
Well. It's because of someone.
That wench is over there.
They're dead.
Excuse me.
I'm Lieutenant Han from
the Third District Station.
You were just jaywalking and...
...you violated traffic law
article 10 of section 2.
I haven't even crossed the street yet.
What are you talking about?
Why are you making a fuss?
I heard everything.
Who is that wench?
You said you were going to kill her.
You jerk. You guys were going
to beat up someone, weren't you?
No. We weren't.
You can't run around like hyenas looking
for rotten meat and beat up people.
Do you understand?
Follow me. Follow me.
Why are you doing that?
Follow me.
-Follow me.
-No, please!
-Follow me!
-I'm sorry!
What's wrong? Are you hurt?
I'm not, but it feels like its burning.
I wonder what's wrong with me.
Hello.
Daehee.
What happened?
Can you hear me?
He's not opening his eyes.
Daehee. This is not true, right?
What happened?
Why is his body so cold?
Wake up. Chohee is here.
I took his shift and now
I have to observe an autopsy...
The curse of Han River District
Prosecutors' Office strikes again.
The younger brother
didn't wear his seatbelt.
Due to the impact, his skull was
fractured and his neck was broken.
My gosh.
Why didn't he wear his seatbelt?
I know, right?
Just a moment.
He's not bleeding much for
the severity of the accident.
-Should we perform the autopsy?
-No.
I don't want the autopsy.
But in order to find
the truth of his death.
No. You can't do that.
I killed him.
He could've taken the bus but I drove him.
I'm the one who killed him.
If that is the family's wish,
let's skip the autopsy.
I'm home.
Wow.
Why did you buy so many crabs?
Mom. I saved that person.
The student who got hurt in my dream.
So as you promised...
I never promised.
You're the one who said
I promised on your own.
Mom.
You know that I like writing in my diary.
I wrote in my journal every day
in my teens...
...even if I couldn't
sleep for more than an hour.
I probably wrote 10 pages just
criticizing my superiors at work.
But I finish writing in
it after I write six lines.
It's similar to yesterday.
I can even write ahead of time.
It will be similar tomorrow.
I saw that the whole year's worth...
...wasn't even as long as
one day worth from before.
What are you trying to say?
Mom.
I just want today to be a little more
wonderful than the day before.
I don't want to waste by doing
nothing just because I'm scared.
So you're going to go back to work?
Even though you dreamed that you saw
yourself die as a reporter in your dream?
I'm not going to die.
I can just change my dream.
I can change the dream after
I met Jaechan and Wootak.
I changed it today too.
I understood while
I was changing the future.
There is one certainty in life.
What is that?
There isn't a single thing that
has been decided for sure in life.
You're not asking for my permission.
You're just informing me.
I'm not informing you.
I won't return to work
without your permission.
It's gone bad.
What is this?
Breakfast is my responsibility.
Cooking?
I'm a great cook.
When you come back to
Korea during your vacation...
...I'll grill you some mackerel.
I'm amazing at grilling mackerels.
Soyun. He's totally lying.
You should try a video call.
Move away.
There's a fire. There's fire.
"Hongjoo's dream, Jaechan's dream,
My dream"
Do you usually have breakfast here?
What are you doing here?
I made some toast, but I burnt them.
So, I was going to
have this as my breakfast.
What about you?
I'm in a similar situation.
I wanted to ask you a question.
What is it?
That car accident back then.
I felt really strange
when the accident happened.
You clearly saved me from
the accident...
...but strangely...
...the moment before I felt like I was
dying after getting hit by the car.
That feeling was unbelievably real.
Did you ever experience
something like that?
The experience of surviving
from almost dying?
I do.
Really?
When?
It was when I was really young.
I fell in the water once.
But someone saved me.
I was saved because of that person,
but strangely...
...I felt like I was drowning.
It felt so real.
I knew it.
Was the person who saved you...
...happen to be Nam Hongjoo?
Excuse me?
What if we look at it this way?
I was really thankful to
you because of that feeling.
I could've really be dead.
I thought,
"I want to repay him for saving me."
-Because of that thought...
-Because of that thought?
I started having the dreams.
I see the future of the one
who saved me in my dreams.
You dream about Nam Hongjoo.
So, the one who saved
you was Nam Hongjoo.
What do you think?
That's impossible.
Why?
The one who saved me was a man.
It wasn't Nam Hongjoo.
Are you sure?
Yes. I'm positive.
The one who saved me was called Bamtol
and he was a boy who loved baseball.
And he was strong and energetic.
I'm back.
Mom. There was a sale on
vitamins on my way back.
Mom.
Where did she go at this hour?
Is this considered as food waste?
Is that perhaps...
Is it the mackerel that I gave you?
No. This is...
Grilling this was harder that I thought.
It was difficult to control the heat too.
Why don't you just have breakfast
at my house from now on?
No. That's okay.
It's because I have
a favor to ask of you.
You don't know why Hongjoo
quit being a reporter, do you?
She dreamt that she died as a reporter.
That's why I told her to quit
being a reporter immediately.
You know, don't you?
That Hongjoo's dreams are special.
Yes. I know.
But that rotten girl wants to
return to work in the end.
I should've tried to stop her.
But I gave her permission
because I felt so bad for her.
I felt bad for her because she wasn't
doing what she wants to do in life.
Anyway...
What do you like to eat, Prosecutor Jung?
I worked at Korean, Chinese,
Western and all sorts of restaurants.
So I can make all kinds of food.
So just tell me.
I'll make what you and your
brother likes every morning.
For free. It will be free.
Gosh.
But why do you want to make me breakfast?
It's because I'm thankful
to you for everything.
I heard that you saved
my daughter several times.
I wanted to repay you.
And... I might be
indebted to you again.
Well...
I shouldn't be asking you this.
But if something happens...
...please protect my daughter.
Should I return to work or not?
It wasn't because she didn't want to.
She wanted to, but she was scared.
Face expressions are so mysterious.
Let's do it!
You can tell one's mood...
...thoughts...
...and emotions easily....
...through one's facial expression
as if you're looking into the mirror.
Mom.
Don't worry. I'm still in the bus.
Can't you believe your daughter?
Okay. Okay.
I feel great.
But you can also hide your mood...
...thoughts, and feelings with your face
expressions like putting on a mask.
But in the flash of a moment...
...there's a moment where...
...the boundary between that
mask and mirror comes down.
The truth that no one saw...
That feeling that you
didn't want others to see.
The moment it surfaces
to the world for a moment...
If we face that moment,
let's not close our eyes.
Let's not ignore them if we see them.
Let's not avoid them,
but let's face them.
Hello.
Nam Hongjoo has returned to work.
It's been a long time.
Welcome back, Nam Hongjoo.
Welcome to hell.
It's been a while.
Yes.
Captain. I've returned to work.
Is your health better?
It's nice to see you again.
Congratulations on having a baby.
Your eye make-up smeared.
Don't you look at yourself in the mirror?
I've returned to work.
I put your uniform
on that desk over there.
I guess you are her supervisor
since you took care of that.
You don't act like
how you feel. You jerk.
Captain. What are you doing?
You're my supervisor,
but you don't even help me.
What are you doing?
We got a different design this time,
so our uniforms changed.
I was sick of purple uniforms.
Try it on to see if it looks good.
Is it that difficult to
cross the crosswalk?
I know.
Maybe it's because
I haven't been here in a while.
It's hard and I'm nervous for no reason.
Then what would you like me to do?
Do you want me to go inside with you?
What's wrong with you?
I might start to misunderstand again.
I might cling onto you and ask
you to take me to work every day.
And whine to you about protecting me.
Why don't you do that?
Excuse me?
Cling onto me, ask me to take
you to work and protect you.
I'll give it a try.
If that puts you at ease,
Why are you saying that?
It sounds like you mean it.
I meant it.
Don't you believe me?
Is that why you're crying?
I'm crying because I believe you.
Because I feel relieved.
I really wanted to hear those words.
That's why I'm crying.
My eye make-up has smeared.
Excuse me.
You said you'd protect me.
Can't you at least do this for me?
You're not avoiding it today.
Don't you like it?
No.
I really like it.
"While You Were Sleeping"
Did you kill your younger brother?
I'm asking you to make me innocent.
The opposing attorney
is Lee Yoobum.
He'll be found guilty by 99 percent.
Of course.
We're the 99 percent.
Your Honor, the defense council is...
All of these records here are
denouncing the prosecution's claims.
If he is released like that and kills more
people, you'll be the one responsible.
You prosecutors are responsible
for not proving that he's guilty!
Jung Jaechan!
"While You Were Sleeping"