THIS DRAMA IS PURELY FICTIONAL
AND IS NOT ASSOCIATED WITH
ACTUAL PEOPLE, PARTIES, LOCATIONS,
CORPORATIONS OR INCIDENTS
What time is it?
It's still early.
You should get more sleep.
Why did you wake up so early?
You didn't get much sleep yesterday.
Don't overwork yourself.
My situation is a little different
from yours, Ms. Assemblywoman.
Here's the next story.
Some are suspecting
that Assemblyman Jo Gap-yeong is being
unreasonably lenient toward
Bugang Electronics during the audit.
Assemblyman Jo denied the speculations,
but the Environment and Labor Committee
is discussing whether Assemblyman Jo...
When do you think
the hearing can be resumed?
I think the audit will end like this.
Unlike someone, I don't have the ability
to salvage such a mess.
What about you?
I just need to tackle KLAC
and the Ministry of Justice now.
The latter will be the highlight.
People call the Minister of Justice
a weasel.
He's good at weaseling out of things.
Can you catch him?
Tae-jun, I can't stand seeing people
who should be behind me
hovering in front of me.
To give you my position,
I have to clean up the mess
in front of me. Am I wrong?
I have to catch him.
Just be careful.
The Minister of Justice oversees all
the prosecutors in this country after all.
It won't be easy.
Even Assemblyman Song
was taught a lesson, you know.
-He even got ousted--
-Weasels have sharp teeth indeed.
Who knows what can happen to me
if I'm not careful?
That's why
I must take him down in one blow
and make sure he can't fight back.
I've come this far, so I can't give up.
If there is something blocking my way,
I must jump over it.
In order to make sure
you can jump over it,
I'll lend you my shoulder.
Hello.
Everyone has a different starting point
and their own reasons for their choices.
HAN DO-GYEONG
However, everyone is taking a step forward
to find their own place in the world.
This stop is National Assembly.
The doors are on your left.
The doors are opening.
WHISTLEBLOWER PROTECTION ACT
Hello.
Sir.
Hello there, Ms. Kang.
-Let's go in.
-Everyone's position may be different,
but we're all here on our own journeys.
EPISODE 3
Tae-jun.
Did you see the news?
The sign from Assemblyman Lee's
district office fell on a passerby,
resulting in a severe injury.
The victim of the accident,
a woman in her 40s,
was sent to a hospital nearby and is now
-undergoing her second surgery.
-It's your fault!
The police are investigating if the sign
violated any of the regulations
for signs and advertising devices.
Assemblyman Lee Seong-min
expressed his regret
and visited the victim,
but the victim's family
refused to meet him.
-How much are you willing to pay...
-Say a few words.
-Please make a comment.
-Do you admit it?
-I'll look into it.
-Sir, let us interview you.
Hello.
Which one is a latte?
Oh, the latte is for the chief of staff.
Mr. Jang doesn't drink latte.
No, the other one.
"The other one"?
Who?
The sign from Assemblyman Lee's
district office fell on a passerby,
resulting in a severe injury.
Mr. Oh Won-sik is here
from the district office.
The victim of the accident,
who is a woman in her 40s,
was sent to a hospital nearby
and is now undergoing her second surgery.
You see,
because he keeps going on about labor laws
and regulations,
it's practically impossible
to run a business here in Seongjin.
When he asked me to come here for drinks,
I knew something was up.
That must be it.
I'll talk to Mr. Lee Seong-min.
No, it's okay. I'll take care of it.
The police are investigating
if the sign violated
-any of the regulations for signs
-Hey.
and advertising devices.
-You're here.
-Assemblyman Lee expressed
his regret and visited the victim,
but the victim's family refused...
Oh, boy. I hope her injury
isn't too serious. This is terrible.
The lack of attention to safety
in this country is a serious problem.
Here's your latte, sir.
-Mr. Oh.
-My gosh! How have you been?
Not well, obviously.
I've been so bored without you, sir.
Right, I bet.
So how's it going? Are you liking the job?
Yes, sir. I'm doing my best.
-Do you know him?
-Mr. Oh recommended me for this job.
He did? I didn't know.
Oh, here you go.
Why didn't you tell me sooner?
What brings you by?
Mr. Song wants to see me.
Hey, yes. Hang on a second.
Are there any sticky notes lying around?
Yes. Song Jin-seok.
SONG JIN-SEOK
Wonseong Bio. Okay.
All right, I'll call you.
Then I should...
Oh, sit down.
-Let's go for a smoke.
-Sounds good.
Do-gyeong, do you want to come?
I don't smoke.
All right, then.
-Ms. Yun, how have you been?
-Hello.
Jeez, you're making it so obvious
that you hate me.
Smile a little, please.
-Hello.
-Hi, long time no see.
My, it's so nice to be back in Seoul
after such a long time.
Yes, it's important to wear this
here in Seoul.
There. Nice one.
-Who is he?
-It's Mr. Go Seok-man.
-Hello!
-Oh, hello.
Jeez.
-Any updates?
-I spoke to those at the local precinct.
It does look like someone
touched the connecting bracket,
but it could've been for a repair job,
or someone could've tampered with it.
They're not sure yet.
Was anyone caught on the security footage?
It's an old building
so there are no security cameras.
The rooftop is always open,
so anyone can get in.
We'll close it
as a negligent maintenance case,
but I heard the victim is preparing
to sue Assemblyman Lee.
-I just sent you some photos.
-Okay.
LEE SEONG-MIN
I guess you have time to enjoy cycling.
Don't even get me started.
My boss won't take it easy
even if the audit is halted.
From a meeting and a public hearing
to this local cycling event,
I already made three stops.
-Jungil-gu?
-Yes, Ms. Kang was born in that area.
She needs to build support
in the district for the upcoming election.
She doesn't have a super supportive one,
unlike your boss.
She only has a ten-percent chance
of getting reelected.
-We'll do anything at this point.
-So you participated in the race?
Of course.
As her chief of staff,
it is my duty to run and sweat
to meet and listen to the people.
Look at you always dressed in a full suit.
You won't get anything done.
You pretentious jerk,
you only care about looking good.
By the way, I saw Mr. Oh earlier.
Right.
What?
What's up with that nonchalant answer?
He was shunted off because of you.
He won't just sit still.
If you're not careful,
he'll end up reaping
all the rewards of your hard work.
-Don't worry about me.
-Hey.
Just continue to run
as hard as you can for your boss, okay?
That prick. Jeez, what a jerk.
No, that's not right.
Those things must be discussed in person.
-Hey, you see--
-Then I'll...
-Won-sik.
-Yes.
Spare me a second.
Why are you here?
I told you that Mr. Song summoned me.
Are you deaf or what?
How did you hurt your hand?
My hand? Oh, this?
-While doing something.
-What time did you get here?
Hey, Jang Tae-jun.
Are you interrogating me or what?
Do you still think you're a cop
like ten years ago?
How dare you act like one?
Were you behind the incident
regarding Mr. Lee?
You have so many questions.
Do you like me or something?
But I don't like you.
Just focus on your work. Don't poke
your nose into others' business.
Also, why are you trying to lay eggs
in someone else's nest?
Are you a cuckoo or what?
Don't cross the line, Tae-jun.
You might get hurt.
Got it?
That prick.
I'm back.
Thanks for doing that.
You finished the race today,
so you may be in the top tier next time.
Don't even go there. I can't do it again.
Here, take this.
Are you giving me this
to make me work even harder?
I might die at this rate.
I have no energy these days.
That's why I got this for you.
I hope it energizes you.
We're only starting now.
Have you arranged the meeting
with the mayor of Jungil-gu?
He keeps avoiding me.
And he hasn't commented on the proposal.
Many low-income earners live in Jungil-gu
and the percentage
of lone-parent families is high.
Also, the district's child poverty rate
is 69.4 percent.
It is crucial for the election as well,
but we absolutely have to
pull this project off.
That's why I mentioned it to those
in Assemblyman Jo Gap-yeong's office,
but will he help us out?
We'll have to make him help us.
-Is the weekly briefing note ready?
-Yes.
I just need to revise it.
I'll take care of it.
After I finish revising this,
please send it to Assemblyman Jo
and other top-tier members.
Sure.
I got the list,
but why haven't you sent
the supplementary materials yet?
The Ministry of Justice is refusing
to send the materials.
This is Jang Tae-jun.
We requested them a week ago.
How could they not be ready yet?
Send them by this afternoon,
or I'll send someone there.
Cuckoo, cuckoo, the cuckoo
Cries in the woods
Why did you guys leave the door open?
-Hello, sir.
-Hello, sir! I'm here.
Hey, Won-sik!
Thanks for coming all the way here.
-Come on in.
-Sure.
Hey, he wants to have the meeting now.
Got it, sir!
Hey, what are you doing?
Aren't you coming?
I'm still just an intern, sir.
Interns should sit in these meetings
and learn.
Come on in. Join us.
Come join us.
Yes, sir.
INTERN
HAN DO-GYEONG
We'll bring the Bugang Electronics case
to the table at the MOJ hearing
during the audit
and pressure the Minister of Justice.
We'll interrogate him
about the investigation
being delayed
and if he was involved in the--
Don't you think we need
something stronger?
We don't have firm evidence
to prove his involvement.
Oh, boy.
What do you think?
What do I know? But I agree
that it doesn't sound impactful enough.
Don't worry too much though.
The MOJ hearing is tomorrow,
so I'm sure Tae-jun has a plan. Right?
Shall we go arrange the documents?
This sounds like...
What does this mean?
Got it, sir.
That prick, Park Jong-gil,
must have buried his shit
deep in the ground.
He left no trace.
-Then we should dig even deeper.
-Got any leads?
-Cha Dong-ho?
-He's the whistleblower
that reported Bugang's slush fund
four years ago.
He disclosed Bugang's slush fund
of over ten billion won,
but the prosecution
investigated him for defamation
and spreading false information,
and Bugang was acquitted
for lack of evidence.
The investigation
was overseen by the deputy--
The current Minister of Justice,
Park Jong-gil.
Yes.
That's right.
MINISTER OF JUSTICE
HOLDS PROSECUTION LIABLE
It's about time the flower fell.
The floor leader and the chief
of the central prosecutors' office.
The Minister of Justice
is the only one left now.
Sir, you promised me
that you'll nominate me
if you're appointed Minister of Justice.
Please keep that promise.
When the tables turn,
I shall certainly take care
of my most loyal aide first.
Come on. It's a given.
Then what about Mr. Oh?
Gosh, no. Don't worry about Won-sik.
I summoned him for a task, that's all.
Don't worry about anything else.
Just focus on Park Jong-gil for now.
If I manage to get him ousted
and make that title mine,
who do you think will get my district?
You know what I mean?
If we can't get him ousted this time,
and if he manages
to reform the prosecution,
it'll get even harder.
This is our last chance,
both for you and me.
I promise I'll make you
the next Minister of Justice, sir.
Sir, the hearing
for KLAC is about to begin.
Jeez, what a hassle. Oh, dear.
Gosh. Darn it.
Goodness.
You have a lunch meeting
with the Judiciary Committee
and the Minister of Justice at noon.
What? Why do they want
to have lunch together during the audit?
How dare he summon me for just a meal?
-Let's go, sir.
-Okay.
See you later.
Look into the Cha Dong-ho case closely.
I will, sir.
-About this...
-Hello, Ms. Kang.
Now may not be the best time.
Are you doing your job?
What's with these ridiculous articles?
Do your job better!
I made sure to explain everything
to the reporters.
Jeez, they never listen. I apologize, sir.
Yes, come in.
Find out who sent that document
to Lee Seong-min.
Yes, sir.
CAREER OF JO GAP-YEONG'S SON
PAVED WITH FAVORS
How's it going
with the issue about your son?
Gosh, I'm backed into a corner
because of it.
I wonder how Lee Seong-min
obtained that information.
Is it that prick, Jang Tae-jun, again?
Any guesses?
I'm not sure.
Maybe it was done by the opposition.
We'll soon find out who did it.
Please don't hesitate to let me know
if you need anything.
I'll help.
I read the briefing note
of the weekly meeting,
but there's nothing about me.
I was told to refrain from bringing up
the issues involving you.
I know everyone in politics
is exploitative and cutthroat,
but isn't this too harsh?
The party should be helping me
at a time like this.
I heard you're doing a project
with the mayor of Jungil-gu.
Was it for supporting lone parents?
Yes, sir.
-It's not easy though.
-He's my friend!
I'll put in a good word for you.
I read the proposal,
and it's for such a good cause.
It needs to be done.
Thank you, sir.
At the briefing, I'll do my best
to explain your situation.
-That's the least I can do for you.
-I'd appreciate that.
It should be explained
at such an official occasion,
and I'd love it to be done by you,
our spokesperson.
Right.
MINISTER OF JUSTICE PARK JONG-GIL
Excuse me for a second.
Yes, sir.
Prosecutor Seo
at the Western Prosecutors' Office
is investigating Jang Tae-jun
and Assemblyman Song at the moment.
If you give him some support,
he'll take care of the issue with Bugang.
Yes. Understood, sir.
Oh, and...
-You may leave now.
-Okay.
And before you go...
Mr. Jang, who's Cha Dong-ho?
He’s a whistleblower who exposed
Bugang Electronics' irregularities.
Oh, I remember him.
But that case already ended.
What more would there be?
Mr. Kim, you should go talk
to Mr. Cha Dong-ho.
Pardon? Me?
But I need to attend the hearing
for KLAC later.
I'll go.
I'm okay. I can be in control of this.
I know how much you need
Cha Dong-ho right now.
And the same goes for me.
You know why I started
working here in the first place.
Mr. Cha is still suffering
due to the compensation trial
that Bugang started.
I want to help him.
Please let me go meet him.
It's the list of evidence he had
during the prosecution investigation.
There may be material
that hasn't been revealed.
-Any story will be of value to us.
-Yes, sir.
-Mr. Han.
-Yes?
I want you to go meet Mr. Cha
with Ms. Yun.
Okay, sir.
Ask the central prosecutors' office
for the investigation materials.
-I'll go fetch them myself.
-Okay, sir.
I'll see you when I get back. Let's go.
See you later, sir.
JEONGGIL GARDEN
-Is this the place?
-Yes.
My goodness.
-Enjoy your meal, sir.
-Okay, thanks.
My gosh, the weather is amazing.
LUNCH WITH JUDICIARY COMMITTEE
My gosh, take some rest.
Aren't you tired of driving at that age?
Of course, I'm tired.
I'm doing this
because I need to earn a living.
You should've learned a skill or two
when you were young.
My gosh, he's living such a tiring life.
JEONGGIL GARDEN
Enjoy your meal, sir.
Long time no see.
I thought you got ousted by Tae-jun
and were shunted off.
What are you talking about?
I was just there to get some fresh air.
You must not be getting ready
for the audit.
You look way too comfortable.
Are you kidding me?
My team is going through so much shit
because of Jang Tae-jun.
He talks for two hours over the phone
asking them for one material.
My gosh, no wonder they call him a viper.
He's so persistent.
-He's so harsh to the same ruling party.
-He's known to be hardheaded.
Tell me what you guys are preparing.
Let's help each other out.
How can I tell you when I know nothing?
Should we go for a smoke?
I'm sorry
that short rib soup is the best
I can treat you to at the moment.
But it's made with premium beef,
so it'll taste very nice.
But I'm not sure
if it'll suit your palate, Mr. Song.
Mr. Song used to be a butcher,
so he knows meat like no other.
If you all help me pass the reform bill
regarding the prosecution,
I'll treat you all to some beef next time.
Minister, I've seen a lot of people
get their jaws dislocated
while trying to butcher a cow
because they didn't do it right.
So be careful.
This is nice. Let's eat, everyone.
Eat up.
129-16 JEHYEON-RO
Is anyone here?
Dad, someone's here.
This is the list of evidence you handed in
during the investigation.
Can you please check
if there's anything missing?
We'll make sure this doesn't harm you.
We'll do everything we can
to make sure your courage
doesn't go to waste.
This is the bill
we're preparing to submit.
We're going to amend the current bill
so that whistleblowers like you
won't have to suffer from damage.
If this works out well,
you and other victims
will start getting protected by the law.
Is someone here?
Hello, I'm Yun Hye-won.
-I work for Assemblyman Song Hui-seop.
-I'm Han Do-gyeong.
Please leave.
We don't want to meet anyone
whether that person is
an assemblyman or the President.
We can set things straight this time.
-If you help us...
-You want us to help?
How can you say that
after seeing how we're living?
You're just here to use us
to your advantage!
Don't ever come here again.
We don't need stuff like this!
So please leave.
Get out!
Get out of here right now!
129-16 JEHYEON-RO
How did Mr. Cha end up living like this?
The company found out
that he exposed their slush fund.
This is what always happens
to whistleblowers.
Once their identity gets revealed,
their lives become miserable.
Mr. Cha Dong-ho, the man who exposed
Bugang Electronics' slush fund,
attempted suicide last night
and ended up in a critical condition.
He was feeling tormented
due to his personnel appointment
after he had reported his company.
It turns out he ended up
overdosing on tranquilizers.
Excuse me.
Is this Mr. Cha Dong-ho's place?
Yes, who is it?
We're from Seoul District Court.
You've failed to compensate
Mr. Kim In-gyu,
so we'll be carrying out
a provisional seizure.
What are you talking about?
From what I know,
we still have some time left.
If there's a problem,
you can file an objection in court.
Let's get it done.
But this is... Wait.
Wait!
Ms. Kang.
The mayor of Jungil-gu
wants to meet with you tonight.
He's willing to use their budget
to proceed with the project.
He even sent a budget proposal
to meet the cost.
How did you manage to do this?
It's all because you wrote
an amazing proposal.
I guess he just didn't want
to lose his chance.
Make the dinner reservation,
and send the additional proposal
to the mayor.
Okay.
Hello?
Ms. Kang, the reporters have gathered
in the press room.
You should go first.
I left something in my office.
Okay.
Where are you coming from?
The doors are closing.
The central prosecutors' office.
Because of the audit.
I tried calling Mr. Lee,
but he won't even answer.
I can't reach him either.
If you do get a hold of him,
tell him that I'm willing to help.
Tell him I can help him
with the legal stuff.
Okay, I'll let him know.
Do you know Prosecutor Seo
at the Western Prosecutors' Office?
Prosecutor Seo Hyeong-cheol?
May I help you?
I'm here to meet Prosecutor Seo.
He and Mr. Jo are from the same college.
He issued the search
and seizure warrant on me.
The Minister of Justice
is going to use Prosecutor Seo
to investigate both you and Mr. Song.
You need to hurry up.
You'll be in trouble if you fail
to bring down Mr. Park at the audit.
Mr. Song won't protect you either.
Hey, how did it go?
Okay.
-What is it?
-I think the Ministry of Justice
is already on the move.
I'll call you later.
Mr. Jang, it's weird
that they seized Mr. Cha's house
when there's still some time left
until the due date.
-Who's the creditor?
-Kim In-gyu.
He was Mr. Cha's colleague at Bugang.
He lent Mr. Cha money when
Mr. Cha started having financial trouble.
Kim In-gyu became the team leader
of Bugang Electronics' finance team.
The Ministry of Justice did this
to prevent Mr. Cha from talking.
-What's all this?
-They're from the Ministry of Justice.
They mixed everything up.
It'll take a few days to organize these.
But the audit is tomorrow.
They're totally trying to screw us over.
How did the Ministry of Justice find out
that we were going to meet Mr. Cha?
Where's Mr. Cha's investigation file?
All his statements are censored.
I don't think it's going to help.
The opposition parties
including Kookmin Party
were busy badmouthing each other
-which caused eyebrows to raise.
-Sir.
What is it?
I asked the guys
at Mr. Lee Seong-min's office.
They didn't come up
with the questions that Mr. Lee asked.
But right before the audit,
Ms. Kang and Mr. Lee apparently met up
for a very short while.
We promise we will diligently carry out
the rest of the audit.
-About Assemblyman Jo's son...
-She is unbelievably cunning.
Look at her smiling
after having stabbed me in the back.
After all I did
to put her in that position.
What will you do, sir?
I'm going to wipe that smile off her face.
Please refrain from
writing any speculative articles.
Excuse me. Are you Mr. Kim In-gyu?
Yes, that's me.
I'm Jang Tae-jun
from Assemblyman Song Hui-seop's office.
Can you please just leave me alone?
I'm already having a hard time.
Mr. Cha's going through a lot worse.
The court even seized his house.
There was nothing I could do
to help Dong-ho.
So please leave,
and I hope we never meet again.
You're really putting me in a pickle
by coming here like this.
The prosecution is carrying out
a reinvestigation into Bugang Electronics.
If you just stay still,
you might end up getting hurt too.
Let me go.
Mr. Kim!
-Here.
-Thank you.
Did Mr. Cha pick up?
No.
I got a call from Mr. Oh
saying he's going to get off work
-along with Mr. Song.
-Okay.
And I think I also need to go home.
Okay, you should go.
-Okay. Bye, everyone.
-Go home safely.
I knew she was going to go home soon.
Bring me the budget and settlement
of the Ministry of Justice.
Everything?
Got it.
I'll go bring them.
Yes. I know that.
Yes, I know.
Ms. Kang, the mayor of Jungil-gu
can't come because
he has another appointment.
What appointment?
Well, he apparently needs
to meet with Mr. Jo Gap-yeong.
And he put a hold on the budget proposal.
I think Mr. Jo found out
that you gave those materials to Mr. Lee.
I guess I took things a bit too far.
After all, he got elected three times,
and he's on the same side
as the Minister of Justice.
He was never an easy mark.
What a waste.
Let's eat before we leave.
Excuse me. Mr. Jang.
I don't think organizing these materials
is going to help us.
They're mostly insignificant receipts.
And I need to go to the audit tomorrow.
Okay, fine.
-You can go home.
-Okay.
Why are you guys still here?
Aren't you going home?
I'll go a little later. You can go first.
-What about you, Do-gyeong?
-I'll go later as well.
Okay, then.
Don't spend too much time
on those receipts. You won't get anything.
It's okay. I'm enjoying it.
"Everything starts with something small."
It's what Mr. Jang once said
in an interview.
I should do my best
even if it seems petty.
Okay, then. Do your best.
See you.
Bye, sir.
WHISTLEBLOWER PROTECTION SYSTEM
Ms. Yun.
Yes?
Can I also take a look at the files
you organized
regarding the whistleblowers?
I'd like to know how a bill gets prepared.
WHISTLEBLOWER PROTECTION SYSTEM
HOW TO PROTECT WHISTLEBLOWERS
Sure.
Thank you.
Why are you here? I'm sure you're busy.
How's the patient?
Fortunately, she's better now.
Then why are you still here?
You should just go home.
I should be here when she wakes up.
I heard someone tampered with your sign.
You should request an investigation.
Don't try to take the blame
for everything again.
Ms. Kang also offered to help,
so you should talk to her.
How nice of her.
But I should focus on the patient for now.
I'll think about the rest later.
Don't worry.
By the way,
is there something wrong?
What do you mean?
You always come to me to nag
every time something doesn't work out.
You put on that nasty frown
like a mother-in-law who didn't eat.
What are you talking about?
I came because I was worried.
Aren't you sick of living like this?
Of course, I'm sick of it.
But I need to bear with it.
I worked so hard to get here.
A personal assistant, secretary,
and now the chief of staff.
I put up with taking care
of the old men for ten years.
So how can I stop now?
I need to climb up the ladder.
Yes, you deserve to climb that ladder.
You worked harder than anyone
and are smart.
But
don't climb up too high.
The higher you go, the harsher it gets.
Make sure you don't skip your meals.
ASSEMBLYWOMAN KANG
How about we get some fresh air?
Ms. Yun.
You don't need to feel sorry.
You can go home now.
-No, never mind. It's okay.
-You're making me feel uncomfortable.
You should go home.
Well, I do need to catch the last train.
I'll be off now.
Bye, Ms. Yun.
This is what I'm talking about.
It's nice to be here after so long.
You really like this place.
I get to sit here absentmindedly
without having to deal with anyone.
-Isn't it nice?
-Yes, it is nice.
What are you going to do with Mr. Jo?
We had our good days,
so I should at least give him
a proper farewell.
There's no such thing
as a beautiful farewell anyway.
You're the one who seems exhausted.
You're right.
This is all quite tiring.
Don't worry. No one can beat you.
Apart from me, that is.
So don't go around
looking like you lost already.
It doesn't suit you.
Let's do everything we can
to bring down the Minister of Justice.
I'll help.
Thanks. Let me rely on you.
HANSUNG LAUNDRY
Do-gyeong, is that you?
You just got home?
Yes, Mom. You're still awake?
-Why are you always so late?
-Well...
The civil service exam is coming up.
Goodnight.
Gosh, I wore it backwards.
HANJANG CONSTRUCTIONS, SUSPICIONS ARISE
REGARDING THEIR BLUEPRINT EDITS
SHIN JAE-GYEONG RAISED SAFETY ISSUES
BUT WAS COMPLETELY IGNORED
DODAM DAILY, REPORTER YUN HYE-WON
My goodness.
Hello, ma'am.
Okay.
No, there's no need to come.
Hey.
He's trying to show that it's his turf.
-Sir.
-Hello.
-I hope things go well.
Hello, sir.
-Have you found anything?
-No, not yet.
Question the relations between Bugang
and the central prosecutors' office.
-Meanwhile, I'll try to find something.
-Okay.
-Let's go.
-Yes, sir.
Do a better job.
Let's go.
How did Won-sik end up coming here
with Mr. Song?
They drank together all night last night
and slept at a dry sauna.
Don't be too bothered by him.
He's heading back today.
But I feel like he's up to something.
Mr. Oh met up
with the Minister of Justice's
chief of staff yesterday.
But don't say anything to him.
Ms. Yun
has been organizing all these materials
regarding the bill herself.
These are about
how to improve the current
whistleblower protection system.
I thought it might help
if at least one person read it,
so I brought it back.
129-16 JEHYEON-RO
Mr. Han.
The Minister of Justice will read
the oath out loud as the representative
and hand it in to the chairperson himself.
"I solemnly swear
that I, the Minister of Justice,
will sincerely receive the 2019 audit
regarding all the duties that fall under
the Ministry of Justice's jurisdiction
based on Article 61 of the Constitution,
-Good luck.
-Article 127 of the National Assembly Act,
and Article 10
of the Act on the Inspection
and Investigation of State Administration.
And in testimony as a witness,
I will speak truthfully
based on Article Seven of
-the Act on Testimony and Appraisal
-Send me the video of his testimony.
-before the National Assembly.
-Okay.
And if there is a lie in my statement
or written answer,
I swear that I will be punished
for perjury."
Hey.
Mr. Cha?
How did you find out?
-Who?
-Mr. Han...
This might be a little different,
but my dad also had to go through
a rough time.
No one even bothered to listen to him
including the police
and the company he worked for.
But there was one person
who stood by his side and supported him.
Thanks to him,
my dad was able to fight until the end.
Ms. Yun and I
will do everything in our power
to help people like you
who are fighting a hard battle.
We're trying our best to be of help.
We're not trying to use you, sir.
I know you're suffering,
but I came because I wanted to tell you
that there are people
who support your courage
and wish to help you out.
ANALYSIS ON THE IDEAL AND THE REAL
THAT WHISTLEBLOWERS GO THROUGH
Mr. Jang, this is Han Do-gyeong speaking.
We should find the transaction details
of the corporate credit card.
The CEO of Bugang, the chief prosecutor,
and the Minister of Justice
met up every month.
They used Bugang's corporate card
to pay for everything.
-Paid by whom?
-Kim In-gyu.
Send me the recording file.
Mr. Han, good work.
Thank you, sir.
INTERVIEW WITH MR. CHA
ASSEMBLYWOMAN KANG
Hey, I just sent you an audio file. I need
Bugang's credit card transaction details
and the testimony of Kim In-gyu.
Can you do it?
The news department of KTN is covering
the relations of the police
and Bugang Electronics.
I think they'll be interested
in the audio file.
I'll call the head of the news department.
Okay.
CONFERENCE HALL
AUDIT IN PROGESS
I think Tae-jun found something.
I couldn't hear it specifically,
but he mentioned something
about credit card transaction details.
Credit card?
If you stop Jang Tae-jun,
Mr. Park will help you
with your son's issue.
Just help us get through the audit.
Darn it.
He always orders me around
when he does nothing for me.
Mr. Kim!
Come in.
What brings you here?
I wanted to resolve
a misunderstanding between us.
-What misunderstanding?
-You seemed to be cautious of me.
You know Mr. Park was in charge
of Bugang's slush fund case
when he was
the deputy chief prosecutor, right?
Mr. Jang Tae-jun has been
looking into that case.
-I know that.
-Then do you also know
what Mr. Jang is up to?
What? Do you know anything?
-Yes.
-What is it?
What is he up to now?
Before I tell you,
please do make a call.
A call?
All right. Making a call
isn't hard to do.
Hey, Mr. Lee.
It's me.
If the personnel information
gets disclosed,
it may disrupt the duty of...
The police have begun
the search and seizure on Bugang.
-Reporters are there too.
-How dare you whisper to each other?
-Come on, Mr. Park.
-Call the Western Prosecutors' Office.
Mr. Park, you need to be aware
that the Ministry of Justice
isn't just any executive branch.
Let's go.
-Who are you?
-What did you say?
Darn it.
From now, the Western Prosecutors' Office
will conduct
the search and seizure on Bugang.
Let's go.
Like you said,
the prosecution made a move.
It's because you helped me out.
But the prosecution will take
all the documents. Is that okay?
The police would have
taken those away anyway.
I need to get something better.
Anyway, thanks. I want
to give you a present. Do you have time?
A present? What is it?
It'd not be fun if I told you already.
It'll be a surprise.
Okay. I'll look forward to it.
FINANCIAL TEAM LEADER
KIM IN-GYU
-Hello?
-This is Jang Tae-jun.
The prosecution will come
with a search and seizure warrant
for the finance team
as well as one for your arrest.
An arrest warrant?
-What are you talking about?
-How can I help you?
I'm Prosecutor Seo Hyeong-cheol.
Where is Mr. Kim In-gyu?
I'll tell you how you can survive.
Come to the parking lot right now.
-Begin the search.
-What is this?
You don't need to know.
Hey, start searching.
We will adjourn the session for dinner
and continue at 9:00 p.m.
-Sir.
-Yes?
Have you heard from Tae-jun?
No. I think he's doing this and that,
but I haven't heard from him.
You must be hungry. Let's eat.
How can I eat in this situation?
Jang Tae-jun, that idiot.
What in the world is he up to?
They found the documents,
but they lost Kim In-gyu.
-They lost him?
-They checked the CCTV footage,
and he got on Mr. Jang's car to escape.
-Get him on the wanted list and find him.
-Yes, sir.
Have you ever visited Mr. Cha?
His limbs are paralyzed
because of brain damage.
He used up all of his money
on the hospital bill and the lawsuit.
Are you trying to make me feel bad for him
and bear witness?
Don't be delusional.
If men like you had had any conscience,
this wouldn't have happened.
I'm letting you know
that you will end up
like Mr. Cha very soon.
That won't happen.
Do you think the Minister of Justice
will help you?
He's the one who approved
of the arrest warrant for you.
Did you plan this with Bugang in advance
to make Seoul Central District
Prosecutors' Office
delay their investigation?
That did not happen.
I'm aware of the seriousness
of the Bugang case, so I ordered
the Western Prosecutors' Office
to investigate Bugang's financial team
and related persons.
If Bugang and I have any connections,
I will resign from my office.
Stop asking that question now.
"Stop asking"? I continue to ask you
because of your half-hearted answers.
What should I do now?
You should stay in hiding for a while.
Hotel Chantier, Room 1813.
-Until when?
-That depends on what you can tell me.
All the documents that could be
used as evidence were destroyed.
I heard Mr. Park, Mr. Choe,
and the CEO of Bugang
have a meeting periodically.
They used to meet in Gwacheon,
but after what happened to Dong-ho,
I heard they meet at a restaurant
in Samcheong-dong.
Where is that?
No idea.
They travel by taxi, and they
use the corporate credit cards
of Bugang's subsidiaries,
so there is no way I can find out.
When do they have that meeting?
Once a month,
on the last Friday.
Who's that?
Someone who will protect you.
This is a huge surprise present.
He's on the wanted list.
That's why I said it's a surprise.
He's more like a bomb, not a present.
Let's keep our eyes on him
and see if he'll be a bomb or a firework.
Please take care of him.
-Yes, sir.
-Check Mr. Park's schedule
for last Friday of each month.
Get me a list of restaurants
-near Samcheong-dong.
-Yes, sir.
Mr. Han, Ms. No. I need your help.
-Sure.
-Okay.
Is this Cheongwon Prison?
I'm Secretary Yun Hye-won
from Assemblyman Song's office.
I called to check the schedule
of the Minister of Justice.
On March 29th, 2019,
it says he stopped by to visit.
Is this true?
Thank you.
Mr. Park canceled everything
that was scheduled on Friday afternoons.
The Ministry of Justice refused to say
where he went
on Friday afternoons
because that's his private life.
-Ms. No.
-Yes?
I listed up the restaurants
that high-ranking officials usually go to.
There are 32 restaurants
with private rooms.
I think we can narrow it down.
I organized the receipts
of his corporate card on last Fridays.
I found receipts for taxi rides.
The time he got on and off
and the distance are all similar.
It was last used the next day
after the audit ended.
Mr. Park's office is 26km away
from Samcheong-dong.
Check the distances between his office
-and those restaurants.
-Yes, sir.
-And Mr. Han...
-Should I call the taxi companies
and find out where Mr. Park got off?
-That's a good idea. Do that.
-Yes, I will.
Can we get all this done before midnight?
We have to try.
Call me if you find anything.
-Yes, sir.
-See you.
Why midnight?
According to the National Assembly Law,
the audit must end before midnight.
If it must continue after midnight,
the assemblymen must come to an agreement.
If they don't, the audit will be over.
Over?
It'll be the end of this year's audit
for the Ministry of Justice.
Is this Wooseong Taxi?
-He doesn't pick up, does he?
-No.
Darn it.
Thanks.
-What are you doing here?
-I was just...
Where's Tae-jun? Come here.
-Sir, please...
-Come here. Attention!
-Darn you.
-Sir, let's go.
-I'm sorry!
-Call Tae-jun.
Darn it.
Mr. Jang, where are you?
-Mr. Song is looking for you.
-I'll be there shortly.
Call me if they agree
-to continue the audit after midnight.
-Mr. Jang!
-Yes?
-Mr. Jang, we found the restaurant.
It's 47-1 Samcheong-dong.
DETECTIVE LEE
The audit will resume now.
Everyone, please be seated.
-Where's Tae-jun?
-He'll be here soon.
That punk said that he'd find something.
Where in the world is he?
Tell him to come quickly!
Yes, sir.
Goodness.
Everyone, please come inside.
Hello.
I don't think Tae-jun found anything.
-Really?
-I mean, he hasn't shown up.
You remember what I asked you
this afternoon, right?
If the audit ends smoothly,
I'll take good care of it.
Mr. Jang.
-Hey.
-Hello.
Excuse me.
Do you have a reservation?
Hello.
I'm a detective.
-Can you cooperate with...
-This is our business hour.
I know, but it'll only take a second.
We received a tip-off,
so I just need to ask a few questions.
RESERVATIONS
NAME: BUGANG, CENTRAL, JUSTICE
They're discussing whether
to continue the audit past midnight.
Yes, get me Mr. Song.
It's an emergency.
Darn it.
Assemblyman Song,
won't you ask any questions?
Mr. Park apologized to you already.
That wasn't a proper apology.
He just said a few excuses
that didn't even make sense.
How can I ask him any questions?
Mr. Song.
-Where are you?
-Mr. Song,
you should end the audit
for the Ministry of Justice now.
Okay. Hang up, you jerk.
Assemblyman Song,
do you have any questions?
Assemblyman Song, any questions?
I have none.
All the assemblymen
have asked their questions.
Is there anyone
who wants to ask additional questions?
If you do not have any objections,
we will not continue the audit.
That will be the end of the 2019 audit
for the Ministry of Justice.
I announce the end of the audit.
Look how happy he is.
He looks like a victorious general.
The fight isn't over yet.
He can't be a victorious general.
You returned empty-handed.
Stop spewing nonsense.
Mr. Song, you should end the audit
for the Ministry of Justice now.
The audit for the Ministry of Justice
has just ended.
But Assemblyman Song Hui-seop's office
found the evidence of a false witness
among Minister Park Jong-gil statements,
and they plan on taking legal actions.
Minister Park denied the charge
that he periodically met the CEO of Bugang
and the chief prosecutor
to delay the investigation.
However, he had regular meetings
with them every month.
And it's been confirmed that
some young women accompanied them.
-Please move aside.
-Did you lie?
-Did you just bear false witness?
-Tell us something!
You're right.
We'll charge the Minister of Justice
for perjury tomorrow morning.
I will send you the press release soon.
Breaking news.
Minister Park is being accused
of delaying the investigation
regarding the unfair dismissal
of Bugang employees
after meeting the CEO of Bugang
and the chief prosecutor.
This is why you told me
to finish the audit.
Bearing false witness during an audit
will get him at least a year,
up to ten years in prison.
When a general loses in a fight,
he must give up his life.
Shouldn't we twist his neck even more
so that he can't fight back?
Ms. Kang is working on it already.
Minister Park will face at least a year...
I already told you everything that I know.
You might remember more.
Then
shall we start again?
PROUD FLESH OINTMENT
You can use this.
Thank you.
Ms. Yun, wait for me.
This stop is Dangsan.
The doors are on your left.
The doors are opening.
Great work today.
See you tomorrow.
Great work.
-The doors are closing.
-Ms. Yun!
-Yes, of course.
-Great work.
Mr. Lee, thanks for waiting.
Thank you.
Tae-jun, let's eat lunch tomorrow.
-Yes, sir.
-Good. Let's go.
Goodness.
Where's Mr. Oh?
He went back to the district office
after saying goodbye to Mr. Song.
Yes, Mr. Oh?
The passcode for our office?
It's 57983.
Sure.
-Was that Mr. Oh?
-Yes.
He said he left something in the office.
Are there any sticky notes lying around?
You should take a taxi.
ROOM 803, SHIN J GYEONG
I checked the contents,
and those were the files
that Mr. Jo's office had kept.
What about Mr. Jo's materials on me?
They have been destroyed.
I told him to plow the field,
but that ox has been
planning something else.
Did that idiot forget who his owner is?
Who's your owner, idiot?
It's me. I'm your owner.
I'm your owner, you son of a bitch!
There's this stupid ox
who won't listen to its owner.
You even steal now?
If you had such an important thing,
you should have kept it well.
You should go down to the district office.
Mr. Song wanted me to tell you
that you can come back
once you deal with Seobuk Market.
We need to end this well.
Where is Kang Seon-yeong?
You were plotting against me
in a place like this?
So, you've been digging a pit for me?
Mr. Oh told us where you were, you fool.
I suppose Mr. Song got us under his thumb.
Kim In-gyu is my final card.