Tae-jun.
If you dig a little deeper,
you might end up burying
Kang Seon-yeong in that pit, not me.
TRANSACTION HISTORY, JEONG YU-MI
PRIVATE ACCOUNTS OF JEONG YU-MI
SAMYEONG BANK
"Samyeong Bank"?
What about it?
The president of Samyeong Bank
is her father.
Truth buried deep beneath the lies.
That appalling truth
now has risen to the surface.
Did you think that fox became
an assemblywoman
only through proper means?
If you take this a step further,
you will not be taking me down.
You will be taking Kang Seon-yeong down.
An opponent with his back against the wall
does not hesitate
when he sees a chance to retaliate.
However,
I can't let him eat us alive like this.
There will only be one outcome.
EPISODE 8 HUNT
What are you doing here?
I thought you were never
going to talk to me again.
That's what I thought too.
It seems like you had a rough time.
PRESIDENT OF SAMYEONG BANK,
KANG SEONG-YEOP
Are you involved in these bank accounts
under borrowed names?
-Is this what you came here to ask?
-Answer me.
Must you hear me say it?
Do you know
where that money
came from?
Dad?
I know.
Then do you also know
what that money was used for?
Is that important?
You helped launder money for a slush fund.
I don't care who it was from.
That money is the reason
this bank is still up and running.
It also helped me raise you
and put food on our table
Save the excuses.
The money was for yourself.
Mom and I managed perfectly
without your help.
Do you really believe
you became assemblywoman
of the Daehan Party by yourself?
-What are you saying?
-I said what I said.
Why do you think those people
nominated you for the spot?
Even if Kang Seon-yeong
were a hot-shot lawyer
and the host of a current affairs TV show,
did you seriously think
she could have made it
into the National Assembly
with no backup at all?
Her father's power and influence
got her the spot.
Both your father and hers
do have a knack in
getting in their children's way.
My goodness.
KANG SEON-YEONG
JANG TAE-JUN
-Where's Won-sik?
-He was spotted at
the airport parking lot,
but it seems
he left the car and fled the scene.
After calling his family
in the Philippines,
he turned off his phone too.
Find Won-sik and bring him to me.
Make sure he's alive.
Yes, sir.
YUN HYE-WON
-Yes?
-Oh Won-sik is in the wind.
Ask Mr. Yang to check
the prosecution's movements.
We must find him
before Song Hui-seop does.
ASSEMBLYMAN JANG TAE-JUN'S OFFICE
Mr. Han.
Are you done
looking into the bank accounts?
Does Mr. Jang's office know?
No, not yet.
Don't tell anyone. If word gets out,
Ms. Kang might have to resign.
I'll talk to her myself.
Mr. Han?
No, Ms. Kang is still looking into them.
Please let me know
once you know something.
Yes, of course.
Ms. Kang.
Seung-u, it's me.
We're still looking into
the bank accounts.
We need more time.
-Good morning.
-Sir, good morning.
Yes.
I'll send a press release
as soon as I know more.
The prosecution doesn't have
an all-points bulletin out on Mr. Oh yet.
They know that an open investigation
will hurt Minister Song too.
Is Mr. Oh avoiding your calls as well?
His phone has been turned off.
It seems he's gone into hiding.
Minister Song will have
a hard time tracking him down then.
That applies to us too.
It seems like there is only one way left
to find Oh Won-sik now.
We must expose the bank accounts.
Ms. Kang's office will soon
send over the files.
The bank that authorized them
is Samyeong Bank.
Samyeong Bank?
Then Ms. Kang...
No wonder Mr. Han kept the truth from me.
The National Tax Service
sent files to Ms. Kang
on accounts that they suspected
of being in borrowed names.
However, Mr. Han didn't mention it.
The files regarding the bank accounts
must be in Ms. Kang's possession.
If Ms. Kang turns against us,
the files that prove the accounts exist
could be destroyed.
If your father is involved,
it's sure to wreak havoc on the case.
I'm aware of that.
I don't know what I should say
to Assemblyman Jang.
Don't say anything
and let me take care of it.
I'll meet with your father
and deal with the bank accounts.
I can't bury this.
I'm not saying that you should.
It's election season soon.
You can reveal this
after you're reelected.
It doesn't matter
that you had nothing to do with it.
You know how it will look for the press.
If they question your initial nomination,
everything, including the election, fails.
Ms. Kang.
I searched everywhere for Mr. Oh,
but he is still in the wind.
-Even his old family home?
-Yes.
Then check everything again
from the beginning.
Also, tell him this
as soon as you hear from him.
Tell him to come home and stop
making things harder on himself.
Yes, sir.
Imbecile.
Shit.
Mr. Lee.
Oh, hey.
Did Mr. Oh cause some sort of trouble?
I'm not sure. It's not like
I should know everything.
What did Minister Song say?
I'm supposed to find
even the smallest trace.
How can I locate someone
who's off the grid?
Anyway, I'll get going. Take care.
Sure. Carry on.
HOTEL ROO
Based on witness statements,
the fire department
has begun its investigation
by focusing on
where the fire originated from.
Yesterday around 9:50 p.m.,
near the East Yeongcheon Interchange,
a tow-truck crashed into a median strip.
The injured driver
who was transported to the hospital
didn't suffer any fatal injuries.
The police are investigating the accident
based on the driver's statement...
PHILIPPINES HOME
...that it was caused
due to one of the rear tires falling off.
Three months into the movement
of boycotting Japanese goods
has led to a new trend in workplaces.
Over ten years...
Ms. Yun.
Can we talk?
Ms. Lee asked me
not to reveal the document.
Of course.
I would've asked the same thing
if I were her.
I'm not sure if this is what's best
for Ms. Kang.
She believes that a formal investigation
into Minister Song and Youngil Group
must be conducted.
So not revealing this information
isn't what she'd want.
Keeping one's integrity
and upholding justice.
I've seen too many
who crumbled while trying to do so.
You know someone
who fits that description too.
It's sad, you know.
If only he compromised just a little bit.
It's also upsetting
how you can't survive
unless you join hands
with someone with greater power.
Do you think that she shouldn't
reveal the truth about the bank accounts?
That choice is yours.
Her secretary is you, not me.
Just think about what our role is.
Protect Ms. Kang in your own way.
That is our job.
Tae-jun, I'm sorry
for not calling sooner.
Did you meet your father?
You know about it?
Why didn't you say anything?
What if I had destroyed the evidence?
I trust you'll make the right decision.
You're different from me.
Why did I never connect the dots?
I always thought
I got here on my own.
I am Kang Seon-yeong of the Daehan Party.
We'll begin the press conference
calling for Floor Leader
Song Hui-seop's resignation.
This person has contributed greatly
in improving women's rights
-as a proud woman of our society.
-Thank you.
We call for an immediate resignation
of Assemblyman Lee
who's undermined the constitutionalism.
We must not wait any longer.
We must conduct this audit
to figure out the truth
behind the chemical spill.
You did get here on your own.
Don't ever deny that.
Without my father's reputation,
it wouldn't have been so easy.
I will start all over from square one
solely on my own.
What are you doing here now?
I thought I'd at least say goodbye.
Must you be so stubborn?
What's done is done.
Nothing good will come from
digging up the past.
That's not true.
Many will learn that whoever abuses
power and status to maintain power
will be punished.
However small and old
their wrongdoings may be,
it is impossible to erase them.
People will learn that.
Someone else would've done it
even if I had chosen not to.
Companies grew because of it,
and new jobs were created.
You call that an excuse?
You'll be in trouble
once this is revealed too.
It's election season soon.
You could end up
losing your position in office.
And why does that scare you?
What?
You were never afraid
when Mom and I left you,
so why are you worried
about me losing my position?
Seon-yeong.
I thought I had escaped you,
but I was still living under your shadow.
I refuse to walk on the path
you cleared for me.
Even if I trip and get mud all over me,
I will go my own way however I see fit.
PRESS ROOM
Here's your speech.
Good job.
Send out the press release once I'm done.
Yes, ma'am.
You'll be all right.
You've been through worse, right?
Thank you for saying that.
I am Assemblywoman Kang
of the Daehan Party.
Minister Song Hui-seop's chief of staff,
Mr. Oh Won-sik,
has been found
to have received illegal funds
through a borrowed-name bank account.
Mr. Oh was found to possess a slush fund
of 2.7 billion won that currently sits
in a bank account under his wife's name.
The true owner of the account
seems to be Minister Song.
Since the current
Minister of Justice is involved,
a thorough investigation
must be conducted.
The source of this money should
also be revealed as soon as possible.
I will start all over from square one
solely on my own.
I'm talking to the press tomorrow.
You'll be under the media's scrutiny too.
I'm ready for that.
Your job now
is to find Oh Won-sik.
-Ms. Kang!
-There she is.
Do you have proof
that the account is Minister Song's?
Oh Won-sik served as
Minister Song's chief of staff
for the past ten years.
Meanwhile, Mr. Oh's wife hasn't earned
a single penny since their marriage.
The amount of money found in the account
couldn't have been reached
with a chief of staff's salary.
There's reason to believe that the account
is Minister Song's instead.
In your opinion,
how should the investigation be conducted?
Whether Minister Song truly owns the money
as well as the source of the money,
and what favors and privileges
were exchanged
should be brought to light.
That being said,
since Minister Song is a prime suspect,
I am worried about the prosecution
conducting a fair investigation.
Samyeong Bank is on the list you provided.
Isn't the president of Samyeong Bank,
Kang Seong-yeop, your father?
Yes, he is.
Ma'am, we should go.
-He's your father?
-Coming through.
-Is your father involved?
-A press release will be sent out.
-Ma'am!
-Ma'am, wait.
Ma'am, hold on.
Minister Song will make his move.
Send out the press release.
-Yes, sir.
-Ma'am, hold on.
Assemblywoman Kang of the Daehan Party
raised suspicion in regards to
Minister Song's chief of staff Oh Won-sik
receiving illegal funds.
According to Ms. Kang,
a slush fund of 2.7 billion won
was found in a bank account
under Mr. Oh's wife's name.
She asked an investigation to be held
-to prove Minister Song's ownership
-She dug her own grave.
and to find the source of the fund.
Meanwhile, many of the accounts
-were opened at Samyeong Bank...
-Have my car ready.
Sir!
There are reporters outside.
Sir, what do you know
about these accounts?
-Is this a result of bribery?
-How long have you worked with Mr. Oh?
I apologize to the public
for even being named
in an unfortunate scandal.
I was aware of the bank accounts,
and an internal investigation
was being conducted.
Mr. Oh Won-sik
went into hiding during our investigation.
He is currently on our most wanted list.
I had no idea what was happening,
but since my chief of staff is involved,
I am at fault too.
Even though he is my chief of staff,
I will make sure that a serious
and thorough investigation is conducted.
JANG TAE-JUN
Mr. Song banned you
from leaving the country.
If you want to live, call me.
-Sir!
-Just one more thing.
-Wait.
-Sir, please.
We will soon send over a press release.
-Wait.
-Sir!
-Please.
-Any more words?
Jang Tae-jun, you bastard.
How dare you set my house on fire
just so that you could find my stray dog?
Jong-uk.
Feed Kang Seon-yeong and her father
to the press.
Yes, sir.
Those sons of bitches.
CHAIRMAN SUNG
With suspicions raised regarding
illegal funds received
by Oh Won-sik, his chief of staff,
Minister Song...
-Tae-jun,
-issued an all-points bulletin...
help me.
-The immediate search...
-Where are you?
Tell me if you wish to live.
Where are you?
Yes?
No, Ms. Kang isn't involved.
-Yes?
-Mr. Mun, yes.
-That's right.
-You'll be
the first to receive our press release.
-Thank you.
-Ms. Lee?
Wait, are you good to be here?
Of course not.
But how can I sit around
in a time of crisis?
-Is that the press release?
-Would you look over it?
Who organized the press conference?
-Was it you?
-No, ma'am.
It was Mr. Han.
Get over here.
You kept the press conference from me.
Ms. Kang said
that you'd be against it.
Still, you should've told me.
You knew of the risk it entails.
-I did.
-Then you should've stopped her!
I know what you're worried about,
but following Ms. Kang's lead
and encouraging her choices
are what we're supposed to do.
You know very well
how hard she worked for this matter.
I didn't think it was right
to give up on this chance.
There would've been
another time to reveal the truth!
No.
This moment
was our only window of opportunity.
If we don't reveal the truth now,
-we'll never be able to bring them down.
-Ma'am--
Minister Song
was aware of my weakness.
He knew, but he kept it to himself.
I was never a threat to him.
He knew he could get rid of me
at any given time.
He also now knows
that I will never be his puppet
which means he won't nominate me.
As Minister of Justice,
he will control the prosecution
and intimidate those of high power.
I won't even be able to run for election.
This is our last chance.
Minister Song
will try to have the press
focus on you and your father.
We must highlight just how serious
Minister Song's scandal is.
I'll rewrite the press release.
Thank you.
I'm on my way to meet Mr. Oh.
It'll take about an hour.
ROOM 422, CHEONGMOK MOTEL,
Will Mr. Oh talk easily?
I'll have to make him talk.
-I'll stay in touch.
-Yes, sir.
The scandal involving my chief of staff
will soon subside.
We should eat.
Feeding him to the wolves
won't be enough to bury this scandal.
I know, sir. Considering what it implies,
I'll have to at least
bring in the president of Samyeong Bank
for questioning.
It will take some time,
but it'll be solved--
Is it really necessary
to get him involved?
I'll choose a scapegoat of a lower rank,
so let the case end with him.
But sir,
without questioning the president,
the public--
Then you should've taken care of things
before it got this far.
You're the Minister of Justice,
aren't you?
My apologies, sir.
It seems like old age
has taken away the cleverness
you once had when you were young.
Hey!
This beef tastes like a dead old cow.
How dare you serve this for me to eat?
My apologies, sir.
I'll have them make another one.
-Dismissed.
-I'm sorry, sir.
Minister Song,
you can always set another table
if you hate the meal you're served.
I really hope that won't be
the case between us.
Yes, sir.
It's me.
Mr. Song can't do this to me.
The number of dirty things
I did for him...
I didn't question him
when he nominated you.
You know that.
I'm not here to hear you whine.
You said you'd help me.
Then start talking.
Save me first.
Get me on a boat to China or Vietnam.
Then before I set sail,
I'll tell you everything I know.
You have about 20 minutes.
To do what?
I gave the prosecution this address.
-What?
-Wake up, will you?
Know that I'm the only one
who can help you out of his mess.
Now, sit.
I'll get you a lawyer.
It's me.
One second.
Go ahead.
ASSEMBLYWOMAN KANG SEON-YEONG
This is Kang Seon-yeong.
Who financed Minister Song's slush fund
and how was it laundered?
I want to know everything.
Begin.
Minister Song...
took bearer bonds in exchange for stopping
the Youngil Group
slush fund investigation.
The bearer bonds were then
split into smaller bonds to buy
real estate via offshore trust companies.
Some were cashed in and put into
borrowed-name accounts.
That cash
was then used to fund Samil Association
by Minister Song and Chairman Sung.
How much are we talking about?
I don't know the exact amount,
but I know there are other
borrowed-name accounts than mine.
The total amount
should be around 32 billion won.
How was the money transferred?
The money was delivered
upon request in 50,000 won notes.
-Is there proof?
-No.
I made the delivery myself.
If there's no proof
that Minister Song received the money,
it'll just be taken as
Mr. Oh's sole claim.
Then we must find proof that Minister Song
and Chairman Sung are connected.
I'll call you back once I wrap things up.
All right.
Tae-jun.
What will happen to me
if you can't find proof?
You'll take the fall
for all the illegal money
stashed by those two.
They will be there in five minutes.
What is it?
Run now and you will never
see your family again!
Then what am I supposed to do?
You must help us get Minister Song.
What happened?
The prosecution just arrested him.
Will Chairman Sung make the move
you're anticipating?
I'll have to force him to.
Minister Song, they found Mr. Oh.
Where is he?
Prosecutor Seo is bringing him
to the Ministry.
YUN HYE-WON
-Have you found out?
-Yes,
Mr. Sung is attending
the Global Business Forum
held at Sevita Hotel.
Okay.
Hello, Chairman Sung.
Hi.
Chairman Sung.
THE 5TH GLOBAL BUSINESS FORUM
Well, if it isn't Assemblyman Jang.
What brings you here?
May I have a word with you?
I don't believe
we have anything to talk about.
Please make an appointment next time.
You'll want to hear this
if you want to know
what Minister Song's plan is.
Why did you disappear?
Well...
I just...
Did you think I'd kill you?
I'm sorry, Minister Song.
-Won-sik.
-Yes, Minister Song.
Confess to the prosecution
that the money in the bank accounts
belongs to Mr. Sung.
Don't worry about your wife and daughter.
I'll look after them.
Minister Song.
How long have you been working for me?
I've served you for ten years now.
Ten years is a long time.
I'd say it's time for you
to grab some power yourself.
Pardon?
You'll probably serve two to three years.
Consider it a little vacation.
By the time you're back,
I'll be the president of this country.
Of course.
You can be
the Chief Presidential Secretary,
the director of the foundation,
you just name it.
What will happen to Mr. Sung then?
-It's Prosecutor Seo.
-Come in.
-Is everything ready?
-Yes.
Request an arrest warrant for Mr. Sung.
Yes, sir.
Goodness.
JANG TAE-JUN
I'll leave my past behind
and enter the Blue House as a new person.
All you have to do
is mention Mr. Sung's name
to the prosecution.
I'll take care of
everything else from there.
Yes, sir.
-Take him.
-Yes, sir.
OH WON-SIK
He's biting the hand that's fed him
all these years.
Why did you come to me?
I'm here to get the information
on the political funds
I failed to get from Mr. Lee.
Why should I
give it to you?
Isn't what you just heard reason enough?
Minister Song is holding
all the material on Mr. Lee
that Seoul Central Prosecutors' Office
was investigating.
Now that Minister Song
has ordered you arrested,
you'll probably spend
the rest of your life in prison.
Let me think about it.
It's been revealed that Kang Seong-yeop,
the president of Samyeong Bank,
was involved
in the management
of Oh Won-sik's illegal funds.
Mr. Kang is the father of Assemblywoman
Kang Seon-yeong of the Daehan Party
and is suspected of playing a part
in Assemblywoman Kang's nomination
for the last legislative election.
While the Election Committee requested
the prosecution for an investigation,
if the allegations turn out to be true,
Assemblywoman Kang
will most likely have to face
legal processes.
If she ends up
being sentenced to prison
or fined more than a million won,
her election will be annulled.
They make it sound as if
you handed out bribes to be nominated.
It sure makes a nice story.
It's easier to grab people's attention
when things are up in the air.
Would there be a way
to turn the public opinion around?
The illegal funds should be
at the center of attention.
Let's use the public against them.
Please schedule an interview.
Will you be all right?
I know what people want to hear.
I want them to hear it from me.
There is much speculation
about whether Assemblywoman Kang
was involved in Mr. Kang Seong-yeop's
illegal funds deal.
The information about the accounts, sir.
The rest has been destroyed,
and the traces left in the database
are being deleted at the moment.
Okay. You may leave.
If the allegations prove to be true,
Assemblywoman Kang will be
sentenced to prison or fined
more than a million won for violating
the Public Official Election Act.
This might lead to Assemblywoman Kang's
losing her seat in the National Assembly.
ASSEMBLYMAN KANG SEON-YEONG'S OFFICE
Ms. Lee, you got out of the hospital?
How are you doing?
Not very well at all.
But Ms. Kang's situation seemed
much worse than mine,
so I couldn't lie still.
-Don't strain yourself.
-I won't.
Where's Mr. Jang?
He's meeting with Mr. Sung.
He better sort it out quickly,
or Ms. Kang will get hurt first.
How's Ms. Kang holding up?
She asked for an interview.
She wants to come to the front.
It might be better than letting
all kinds of rumors spread.
We'll monitor the situation too.
Tell me when the interview is scheduled.
Will do.
If anything happens to Ms. Kang
because of this,
I'll hold Jang Tae-jun responsible
whether he's an assemblyman or not.
Make sure he sorts it out.
Going down.
"Jang Tae-jun"?
While most of
the borrowed-name bank accounts
held by Oh, the chief of staff
of the Minister of Justice,
turned out to have been opened
at Samyeong Bank,
its president Kang Seong-yeop
was found to be father to Assemblywoman
Kang Seon-yeong of the Daehan Party.
-Come in.
-Mr. Kang's
involvement in the management
of Mr. Oh's illegal funds
-was followed by...
-This is Mr. Oh's cell phone.
It seems like he was on the phone
with Jang Tae-jun
when he was here earlier.
CALL HISTORY
JANG TAE-JUN
What will happen to Mr. Sung then?
Request an arrest warrant for Mr. Sung.
CHAIRMAN SUNG
Chairman Sung has summoned
the Prosecutor General
and the chief prosecutors
at the Anti-Corruption Unit.
-Find out where they meet.
-Yes, sir.
Okay. Oh, is that right?
Did Dad really say that?
My goodness.
English is important,
but Korean should be a priority
for Koreans, don't you think?
Right.
Seung-a, sweetie, you must be big by now.
All right. I'll give the phone
to your dad now.
-Won-sik.
-Yes?
Seung-a doesn't like her English friends.
She wants to come back to Korea.
Talk to her.
Hi, Seung-a.
Daddy was busy working
and couldn't call you.
-Won-sik.
-Yes, sir.
I even offered to help out
while you're in prison.
How could you stab me in the back?
-How could you?
-Minister Song.
I can see to it that Seung-a and your wife
can never set foot in Korea again.
Minister Song, I'm sorry.
I made a terrible mistake.
Please forgive me.
How much
does Jang Tae-jun know?
Well...
Tae-jun.
Let's go get something to eat.
-Enjoy.
-Thanks.
I haven't eaten anything all day
because of you.
I'm starving.
Let's eat.
I feel sorry for Won-sik.
You should leave him alone.
I don't want to go
to his funeral just yet.
You're the one who's sacrificing him
after having him at your beck and call
for ten years.
Who's sacrificing who?
He's just paying for what he's done.
What Oh Won-sik got is just the crumbs
while you pocketed
a whopping 32 billion won.
You should both pay for what you've done.
A "whopping" 32 billion won? You think?
Hey, I wouldn't be satisfied
with 320 billion won.
Hadn't I handed out that money
to everyone,
I wouldn't have made it here.
You did a good job as the mother bird.
So are you proud of being alive
after you've corrupted the political world
to such extents?
Look, Tae-jun.
You used to be in my nest too.
When you begged me for nomination,
you were like a baby bird
desperately waiting for food
with your mouth wide open.
Now that you're wearing that gold badge,
have you forgotten that all?
If there's something
I should pay for, I will.
But still,
I must change the world.
You want to see it through?
Yes.
I cannot let someone like you
influence the world anymore.
ASSEMBLYWOMAN KANG SEON-YEONG
DAD
What's the matter?
Can we meet? I have something to tell you.
All right.
Hello, Mr. Seo.
Where's Chairman Sung right now?
Okay.
-Turn the car around.
-Yes, sir.
Song Hui-seop
is the current Minister of Justice.
Investigating him might backfire on us.
He still has many prosecutors on his side.
If you don't want any risks,
you could stick to catching
guppies in a small stream.
But shouldn't
men in your positions aim higher
and catch a boatful of fish
to make your time worthwhile?
By investigating Minister Song,
we'll lose some,
but we'll win even more.
The Prosecutor General who dug into
the corruption
of the running Minister of Justice.
Wouldn't that title give you an edge
in the next legislative election?
If being an assemblyman is not your thing,
how about the Minster of Justice?
I thought you left me out
because the food was too humble,
but apparently, you were enjoying
a feast without me.
Will you excuse us?
I have something to discuss
with Chairman Sung in private.
Chairman Sung is under investigation.
Would you like to accompany him to the
interrogation room with your badges on?
Leave now.
Chairman Sung.
The two of us going after each other
isn't going to make anyone happy.
So why couldn't you make sure everything--
That bullshit again.
Are you out of your mind?
You're the one
who made things complicated!
You seem to keep forgetting,
but the man sitting in front of you
is the Minister of Justice
of this country.
You've completely lost your mind.
Without me,
how are you going to get away with
ordering their murders?
Choe Yong-hyeon, Go Seok-man,
and Lee Chang-jin.
They were all killed
to clean up the mess you made.
You need me as the Minister of Justice
if you want a chance
at being released on bail, paroled,
or given a special pardon.
There's no statute of limitations
for murder by proxy.
Complaining is useless.
Don't you dare think about starting over.
Just take whatever you have left
and enjoy them.
The president of Samyeong Bank
will be arrested.
You'll be investigated too.
Wait quietly for my men tomorrow.
Got it?
Song Hui-seop seems to know everything.
He might even have evidence.
What do you want me to do?
I'll leave my past behind
and enter the Blue House as a new person.
All you have to do
is mention Mr. Sung's name
to the prosecution.
I'll take care of
everything else from there.
I've been giving my cow
only the best fodder I could find,
but it just won't listen to its master.
That leaves me no choice
but to handle it my way.
Have you heard back from Chairman Sung?
He's swayed, but I'm
still waiting for his answer.
What if he refuses
to hand over the information?
Even so, a crack has started.
Everything will crumble away soon.
How's Ms. Kang?
Things aren't going well.
The Election Committee will
start looking into her nomination process.
CHAIRMAN SUNG YEONG-GI
Hello. Are you done thinking?
I know where it is. I'll be right there.
I'll call you as soon as I have it.
Okay.
Have a seat.
It'd been such a long time,
and we ended up fighting.
Let's eat together.
You'll have to eat alone.
I wouldn't have come
if I knew this was in store.
Your mom.
I hear you visit her often.
And I could tell.
You went to visit her?
Yes.
Why'd you wait
until she was dead to do that?
There are many things
you don't know about.
I'm not interested.
Nothing you tell me today
could ever change the fact
that you abandoned me and Mom.
But...
Supreme Prosecutors' Office.
Come with us quietly.
I hope we'll get
another chance to eat together.
I asked the caretaker
to give your mom's grave
a little touch-up.
Go take a look.
I haven't held
a press conference
in a while now, right?
I'm sure you have many questions.
Please feel free to ask me anything.
I'm ready to answer.
Thank you for arranging this.
As far as I know,
Mr. Oh Won-sik has worked for you
for many years now.
Were you really not aware of what he did?
It's really unfortunate indeed.
He's such a family man.
He adores his daughter.
Aren't all parents the same?
He must have wanted
some money for his child.
I was actually thinking of helping him out
with his daughter's college tuition
in the future.
But I regret not helping him earlier.
I should've been more thoughtful.
Is the investigation being conducted
as it should be?
Of course. It definitely is.
But to see my own man
being investigated like that
sure does make me sad.
I can't even sleep well these days.
Still, what can I do?
I couldn't cover up for him
just because he's worked for me.
Oh Won-sik, who had been
under investigation
for his illegal funds allegations,
-Ms. Kang.
-confessed
that the bank accounts belonged to him
and has been taken into custody.
He has received
billions of won from businesses
in return for dealing with
complaints against them.
He also stated that Minister Song
was unrelated to the case.
The prosecution is trying to find out
which companies slipped money...
Does this mean
that Mr. Oh is taking all the blame?
Mr. Oh is back
on Minister Song's side now.
He's not saying a thing
about Youngil Group or Minister Song.
This doesn't feel right.
...denied any involvement in the affair.
Some people say that Youngil Group
slipped money to Mr. Oh.
I've heard that rumor myself.
If anything is found, Youngil Group will,
of course, be investigated.
I promise the investigation
will be thorough
and will leave no doubt.
Don't worry.
-Thank you.
-Thank you for coming.
Bye.
I told you to wait quietly.
What are you doing out here?
Minister Song.
I'd like to show you
something interesting.
I shouldn't have all the fun, should I?
-Get in.
-I'm tired. I'll take a rain check.
Do get in.
There are people watching.
Mr. Oh has been Minister Song's
closest aide for many years.
Minister Song denied
-any involvement...
-Is Mr. Jang not in?
He went to meet Chairman Sung.
As Minister Song promised
a thorough investigation himself,
it is predicted
that there will be no cover-up.
KANG SEON-YEONG
Hello.
Tae-jun.
Hello? Tae-jun.
Do you know
where he is meeting Chairman Sung?
Where are we going?
We're almost there.
What's going on here?
A viper full of venom
shouldn't be kept alive.
When you hunt, you have to
make sure the prey is down.
Go ahead.
The current Minister of Justice
stood by the scene of a murder.
What will happen if this gets out?
I wonder if there is
any statute of limitations
for covering up a murder.
Whether you like it or not, you and I are
in the same boat now.
OPPOSE TO PROTECT THE RIGHT
TO AN ADEQUATE STANDARD OF LIVING
SEOBUK MARKET COMMITTEE
AGAINST REDEVELOPMENT
Man, he's a tough one.
Run him over.
Tae-jun!
We're both covered in shit now.
It's time to wash up.
Ms. Kang is the only person
who can go after
Minister Song and Chairman Sung now.
I need your help, Chief Choe.
Can you help me?
Ms. Kang is preparing
a special investigation
into your slush funds, Minister Song.
I know she's reckless,
but how dare she mess with me?
Why would I be afraid?
It won't be easy,
but let's take the bull by the horns.