Today, we are going all out.
All out hotness from the VMX Goddess
that has made you experience
all out sexual adventures.
I’m Dyessa Garcia,
who will go all out with you today.
And I’m ready to share with you
the steaminess brought on by
the hottest scenes of VMX A-lister -
AJ Raval.
This is
All Out: AJ Raval
What did you dream of
becoming when you were a kid?
I used to dream of
becoming a famous singer.
But now I’m one of the
women of your dreams.
We meet AJ Raval’s character Twinkle
in the movie
Paglaki Ko, Gusto Kong Maging Pornstar.
This sexy-comedy movie
was the initial offering of VMX
during its launch in 2021.
And this is where AJ
had her first nipple-reveal.
Wow!
AJ also starred with
goddesses Ara Mina,
Maui Taylor, Alma Moreno,
and Rosanna Roces.
And this is where we’ll see the viral clip
of the sexy experts teaching
AJ’s character how to properly—
You know, the right facial
expression is important.
When you moan,
you need the right body
language that go with it.
And to get you into it,
you have to…
you have to show
the whites of your eyes.
Have you ever climaxed?
Do you know what happens
when a woman reaches climax?
Your legs go stiff.
And her back arches.
And her fingers want
to grab and scratch.
And she bites her lips.
Sometimes you make the same sounds
like when you're pooping.
I have to agree.
Even in the BPO industry,
it's a rule of thumb.
When you smile, you sound happy.
The voice follows what the face is doing.
Ah, shit!
Hey! Make it more intense.
- Yeah!
- Okay. Intense.
Intense.
You sound like you're trying
to scare someone!
That was intense.
- Geez, give it your all.
- Your all! Everything!
Fine, I'm giving it all.
Twinkle.
Alright.
Listen to me. Curacha,
The Girl Who Never Sleeps.
First day in cinemas,
77 million!
There were only 50 cinemas back then.
Watch me.
This part is for when
you're about to climax, alright.
Shit, feels so good!
Mic test.
- Test. Test.
- Hey!
What are you doing?
That's Mic's testes.
Moan!
You see, I just remembered
our first meeting de avance.
Screw that!
Start moaning!
Fine, here I go.
Alma Cares.
Great job.
Shit, you're so good!
Yay!
This cold drink is
fitting for the hot season.
And good thing this film has taught me
how to properly take a sip.
Who would’ve thought this cold drink
could make you hot?
But we can also give tips
on how to give a fellatio,
on this humble old ice candy.
Okay, watch.
This is how you do it.
Lick around the edges.
Don't laugh, jeez.
- You're being silly.
- Just like that.
Pretend this ice candy is a cock.
When ice cream drips,
you lick it.
You're so good at this.
Like that.
That's how you treat a penis.
Ice candy!
It's the same thing.
- Here, ice candy.
- Correct.
You better listen up.
Start from the bottom,
and work your way to the tip.
This is how you do it.
Just stare at it.
Be quiet. You.
- Here.
- How? Show us, quick.
God's sake!
- I can't concentrate!
- Hurry up.
Teach her!
- Is this right?
- Good job! Check.
I'm sorry, I don’t know how to do this.
This is how you do it.
There we go.
With feelings. Put more feelings.
That's enough.
- So, what.
- Then, do this.
You're going to bury it
in your mouth, like so.
When it's inside your mouth, snug.
Just leave it there for
about five to ten seconds.
What happens when
it's inside your mouth?
- Push it deeper.
- Deeper.
It won't go any deeper.
But I throw up easy.
Idiot!
It's called a gag reflex. Christ.
You can train your throat
to be desensitized...
so you won't want to throw up.
Correct!
- It's a big one.
- Practice on it.
You really know how to
put it in your mouth.
You're so good at this!
I'm just starting.
What's the matter? Is it really that big?
Do you want a dick or what?
Ice candy!
This will do.
It's soft, wrapped in plastic.
It's as good as any dick.
See, this movie’s really amazing.
Four goddesses came together to teach AJ
how to let out her allure.
And look, now she’s
become a goddess herself.
How I wish!
The proper way to make men go crazy.
To keep the audience thrilled.
Death of a Girlfriend.
The title alone is already intriguing.
In this movie, AJ Raval stars
with the handsome Diego Loyzaga,
son of popular action star, Cesar Montano.
And it's amazing because AJ’s father,
Jeric Raval, is also an action star.
Many were excited because
this was Diego’s comeback movie.
But many were equally in anticipation
of AJ’s beauty in this movie.
AJ plays Christine
while Diego plays Alonzo.
They always walk home
together through a forest.
Oh, I like it.
It seems they’ve had many
steamy moments there.
You’re mine, virgin boy.
You got the moves, ex-virgin boy.
Many were left wondering about what
happened to AJ’s character, Christine.
But I’m sure
no one would question AJ’s
enchanting sexiness in this movie.
It’s got everyone totally hooked.
You’d definitely want to watch
the whole movie after this.
Now we’re diving all in
on scenes from Nerisa.
The sex appeal of lead stars,
Aljur Abrenica,
and Cindy Miranda are overflowing.
But we can’t discount AJ Raval’s presence.
AJ Raval plays Lilet, a pure and sweet girl
who also oozes charisma.
It was the people on the island
who bestowed her the name "Nerisa".
I delight in Nerisa's arrival.
I may have found a friend in her.
Though I know that Obet
is Nerisa's whole world,
Many have been enthralled
by AJ Raval’s innocent look.
This young vibe is natural to her
since she was actually born
on September 3, 2000.
That’s why she looked really fresh here.
But while she looked innocent,
this sexy goddess still had a wild love
scene at the beach with Sean De Guzman.
Oh, I love it!
We’ve hit the jackpot in this next film.
It’s filled with steamy
scenes from AJ Raval.
Here she was recognized as
the newest People’s Fantasy.
And you should definitely bet on her.
Because, with AJ, you surely won’t lose.
AJ grew bolder and bolder with every film.
And in the
Psychedelic-Erotic-Thriller movie Taya,
she was even more daring.
Do you want a taste?
I’m sure you’d be craving
peanut butter soon.
He’s the boss of my bosses.
My boss was the one who blocked
you on social media for being too eager.
Well, he wasn’t replying to me.
Wait, how did you even end up
in that kind of job?
You mentioned a while ago
that you’re…permanent?
Permanent. Meaning
this is really our main job.
We have protection from the higher ups.
Downside is, we can’t escape
because they’ll hunt us down if we ever do.
The girl you’re fantasizing
about is a freelancer.
Students, single mothers,
or those who just wanna give it a try.
But they better be careful not to fall into
a huge debt with their agents,
or else they won’t be able to escape.
Like you?
Pretty much.
Are you from the province?
Yeah. Nueva Ecija.
My mom just wanted me to study here.
But it feels like we’re just
squandering our money.
It’d be better if you’re only losing money.
It could be worse. You
could also lose yourself.
Is that too deep?
How about you?
What province are you from?
I’m from Mindoro.
Someone recruited me
to become a saleslady here.
But when I got here, I didn’t know I was
already the prize to a gambling scheme.
At first, I did it because I was afraid
they’d kill my parents in the province.
But ever since my mom got a heart attack,
I just couldn’t quit.
Why?
I don’t know. It feels like this
is the only thing I know how to do.
I’m used to it anyway.
Pay-out’s huge, too.
And if they don’t win, we get all of it.
Sometimes, I miss life in the province.
But I don’t even know where I’d go.
Honestly, I also
want to go back home.
But my mom insists I tough it out here.
Okay, then.
We’ll be able to go home someday.
AJ played the character
Nanette in this film.
She once again starred with Sean De Guzman,
who played Sixto,
a guy who always fantasizes
about his crush.
Tsk, tsk. I think many of you are
like Sixto - always having wet dreams.
Those who are guilty, raise your hands.
Oops.
I’m also guilty.
Oh, I didn’t see you there.
I was taking a selfie, trying
to channel my inner Elle.
AJ Raval’s character in Crush Kong Curly.
AJ was unbelievable here.
Even I felt hot watching
her seductive moves.
An automatic like
and subscribe for me.
Wow!! AJ is totally sizzling.
She not only flexed her
sexual powers in this film,
but also her comedic chops.
And this got even more people
fantasizing about her.
Oh, seems very true to life.
AJ Raval stars in this sexy romcom
with Wilbert Ross.
He played Peter, a very conservative guy.
But nevertheless, he still
couldn’t resist AJ’s allure.
She’s just so enthralling.
Elay! Elay!
Elay!
This time, AJ Raval brings fierceness
as she plays a cool character
in this sexy romantic crime movie Hugas.
In this movie, AJ once again
acts opposite Sean De Guzman.
She plays Liezl, a girl who enters a
crime syndicate through her uncle.
Sean plays Al, a clever hitman.
It’s Sean and AJ’s third movie together.
It’s evident how much more comfortable
they are with each other.
You wouldn’t wanna miss
their really intense intimate scenes.
Al and Liezl met at a gang.
But when they
decided to get married,
Liezl thought of quitting
the crime syndicate.
Wow. Besides the action scenes,
we’ll also see a different kind
of roughing up in this movie.
Oh, the kind of roughing up I like.
This heat is tiring.
I think even AJ is tired from all the
emotion she showed in Kaliwaan.
You’ll definitely feel
her acting skills here.
So, ready your tissues.
That’s for your tears, okay? Not—
AJ’s character Monica was really tired
because she had steamy scenes with not only
one, two, or three, but four handsome men.
First is Juami Gutierrez who played Raji,
a man from an influential clan.
You're such a tease!
Here.
Here, this is thirty thousand.
You’ll still resist?
What?
Come on.
Mark Anthony Fernandez
played Marlon, a policeman.
Screw you. Think you’re brave?
What?
We’ve been talking to you,
but you’re tough.
Are you innocent?
You whore, know who
you’re dealing with!
Please don't.
Why can't you retract
your statement against Boogie?
That hurts!
This is your fault.
No!
Please stop!
The butcher, TJ, was played by Felix Roco.
Shut the hell up!
I'll shoot you, don't scream!
I’ll pull the trigger!
Damn you!
Please don't!
And Vince Rillon played
Boogie, Monica’s boyfriend.
Even just watching it, I felt tired.
Maybe that’s why during
the presscon for the movie,
AJ almost cried because
she really felt the scenes.
So we know she definitely proved
her skills in this movie,
making it an absolute must-watch.
Now, I’m going to show
you an all-out scandal!
Wait, are you thinking of
a different kind of scandal?
What I’m about to show you is Iskandalo,
a sexy-crime series that you can only
watch here on VMX.
Cindy Miranda stars as Detective Patricia,
investigating the death of
Em Celera played by AJ Raval.
And here, AJ was once again paired
with Sean De Guzman.
Also in the cast was her fellow A-lister
Ayanna Misola, who played Agatha,
Em’s superfan who pleasures herself
while fantasizing about her idol.
Speaking of idols,
as one of the original A-listers of VMX,
AJ gained a lot of fans.
Agatha will take home the crown because
of her wild imaginations about her idol.
AJ was also paired here with Jay Manalo,
who played Congressman Stephen.
It’s amazing because
AJ’s mother, Allysa Alvarez,
also worked with Jay Manalo
in the film Totoy Mola back in 1997.
But AJ’s sexy curves brings
a different level of sexiness
to her love scenes with Jay Manalo.
Sitio Diablo delivers sex and violence.
But amidst the chaos,
of course, there’s still love.
VMX maximum crush AJ Raval
was also paired here with
the hunky actor Kiko Estrada,
who played Bullet.
AJ played Aina,
who grew up in a family of gang leaders,
that’s why she’s really good at fighting.
And in case you didn’t know,
AJ can defend herself too.
According to her, she once punched
a guy in school for disrespecting her.
You go girl!
She knows when to fight,
and when to share love!
You son of a bitch!
From chaos, we will now witness
a destructive and passionate story.
AJ Raval and Kiko Estrada reunited
on screen, this time as a married couple.
In the movie Us x Her, we will see
an unhappy wife,
an unfaithful husband,
and an obsessed mistress.
We tried for four years.
Four damn years.
Now we finally made it.
I'm going to be a dad.
What? You want to do it again?
So, we have a backup?
Can you do it again?
Yeah. You? Can you handle it?
What's taking you so long?
Let's go!
But do you know what’s sexier?
AJ Raval and Angeli Khang,
two gorgeous queens
in one intense encounter.
And it gets even wilder
when we see the three of them
enjoying a very naughty night.
So, what’s next?
We’re going to love one another.
I’m pregnant.
Our final movie today
is the most recent VMX film
done by VMX Sexy Queen AJ Raval
as of the moment.
This was her comeback movie
after lying low to finish her studies.
In Sugapa,
AJ Raval and Aljur Abrenica
reunited on screen,
but this time as a couple.
AJ also said in an interview that
she’s going “all in” for her role here,
which got the fans very excited.
Not now.
Mom’s awake downstairs.
So what? We’re married.
And of course, the sexual chemistry
in love scenes is on a different level
when there’s real love involved.
And I think we’ll witness that here,
a true, all-out love.
As we end,
my only wish is that you got hooked
on the all-out scenes, all-out info,
and all-out sexiness
brought to you by AJ Raval.
Once again, I am Dyessa Garcia,
and this is All Out: AJ Raval!