Episode 16
This message is really interesting.
If the phone booth number nine
can really grant her wish,
Can you make her forgive me?
Could it be
Fu Chen wrote to Fang Xiaocheng?
How is that possible?
Zhou Yihuan, what's wrong?
Are you going to fight with Fu Chen?
Let me take you somewhere.
What about the investigation?
Let's split up.
It hurts!
You deserve it.
Aren't we too high-profile?
It's okay.
Just get used to it.
I wish
time can stop at this moment.
Why do you suddenly say that?
Nothing.
I just feel
happiness came so suddenly.
Everything is so fictional.
In the future,
we will have a long time.
Why did you bring me here?
I suddenly remembered
we haven't had a proper date
we haven't had a proper date yet.
Wait here.
I'll be right back.
Where are you going?
Wait for me.
Why are you so silly?
Zhou Yihuan, what are you doing?
Be my girlfriend, okay?
Didn't I
promised you before?
I told you
I want to give you an unforgettable confession.
Do you like it?
Yes.
But this ring is too expensive.
This DR diamond ring
can only be customized for a lifetime.
It represents
you are my only true love.
So I think it’s perfect to give you this.
Dumpling, I want to tell you
no matter where you are,
as long as you take it,
I will find you.
I wish
time
can stay at this moment forever.
I hope
time can be faster.
until we grow old
to the end of life.
Because I want to prove to you
Even if the time and space are in chaos,
I can still
love you
for the rest of my life.
I trust you.
This ring is the best proof.
No matter where I was born,
I will take it
until you find me.
You two...
Stop!
Give me back my hat!
Run!
Stop! Stop!
My good uncle.
Can you check the CCTV for us?
Please.
It's been so long.
How can we still find it?
We have a new clue.
We want to see the scene.
Brother.
Listen to me.
Excuse me.
Don't worry.
I was careless.
I'll look for it again.
What did you say to the security guard?
Nothing.
In other words,
you can hit ten.
Stop.
Zoom in.
I found it.
Thank you
Isn't this Anki?
Why is she here?
I'm leaving. Bye.
Have a good rest. Take care.
Coming.
Hello
Looks like something happened
in Oh Anki's house.
I'll go take a look
Anki.
Miss Wu
What are you doing?
Let me remind you.
Debts.
Pay me back!
This has nothing to do with you.
You can leave now.
Let's go.
Come with us
with us.
Let go of me!
I don't know you.
If you keep pulling and pulling,
I'll call the police.
Go ahead.
Do it!
Your dad borrowed our money.
Now your dad ran away.
and sold the house.
I can only ask you for money.
I don't have money.
It's killing me.
Not bad.
You're quite tough.
Who are you?
Zhou Yihuan.
Why are you here?
Angel
Fang Xiaomei
Why are you here?
Anki.
Don't be so double-standard, OK?
Stop pretending.
Aren't you here to laugh at me?
We're just unnecessary.
I don't need it.
What are you doing?
I'm asking for money.
Can you respect my profession?
Actor table.
Zhou Yang as Fang Xiaomei
[Ming Peng as Lu Tianlang]
[Chen Ji Hui as Fu Chen]
[Feng Yuting as Su Tian Tian]
He Jing by Qu Qin Han
Yang as Director Zhou
as Zhou Ziqi.
Zhou Yunjun as Li Xiaoguan.
Song Mingchun as He Jing's father
as He Jing's mother.
as Anki Wu's father.
Li as the guarantor, An
Wei by Hong Kong, An/Referee
Liu Pei'er as Lin Shen
as Lu Tianlang.
Li Jinze as a classmate.
Qi Lei as Brother Scar
Yang Cong as a human trafficker
Yang Guangyi as the kidnapped child
Attendant Han Bingyan
Wang Tianzhu as a female administrator
Jin Bin as the assailant
Duan Guohua as the bad guy
to perform.
[Pang Yu-jin, Woo Byung-man, Han Byung-yan, Noh Jong-soo]
Chen Cai Wang Nolan
Yvonne Wang, Liu Ju, Chen Li Yan, Zeng Yu Lan.
Zhou Zhifen, Mo Ling Ling, Tang Yongqin, Huang Wenqi.
Yu Ben Xuan, Zhao Jintao, Luo Guo Shun, Yuan Ge.
Luo Hao Xiong, Bai, Qing, Zhang, Qin, Shi Hou Cheng.
Wang Anzhi, Huang Jingyu, Luo, Jiang, Deng Aixiang.
Yang, Min, Li De Long, Zhao Ying Pu, Luo Feng Long.
To the west, Tao, Xin, Lin Yuxi, Zhang Yiping.
Yin Jiaojiao, Chen, Tao, Xu Shuang Ping, Zhang Zhongqiu.
Zhang Zhen Xiang, Liu Jiajing, Yang Zejing, Meng Meimei
Yao Maogui, Wu State towel, Luo Qikang, Liu Yurui.
Zhai Pengju, Liu Yongqing, Huang Zhaotong, Wen, Li,
Yang Yonghong, Wu Shasha, Wu Xinyue, Wei Bogui,
Ding, Tao, Yu Yunyun, Guo, Min, Tu Qitan.
Zhang Ke Sheng, Sun Qianqian, Wu Kailin, Li Jialin.
He Yanlin, Ou Kaixia, Luo, Rui, Zhu Kaiyue.
Yang YingQun Ma Kuo Cheng Wang Kuo Rong Liu Cuiping
He missed you, Li, Yun, Deng Aixiang, Chen Zhanxian.
Designer Zhou Zhouyang Huang Tongze
Director Huang.
Fish White.
Director team.
Director Chen Long.
Actor Commander Huang Jingtao
Actor assistant director Wang Linlin Wei Hong Kong
Li Luo.
Mr. Wu Xingfeng.
Production team.
Producer Director Liu Yiting
CFO, Sun Shuang.
Production assistant, Ma Yang.
Cooperation producer Wang Tianzhu
Outer producer assistant, Shu Changxiao.
Life producer, Dragon friend.
A car producer, Yong friend.
Producer Kwok Hak-kyu
Xu Wansheng, Li Yuxuan
Photography team.
Photography team leader
A camera, Song Guangda.
Phone B, Shi Yuntao.
Camera A focus, Li Dongbao.
Photographer assistant, Yuan Bao Shuai.
and the pilot, Zhai, Hao.
Lighting Team.
Lighting assistant, Li Peng Lei.
Lighting assistant Li Xianhai
Lighting assistant Guo Jianqiang.
Lighting assistant Zhang Chaobo
Art team.
Arts Instructor Chen Siyan.
Art assistant Zhu Jiangjiang.
The prop team leader, Zhu Xinfeng.
Head of decoration, Jiang, Long.
Props for the scene, Jin Bin.
Props on site, Zhang Yang Fan.
Planning worker, Liu Shijia.
Planner Hou Tie Gun
Furnisher Fu Bin.
The styling team.
The styling instructor, Shi Yu Jun.
The team leader, Lee Yoon.
Costume main focus, Leng Yuqing.
The main focus of makeup is Yu Wenting.
Costume assistant, Baby Xu.
The recording team.
Recorder Zhang Hyo Xiong.
Chen Qi, recording assistant.
Instructor of editing, Chang Zhichao.
editing Liu Zheng.
The film crew. Okay.
Late production.
Beijing Huanyu Production Co., Ltd.
to lead Song Haijing.
Video Director He Bilong
Voice Director Feng Lei
Recorder Zhu Jianqin.
Information. Cao Gewei.
Foley Liu Yan.
The lines, Zhang Xiaochong.
Wei Tianwu, film design.
Character, Scene, Tan Wenjun.
[Technique/Packaging Wei Tianwu]
Voice director Zhu Jian Ping
Lin Zhaoyan, Fang Xiaomei
Kenhao Liu, Zhou Yihuan.
Guo, Hao, Lu Tianlang.
Chen Zimeng, Lin Shen.
Zhu Ren, Su Tian Tian.
Kiki Ma Anki Wu
Jing Yan Chen He
Other dubbing
Sun Long, Zhou Yi Qing.
Zhang Lin, Qi Xuan.
Theme song "Light".
Lyrics Cao Tingting and Long Fei.
The female version of Feng Yuting.
Electric piano, Chen, Ke.
Box Qin Longze.
Electronic guitar Chen Hui
Drumer Long Fei.
[The harmony]
The harmony
Recorder Wang Zhuang
Music production.
Beijing Huayi International Film and Culture Media Co., Ltd.
@Dragon Yuyi Music Team
Product company.
Beijing Yuge Culture Co., Ltd.
Beijing Yiya Culture Co., Ltd.