Bro.
You must be surprised
Surprised, right?
Accident?
Not really.
You surprised me.
That night,
you were the one
is you, right?
Who is it?
He Jing.
Everyone has their own troubles.
I just didn't expect
you're our first client.
I didn't expect
you would help me.
After all,
I bullied you
bullied you.
No matter what,
since
has become our client,
We will do our best
to fulfill your wish.
Yes, He Jing.
Just say it.
Come with me.
Let go of my mom.
Come back with me.
No.
Get in.
Get out!
I told you to run!
Let go of my mom!
Run!
Let her go!
You two get lost.
and never come back.
You jinx.
You loser!
Get as far as you can.
It should be here.
Look
Is that Nanny Fan?
That's He.
Please come in.
He Jing.
Hurry up.
What's wrong?
These clothes are for you.
Just keep them.
Don’t thank me.
WAIL
All.
Let me tell you.
these clothes are expensive.
At least your mother
three months' salary.
Take it and wear it.
Thank you.
Get me a glass of water before you go.
You're blocking me from sunbathing.
I want some water.
What's wrong with you?
You can't even massage properly.
Throw these shoes away for me
So dirty.
Get the clothes.
So
Anki and I
look good friends.
but I'm the only one who knows.
I'm just
a servant of her.
Just like my mom.
just like my mom.
I know I shouldn't complain
After all, it's Anki's house.
She gave me
to live with my mom.
But...
I'm just sad.
I'm a girl too.
But every time...
Every time
by Anki's side,
I can only be
as a green leaf that suits her.
Do you think
Am I too greedy?
But I just want to try again.
I want to live a different life.
Don't do anything
[what you don't want.]
Since you've experienced
being bullied,
Why do we have to do the same thing
do the same thing?
Bro.
Sorry.
It's okay.
It's all in the past.
Since the past can't be changed,
then from now on,
live for yourself bravely.
So what is your wish?
I want to be
of this summer ball.
I'm going to stop Zhou Yihuan
to be the star of love.
Why don't we take the risk?
How about this?
Let Zhou Yihuan
to be your partner for the summer ball.
Really?
But we have a condition.
What is it?
After we help you fulfill your wish,
you have to answer us a question.
As long as you can help me fulfill my wish,
I’m willing to do anything.
Fang Xiaomei.
No means no.
Please.
Please, Zhou Yihuan.
Fang Xiaomei.
No wonder you took Zhou Yihuan to join Yuanmeng Club.
So that's your plan.
Let Zhou Yihuan
to be your tool.
What's wrong with being a tool?
You didn't even help me.
Cheapskate.
A favor?
Do you know what this prom represents?
A small favor.
Fang Xiaomei,
Have you considered my feelings?
Are you worried
the prom will affect you
or what?
Do you really want me
to be He Jing's dance partner?
Of course.
If you can come this time,
our wish order
will be done easily.
If Zhou Yihuan is willing to be He Jing's partner,
it'll definitely be an explosive news in Ming Da.
He Jing.
Zhou Yihuan.
It reminds me of you.
I don't think so.
He Jing doesn't deserve to be Zhou Yihuan's partner.
She just wants to be seen by more people.
Don't tell me
you want He Jing
to be a star in campus?
Why not?
People shouldn't be bound by single standards.
I want you to know
apart from delicate appearance,
and slim figure,
there are many beauties.
Every girl can shine brightly.
This time,
with the influence of Zhou Yihuan,
He Jing can stand on the stage.
maybe
become the star of love.
Fang Xiaocheng.
Why don’t you understand this?
Just tell me.
Summer Ball in Ming University.
It's also called "Heartbeat Dance".
It's supposed to dance with someone who's excited.
In other words,
we'll be dancing partners that day.
We all like each other.
Zhou Yihuan doesn't want to be He Jing's partner.
because of you.
Lu Tianlang, what are you talking about?
How could I not know?
But saving you now
is more important than anything.
Fang Xiaomei,
I promise you.
Are you looking for me?
Yihuan is back.
Accompany me.
with Dad.
Actor table.
Zhou Yang as Fang Xiaomei
Han as Zhou Yihuan
[Chen Ji Hui as Fu Chen]
Feng Yuting as Su Tiantian
Pan Li Tong as Anki Wu
Director Zhou by Yang Feng
as Zhou Ziqi
Liu Yiting as Mr. Liu
Zhou Yunjun as Li Guan
Song Mingchun as He Jing's father
as He Jing's mother.
as Anki Wu's father.
Hau Wan Fen as Anki Wu's mother
Wei by Hong Kong as Ahn/referee
Liu Pei'er as Lin Shen
Yuan as Lu Tianlang
[Li Tengxuan as Zhou Yihuan]
Qi Lei as Brother Scar
Yang Cong as a human trafficker
[Yang Guangyi as the kidnapped child]
[Li Ai Yao as Lu Tianlang's mother]
Li Jiao plays Huan as the backup.
Wang Tianzhu as a female administrator
Ben Kim as the assault
Duan Guohua as a bad person
Chae Yishi as Host B
to perform.
Pang Yu-jin, Hu Wen, Han Byung-yan, Noh Jong-soo.
Chen Cai Wang Nolan
Zhu Qiqing
Yu Wenxuan, Zhao Jintao, Luo Guo Shun, Yuan Kan.
Luo Hao Xiong, Bai, Qing, Zhang, Qin, Shi Hou Cheng.
Wang Anzhi, Huang Jingyu, Luo, Jiang, Deng Aixiang
Fang, Bo, Wu, Zhong, Long Qiu Yu
To the west, Tao, Xin, Lin Yuxi, Zhang Yiping.
Yin Jiaojiao, Chen, Tao, Xu Shuang Ping, Zhang Zhongqiu.
Zhang Zhen Xiang, Liu Jiajing, Yang Zejing, Meng Meimei.
Wang Xingping, Xiao Tong, Wei Yongli, Cheng Weiyuan.
Zhai Pengzhu, Liu Yongqing, Huang Zhangtong, Wen, Li,
Yang Yonghong, Wu Shasha, Wu Xinyue, Wei Bogui,
Ding, Tao, Yu Yunyun, Guo, Guo, Guo, Tu Qitan.
Zhang Ke Sheng, Sun, Qian, Wu Kailin, Li Jialin.
Yang Ying Qun Ma Cheng Wang Kuo Rong Liu Cuiping
He misses Li Yun, Deng Ai Xiang, Chen Xiang.
Staff table.
Writer group.
scriptwriter Cao Ting, Chen Long.
Director team.
Director Chen Long.
Executive director, Li Lanqing.
Actor assistant director Wang Linlin Wei Hong Kong
Li Luoluo.
Sun Shuang from Finance Department.
Production assistant Ma, Yang Yang.
Director-in-chief producer Wang Tianzhu
Foreign producer Fang Zhimin
Life producer, Dragon friend.
A car producer, Yong friend.
Producer Kwok Hak-kyu
Director of the venue, Li Chunlin.
Photography team.
Photographer, Li Lu Yao.
B camera, Shi Yuntao.
Camera A focus, Li Dongbao.
Focus on B, Xu Weijie.
Photographer assistant Ga Ildy
and the pilot, Zhai, Hao.
Lighting team.
Lighting instructor, Liu Lian Sheng.
Lighting assistant Li Xianhai
Lighting assistant Guo Jianqiang.
Lighting assistant Zhang Chaobo
Art assistant Zhu Jiang
The prop team leader, Zhu Xinfeng.
Leader of decoration, Jiang, Long.
Act tools, Ru Lizhong.
Props on site, Zhang Yang Fan.
Planning worker, Liu Shijia.
Planning worker, Hou Tie Gun.
Planning worker, Zhao Hongjun.
The styling team.
styling instructor, Shiyu Jun.
Wang Xiao Lei, the makeup team leader.
Makeup artist Liu Wai Xiong.
Costume focus, Leng Yuqing.
The main focus of makeup is Yu Wenting.
Dress assistant, Baby Xu.
Recorder Zhang Hyo Xiong
Recording assistant, Chen Qi.
The editing team.
The crew.
Ma Anning, the photographer.
Late production.
Beijing Huanyu Production Co., Ltd.
Producer Ren Yanchao
Video Director He Honglong
Voice Director Feng Lei
Recorder Zhu Jianqin.
Schedule, Fung, Lei.
The lines, Zhang Xiaochong.
Wei Tianwu, film design.
The end design, Song Haijing.
Color cooler Ryu Sam.
Technique/packaging Wei Tianwu
Voice director Zhu Jian Ping
A dubber?
Kenhao Liu, Zhou Yihuan.
Guo Hao, Lu Tianlang.
Chen Zimeng, Lin, Shen.
Huang Zhiyu Fu Chen.
Chen Jing Yan He Jingjing
Dong Can, Luo Jie
Mr. Zhou.
Wu Qian Yu, Mr. Liu.
Bra.
Other dubbing.
Sun, Long, Zhou Yi Qing.
Zhang Lin, Qi Xuan.
Wang Fei Yang, An, Mo.
Theme song "Light".
Lyrics Cao Ting Long Fei.
Long Ze.
Lyrics by Dragon Flying Dragon Taek
Singing Dragon Flying Longze
Female version of singing Feng Yuting
Vocal Producer Long Fei Long Ze
Electric Piano Chen Keke
Box Qin Longze.
Electric guitar Chen Hui.
bass player, Chen Hui.
The harmony is written
The harmony
Recorder Wang Zhuang
Mixed Master Yu Xinfold.
Beijing Huayle Yuri International Culture and Media Co., Ltd.
@Dragon Yuyi Music Team
Product company.
Beijing Yuge Culture Co., Ltd.
Beijing Yiya Culture Co., Ltd.