(The second voice message to Jun Seong)
The second voice message.
Jun Seong.
Did you wait for a long time?
I just want to thank you.
Seong Ho: I want to tell you this.
Seong Ho: So I left this voice message.
Seong Ho: See you later.
(Pick up the phone again nervously)
Yung Hee: What will we do tomorrow?
Yung Hee: I'm looking forward to tomorrow again. What will we do tomorrow?
Seong Ho: Excuse me.
-Seong Ho: Hello.
-Jun Seong: Hello.
Seong Ho: Hey.
I waited for a long time.
-You waited for a long time?
-Yes.
Seong Ho: Thank you so much today.
Jun Seong: I can wait longer.
Seong Ho: Then wait for two more days.
-Jun Seong: Okay.
-Seong Ho: You're okay with waiting for two more days?
-Jun Seong: I had a great day.
-Seong Ho: What made it so great?
Being with you.
-That's all?
-Yes.
Me too.
-Jun Seong: See you later.
-Seong Ho: Okay.
(Has Seong Ho finally reciprocated Jun Seong's feelings?)
Hyeong Jin: Are there any messages for me? No?
Hyeong Jin: I'm both nervous and expectant.
You have one new message.
Hyeong Jin.
Min Seong: I don't know who you've given your heart to.
Min Seong: I'm curious about this, so I'm leaving you a message.
Min Seong: Yes, I'm just curious.
Hyeong Jin: I'm still hesitating,
but I think I can't delay it anymore.
Hyeong Jin: I want to be brave for the person I have feelings for.
Hyeong Jin: Hello.
(Hyeong Jin wants to be brave for that man)
(Min Seong)
Hello?
(Hyeong Jin wants to be brave for that man)
(Min Seong)
-Hello.
(Hyeong Jin wants to be brave for that man)
(Min Seong)
-Do you know who I am?
-I do.
(Peeking)
(Pretending not to know)
Hyeong Jin: If I can have a chance to go on a date with you,
Hyeong Jin: I'll be very glad. So I called you.
Min Seong: Okay. Thank you.
-Hyeong Jin: I'm hanging up. Thank you.
-Min Seong: OK. Thank you.
Hyeong Jin: I have to fight for myself.
Hyeong Jin: If I keep waiting, it'll all be over.
Hyeong Jin: I'm getting anxious.
Min Seong: If possible, I really want to go on a date with him.
(Next is Hyeong Joon)
(Whose message will Hyeong Joon find in his mailbox?)
No new message in your mailbox.
("No new message in your mailbox")
Hyeong Joon: I thought Min Seong would leave me a message, but he didn't.
Hyeong Joon: I have to say I'm a bit disappointed.
Hyeong Joon: Maybe he's not sure about us.
(Hyeong Joon made the call without thinking for too long)
(Hyeong Joon is calling Min Seong's roommate Seon Woo)
It startled me.
Seon Woo: Hello, I'm Seon Woo Yoo.
Hyeong Joon: Hello, I'm Hyeong Joon.
Hyeong Joon: I just called to say thank you.
Hyeong Joon: I'm sorry to let you worry so much about me.
-Seon Woo: Oh, I didn't do much.
-Really? Anyway…
-Seon Woo: I had a great time too.
-Hyeong Joon: Thank you very much.
-Keep fighting to the end.
-Okay. I know.
(Hyeong Joon expressed his gratitude to Seon Woo on the phone)
-Keep fighting to the end.
-Okay. I know.
(Hyeong Joon expressed his gratitude to Seon Woo on the phone)
Min Seong: I didn't mean to eavesdrop but I heard it anyway.
Seon Woo: You heard everything?
Min Seong: I didn't want to hear anything but I heard his voice.
Min Seong: I didn't hear what he said.
(Seon Woo: Just because he called me doesn't mean he has feelings for me)
Just because he called me doesn't mean he has feelings for me.
Seon Woo: He just called to say thank you.
(Hyeong Joon came back to his room after the call)
Yung Hee: I can't see anything in your face.
Hyeong Joon: This is just my normal face.
Yung Hee: How's it? Did you receive it?
-Hyeong Joon: You asked me if I received the message?
-Yeah.
Hyeong Joon: Ah, voice message? No.
-What?
-No.
-No?
-Yung Hee: How about the call? Did you call someone?
-Hyeong Joon: Yes.
Yung Hee: Min Seong?
-Hyeong Joon: No.
-What?
-No.
-Yung Hee: Don't lie to me again.
Yung Hee: I must have called Min Seong.
-Yung Hee: I know you.
-Hyeong Joon: You're quick-witted.
Yung Hee: What if I suddenly receive a message saying the calling time is over?
That would be…
(Yung Hee, please go to the phone booth, and after confirming the voice messages, express feelings to someone you have a crush on within 30 seconds)
-It's hard to say how I feel.
-Bye.
(Yung Hee, please go to the phone booth, and after confirming the voice messages, express feelings to someone you have a crush on within 30 seconds)
It's hard to say how I feel. I'll be back soon.
Hyeong Joon: Don't call me.
Yung Hee: Why would I call you?
-Hyeong Joon: Then you run downstairs?
-Yung Hee: I didn't say who I'll call.
(Sighing)
Yung Hee: To be honest, I'm tired and not looking forward to it.
You have one new message.
Hello, Yung Hee.
Chung-ook: I'm Chung-ook. Hi.
Chung-ook: I wish one day
Chung-ook: I could go bungee jumping or skydiving with you.
Chung-ook: I wish that could come true.
Chung-ook: Anyway, see you soon. Bye.
Yung Hee: I'm carrying a torch for someone.
Yung Hee: So is Chung-ook.
Yung Hee: I feel grateful and also sorry.
(Sighing)
(With a heavy heart, Yung Hee picks up the phone again)
(Yung Hee is calling Seon Woo)
-Seon Woo Yoo speaking.
-I'm Yung Hee Kim.
(Yung Hee is calling Seon Woo)
Yung Hee: Have you gotten tired of my voice?
Yung Hee: You've been hearing it all day.
Yung Hee: I'm just curious about what you're doing
Yung Hee: and want to hear your voice, so I called you.
-Seon Woo: We can have a chat later.
-Yung Hee: Do you mean it?
-Do I mean it?
-Yeah.
Seon Woo: I do. It's a deal.
-Yung Hee: Okay. It's a deal.
-It's a deal.
-Yung Hee: See you later.
-Okay.
(Yung Hee mustered up his courage again)
Yung Hee: In the rest of the time,
Yung Hee: I'll try my best to win his heart.
Yung Hee: During our date today,
Yung Hee: he didn't give me a positive answer.
Yung Hee: I think it's because he has feelings for me too.
Yung Hee: Why couldn't he just be honest with me? He's so bad.
(Sobbing)
(Seong Ho, please go to the phone booth, and after confirming the voice messages, express feelings to someone you have a crush on within 30 seconds)
Seong Ho: I'm having a lot of feelings
Seong Ho: because I haven't figured everything out.
Seong Ho: I still have feelings for Seon Woo.
Seong Ho: I think I'll have mixed feelings for a while.
You have two new messages.
The first message.
(The first voice message to Seong Ho)
Seong Ho, it's me, Seon Woo.
Seon Woo: When I first met you, I never thought
Seon Woo: I'd leave you a message on the fourth night like this.
Seon Woo: We met, understand, and cherish each other.
Seon Woo: I want to know you better.
Seon Woo: This wish itself
Seon Woo: is so special that I'll remember it for a long time.
Seon Woo: Meeting you
Seon Woo: makes me feel that it's so good that I came here.
Seon Woo: I'll forever remember this experience.
Seon Woo: Thank you. Bye.
Seong Ho: I felt a bit sad.
Seong Ho: I could feel his emotions
Seong Ho: in his voice.
Seong Ho: It made me want to cry.
(The second voice message to Seong Ho)
The second message.
Hello, Seong Ho.
(Want to cry)
Jun Seong: I don't know what to say.
Jun Seong: Everything I said to you in the past four days,
Jun Seong: I meant them.
I can't see anyone except you.
Jun Seong: I was very happy today. I've been very happy
Jun Seong: and will be happy in the future.
Jun Seong: See you in the house.
(Sighing)
Seong Ho: I really wanted to cry.
Seong Ho: My feelings for Seon Woo
Seong Ho: are tangled with all the other feelings.
(Who will Seong Ho choose to call?)
Why hasn't anyone called me?
There are too many voice messages.
Maybe someone left a long message.
I've moved on from that. Wait a sec.
(Someone's phone is ringing)
What's going on?
(Seong Ho called Jun Seong today)
-Seong Ho: Hello.
-Jun Seong: Hello.
Seong Ho: What are you doing?
(Turn up the volume)
Jun Seong: Nothing.
-Seong Ho: Nothing?
-Jun Seong: Yes.
-Seong Ho: I had a great day.
-Jun Seong: Mine was greater.
Seong Ho: Don't forget your promise to travel with me.
Jun Seong: I won't forget. We'll definitely travel together.
-Seong Ho: Don't forget our promise.
-Jun Seong: I won't.
Seong Ho: Okay, I'm hanging up.
(Seong Ho and Jun Seong called each other for the first time)
Seong Ho: Every moment of our date,
Seong Ho: I felt very happy.
(Seong Ho: I've never been so happy before in the show or in my life)
I've never been so happy before
Seong Ho: in the show or in my life. It was like a dream.
Seong Ho: Wonderful moments like that are rare.
(It's Min Seong's turn to call)
You have one new message.
Hyeong Joon: Min Seong, how could you give me cookies
Hyeong Joon: but choose someone else?
Hyeong Joon: What's going on? You need to explain everything, okay?
Min Seong: I anticipated it.
Min Seong: I've decided who to call today before I came out.
(On the other side, it's depressing in Hyeong Joon and Yung Hee's room)
Hyeong Joon: No calls.
Hyeong Joon: What do you think?
Hyeong Joon: There's nothing we can do, right?
Yung Hee: Let's go on a date tomorrow.
-Hyeong Joon: No.
-Yung Hee: Why?
Yung Hee: I got dumped every day.
(Bickering)
(Hyeong Joon: Not every day)
Yung Hee: I got dumped every day.
Not every day.
(Bickering)
(Hyeong Joon: Not every day)
(Yung Hee: You dumped me)
Not every day.
(Bickering)
(Hyeong Joon: Not every day)
You dumped me.
(Bickering)
(Yung Hee: You dumped me)
You dumped me.
(Me?)
(Meaningless bickering)
You dumped me.
-Me?
-Yes.
(Me?)
(Meaningless bickering)
(Yes. You can dump me too)
-Me?
-Yes.
(Me?)
(Meaningless bickering)
You can dump me too.
(Yes. You can dump me too)
(Meaningless bickering)
You can dump me too.
(Min Seong decided to call Hyeong Joon)
Hyeong Joon: Hello?
-Min Seong: Hello.
-Hyeong Joon: Mmm.
Min Seong: Do you know who I am?
Hyeong Joon: Min Seong, right?
Min Seong: I had a good day.
Hyeong Joon: Me too. Come to the patio later.
-Min Seong: I see.
-Okay.
(Smiling)
-Is that Min Seong?
-Yes.
Gosh.
What should I do?
(He's finally smiling again)
We were comforting each other just now.
(Min Seong's call lightened the atmosphere)
-We were about to take photos like this.
-Are you crazy?
(Min Seong's call lightened the atmosphere)
-We were about to take photos like this.
-Are you crazy?
Min Seong: I've made up my mind. It's Hyeong Joon.
Min Seong: By the way, Hyeong Joon smells really nice.
Min Seong: I like people who smell nice.
Min Seong: And his perfume smells really good.
(Lastly, it's Chung-ook's turn)
Chung-ook: I think my heart is empty.
(With an empty heart, he checks the mailbox)
No new message in your mailbox.
("No new message in your mailbox")
(Chung-ook finally put down the phone)
Chung-ook: For a few seconds, I didn't want to call anyone.
Chung-ook: I was very frustrated.
Chung-ook: My mind went blank.
(After thinking for a long time, he picks up the phone again)
Yung Hee: Hello, I'm Yung Hee Kim.
Chung-ook: Hey, I'm Chung-ook.
Yung Hee: I got your voice message.
Chung-ook: You did? You've already been here?
Yes, I've been there.
Yung Hee: I keep telling everyone
Yung Hee: that meeting you is the best thing that has happened here.
Really?
Yung Hee: We must go bungee jumping and skydiving together.
Chung-ook: OK. Thank you.
-I see.
-Thank you so much.
-Chung-ook: OK. Let's have a drink later.
-Yung Hee: Okay.
-Okay.
(A bit cold but conveyed his feelings anyway)
Chung-ook: To be honest, I do have feelings for someone.
Chung-ook: But I didn't know what else to say.
Chung-ook: To win him over, I need to try harder to let him know me
Chung-ook: or repeat the same words I said before.
Chung-ook: Maybe just receiving a message can make someone happy.
Chung-ook: I thought it'd be fine to call without thinking too much.
So I called him.
(Chung-ook: So I called him)
(The calling time is over)
Seon Woo: After I tried it, I realized
Seon Woo: that it took a lot of courage to call someone
Seon Woo: who wouldn't call back.
(Chung-ook is sitting alone in the room)
Seong Ho: Are you okay?
Seong Ho: Hyeong Jin told me.
-Chung-ook: Really?
-Yes.
Seong Ho: Do you want to be alone?
-Chung-ook: I don't know.
-Seong Ho: You feel helpless, right?
(Chung-ook: Yeah)
Yeah.
Chung-ook: I just think… I think
Chung-ook: this is useless. So I…
Chung-ook: I'm fine. You can go downstairs.
Seong Ho: Do you want to be alone for a while?
Seong Ho: You need time to figure things out, right?
Yes.
(Patting)
-I don't know.
-It's okay.
(Patting)
-I don't know.
-It's okay.
Seong Ho: Fighting.
-Seong Ho: See you later.
-Chung-ook: Okay.
Seong Ho: Should I turn off the lights?
Chung-ook: No. It's OK.
Seong Ho: Tell me when you feel better.
(Nodding)
(Seong Ho left Chung-ook to process his feelings alone)
Chung-ook: I must be crazy.
(Finally, he's crying)
Chung-ook: It was so hard.
Chung-ook: I never cried in my last eight-year relationship.
Chung-ook: I was depressed after breaking up, but I didn't cry.
Chung-ook: I don't know how to express my emotions.
Chung-ook: But today, I lost it and let it all out.
Chung-ook: The tears I've held back in the past eight or ten years
Chung-ook: all streamed down today.
(Chung-ook spent the night with the emotions he's been suppressing for 8 years)
-Seong Ho: Am I excluded?
-Excluded.
Seong Ho: I'm excluded.
Seong Ho: What's wrong with these two guys?
(Min Seong and Hyeong Joon's date photo)
Seong Ho: Wow, it's true.
-Seong Ho: They went on a real date.
-Yes.
-Seong Ho: These photos are really cute.
Seon Woo: Your photos are amazing too.
Seong Ho: Ours?
Seon Woo: Because your styles are very similar.
Seon Woo: That's right.
Seong Ho: What? Why are you suddenly talking like my ex-boyfriend?
Are you happy?
-But you…
-You look very happy, dot, dot, dot.
(You look very happy…)
-But you…
-You look very happy, dot, dot, dot.
Seon Woo: Jun Seong came to me at midnight yesterday.
Seon Woo: He looked so eager.
Seon Woo: He asked me what you meant to me.
Seon Woo: I had left you the voice message by that time,
Seon Woo: so it was easy to answer him.
You're just special to me.
Seon Woo: When I thought about who I might meet,
Seon Woo: they were not someone like you.
Seong Ho: Me too.
Seon Woo: Yes. So I think I may have changed.
Seon Woo: Well, it's really hard to change someone.
Seon Woo: I don't think people can be changed.
Seong Ho: I agree with you.
Seong Ho: It's like magic. After meeting you,
Yes. Seong Ho: I realized that I'd be drawn to someone like you.
Seong Ho: I really like you.
Seon Woo: Yes. That's very meaningful.
-Seon Woo: I learned something this time.
-Yeah?
Fate is all about timing.
-That's what I learned.
-Yes.
Seong Ho: Keep that in mind.
Seon Woo: I tried and know how it feels now.
Seon Woo: It took a lot of courage.
Seon Woo: It took a lot of courage
Seon Woo: to call someone who you knew wouldn't call back.
Seon Woo: I found it out too late. That's why I feel sorry for you, Seong Ho.
-You understand?
-Yes.
(Want to cry)
-You understand?
-Yes.
(Want to cry)
Seong Ho: Why do I want to cry whenever I see you?
Seong Ho: Dating has a great influence.
Seong Ho: My attitude to Seon Woo has changed too.
(Seong Ho: When I chatted with Seon Woo at home)
When I chatted with Seon Woo at home, my mind was clearer
Seong Ho: than when I was on a date with Jun Seong.
Seon Woo: Seong Ho said he had completely sorted out our relationship.
Seon Woo: "You should learn from it that timing is very important."
Seon Woo: "Let's put an end to it."
(Today ended in the men's tears)
(Love triangle)
(As usual, Seong Ho got up early to get prepared)
(Where is he going first after getting prepared?)
(Grab)
(Seong Ho came to wake Jun Seong up)
(Patting)
Hey.
Sir.
Get up.
(Cover)
(Where are you hiding?)
Sir, wash up.
(Sweet)
(Turn around)
(What?)
(Turn back)
(Seong Ho's sweet and scary wake-up service)
Seong Ho: Go wash up.
(Happy)
(Grab)
(Revenge)
Hyeong Joon: I'm stretching my arms.
Jun Seong: Stop.
Hyeong Joon: Buck up.
Seong Ho: Where are you going?
Hyeong Joon: I'm ready for the date.
Seong Ho: Are you going to say goodbye?
Hyeong Joon: It's so funny.
Hyeong Joon: This looks funny too.
Jun Seong: Where is Min Seong?
(Over there)
(Hyeong Joon walks to Min Seong who is sleeping)
(Knock)
(Gently)
(Min Seong is sleeping soundly)
(Give up)
(It's hard to wake up Min Seong)
-Seon Woo: Let's eat.
-Enjoy the food.
Yung Hee: Enjoy the food.
Enjoy the food.
Today's breakfast is fried tofu sushi and seaweed soup)
-Enjoy the food.
-I'll start eating.
Today's breakfast is fried tofu sushi and seaweed soup)
Hyeong Joon: We used to wait for everyone to be at the table.
Hyeong Joon: Now we just start eating directly. They'll come down themselves.
-Jun Seong: The seaweed soup is really good.
-Seon Woo: Yeah.
Seong Ho: Yes. The soup is good.
Jun Seong: It's warm.
Seon Woo: Yes, we need to eat something like this.
Yung Hee: Oh, he's coming.
Min Seong: Hello, everyone.
-Hyeong Joon: You're in green today.
-Yes.
Green.
(Min Seong: Wow)
Yung Hee: Surprised?
Yung Hee: It's really delicious. Try it.
Yung Hee: How many sushi rolls did you have?
-Jun Seong: About three.
-Three?
Yung Hee: You ate a lot.
Hyeong Joon: I'm eating my sixth.
(Whoosh)
Jun Seong: What hairstyle will Hyeong Jin have today?
Seon Woo: I'm looking forward to it.
Wow.
Yung Hee: Come have breakfast.
Seong Ho: Ah, the bangs' place changed.
(Puff)
Place.
Seong Ho: They were on this side.
-Seong Ho: They're on this side today.
-So funny.
Hyeong Jin: It's really delicious.
Hyeong Jin: Who made this?
Breakfast?
Yung Hee: I, Chung-ook, Seon Woo, and Seong Ho.
Min Seong: It's great.
Hyeong Jin: You look great in green.
-Min Seong: What?
-Hyeong Jin: You look great in green.
Chung-ook: It suits you very well.
(Glance)
-Min Seong: Really?
-Yes.
(Glance)
-Min Seong: Really?
-Yes.
Hyeong Jin: Which one do you prefer?
Min Seong: Seaweed soup.
Hyeong Jin: How about fried tofu sushi?
This.
Hyeong Jin: Why don't you eat?
Min Seong: I'm full.
-Hyeong Jin: Liar.
-It's true.
Min Seong: I don't eat breakfast.
Hyeong Jin: Neither do I.
Hyeong Jin: I can't eat anymore.
Hyeong Jin: I'll do my hair one last time.
Hyeong Jin: Leave the bowls on the table. I'll clean them up.
-Put the bowl in the sink.
-Okay.
Jun Seong: Put it in the sink.
-Seong Ho: Because we have a volunteer.
-Jun Seong: Someone volunteered to wash the dishes.
-Put it in the sink.
-Because there's a volunteer.
-Hint game.
-Everyone is waiting for a volunteer.
Hint game?
Everyone is waiting for a volunteer.
Yung Hee: What are you staring at?
-It's so funny.
-Min Seong: I'm still half asleep.
-You must be tired.
-Hyeong Joon: Why did you stay up so late?
I lost the hint game.
Seong Ho: Should I brush my teeth?
I like kimchi.
(Seong Ho suddenly starts running)
(Today's mission is finally out)
Hyeong Joon: Oh.
Seong Ho: Bye.
Hyeong Joon: Why?
Hyeong Joon: Hey, give me the card. They haven't seen it yet.
-Really?
-Hyeong Joon: I can't believe it.
Chung-ook: What's going on?
-Have you seen it?
-Chung-ook: What's this? What's this?
Hyeong Joon: Have you seen it?
Min Seong: What's going on?
Hyeong Joon: I see.
Hyeong Joon: I'll show it to others.
Min Seong: Unbelievable.
(Seong Ho and Jun Seong called each other last night, so they'll go on a date today.
Others will have a date together.)
(Embarrassed)
Min Seong: So funny.
Haven't you seen it?
-Seon Woo: What's it?
-Yung Hee: What's it?
Now?
What?
-Yung Hee: What's going on? So sudden.
-Is he not here?
Come.
Come here.
(Mission Card)
(Running)
(They all find the mission hilarious)
Yesterday, I…
I'm so angry.
You should've called him.
(Mission card. Just take it and go out)
-Just take it and go out.
-I feel…
(Mission card. Just take it and go out)
Yung Hee: Get out.
Yung Hee: Don't sit down.
Seong Ho and Jun Seong called each other last night,
so they'll go on a date today.
Others will have a date together.
Jun Seong: Good job.
-You're so annoying.
-This is how it feels.
Out.
Seon Woo: I felt embarrassed and frustrated.
Seon Woo: It was a new feeling for me.
Hyeong Joon: I didn't call Min Seong yesterday.
Yung Hee: Oh.
My goodness.
What?
Can't believe it.
(Patting)
Seon Woo: Hey, I'm sorry.
Hyeong Joon: Not at all.
Hyeong Joon: This is so bad.
Hyeong Joon: If I had called Min Seong yesterday,
Hyeong Joon: I could go on a date with him today, right?
(Sighing)
(Sad)
No.
Seon Woo: Hyeong Joon called me yesterday.
Seon Woo: He thanked me for helping him and Min Seong.
Seon Woo: He happened to call me that day.
(Seon Woo: If he hadn't, he and Min Seong could've been a match)
If he hadn't, he and Min Seong could have been a match.
Seon Woo: I think my interference ruined their date.
Seon Woo: That's all I was thinking about.
Jun Seong: Have you seen this?
Seong Ho: Yes. I'm the first one to see it.
Jun Seong: Why didn't you tell me?
Seong Ho: Because I was brushing my teeth.
Seong Ho: But yesterday,
(Seong Ho: Didn't Hyeong Joon call Min Seong?)
didn't Hyeong Joon call Min Seong?
Jun Seong: I'm confused too.
Seong Ho: What's going on between them?
Seong Ho: What are you going to wear?
Jun Seong: Just this.
-Seong Ho: Are you sure?
-Yes. I came out in it.
Jun Seong: Do I need to change?
-Do you want to see it?
-Seong Ho: You don't have other clothes, do you?
-Jun Seong: Other clothes?
-Yes.
Jun Seong: I have.
Jun Seong: Does anyone have green clothes?
Seong Ho: Hello, we're here to buy clothes.
Seong Ho: Do you have green clothes?
(Seon Woo's racks)
Jun Seong: These colors are a bit dull.
Yung Hee: I do, but I don't want to lend it to you.
I do, but I don't want to lend it to you.
(The youngest man is jealous)
-Show me.
-But it's too bright.
(The youngest man is jealous)
I do, but I don't want to lend it to you.
-Show me.
-But it's too bright.
(Yung Hee: It's green but too bright)
-Show me.
-But it's too bright.
-It's too bright.
-It's okay.
Seong Ho: This clothing store is lame.
Jun Seong: Oh, clothes here are a little dull.
Seon Woo: That's too much.
Seon Woo: Are you talking about my clothes?
Jun Seong: I don't know whose clothes they are.
Seon Woo: I suddenly found that they came to my room
Seon Woo: and checked my wardrobe.
Seon Woo: And they said that my clothes are too dull.
Seon Woo: Then they went out hand in hand.
Seon Woo: I was speechless.
(Ridiculous)
I can't believe it.
Yung Hee: Is Seon Woo a saint?
Yung Hee: How could he watch them laughing and do nothing?
Jun Seong: Why didn't they call each other?
-Why didn't they call each other?
-I don't know.
Yung Hee: Yes.
But yesterday,
Seong Ho: Hyeong Joon said he called someone he's grateful to.
Gosh.
This is so…
(Depressed)
Yung Hee: I wore it on the second day.
Jun Seong: It's OK. The color is so bright.
-Jun Seong: The tone is different.
-Different.
Seong Ho: It's a bit different.
Jun Seong: Let's borrow this.
Seong Ho: This one?
O-Okay.
Okay.
-Jun Seong: You don't sound very sure.
-Seong Ho: Okay.
Okay.
-Jun Seong: Should we borrow it?
-Okay.
Seong Ho: Ask him first.
-This is Chung-ook's.
-Chung-ook.
(Seong Ho: Chung-ook, can we borrow this couple jacket?)
-This is Chung-ook's.
-Chung-ook.
Can we borrow this jacket?
(Seong Ho: Chung-ook, can we borrow this couple jacket?)
Chung-ook: Ah, you want to wear the couple outfits?
Seong Ho: Both of them are yours?
Seong Ho: I'll go downstairs and ask around.
Chung-ook: Go ahead. I can lend mine to you.
-Jun Seong: Go grill Hyeong Joon.
-I won't wear it.
Seong Ho: OK.
-Grill.
-Jun Seong: Ask him what he is doing.
Seong Ho: What he is doing?
Seong Ho: Aren't you in a relationship?
Seong Ho: Are you Baek Ji-young?
Seong Ho: Won't you fall in love again?
Jun Seong: Ask him if he was shot.
(In the kitchen, Min Seong is with Hyeong Jin who's washing the dishes)
Thank you.
Hyeong Joon: So many dishes.
(Glance)
Min Seong: Let me help you.
Hyeong Jin: You'll help me?
Min Seong: Yes. Too many dishes.
Seon Woo: Look, I…
Seon Woo: I was afraid something like this would happen.
Seon Woo: This shouldn't happen again.
Seon Woo: The timing… Unbelievable.
Hyeong Joon: The crew is waiting for this moment.
Min Seong: It's a pity.
Min Seong: But I don't like it when they do this.
Hyeong Jin: Can you get me a cup of coffee?
-Min Seong: A cup of coffee?
-Okay.
Okay.
More dirty dishes?
I thought we'd washed them all.
(Hyeong Joon stays by Min Seong's side)
Hyeong Joon: Because I somehow felt guilty too.
Hyeong Joon: So I kept hanging around Min Seong.
Hyeong Jin: I hope it can be peaceful today.
Min Seong: Do you want some coffee?
Hyeong Joon: Yes.
Min Seong: Let me get you a cup of coffee.
-Hyeong Joon: No, no, no.
-No?
Min Seong: You don't want coffee?
Min Seong: Do you want it or not?
Hyeong Joon: Do you want it?
-Min Seong: Yes.
-Hyeong Joon: Then I want some too.
Min Seong: What? Why do you mimic me?
Hyeong Joon: I like it.
-Seong Ho: Brother Hyeong Joon.
-No, brother.
Seong Ho: Lend me your clothes.
-What? -Lend me your clothes.
-Hyeong Joon: Flowers?
-Seong Ho: Clothes.
-Hyeong Joon: What flowers?
-Seong Ho: That baseball jacket.
Hyeong Joon: You want to borrow my jacket? Sure. I'll lend it to you.
Hyeong Joon: Go try it on and see if it fits.
Hyeong Jin: Is there anyone you want to date?
Hyeong Jin: Not anyone you've dated.
Someone else.
Hyeong Joon: I don't think so.
Hyeong Joon: Anyway, I have had a date with him.
-With Min Seong?
-Hyeong Joon: Because I have dated Min Seong.
Hyeong Jin: You're kind of a pacifist.
-Me? -Yes.
Hyeong Joon: A little.
Hyeong Jin: If
Hyeong Jin: you have a lover,
Hyeong Jin: no, someone you like,
Hyeong Jin: but a friend of yours or someone else also likes him,
Hyeong Jin: will you back off or…
Hyeong Joon: I won't back off.
Hyeong Joon: I'll respect his choice.
Hyeong Joon: I'll just do what I should do.
-Hyeong Joon: Let him make the decision.
-Okay.
Hyeong Jin: As for the current
Hyeong Jin: relationship among me, Hyeong Joon, and Min Seong,
Hyeong Jin: I want to ask him indirectly.
Hyeong Jin: But I won't put too much meaning into Hyeong Joon's answer.
As long as I like someone, I'll strive for his love.
Seong Ho: Hello, I'm here to see the jacket.
Chung-ook: OK.
Chung-ook: How about this?
Seong Ho: Is this the jacket I ordered?
Chung-ook: Yes, this is in a small size. It should fit well.
Seong Ho: It's a little small. A little small.
Chung-ook: It suits you.
(Oh)
Seong Ho: I need to wear a T-shirt inside this.
Right?
-Jun Seong: Seong Ho.
-Seong Ho: Yes?
Seong Ho: What?
Jun Seong: I need to try this on.
(Jun Seong tries on Hyeong Joon's jacket)
Jun Seong: It suits me well.
Chung-ook: Oh, it suits you so well.
-Yung Hee: Oh, wearing that. Okay.
-Gosh.
(Hey)
-Yung Hee: Oh, wearing that. Okay.
-Gosh.
It's so annoying.
-Yung Hee: Go get the clothes.
-Hyeong Joon: Do you want to borrow my shoes, too?
(Shaking his head)
-Yung Hee: Go get the clothes.
-Hyeong Joon: Do you want to borrow my shoes, too?
(Shaking his head)
Hyeong Jin: Oh, you look good. You look like a college student.
(Making a V gesture)
(Chung-ook: The jackets suit Jun Seong and Seong Ho both well)
The jackets suit them both well.
(Making a V gesture)
(Chung-ook: The jackets suit Jun Seong and Seong Ho both well)
-Hyeong Jin: Do you want to go smoke?
-Hyeong Joon: Okay.
Where's Seong Ho?
Hyeong Jin: What do you think of this situation? Is it fun?
-Hyeong Joon: Did you ask me if it was fun?
-Hyeong Jin: Or do you just feel tired?
Hyeong Joon: No, I was busy adjusting at first. I was a little tired then.
Hyeong Joon: I seldom showed it.
Hyeong Joon: Now it's more and more like a battlefield.
Hyeong Joon: Anyway, it has nothing to do with me.
Hyeong Joon: But until two days ago,
Hyeong Joon: I didn't talk much or listen to others.
Hyeong Joon: I heard nothing because I didn't talk to others much.
Hyeong Joon: You know what I mean, right?
Hyeong Joon: Since I made it public, I now know many things.
Hyeong Joon: I didn't know those things before.
Hyeong Joon: I also feel a sense of crisis now.
Hyeong Jin: But being in this place,
Hyeong Jin: I can say you have to fight. We fight for each other.
Hyeong Jin: You can't help but feel competitive.
Hyeong Joon: Everyone is hiding a dagger in a smile.
Right?
Hyeong Jin: If it goes on like this, will you change your face in the end?
-Hyeong Jin: Will you take out an electric saw?
-Hyeong Joon: Sixth sense.
Hyung Jin: Giving us an unexpected ending.
Yung Hee: How is my skin?
Yung Hee: I've had a lot of zits, right?
Chung-ook: But it doesn't look dirty.
(Watch carefully)
Yung Hee: But why do I mind it so much?
Yung Hee: What about dark circles? Are they all right?
Chung-ook: I don't think they're very serious, either.
Yung Hee: Can you help me check it?
-Yung Hee: Fix it for me. I'll take a look at you too.
-Chung-ook: There's still time anyway.
Chung-ook: Take care of your skin when you're still in your early 20s.
Yung Hee: I'm going to take care of my skin starting today.
(Clapping)
(Chung-ook's hand touches Yung Hee's face)
Chung-ook: It feels different.
Chung-ook: Yung Hee asked me to put a little makeup on him.
Chung-ook: I put on a base of makeup for him.
Chung-ook: I've never felt such complicated emotions all at once before.
-Hyeong Joon: Which shoes should I wear?
-It's the opposite of me.
Hyeong Joon: Which pair is better?
-But I think this kind…
-Hyeong Joon: Which pair is better?
They're not suitable.
Jun Seong: It looks better with Air Force style.
-Hyeong Joon: This pair or that pair?
-Hyeong Joon: This pair? -Jun Seong: If you wear those, you'll look like a white bear.
-This pair? -Yes.
-Jun Seong: It looks better with Air Force style.
-OK.
Hyeong Joon: They're better than the black ones, right?
Jun Seong: Yes. Do you want to borrow mine?
(Jun Seong: You can wear them together with Min Seong)
-Me? -You two can wear them together.
Jun Seong: Do you wear size 260?
Hyeong Joon: I wear 260, but…
(Jun Seong: Min Seong wears size 250, right? He can wear 250)
Min Seong wears size 250, right? He can wear 250.
Hyeong Joon: Who? But the air force itself…
Hyeong Joon: Ask him first. I'm fine with anything.
Well.
-Jun Seong: Sir. -Yes?
Jun Seong: Do you want my shoes, "Soybean Paste?"
Min Seong: No, thanks.
Jun Seong: Hyeong Joon said he wanted to wear "Soybean Paste."
Min Seong: I'm fine.
Jun Seong: But your outfit doesn't match "Soybean Paste."
(Looking around)
Jun Seong: Don't you have any clothes with an Activity Style? A more casual outfit.
Min Seong: Activity?
Jun Seong: Yes. A little more like Hyeong Joon's style.
Jun Seong: So it can create a kind of ambiance.
Min Seong: It's OK. We coordinated yesterday anyway.
Jun Seong: Are you drawing a line because he didn't call you?
Min Seong: No, it's not like that.
Min Seong: It's not like that.
Jun Seong: Don't you have wide-legged pants?
Min Seong: Wide-legged pants? I didn't bring such clothes here.
Min Seong: All I brought are formal clothes.
Jun Seong: Where's my coffee?
(Here)
(Jun Seong: I wanted to match Hyeong Joon's and Min Seong's clothes)
I wanted to match Hyeong Joon and Min Seong's clothes.
Jun Seong: Min Seong doesn't have any suitable clothes.
Seong Ho: Yung Hee has green clothes.
Jun Seong: No, I wanted to go with Hyeong Joon's style.
Jun Seong: Because Min Seong wears formal clothes every day.
Seong Ho: Are we going for an outing today?
Jun Seong: Are you the minister today?
-Min Seong.
-Seong Ho: Today's outing fashion.
Chung-ook: You look like you're going to play golf.
-Something like that.
-Yung Hee: Yeah. Like playing golf.
Chung-ook: Right?
Going to play golf.
-Jun Seong: It looks like a golf uniform.
-Golf uniform.
Hyeong Jin: Do you need a lint remover?
Jun Seong: Yes, please.
(Jun Seong: I wanted to make it look like a leisure style for Hyeong Joon and Min Seong)
I wanted to make it look like a leisure style.
-But I think it looks nice this way.
-Come with me, sir.
(Hyeong Jin: But I think Min Seong looks nice this way)
(Seong Ho: Come with me)
-But I think it looks nice this way.
-Come with me, sir.
Hyeong Jin: No, just stay here. Just wear this.
-Hyeong Jin: Wear jeans.
-Yung Hee: Yes. It looks nice.
Hyeong Jin: Right? I said it's pretty.
-Min Seong: I'm not going to change.
-Hyeong Jin: OK.
Hyeong Jin: I'll block them for you.
Yung Hee: What does he mean by "block?"
Chung-ook: Block?
Yung Hee: Execute. -Execute.
Yung Hee: He's going to kill them.
(Puff)
Like this?
Hyeong Jin: Min Seong thinks he looks good that way.
Jun Seong: Like this?
Seong Ho: Should we wear Nike Killer Whale shoes?
-Jun Seong: Us? -Seong Ho: The shoes.
-Jun Seong: Do you have Nike Killer Whale shoes?
-Seong Ho: Yes. They are Min Seong's.
Seong Ho: We have the same shoe size.
Jun Seong: I have the same size as Hyeong Joon.
Seong Ho: Does he have Nike Killer Whale shoes?
Jun Seong: Yes.
Seong Ho: Like these? -Yes.
Seong Ho: It's too exaggerated to borrow even shoes. It's disturbing, isn't it?
Right?
Seong Ho: Min Seong.
Seong Ho: Can you borrow me the shoes… Are you wearing Nike Killer Whale shoes today?
-Min Seong: No, I'm not.
-Seong Ho: Really? Then lend them to me.
Min Seong: Okay, you can wear Nike Killer Whale shoes.
-Min Seong: They're right in front.
-Seong Ho: I want to wear them together with Jun Seong, and you and I have the same shoe size.
Min Seong: Okay, go try them on.
Seong Ho: Okay.
-Seong Ho: Are these them?
-Min Seong: Yes. Those.
-Hyeong Joon: Mine is 260.
-Try them on.
-You wear 260 too?
-Jun Seong: Me too.
-You can wear these.
-Do they fit?
Jun Seong: You look cute.
-Hyeong Joon: Yes, it's good.
-It's good. Very cute.
Min Seong: Is it OK? The size?
Seong Ho: Yes, they fit well.
Min Seong: Then wear these.
-I'll wear them cleanly.
-It's okay.
(Jun Seong and Seong Ho borrowed shoes for couples)
-I'll wear them cleanly.
-It's okay.
So cute.
(Jun Seong and Seong Ho borrowed shoes for couples)
Jun Seong: I'm grateful that he said readily "You can wear them."
Jun Seong: He just lent his shoes like that.
Jun Seong: I feel a little sorry at the same time.
Seon Woo: How do we share the cars?
Three to three?
(Yung Hee: 3:3?)
(Nodding)
(Seon Woo: Hyeong Joon and Min Seong, you two go together)
You two go together.
(Nodding)
(Seon Woo: Hyeong Joon and Min Seong, you two go together)
Hyeong Jin: Hyeong Joon, come take a photo with us. We didn't take a photo, did we?
-Hyeong Joon: What? -Hyeong Jin: Photos.
-Photos. -Photos.
Hyeong Joon: Let's take it together.
Hyeong Jin: Why? I want to take a photo of four.
-Hyeong Joon: A group photo.
Hyeong Jin: We took a lot of group photos together.
-Hold on.
-Hyeong Jin: The four of us, take it together.
Min Seong: Now we're joining one by one, right?
Min Seong: Then the eight of us will take it together.
Chung-ook: We should do it like this, right?
Hyeong Jin: But it looks better this way.
Chung-ook: Yes, you're right.
One, two, three.
(A glance)
My eyes.
Hyeong Jin: You two take a photo too.
Min Seong: Us? We have a lot of Polaroid photos together.
-Hyeong Jin: A lot?
-Hyung-joon: A lot.
Hyeong Jin: Then I'll take some photos with Min Seong.
Hyeong Jin: I don't have a lot.
Let me see.
(Hyeong Joon: Are your pierced ears healed?)
(Min Seong: Yes)
-Are your ears healed? -Yes.
(Hyeong Joon: Are your pierced ears healed?)
(Min Seong: Yes)
-The ear stud. -Hurry up.
(Hyeong Jin interrupts Min Seong's conversation)
-The video we took yesterday,
-No.
(Hyeong Jin interrupts Min Seong's conversation)
-did you watch it?
-No, I don't want to watch it.
(Hyeong Jin interrupts Min Seong's conversation)
Min Seong: I watched a little, but I don't want to watch more of it.
(Turning around)
Hyeong Jin: Have you watched a little?
(Hyeong Joon leaves his position in the end)
Quietly.
(Jun Seong and Seong Ho are left alone)
Seong Ho: Why did everyone leave?
Jun Seong: Let's go out too. Everyone is avoiding us.
Seong Ho: I came here
-because I wanted to talk to everyone.
-Everyone is avoiding us.
Jun Seong: Why does everyone avoid us?
Jun Seong: Do they feel uncomfortable with us?
Hyeong Joon: Because you're revolting.
Yung Hee: Let's go back to the room.
(Joking)
Why are you avoiding us?
Seon Woo: How do you want to share the cars?
(Whispering)
Min Seong: I'll just go with the flow.
Seon Woo: Can you do that?
Min Seong: I want to sit next to you naturally.
-So… -Sit next to you.
(Paying attention)
(Seon Woo: If we sit together, then Joon and Jin will be in the other car)
If we sit together, then Joon and Jin will be in the other car.
Seon Woo: Okay.
Seon Woo: It should be fun.
Min Seong: Let's ride together.
Seon Woo: It's a deal, then.
Seon Woo: It's comfortable sitting there.
Yung Hee: It's more comfortable here.
There's a lot of hair on it.
Seon Woo: Right? I think the beds in this room are the most comfortable.
Yung Hee: Yes.
Yung Hee: I'll get some sleep just in case.
Seon Woo: I want to ride in your car with Min Seong.
Yung Hee: What did you say?
(Get up)
(Seon Woo: If three people ride in one car)
Yung Hee: What did you say?
-Seon Woo: Min Seong and I want to be in your car.
-Oh, really?
(Seon Woo: Min Seong abandoned Hyeong Joon and chose me)
-It's my pleasure.
-Min Seong abandoned Hyeong Joon and chose me
(Seon Woo: Min Seong abandoned Hyeong Joon and chose me)
-It's my pleasure.
-Min Seong abandoned Hyeong Joon and chose me
Seon Woo: You give me a ride.
Yung Hee: Can't we be like 2:4?
-Seon Woo: What?
Yung Hee: Two to four.
(Puff)
-How is it?
-Yung Hee: Who did Hyeong Joon call yesterday?
Yung Hee: I heard that he called you.
Seon Woo: Joon? Yes.
Seon Woo: He wasted one precious phone call.
Seon Woo: He's so relaxed.
-Yung Hee: Oh, my.
-Seon Woo: Oh, my.
Yung Hee: He's a total fool.
(A snowy day)
Jun Seong: Today's weather is so beautiful.
-Seong Ho: It suddenly snowed.
-It's a different beauty from yesterday.
The sun was bright yesterday. Today it's a bit overcast.
(Jun Seong and Seong Ho are wearing matching outfits from head to toe)
-Jun Seong: Where should we go?
-Seong Ho: This way.
-Seong Ho: Over there. The sleigh field.
(Found it)
-Jun Seong: Where should we go?
-Seong Ho: Over there. The sleigh field.
Seong Ho: Where? Oh, over there.
-Seong Ho: I thought it was here.
-Jun Seong: It's in the open air.
I'm a little nervous.
(Today's first date place is in a sleigh field)
Seong Ho: I'm a little nervous.
Jun Seong: Do you like amusement facilities?
Seong Ho: I didn't sit there by myself.
Seong Ho: The safety device tied me up.
Jun Seong: Safety device?
-Jun Seong: Safety device?
-Seong Ho: Yes. It ties me up.
(Cute)
-Jun Seong: Safety device?
-Seong Ho: Yes. It ties me up.
Seong Ho: I'm a little scared.
(Jun Seong: No, but the sleigh will go to the back)
No, but the sleigh will go to the back.
-Jun Seong: What if we fly out?
-Seong Ho: I thought…
-Jun Seong: What should we do?
-Seong Ho: we would fly there.
Jun Seong: What if I fall from fear? I don't think so.
-My stomach hurts.
-I weigh 70kg.
(Two men are similar in terms of being afraid of this)
-My stomach hurts.
-I weigh 70kg.
My stomach hurts.
(Two men are similar in terms of being afraid of this)
Are you nervous?
-My stomach hurts.
-The color of the snow is going to be changed.
Snow… No.
Seong Ho: I'm a little scared.
-Jun Seong: I'm a little nervous.
-Seong Ho: How do we get down?
Coach: Stretch your feet out. Just sit inside.
Jun Seong: The heating pad won't fly away, right?
Press down the cloth on both sides first.
(Nervous)
Okay.
Raise your feet.
After you shout one, two, three, just push yourselves out.
OK.
Coach: 1, 2, 3, go.
(The two men keep screaming from the beginning)
Jun Seong: Wait.
Jun Seong: Ah, wait.
Jun Seong: Wow, it's so fast.
Jun Seong: Wow, so fast.
(Dizzy)
(Cute)
Seong Ho: It was so fast.
Jun Seong: Too fast.
-Seong Ho: But it's fun.
-Jun Seong: Yes.
Seong Ho: Let's do it again.
Jun Seong: I can't say anything.
Seong Ho: I was a little scared just now.
-Jun Seong: It's too fast.
-Seong Ho: Yes. Let's do it again.
Seong Ho: Just once? We're already here.
Jun Seong: Let's make a bet with this.
-Seong Ho: What do you want to bet?
-Jun Seong: Let's see who comes down first.
-Jun Seong: Usually when I say we should bet…
-A warm-up match.
I'd lose, most of the time.
Seong Ho: This is a warm-up game.
-Jun Seong: Help each other realize a wish.
-Seong Ho: A wish? Sure.
-Jun Seong: But the deadline is tomorrow.
-To Men's House.
Seong Ho: Until tomorrow.
Until tomorrow.
-Seong Ho: Until the 7th day. -Jun Seong: How about until the 7th day?
-Seong Ho: Okay. Is there any limit?
-What?
Jun Seong: Don't make it material.
Things like that.
Jun Seong: You know what I mean, right?
Jun Seong: Do you know how it feels?
Seong Ho: Ah, I don't know.
-Jun Seong: I'll win.
-Seong Ho: I will win.
-Jun Seong: I will win.
-Seong Ho: Here I go.
Seong Ho: I can win. I can't lose this.
(Cheering)
(Confident)
Higher.
Coach: 1, 2, 3, go.
(Joon-sung leaves a little late)
I'll give you an advantage.
Jun Seong: Wait, I'm still faster than you.
(Making a V gesture)
Jun Seong: Can everyone go this high?
Seong Ho: Maybe it's because you're heavier than me. Right?
Jun Seong: Did those kids go this far?
Jun Seong: I won.
Jun Seong: So tired.
Seong Ho: Let's go. My legs have turned to jelly.
Seong Ho: First, we agreed it can't be anything material.
Seong Ho: Well... We agreed not to borrow money or pay the deposit.
Seong Ho: Ah, I'm a little worried about what kind of wish he'd say.
Seong Ho: Because he's naughty.
Seong Ho: I dare not imagine it.
Jun Seong: I'm very happy. Very very happy.
Jun Seong: I want to bet more. I want to bet something that goes even farther.
Jun Seong: I've been thinking about this.
(The two came to the store after the sleigh rides)
It's cold.
Jun Seong: Can we eat spicy rice cake? I want to eat spicy rice cake.
Seong Ho: I want to eat snacks too.
Jun Seong: I like this very much.
Seong Ho: You know the souvenir store is the key, right?
Seong Ho: Oh, no.
-Jun Seong: Why? It's Pearl's Secret.
-Seong Ho: Then you buy it.
-Jun Seong: buy Pearl's Secret.
-Seong Ho: I don't like the princess stuff.
Jun Seong: Why not? It's good.
-Seong Ho: Then buy one.
-Jun Seong: No. Let's take a look at other things.
Jun Seong: If there's nothing else to buy,
Jun Seong: I'll buy dozens of them.
-Seong Ho: Are you going to buy them in bunches?
-Jun Seong: Dozens.
In bunches?
Jun Seong: Ah, it's a medical hospital game.
It's so childish.
Seong Ho: It's for pupils.
-Jun Seong: There should be something like that.
-What?
Jun Seong: Oh, I found what to buy for you.
Seong Ho: No, I don't want it. Princess again?
Jun Seong: I'll buy you this. Take it with you.
Seong Ho: I like new handbags and phones.
-Seong Ho: When I go to work...
-Every time I called…
Seong Ho: I'll take this with me, okay?
Jun Seong: you never answered my questions. You just said what you want to say,
-and then hang up.
-It's not that serious, is it?
Seong Ho: It's fake. It's thinner than a Samsung phone.
Jun Seong: Ah, it's so funny.
-Jun Seong: Wow.
-Seong Ho: This is the atmosphere light.
(The atmosphere light)
-Jun Seong: Wow.
-Seong Ho: This is the atmosphere light.
(The atmosphere light)
Try to do this.
-It's so funny.
-Seong Ho: Buy this. I want to buy this.
-Jun Seong: This?
-Seong Ho: Yes. Can you buy it for me?
-Jun Seong: Do you want this?
-Seong Ho: Yes.
-Jun Seong: This?
-Seong Ho: Yes. Aren't you going to buy it?
Jun Seong: I won't buy it. You buy it for me.
Seong Ho: OK, I'll buy this for you.
Seong Ho: Buy something cute. Don't buy anything useless.
Jun Seong: Well, this is...
-Jun Seong: His eyes are open.
-It's of bad quality.
-Jun Seong: What if they accuse us of doing it?
-Seong Ho: No, no.
-No.
-Jun Seong: Pretend you didn't see it.
-I didn't see it.
-Jun Seong: The green one looks better than this one.
Seong Ho: The green one is the cutest.
Seong Ho: Buy two green ones. Let's hang them here.
-Isn't it cute?
-Jun Seong: Buy two. Now!
-It's cute.
-Jun Seong: Great idea.
Seong Ho: Hang it on the pants.
Seong Ho: Actually, I don't use a phone chain recently.
Look at it.
Seong Ho: We went to the souvenir store
Seong Ho: and saw cute keychains.
Seong Ho: So we bought keychains for couples.
Seong Ho: The atmosphere light emits lights like aurora
Seong Ho: and like the universe.
Seong Ho: So we each bought one as a couple.
Jun Seong: Instead of declaring our relationship as a couple,
Jun Seong: it's more like an expression of the same feelings from us.
(Men's House) (Six men are preparing for a group date)
How do we share the cars? We have to decide on that too.
I think we should decide first. About later.
Chung-ook: Who wants to ride in my car?
-Today… -Who wants to ride?
(Yung Hee: Wait… Are Chung-ook and Hyeong Joon driving? )
(Chung-ook: Yes)
-Today… -Who wants to ride?
-Wait. Are you two driving?
-Yes.
(Yung Hee: Wait… Are Chung-ook and Hyeong Joon driving? )
(Chung-ook: Yes)
-Then I'll go first.
-Hyeong Jin: Are they driving?
(Yung Hee: Wait… Are Chung-ook and Hyeong Joon driving? )
(Chung-ook: Yes)
-Then I'll go first.
-Hyeong Jin: Are they driving?
I want…
(Hyeong Jin: I want to ride in Hyeong Joon's car)
Then I'll take Hyeong Joon's car.
What do you mean?
Hyeong Jin: Chung-ook and Hyeong Joon will drive later.
Hyeong Jin: We can take two separate cars.
Hyeong Jin: I'll take Hyeong Joon's car.
Seon Woo: Okay.
Seon Woo: Oh, okay. Then Min Seong can take that car.
Hyeong Jin: Min Seong, you can really sleep anywhere.
Min Seong: It may be narcolepsy. I fall asleep accidentally.
Hyeong Jin: Are you too used to this place?
Min Seong: Is that so?
Yung Hee: Are you up? Yes.
Yung Hee: Ah, I'm sleepy. I'm so sleepy that I can faint.
Yung Hee: What is that? Is it to reduce swelling?
Hyeong Jin: Yes. Min Seong and I will take Hyeong Joon's car.
Oh, really?
(Min Seong is silent)
I'm asking if you want to ride with us.
Hyeong Jin: I want to ride in Hyung Joon's car.
Hyeong Joon: Me? Do you want to ride in my car?
-Yes. Can I?
-Hyeong Joon: You've never been in my car.
-Yung Hee: Then let's divide like that.
-What do you think it'll be?
Let's just sit like that.
Yung Hee: Let's take Chung-ook's car.
Chung-ook: We can sit separately like that.
(Yong Hee: Me, you, and Seon Woo, we three take one car, and Hyeong Jin, Hyeong Joon, and Min Seong, you three take the other)
(Chung-ook: Okay)
Chung-ook: We can sit separately like that.
Yes, the three of us take one car. They three take the other.
(Yong Hee: Me, you, and Seon Woo, we three take one car, and Hyeong Jin, Hyeong Joon, and Min Seong, you three take the other)
(Chung-ook: Okay)
Okay.
(Yong Hee: Me, you, and Seon Woo, we three take one car, and Hyeong Jin, Hyeong Joon, and Min Seong, you three take the other)
(Chung-ook: Okay)
-Hyeong Jin: Let's go. Are you ready?
-Min Seong: Yeah.
Hyeong Jin: I have to go to the bathroom.
(Sigh)
-Min Seong: I won't let you go.
-Me?
I won't let you go.
Seon Woo: What's wrong? I can't help it.
-Isn't that right?
-Min Seong: Why am I automatically assigned to their car?
Seon Woo: Just together… Wait. What do you want?
(Min Seong: I don't know… Actually, I'm not comfortable with either Hyeong Joon or Hyeong Jin)
I don't know… Actually, I'm not comfortable with either Hyeong Joon or Hyeong Jin.
Seon Woo: No. I think it's still okay for you to change your mind now.
Seon Woo: But I think
Seon Woo: it may help you to make up your mind.
Min Seong: No, I think... I think I should give up both of them.
-Seon Woo: Stop kidding. Let's see.
-I mean it.
Min Seong: I might have to give up both.
-Min Seong: Who wants to switch with me?
-What?
-Min Seong: Who wants to switch places with me?
-Seon Woo: Why?
-Why?
-I want to ride in Chung-ook's car.
(Min Seong: I want to ride in Chung-ook's car)
-Why?
-I want to ride in Chung-ook's car.
I want to try it once.
(Min Seong: I want to ride in Chung-ook's car)
(Seon Woo: I think you prefer Hyeong Joon's car, don't you?
I want to try it once.
I think you prefer Hyeong Joon's car, don't you?
(Seon Woo: I think you prefer Hyeong Joon's car, don't you?
-Seon Woo: Don't you?
-Min Seong: Er…
(Hyeong Joon called Yung Hee aside alone)
-What?
-Do you want to drive?
(Hyeong Joon called Yung Hee aside alone)
-What?
-Do you want to drive?
Yung Hee: By the way, why did Min Seong suddenly say he didn't want to take your car?
Hyeong Joon: It's OK. We don't have to ride together.
Yung Hee: Then I'll drive.
Hyeong Joon: Then we have to change members.
-What?
-Hyeong Joon: We have to change members again.
Yung Hee: Ah, it's okay. Just go and tell them.
Hyeong Joon: We have a new driver.
(Hyeong Joon: Chung-ook, Seon Woo, and Min Seong, the three sit together and I'll take this one)
The three sit together and I'll take this one.
-Hyeong Jin: Are you driving?
-Yung Hee: Yes.
Hyeong Jin: I'll sit in Yung Hee's car. Is that OK?
Seon Woo: Are you sure
-Seon Woo: we can choose freely which car to take?
-Min Seong: Can't we?
Hyeong Joon: I wanted to ride with Seon Woo and Min Seong,
Hyeong Joon: but I felt Min Seong didn't like it.
Hyeong Joon: So I was in a bad mood at that time.
Hyeong Joon: Though I felt sorry, I asked to sit in the other car.
Hyeong Joon: Because I was in a bad condition to drive.
Hyeong Joon: I was in a bad mood.
-Chung-ook: Min Seong, sit in the front.
-Min Seong: Should I sit in the front?
Seon Woo: Why should I sit in the back?
-Hyeong Joon: See you later.
-Chung-ook: Please fasten your seat belt.
Okay.
Min Seong: I think I feel uncomfortable being with Hyeong Joon and Hyeong Jin together.
Min Seong: I think that's the main reason.
Min Seong: If we are all together, I feel suffocated.
Min Seong: I don't know what I should say in that situation.
Min Seong: So I think it's kind of awkward.
Min Seong: I feel so at ease here.
Chung-ook: Because of the car?
Min Seong: Both the car and the atmosphere are comfortable.
Seon Woo: Who makes you uncomfortable?
(Min Seong: Hyeong Joon and Hyeong Jin, those two)
Those two.
Seon Woo: The fact you're not comfortable putting aside, haven't you already preferred one of them?
-Min Seong: Me? -Yes.
Min Seong: No, I don't prefer anyone.
Why are you behaving like that, too?
Seon Woo: You might end up like me if you keep sounding out…
Min Seong: I'm not sounding out anyone.
Min Seong: To be honest, I thought I could make a choice yesterday.
(Seon Woo: Why did you get angry? "I'm not sounding out anyone")
"I'm not sounding out anyone."
Min Seong: But... No.
Seon Woo: Oh, you thought you could make a choice, but you couldn't?
Min Seong: Yes, I thought I preferred one of them.
-Min Seong: Yes. After our date, I thought I already preferred one.
-Uh-huh.
Min Seong: But why? Why are they pushing me again?
Seon Woo: What do you think?
Seon Woo: Both of them. Did you notice their love triangle?
Chung-ook: Well, is there a problem?
-No, well...
-Chung-ook: I think I know
Chung-ook: who likes whom.
But I don't know if there is a love triangle.
(Chung-ook: But I don't know if there's a love triangle)
Who do you think is better? Jin or Joon?
But I don't know if there is a love triangle.
(Seon Woo: Who do you think is better? Jin or Joon?)
Who do you think is better? Jin or Joon?
Jin-Joon.
-Chung-ook: Personally, I think…
-Yeah.
Chung-ook: If being in a relationship,
Chung-ook: I might like Jin more, in terms of personality.
Chung-ook: Joon is interesting,
Chung-ook: but sometimes he's not serious enough.
Chung-ook: Because he wants to solve every problem without hard feelings.
Chung-ook: In terms of personality…
Seon Woo: Oh, I'm a little surprised.
(Min Seong: That's how I feel, because I talked more with Jin, Hyeong Jin)
That's how I feel
because I talked more with Jin.
(Min Seong: That's how I feel, because I talked more with Jin, Hyeong Jin)
I started to have feelings for Jin during our conversations.
(Min Seong: I started to have feelings for Jin during our conversations)
Really?
Min Seong: At first, I wondered what was wrong with him.
Min Seong: He didn't like what I liked.
In my eyes, Joon is far far better.
(Seon Woo: In my eyes, Joon is far far better)
(Seon Woo: It must be Joon, Hyeong Joon)
It must be Joon.
Seon Woo: I see. Isn't that too much?
Seon Woo: Okay. I won't set you up anymore.
Min Seong: But that's what I'm worried about.
(Min Seong: I'm worried that Joon and I have different lifestyles)
I'm worried that Joon and I have different lifestyles.
Min Seong: And I don't really want to date famous people.
-Right.
-I think it'll be stressful.
(Min Seong: I think it'll be stressful)
(Chung-ook: You'd feel pressured?)
-Right.
-I think it'll be stressful.
You'd feel pressured?
(Min Seong: I think it'll be stressful)
(Chung-ook: You'd feel pressured?)
Yes, I'd feel pressured to date a celebrity.
(Min Seong: I think it'll be stressful)
(Chung-ook: You'd feel pressured?)
Chung-ook: Why?
Min Seong: I'd feel tired in the end. I mind a lot of things.
Min Seong: Because if he knows a lot of people,
Min Seong: many people may contact him.
Min Seong: Well, I still mind those things.
Min Seong: I didn't have any feelings for Hyeong Jin at first.
Min Seong: I didn't think he was my type.
Min Seong: But after our conversation, I found he's a nice guy.
Really?
(Min Seong: Considering Joon's shortcomings in his different lifestyles, Jin suits me in this aspect)
Considering Joon's shortcomings in his different lifestyles, Jin suits me in this aspect,
(Min Seong: Hyeong Jin's lifestyle is the same as mine)
(Min Seong: Considering Joon's shortcomings in his different lifestyles, Jin suits me in this aspect)
His lifestyle is the same as mine.
(Min Seong: Hyeong Jin's lifestyle is the same as mine)
Min Seong: They both have advantages and disadvantages in different aspects.
Seon Woo: If I fall in love with someone,
Seon Woo: these parts won't matter.
Seon Woo: It must be hard to be in love because our lifestyles are different.
Seon Woo: But to me, those problems are not as important as the attraction.
Min Seong: See? I guess I'm really an avoidant type of person.
Seon Woo: Not avoidant, you're just realistic.
-Chung-ook: Yeah, you're not avoidant.
-Well.
Yung Hee: It's snowing again today.
-Hyeong Joon: It's snowing.
-Being…
Yung Hee: Being able to pair up and go on a one-on-one date on a day like this,
(Yung Hee: Jun Seong and Seong Ho must be very happy)
They must be very happy.
Hyeong Jin: I know.
Longxin Pavilion.
Hyeong Joon: But to be honest, the reversal of today's mission is me, right?
Hyeong Joon: Don't you think so?
Yung Hee: Did everything go well for you guys?
Yung Hee: After today, tomorrow is the last day.
Yung Hee: Wow, it's really the last day.
Hyeong Joon: Tomorrow is the last day. Last night.
Yung Hee: Yes.
For a long time…
No, for a short time.
(Correction: For a short time)
We become friends who have feelings for each other.
No, for a short time.
There's no need to say goodbye. Let's meet in Itaewon.
See you in Itaewon.
Yung Hee: How about we go to Itaewon? The three of us.
Hyeong Jin: Great.
-Hyeong Joon: Wow.
-Let's go to Itaewon.
Hyeong Joon: OK.
(Six men arrive at the meeting place for the group date)
Go! Go!
Yung Hee: Thank you.
Let's go.
Seon Woo: A group date. I'm so excited.
-Hyeong Jin: Did you bring heating pads?
-Min Seong: What?
Heating pads.
(Look)
Hyeong Jin: Then why are you walking like this?
-Why? -Are you cold already?
I'm a little scared.
(Men's first group date: karting)
The karts are so cute.
Yeah, so cute.
(Men's first group date: karting)
Chung-ook: They're smaller than I thought.
-Sit on it. -You can step on it.
Seon Woo: What is this?
If you step on this, you'll rush out, right?
(Everyone chooses a kart they like)
I can't step on it.
The brake is on the left and the accelerator is on the right.
(Before starting the karts, the six men learn safety instructions first)
If you step on both together, you won't go forward. Just step on one.
The accelerator, the brake.
Step on the accelerator hard to move forward.
Yung Hee: Should we make a bet today?
Min Seong: No.
Okay, no bets then.
(The youngest is angry)
-Hyeong Joon: Let's bet.
-Min Seong: Let's play.
(The youngest is angry)
-Hyeong Joon: Let's bet.
-Min Seong: Let's play.
Yung Hee: No, I'm not playing. I'm sad.
(Hyeong Joon: First of all, let Jun Seong and Seong Ho do the dishes today! What do you think?)
First of all, let Jun Seong and Seong Ho do the dishes today.
What do you think?
(Hyeong Joon: First of all, let Jun Seong and Seong Ho do the dishes today! What do you think?)
Seon Woo: I'm afraid they won't come back today.
They're not coming back?
Will they stay out tonight?
They won't come back.
Hyeong Joon: What should we bet on?
-Min Seong: Do the dishes.
-Do the dishes?
-Do the dishes.
-Hyeong Joon: What else?
Yung Hee: Do the dishes and make supper.
-Min Seong: OK, supper.
-Make supper.
Do the dishes and make supper.
Hyeong Joon: Do you all agree?
-Yes. -OK.
-OK. -OK.
(Ah)
(Confused)
Shouldn't we fix this?
(Worried)
Seon Woo: You all should be careful. Don't get hit by me.
Yung Hee: Do you have a driver's license?
Seon Woo: Of course I do.
Now move to the track.
(Men's group date officially begins)
Three, two, one, go!
(Men's bet: The winner can appoint "a maid" to do the dishes)
One lap?
-Yes. -One lap?
(Men's bet: The winner can appoint "a maid" to do the dishes)
Hyeong Joon: Should I make it look real?
Yung Hee: Make it real.
(Start to drive like driving a car)
What?
Hold on.
(Start to drive like driving a car)
Seon Woo: Oh, washing dishes is not a big deal.
Min Seong: That's right. No big deal.
Seon Woo: Washing dishes is not a big deal. Why risk your life?
(Hyeong Joon passes the finish line first)
No.
There's a car accident.
(Hyeong Joon passes the finish line first)
Right.
No.
(Team 1: Hyeong Joon wins)
It stopped.
(Round 2: Hyeong Jin and Chung-ook's battle)
My legs are cramping.
Step on the brake.
Go.
-Hyeong Jin: Can we go now?
-Yes.
-Seon Woo: The start is important.
-We have to win.
(Oh?)
-Seon Woo: The start is important.
-We have to win.
Chung-ook: It stopped.
Don't stop. Step on the accelerator.
(Hyeong Jin takes this chance and races forward)
It stopped.
Reverse it then.
(Hyeong Jin takes this chance and races forward)
-Chung-ook: No.
-Why can't I see you?
Bro, hurry up!
-The first place. -Seeing this…
(Team 2: Hyeong Jin wins)
Congratulations.
What should we do? Should we replay the game?
(Team 2: Hyeong Jin wins)
Yung Hee: You've made it to the final.
Hyeong Joon: Did he make it to the final?
Yung Hee: Yes.
(V)
-Hyeong Joon: The first place in my heart.
-It's great to finish the game.
(V)
Yung Hee: Yes.
-Hyeong Joon: The first place in my heart.
-It's great to finish the game.
Hyeong Joon: The first place in my heart.
To be able to finish the game, you are already...
Hyeong Jin: Why did you stop?
Chung-ook: No, it stopped suddenly.
Hyeong Jin: I didn't know if I should stop or move forward.
Yung Hee: I didn't see you hesitate at all.
Really?
You stepped on the accelerator with all your might, right?
Yes, I saw you rushing out.
(Embarrassed)
The first place is mine.
You didn't even look back.
(Round 3: A battle between roommates—Min Seong and Seon Woo)
Roommate battle.
Come on.
(Round 3: A battle between roommates—Min Seong and Seon Woo)
Three.
Hyeong Joon: I bet two heating pads that Min Seong's gonna win.
-It begins. -It begins.
(Round 3: Min Seong and Seon Woo start)
Min Seong, go!
(Hey) (The battle between the two has been exciting since the beginning)
Hey.
This is fun.
You think I'm easy to deal with?
I'm good when I'm serious.
Seon Woo: In fact, I felt a little depressed.
Seon Woo: When the couple went out to date, I felt a little empty.
Seon Woo: But when we drove, I became very happy.
Seon Woo: Go away. Go away.
Go away. No, no, no.
Hyeong Joon: Come on. Come on. Come on.
I told you. That's a blind corner.
Let go.
(Relaxed)
(Min Seong successfully overtakes on the final bend)
The last-minute sprint is amazing.
(Group 3: Roommate Battle, Min Seong wins) (Pity)
Seriously.
Min Seong: I was almost in danger.
(The last round: Hyeong Jin, Min Seong, and Hyeong Joon) (The final of the three)
I support Hyeong Joon.
-Sit tight.
-I think Hyeong Joon will win.
(The last round: Hyeong Jin, Min Seong, and Hyeong Joon) (The final of the three)
-Sit tight.
-I think Hyeong Joon will win.
Hyeong Jin: At that time I was thinking I should fight for the first place.
Hyeong Jin: I thought I would get a reward like the mission card,
Hyeong Jin: so I struggled to win.
-Let's go. -Come on!
(The final begins)
Never mind.
I want to change a person to support.
(Min Seong rushes to the front right away)
-Me too.
-I wanted to change from the first second.
(Min Seong rushes to the front right away)
(Currently No.3)
Hyeong Jin: You can't take the first place.
(Hyeong Joon: Wow)
Hyeong Jin: You can't get the first place.
Seon Woo: Min Seong, you have to win!
(Min Seong is racing fast until the very end)
(He's always in the lead) (Min Seong wins the "Doing Dishes" Karting Final)
-Yeah! -Yeah!
I won.
Hyeong Jin: When Min Seong got the first place,
Hyeong Jin: I thought, he was more competitive than I thought.
Hyeong Jin I saw an unexpected side of him.
(Second Activity for Group Date: Zip Lining)
Left foot. Left foot.
Left foot. Not this. Left foot.
(Second Activity for Group Date: Zip Lining)
Ranger! Ranger!
Hyeong Joon: It's my first time playing zip lining. I'm so scared.
Safety agent: Look here. There are two ropes.
Safety agent: You can do it in twos, hand in hand.
Safety agent: Which two will play first?
Yung Hee: Us.
Yung Hee: I want to team up like this.
Yung Hee: Oh, this is an opportunity.
Yung Hee: Only those who are confident can get love.
Yung Hee: So I said first that I want to do it with Seon Woo.
-You two? -Let's go.
Yes.
-Okay. This way, please. -Us, too.
Chung-ook: I can see that Yung Hee actively tries to get chances to be with Seon Woo.
Chung-ook: His behavior made me a little jealous.
I feel like I've been ignored all day.
Hyeong Joon: Switch with me.
Switch with me, please.
(Hyeong Joon wants to go with Min Seong)
Switch with me.
Chung-ook: OK.
(Hyeong Joon wants to go with Min Seong)
-Hyeong Jin: I want to switch too.
-Hyeong Joon: With what?
Hyeong Jin: I want to be in that group too.
Hyeong Joon: You sit in the middle then.
Hyeong Jin: How about rock paper scissors?
Hyeong Joon: Why?
Hyeong Jin: I want to sit with Minseong, too.
Hyeong Joon: Really?
Hyeong Jin: Sit with him if you want. I was just kidding.
(Min Seong: Then Hyeong Joon and Hyeong Jin, you two sit together)
(Hyeong Jin: Just kidding)
Hyeong Jin: Sit with him if you want. I was just kidding.
Then you two sit together
(Min Seong: Then Hyeong Joon and Hyeong Jin, you two sit together)
(Hyeong Jin: Just kidding)
Just kidding.
(Min Seong: Then Hyeong Joon and Hyeong Jin, you two sit together)
(Hyeong Jin: Just kidding)
Hyeong Jin: If I insist too much, Chung-ook might think
Hyeong Jin: it's because I don't want to sit with him.
Hyeong Jin: It could lead to a misunderstanding.
Hyeong Jin: And I also suddenly realized that Min Seong might feel awkward.
Hyeong Jin: There are still many chances anyway.
Hyeong Jin: And I'm also very confident.
Hyeong Joon: What is he doing?
Hyeong Joon: Everyone was there. In front of everyone.
Hyeong Joon: Why did he do such a thing?
Hyeong Joon: Well, Anyway, everyone knows our relationship,
Hyeong Joon: although we are not officially in a relationship.
Min Seong: It can be seen as a psychological battle.
Minseong: I think the tense atmosphere that no one gives up
Min Seong: makes me uncomfortable.
(Hyeong Jin starts to express his feelings to Min Seong)
Eat this.
I feel something is wrong.
("Something is wrong")
Suddenly a catfish came in.
(How will the relationship among the three develop?)