♪I want to just lean on
your shoulder like this♪
♪Through the curtains♪
♪Quietly admiring
the arc light in the filter♪
♪Just like our life♪
♪We need to know
how to adjust colors and lighting♪
♪I want to hold your hands♪
♪And stand by your side♪
♪See through the lies in the world♪
♪Tear down the walls
obstructing our thoughts♪
♪Just like our souls♪
♪We need to know how to stay refreshed♪
♪The streets are crowded♪
♪Time rushes by♪
♪Shadows dance
in the streetlamp's cold light♪
♪The story has just begun♪
♪Our simple days are ahead♪
=Simple Days=
=Episode 26=
I arranged for the meeting
between Moli and Zhou Yu.
I did it intentionally.
Because I knew
Moli has harbored the dream
of becoming an artist.
I knew that she has been
good at painting.
I think I've always
felt guilty about hurting her
and I've been looking
to make amends.
That's why I pulled the strings.
I think
with Moli's talent
and Zhou Yu's resources,
Moli will achieve something great.
When I heard
she was going to have an art exhibition,
I was so thrilled.
I didn't expect
introducing Zhou Yu to Moli
almost got her into trouble.
I lacked
the professional insight of a lawyer.
But fortunately, you were there.
You found the problem in time
and gathered evidence.
You put this to an end in time
and avoided serious trouble.
I'm responsible for what has happened
to Moli.
I'm sorry.
I see.
You meant well.
I don't blame you.
I think Moli won't blame you either.
Jincao,
what you did proved
Moli had made the right choice.
No matter what,
you'll always put her safety first
and protect her.
That's quite rare.
I will delete both of your phone numbers
once everything is settled
and disappear from your life.
You are everything she needs.
I see.
I have to go now.
Jincao,
Moli is a good woman.
You deserve to be together.
I hope you two never part.
Thank you.
I have made it clear in court.
This house is mine.
The house in Shanghai is also mine.
I know you too well.
You don't have a place
to stay once you leave.
Therefore,
you can live here
after the divorce.
I'll take the big room.
You'll take the small room.
Then I'll take the small room.
You can have the big one.
No need.
You are always
trying to act tough.
I'll move out
if you insist on it.
I'll rent a place.
You can live here.
Here are
all our savings.
I've withdrawn them all.
I cashed out everything
from these two accounts.
It's 73,651 yuan in total.
Seventy thousand yuan for you.
Three thousand yuan for me.
We are getting a divorce.
We must settle the accounts.
I don't want it.
You're trying to act tough again.
You're retired from kindergarten,
with a pension
of 1,000 yuan or so every month.
How are you going to live?
Take these 70,000 yuan
in case of any emergency.
You wouldn't have to
ask your son for help.
How are you going to make it
with only 3,000 yuan?
Don't worry about me.
I was the head of the publicity dept.
of a machinery factory.
I get a pension
of almost 4,000 yuan.
Can you compare with me?
Just take it.
Hurry up.
The accounts are settled.
There are a few things I'd like to say.
Zhang Shanya.
We've lived together for 36 years.
You know what's on my mind.
And I know
what's on your mind,
why you're divorcing me,
and why you're back.
I know everything.
I-I don't know what you're saying.
I stand by what I said.
As long as
I'm alive,
I have the final say.
As for your little schemes...
Forget it.
Are you done?
Kind of.
Zhang Shanya...
If you have nothing else to say,
I need to pack up.
Jincao will be here soon.
I'm sorry.
Sorry...
Dali.
Dali, what happened?
Wake up.
Dali.
(Operation Room, In surgery)
Sorry, we've done our best.
Your father passed away
at 10:52 PM.
Condolences.
Mom.
No way.
(Honey)
You finally called me.
Where are you?
My dad passed away.
Please bring Ke here.
Grandma.
Why did you put Grandpa's photo here?
Your grandpa
has gone on a long trip.
Where did he go?
Somewhere far away.
What do I do if I miss him?
Ke.
You didn't sleep all night.
You should get some sleep.
I want Grandma to watch me as I sleep.
Ke, be good.
Grandma is not feeling well.
Come with me.
(Overseas Education Training)
Liuliu, I haven't managed
to solve my problems all these years.
But I don't think
that happiness
necessarily requires a marriage.
I know you have opinions about me.
But you must let me explain it.
It's okay. Take your time.
But I hope
this is the last time.
I remember I told you
how I became the way I am now.
I'm an only child.
My parents have always
had high hopes for me.
They invested everything in me.
But I grew up
and felt that their love for me
was rather controlling,
demanding, and oppressive.
It suffocated me.
I know I shouldn't speak ill of them.
But I'm trying to tell you
that my family background
makes me scared.
Once I start a family
and have children,
I might force my kids
to follow the path
I laid out for them
and force them to do things they hate
in the name of love.
It's terrifying.
I'm not sure.
I've asked myself
whether I'd be able
to provide for my family
and protect them
from harm.
I'm not sure about that either.
If I can't make my family happy,
why should I get married
or bring a new life
to this world?
That makes sense.
So why are you contemplating?
Because I met you.
I feel so insignificant
and so selfish.
I like you so much.
But I'm afraid of taking responsibility.
I dare not express myself.
I remained indecisive
even after you got pregnant.
And you?
You are so brave.
Qianniu told me
you'll give birth to the child
even if this child has no father.
And this newborn
is partly mine.
Also,
there is a woman who is willing to
give her all for me.
How can I not care?
How can I remain indifferent?
So I came here to tell you
I want to be the father of this child.
I want to be your husband.
♪My understanding of life♪
♪Across several streets of affection♪
♪From two people talking
about everything♪
♪To being alone in the crowd♪
Liuliu, marry me.
My condolences.
Thank you.
Condolences.
Excuse me.
You must be his son
who works in Shanghai.
Yeah, it's me.
I sell breakfast on the street.
I remember you.
Your dad gets breakfast
from me every day.
I came over as soon as I got the news.
Your dad had a bit of a temper.
He argued with me
many times over a few cents.
(My daughter)
(had severe Kawasaki disease.)
(I started fundraising)
(as someone suggested.)
(Your dad was the first one)
(who brought me money.)
(And he gave me 3,000 yuan.)
(It's more than enough)
(for breakfast in a whole year.)
I said it was too much.
But he insisted on giving it to me.
Thank you.
Sister-in-law.
Director Liu, what brings you here?
Mr. Zhu passed away.
Why didn't you tell us?
You are quite busy.
Don't talk like a stranger.
Chief Zhu is an esteemed senior.
We have to come
no matter how busy we are.
Thank you.
♪Like a continuous shot♪
♪Like a camera that's always on,
never shutting off♪
♪Scene by scene, these memories♪
You are Jincao, right?
You've grown up so much.
Jincao, you're what makes your dad
proud of himself.
He always praised you,
saying that you are independent
and work on your own
in Shanghai without him worrying.
You even bought an apartment.
All of us have lost
(much of our laughter
ever since your dad retired.)
You have no idea.
Your dad was always the lead drummer
for the annual performance.
Without him,
the performance lost its vigor.
♪Like a continuous shot♪
♪Like a camera that's always on,
never shutting off♪
(Also,)
(your dad would stay up all night)
(writing Spring Festival couplets
before the Lunar New Year.)
After all these years,
the couplets he wrote
have reached every village
and town in our county.
What a pity.
We won't hear the drum
or see the couplets anymore.
Condolences.
Sister-in-law, my condolences.
Thank you.
Let them be.
Your dad made those.
He made three bowls of them.
He broke one bowl.
These are the only two bowls left.
It was the first time
your dad cooked for us.
Let's keep them.
Ke's Grandma.
I made some porridge.
Have some.
Mom.
You haven't eaten for two days.
You'll fall sick if you go on like this.
Ke is not coming out of the bedroom.
She says she won't eat until you eat.
I don't have the appetite.
Our family has undergone
some changes over the years.
You got married in Shanghai
and gave birth to Ke.
Your dad told me
to retire early
and look after Ke in Shanghai.
Babysitters cost a lot there.
And they don't take
great care of the kids.
So, I went to Shanghai.
I did my best to take care of Ke
and your family.
Right, let me show you.
I found it some days ago
when I was packing.
His medical exam report.
His blood pressure and blood lipids
have been getting higher
over these three years.
The medical advice says
that he needs
regular check-ups and treatment.
But no one reminded him.
Nor did anyone care about him.
Whenever I called,
he said, "I'm fine.
Don't worry."
I didn't expect it to be so sudden.
The divorce was the fuse.
We didn't tell you
when we were getting divorced.
First, we're not so young anymore.
Getting a divorce at this age
might be embarrassing for both of you.
Secondly,
I thought
I couldn't leave this household.
That's what I have decided.
I've spent my whole life with him.
Where could I go?
We came out of the court that day.
He took out all his savings,
73,000 yuan.
He kept
only 3,000 yuan for himself.
I had no other choice.
I think your conflicts
all started
because of that small apartment.
You were talking about selling it
to get a bigger one.
I called your dad over
from our hometown.
It has been chaotic
since then.
Not a single day passed in peace.
I am the one to blame.
So I wondered what to do.
The only solution was
to switch to a bigger house.
But your dad was against it.
And your parents wouldn't budge on it.
So I thought
maybe I should get a divorce.
Only by getting a divorce
can I get half
of that apartment in Shanghai.
You don't have enough
for the down payment.
I was thinking
if your parents could help you out
with the down payment,
you could get a bigger apartment.
Your family of three
could live your life happily.
Let's eat.
I have no appetite.
Zhu Dali
had a bad temper,
but he was not a bad person.
Look how well he treated Ke.
He was just proud.
It's too late now.
It's my fault.
He was proud.
I could be less aggressive.
It's all for the kids.
Why would I be against him?
Who knows
he'd have a cerebral hemorrhage?
It hasn't been easy for Jincao.
He got divorced and lost his job.
And now his father passed away.
I'm worried he can't handle it.
Gu,
am I too harsh on Jincao?
Yeah, me too.
No matter what has happened
over the years,
he's been genuinely in love with Moli.
I can see this.
Yulan, let's agree on this.
Let's stop meddling
in the kids' affairs from now on.
Let them live their lives.
Alright?
Grandma,
is Grandpa really not coming back?
But,
what should we do
about these unfinished boats?
Grandma will finish them for you.
Do you know how to do it?
No.
But I can learn.
But can you do it as well as Grandpa?
I will try my best.
I guess
you can't do it as well as Grandpa.
That's right.
I can't do it as well as Grandpa.
So, let's keep these boats
well-preserved
as keepsakes.
Grandma,
where did Grandpa go?
Come here, Ke.
Listen to me.
Grandpa has gone to heaven.
If you see the brightest star
blinking at you at night,
it's Grandpa saying hello to you.
♪Twinkle, twinkle, little star♪
♪How I wonder what you are♪
♪Up above the world so high♪
♪Like a diamond in the sky♪
♪Twinkle, twinkle, little star♪
♪How I wonder what you are♪
Every word that my mother
said today
was like a knife stabbing my heart.
I never knew
that she did it all for me.
I've been ungrateful.
Apart from causing them
trouble and pain,
I've never
done anything wholeheartedly for them.
My life shouldn't be like this.
I've put up with so many things
and compromised so much
just to enjoy our simple days.
Why is it so hard?
Jincao.
Don't be harsh on yourself.
I'm the one who should feel guilty.
I used to be willful
and spoiled.
You spoiled me.
If I could be more tolerant
and more patient,
our families wouldn't have
so many misunderstandings.
Our parents
dedicated everything they had
to our family.
It would be their deepest regret
if we were not happy.
Jincao.
Let's remarry.
You calm down and think it over.
I'm very calm.
I don't want to have any regrets.
Since we love each other,
we should never part.
Moli.
This is the Premises Permit
of your apartment.
First things first.
Sell the apartment
and get a new house.
(Premises Permit)
Take it.
And take the money of 70,000 yuan.
No, I can't take the money.
You have to pay off a loan
once you get a new place.
It's not much.
Spend it wisely.
No, we can't take it.
Moli.
Take it.
Grandma, come back to Shanghai with me.
Ke, be good.
Grandma can't go back with you yet.
I will visit you
after a while, okay?
Come, let me kiss you.
Mom, I'm worried about leaving you
here alone.
Come with us.
I can't go.
If I leave,
your dad won't be able
to find his way home.
Besides, he passed away too suddenly.
I had to explain to
our relatives and friends.
I'll be fine.
Don't worry, son.
Hurry up.
It's quite a long ride.
Drive safe.
Get going.
(A few months later)
We need to hurry.
Liuliu is waiting
at the civil affairs office.
We must be there.
Forget it.
Nothing matters more
than making you a painter.
(Marriage Registration Office)
Open your mouth.
I want some milk.
Here it is.
Here, slowly.
What kind of bestie is she?
It's the most important day for you.
You didn't
invite anyone but her.
And she stood you up.
What kind of cousin is he?
Didn't you invite just him?
And?
He promised to come,
but he wasn't texting back.
You can't count on him.
They're just the same.
Yeah, exactly.
Watch how I deal with Gu Moli later.
I will ask Zhu Jincao
for compensation.
Ask for money.
Absolutely.
Wipe your mouth.
Civil registration number 23,
please come to window No. 3.
Here.
Honey, please proceed.
Honey, please.
Let's go.
Be careful.
Wait.
What's wrong?
I'm about to give birth.
Marriage registration.
Hurry up, please.
My wife is about to give birth.
Maybe you should
go to the hospital first
and come another day.
No way.
She was single
when she got pregnant.
But she wants to
be married to give birth.
(Marriage Certificate)
Mi Na.
Sit down.
- Okay.
- Take a seat.
Thank you, Mi Na.
I have no idea
how you persuaded your boss
to display my paintings.
You even sold two of them!
You're just lucky.
Your husband dotes on you.
And you have a benefactor.
Who is that?
Na.
Na is our benefactor.
How can you make
such a comeback without her?
Right.
Thank you, Na.
Two paintings.
A total of 31,000 yuan.
Minus 6,200 yuan in commission,
you have 24,800 yuan left.
Alright.
Count it.
No need.
Honey.
I believe this is just
the good beginning.
We will get on the right track.
Let's talk about our contract now.
- Alright.
Your place is really far away.
It's such a long drive
after we get off the highway.
I feel I'm falling apart.
It's so hot.
Here.
- Have some water.
- Thank you.
It is quite far.
Why did you come
all the way here?
Shanya.
Some misfortunes
have occurred in the past few months.
Life is unpredictable.
So,
this is what I think.
Alright, stop.
Let me say it.
Zhang Shanya.
What's wrong with you?
What about me?
Didn't you say you'd do anything
for the happiness
of our kids and Ke?
How can they be happy
with you like this?
You're living alone here
while they're in Shanghai.
They're worried about you
all day long.
Can they be happy?
Let me tell you.
You can't be selfish.
You know.
Hurry and pack up.
Come back to Shanghai with us.
Wu, I really can't go.
Come on.
How come you never listen to advice?
I've called you several times.
Right? You wouldn't listen.
Now that we're here,
you still won't listen.
Listen to me.
I'm not worried about your son.
I'm worried because
it concerns my daughter
and my granddaughter.
I know.
I totally get it.
But we have a rule here.
I can't leave home
for these three years once he's gone.
I have to stay by his side.
You can't have a life once he's gone?
Do you have to be so stubborn?
Do you, Zhang Shanya?
Yulan, sit down. Let's talk.
Zhang Shanya.
We've come here
to inform you of something.
Jincao and Moli have bought a new house.
I lent them the money
for the down payment.
Zhu Jincao and Gu Moli
have written me an IOU.
They will repay me.
That is to say,
you get to keep
that 57.2-square-meter small apartment.
You can't just leave it there, right?
You'll have to live there.
Also,
the two of us rented a bigger apartment
in your neighborhood.
It has two bedrooms.
Here's what I'm thinking.
We can live together
to look after each other.
You're a great cook.
You make great buns,
dumplings, and noodles.
And
Gu is also a great chef.
He makes Ningbo cuisine.
Have a taste of his dishes.
We can have variety.
I've made myself clear.
It's up to you whether you're coming.
Shanya.
Come back to Shanghai with us.
You have
your son,
your daughter-in-law,
your granddaughter,
and us there.
We are all family.
We all miss you.
Thank you.
We are a family.
So,
a family
should live together, right?
Isn't that right?
Listen to me.
Pack your things.
Let's go back to Shanghai.
Wu, let me think about it.
I may go back
on my own later, okay?
No way.
Let's do it today.
Listen to me.
Gu.
In-law.
Excuse me.
Let's take you back to Shanghai.
Listen to me.
♪The reason for growth♪
♪Cannot be easily guessed by anyone♪
Grandma.
Ke.
I've missed you!
Finally home.
Hello, Grandpa, Grandma.
Mom, the food will be ready soon.
Why did you
bring Grandma here?
Dad, let me.
So many dishes!
Dad.
Thank you.
Another dish?
Mom.
She's calling you.
This is my first time making a stew.
I'm not sure if it tastes good.
Please try it.
Okay, I'll try it.
♪It's just not♪
♪What I pictured♪
It's nice.
It's perfect.
The whole family is here.
For the reunion.
Cheers.
- Come on, cheers!
- Cheers!
Ke.
Come on, drink with Grandma. Alright.
Cheers.
Perhaps that's life.
We gain and lose something
at the same time.
But no matter what happens,
we ordinary people
must move forward
with firm steps every day.
Our good days
will come sooner or later.
♪The window is already filled with♪
(The End)
♪The reason for growth♪
♪Cannot be easily guessed by anyone♪
♪We always wish time could rewind♪
♪With no setbacks♪
♪What I got at first♪
♪Can always be held in my hand♪
♪Sweet moments♪
♪Can never pass♪
♪At the end of happiness♪
♪There's always someone
reaching out first♪
♪Always wanting
to achieve success first♪
♪Before salvaging the relationship♪
♪Behind the harsh criticism♪
♪Is another kind of gentleness♪
♪It's just not♪
♪What I pictured♪
♪No need to use letting go♪
♪As proof of this love♪
♪Give you enough freedom♪
♪To satisfy your needs♪
♪No need to use worries♪
♪To express inner thoughts♪
♪The tender courage♪
♪Soothes wounds laced with salt♪
♪No need to shout loudly♪
♪As an excuse for deep love♪
♪Genuine feelings♪
♪Come from each other's gentleness♪
♪No need to use tears♪
♪To end the guilt of this moment♪
♪The window is already filled with♪
♪My reluctance to see you leave♪