♪I want to just lean on
your shoulder like this♪
♪Through the curtains♪
♪Quietly admiring
the arc light in the filter♪
♪Just like our life♪
♪We need to know
how to adjust colors and lighting♪
♪I want to hold your hands♪
♪And stand by your side♪
♪See through the lies in the world♪
♪Tear down the walls
obstructing our thoughts♪
♪Just like our souls♪
♪We need to know how to stay refreshed♪
♪The streets are crowded♪
♪Time rushes by♪
♪Shadows dance
in the streetlamp's cold light♪
♪The story has just begun♪
♪Our simple days are ahead♪
=Simple Days=
=Episode 3=
I didn't want to call you.
But it's a serious matter.
I don't want you to blame me
for not telling you.
You did well.
Call Zhu Jincao.
Tell him I'm here.
Ask him and his wife to come back now.
Grandpa.
This is fun.
It took me a month
to build this ship for you.
Do you like it?
I love it.
Did you miss Grandpa?
Yeah.
I bet you forgot about me.
No.
And another kiss. Alright, I'll make you
a smaller one when I'm back.
Let's cut to the chase.
Your mom said you wanted to
sell this house and get a bigger one.
I'm telling you, no way.
It won't happen.
Dad, I've been married for seven years.
Mom has been living here.
Ke is growing up.
We need a bigger house.
Why are you so against it?
Let me explain to you.
First of all, I covered
the down payment on this house
as your wedding gift.
You have no right to sell it.
Second, as Shanghainese say,
"Make the most out of the least."
It's big enough with two bedrooms.
Two? Are you counting
the closed balcony as a bedroom?
Woman, be silent.
Do what you're capable of.
Don't dream of something
beyond your reach.
I won't stop you
if you're able to get a bigger house
on your own.
You just can't
sell this one, understand?
You know how pricy the houses are.
We could have gotten
a big house with Moli's parents' help,
but you were strongly against it
and got this place on your own.
Now that the price has skyrocketed,
we can't afford a big house anymore.
You're telling me to get my own house
to give me a hard time?
Son, talk things through with your dad.
I paid for your tuition and your house.
I think I've done my job as your father.
Naturally, I have the right
to make requests.
Jincao, we must be independent.
Give me my down payment back
or forget about it
and just live here.
Do you have money?
No?
Well, then give the deed to your mom.
Zhu Jincao, I'm talking to you.
Didn't you hear me?
Do I have to do it myself?
Dad, here is the deed.
(Premises Permit)
Rest assured. We don't want your house.
Jincao, the food is ready.
Where are you going?
Moli, your dad just came.
Let's eat together.
Get him back here.
He's not going to starve yet.
Let him reflect on himself.
I'll check on him.
Zhu Jincao had always been
a good kid before he got married.
How come he's talking back at me now?
Who taught him that?
I'm so useless.
I've been working for years
but still can't get you a bigger house.
You're the best, the smartest,
and the most amazing.
Me? Stop making fun of me.
You spoke up in the face of power
and fought back. Isn't that amazing?
My dad is right. I don't have money.
Jincao, look.
(Relinquishment of Property Ownership)
Where did you find it?
Hey, stop.
You've been through a lot these days.
I'm angry and worried.
We don't want your parents' house
or my parents' money anymore.
I value my dignity.
I will not suffer any humiliation
from your parents.
Neither do I want you
to feel inferior in front of my parents.
♪I want to just lean♪
♪On your shoulder like this♪
Thanks, honey.
Give me some time.
Two years. Three, tops.
I'll make enough money
to get us a big house.
Nobody gets to say anything then.
We'll get up whenever we want.
I'll sleep in any room.
We'll get any takeout we want.
We'll sing out loud as we please.
It's amazing to just think about it.
♪See through the lies in the world♪
What's so funny?
Nothing, I just realized that
you were even calmer than me.
Because you got bullied.
I have to support you.
It's the conservation of energy.
You're the best.
♪The streets are crowded.
Time rushes by♪
♪Shadows dance
in the streetlamp's cold light♪
♪The story has just begun♪
♪Our simple days are ahead♪
♪We'll travel far together♪
Dad.
Jincao.
Put it on.
Why?
What's going on?
We can buy soy milk.
Why do they have to grind it at home?
How are we going to sleep?
Just bear with it. He's leaving soon.
Stuffed buns. It's burning.
Let it cool down.
Moli.
I told Lingxiao and Qianniu
that I had come to Shanghai.
They'll come and visit me.
Make dinner for us.
Among the three of them,
only Jincao has a house in Shanghai.
That means he has settled here.
It's your chance to impress them
as their sister-in-law
and be a role model
for your future sisters-in-law.
I never knew I was so distinguished.
I can be a role model?
Dad, let me take care of it.
Let's get a table in a restaurant.
What for? It's a family gathering.
Let's just stay home like a family.
And it's more economic.
Sure, what do you need, Mom?
I'll get the ingredients online.
Jincao, it's pricy to order online.
I'll go to the market and make dinner.
Let Moli do it.
She's busy. She's going to work.
I'll do it.
She will do it.
Dad, I can't.
I don't even know when I'll be off work.
I don't have time
to cook for six people.
Your mom had a one-hour noon break
before she retired.
She'd ride a bike
to make a decent lunch for Jincao.
You want to run the household
but you're incapable.
I-Isn't that inappropriate?
You're Jincao's wife.
Wouldn't it be nice
if you could make dinner
for his relatives or friends at home?
If you can't do it,
aren't you a grown-up baby
as they say online?
Fine, it's just dinner. I'll do it.
Jincao, breakfast.
Do you like the soy milk made from
the soybeans Grandpa brought?
Is it nice?
Yeah.
You should nod.
Dig in.
Honey, don't be mad.
My dad rarely visits.
He only wants
to treat our relatives to dinner.
He's going to be happy after dinner
and get ready to go home.
He'd better not do it again.
Or I won't make it.
I don't even know how to cook.
I know. He's not going to ask for more.
I know it's tough for you.
Don't worry. I'll come home
right after work and help you.
I won't let you do it alone.
Don't try to fool me
with what you tell your team.
Ms. Kang, this is quite different
from the original piece.
I told you.
It was painted a year ago.
My mindset has changed,
so I may not be able to restore it.
You shouldn't have
damaged my painting to begin with.
Art is not from an assembly line.
It needs inspiration.
It's not like copy and paste.
But you can't change the basics
like the theme and style.
Or it's not the painting
our customer has bought.
Well, it is not.
I could have raised the price.
Don't you know how much I charge now?
He's buying my painting
at last year's price.
He's profiting.
But you promised you'd fix it.
How am I going
to give it to our customer?
That's your problem.
Alright, Ms. Kang.
You've done enough.
You even brought the painting yourself.
Who cares if Mr. Tang doesn't want it?
It's not your fault.
I'm so happy to see you.
My friends brought me
some shawls from Nepal.
There is a red one
that is perfect for you.
Let's go try it on.
I'll keep it down.
You haven't had any water
the entire morning.
I made you some tea with goji berries.
Leave it there. Can you just be quiet?
I told you not to disturb me today.
I'll take a walk
in the neighborhood. Take your time.
Rice with crab roe! Oh my!
What did I do right?
My bestie got me
the most luxurious takeout in Shanghai.
It must be pricy.
Not me, Ms. Wu got it for you.
She placed the order and called me
so that I join you for lunch.
She said you were mad and wouldn't
answer her calls. She was so upset.
She got me wrong.
I was occupied the whole morning.
Gu Moli, I've known you
for almost 20 years.
So don't give me that.
Why are you holding a grudge
against your mom?
So ungrateful.
You have no idea. It's not my fault.
I know everything.
She's your mom, after all.
Just do as she says even if she's wrong.
Listen.
You'll regret it if she falls ill
because of your caprice.
No one will look after you.
Are you going to
dine with me or lecture me?
Will you let me eat?
All you care about is food.
Well, it's really good.
Which restaurant is it?
Hello, Moli.
Mom, I'm going to make dinner today.
Can you pick up Ke with Dad
and take her to Mr. Wu
for the painting class?
Isn't the painting class tomorrow?
Yeah, he's going on a business trip.
So we rescheduled it.
Also, since Dad is here,
I'd like him to take a look
at Mr. Wu's calligraphy
and give some instructions.
Alright, don't worry. We'll go.
Thank you, Mom.
No problem.
Why are you doing everything?
Why can't she pick up the kid
because she's making dinner?
She hasn't run the household before.
Let her take it slow.
Besides, it shows how much
she values what you say.
I'll go alone if you're bored.
No, I'll pick up my granddaughter.
And I can check on the art teacher
just in case he's no good.
Alright.
When should we pick her up?
In an hour.
Alright, I'll hurry up.
A takeout?
Yeah, classic Shanghai cuisine.
A set for six people is 1888.
It's going to be amazing.
Can you handle semi-finished food?
Do not doubt me.
Here's the plan.
I told your parents
to take Ke to the art teacher.
Dinner will be ready once they're home.
Nobody will suspect anything.
Perfect, huh?
You're the smartest.
Alright, send me the address.
I'll pick up the takeout.
Moli, you're off work early.
I have work to do at home. Bye.
Mr. Zhu, the server is down.
Boss told us to stay on standby
and wait for IT to fix it.
Are you kidding me?
Mr. Zhu, we're so unlucky.
They sent a newbie here for maintenance.
He messed up and the server was down.
The administration staff
is getting dinner for everyone.
I think we'll have to stay overnight.
Honey, where are you?
I don't think I'll make it.
The server is down. They're fixing it.
I have to stay.
Zhu Jincao, are you doing it on purpose?
No, it's a top emergency.
I have to stay and fix it.
Are we having dinner or not?
Calm down. Listen.
Tell Mr. Wu
to extend the lesson for an hour.
We can double the fee. Stall my parents.
I'll get a delivery man
to pick up the meal.
No need. I'll go.
Lingxiao, where are you and Qianniu?
Something came up.
Don't get in yet.
Wait for my parents outside.
Stall them once you see them.
Yeah, stall them.
Don't let them go upstairs.
Let's go home.
Ke, have some water.
- Have some water.
- Here.
Grandpa, there is no water.
Give it to him.
There is no water?
It's my fault.
Uncle, what's the address again?
You forgot again?
Listen, it's Room 802,
Unit 1, Building No. 7.
I know it's 802.
But I can't find the building.
You can't? Listen.
It's right...
Alright, listen. We're at the entrance.
There's a pool here.
We'll wait for you there.
Is that Qianniu?
Who else can it be?
Let's wait at the entrance.
No way.
He and his mom visit all the time.
How can he forget which building it is?
What's so weird about it?
All the buildings look the same here.
I don't believe it.
I'm done with the call.
I heard you. Do you remember the lines?
Yeah. Can I improvise?
Don't. Stick to the script.
Okay, look after me.
Take over once I can't handle it.
Got it. Go.
You're spoiling her.
- Let her play on her own.
- Hello, Uncle, Auntie.
Ke.
Hello, Uncle.
How come you still
can't find the building?
It's not his fault.
The neighborhood looks so different now.
How can he remember everything by heart?
Alright, let's go.
Wait, I was running around
and my shoelaces got loose.
Just a second.
What a great environment.
This neighborhood is huge indeed.
Uncle.
I always feel refreshed when I'm here.
What's wrong with him?
Right?
Yeah, your residence sits here
among the trees and winding paths,
with birds chirping
and flowers blooming.
Seeing that, I feel like making a poem.
This is such a fine neighborhood.
Alright.
Whoever lives here is carefree.
A positive person doesn't age.
It's so nice here I'd like to shower.
Get into the pool.
- Come on, Auntie.
- Silly boy, how's that a poem?
You'd like to "shower"? Let's go home.
Let's go.
Wait, Uncle, Auntie.
I-It came out naturally.
Uncle, I have a question.
Yes?
Who picked this amazing neighborhood?
Who? Me.
Look at the priciest building.
These apartments may be the priciest
because they're the biggest.
But they don't have
the great sunshine we have.
Look, our building
is having great Feng Shui.
With great Feng Shui...
Enough with Feng Shui.
Don't get him started.
Wait, Auntie,
I've been studying Feng Shui.
Tell me more about it.
Hurry up. Qianniu and Lingxiao
are stalling my dad.
They may not be able to hold out.
Stop nagging me.
I can't take those boxes up.
What if your dad finds out?
You're so thoughtful. What do we do?
I'll throw away the boxes. Park the car.
Feng Shui is highly sophisticated.
It's not something
I can explain so easily.
If you're really interested,
we can talk all about it later.
Uncle, I have another question.
Ke is thirsty. There is no water.
There is no water.
Hello, Auntie.
Hello, Lingxiao.
Lingxiao.
Hello, Uncle.
Hello, Ke.
Everybody's here. Let's go.
Let's go.
Wait. Let me tie my shoelaces. Hold it.
Uncle.
I always feel refreshed when I'm here.
Your residence sits here
among the trees and winding paths...
With birds chirping
and flowers blooming.
Are you going to write a poem too?
Actually, I did make a poem.
What's with you?
It's like you share the scripts.
What's going on?
Ke needs water.
Okay.
Come on, you said my line.
You said my line!
I ran out of lines, okay?
I had to use yours.
So many boxes.
A box for a few slices of carrots.
This is not eco-friendly.
Stop complaining. Hurry up.
What's wrong?
Mom, are we having takeout today?
Heard it? Takeout.
What a disgrace.
Lingxiao and I brought this as a gift.
I hope you like it.
Thank you, Qianniu.
I bought it.
It's the same.
Grandma, when are we having dinner?
Should I make some noodles?
It will only take ten minutes.
Sit there.
Dinner can wait.
Dad, we have to eat.
The food is ready.
They just need a bit of cooking.
Besides, Lingxiao and Qianniu
must be hungry.
Dinner can wait.
We have to make things clear first.
They're grown men.
They can starve for a while.
Why don't you get something?
Don't let Ke starve.
Okay.
Let's go. Granny is going to
get you something to eat.
According to the plan...
Go to the sofa.
We should be gathering as a family,
raising our glasses in joy.
But Zhu Jincao's wife
is immature, irresponsible,
sneaky, and lazy.
That's why we're sitting here, starving.
Dad, it's my fault.
Something happened at work.
Protecting your wife
won't bring harmony.
We see what's going on in this family.
I suggest we put everything in order.
I worked on it the whole day
and wrote Zhu's family teachings
(Zhu's family teachings)
for your reference.
You're not our direct family.
But it won't hurt to learn it.
So outdated.
Stop!
Inspired by the spirit of our ancestors,
the 63rd generation of the Zhu family
has formulated these family rules.
All descendants of the Zhu family
should reflect on themselves daily
and follow the teachings.
First, the nation thrives
when it's on the right track.
The family thrives
when its members are regulated.
All family members should be diligent
and follow four precepts.
Work hard, study hard, and think hard.
Abstain from oversleeping,
laziness, luxury, and pride.
People in Zhu's family
should be diligent and thrifty.
Be grateful for the food we have
because it's hard-earned.
Be grateful for the clothes we have
A member will be expelled
if they lead an extravagant life.
Second, all daughters-in-law
who marry into my family
must treat everyone with sincerity
and know their places.
Do not upset the elders.
Do not doubt
the family members and grow distant.
Do not do things
that hurt the family bond.
Be filial and show respect.
Work hard and do what's right.
(Third, do not speak
during meals or before bed.)
(Dress properly at home.)
(Take the initiative
to greet the elders.)
Twenty-fourth,
whoever violates the teachings
shall reflect on themselves
and accept any punishment.
Uncle, it's a great pleasure
to hear the teachings. I'm inspired.
I have an appointment. I have to go.
I'll visit you again.
Your teachings value
way more than a dinner.
I'll starve tonight. Bye, Uncle.
Go ahead. I won't walk you out.
Come and visit us.
See you, sis.
Take care.
See you.
Dad, do you have to do it?
Make Lingxiao and Qianniu stay
and watch us get humiliated?
You feel humiliated?
Was I trying to humiliate you?
You did it to yourself.
I didn't ask too much.
I just wanted a dinner.
And how did it go? You ruined it.
You can't even prepare a meal.
Don't you need some family teachings?
You're making a fuss.
What?
Now I get it.
It's not about the dinner.
You're just looking
to announce the teachings.
Dad, let me remind you of the teachings.
Wake up early to greet you.
Wash up after you.
Be well-dressed outside the bedroom.
Drink water ten times,
one-fourth of a cup every time.
Do not play on the phones before bed.
And our farts have to be silent.
Jincao, you made a sound.
It's against the rules.
You're regulating us in all aspects.
Are you treating us like babies
or trying to set up some rules?
Nobody can make it without rules.
I will help you
learn the teachings one by one by heart
instead of memorizing them.
You must learn to be our family member.
Jincao, we'll clean up the place,
starting next week.
I'll teach you how to
live decently and casually
in a small apartment.
You're going to stay here?
Now you know why I did that.
I bought you the house
and I'll teach you how to live here.
It's already...
According to the family teachings,
take Ke to wash up.
She's sound asleep.
Why should I wake her up?
Honey, I'm sorry. It's been hard on you.
Family teaching No. 3.
Do not speak during meals or before bed.
Good night.
Why are you up so early?
Where are you going?
Zhu's family teaching No. 8.
Do not make loud noises
before the elders get up.
Our boss texted me to go to Jingdezhen
on a business trip.
Really?
You think?
I left the egg pudding in the fridge.
Take it out once Ke wakes up
for breakfast. It should be just right.
I know you're upset.
Give me some time. I'll handle it.
Our elders are home.
Watch your behavior.
Let me take you to the station.
No need. It's in the opposite direction
from your office.
You'd be late for work.
Just stay home
and study the family teachings.
Your dad may want
a 5000-word essay on it.
See you.
(Zhu's family teaching)
Liu, get ready.
I'll crash at your place tonight.
Don't post anything about me
on WeChat Moments these days.
Nothing.
Again? You fought with Zhu Jincao?
It wasn't him. His dad was unbelievable.
Talk later.
I don't want to ruin my mood.
I have something important to do.
I must not fail.
Good luck. Let's have a feast tonight.
Ke.
Morning, Grandpa.
Morning, enjoy your breakfast.
She has to go on a business trip
right after
I announce the family teachings.
Is she shunning me?
Why would she do that?
That's our line of work.
It's the same for me.
Even if you have work,
you should take some days off
to serve your father-in-law
who rarely visits you.
What are you talking about?
We can get fired at any time.
Will you take responsibility for that?
Ke, are you done?
Yeah.
Let's go to kindergarten. Let's go.
Bye, Grandpa.
Bye.
Bye, Dad.
Jincao, come out.
I couldn't say it
in front of your daughter.
I don't mean to turn you against Moli.
All parents
want the best for their children.
But she's not taking you seriously.
Do you find my teachings
outdated and ridiculous?
Think about it.
Gu Moli is full of herself.
And you keep compromising.
How are you going to
make it work in the long run?
I don't think I need to prove anything.
Are you feeling insecure
and trying to prove something?
Zhu Jincao, mind your attitude.
Read the teachings three times.
You can't avoid it.
♪The reason for growth♪
♪Cannot be easily guessed by anyone♪
♪We always wish time could rewind♪
♪With no setbacks♪
♪What I got at first♪
♪Can always be held in my hand♪
♪Sweet moments♪
♪Can never pass♪
♪At the end of happiness♪
♪There's always someone
reaching out first♪
♪Always wanting
to achieve success first♪
♪Before salvaging the relationship♪
♪Behind the harsh criticism♪
♪Is another kind of gentleness♪
♪It's just not♪
♪What I pictured♪
♪No need to use letting go♪
♪As proof of this love♪
♪Give you enough freedom♪
♪To satisfy your needs♪
♪No need to use worries♪
♪To express inner thoughts♪
♪The tender courage♪
♪Soothes wounds laced with salt♪
♪No need to shout loudly♪
♪As an excuse for deep love♪
♪Genuine feelings♪
♪Come from each other's gentleness♪
♪No need to use tears♪
♪To end the guilt of this moment♪
♪The window is already filled with♪
♪My reluctance to see you leave♪