♪I'd rather soar like a mayfly
in another dimension♪
♪Restart my life
and gaze at the rainbow together♪
♪I do not regret my promise to you♪
=My Deepest Dream=
(Changsha Stinky Tofu)
(We dream every day.)
(Sometimes it's a sweet dream,)
(a nightmare)
(or a lingering dream.)
(However, has it ever occurred to you)
(that life is a dream itself?)
(And we wake up)
(out of blue.)
He's dealing with something serious.
I know he stopped me
for my sake.
On top of that,
we haven't made up yet.
I have no reason to be sad.
Cheer up.
Qizhu.
Cheer up, Qizhu.
You're the best.
Come on.
Get it together.
You can do it.
It's beautiful.
Indeed,
it's a beautiful encounter.
Even though I exist in this world,
however, everything that happens here
has no connection with me.
So, you're not just a passerby.
You're my only connection to this world.
If I'm your only connection
to this world,
I won't let go of you anymore.
From now on, our time is
at the same pace.
I've lost so much.
I don't want you
to be in danger as well.
So,
live your life
and be a carefree writer.
(It turns out that
the most torturing pain)
(is when he's a dark cloud)
(and you're the bright moon.)
(The dark cloud meets the bright moon.)
(Yet the moon fails to register
the departure of the cloud.)
=Episode 7=
I remember when I first met him,
there was a rainbow
over the horizon of the sea too.
It seems like
you still can't get it over with.
Pull yourself together.
He's gone for his sister.
It didn't mean
that he doesn't care about you.
Probably he'll be back soon
after everything is settled.
It's been half of a year.
Hasn't he got it settled?
Who knows how long will it take?
Besides, he told me
that we won't meet again
in the future.
There, there.
Don't cry.
I'm not crying.
To be frank, I still don't get the point
of the cruise,
our encounter,
my lost memory,
Zhu's case,
and Wu Miao's disappearance.
All these that have happened
in our lives,
what's the meaning behind all these?
Since the universe
has both of you meet again and again,
it means
that there's a strong and
invisible attraction between you.
Have you heard of quantum entanglement?
Even if the pair of entangled electrons
are transferred to the Sun
and Pluto separately,
they are still correlated.
If one of the electrons changes state,
the other will change too.
I think this explains your relationship
with him.
Hey.
Can you make it understandable?
I don't understand.
What I'm trying to say
is that you'll meet him again for sure.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Besides,
I think you can record this feeling
in your new novel
and publish it in instalments.
You can wait for him
while writing the story.
Perhaps he'll be back
when you finish writing.
Don't you think
it's romantic?
Right?
It seems
your idea makes some sense.
Right.
Don't be sad.
Come on, show me a smile.
Come on.
You're ugly.
You look silly.
You're sillier.
Don't pull my hair.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I've decided to start a new novel
from today on.
Master, you're finally back.
We miss you so much.
I'm ready
and wait with bated breath.
♪The ocean ahead and thorny bush below♪
♪Is this an adventure or a gamble?♪
Qizhu has finally appeared
after repeated calls.
A sweet yet heart-wrenching romance
between the proud high-maintenance lady
and two-faced intelligent macho
with a happy ending.
(Send)
♪I run desperately
chasing after the future you♪
She's not high-maintenance.
It's a pure lovey-dovey story
without any emotional setting.
♪Proust once said♪
♪The shelter of life♪
♪Is a flower you meet by chance♪
♪Blooming brightly♪
Shall I send him a message?
What's up?
Wonder if he has done work.
♪Even if the meaning of my existence
is abandoned♪
♪And everyone's mouth is blocked♪
♪As wind blows♪
♪Dark clouds drift by♪
♪They proved our love♪
Don't interrupt my train of thought.
Well.
Are you already stop seeing him?
Have of heard of the dry joke
about Mr. Ten Yuan?
What's that?
Forget it then.
It's a torturing experience
listening to his dry jokes.
He's not my type.
Take him if you want.
Yes!
Hi.
It's a peer gathering,
but why is it only you here?
Actually,
I want to have a meal with you.
I don't think it's appropriate.
I have plans.
Please don't...
Don't beat around the bush.
We're friends, right?
Come on, have a seat.
Right.
Sit.
What would you like to eat?
Order anything you want.
I'm fine with anything.
You order the food.
I'm sorry to keep you waiting
on our first meeting.
I was tied up with work just now.
It's fine.
Ms. Chui told me that you're a police.
Are you an elementary school teacher?
Staid Shen.
You came here for a blind date?
I don't eat much for dinner.
You can order anything you want.
Are you on a diet?
Do I look like I need that?
What has happened?
What are you laughing at?
Nothing.
I realise that you don't talk much.
This is good.
I don't like talkative guys.
Yes.
I don't talk much.
How about I tell you a dry joke?
One day, Mr. Ten Yuan
is kidnapped by someone.
So, the kidnapper...
I'm sorry, Mr. Shen.
I'd like to apologise to you.
Why?
To be honest, I have a boyfriend.
I'm sorry.
My mother looks down on my boyfriend
and disapprove of him.
So, she insisted to arrange
a blind date for me.
Can please tell the middleman
that
I'm not to your liking
and we're not a good match.
Hence, I can explain it to my mother.
Sure.
I'm really sorry
to put you through grief for nothing.
It's fine.
Xiaoyu.
All dishes are served.
Eat them while it's hot.
Sure.
My phone is out of juice.
Can you please go to the bar counter
to get me a power bank?
Thank you.
Sure.
I'll be right back.
Thank you.
Mr. Shen.
Are you angry with me?
No.
Didn't you say
that you have a boyfriend?
So, it's not appropriate
if I talk to you more.
Let's just get on with our meals.
Don't mind about me.
Alright.
Let's just get on with our meals?
Wonder what's in his mind.
Why can't I drink?
What are you looking at?
Don't be rude to women.
Shut your trap.
Do you want to challenge me?
Don't you?
It hurts.
You disturbed public order,
launched an assault
against women.
You attempted to do this.
Come with me.
Who's you?
Shen Shiyan, third-level superintendent
of the Municipal Criminal Police Force.
Do you want to challenge him?
It's you?
Let's go.
Xiaoyu.
Where are you going?
♪Looking at your moving silhouette♪
♪I follow you closely♪
♪I chase after♪
♪Each and every step of yours♪
♪No matter where the wind comes from♪
♪It won't change♪
Why haven't you left?
♪No matter where you go♪
I'd let down
your heroic act
if I left secretly.
Let's go.
Let's eat hotspot. It's on me.
♪Illuminating my direction♪
Come on.
♪My hometown
is where my heart rests♪
Do you eat spicy food?
Yes.
I see.
Do you prefer
sesame paste or sesame oil?
Sesame oil.
Cocacola or Pepsi?
Cocacola.
Beef or mutton?
What do you like to eat?
That'll be a lot.
I thought you were eloquent
as you were good at arguing.
But, how could you say a woman was fat
when you first met her?
So, I'm single because of this?
Yes.
I'm really impressed.
Thanks a bunch.
(Qizhu Spicy and Fragrant)
Tan Jiao told me
that you have many suitors.
Was the man
one of your suitors too?
No.
He's my friend.
You're cute.
It's understandable
that you have suitors.
Erm...
Did you accept him?
No, certainly not.
Didn't you see he's such a coward?
It's out of the question.
By the way,
except for this man,
do you have other suitors?
I think
there are two or three of them.
They're not important.
Two or three?
You don't even approve of
any of them.
What kind of guy do you like then?
I like a guy who's composed,
rational,
mature
but slightly childish.
Childish...
It'd be better
if he's in uniform.
Are you interrogating me?
I'm sorry.
It's my work habit.
I'm so sorry.
What do you mean by
uniform?
Well...
Erm...
Eat up.
Hurry up.
Eat the food.
Eat up.
Master Qizhu.
I really like the story
that happened on the cruise.
A pure sweet romance is the best.
It's like the story appears
in real life.
You got this, Master.
Silly girl.
Stop imagining your life
is a romance drama.
Thank you, dear.
You'll discover
more loving moments in life
if you observe well.
The story is well-written.
I believe in love again.
This couple is meant to be together.
Looking forward to it.
Do you really think it's a sweet story?
Although the story is intriguing,
I can sense something lovelorn about it.
How dare you?
Curse you, lovelorn whelp.
Your words are hopeless.
What the heck is this?
Heads-up!
I'll update the story tonight.
You'll be overwhelmed
with sweetness tonight.
Stop pretending,
or you'll get hurt more seriously.
Good luck.
Sod you.
Who tells you I'm lovelorn?
You must be a hater.
I'm happy.
My life is sweet and nice.
I'm faring very well. I...
Wu Yu.
Why are you...
(Thursday, 5th August)
The fifth.
What's today's date?
It's 5th August, madam.
What year?
Now is
the 5th of August, 2021.
Madam.
How may I help you?
No, thank you.
You're welcome.
It's 2021.
I'm back again.
Sorry.
- I'm sorry
- I...
Are you alright?
Miss, are you alright?
I'm fine.
Sorry.
Sure, please be careful.
Wu Yu.
♪May time flies♪
♪May you appear before me♪
♪May you hold my hands♪
Tan Jian, wake up.
If this is a dream,
it means we've just
known each other for less than a day.
Wait.
♪May you live a life full of love♪
Do you know Wu Yu?
I've applied for membership
from Wu Yu.
There are around 600 yuan left
on the card.
Not only that,
but we've also eaten noodles together.
♪To watch my previous love life♪
That's great.
Everything is real.
It's not a dream.
But...
What's going on now?
If I'm not wrong,
we've triggered
some kind of function in time and space.
It means
we're back.
Wu Miao.
Don't worry.
She'll be fine.
Yu.
Yu, are you out of your mind?
Let go of me.
What has happened to you, Yu?
Your brother
hasn't seen you for a long time.
So, he's a bit excited.
He hasn't seen me for a long time?
Didn't we just meet?
Why are you crying?
Don't scare me.
What's wrong?
Wu Miao, give me your handphone.
Why do you need that?
On the 5th of November, 2021,
you must stay at home.
Mark this date.
Isn't that my birthday?
I'll hang out with my friends for sure.
No, you can't. You must listen to me.
Yu.
What's wrong with you today?
You act weird.
Besides, it's only August now.
Yet, you're interrupting my arrangement
in November.
You're manipulative.
Dear.
This is very important.
Why?
You can't tell, right?
Let me tell you this.
I won't concur with
this unexplained and ridiculous request.
Wu Miao.
You must listen to your brother.
Who are you?
I'm Tan Jiao.
Your brother's friend.
The novel on the table
is written by me.
You're Master Qizhu?
Are you his friend?
This is unbelievable.
Wu Yu, can I ask for her signature?
Master Qizhu.
Could you please sign it for me?
I really like your novel.
Sure.
But you have to promise me
that you must keep
what he told you in mind.
You mustn't go out
on the 5th of November.
It's very crucial to you.
Fine.
If Master Qizhu said so,
I'll act accordingly.
I agree with anything she says.
Unlike someone
who despised the book I read
ten minutes ago.
This book
is well-written.
Don't worry.
Qu Miao has kept that in mind
and she has promised me that.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Even though
she promised you,
she won't take it seriously.
Please help me
to take care of her.
Don't worry.
I'm good at interacting with my readers.
By the way,
didn't you
go to another city?
I planned to leave for it,
but something happened.
What's it?
Miss Zhu.
I have something to inform you of.
I was straightening things up
a few days ago.
I discovered this.
Regarding the cruise,
I couldn't recall anything of it.
But, Miss Tan is in this photo.
I think I should show it to you
perhaps it might be helpful to you.
What's wrong with the photo?
In this photo,
except for you, Yan Yuan,
and Zhu Jirui,
everyone in the photo is dead.
Are all of them dead?
How could it be possible?
Miao,
Professor Chen and his family,
and a little boy named Zhu Yutong
died in accidents within a year
after disembarking.
Since we've come back to the cruise,
we have the chance to change everything.
Whether it works or not,
we must give it a shot.
Oh, right.
I ran into Yan Yuan on my way here.
I remember that Zhu Jirui said
Yan Yuan and her met
the next day the cruise departed.
It's tomorrow.
Do you mean
we're going to stop them from meeting?
Yan Yuan wouldn't get access
to the Zhu's family
and the tragedy can be avoided
only if they didn't meet.
That's right.
If that's the case,
we'll meet up here first thing
in the morning.
We must figure out a plan
to stop them from the meeting.
What's wrong?
Do you
have anything to tell me?
Not for now.
Anything's wrong?
No.
Take an early rest then.
We'll meet here tomorrow.
Okay.
Good night.
♪A long face appears in the mirror♪
♪Who's she thinking?♪
Not for now?
That's all?
♪The mystery of time travel♪
♪Is an imaginary reflection♪
♪A promise under the shinning lights♪
♪A decision has finally turned up♪
♪Because I care about you♪
How could you not
mention that at all?
That was my first kiss.
♪I'll venture for my own destiny♪
♪Be a superstar♪
♪Be a superhero♪
♪Eating vitamins every day♪
♪Preparing a Panini for you every day♪
Thank you.
Taste good.
- Right?
- Taste nice.
Professor.
♪Honestly, it smells good♪
Wu Yu?
Wu Yu.
Why are you here?
♪It's a wonderful feeling♪
Wu Yu, I didn't expect to see you here.
Wu Yu.
What brings you here?
I didn't expect
that we can even meet on the cruise.
Oh.
Do you come with Miao?
Father.
You should've listened to me
to invite Wu Yu.
But, you argued that you're busy.
Isn't this unexpected encounter
better than inviting him?
No one can escape
if fate wills.
How's it?
Do you have plans after this?
Do you want to join us?
That's right, come and join us.
Hey.
Yu has already worked for you
in the university,
can't you give him a break?
Am I right, Yu?
Mrs. Chen.
You're happy to have him with you,
but Yu might feel stressed though.
Stress?
You can ask him.
Not at all.
Professor has been
taking great care of me.
Please don't say that.
Your parents are my peers
and your father is my best buddy.
I deem you and Miao
as my children
just like Ying.
That's right.
I should take care of you.
Why are you...
What's wrong with you, Wu Yu?
There's a special shop over there.
I'll take her there.
Let's go.
Well...
Bye-bye.
Sit down.
What has happened?
Is it anything serious?
Professor.
Due to some unknown reasons,
I've experienced the future.
Future?
I can't explain this.
But, if I tell you,
it might not happen though,
that your family will encounter
an accident
half a year later,
would you think I'm being ridiculous?
♪May time flies♪
♪May you appear before me♪
♪May you hold my hands♪
♪As you take the oath♪
♪May you live a thousand years♪
♪May you live a life full of love♪
♪May your heart skip a beat♪
♪Whenever you meet me♪
♪May you have a space♪
♪To watch my previous love life♪
♪May you have clairvoyance♪
♪To see when we will meet♪
♪The fish and the bird♪
♪Who is meeting whom♪
♪How deep does our love go
and whose life will be spent?♪
♪The cloud and the moon♪
♪Who runs into whom?♪
♪Flowers bloom and wilt
as time passes by♪
♪May you live a thousand years♪
♪May you live a life full of love♪
♪May your heart skip a beat♪
♪Whenever you meet me♪
♪May you travel far and wide♪
♪To witness all flavors of love♪
♪May you travel with me♪
♪For the blissful moments to come♪
♪The cloud and the moon♪
♪Who is meeting whom♪
♪How deep does our love go
and whose life will be spent?♪
♪The fish and the bird♪
♪Who runs into whom?♪
♪Flowers bloom and wilt
as time passes by♪
♪The cloud and the moon♪
♪Whose and whose oath is it?♪
♪How deep does our love go
and whose attachment is this?♪
♪The fish and the bird♪
♪Whose and whose trial of love is this?♪
♪Flowers bloom and wilt
as we shine in time♪