Episode 16
Princess, do you have a dream?
My dream is to have my first love, Chen Zhengguo.
The End
We're in a flash marriage.
What flash? It's been seven years.
But I think the photos are not as good as the photos in the Treasure magazine.
They're pretty good.
Really?
But I was the one who proposed back then.
I feel like I was the one who proposed.
Are you embarrassed?
Then wait for me.
Li Xun, do you remember?
We came here that year.
During the New Year, this office building was lit up.
I remember.
I remember I told you
that there will be a familiar name on the building.
Look.
I passed through the world
and passed through the night
You think I don't understand English?
The people in the mountains are gone
You're over there in the fireworks
It's the intuition of a dream
Breaking through the border
A night of rain
A full moon
Then you won the world for me
The car in the city never stops
I lean on your shoulder
We will not be separated
You're writing a white-page novel.
Li Xun, I'm serious.
No matter what you want to do in the future,
whatever your goals are,
you can count me in.
Today I want to tell you
that my goal is
to spend the rest of my life with you.
Because I believe I want to
I can meet you today.
I will take his course
The burning fireworks
are always your light.
Because I believe I want to
I love you
I will take his course
I'm by your side
I spend a long time with you
Because I believe I want to
I will take his course
The burning fireworks
are always your light.
Cheers.
I say, guys,
now the two leaders
have fulfilled their wishes.
And now our company is also
on the right track.
I think
at this point,
if you have any wishes
that haven't been fulfilled,
maybe they will be fulfilled.
Can you call it learning?
You choose to eat, right?
I'm just kidding.
I hope that from next year
I can recruit one hundred people for the company.
Then I hope that
our five families can be in the top three in the year.
OK.
This is good.
This is all for you to find.
You come.
Dongdong, you say one.
Say one for you.
I hope this year
can be a top-class driver.
What is it?
No one can do it.
I'll discuss it with you.
OK.
Five-star driver, I'll help you.
Then I'll say it.
I hope I can get the offer.
Offer.
Is it?
Right.
Offer.
I mean,
I can get this.
I also want to thank your wife.
If it weren't for you,
I wouldn't have met Mr. Tian.
I wouldn't have written a recommendation letter.
So thank you.
You don't have to thank me.
I did it myself.
I'm done.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
What are you looking at?
What are you doing?
Nothing.
I'm looking at you.
Are you in love?
What are you doing?
I'm the worst.
Are you in love?
No.
Big news.
It's the top three of the hot treasure.
The boss of LP announced the offer.
Of course.
What did you say?
Say the words.
No.
Until today,
I was called to open up a new site.
But I didn't continue.
I've been afraid to say that
I'll definitely fail to do it for the money I have.
Do you really think you'll make it?
Big surprise.
I just should have told you cinnamon.
I've been told that
someone is scolding Zhu Yu
in the comments.
What a coincidence.
Find a way to stop him.
I'm watching.
I'll try my best.
It's the holiday season now.
The speed of rising must be very fast.
Try your best.
It's a big deal.
Come on.
Continue to eat.
Drink one.
Come on.
What are you doing?
This is what you said.
Don't regret it.
What's wrong?
The red and blue band,
all engaged.
It's a holiday.
Let me tell you.
I want to make a fortune.
Look, they all have it.
Look.
I want to make a fortune.
I want to be a big star.
Come on.
Just because of your popularity,
our company will be in a big trouble.
Yeah.
You said it.
I want to make a fortune.
Look at them.
No way.
The.
The lid.
Why are you selling these?
They'reن
Want to die?
Do you know how dangerous these refertiles are?
These BCG
goes throughı the septic balloons
and bevorf constant pressure.
The highest pressure can be up to
10-15kg.
Why are you doing these little water flowers?
Little water flowers?
The water in front of the police station is very high.
You can try to open it.
Why do I have to open it?
I have to work later.
You opened a computer in the company today.
You opened it quite carefully.
Here.
Here's the water.
Hey.
Come on.
To celebrate your admission.
And then hold the goal of winning back L.P.
You can be with Li Xun as a normal colleague.
And live in peace.
Cheers.
But in fact,
we are not ordinary colleagues.
What?
We are ordinary, upper and lower-level relationships.
Who is upper and who is lower?
I'm lower than him.
I'm the team leader now.
Then it's not ordinary.
Team leader Zhu.
How do you feel about commanding Li Xun?
How can I command him?
But I think he deserves it.
This is his reality.
I like the way he looks at me
and makes me feel uncomfortable.
Interesting.
Try it.
Come here.
I'm heavy.
Do I look like it?
Do you like the air up there?
Not bad.
Not bad?
Is it good?
Yes.
Really?
Li Xun.
I'm sorry.
I...
visits you.
Any dream?
No.
How come?
I haven'tiny thought carefully.
No matter what the price is,
I won't regret it.
Then you've completely
completed
your self-righteous idea.
So I said to continue like this.
Which one do you want to eat?
You cook it for me first.
Okay.
Thank you.
Can't someone grill the ear?
The pot.
Why is the pot so big?
You don't want to eat?
Zh Sí,
Let me twist it for you.
I don't understand you.
It's hot.
Get some water in.
Pour some water in.
He is almost freaking out.
I'm so tired.
The End
Little Spider, we can be together in a fair way.
Happy New Year.
Princess, do you need a heart?
Li Shen, choose me. I won't betray you.
Don't be angry.
You worry, I'll take care of everything.
Understand?
Yes.
Happy New Year.
Let's continue.