YoYo English Channel YouTube
I don't believe that anyone can save anyone
Until you break into my world
Even if this world shatters into darkness
We will fight in the darkness
Even if the light is very bright
I will still watch over that vast vast land
I see the direction of the boundless atmosphere
Every day, the lens is a little bit yellow
Even if I am light
How can I be alone in the vast night?
I burn up the night just for you to remember
How everything was in the beginning
If I am light
The wind and the color of the night are like wild grass
I am still by your side
Everything is the original look
The King of Blaze
Episode 1
Miss Yu
Okay, just a moment
Thank you
Welcome to come again
You are handsome
That's a good thing.
Coming.
Lin Xun, I'm Chen Min Min from the outside.
Let's go eat together later?
No.
Are you going back to the dorm?
If you need anything, just tell me.
I don't need anything.
You're so good at acting.
Shin Si Ke
Do you have fun?
I'm not following you.
I'm asked to come here to talk to you.
Really?
Here's the thing.
The department of early childhood is investigating
the early childhood rate of the early childhood.
We're new students.
We just started school.
So the department is keeping a close eye on us.
You're going to primary school or kindergarten?
Do you think early childhood is useful?
It's not about whether it's useful or not.
The school has its rules.
We should...
Give it to me.
An Kong.
What?
What's wrong?
An Kong.
A game?
You have to move up and down.
You have to avoid the ball that's floating up.
You have to go through the river.
You have three chances.
If you don't die, I'll go to the early childhood.
You have a point.
You call this a ball that's floating up?
It's obviously thrown down.
How many balls are there in total?
Three chances, two balls.
I already know the first ball's landing.
The second ball is the landing of the next ball.
The third ball passes the first ball.
It's that simple?
Your ball is too fast.
My hands are the fastest speed keyboard.
You admit defeat?
Isn't there another chance?
Go.
Game over.
What's going on?
Editor?
This is the first chance.
You have to go through the river.
If you get hit by a ball, you'll die.
If you go through the river, you'll die.
Did you get it wrong?
No.
Then I'll die no matter how I play?
Yes.
Then this game is a draw?
Then why did you let me play?
Because you don't look good.
What?
Because I don't look good.
Why?
You are...
You are too fake.
You lost.
Don't come to me for the morning self-study.
And...
This is my place.
You are not allowed to enter the place without my permission.
Why can't you go through the river?
I did.
What's the use of it?
He designed that program.
I can't go through it.
You are playing a fool.
Actually,
the game is quite simple.
Although I don't understand the meaning of the letter,
the code is simple.
Although I don't know how the rich
become rich,
I think the logic is simple.
Fang Shumiao.
Who did I get this humiliation for?
You will get four points tomorrow.
Four points minus four points.
Four points is more than enough.
What's the use of reading it now?
You are familiar with it.
He said I was fake.
I think he just doesn't like it.
He is so bad at making up stories.
What's wrong?
Look at this.
Isn't this Guo He Si?
He said he was a great man.
You are using the same program.
Stop reading.
Don't stay up late. Go to sleep.
Li Xun is so excited about you.
Very excited.
You...
Hurry up.
birthday
Zhou Yu.
Good morning.
You don't have a made-up JD anymore, right?
Yes.
Well,
it's google connection.
Where are you from?
I'm from Xiao Xin Housing.
I finally got it out of the water room.
Wait for me.
Let's play basketball in the afternoon.
How about yesterday?
It's a bit empty.
Why are you sitting so close?
The computer is hot and people are easily sleepy.
I won't fall asleep if I sit in front of you.
It seems that you have really gotten into a fight with the leader.
Is it worth it?
I only deducted four points this morning.
It must be worth it.
This professor's surname is Lin.
I heard from my sister that they call him Old Lin in private.
He has a long history.
He is considered the oldest in the circle.
Ten horse-drawn, nine rabbit, and a hair-cutting book.
It's really not exaggerating.
This is not here.
The first class of the professional class doesn't understand.
It's not as crazy as this.
This computer is broken.
It's broken.
Yes.
It's so hot.
No, no, no.
You are a pervert.
Classmates, who of you has already known C languages before?
Or have you tried to write some small programs in C languages?
Everyone knows that now it's a information society.
The computer is developing very fast.
The programming language is also developing very fast.
Compared with C languages and the new programming languages,
it's like I'm standing in front of you now.
What do you mean?
Just like an old aunt.
There is an old saying that goes,
Jiang is still old.
Old has the benefits of old.
Old, rich, and strict.
No matter what you want to study in the future,
or continue to study programming, database, and operating system,
the C language skills you learned today
will become the basis for all your programming in the future.
The skills are beyond the skills.
Don't do what good students usually like to do.
The four books.
Let's talk about C languages.
First, we need to understand what C is.
Then everyone, tell us what C is.
Raise your hand.
I learned it for so long last night.
You're so stubborn.
Let me see.
What are you talking about?
Looking at the books?
The notes?
You remember them very well.
This student, can you answer my question?
C language is a face-to-face programming language.
It's widely used in the base level development.
C language can be compiled in a simplified way.
It handles low-level storage.
C language only produces a small number of machine languages.
And it doesn't need any operating environment support.
It can run high-level programming language.
Although C language has many low-level functions,
it still maintains the feature of this platform.
It can also include similar input processors
and super computers.
It can be compiled in many operating platforms.
Well said.
Let's give her a round of applause.
Please.
I have nothing to do with death.
Sikersuper.
What's your name, student?
Zhu Yun.
Good name.
Sounds good.
You are the class representative.
Teacher, I can't.
You can.
Why not?
It seems that you are not only shy but also humble.
It's settled.
Don't be modest.
Let's continue.
Let's go.
Teacher,
you should change the class representative.
Why?
Are you afraid of wasting time?
No.
I just think it's troublesome.
Troublesome?
What's the difference?
Don't make a decision yet.
Think about it.
We have classes tomorrow.
Give me an answer when the time comes.
I have to go to the market.
The braised pork will be gone soon.
Don't be so angry.
We will talk tomorrow.
It's good to be the class representative.
You are so good at it.
Old Lin is the senior in the circle.
He will teach us several classes in the future.
I will talk to him.
I will do my best.
Hurry up.
I am waiting for you.
I have been the class representative since I was a kid.
I have been in the language, math, English, biology, chemistry and geography.
I have been in all of them.
If I am serious, my classmates will be annoyed with me.
If I am not serious, my teacher will scold me.
I am tired and I can't speak well.
I finally go to the university.
I don't want to be the class representative again.
Are you afraid that the class representative will make troubles for you?
One of the reasons is that you are the best example.
Some people think that the college entrance examination is the end.
This is absolutely wrong.
The college is the place to teach you to be safe.
So, the college entrance examination is the end.
You can't even be the top student.
You can't be so careful after you enter the college.
It's time for you to choose the class representative.
Did you participate?
No.
What about the class representative?
The class representative has the most contact with the teacher.
It's also important.
There was one.
Which class?
C language.
That's great.
Do your best.
Let the teacher see your ability.
I didn't agree.
Why?
You don't like this class?
Or you don't like to recognize the teacher?
You can't be so willful.
Whether it's study or work,
it's a very hard and troublesome thing.
Mom, I really don't want to be the class representative.
No.
Listen to me.
I worked in the school system for a lifetime.
I can tell you responsibly.
You are the class representative.
It's only good for you.
But...
Don't say but.
When is the next C language?
Tomorrow.
Okay.
Tell the teacher tomorrow that you are willing to be the class representative.
Do you hear me?
Mom.
Do as I say.
I have a meeting soon.
I'll talk to you.
Be good.
Do you still have to wash it?
Okay.
Your idea is very good.
If you don't knock a few keys,
it can't be an excellent program.
What?
Ma, you can try it.
Okay.
What are you doing?
Ms. He,
come here.
Give this information to everyone.
Each of you.
Mr. Liu, I haven't decided yet.
You do it.
Is Director Liu your mother?
Yes.
Your mother told me
about your worry
through a hospital leader.
Actually,
you don't have to worry.
I asked you to be the class representative.
It means I fully believe
that you have the ability.
Right?
My mother said I was willing to do it, right?
Yes.
Why? Do you have a problem?
No.
Jian Hong said he would organize
a programming interest group.
You also come to participate.
I also want to participate.
Of course.
Even my professional teachers participate.
Can you not participate in the class representative?
Mr. Lin has agreed to be
the instructor of our interest group.
He also said he would give us a place
to do activities.
Let's participate.
So you don't just have to participate.
You also have to be in charge with Jian Hong.
One month later
I finally get you back.
I tried to use C language
to produce a pull-back program.
I have failed to execute it.
I made it up
as you have helped to see.
I have told the个只真
that
we will only need to give sane Henry
can directly operate the Note.
Why?
Because there is a Note in the space of the Graph.
I applied for the Graph.
Of course, I have to give the Note
the space of the memory.
Then why can't you do it correctly?
Because I didn't give the fart needle
the memory space address of the Graph.
You know the answer.
Why do you ask?
Li Xue.
Old Lin promised to give us
a group of interested people as a guide.
And he also gave us the space
to be a venue.
So I participated.
I participated.
So?
I was going to try
Li Xun's C language level.
How is it?
I didn't expect to be fooled by him.
I picked the question myself.
I think Li Xun is a master.
He deliberately guided you to say the answer.
It means he knows the answer.
I think so, too.
Li Xun writes codes in the dormitory every day.
I can't understand what he wrote.
I don't think so.
Some people
just pretend to be a gentleman.
They don't know anything.
It's a good thing if you don't know.
Someone was blinded by hatred.
Someone's arms are turned out.
It's hard to tell.
Zhu Yu is right.
It's a wheel, isn't it?
Pull it out and walk.
I want to see how Li Xun's level is.
I also want to see what he wrote.
Anyway, the last time he did the crossword,
he wrote it in several classes at the door.
It's the most basic thing.
I don't think so.
Right.
This is the place
Mr. Lin applied for us.
In the future,
this is the home of our programming team.
This is where we work.
How is it?
It's quite big.
It's wide.
It's a little dirty.
Clean it up.
It's still
quite clean and neat.
It's a good thing.
It's good.
Gao,
why are you so interested
in Li Xun's programming level?
I just want to know
how big the gap between us and the top is.
You don't agree?
No one doesn't want to be the top.
Zhu Yu,
do you agree?
Maybe the other top
is a little bigger.
He?
You saw it, right?
I think it's good to be an ordinary person.
You're already very unusual
after you got into Nanhu University.
Did Li Xun teach you
the homework that Mr. Lin arranged for the class?
I didn't teach him in the whole class.
I'm so embarrassed
to explain it to Mr. Lin.
Then you can urge him.
I can urge him.
I can't even avoid him.
Are you afraid that Mr. Lin will hurt you?
I can't help it.
Li Xun is so arrogant all day.
He looks down on you.
He doesn't like you.
Aren't you curious
how good he is?
You're so mad.
You're not afraid of being exposed?
Didn't I say
that I shouldn't come up
without my permission?
You didn't teach me
the whole class C language.
I didn't teach you.
I didn't write it.
You can give me your grades if you don't teach me.
Whatever.
Are you afraid to teach me?
I'm not afraid to teach you.
Yes.
You carry this computer every day
and knock it over and over again.
You're like a singer-songwriter.
If everyone sees
the homework you taught,
it will be full of bugs in the code.
Isn't that embarrassing?
You're so annoying.
So the best way
is not to teach me, right?
Yes.
You're so interested
in my programming skills.
What if you're a embroidery pillow?
What's the most important thing?
Find the biggest paper in three numbers.
It's so long.
Why didn't I
finish it on the tenth?
Paper.
You're really like your master.
Here it is.
You got the homework?
I'm sure
it's an embroidery pillow.
How?
The logic of this homework
is very simple, right?
You can get it
with ten codes.
But it's good.
You wrote a hundred codes.
What's the most important thing
in writing codes?
It's the simple one.
You made such a simple logic
so complicated.
You're so confused.
It's not an embroidery pillow.
Imperial Library
Is this virus?
An I TM processor
16G memory.
Girl,
are you from the computer department?
How can you tell?
You're really experienced.
How can a normal student
use such a high configuration?
You spent a lot of money on this selection.
Can you fix it?
Silly girl.
It's just a small virus.
It's simple.
Five minutes.
I'll fix it in five minutes.
Okay.
Girl,
is Mr. Ling
still the director of our department?
Are you the senior?
I'm the first year.
Are you the new student?
I'm telling you,
you're a bad student.
Our computer department
is a famous profession.
It's convenient to find a job in the future.
I used to work in the factory.
Why didn't you work there?
Well,
the factory sounds nice.
To be honest,
it's an IT master.
No.1 is youth.
No.2 is hair.
No.3 is waist.
Each of them
looks like they're in their thirties.
You're out of the office.
You're in the emergency room.
If you don't want to die,
you should change your job.
Who...
Who did this to you?
My classmate.
Who?
Your classmate?
It's impossible.
You're in the first year.
You only learned a few lessons
after you learned C.
How could you do this?
Wait.
I have a virus.
Yeah, I can't kill the fat guy.
I'll change my job.
Don't worry.
I got it.
It's still not working.
How about this?
We can't
restart the system.
What's wrong?
It's so late.
Come on.
Hurry up.
Change your job.
Come on.
Use your secret skills.
Hurry up.
Brother Cheng, you've done it.
I've done it.
No need.
Just here.
You see,
it's out.
Is it
the guy
who made it up?
No.
His classmate.
His classmate?
Sister.
The first-year student?
Impossible.
It's impossible.
Yeah.
If he...
We can't solve it.
If his classmate is capable,
he won't go to any university.
Right?
He's very professional.
He's better than us.
Try again.
Let me teach him.
Go.
Okay.
Sister.
It's done.
Not yet.
Can you
call your classmate
here
to introduce us?
Yeah.
Call him here
to discuss it.
Yeah.
Call him here.
I haven't decided yet.
Gao.
Here's your practice machine.
Okay.
Oh, no.
It's totally out of focus.
Zhu Yu.
Why don't you find Li Xun
and tell us
how you solved it?
Even if it's a brick,
I won't go to him.
I'll go to the library
to check the information.
I don't believe
there's only one virus.
You're still not convinced.
I think Li Xun is a genius.
He deserves to be the top.
Is Feng Shu and Miao Miao
good-natured?
But
no matter how smart they are,
they can't be a big hit
without a good personality.
Yu Yu.
What about your homework?
Oh, no.
The leader is still waiting for me in the office.
You don't want to
write a virus
without a homework, do you?
Don't be so convenient.
Let me see
what kind of great virus it is.
Who wrote this virus?
Li Xun.
You wrote this virus yourself?
You brat.
Hurry up.
Sit down.
Li Xun.
You'd better
sit down.
Sit down.
What did you write?
It's a insect.
Insect?
You tricked me.
And you hid it from me.
I just got the supply.
Zero day also repaired.
What else can I do?
You can't rebuild the system.
I got the virus in every plate.
Every plate?
Go on.
I just want to try
whether I can make one
like a panda burn incense
that can infect the system
with EXC,
COM,
PIF,
Source,
HTML,
ASP,
and the anti-virus software.
It will also delete
the backup files of GHO
and can't rebuild the system.
You're so scary.
You want to
make all computers
in our whole hospital
bankrupt?
But the technology of
the panda burn incense
is still too low.
It's not that clever.
The more hidden the virus, the better.
What are you going to do?
Sir.
In fact, the current virus
is for getting user information.
It can intercept the browser
and install software.
Or use it as a machine.
But it's not very valuable
to use a single computer as a machine.
What can ordinary computer users
steal?
It has the value of attack.
But there are many things
that ordinary people
don't want to lose in computers.
For example, graduation papers, family photos,
design drafts, company documents.
All these can create the value of exchange.
For example,
the 2008 Confector
is actually the same.
It's just a Internet transmission.
Now, these firewalls
are getting more and more intelligent.
When the system is broken,
it's getting harder to attack.
But the Autorun virus
is still effective.
That's right.
So I want to make this computer
an infector.
It finds different people to break the virus.
Every time it builds a system,
it will connect different disk drives
and can directly get information.
Inst gaator finalize this project and
We'll get data and no trace of you.
No fishing sorrow,
only causing to be caught in the past.
Teacher,
have you also used a hard drive
to launch a system?
I am just letting your devil finance.
Don't worry.
I only wrote32 hardwareq cable,
Not signals andате nordic 2012.
Li Xue,
tell them to me.
Now Windows XP still has a hole.
This way, go to this office.
This way, come here.
Add another line.
Then add another line.
Professor.
Your phone.
Your...
Old Lin.
What time is it?
I forgot to bring the key.
Come back now.
Why did you bring the key again?
Okay.
I won't say it anymore.
I'll go back right away.
Sorry.
My leader.
How about this?
Let's continue to talk another day.
Okay.
Secretary Ke.
Why haven't you left?
Professor, that virus...
Sorry. Sorry.
Yixuan.
Unlock his computer quickly.
Okay.
Goodbye, Professor.
Goodbye. Goodbye.
Yixuan.
Hello.
Li Xun.
Here.
Unlock it.
Forget it.
What time is it?
Don't pull.
Let go, little girl.
Go back. Go back.
Teacher Lin asked you to unlock it for me.
I made it clear in the office just now.
You can't remember it?
I can't understand even if I remember it.
You can't understand it?
I thought the people who can be the class representative are all excellent.
It seems that your interest group
didn't teach you anything.
Will you unlock it or not?
What's the point of not unlocking it?
You still have to be a teacher.
Li Xun.
I admit that I'm not as good as others.
I sincerely ask for your advice.
Please help me unlock it.
Okay?
Zhu Yin.
Since you're not as good as others,
then learn it well.
I'm not as good as others.
By this way.
What happened?
Isn't it just an disease?
I can't do that. I can't unlock it.
Why did you pick this one?
Do you want to die?
I'm not calling you.
I'm calling you.
Yes.
Yu, wake up.
I'm not going.
Why can't you?
You're forcing me to do this.
No, I'm not.
Wake up.
Come on.
I don't want to go.
Yu.
We have tea class today.
Wake up.
I want to go.
What if you don't go?
You'll deduct my points.
I don't want to go.
Get up.
I'll wipe your face.
Get up. I'll wash your face.
What's wrong?
I'm so happy.
I've finally figured it out.
Go wash your face.
Youyou, Beiyang,
Shuhai, Fuyang.
Today's closed time is coming.
Nanhu University Library.
Welcome to your next visit.
I'm so happy.
The mutton skewers from A'Dao are delicious.
I'm thanking you.
I've solved the virus.
Didn't you tell Mr. Lin
about the virus?
I've studied it with Gao.
It's really solved.
Although the virus is also
given by you,
but at least it has a profit.
Thank you.
Li Xun,
your grades look good.
In fact, early self-study
is a good time for the students to communicate.
Do you want to
guide the students?
I don't have time.
The bonus I was given
is really meaningful,
not including the teachers and students.
But you're always lacking in love.
If this goes on,
our class can't be in a good shape.
Fang Sheng Miao can't be in the health care department.
She might be upset
because you didn't go to the jujube department.
She's been unhappy for four years.
I know
you don't care about whether you get a point or not.
But we are a group.
You should think about everyone more,
right?
I knew you weren't that cold-blooded.
But many people
are so lazy when they get to college.
They waste their four years in college.
Actually, it's important to study early.
Enough.
I'm done.
So you agreed?
What's the point?
Except for your ten pairs of sunglasses,
you have to wear a necklace.
You're leaving so early?
It's okay.
I can go back to the dorm.
I forgot my phone.
Open the door.
You're a man.
You don't follow the rules
and let others take the responsibility.
Do you have any responsibility?
Open the door and give me your phone.
Open it.
You...
Don't answer the phone.
Don't move.
Hello.
Hello, Xinyu.
Do you want to be with me?
Sorry.
Zhu Yu is busy now.
Okay.
Sorry.
It's okay.
Open the door.
I'll drag you to the bath today.
Don't just
play with me.
I don't believe you.
If you don't open the door,
how can I wait for you?
Open the door.
You...
самое Katara
you don't need to
Get back to body
We will not be separated
Escape from the noisy world
Accompany me, I am your new point of view
Raise me up bravely
Like the flame of the night
Cause I believe I love you
True love will take its course
I am by your side
Spending a long time with you
Cause I believe I want you
True love will take its course
That burning fire
Is always on your side
Ah
Its justGG confusing
I'm sorry.