YoYo English Channel YouTube
I don't believe that anyone can save anyone
Until you break into my world
Even if this world shatters into darkness
We will fight in the darkness
Even if the light is very bright
I will still watch over that vast vast land
I see the direction of the boundless atmosphere
Every day, the lens is a little bit yellow
Even if I am light
How can I be alone in the vast night?
I burn up the night just for you to remember
How everything was in the beginning
If I am light
The wind and the color of the night are like wild grass
The mountains are broken, but you are still by my side
Everything is how it was in the beginning
The King of Blaze
Episode 1
Episode 2
The King of Blaze
Is your waist okay?
It hurts
Where? Here
Don't touch
No
Then let's tie it up
Come
Don't move
Slow down
What did you eat this morning?
I ate buns
I'll take you to the toilet
Don't lock
Okay
Don't move
I'll help you up
I'll do it myself
Don't be angry
You are also very young
Morning
You continue
Help me
No
I'm sorry
You slept at the company last night
What are you thinking?
He slept in the company.
What? It's been a night.
I want to sleep in the company.
Sleep again.
You didn't say a word.
They're right.
He did sleep in the company.
He slept in the company.
I'll go to the bathroom.
Your shirt is still with me.
When will I return it to you?
Don't think about the autumn in the fairy tale
It's a destined encounter
Let me feel your care
Your simple wish
A blink of an eye
The time of the earth
No longer afraid of falling into the world
With you by my side
Put it on.
Don't be afraid.
A little love
Don't think about the autumn in the fairy tale
It's a destined encounter
Let me feel your care
Your simple wish
A blink of an eye
The time of the earth
No longer afraid of falling into the world
With you by my side
Put it on.
Good night
It turns out to be your ring
Hello, master
Ok, I'm at the door now.
Hurry up, hurry up, this way.
Hurry up.
Be careful, don't touch people.
Come, be careful.
Come here, this position.
Hurry up, hurry up, this way.
Put it here, this way.
Yes, yes, yes.
Ok, follow this bridge.
Put it along this bridge.
Ok.
Master, isn't this on the
How to dismantle
Who knows
You are fast
We have to change
No way
Or you go over there
Don't touch you
This one, this one, change
Ok, come
Be careful
Put it right, put it right
Come
Look at the layout
Come, be careful
Give it to me
Zhu Yue, it's really you.
What's up
How about it
Did our seven countries win and lose?
Seven countries win and lose
You don't say
I thought it was our invincible
The same type of game
Anyone can develop
But whether it can be successful
It depends on fate
How about it
Your game
Is there any movement now?
Do you know
We put a lot of publicity fees
To make this game
Do you know
How many sound effects we have
Play with me
You and Li Xun
Don't be naive
Think I'm the same as I was in college
Can only rely on ability
Can only be out
You know our two games
The biggest difference is there
You only have that
A little bit of small money
That little weak mouth
Once it's gone, everything is gone
But we can still make money
As long as we
Take a little bit of care
Can make you
Press it to the core
This is a joke
I know
You are not afraid of me
You must be scolding me now
Despicable and shameless
Many people have been scolded
Scolding LP
Superb
No bottom line
It's okay
Anyway, this world
Is a failure in the end
People
Have always been the winners
Zhu Yue
Do you think
This scene
So familiar
Are you done
gone
I'm done
Your car
Half a year
Ran more than 50,000 kilometers
A bit more
What is this
Watch the airwaves
OK OK OK
Dong Zong knows to sell cars
It seems to be
We just talked about it
In Jianghu
I tell you
You are a business man, you know
I spent 48,000 yuan on this car
Why does Tong Feng sell cars
Why sell cars
why
Company difficulties
Tianhe Company
Our company
Already in this situation
What do you think
Cherish the working days now
I guess our company
It's going to be a mess
This LP
To promote this seven countries
It's simply not worth the cost
Now open a website
Can see this net red face
This is really going to kill me
I played this seven countries carefully
Their content and martial arts are like a book
But their system
There is no martial arts skill at all
Yes
But i think
LP didn't want
Seven countries go far
Just a wave
How much can you earn
Just this kind of bad thing
They did it before
Good skill
It just happened to be able to kill us
The key is
Their game compatibility is too strong
LP
In the total number of users in the country
Is twelve
So their gold coins
Can be used
Even if you don't play seven countries
They can still play other things
How do we compare this
It's not comparable at all
I see this company
You really have to ask
Look at this
Just don't come
This Zhang Fang
Really has a stock
Just two
One for each of us
But Zhao Teng
That selection
The fix is not very good
The code quality is not enough
You have to change it again
OK, team leader
In fact, since you came
From the first day
I know you are not ordinary
So
Although I am older than you
But I always call you team leader
Because of respect
But the world has not been so far
Still bug
Do you think this is necessary
OK, sister
Face reality
Come, let's do it
Just respect yourself
In fact, you can put
The dead horse of the five generals
For now
It's a miracle
So
I think we really tried our best
No regrets
But no matter what
First ensure the update of the day
I'll go find Li Xu
Do you usually play games
Play games
I don't play games
What are you playing
Yes, I don't play games that much
I recently have a game
Played a lot
It's about anime
Play games
You should watch my videos
It's a pretty fun game
Really
Yes, and the image design inside it
Special anime image
That's pretty good
What are you talking about
That game
Just talk about
An anime character adventure
Then
Really
Your friend
OK
Then you talk first
I have a few bye bye
Dong Siyang car
Dong Siyang car is sold
The company is almost gone
Why are you still here
Now the publicity of the Seven Kingdoms
It's all over
What can I do
What do you do now
The bullets are all out
Can you turn the corner in the middle
Let nature take its course
What is nature take its course
Don't do it if you don't have money
Anyway
Can't compare with the water supply of LP
Instant damage
That's it
Of course not
You and Zhao Teng continue to make games
Update the day after tomorrow
What about you
Continue to drink coffee here
This is the personal privacy of the staff
Director Zhu
Anything else
I'm going to the bathroom
Don't help me wash
You are so free
I won't wash it myself
What are you doing
This company is not closed yet
Open house
No, Dong Liu
You know our character
We are not people who love money
I'm not a person
I'm so just
So just
I'm the one who taught you
I told you
I amista
Good
Not very good
I felt
Dis hooks
principal
I think
We have to find him
and settle it
We got the
Where might it be
I would like to ask...
For tonight's surprise,
there will be only a huge festivity.
Okay.
But right now,
Monster radio is going first.
filtered XZ spawn.
When we notice and act cute,
If the weather is like this, it will kill people again.
This is the first time we have a big reunion.
It's good. Don't jump to the bottom.
At this time, the reunion is four meters.
You don't understand.
The more the end is, the more we get closer to the world.
Right.
For example, comrade Zhang Fang,
as the director of HR,
the first one to shout out the pre-competition,
lead the way to shake the heart.
I call it management.
At this time, we can see who will be the leader.
Okay. You are still fishing.
Anyway, I am working with the company of Fly-Joy.
Right, Dong?
Go away.
Li Xun didn't sleep last night.
He can't sleep in the cafe.
No. He is working overtime in the company.
Go.
How long will it take?
Soon.
Where will we go?
You'll know when you're there.
Hello, Boss.
Wow.
Welcome.
Boss,
the room is ready.
I'll go to work.
Okay, go ahead.
Okay.
Let's stay here tonight.
No one can work today.
He's going to soak me in hot spring.
He'll soak me back.
I've spent a lot of money.
One by one.
You should have stayed a night.
You didn't bring anything.
What did I bring?
There are toiletries and hotels.
I've never stayed in a hotel.
Make-up?
You look so good.
It's better without makeup.
Right.
Okay, I'm not going back to my room.
Go and have dinner with me.
Go.
Let's go.
Today,
we're going to meet in a group.
I'll say a few words.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Don't worry.
Just go and have dinner with me.
Okay.
I'll go.
Bye.
See you.
You're so good.
You know the difference between work and work.
You're a bitch.
You don't know what you're doing.
Why am I a bitch?
I'm a bitch.
You're a bitch.
Okay.
I'm a bitch.
Don't be so arrogant. Drink.
Come on.
You're really good.
You're a good sister.
You're amazing.
Yes.
I can see that.
You're waiting for a hero to save you.
Come on. Give me a pour.
Give me a pour.
Come on. Another one.
No.
I'll do it.
Okay.
Come on.
Listen.
If a woman wants to drink,
she's amazing.
Listen.
Amazing.
If a woman can't drink,
we can't drink either.
No more.
Let's drink three cups of wine.
Okay.
Come on. Pour it for me.
disciples
Never mind
Is the character anuman?
It's very good
Let's
get this right.
Any more createdFire fridge?
No, I'll get some free coffee.
My opinion should be
a heavy set of
cheap, cheap
and local ones.
The choice is made.
You're just no better.
There's order.
You're doing a good job.
I'm doing well.
You've said that
this is
I was thinking
The plan didn't change quickly
I haven't retired yet
The airport is closed
I'll go to drive a taxi
Later I was fighting because of a buddy
I went in for a few years
After coming out
I don't want to drive this taxi anymore
I want to do something good
Just walk on the street
I remember that was a summer
It was hot that day
Like a fire
This is hot for me
Pass by a what
At the door of the IT company
That electric glass door
Open the air conditioner
Blow to ten meters away from me
You know, it was cool for me
Cool
I sit at the door
I said I blow the wind
What happened
The security came over
I drove me away
I thought at that time
I know what I did
I want to open an IT company
I just blow the air conditioner
No one coax me
Come come come
I just blow the air conditioner
No one coax me
Come
Cheers
To be honest
I'm in this industry
Also
Also ten years old
Actually I want to work
Yes, my company has changed four or five
But I still want to do it
Good game
I thought this time
Invincible
Yes yes
I thought this time
Invincible
Can make some noise
Pity
Actually, think about it
You see
It's quite sad
We are such a small game
It's not easy to make some money
Make this kind of thing
You said
Why do you always drag us
Don't let go
I can go to the flower
You drink first
I'm back
No, I haven't left yet
Play with it
Afraid
Can't drink
No, I'm still young
This can't be out
Let's drink
I'm back
Because of us
Because Li Xun and I
Have a private feud with that company
Which company
LP
Two bosses of LP
One of them should be
Our college classmate
We started a business together before
Just LP
Li Xun was the leader
But in the early stages of the business
Something came out
You all know he went in
The reason he went in
Is that he closed the eyes of another boss
Didn't you all ask me
Why are you here
After Li Xun was released
The choice of Yin Cha Liang Cu
Start here
And I always stand on his side
That's it
Wait a minute
I'm a little confused
Li Xun
Stunned
Why did he hit her
This is Li Xun's private matter
I can't say
Li Jiecheng is enemies
You mean the one who started the business
Li Xun
Correct
I knew it a long time ago
I knew it was wrong
I also told him
I said, are you a kid
Hidden
You pretend here
I said these
Just want to tell everyone
Whether LP is blackening us
Hit the teeth
This project can't be done
We will do the next one
If it doesn't work, we won't give up
So we will be with LP
LP has always been a mess
Just remember
What else can I do
We are now
It's already a team
At the worst, let's finish it together
If they don't come
Our company
Dongdong, don't be angry
At most, it will be a year or two
Right, we all know
We are now barefoot
Not afraid of wearing shoes
Right
Yes, nothing to say
I love to listen to this
Just remember
What are you afraid of
Is it
Our new Feiyang company
Just do it
This big waste
And fart
Do it
Hit him
Hit
Dongdong
I want to apologize to you
I'm sorry
We hid so many things
I thought after coming in
At least a year
They will have a movement
I didn't expect it to be so fast
You think
I can't see it
You two had a story
When did you know
Come from Li Jun
He looked for you
You know he's looking for me
You think I will let one
Just got out of the prison
Even a resume
People who can't get it
Enter my company
What did he tell you
You want to know
How does he say himself
Or how do you say
This
Dong Siyang gave me a room card
We didn't go wrong
Didn't go wrong
There are two rooms
There is another one
Which one do you want to choose yourself
Where are you going
Or I will open another room
Whatever
Did you put our things
I told Dong Siyang a long time ago
Dong Siyang is a smart person
I guessed it all
Do you still have to tell me
This photo has always been with him
He told me
Zhou Yun thinks too much
Sometimes naive
Love to be stupid
But absolutely capable
Especially loyal
Especially determined
You said you two
This matter
Others see it clearly
What are you doing here
This is life
This love is not easy
Just like playing games
Only this knife and sword
No love and hatred
Who said it was fun
Right
This layer of window paper
It's so hard to read
Are you cold
Isn't it cold standing
Cold
Come down
Why did you drink for me today
Self-righteous
Then Dong Siyang let you drink
I don't drink anymore
I really drank too much
Can you still walk
I won't leave if I can't leave
I can't leave
Why is my photo with you
Then put it on
I will deal with my stuff
Why is it your stuff
Otherwise yours
It's mine
OK
Go back and take it away
I will deal with my stuff
Little fool
Look at you
I remember when I was in school
I went to find you for homework
You are on the rooftop
Lying on the broken bench
He looked at me
Like now
Li Xun
Have you ever thought of me
You are not my friend
I don't know
What if you don't
I don't believe
You are thinking about the company now
You don't mention
I don't mention
What happened before
We just ignore each other
What's wrong
I told you before
I'll suffer losses anyway.
These are the old days.
I've forgotten about them.
Just eat.
Thanks.
Or about hot lap早泡
Other unhappy people.
AOA trip
is boring.
If I do something,
he will blame me.
No.
Let's talk with him.
Please think it over.
What if he was wrong?
No.
I think you should
take him in and talk with him.
I have to.
I'm not ready to talk with him.
Bow over your head if you like him.
I need to.
Well,
totally agree.
Liu course will be director Scott sl malaria
Liu and reser found
Isn't it
Do you have pickles
Which bread is good
I found that there is something
You compatama
All don't equilibrium
Now is the most expensive time
It takes us to consume
Call this your routine
There's a backer, right?
I met Fang Zhijin that day.
He said he was coming for us.
He said our game
only has no profit.
He can surpass us
as long as he can just take the lead.
I really hate him.
But I didn't even scold him.
You're afraid of him?
That's right.
I'm afraid of him.
I hate him.
But I've hated him for so many years.
But I didn't do anything.
I can only be angry.
He bullied Xiao Yan.
I can only watch.
Then he hurt you.
You're not afraid of Fang Zhijin.
You're just afraid
that we can't win this time.
If it weren't for me,
you wouldn't have taken revenge on him.
If I hadn't dragged you to the game,
Li Lan would not have been in trouble.
Zhiyun.
You think too much.
You only think about the facts.
In the end, you will only fail.
Don't worry.
Your fear of him
is far less than their fear of me.
I'm afraid of everything.
You're afraid of him.
So you've been following him for so many years.
And they're afraid of me.
So they stared at me as soon as I came out.
You don't have to worry
about what they're doing to us.
If they really
do what they want,
maybe I can't do anything
about them in the short term.
But they have to stare at me
and try to step on me.
This is an opportunity.
So it's fair.
You're afraid of him.
They're afraid of me.
Then who are you afraid of?
I'm not afraid of anyone.
Silly.
You haven't changed.
Each time, you always left.
After you wake up,
I want you to look at me.
Don't go.
Fate isn't a journey.
Do you still believe me?
I would believe you if you dare to say.
You are everything to me.
I can't help myself.
I'm too useless to you.
I still love him.
I'm waiting for the perfect look
I'm still waiting for the impossible
Gao Jianhong and Fang Zhijing
are planning to launch an excuse
This person needs to be investigated
Be careful he will give us a social situation
He knows Li Xun the best
I'll leave the painting here
If he succeeds in the market
I'll take the picture of the picture
and give him a son
You have a plan?
I'm waiting for the perfect look
I'm still waiting for the impossible
If love is too cold and cold
This dream will be pushed back automatically
Wake up and leave you alone
Don't leave, fate is not a map
Grab my hand
The soul is shining
You are my everything
The soul is not enough
I care too much about you
I'm waiting for the perfect look
I'm still waiting for the impossible
If love is too cold and cold
This dream will be pushed back automatically
Wake up and leave you alone
Don't leave, fate is not a map
Grab my hand
The soul is shining
You are my everything
I care too much about you
Don't leave, fate is not a map
Grab my hand
The soul is shining
You are my everything
I care too much about you
Don't leave, fate is not a map
Grab my hand
The soul will be pushed back automatically
Wake up and leave you alone
Don't leave, fate is not a map
Grab my hand
The soul is shining
You are my everything
I care too much about you
Don't leave, fate is not a map
Grab my hand
The soul is shining
I'm so tired.