What is that?
Report!
The Sea Clan army is invading!
Li Jing!
Archers, ready!
Draw bows!
Loose!
Oh no! It's trying to climb up!
Heavens!
How can this be?
Darn it!
We can't hold them!
What do we do?
Darn it!
They're coming!
General!
Can we still hold Chentang Pass?
Okay.
Welcome back to Tianjin Traffic Radio FM106.8.
It's another sunny day.
I hope your mood is as bright as today's weather.
Yu Han.
Did you see Er Tiao when you left for work?
I can't find him anywhere.
Where could a little bird go?
Hey, stop looking.
He flew to my office to find me again.
How many times have I told you not to run off?
You don't have a phone.
What if you got lost?
Look at you.
You act cute whenever I scold you.
Alright, alright.
Hurry home.
Where nine rivers meet the sea,
Chentang guards the coast.
We pray for a prosperous year,
with gentle rains and fair winds.
How did you get in here?