[English subtitles are available]
[The Fearless Season 1]
[Episode 33]
Hello?
Is it the automobile 4S store?
My car
is powering off,
so I have to park it by the roadside.
Can send someone to help me?
I'm at Jingwang East Road，
around the intersection.
Righteous Luo.
What do you want?
Where are you?
Does it matter to you?
Of course it does.
I represent the bank.
I want to meet you and discuss the case.
Seriously? Unscrupulous Chen,
is it the way you practice law?
You represent the plaintiff,
but you discuss the case with the defendant.
Does the law forbid lawyers from contacting
the clients of their opposing counsels?
Fine. I happen to need a life coach.
Come and meet me then.
Zhang Shilan, give me my bag.
Where are you going? I'll go with you.
I'm meeting with a client. Give it to me.
What... What about me?
Get yourself a ride back to the law firm.
-Hello.
Is this your car?
Yes. My car...
Has it powered off?
Yes.
Okay. First thing first,
we'll charge a fee for towing the car away.
Okay.
Wait!
I'm a VIP customer.
Do I need to pay for that?
I'm afraid so. It's our rule.
Okay, here's the key.
-Don't forget to put the tripod away.
-Okay. Consider it done.
Be careful when you tow it away.
Thank you, sir.
No problem.
What happened? Has your car powered off?
It's none of your business. Just drive.
Where are we going?
I've driven for a while but you haven't told me a destination.
Do you have a problem with that?
You're driving a luxury car. Don't tell me you're gonna skimp on the gas.
Just stop asking me questions.
Keep driving.
I'll tell you when we need to make a turn.
Now spill it.
What do you want to teach me?
Why did you appeal at the last moment?
You're funny.
I'm entitled to file an appeal within the statutory time limit.
Whenever I feel like doing so,
I go with it.
What? Does it bother you?
Turn right.
Okay.
Listen.
I have no doubt that you'll lose
when you're up against me in court.
However, I do have doubts,
if you go down without a fight.
I don't believe there isn't a trick up your sleeve.
Take it down a notch, braggart.
Didn't you lose to me in a previous case?
Try doing my job, I dare you.
I was supposed to get my client off a charge of sexual harassment.
But he turned out to be rapist.
Even God couldn't help him out.
Tell me. What's on your mind?
Nothing.
I'm just bored.
I've got nothing better to do.
I happen to be in the mood of teasing you.
That's impossible.
Slow down.
Over there. Pull over.
Okay. Okay.
Thank you.
What is this place?
Did you really think
I'd talk about the case with you?
My car broke down.
I was using you as my chauffeur.
I'm leaving.
Thank you.
Hold on!
Is this a cosmetics store?
Yes.
Are you buying cosmetics?
Oh. Come on.
Can't a woman shop for cosmetics?
Are you okay?
I'm leaving. Bye.
She fooled me again.
Bye. We look forward to your next purchase.
Hello, I wanna ask you about a person.
There used to be
an employee in your store
named Wen Li. Do you remember?
Wen Li?
We don't know her.
Just a second. I have her photo.
Do you remember her?
Isn't it Ms. Wen?
Yeah.
Her name isn't Wen Li.
What do you call her then?
Wen Rong.
She worked here before.
But she left after a few months.
Who was she familiar with
when she was working here?
Ms. Li.
A customer would like to ask you about Ms. Wen.
Ms. Wen?
Yes.
Hello.
You can call me Ms. Luo.
This is my business card.
Hello, sir.
How can I help you?
A woman in shorts
got in here, right?
Did she buy anything?
Nothing.
She came to ask about
a girl who worked here before.
She came to ask about a girl then.
Who's that girl?
When that girl was working here,
she went by the name of Wen Rong.
For some reason, this lady calls her Wen Li.
I don't think you should ask more questions.
We're not supposed to disclose customer information.
Wen Li is my younger sister.
Why would this lady ask about her?
Who... Who is this lady then?
She's my girlfriend.
We're getting married soon.
She goes around, asking everyone about me.
Really?
Maybe she just wants to know more about me.
I suggest
you should be careful around her.
I really should.
Okay, I got it.
Thank you.
I'll take this.
-Okay. I’ll get you the bill.
-Okay.
Thank you.
Wen Li...
Who is this woman?
Is she relevant to the case about the bank?
Do you mean that she seduced another woman's husband?
Yes.
She colluded with my client's husband
to transfer all the property
that my client owned with her husband.
What else
do you know
about her?
Now that you've spoken of it,
I remember
how I felt about her.
She seemed
quite gentle
and
she was a smooth talker.
She's smart at work.
But she appeared to be quite introverted.
Several senior employees
took advantage of her
and made her do the most tiring chores.
She never fought back.
Instead, she lapped up the entire workload.
Sometimes
I felt sorry for her,
so I helped her.
At that time,
Ms. Wen was such a poor girl.
Look,
she couldn't make much money from her job.
She had to use the most part of her salary
to pay her monthly rent.
On occasion, she couldn't afford her rent.
So her landlord evicted her.
She would sneak back
and sleep in our office.
I felt like I had to do something.
I sympathized her.
So I let her stay at my place.
However,
something happened at that time.
My husband is a college teacher.
Maybe I misread his interaction with Ms. Wen.
Ms. Wen seemed to be extra nice
to my husband, behind my back.
Later on, she figured out
that I was wary of her,
so she moved out soon.
She knew she had aroused your suspicion, so she left. Right?
Did anything else happen?
Please try to think about it.
Maybe Wang Liang was the reason for her departure.
That young man used to take his girlfriend
to buy cosmetics in our store.
There's gonna be a huge discount.
Plus this eye cream, the total will be 3,000, right?
Yes.
We'll give you two samples as well.
Wang Liang.
It's gonna be 3,000.
It's okay. We'll buy whatever you like.
I'll take this 3,000-worth makeup kit then.
Get off your phone.
We have some new facial masks over there.
Why not browse around?
Sounds great.
Before I knew it,
that young man had become close to Ms. Wen.
He even came to my house to meet her.
I saw that happen once.
Ms. Wen was very embarrassed.
She said that man wasn't the one I knew of.
Since then,
she disappeared.
Wang Liang
then became Wen Li's boyfriend.
Thanks to him, Wen Li was able to register
as a permanent resident in Jingbei.
Then she dumped Wang Liang.
Gosh!
Is this...
Is this real?
It seems...
I didn't expect her to be such a person.
If she is a terrible person
like you have described,
wouldn't she
take revenge on those senior employees
who used to  bully her in the store?
She just left
and never declared to take vengeance.
That's because she didn't care about
those girls.
She is very ambitious.
She's got a bigger goal than that.
This...
This is really...
scary.
Don't you know what courtesy is?
Do you think you can get your way around?
Haven't your mother taught you anything?
I'm sorry. Sorry.
Are you gonna cry over this?
What do think you are doing?
Have I done anything to you?
Turn off the waterworks!
I'm not buying any of this!
It won't work here.
What did I say?
Did I hurt her or what?
Have I done anything to make you cry?
What do you mean by this?
Listen up. Your little stunt won't work.
You'll either do your job or just quit.
Come on in, Ms. Luo.
Have a seat.
I’ll get you some water.
Wang Liang.
What a coincidence!
You said you wanted to see me.
I was also gonna ask you for a meeting.
What do you have to say?
Actually,
I wanna know
if you have got any news about Wen Li.
Yes.
She
has returned to the country.
And I'm sure she came back alone.
You met her
at Cornell Cosmetics, right?
Cornell Cosmetics?
No.
No?
You had had a girlfriend before you met her.
You and your ex-girlfriend shopped for cosmetics there.
Did that not happen?
It might have happened.
But does Wen Li have anything to do with it?
She certainly does!
She used to work there.
She served you and your old girlfriend.
Don't you remember?
How come I can't recall any of that?
Well,
I get sleepy when I enter a cosmetics shop.
In the store,
my ex-girlfriend shopped around
while I played with my phone somewhere else.
When she picked out what she wanted,
I went up and paid for it.
I didn't notice the employees there.
How did you and Wen Li meet?
We met in a restaurant.
My ex-girlfriend and I...
You're supposed to dine with me, not to play with your phone.
It's gonna be over. Just give me one second.
I don't think...
What's wrong with you?
-I’m sorry. -It hurts!
Are you okay? Let me see.
I didn't mean it.
Are you blind?
Couldn't you be careful?
Let me take you to the hospital.
I'm so sorry.
A large area of my ex-girlfriend's skin was burned.
Besides, it was summer.
So Wen Li and I took turns to take care of her.
Are you stupid or what?
You've spent 5 minutes peeling an apple.
Don't you know how to do it?
You hate for me to have it, don't you?
I'm sorry. I'll give it to you right away.
Don't bother. Now I don't want to eat it.
Looking you peel an apple makes me sick!
You must be blind.
Can't you see my glass is empty now?
I'll get you some water right away.
Hurry up!
Honey, I'm here.
What took you so long?
Go over there.
Is there someone else you wanna burn again?
Sorry, honey.
I was stuck in traffic.
Every time you...
I'll be right back after filling the kettle.
Thank you.
You’re welcome.
Wang Liang,
is there gonna be a scar?
My skin used to be fair and smooth.
What if this leaves me a scar?
The doctor said
luckily we came to the hospital in time.
Don't worry. There won't be a scar.
It's all that stupid woman's fault.
You should be polite to her.
She didn't mean to injure you.
Fine.
That's gonna be my excuse too.
I'll say I don't mean to hurt anyone
while I kill people and burn down houses.
That's not what I meant.
Then what did you mean?
Now I'm the one being hospitalized.
Alright. Alright.
Look what I brought you.
Your favorite food!
Here, take a look.
Don't change the subject.
What did you mean?
My ex-girlfriend
had a bad temper.
She was the one who got hurt in that incident.
So she was really mean to Wen Li.
She yelled at Wen Li and even hit her.
In several occasions, I couldn't stand it.
But Wen Li
just took the heat.
Stop it. I don't want the apple now.
You'll want it after I'm done peeling it.
Here I come!
I only asked you for two cups of boba tea.
Why did you come back so late?
Sorry, I was waiting in a line.
This is jasmine tea with milk.
And this one has red beans in it.
Thank you.
You should have it. I'm not thirsty.
You don't have to be polite to her.
She's supposed to buy us boba tea.
Put it there.
I'll drink it later.
Why is it so sweet?
Didn't I tell you to cut the sugar by half?
Do you want me to get fat or what?
I'm sorry.
I'll buy you a new cup of boba tea.
What's wrong with you?
Do you want me to get burned again?
You did it on purpose, didn't you?
It's an honest mistake. I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
Yes. I'm fine.
I'll wash it off in the bathroom.
I'm sorry.
Sorry.
Wang Liang.
Just leave her alone.
She can only blame herself for being clumsy.
You're getting out of line.
Am I?
I'm in the hospital because of her.
How could you say I'm out of line?
Who is your girlfriend now?
Why don't you make her your girlfriend
since you care so much about her?
Wen Li,
I'm truly sorry.
My girlfriend is always like that.
Please forgive her.
In fact, I know
when I am away,
she treats you badly.
Actually,
sometimes, even I...
Let me ask you a question.
How many policemen does it take to screw in a light bulb?
None. Because it turns itself in.
I get the pun!
It's funny, isn't it?
Quite amusing.
You didn't do anything wrong.
Why the long face?
You should always be happy like you are now
and smile more.
She was the one being mistreated,
but she chose to comfort me.
Gradually,
we spent much time together on the roof.
One day,
a man whose face resembles a bike,
walks on the street and is ridden away
because someone thinks he's a bike.
Is it a bad joke?
I can tell you another one.
One day,
a man whose face looks like a brick
goes for a walk by the lake.
A toad pops up,
points at him, and says:
"Do you dare to toss yourself to the lake?"
Is it also a bad joke?
It's not that.
Then why aren't you laughing at it?
Because your awkwardness is more laughable!
You...
Look what you've done to me!
Because of you,
I'm stuck in the hospital!
Look what you've done!
Hey! What do you think you are doing?
Am I doing anything wrong?
You're being rude.
This time you've gone far out of line!
Fine.
You should be with her.
Go and be with her!
Anything wrong?
You tell me.
Think about it.
At the moment you played with your phone,
you had been targeted.
She knew from the beginning
that she could trap you.
Every step you took thereafter
was within her plan.
Isn't it horrifying?
[Mr. Wang]
Hello, Mr. Wang.
Mr. Chen.
Have you heard?
Luo Yingzi has filed an appeal.
I've heard about it.
Don't you also know that?
We can't proceed with the auction now.
It's okay.
That house will be auctioned at last.
We've also got the news
that she has reported to the police,
saying that her husband's loan is a fraud.
Well,
she has the right to do so.
We're in no position to stop her. Right?
I have a question.
As far as I know,
criminal offences must be dealt with first
before the civil part of the case gets its turn.
Her husband has gone abroad.
When will this case end?
We'll never be able to collect the debt!
You seem to know a lot about law.
The court won't easily judge it as a fraud.
That's right.
We'll insist that the loan was put through
a legitimate process before it was granted.
The court will take it into consideration.
The agreement
was signed by them both.
They came together to apply for the loan.
Obviously, this couple staged a fraud!
That's not it!
Mr. Wang, that's not what I meant.
Look.
She's in trouble because of her husband.
There's no way they would plot it together.
Mr. Chen,
it's our bank that has hired you, right?
You should protect our interests.
You can't side with her
just because you care for a poor woman.
Alright.
Just leave it be. I've got what I wanted.
Okay. Bye.
Mister...
Shuo, the documents are ready.
Where are you going? I'll go with you.
I need to go out for an emergency.
Can you give me a key to your apartment?
A repair guy will fix your air conditioner
in the afternoon, while I do some cleaning.
It's a combination lock.
I'll send you the password
and address later.
Okay.
See you later.
Done!
Come in.
Mr. Wang.
Mr. Chen.
What brought you here?
You rarely show up.
But now you came after a talk on the phone.
The defendant filed an appeal at the last moment.
Given its importance, I had to come.
On my way here,
I did some thinking.
In my opinion,
even if the police determines
that Luo Yingzi's husband
has staged a fraud,
we can still find a way
to get the money back from her husband.
It's unnecessary to make Luo Yingzi...
Are you
into that girl?
You're getting off topic.
Let's focus on the case.
That doesn't give you a reason
to speak for her again and again.
Mr. Chen,
I understand what you said.
How should I put it?
You are a lawyer.
A lawyer
should provide legal advice to his client.
The final decision
will be made by the client,
instead of the lawyer.
I assure you
that I understand everything you said.
I'll take care of the rest.
Sure thing.
Do you wanna go out for dinner together?
Mr. Wang,
I respect your decision
to handle the rest by yourself.
That said,
I feel the need
to tell you something.
Go ahead.
Look, I'm representing the bank.
I'm not your personal lawyer.
I will do my best
to help the bank collect debts.
However,
well,
if you do something
on your own
without informing me,
and have the bank suffer unnecessary losses,
I'm afraid
I won't be responsible for that.
Mr. Chen, that's too strong a word.
Don't worry.
I won't take any actions.
As long as the bank can get the money back,
I'm fine with everything.
That's right.
Money is the only thing we target, right?
Aren't we going out for dinner?
Thanks, but no.
You're a busy man. I'd hate to bother you.
I should get going now.
Okay, bye.
Okay.
I'm afraid you'll have to show yourself out.
No problem.
This room should be reserved for our baby.
If my parents come, they can also stay here.
[Shuo]
Hello, Shuo.
When I rushed out of the office,
I left some documents unsorted.
If the work at my place is done, you should go back to the office.
It's not done yet.
By the way, Shuo, I made you dinner.
When are you coming back?
I'm having dinner with my friends.
I'm not going home tonight.
What friends?
Shuo, have you made a new girlfriend?
Well,
whether I have a girlfriend or not doesn't concern you.
Just go.
I'm sorry.
Come on.
We're waiting for you.
Thank you.
Hello, Liangcheng Law Firm.
There's a result already?
Yingzi, we've got a result!
Of Xu Jianshe's case?
Am I gonna get it myself or not?
Hold on.
Shall we go and get it?
Ask them mail it to us.
Sorry.
I'm afraid I can't go get it now.
Would you mail it to me?
The address?
Don't!
What address should we tell them?
Just forget it.
When people in the firm see it, they'll laugh at us.
I'm sorry. Please don't mail it.
Would you give me a second?
You don't want to get it yourself or have it mailed here.
What on earth do you want?
I don't know.
We'll get it ourselves.
We'll go get it.
Tell them we're going to get it.
Sorry.
I'll come and get it.
Okay.
Bye.
What's the verdict?
They can't tell me on the phone, can they?
We won't know it until we see it.
You'll go get it.
No.
Why should I go?
You said you would go.
You're gonna do it.
I'm not.
I won't go.
If our claim is dismissed,
I'll go crazy right on the spot.
You handle bad news better than I do. You should go.
I can't go. Qiu Hua,
please!
Stop your reading.
I beg you.
It's true that you might go crazy,
but I'll go insane if I am there.
Over these years,
I've had my fair share of surprises.
You can't stab a knife in my chest again.
Drop that act.
You're such a good actress.
Luo Yingzi, are we doing this now?
My heart aches.
Fine.
I'll go.
What's the harm?
No big deal.
Maybe the case stands some chances. Right?
You wish. It's impossible.
What if it's dismissed?
Tell yourself this:
it's normal if our claim gets dismissed;
it'd be an accident if it doesn't.
Just go, brave girl.
Easier said than done.
Why don't you go instead?
I'm too scared!
Ma'am, let me get your bag for you.
Go. Do your best.
Good luck.
Remember to send me a message.
I'm gonna flip the coin one more time.
Please let it be heads!
Thank you.
[Archives]
Ladies.
You busy?
What's wrong with them?
I don't know.
Come in.
What's up?
A ruling has been made
on the case.
Which case?
Is it Xu Jianshe's case?
How is it going?
We've got a retrial.
No trial, right?
What did I say?
The court would definitely dismiss it.
It's okay.
Nothing serious.
We've earned the money.
Let them finish.
Is there a retrial or not?
The court has ruled that the initial trial made an unclear judgement on the facts,
and a decision based on insufficient evidence.
The court has accepted our defense claim,
and ordered a retrial.
This is the verdict. Take a look.
They're acting weird today, aren't they?
Yes.
What happened just now?
Don't you know what's going on in your department?
What is it about?
They've helped a client who was sentenced to life imprisonment to get a retrial.
A retrial?
What?
It's a retrial!
Retrial!
This is the first retrial in our firm!
I haven't seen such a thing happen
during all these years.
A client sentenced to life imprisonment gets a retrial!
The girls in this firm are better than men.
Awesome!
It's so weird.
It's really a retrial.
I can't believe we'd get a retrial for such a huge case.
How long has it been since our firm
last handled a case like this?
About five years.
Last time, the miracle was made Ms. Fang.
But this time,
it's made by two junior lawyers.
What's the big deal?
I got Wang Dafu acquitted in a previous case.
That's because those young lawyers
found exculpatory evidence.
What do you mean by that?
Are you jealous?
Jealous of what? Your incompetence?
Tao Zheng, what's that supposed to mean?
Do a criminal case, I dare you!
Do you think I don't know what you're doing?
As the director of the Management Committee,
you keep all lucrative cases for yourself.
Mr. Han, watch your mouth.
Otherwise, don't blame me for being rude.
I also know what you've done.
What have I done?
Enough.
No more quibbles.
Don't you feel pressured?
It was a radical decision
to allow them to form a team.
Mr. Tao is right.
Ms. Fang,
I don’t think you’ve thought it through.
What kind of law firm
would let two junior lawyers make a team?
Now they've become self-sufficient.
What good will it do to our firm?
How about
assigning Xia Shu to them?
Xia Shu is a partner of the firm.
It shows how much the firm cares about them.
That's a good idea.
Hello. Dad.
Are you off work?
Yes.
What's up?
Dad,
I have some good news.
I got a retrial for a case.
Yingzi,
congratulations!
Dad, where are you?
I'm with your mom.
Put her on the phone.
Okay.
Jiayi,
our daughter wants to talk to you.
Listen carefully.
Our daughter has done a great job.
Hello, mom.
This is Yingzi.
Mom, I've got some good news.
A client who was sentenced to life imprisonment in the initial trial
now gets a retrial because of me.
Mom, do you know
how hard it is to handle such a case?
Few people in my firm could do it.
But I, a junior lawyer,
made that happen.
Mom,
I've made you proud, haven't I?
Take good care of yourself.
Just watch how I'm gonna fight for you.
I'll visit you when I have time.
Cheers!
Qiu Hua.
Your won the battle gracefully.
You didn’t see how angry Mr. Han was
in the meeting.
Really? What did he look like?
You have no idea!
Luo Yingzi, you're back at the right time.
I was just talking about Mr. Han.
Here, let me fill up your glass.
-It's not empty yet.
-In today's meeting...
Everyone was happy,
except Mr. Han.
Tao Zheng quibbled with him.
He almost got into a fight with Tao Zheng.
Would he be able to defeat Tao Zheng?
What do you think?
Guys,
to be honest,
it's been a long time since our firm
last made such an achievement.
Right?
Yes, yes, yes.
It's a glory for the Criminal Defense Department.
Yes, that's right.
Ms. Luo.
Ms. Qiu.
Through this case,
I find you two admirable.
What you've done is impressive.
I...
Wait.
Well,
I remember someone had a problem with me
and Ms. Qiu when we started taking on cases.
Who was it?
No one would...
It's you!
Why would I have a problem with them?
You did!
After all,
we are in the same department.
If you need help in a future case, just let me know.
I'd love to learn from you.
May I propose a toast to you?
I'm gonna drink it all.
Come on.
I've been working in the firm
for a long time.
I haven't achieved anything yet.
I also need your help.
Hua, don't join them in the horseplay.
We are in need of your help.
Queue up, alright?
Don't jump the line.
If you are to help anyone, it's me, right?
Shut up.
Come on, guys.
It's rare for us to have a party.
We'll drink as much as we can!
Sure.
Cheers!
One, two, three.
Two, two, three.
You're wrong again.
I feel relieved.
When we first took on cases,
none of them showed support. Right?
But today,
they couldn't wait
to fawn on us.
It feels so good to be fawned on.
Wipe that smug look off your face!
I'll be honest with you.
Look.
We started taking on cases
just a year ago, didn't we?
Now, we've got a retrial for a client who's sentenced to life imprisonment.
Who could do that?
We made it.
We upheld justice and made money
without compromising our dignity.
We've got fame and fortune at the same time.
Now we've only been granted a retrial,
not an acquittal. Don't get so conceited.
No way. Just let me have fun
for the time being.
Frankly,
Yingzi,
I owe you many thanks.
You're getting serious.
You must have a load of compliments for me.
Come on.
I'm all ears.
I want to thank you
for helping me get rid of Mr. Han.
Otherwise, I would still be bullied by him
just like other guys,
and never make a name for myself.
Don't even mention it.
Listen.
You could get what you have now
because of your intelligence and hard work.
I should thank you instead.
This topic ends here.
Let's have more fun.
We''ll go drinking now.
Let's get drunk!
Come on.
How about we take a rain check?
I've got something to do.
Are you really heading to another party?
Qiu Hua.
I didn't know
you could be a party animal.
Well...
We'll drink next time.
Now I see why you keep looking at there.
Isn't that your suitor,
Zhang Quanquan?
Lower your voice!
Do you have a date with him?
Are you two in love?
Stop gossiping.
Keep your voice down.
If he and I get in a relationship,
you'll be the first one to know.
Alright.
Off you go.
I’m leaving then.
Okay.
Text me when you get home.
Just go. I know you can't wait.
Bye.
Quanquan!
Ms. Luo.
The car is here.
Ms. Fang.
Xia Shu?
Qiu Hua, there you are.
Good morning, Ms. Qiu.
Morning.
Qiu Hua.
I just asked Ma Lili to come.
She should be on her way now.
She'll be here soon.
Xia Shu,
I have something to discuss with Ms. Luo.
Would you excuse us?
Qiu Hua.
Xia Shu has become part of our team at Ms. Fang's request.
Do we have a team?
It's only the two of us.
With me, there's a team.
Ms. Qiu,
I was wrong last time. I'm sorry.
I just wanted to win.
I won't do it again. I assure you.
Xia Shu, stay here.
Ms. Qiu and I need to talk in private.
Hua,
even though we hate it,
we'd better act like we don't.
Wipe that look off your face.