[English subtitles are available]
[The Fearless Season 1]
[Episode 25]
Keep calm and quiet.
Are you saying you taking drugs
is related to the defendant's insult?
Of course, it's related.
I'm the one who's insulted and harmed,
while he
continues to hold a high position,
making big money.
He can still maintain a good reputation
in society.
As for me,
no one understands my pain.
I could only tell my husband,
who then divorced me.
Why?
What's the justice in that?
Can someone tell me?
I want to make that heartless guy
pay for his actions.
I'm done asking.
I don't think she can hold on much longer.
We should wrap it up.
Defense attorney,
do you have any questions for the witness?
Yes.
Witness Xia Linlin.
Is everything you said true?
No, let me put it another way.
Is everything you said
all the truth?
What does he mean?
Yes.
Xia Linlin didn't hide anything from us, did she?
You were harassed by the defendant,
lost your job,
your family, and marriage,
and even went to rehab
after using drugs.
It's truly a heartbreaking story.
Your Honor.
Defense attorney,
ask questions, don't make judgments.
Xia Linlin.
Besides sexually harassing you,
did the defendant do anything else?
He also raped me.
Why did the defense attorney ask this?
He's asking for evidence against our client.
Because he knows that there's no way to prove it.
I can't believe such things happen.
Can you tell us
how this happened?
Once he took me on a business trip,
and poured a lot of alcohol into me.
He made my secretary, Xia, drink for me.
Then he insisted on pulling me into his room.
I didn't want to go,
but he forced me.
That's when he raped me.
Was it rape
or consensual sex between two people?
It was rape.
Rape.
That was rape.
I repeatedly tried to escape,
but he dragged me back.
I begged him, but he didn't listen.
I even tried to fight, but I couldn't overpower him.
How was that not rape?
But there's no evidence
to prove he raped you.
But he did. He did rape me.
Your Honor.
Xia Linlin previously told the attorney
that Yang Weida raped her,
which is the most important reason
of the breakdown of her marriage.
However, the facts she stated
may involve criminal offenses,
and Xia Linlin is not the party in this case.
That's why we  didn't mention it in court.
Otherwise, we wouldn't be sitting in a civil court.
So,
I suggest the court not to testify
any evidence that has nothing to do with this case.
Your Honor.
Rape is a more serious charge than sexual harassment.
What I'm questioning now
is the reliability and objectivity of the witness's testimony.
My cross-examination
is highly relevant to this case.
Defense attorney,
you can continue questioning.
It'll be troublesome if he drags this on.
What a heartless beast.
I'm sorry.
Xia Linlin.
How many times have you been to a rehab?
Three times.
After coming out of rehab each time,
did you need to sign a pledge
with the rehab center and the community,
promising not to relapse?
Then why did you go in there three times?
Your Honor.
The questions the defense attorney asked
is irrelevant to the case.
Yes, it is.
What I want to prove
is that the witness has been untruthful.
If that's the case,
how can we believe
everything she said in court today?
Your Honor.
As we all know,
overcoming drug addiction is a very difficult process
once it becomes an addiction.
It has no direct relation
to the witness's character
or whether
she tells the truth.
Whether it's related to
the reliability of the witness's testimony
and her character,
I believe the court
will make a fair judgment.
Please don't interrupt my questioning.
Xia Linlin.
I've read all the text messages
you submitted to the court.
I want to ask,
are these text exchanges between you and the defendant?
Yes.
Didn't Ms. Luo tell you
that these messages had been notarized?
But they only prove that this information
is from the phone
submitted to the notary office.
Is this phone yours?
Of course it's mine.
But as far as I know,
you would sell everything around you
for money to buy drugs,
including the phone you just mentioned.
I did sell it,
but I bought it back
right away,
because I knew
if I sold that phone,
I wouldn't have evidence
of Yang Weida harassing me.
That means this phone
has not always been with you?
So, it went through the second-hand market.
As we all know,
when we sell a phone,
we usually
delete all personal information beforehand,
right?
I was in a hurry to get money,
so I forgot to erase it.
Forgot?
But those people who sell used phones
would delete it.
The first thing they do
is to erase all the information
from the phone,
right?
When I sold it,
I bought it back immediately,
so he didn't have time to erase it.
Anyway, these messages are still here.
Alright, let me ask you another question.
Are these
all the messages
between you and the defendant?
Oh no.
Is there anything else?
Didn't she tell us that's everything?
Your Honor.
We have new evidence to present to the court.
Your Honor, the deadline for presenting evidence has passed.
Plaintiff's attorney,
you've always emphasized
bringing in new witnesses to testify.
According to the Supreme People's Court's provisions on the application
of the Civil Procedure Law
of the People's Republic of China,
Article 99, Paragraph 3,
the application to present rebuttal evidence
is not limited by the previously determined deadline.
Your Honor.
Do I need to reapply for an extension to present evidence?
You can submit it in court.
Your Honor.
This is the record of the text messages
between the witness and the defendant in 2016,
duly notarized.
From this record,
it's clear
that the witness,
using alleged sexual harassment as an excuse,
repeatedly extorted my client,
with the amounts
escalating each time,
reaching an astonishing one million in the end.
Secretary.
Please show the evidence to the witness.
Witness.
These messages are from you, right?
Yes.
After Yang Weida raped me,
he lied,
saying his relationship with his wife was bad
and he would divorce her to marry me.
Then he tricked me
into having relations with him repeatedly.
But later,
I found out he had no intention of marrying me.
Instead, he fired me from the company.
I just wanted to find him
and claim some compensation for mental distress.
Your Honor.
The evidence presented by the defendant
precisely proves
that the defendant deceived the witness with lies
and engaged in an improper sexual relationship with her.
Before the sexual relationship occurred,
the defendant had subjected the witness
to prolonged sexual harassment.
No.
These text messages can at most prove
that they had a sexual relationship.
As for who harassed whom
or who seduced whom
before the relationship,
that's uncertain.
Plaintiff's attorney,
you presented the later text messages between them
after they had a sexual relationship.
We obtained the earlier messages.
These two parts, combined together,
clearly outlined the development of their relationship
—harassment first, then rape.
You can't only acknowledge the latter part as rape
and ignore the prior sexual harassment.
No, we have never admitted the rape.
We only acknowledge
that they had a sexual relationship.
As for the two parts of the messages
you mentioned,
I'd like to remind the court
that they can't be proved
to come from the same phone.
As I questioned earlier,
the witness's phone went through the second-hand market.
Also, we checked with the communication company,
and the messages provided by the other party
have no original records,
while ours
do.
Defense attorney, any further questions?
Yes.
Your Honor.
Yang Weida is not a perfect man.
He couldn't resist temptation
and had a sexual relationship with the witness.
That was his fault,
but he immediately
confessed to his wife
and gained her forgiveness.
Now, looking at the witness,
she deliberately seduced Mr. Yang Weida
and extorted him repeatedly,
receiving a total of 250,000 yuan
from him.
She spent all this money
on drugs,
and in fact,
the witness's behavior constitutes extortion, a crime.
If it weren't for Mr. Yang Weida's leniency
and overlooking her past actions,
she would have been reported to the police long ago.
In that case,
she wouldn't have the chance
to sit in court today,
confidently committing perjury.
Your Honor.
The opposing attorney is not questioning the witness.
He's expressing his opinion.
Defense attorney, do you have any more questions?
Yes.
Witness.
Did you come to testify today
because you ran out of money for drugs?
-That's why you want to get some from Yang...
-Your Honor.
The opposing attorney is attacking the witness.
No.
Yang Weida raped me.
I was raped.
Yang Weida
is a beast.
What a real drama.
[Jingbei Court]
The court believes
there isn't enough evidence
to prove the alleged sexual harassment by the plaintiff.
Therefore,
the court rules to
dismiss the plaintiff's lawsuit
in accordance with the law.
The plaintiff is responsible for the case acceptance fee of 500 yuan.
The court is adjourned.
Guo Yu.
Explain it to us.
Explain it.
Are you still a human?
Why not?
Am I not Unscrupulous Chen?
What?
You came all the way here in the middle of the night
to scold me?
You deserve much worse than me scolding you.
How could you take Yang Weida's money
without a clear conscience?
Why can't I take Yang Weida's money
with a clear conscience?
I did my job.
I won the lawsuit
because of my ability.
Why did you come here to challenge me?
You're Yang Weida's lawyer. That's right.
It's your duty
to defend him.
But how could you
play such dirty tricks in court?
Your tactics against Xia Linlin were heartless.
Do you have any humanity left?
If I had humanity, I wouldn't be called Unscrupulous Chen.
Ms. Luo,
do you still not know
how you lost the lawsuit?
I admit
Xia Linlin hid the content of the messages from us.
It was our negligence at work.
But given how Yang Weida
harmed Xia Linlin,
you still forced her to embarrass herself in court.
Do you realize the additional damage
you caused to her?
Do you even have a conscience?
You're wrong.
Xia Linlin
was the witness you brought.
She's not the plaintiff.
Your client's name is Guo Yu.
You should prioritize
Guo Yu's interests.
Xia Linlin is pitiful, I admit,
so what?
You're a lawyer.
A lawyer
shouldn't let their sympathy
influence their judgment.
Xia Linlin
concealed
all the unfavorable message content.
It's understandable from a human perspective,
but what about you?
You're Guo Yu's lawyer.
Because you sympathized with Xia Linlin,
you ignored all potential risks
and failed to protect your client's interests.
It was your fault.
Also,
why are you here arguing with me?
What are you arguing for?
If you have time to argue,
why don't you persuade Guo Yu
to appeal?
If you think Yang Weida is guilty,
put your energy
into finding evidence to nail him,
instead of coming here
to seek for justice.
Also,
don't you call me Unscrupulous Chen?
Well, maybe I am unscrupulous.
I still have plenty of tricks up my sleeve.
You want justice, huh?
Put aside those
amateur overflowing sympathies.
Win against me first.
If you think Yang Weida is guilty,
put your energy
into finding evidence to nail him,
instead of coming here
to seek for justice.
Chen Shuo was right.
We indeed lost our judgment
because of Xia Linlin's evidence
and failed to make the best decision for Guo Yu.
I...
I even went
to give Unscrupulous Chen a piece of my mind.
Look at me.
What a solid comeback from him.
He left me speechless.
I wished I could find a hole
to crawl into.
I was acting I couldn't handle defeat, right?
Yeah, you're quite bad at handling defeat.
If I weren't Guo Yu's lawyer
and sitting in the spectator's seat,
I would've applauded Chen Shuo
for this splendid victory.
Let's toast to Unscrupulous Chen.
I wonder how Guo Yu is feeling tonight.
She must be going through a rough time.
I hope she can be stronger than us.
Why must she be strong?
It was our fault,
not hers.
Do you think she will appeal?
Probably not.
The case has already ended up like this. There's no need to.
It's just hard to accept.
Here she comes.
Guo Yu.
What do you want to say about this verdict?
Say something.
Guo Yu.
We've been waiting for you.
What do you want to say? Say something.
Stop filming.
Excuse me. Stop filming.
Guo Yu! Guo Yu!
Guo Yu.
I'm a lawyer.
My client
has no obligation to accept your interview.
Stop harassing her, okay?
Guo Yu, say something.
Ms. Luo. Ms. Qiu.
Take a seat anywhere.
Guo Yu.
Are you
planning to pack up and return to your hometown?
Are you…
Are you going to give up?
I lost.
Guo Yu.
Actually, we still have a chance to appeal.
Ms. Luo, Ms. Qiu,
thank you for everything you've done for me.
I told you from the beginning
that I was prepared for this to be a lost case.
I just wanted to give myself some closure.
Now, I have it,
even...
more than expected.
I understand now.
An egg can't beat a stone.
Arms can't twist a thigh.
Thank you for choosing to stand by the egg's side.
But, even with your support,
it's still not enough.
So,
it's all over.
I'm going back to my hometown.
Guo Yu.
Lawsuits may end,
but you don't have to go back to your hometown.
How can I stay in Jingbei
after this case?
You don't have to stay in Jingbei.
You can go somewhere else,
but don't go back to your hometown.
Once you go back,
it means you choose your original life.
Can you really adapt to the original environment?
Let me think about it.
Ms. Luo, Ms. Qiu,
thank you.
Guo Yu, take some time to think it over.
If you have any thoughts,
you can contact us anytime.
This is the price of idealism.
Qiu Hua.
It was my fault.
You've always been more practical than me.
I dragged you down.
But it doesn't matter.
"If a man in the morning learn the truth, he may die in the evening without regret."
Besides, we're just first-year lawyers.
It's never too late to understand.
From now on,
I'll never take cases like this.
Idealism
and the grand concept of justice?
I won't touch them even if you smash them on my head.
If I make the same mistake again,
just kick me.
When we get back,
let's find Mr. Tao and get back that patent case.
We're already in the league of lawyers
earning a few hundred thousand a year.
As long as we don't mess up,
making a few million a year
is just a matter of time.
Aim higher,
in ten years or so,
surpassing Fang Lihong might not be impossible.
Come to think of it,
it's quite optimistic.
By the way,
who was the fan
that gave you flowers at the courthouse yesterday?
Your boyfriend?
Not now.
Maybe in the future.
How is he?
He's okay.
He's nice to me.
He's loyal.
Come on, Qiu Hua.
Being loyal is enough for you?
I might not have been satisfied before,
but now that I think about it,
it might not be bad.
Why?
Security.
Well, as long as you want,
you can earn hundreds of thousands a year.
How can you not feel secure?
Come on.
Look at me,
carrying over ten million in debt.
I'm different from you.
His name is Zhang Quanquan.
This name sounds quite secure.
It sounds complete.
Don't blame me for being straightforward.
I just think you deserve better.
After going through so many things,
if you could choose again,
wouldn't you consider security?
I'm being nosy.
My bad.
I won't ask again.
I know you care about me.
You'll get through this bridge in a while,
then drop me off at the subway station.
Where are you going?
I have something to do.
Fine.
I didn't agree to take this case from the beginning.
Now what's the result?
We ended up with a drug addict
testifying in court,
making our law firm a laughingstock.
What a bad influence it made
to our company's reputation.
Han, it's just a losing case.
It is a case,
but is it just a case?
We can lose a case,
but we have to lose with dignity.
This case has a huge impact.
When I was in the audience,
I wanted to find a hole to crawl into.
Losing a case
is inevitable,
but as a lawyer,
you must choose the most favorable outcome
for yourself
and the client.
This case,
we discussed it in our partner meetings.
Ms. Fang.
You knew the chances of winning were slim.
Since the chances were small
and losing it would have a big impact,
why did you agree to take the case?
Lawyers can lose cases,
but they shouldn't lose stupidly.
This case is just a stupid loss.
I didn't agree them to file a lawsuit for sexual harassment from the beginning.
Alright.
It was all my fault.
I apologized.
Ms. Fang, you did nothing wrong.
What’s wrong with standing up for justice?
Can't you have a bit of a sense of justice?
You know those girls
were sexually harassed.
Ms. Luo and Ms. Qiu did their best.
How could you still say that?
Xia Shu.
We indeed lost this case.
So what?
The path of justice is never straightforward.
You've watched too many TV dramas.
You're the one who's watched too many TV dramas.
When things went awry
for Luo Yingzi in court,
you seemed the happiest.
Why were you so delighted when our own side lost?
I think you just wanted our law firm to lose face.
Why are you coming at me?
Me? Happy?
Don't think I didn't see it.
Your smile reached your ears.
I really look down on people like you.
Ms. Fang.
You can't admit fault. You're not wrong.
Xia Shu.
We're just summarizing our work.
We lost the case.
We need to learn from it.
Sit down.
I'm so disappointed in you.
Xia Shu.
Please don't mind.
She's still too young.
How could you make her a partner before she even matured?
Han, what do you mean?
If you don’t want her to stay in the Criminal Defense Department,
she can join me.
I want her.
What did I say?
What did you say?
We indeed lost the case,
but we had already
foreseen this outcome beforehand.
As a lawyer,
aside from making money,
it's more important
to uphold the fairness and justice of the law.
These young people
insisted on taking this case,
and I agreed
and supported it.
Whatever consequences arise,
I'll take responsibility.
Don't mock them.
The enthusiasm of the young
needs protection and support, everyone.
Ms. Luo. Ms. Qiu.
Ms. Fang wants to see you.
Okay. Thank you.
Ms. Fang.
Come in.
You want to see me?
Do you have anything to tell me?
I should have listened to you
and only let her testify,
not appear in court.
Ms. Fang.
I was wrong.
It's good that you've recognized it.
It's all in the past.
Let's focus on what needs to be done next.
But I still feel uneasy.
After all,
everyone knows this thing did happen, right?
It's not embarrassing enough for you?
It's all in the past.
Don't mention it again.
Even if the client comes back,
don't bring it up again, understand?
I'll leave then.
Ms. Fang.
on my first day here,
in the lobby,
you said those things to us.
You said…
Face the reality, Yingzi.
♫I'm following♫
♫Where the wind blows♫
♫Chasing the sun and soil♫
♫Growing freely♫
♫The wind says♫
♫Keep chasing♫
♫Be a true believer♫
Qiu Hua, where are you?
Let's discuss the next steps
when you have time.
♫And don't be distracted♫
Yingzi, I have something to do outside.
I'll talk to you later.
Sorry, Ms. Tian.
Have you been working in Mr. Yang's company?
I was in another department.
I just transferred to Mr. Yang's office not long ago.
Aunt, did you get stuck in traffic?
It was fine.
Hello, Mrs. Yang.
Don't call me Mrs. Yang.
My surname is Tian. Just call me Ms. Tian.
Please have a seat.
♫But there will always be curves♫
♫More steps♫
♫Night is just the morning fog♫
♫Let him go♫
♫I have my stars to love♫
♫I left in a hurry♫
♫Be your gentle light♫
♫Freedom♫
Cheers, Mrs. Liu.
You scared me.
Don't touch me.
-I’ll sue you for sexual harassment.
-I’m sorry.
Another drink for her. It's on me.
Okay.
Thanks, but no thanks.
I can afford this little bar tab.
Waiter, I don't want it.
Give him a drink on my tab.
Everyone can pay for it.
Why do you always treat me like this?
Because of that case?
Come on. It's just a case.
How about this?
You take me as your mentor,
and I'll teach you how to handle lawsuits.
I think you have potential.
Teach me how to handle lawsuits?
Don't be so arrogant.
You're just unscrupulous.
It's easy to learn to be unscrupulous.
Is this how you lost a case without grace?
Chen Shuo.
A word?
You changed your girlfriend in only a few days.
I'm impressed.
Girls chasing after me are lining up.
I can't get rid of them.
What should I do?
What's her name this time?
Is it Lili or Fangfang?
Qianqian, a flight attendant.
Cool.
Changing so frequently,
aren't you afraid of getting struck by lightning?
I'm still enjoying it.
Chen Shuo.
Who's this?
Let me introduce.
No need.
Chen Shuo.
We've been separated for so long.
Can you stop pestering me?
Goodbye, Qianqian.
What?
She and I...
Hello, Qiu Hua.
Hello, Yingzi.
Where are you?
Come back quickly.
I have something to tell you.
Are you a psycho?
Don't you know what time it is now?
It's almost ten.
Why are you still working overtime?
Working is for a better life.
If you can't sleep,
I'll pick you up and have a drink with you.
Come back soon.
I'll wait for you in the office.
Hurry up.
You're really nuts.
Ms. Qiu.
You're back.
Listen.
You
should really learn from me.
Even if I got beaten up,
I still dressed up and went out for a drink.
Yang Weida is doomed.
What?
He'll be deprived of everything.
He'll be broke.
Why?
His wife.
Come on. Sit down.
I'm telling you.
We will have a big case.
If we handle it well,
we can make a lot of money.
Wait, who will pay for it?
Mrs. Yang.
Wait, Qiu Hua.
What are you talking about?
I don't understand.
Do you remember
when we went to meet Yang Weida,
he had a new secretary?
Tian.
Mr. Yang.
Serve tea for the two lawyers.
Okay.
You mean the girl surnamed Tian?
Yes.
It was her.
I noticed her back then.
If even Guo Yu couldn't escape
Yang Weida's harassment,
she definitely couldn't either.
So, I kept an eye on her,
checked her background in secret,
and asked Guo Yu privately.
It turns out,
she's Mrs. Yang's niece,
also surnamed Tian.
No way.
What's wrong with Mrs. Yang?
Isn't she feeding her family
into the lion's den?
Exactly.
There could be two possibilities.
One is that
Mrs. Yang knows nothing,
and the other is that she knew everything
and intentionally placed her niece beside Yang Weida
to monitor him.
Think about it.
Yang Weida's secretaries have been changing
like a revolving door these years.
Right,.
The security camera in his office
couldn't be installed by himself, right?
It must be installed by his wife.
This woman
is really ruthless.
Qiu Hua, you are a genius.
There's more.
I secretly contacted Mrs. Yang
through Tian.
At first, she didn't say anything.
As soon as our trial was over,
she contacted me immediately.
It turned out to be exactly as I guessed.
Mrs. Yang knew about Yang Weida's bad habits a long time ago.
She hid it
because she had her own purpose.
What's her purpose?
This company belongs to Yang Weida,
but she wants a divorce.
So she has to get evidence
of Yang Weida's cheating on her and sexual harassment.
That way, she can negotiate a good price.
That's it.
Yang Weida founded this company.
Yang Weida is a major shareholder,
with him as the majority shareholder holding 35%.
His wife holds 7%.
Divorce is not her goal.
Her true goal
is to strip him of all his assets.
This woman is really something.
She hesitated before
because she was afraid
it wasn't enough to strip him clean.
It depends on what you think, Ms. Tian.
Do you want to
spend the rest of your life
with a cheater,
or choose to leave him
and start a new life?
Actually,
marriage doesn't necessarily have to involve a real husband and wife relationship.
You can consider this marriage
as a joint venture.
As long as it maximizes the benefits,
everyone can go their separate ways.
It depends on the risks
your partner brings
to the joint venture.
This incident with Guo Yu
should be a risk warning.
As long as your husband doesn't change his ways,
this risk will always exist.
This time it's Guo Yu; next time, it could be someone else.
Will your husband
be so lucky next time?
Besides,
you might just feel that
the current public opinion is favorable to your husband.
But you should understand,
public opinion is a fickle thing.
It can change at any time.
Your joint venture could be in danger
when that happens.
That makes sense.
If I choose to divorce,
what can you help me get from him?
What do you want from him?
I want everything,
his shares,
all of them transferred to my name.
Can you do that?
It depends on how much evidence you have.
A lot.
More than just Guo Yu
has been harassed.
Anyone who entered his office alone
was harassed.
None of the girls funded by the Weidai Foundation
were spared.
Is this enough evidence?
If that's the case,
personally,
I suggest not going to court.
Negotiate with him privately.
I agree with that.
I know him.
You can't push him too hard;
otherwise, he might react recklessly.
He'll either protect his reputation
or his money.
As for what I want,
you know best now.
So, we can only negotiate with him privately,
and use this evidence to force him to give up his shares
and leave with nothing.
You're impressive.
Ms. Tian, you're even more impressive.
Are you willing to take my case?
Of course.
How much do you want?
One million.
You have quite an appetite.