[English subtitles are available]
[The Fearless Season 1]
[Episode 17]
Are you looking for me?
Do you want me to handle a lawsuit for you?
That's definitely a no-go.
We have a conflict of interest.
No, it's not about that.
There's something
that's just perfect for a unscrupulous lawyer to handle.
Please wait a moment.
Bro, how about this?
This is my sister.
Do me a favor.
Wait in the meeting room for a while.
Say please.
Please.
I'm doing this for the sake of my brother.
Wimpy guy.
You two seem to have a funny relationship.
Well, why's he here?
One of my people got into some trouble,
so I asked him for help.
Yingzi.
It's not that I didn't want to ask you.
Well, my man is a bit flirtatious.
When he sees a girl, he…
I know.
I appreciate that, Mr. Zhou.
So, let's talk about Lanlan.
Mr. Zhou.
I hope you don't mind my straightforwardness.
You have a family,
and what you did in this matter was just not right.
Whether indirectly or directly,
Lanlan
got to know you through me,
and it caused a lot of trouble.
I'm in a difficult spot too.
I‘m here today
to ask you about
her saying she wants to marry you.
What's your plan?
Marry me?
Yingzi, to be honest with you,
I've never had any interest in her.
She threw herself at me.
What could I do?
Since she insisted, I had to do something.
She's serious about this,
even wants to have your child.
You believe that?
Can she have a child?
Your wife took people to the school to beat her up,
causing a huge scandal.
It was a disgrace to all the teachers.
I know.
You don't know about my wife.
She usually acts like a sick cat,
but when she gets angry,
she's a tiger.
At the end of the day, this is your fault.
If you don't like Lanlan,
can you end your relationship with her soon, okay?
My bad.
I'll end it right away.
I have your word.
Alright, with your words, I feel reassured.
Well,
but your wife
did beat her.
How are you gonna solve this?
It's already happened, what can I do?
Does she want money?
I will pay for it.
Since you mentioned that,
and I admitted it.
I can pay her 300,000 or 500,000 yuan.
It's up to you.
Lanlan isn't after the money.
She wants you.
Don't you know that?
Mr. Zhou.
Regardless of her motives of approaching you,
you shouldn't talk about her like that.
Money
can't buy a girl's dignity.
I hope you can
handle this matter properly.
Don't make things difficult for everyone.
I don't have any other business.
I'll go meet Mr. Chen.
Let me take you there.
Okay.
Yingzi, it's here.
Do you want me to accompany you?
No, thanks.
I'll talk to him alone.
Bro.
We are family.
Try to settle things without resorting to violence.
Don't worry.
Hold on.
Let me finish this round.
It's reward time.
Got it.
What's up, Ms. Luo?
What do you wanna talk to me about?
Even if we have something to discuss,
it should be in the courtroom.
Unscrupulous Chen, you're really...
What did you call me?
Unscrupulous Chen.
Didn't you call yourself an unscrupulous lawyer?
So I give you the nickname,
Unscrupulous Chen.
That's a good name.
Do I need to go to the police station
to officially change my name to this?
As soon as possible.
Unscrupulous Chen, you're really something.
How dare you make money off Mr. Zhou?
Isn't Mr. Zhou’s money money?
I’m unscrupulous.
Why can't I?
I want to introduce a case to you.
You want to introduce a case to me?
Why?
Is it because I treated you to a meal
a few days ago
and you felt guilty?
I don't have time for that.
I just want a bad guy
to deal with another bad guy.
After thinking about it,
I found no one more suitable than you.
You're absolutely a perfect match.
No need for the preamble. Get to the point.
It's a case
worth thousands of millions in a way.
Luo Yingzi.
I'm definitely  more unscrupulous than you,
but I'm not as stupid as you.
If it's a case worth thousands of millions,
why are you handing me this big piece of cake?
Don't fool me.
Believe it or not,
I have a conflict of interest in this case,
so I can't take it.
But the client
wants us to introduce a lawyer
who is extremely unscrupulous,
that's why you are the perfect fit.
In your eyes,
I'm the most unscrupulous, huh?
Not necessarily.
It's still up for debate who's more unscrupulous.
It will be decided in the courtroom.
Fine.
Since you've put so much effort into it,
I'll consider taking the case.
What's the referral fee?
None at all.
It's against the rules.
Are you a hypocrite?
Who are you scolding?
I have just one condition.
One condition?
Anyway, there's no way to let me
cut you some slack in the banking case.
Listen.
I'm not that pathetic.
My condition is
you must win the case.
You also have to crush him completely,
leaving him no face at all.
Who do you hate so much?
The opposing lawyer
is my mentor,
Han Zhitong from our firm.
What?
From now on, I changed my name
to Unscrupulous Chen.
Unscrupulous Chen.
It's your turn.
Nice change on the name.
I'm not talking about that.
I mean she introduced a case to you.
You two are quite interesting.
What do you mean?
She named me Unscrupulous Chen.
Not about that.
No matter she praises or criticizes you, she's still the buyer.
I've also noticed
she's actually been interested in me for a long time.
But she might want to buy, and I may not want to sell.
I, Unscrupulous Chen, have some taste.
Come on.
Don't act in front of me.
Who knows who is the buyer or seller?
Do you think we should take this case?
Of course.
Why not?
I'm Unscrupulous Chen.
What wouldn't I dare to take?
It's worth millions.
Why would I refuse the money?
Wait, bro.
I'm considering it for your sake.
Sure it's a case worth millions,
but ruining your lifelong reputation
for such a case
is not worth it.
How about this?
Let me take on some of that burden for you.
I'm unscrupulous too.
We can split it 50-50.
Bro, you're really something.
80-20, no more than that.
No, 70-30.
Or...
80-20.
Bullseye.
Dinner is on you.
Qiu Hua.
What's wrong?
It's time to fight fire with fire.
I found someone even more shameless,
more despicable,
and more unscrupulous than Han.
Who?
Unscrupulous Chen.
Who is Unscrupulous Chen?
Chen Shuo, from Dazheng Law Firm.
I gave him this nickname.
Isn't he handling my bank case
and trying to take away my house?
Is there anyone more unscrupulous than him?
So, what do you think about letting him deal with Han?
I'm even proud of myself
for coming up with this plan.
I love this kind of lively drama,
full of chaos.
You don't agree?
Yes.
What made you think of him?
I just went to Mr. Zhou
to talk about my housekeeper.
I met him there.
After I told him this matter,
he was quite interested.
Then it was settled.
Did Mr. Wei agree?
I just called
both of them,
and we made an appointment.
I don't want to
miss a minute of this big show.
You have to go too.
Since both of them are interested,
just let them meet.
I won't go then.
No.
You have to be there
to witness this great moment.
It'll be a brilliant drama directed by me,
and the curtain is about to rise.
You must go.
I have something else to do.
What is it?
You are always busy.
You must go.
Listen.
Even if we are not Mr. Wei's lawyer,
we have to settle
the rest of the things properly, right?
You're back.
I'm exhausted.
How did your play the role of daughter-in-law?
Don't mention it.
It was a nightmare.
I've decided.
I'll never get married.
Tell me about it.
I've never seen so many rules.
When we ate,
my boyfriend kicked me under the table four times.
For a bun,
I had to break it into half,
then I had to wait to eat
before his parents started eating.
After they finished, I had to say,
"Dad, Mom,
I'm done.
Take your time."
Gosh, it's so scary.
And the bathroom.
Well.
No.
I can't say anymore.
I can't eat if I keep talking.
Well, you could be more flexible.
Say, don't stay at their house
and find a hotel nearby. Problem solved.
That's exactly what I did.
I knew that I couldn't stay there after the first day.
That bathroom...
I wouldn't use it even if you paid me.
So the next day,
I found a hotel in the town to stay.
But his parents are pitiful.
He told me that ,
to send him to college,
his older sister and younger sister
had to drop out.
The whole family supported him to go to college.
His dad's back has been already bad
from working hard,
while his mom's eyes shed tears against wind.
Let me guess.
You must have given money to them.
What else could I do?
I had to help them improve their lives.
No, Xia Shu.
There are many people in this world who shed tears against wind,
and countless others with back problems.
Can you help them all?
If you don't plan to marry your boyfriend,
it's better to avoid getting too involved
with his family sooner rather than later.
But I saw it.
How pitiful they are.
Forget it.
It's up to you.
Qiu Hua, it's a deal.
What deal?
We got a case?
Let me join you.
I'm afraid you can't.
It's the case you mentioned before
but couldn't handle,
so it's taken by someone else.
That divorce case?
I thought it was a murder case.
Well,
those two snacks on the windowsill have expired.
Don't eat them. Throw them away.
Alright.
Dear lawyers.
I can't blame others for this matter.
It was all my fault.
I hesitated back then,
and missed the chance to collaborate with you.
I wasn't like this before.
When I was at the company,
projects worth billions
would be resolved
in one or two hours of meeting.
Look at me now.
Whether in personal matters or business,
I'm always overtaken by fear
and hesitant.
I don't even know how I become this.
It's all because of that women.
Mr. Wei.
After listening to your words,
I can totally understand you.
I really do.
But Mr. Wei,
I think
we should leave the past behind.
Why?
Because the person we're introducing to you
will definitely complete the mission
to defeat Han.
Defeat him?
You see,
this is a professional term
among lawyers.
In simpler terms,
it means winning this lawsuit.
I got it.
If I do hire this lawyer,
can I show him the litigation strategy
you two figured out for me?
Why not?
If he thinks it's viable
after reviewing it,
feel free to use it.
Because, to be honest,
we won't be handling this case anymore.
Keeping it in our hands won't do any good.
Giving a rose to others
will leave fragrance on our hands, right?
- So why don't we do it?
-Right.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
How much consultation fee
do you charge, then?
What are you talking about, Mr. Wei?
Bringing up money is too formal.
No.
I must pay no matter how much it is.
This is our fate.
We just want to defeat…
Well...
Winning the lawsuit is the top priority.
Thank you both.
Here, let me pour the tea for both of you.
-Thank you so much.
-Here you are.
Have some more tea.
By the way, there's something I'd like to discuss with you two.
I wonder if you're interested.
Please go ahead.
I happen to have a business partner.
He has a case and
is looking for a lawyer now.
Are you interested?
What kind of case is it?
He told me it's a patent case.
Have you dealt with such cases before?
What a coincidence.
We are currently
working on a patent case.
Really?
Then I've found the right people.
But
this case is not a big case.
It's just worth a few million.
Of course.
I was going to tell you earlier,
but I was afraid you might
think this is too small.
No. Mr. Wei.
Actually, we have to thank you, Mr. Wei.
After all, you introduced the case to us.
When do you think
is convenient for us to meet with the other party
to see if it's suitable for us to take on?
If it's suitable,
we'll take it.
Ms. Luo, what's suitable or not?
Just take it.
He specifically asked me
to help him
find a reliable lawyer.
-Since you two have helped me so much.
-Mr. Wei.
The more it's like this,
the more we should live up to
the trust others have in us.
As lawyers,
we have to take a look at this case first,
and see if we are confident to take it.
First,
we need to live up to the trust of the client.
Most importantly, we must live up to
your faith in us, right?
Great.
If all the lawyers in the world were like you two,
it would be great.
Well...
Why hasn't he arrived yet?
How about I go pick him up at the door?
It's okay. Maybe there's a traffic jam.
Right.
By the way, Ms. Qiu.
I have something you need to know.
Can I have a word with you outside?
Mr. Wei, please enjoy the tea.
Okay.
Enjoy your tea.
Come on.
Regarding financial matters in the future,
it's better for you not to talk about it.
Just let me handle it.
Have you got this rich?
Why didn't you accept his money?
I forgot.
I was only thinking about dealing with Han.
Well,
didn't you see
the immediate returns from this?
The patent case, Qiu Hua.
I need you to pinch me to see if it's true.
You really did that?
It hurts.
The patent case is true,
but can we win it?
You're really good at boasting.
Well, what cases can't be handled?
We can learn if we don't know how.
He just said it's worth a few million.
Two million is also a few million.
Nine million is also a few million.
Alright, don't bother calculating now.
It'll go south if you calculate it.
You called me out here just for this?
No, I was afraid that if I continued to sit in there,
my sneaky expressions thinking of getting rich
might show up.
So I had to come out
to calm myself down.
You're quite the sneak when it comes to getting rich,
but you have to get rich first.
Well, I just want to enjoy the thrill for a bit.
Unscrupulous Chen is coming.
Give me your bag.
Wait for while.
Half an hour.
Disgusting.
Ms. Luo.
What took you so long?
I'm not late.
I've thought about it.
Although I love money,
a gentleman loves money in a proper way.
Unscrupulous Chen.
Don't tarnish the word "gentleman", okay?
Then let's say a sneak loves money.
Even a sneak has a proper way of acquiring it.
If I take on this case,
you'll be the middleman,
and I'll give you a commission.
Regardless of how much I earn,
I'll give you 15%.
After all,
some people still have car loans to repay.
I really admire you
for turning the lawyer's profession
into a business.
But do I look like a broker to you?
Ms. Luo.
Why are you acting so self-righteous?
If I were you,
15% is not enough, I'll make it 20%.
20% doesn't work, 30%.
30% doesn't work, or I'll leave.
20% is fine.
Well,
you're so easy to talk to.
let me tell you.
I'd rather not make this money,
I'd like to see you two fighting.
Qiu Hua.
Ms. Qiu.
20%.
20%, okay?
Long time no see.
After you.
Look at him.
Mr. Wei.
Come here.
Let me introduce Mr. Chen to you.
Hello.
-Hello, Mr. Chen.
-Mr. Wei.
Come here.
Take a sit.
You can go.
We'll take care of ourselves.
Thank you.
Mr. Wei.
You can rest assured
about Mr. Chen.
In terms of professionalism,
he's absolutely on par with Mr. Han.
Your recommendation is surely correct.
Didn't I tell you before?
The reason Ms. Qiu and I
failed to take charge of your case
was we were set up by someone.
So now,
you don't need a good person.
You need someone who is more
manipulative than Mr. Han.
Mr. Chen is definitely qualified.
Mr. Wei.
My name is Chen Shuo.
Just think about it. You're up against Mr. Han.
You need a lawyer
more unscrupulous than Mr. Han.
It is up to you to decide
whether to hire him or not,
but my suggestion is
you'd better do so.
Ms. Qiu, let's leave it to them.
Okay.
Chen Shuo,
I have to remind you.
Use your intelligence
where it's needed,
not elsewhere.
Don't worry. You said I'm professional.
-Bye.
-Have a seat.
Bye, Ms. Luo, Ms. Qiu.
Come here.
Take a sit, Mr. Chen.
Let's get straight to the point.
Okay.
Here are all the files.
She's just waiting there?
I'm really impressed by Chen's taste.
Not bad. This girl looks good.
I forgot something.
What's wrong?
I forgot to ask Mr. Wei for his friend's number.
Wait a minute.
Forget it.
I should play it cool.
I'll ask for it tomorrow.
Let's go.
That's basically the situation.
Mr. Chen.
Do you have any ideas for this case?
Annulment.
Haven't you been under constant threats?
So, that agreement
must not be your true intention.
Mr. Chen.
You do have an extraordinary insight.
It's like heroes see eye to eye.
What do you mean?
I mean, your thinking just now
is the same as Ms. Luo and Ms. Qiu's.
The same as theirs?
Yes.
If it's the same as theirs,
then I need to change my approach.
I can't have the same approach
as two young lawyers.
It would lower me to their level.
Well,
Mr. Chen, I didn't mean that.
I didn't mean to degrade you to their level.
I mean what great minds think alike.
Besides,
the approach you suggested just now is yours.
And I also think
it's the only possible approach to win.
Let's proceed with this approach.
Let me think.
Here's the thing.
This case is actually quite difficult.
Well...
It doesn't mean
there is no possibility to win.
If you're entrusting me with this case,
we have to sign the agreement now.
Sure.
We can sign it.
Okay.
How do you want us to sign the agreement?
Now, considering the current situation,
I think it's best
if we do it in two steps.
If we only file for your divorce
right now,
it will definitely be unfavorable for you.
First,
let's nullify that equity transfer agreement.
Then we can proceed with the divorce and asset division.
This way, it's most advantageous for you.
Considering this,
we're dealing with two cases.
We need to sign two agreements simultaneously.
For the first one, I'll charge you 200,000.
For the second one, it's dependent on the value of the target.
Mr. Chen,
how about this?
Can we sign these two agreements separately?
I mean,
if you win the first one,
I'll definitely
entrust you with the second one.
No.
No way.
If so, Mr. Wei,
I'm sorry. Please ask for someone else.
To be honest,
the first one is only 200,000 yuan.
It's practically a free gift.
What I'm interested in is the second case.
So for the second one,
I will definitely ask for a higher price.
Please understand.
Okay, let's sign then.
No problem.
By the way,
I have a proposal
of the litigation strategy
from Ms. Qiu and Ms. Luo,
and I've got their consent
that you can take a look at it as a reference.
No need.
I have all my ideas in mind.
-Thanks, but no thanks.
-It’s okay.
If you have time, take a look.
You can keep it or discard it.
Just take it.
Okay, I'll take it.
Good.
Okay, here are the agreements.
Okay.
Tingting,
let me know what gift you want.
I've just made a big deal.
How big is it? Show me.
It's confidential.
[Litigation Strategy]
I'm hungry.
Let's grab some late-night snacks.
Chen Shuo, I'm hungry.
Just drive wherever you want to eat.
What about you?
Don't worry about me.
That girl, Lanlan,
is giving me a headache.
You know,
with her and this Mr. Zhou thing...
You don't have to worry too much about it.
They are adults.
They should be responsible for their behaviors.
I think if Mr. Zhou
is willing to solve this problem with money,
it may lead to a good result
for Lanlan.
But
what if Lanlan
does have feelings for Mr. Zhou?
If he resolves it with money,
wouldn't that be an insult to her?
If Mr. Zhou had no money,
would Lanlan still want him that much?
Believe me.
There's nothing new in this world.
Maybe that's what she's looking for.
Hello?
Who's speaking?
♫There are many things in memory♫
Chen Shuo.
♫Using the past to move on♫
It's you.
What's wrong with you, Luo Yingzi?
♫We♫
We've known each other for so long.
How come you haven't saved my number?
♫We have great chemistry♫
Why should I save the number
of an unscrupulous lawyer?
I want to thank you.
You introduced a big deal to me.
♫Among all the people I've lost♫
You're welcome.
I just want to sit on the sidelines
♫I miss myself the most♫
and watch how a bad guy
defeat another bad guy.
♫No pain, no fear♫
Fine.
Well,
I've read the litigation strategy
♫Using silence as a replacement♫
you wrote for Mr. Wei.
It's not bad.
♫After missing you, I didn't say much♫
How about we find some time to meet face-to-face
and discuss it further?
♫I once tried my best♫
It might not be necessary.
♫So it's not a regret♫
Your cunning mind
seems to be enough.
You don't need off-the-field guidance.
♫People born to be optimistic♫
Also,
please don't keep calling and bothering me in the future.
♫Always heal themselves in the deep night♫
Bye.
Wait.
I just want to tell you that
♫I always believe the resolution of tomorrow♫
I've signed the agreement with Wei Tongren.
Fine.
What does it have to do with me?
♫Is my superpower♫
How can it not concern you?
Won't you get a commission?
♫I crossed mountains and ridges to find a solution♫
Well, let me tell you how much it is.
It's 200,000 yuan.
♫After walking a long way, I realized it was already in the past♫
What?
No way.
You're a money chaser.
♫The clear sky appears after the rain♫
How can you be satisfied
♫What is fairness?♫
with only 200,000 yuan?
I did sign the agreement for 200,000 yuan.
But…
we signed two cases altogether.
For the first,
since you want 20% commission,
I signed at a low price on purpose.
As for the second one,
the amount is confidential.
Oh my god.
♫What happened hysterically♫
I can't believe
♫There's no need for proof to leave♫
you split the case
only to cut down the commission fees for us.
♫I once tried my best♫
Unscrupulous Chen.
♫So it's not a regret♫
Han is definitely no match for you.
Since you admitted
♫Missing you also became a part of the scenery♫
you had split the case,
I have to tell you,
♫It's okay if I didn't do well♫
both cases are considered as referrals from us.
So, when it comes to the second case,
♫If the world seems crowded♫
no matter how much you charge,
you still have to share it with us.
♫Stumbling♫
We'll have to talk about it then.
♫I walk alone♫
I can't promise you now.
♫Waiting with warm tears for a response from persistence♫
Thank you. Bye.
♫I'll find that complete self again♫
♫I will love me♫
♫Let's talk about fairness♫
This case is interesting.
The people involved are more interesting.
Do you think I'm having bad luck lately?
Why do I keep running into shameless people
like this?
You have no idea that
he asked Mr. Wei for only 200,000 yuan
only to cut down the commission for us.
But you just said that
it has nothing to do with you whether they signed or not.
I was just trying to be cool.
Besides,
I really didn't want his money.
Why not?
Are you afraid of breaking the rules?
I just feel
when you start to be a lawyer,
you shouldn't be solely focused on money.
I'm sorry, Qiu Hua.
I should have discussed with you beforehand.
After all, you are in urgent need
for money.
I am desperate for money,
but as someone with debts,
you might probably be in much more urgent need than I am.
Since you can give up the immediate benefits
despite the urgency,
I can try to be less desperate.
Thank you, Qiu Hua.
Actually, I was forced
into this line of work.
But after entering this profession
and seeing lawyers
as undignified as Han,
I thought
I might not become
a very successful lawyer in the future,
but I must work hard
to be a decent lawyer.
To dignity.
Cheers.
Lanlan.
Ms. Luo.
Have a seat.
What would you like to drink?
Why do you want to see me?
Well,
I just
picked two good books
for you.
They're helpful for your study.
Did you call me just for books?
Lanlan.
Well,
about Mr. Zhou,
I feel
he's unlikely
to divorce his wife because of you.
He feels sorry to you
on this matter,
so he wants
to compensate you financially.
Can you
accept it?
If he doesn't want to divorce for me,
why did he seduce me in the first place?
Is he trying to get away without any consequences?
Ms. Luo, please tell him
I don't want money.
I just want him.
I also think what he did was wrong,
and he admitted it himself.
When I met him, I criticized him too.
That's why he said he wanted to make a financial compensation.
What financial compensation?
He thinks I'm a prostitute?
Of course not.
But obviously, he's not worthy of your love.
First, he has a family.
Besides,
I don't think he's really into you.
Actually,
I didn't ask him for the money.
It was his offer to
end the relationship with the money.
So I don't think
you should waste your
youth and love on Mr. Zhou.
Fine.
How much is he going to give me?
He...
Anyway,
he said
he can give you 500,000 yuan.
I want 10 million.
Lanlan, are you serious?
Well…
It's such a big gap.
I mean it.
Do you think my youth
is so worthless?
No.
I don't think youth should
be equated with value.
Well,
you see,
it doesn't matter what I think.
It's about whether he can give you that money
or whether he agrees or not.
If he doesn't agree, he shall marry me.
I'm an adult now.
You don't need to worry about
my affairs with him.
Lanlan, you said
you are an adult.
You should take care of yourself.
You have helped me before.
Now that you're in trouble,
I want to offer my help.
But if you say so,
I won't intervene.
Actually, I can't.
Deal with it yourself, okay?
Okay, don't worry.
Well,
I've transferred your salary this month
to your account.
You don't need to.
I have been busy taking classes
and done little work recently.
Besides, you've already paid for the tuition.
You don't have to pay me anymore.
No, we had a deal earlier.
If there's nothing else, I'm leaving.
She doesn't want me to get involved in this anymore.
Just take care of yourself.
What does she want?
She doesn't want to break up with you so easily.
You'd better be prepared.
She doesn't want to end it?
So do I.
Let the game continue.
I have a lot of time,
and I have nothing else to do.
Yingzi,
don't worry about this anymore.
Don't let it bother you.
Yingzi.
Are you busy?
I just bought some books on patent cases,
and we have a bit of work to do.
Can you do me a favor?
Go ahead.
Today is my turn to handle legal consultations,
but I'm feeling a bit unwell.
The client is still in the meeting room.
Could you talk to her on my behalf?
Are you all right?
Do you need a break?
I'm fine.
I just need some water.
Okay.
I'll go.
Go have some rest.
I'll go then.
Hello.
Are you the one who consulted with Lawyer Qiu earlier?
Please have a seat.
Ms. Qiu isn't feeling well,
so I'm here to replace her.
My surname is Luo.
You can call me Ms. Luo.
What's your name?
My name is Guo Yu.
[Guo Yu]
So, why are you here today?
Do you need advice on any legal issues?
I want to ask...
I want…
It's quite normal here.
Actually, if you haven't made up your mind,
you can always come back later.
I work in Weida Group.
You know Weida Group, don't you?
My boss is Yang Weida.
I don't know much about Weida Group,
but…
Is Yang Weida
an online celebrity,
the former youth leader
who started his own business at a young age
and frequently sponsored students
in impoverished areas and children who dropped out of school?
He made presentations everywhere. Is that him?
It's him.
I'm his assistant.
You're very lucky.
Really?
I thought so at first.
After he succeeded,
he continued to contribute to society,
establishing several funds,
including one specifically for supporting female college students.
for supporting female college students.
[Opening Ceremony of Weida Foundation's Dream Project of Supporting Village Girls]
Actually,
I also received help from this fund
to attend college.
It's challenging for rural kids to find jobs.
After graduation,
I couldn't find a job, so I wrote a letter to Mr. Yang.
Then,
I was hired by the company
to work for him.
Really?
He sounds like a good person.
A good person?
You really think so?
I thought so at first.
What's wrong?
Well,
let me get you some more water.
Guo Yu.
Are you okay?
If there's something, take your time and tell me.
He harassed me.
I shouldn't have said it.
After all, he helped me a lot.
But I can't stand it anymore.
Calm down.
You…
Tell me how he harassed you.
I don't know how to put it.
I work around him,
and initially, he seemed really nice to me.
But later on,
things started feeling off.
He often sent me
these suggestive messages.
What kind of suggestive messages?
Can you be more specific?
Like,
he advised me to be more open,
asked if I have a boyfriend,
and if I'm a virgin.
Well,
it's really inappropriate.
He even asked about my bra size
and the color.
Hold on.
Guo Yu, look.
Are you talking about this man?
Yes.
It's said this woman is his wife.
Have you seen her?
Yes, it's his wife.
She's the vice president of our company.
She's very capable.
Actually,
she's been running the company
for the most part.
Guo Yu,
I may have started working a few years earlier than you.
Based on my years of experience,
in society,
there's a type of successful guy
who loves to throw around some verbal advantages
in front of younger girls.
It's all about showing off
their so-called social superiority.
But when you feel offended,
they quickly claim
it's just a joke
or without malicious intent.
Is sticking a hand inside someone's clothes
considered a joke?
Moreover, he enjoys watching porn in the office
when he's alone.
Sometimes when I go to deliver files
while he's watching,
he pulls me to watch together.
At times like this,
he would get his hands all over me.
slapping my butt
and grabbing my thighs.
At first, I thought I was overthinking,
but he's crossing the line more and more.
When there's no one around,
he gets touchy-feely,
hugs me,
and kisses me.
Mr. Han, what are you doing?
How about we booking a hotel room tonight?
How long has this been going on?
I've been at the company for almost a year,
and it's been going on for about half a year.
Half a year?
Then what took you so long to see us?
I didn't know who to turn to before,
and now I'm desperate.