You're hurt. You're hurt.
You're injured. You're injured. You're injured.
You're injured. You're injured. You're injured. You're injured. You're injured. You're injured.
It's just a minor injury. It's just a minor injury.
It's just a minor injury.
But I'm hurt and despised.
It's really disappointing.
Your Highness, if you're disappointed, you can take a look. I'll take a look at it.
Have more hot springs.
Nuannuan.
You've been a playboy for years.
He doesn't look like a playboy.
You've been taking off your clothes in the water
in the water.
You've wronged me.
This hot spring is special.
Other members are injured.
I come to borrow them from time to time.
But bathing with a beauty
I've never seen such a thing.
Then...
He's here. He's here.
She's here. She's here.
Your Highness.
Is this how you repay your savior?
That's how I treat swindlers.
Speaking of deceiving,
you and I are the same.
Then we have nothing to say.
Are you not even pretending now?
I still like
gentle and decent you.
What a pity.
I'm afraid
in the future.
Your Royal Highness is noble.
I'm a liar.
I don't deserve to sleep with you.
You'd better find a place to sleep tonight.
Don't go back to your room.
How bold.
than I thought.
Madam.
Your Highness.
She's so disrespectful to you.
why are you still coaxing her?
Because she has the secret of antidote.
Si Yao is tough.
He doesn’t take the advantage.
If we force it,
I'm afraid I won't get anything.
So now,
I can only coax him.
That's too unfair.
Compared to living,
is nothing.
Your Highness.
His Highness sent these here.
Throw them away.
What a pity.
These
were carefully selected by me.
Is there anything you like?
Are you still angry?
I'm afraid His Highness is annoyed now.
my unreasonable act.
I thought
why didn't you
send a gentle and obedient man?
You think too much.
Since I married you,
you're the only one I'm sure of.
There's no one else.
Princess Consort,
For the sake of my sincere apology,
don't be mad at me.
Don't forget
we are going to travel together.
Can you tell me
why did you help the nameless Pavilion
fight against your sister?
Why did you stop me
when I took action?
The two conflicts
the two conflicts?
There is only one answer
only one answer.
Because...
I want to live.
Okay.
Mother.
The informant said
Uncle Wang and that woman
had a quarrel.
He's been sleeping apart for the past few days.
But Uncle Wang is very attentive.
He tries to make her happy every day.
Chuan,
His relationship with the new princess
What do you think?
Mother.
I guess
that woman does have feelings for Uncle Wang.
Uncle Wang seems to be sincere to her.
Maybe
she can become a new chip
other than Madam Jin.
I didn't expect you to be so young.
You can't understand the love between men and women.
I'm stupid.
Please enlighten me.
Your uncle calls himself a playboy.
When did you see him so infatuated with a woman?
He acted too seriously
and too anxious.
He said he loves Si Yao.
He even contradicted me and wanted to marry her.
But after thinking about it,
the consequences of infuriating me.
how could he not know?
I didn't kill him,
doesn’t mean I won’t kill Si Yao.
If a man really loves a woman,
how could he let her
in danger?
So how much is his love
is true?
We need to verify it.
Mother is wise.
I can't catch up with you.
It's okay.
I'll teach you. I'll teach you. I'll teach you. I'll teach you.
My son...
will be the next master of Yunzhou.
But the most important thing now...
is to let Qinglin take good care of Prince Xuanping's Mansion.
and find clues about the assassin that day.
I will get rid of
of Nameless Pavilion.
Lady Kam!
Ten years of devotion.
Eating vegetarian and praying Buddha.
I really admire you.
Your son should have visited you a few days ago.
But he didn't come.
Don't you want to know why?
As long as my Xie Yuan is safe,
it doesn't matter
doesn't matter.
He is my only brother.
Of course I want him to be safe.
So,
he got married a few days ago.
I attended the wedding myself.
Don't you want to know
which daughter he chose in the end?
He has his own choice.
I don't need to ask.
Yes.
He refused the marriage I selected for him.
But he chose
a courtesan.
If the late king finds out,
if the late King finds out?
Father.
The doctor said you coughed blood again today.
How do you feel now?
I’m here.
It’s my fault.
I haven't found the prescription to cure you.
If there is a way,
I can be healthy.
Would you like to give it a try?
I'll do anything for you.
Okay.
Good boy.
Have a seat.
You must be tired from running all the way here.
Here.
Have some tea.
As for the rest,
later.
Just because of your filial piety to me,
when I get better,
I will treat you well.
What did you give me?
Father.
Ouch!
It hurts.
This is Gu Gu.
It can only be used between blood relatives.
You just took the Ziye Poison.
After I take the poison,
your life
is connected to me.
You can bear the pain for me.
The pain of flesh and blood.
You...
Why are you doing this to me?
Isn't this
what you want to see?
Didn't you just say that you would do anything?
Now is the time for you to be filial to me.
Xie Ciyuan is also your child.
You are a daughter.
You'll marry someone else sooner or later.
But the resentment is different.
He is the future hope of Yunzhou.
How...
Don't be afraid. I'll kill you. I'll kill you! I'll kill you! I'll kill you! I'll kill you!