I heard that you went to Qifeng Restaurant
you went to Qifeng Pavilion today.
His Highness has been having insomnia lately.
I'm worried.
I heard that Xiaoyu
has a secret sleeping incense.
It's the favorite flavor
in Qifeng Pavilion.
That's why
go ask her for incense.
I did do something wrong.
Are you angry, Your Highness?
Prince Xuanping doesn't have so many rules.
Just do whatever you want.
Just do it.
Master Lin,
in the sachet,
there is also a very rare dragon knot grass.
Since you care so much about me,
I should return the favor.
I'll take you to a good place.
Qinglin
is either monitoring me
or Xie Ciyuan.
We can't go on like this.
We have to find a chance to get him away.
Your Highness.
Where are you going?
I'm taking her out
alone.
Are you going to follow me even if you don't know?
Boss.
Have you seen this girl?
No.
Buns for sale!
Fresh steamed buns
Come and have a look.
Sorry.
I mistook you for someone else.
How did you find this place?
This is too hidden.
This is a secret place
my mother gave me in childhood.
I've never brought anyone here.
So,
no one knows this place.
You're the first one.
Why are you so nice to me?
Because the queen
is different from others.
You're glib-tongued.
Maybe
the entrance to Laundry Valley is in Longyu Mountain.
I don't know
if she can remember something.
What are you looking at?
Look, Your Highness.
It's a herb
It's called winter.
It usually grows at the top of the cliff.
It needs to be underneath the trees.
under the trees.
I didn't expect to meet you here.
It has such a good growth.
Since it's so rare,
I'll take it back for you.
No.
The autumn result
Flowers bloom in spring.
When it blooms,
is the real winter.
You know so much about herbs.
Did she learn medicine?
Yes.
I heard there is a mysterious place
there seems to be a mysterious place
called Laundry Valley.
People in the valley are good at medicine.
They are all rare talents.
Have you
heard of it?
Laundry Valley?
Princess Consort, do you remember anything?
Should I remember something?
For example,
your background,
Or
your past
your past.
Princess Consort.
I don't remember.
I don't remember anything.
Okay.
Don't think about it if you can't remember.
I'll take you back now.
Your Highness.
A few days ago, in that carriage,
in the carriage a few days ago.
We have to find them as soon as possible.
I know.
Master Lin has sent someone to investigate.
I guess that car
will go south along Lu City.
Deer City is the most prosperous place
That is the most bustling city
and the most convenient city for transportation.
If those girls were abducted,
Lu City
is definitely a perfect central location.
It's easy to transport people around.
According to the news from Nameless Pavilion,
the guard of Lu City
seems to work for Li Rui.
Li Rui is a great minister.
and powerful.
If this is related to him,
we need to find out the truth.
I'm warning you.
Don't think about going out when you come in.
If anyone runs away,
I'll kill him.
I have plenty of ways
to deal with you.
That girl
crying and looking for death.
So what?
You have to receive my guests.
So,
I advise you to behave yourself.
In this way,
you'll suffer less.
Who are you?
Sir.
Please save us.
Please.
Don't worry.
I'll send someone to send you home.
Thank you, sir.
Recently,
several batches of women who were abducted from Pingcheng
and sent to Lu City.
didn't find you.
I’m incompetent.
Please punish me.
It’s not your fault.
No one wants Mianwan to die.
Over the past year,
we've been inquiring about her.
As long as the body is not found,
that means Mianwan is still alive.
I will find Young Master.
How about this?
Send those girls
back to Pingcheng safely.
No matter what,
I couldn't find my daughter.
It's a good thing
to save someone's daughter.
Your Highness.
I had a nightmare.
I'm so scared.
I'm here.
Madam.
Don't be afraid.
Let's go.
A man
listening to the corners every day.
How shameless.
In order to thank him,
let alone let him listen to the corners,
Even if we let him jump off the city tower,
he won't complain.
He's gone.
Why are you still holding her?
What do you think I want?
Her expression
looks a little disappointed.
Get some rest.
I'm going out.
You...
Where are you going?
It's not a good idea
in the royal mansion.
I have to
out.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I was shocked by your charisma.
I was distracted.
Please forgive me.