Yes.
When I was young,
I had a childhood sweetheart.
But she was from out of town.
She left after a few days.
Back then, we gathered herbs on the mountain every day.
We sold them for silver
just to buy these snacks.
Aren't you the Master's son?
Why did you have to sell herbs for money?
Oh.
I am a concubine's son.
So Father has never liked me.
Oh.
I'm sorry.
I brought up your sad past.
Your father really doesn't seem to like you.
Master Shen.
What?
I'm just stating the truth.
It's all right.
My legitimate older brother
died of illness a few years ago.
So I am the only child left.
Life was actually a bit better.
But...
My birth mother and I were driven out by the Mistress
to live on the mountain for a while.
Life was very bleak back then.
It wasn't until she appeared
that my life had some light.
On the mountain?
Yes.
It was that small wooden cabin.
I can identify these herbs
because she taught me.
The mountain cabin.
Childhood sweethearts.
I don't care if you were childhood sweethearts.
She is my wife now.
We have a marriage contract.
A marriage contract?
But...
I've never heard Doctor Ji mention this.
We are indeed engaged.
But since we aren't married yet,
we don't act too intimate in public.
On my trip to Sitai Town,
he was entrusted by his father
to accompany me.
Right.
My father asked me to ensure Ji Bai's safety.
As for the engagement,
it was decided by our parents.
Naturally, we must obey them.
I see.
I was being presumptuous.
It's just that
I've never heard Doctor Ji mention it,
so I had some doubts.
But Brother Shen,
what did you mean by "childhood sweethearts"
just now?
He took the wrong medicine recently.
His mind is a bit fuzzy.
Don't mind him.
Brother Shen, Doctor Ji,
your relationship is truly enviable.
I hope you fulfill your engagement soon
and tie the knot.
I also hope Young Master Du finds his childhood sweetheart soon
and grows old with her.
Young Master.
The Master is returning.
Excuse me.
I must take my leave.
I must go greet my father.
What he just said...
sounds like the childhood friend you're looking for.
Aren't you going to ask him?
Follow me.
How is your memorization of the Treatise on Cold Damage coming along?
Huh?
You called me here just for this?
You are my temporary disciple now.
Naturally, I must check on your studies.
I am the Heir of the Prince of Zhenbei.
My real name is not Shen Yi.
My name is Xiao Heyan.
During our time together,
I figured it out.
I'm your fiancé.
We both ran away.
The engagement is off.
Besides,
you're too impulsive.
You should go back home.
I just can't stand seeing you with other men.
What?
I won't repeat myself.
Oh.
Don't you...
...have any questions for me?
As long as you ask.
I will be honest with you.
Okay.
Then tell me,
what exactly happened at the Prince's Manor that day?
Whose body was that?
Don't drink it.
Li Si had been by my side for years.
He resembled me the most.
On my wedding day,
I wanted to get him drunk
to stall for time
so I could escape the wedding.
But he ended up dying in my place.
Stop blaming yourself.
It won't change anything.
He's already dead.
What do you mean?
Literally.
You didn't mean to do it.
Besides,
the real killer is the one who wanted you dead.
But I handed him that glass of wine.
He is gone.
He wanted to save you until the very end.
You have to live on.
Don't let his sacrifice be in vain.
Find the real killer.
What are you doing?
Writing to Lord Zhenbei,
asking him to send someone to take you back.
I won't go back.
I still have important business to attend to.
Besides, Brother Li Si's death
must have something to do with this matter.
Nonsense.
I have come of age.
I'm not a child anymore.
Why are you just like my father,
always wanting to lock me up in the manor?
I'm not some unmarried young lady.
Did the Prince of Zhenbei lock you in the manor?
It was fine when I was young.
The older I got, the less he wanted me to go out.
He even forbade me from going to the capital.
I always feel like he's afraid of something.
There are rumors outside,
that I'm actually adopted,
and my father never even married.
The Princess of Zhenbei who died of illness on the battlefield
was also made up by him.
Even though the Prince of Zhenbei was the executioner back then,
I don't hate him.
He spared my son and me.
Do you really trust him that much?
He was a longtime friend of Shen.
I believe
he will agree.
I actually have no memory of anything before I was ten.
But I remember a place called Sitai Town,
and the surname Shen.
So I named myself Shen Yi.
I came here to find my true identity.
The Shen clan.
I'm certain.
I've been here before.
This place feels very familiar.
And this specialty cake of Sitai Town,
the taste is also familiar.
This is Jiujiu's favorite snack.
Why are you looking at me like that?
You like eating this?
Yeah.
It's delicious.
I couldn't stop the first time I ate it.
What are you doing?
I...
I don't think I'm injured.
Now you are.
In broad daylight,
in plain view,
we aren't married yet.
How could you do this?
What's wrong?
You should go back.
It's dangerous to be out alone.
You're so unguarded.
I'm worried about you.
My martial arts are excellent.
It was only because of you
that I let my guard down.
So what if you're skilled?
Danger is everywhere.
Anything can happen in the martial world.
You never know what might happen next.
Don't worry.
I won't die with you here.
Besides, I can protect you.
Yi, Yi, Nan.
Wu, Zhang, Li, Zheng, Chen, Luo, Deng.
Ma, Miao, Lu, Ran.
Lyu, Sun, Zhang, Meng.
Pan, Xiu, Long.
Xu.