♫ This time won't be the last and same like that before  ♫
♫ Cuz you know there's no way to stop ♫
♫ Feels like I'm losing control ♫
♫ My style without hesitation. You can't stop me ♫
Military Prosecutor Doberman
We stand at the crossroads each day, facing the many paths each decision will bring.
One moment's decision changes your fate.
The decision becomes fate.
What fate awaits me now?
Will I accept or reject this destiny?
This itself is another decision to make.
A few days ago
Is this like something you wear off the military base?
Sometimes.
Have you perhaps worn this recently?
What are you so curious about?
I just wear it because it doesn't feel like me.
Because I can become somebody else.
Somebody else?
It's a change of scene. For when I get sick of my military uniform.
But is it a violation of the dress code just to be possessing a wig?
No. Keep on driving.
Military Prosecutor Do.
Yes?
What?
That looks like the new commander's car in front of us.
Oh, it does.
General No Hwa Yeong has vigorously opened the door that was sealed to female soldiers,
stepping into the position of commander.
There have been a handful of two-star female generals previously,
but this is the first time a female has been appointed commander in the combat infantry division, the key to the frontline.
As such, this news is gaining a lot of attention.
Mother, I will explain everything.
Shut your mouth.
What Lawyer Yong said is enough.
It's clear that anything you say will be excuses.
Are you going to make that face in front of the public?
Don't you know what day it is today?
I will correct myself.
You must never forget that you are No Hwa Yeong's son.
After the inauguration,
we will talk in my office about the incident you caused.
Yes.
Unity.
Episode 3
- She's here!
- Oh!
How do you feel about being the first to break the army's glass ceiling,
which is like an impregnable fortress?
It is indeed hard for women to get stars.
There is around one female general among every 100 male generals.
It would be more fitting to describe it as a bulletproof ceiling instead.
Is there anything you would like to say to female officers like yourself?
Rather than focusing on competing with the male generals...
Just look at how many reporters have gathered just for the inauguration of a division commander.
This is definitely a hot topic for sure.
You have to understand that you are simply a soldier, not a female soldier.
Since I'm going to leave soon anyway, you take good care of her.
Looks like she's a great choice for a role model.
Becoming the first female general can't be my goal.
Since Commander No Hwa Yeong has done that already, I'm going to aim higher?
That's it, isn't it?
Flags down.
Unity.
Flags up.
I am here today to take over command of the 4th Division.
It is a great honor.
I will take pride in the fact that I am defending the survival and prosperity of the nation,
properly strategize for operations,
and demonstrate impeccable responsiveness for whatever emergency situations arise.
Peace is not achieved by any one person...
As a military prosecutor, do you have the courage to investigate
even a starred general like Commander No Hwa Yeong?
We must come together in unity...
Investigations are done with facts, not courage.
If a crime has been committed, of course, I will.
With everyone in unity...
You sure are amazing.
Only a military prosecutor can
bring a uniformed criminal to court.
Easier said than done.
Soldiers have ranks.
I will protect my subordinates from danger...
There is no ranking that is higher than the law.
I will shape it into an elite division...
and we will contribute our part to the country's military.
Raise the flags.
Unity.
Elite Army Base with Great Energy
The 4th Infantry Division
Mother, where are we going now?
The child you hit has apparently gone blind.
I will make sure you can never do something like that again.
I'm sorry, Mother.
Get out.
Mother, I'm scared.
Go down.
Go down!
Mother, is this real?
Do you know the most important thing about a grenade?
Gunpowder.
Fifty grams of gunpowder breaks the shell encasing the grenade,
and causes the shards to explode in all directions.
But there's something more important than the gunpowder.
It is this safety pin.
You need to pull this out if you want to make it a weapon for war.
- Mother what are you doing—!
- Hold it tight.
The moment you let go, it will explode.
Mother, please save me.
I will rise to places that female soldiers could never dream of.
I will not allow any man to stand above me.
For that to happen, you need to become a perfect human.
You cannot place even a small stain on the path I am walking.
Answer me.
Will you disobey me next time?
No, mother, I won't.
Have you learned your lesson?
Yes, I have. Please believe me.
No.
A lesson without pain is meaningless.
For this to be a real lesson,
I need to give you a memory that you will never forget.
One hour.
Remember that the moment you let go, it will explode in 4 seconds.
No, please!
Mom! Mom!
Mom!
Don't ever forget today's memories.
Always remember that I am your safety pin.
Mother, I spoke to Se Na about the video.
It won't ever create a problem.
Lawyer Yong Mun Gu will handle that issue.
Don't involve yourself in it any further.
But you...
What did you ask a military prosecutor?
Did Lawyer Yong tell you that too?
You dare ask a military prosecutor to get you exempted from enlistment?
I asked a military prosecutor so that there wouldn't be any future trouble.
So that it would not taint you at all.
Who is that military prosecutor?
I cannot tell you!
Do you think I won't be able to figure out who a measly military prosecutor is?
Mother, I really don't want to go to the military.
I will never come to the place where you are.
Even if I die trying.
Why did you report that I asked Do Bae Man to get me exempted from enlistment! Why?
You knew how she would react.
Are you doing this deliberately because you want to see me go insane?
Come here now. Immediately.
Congratulations.
Our General No is wearing a uniform which fits her so perfectly.
Please have a seat.
General.
My sincere congratulations. Unity!
- Congratulations.
Welcome.
So this is what a female division leader's office looks like.
Congratulations, No Hwa Yeong.
Just kidding.
Division Commander, Loyalty!
The general is the first female division commander.
You truly are amazing.
If possible, please ignore all the useless talk
and just focus on the nation's safety.
When the division must stand upright, the nation's military—
Now is the beginning, the problems which we hesitated tackling all this time,
I am going to solve, one by one.
Didn't the army take forty years to change the water canteen?
Now that the times have changed, I'm going to create a new army.
I will start with the 4th Division.
I couldn't help it in my situation.
I'm sorry.
Huh? The situation?
I want to rip that mouth up, down and sideways.
Military boots stomped on me because of someone.
I must report to the general everything that happens in your personal life.
The general set that rule.
In every sentence, it is "general," "general."
Instead of working under me, you joined my mother, huh?
Don't be in the middle snitching to my mother!
Lawyer Yong Mun Gu, you don't lack for anything.
Sometimes when I think about it, I completely don't understand.
At this age, you don't have any family but you just stay next to my mom...
Don't tell me you like my mother?
Leave. Because I can't stand looking at you.
How did your visit to the hospital go?
What about the video?
Se Na doesn't have it. Allen has it.
Then I will confirm that myself.
Did you know Do Bae Man's female soldier bodyguard?
Female soldier?
Hope
Are you saying you couldn't handle a female? Did she shoot you with a gun or something?
If I got shot, I wouldn't be upset.
That female soldier whipped all my kids with one windshield wiper.
Listen carefully. From now on I'm going to go alone.
Don't meddle with me whether I slice him into sashimi or run him over with a car.
Good timing.
Do Bae Man is going to be discharged in a few days.
After he is discharged from the army, he will be neither a soldier nor a prosecutor.
What does that mean?
Does that mean he will no longer have government authority?
He will be just a lawyer at best.
When that happens, the story will be different.
National Scientific, Criminal & Investigation Laboratory
- Please check if these two are the same wig.
- Yes.
When will the results be available?
Even if they were produced by the same factory, the results can differ depending on how they were used.
I think it will take some time to examine them thoroughly.
I understand.
Are you saying that Prosecutor Cha Wu In is involved in Allen's disappearance?
It came out of my mouth, but it's ridiculous.
If the wig from her car and the wig hair from Allen's place are the same, the answer is obvious.
Why is the person who is being discharged the day after tomorrow so obsessed with Cha Wu In?
Because I want to be properly discharged the day after tomorrow.
If I find Allen and bring him to No Tae Nam, I'll definitely make a good impression on him.
Moreover, if I certainly make him get out of the draft, then—
Then?
It's not that I will be just a Law & One partner or anything.
Yong Mun Gu's position will become mine.
Oh... something is coming.
Then, is there something I should do?
If the red wig belongs to Cha Wu In, then she would have transported Allen's gang
and she would have used a 9 seater van. Find it.
Find out whose car it is and where it went.
Yes. What will you be doing, Prosecutor?
I am tracking Cha Wu In's real identity.
Is she really connected to Allen's disappearance?
If she is, what's the reason?
I would like to wear a jacket with it too.
What's this?
The dress is fine but I'm not sure about the length of the jacket.
Could I see another one?
Oh my.
What are you doing?
The bag is beautiful.
I'll buy it.
No, I'm buying this.
- What's the matter with you?
- Please, please, please.
What are you doing now?
- I'll pay for this.
- It is 7.8 million won. ( ~ $6,300 USD)
7.8 million won.
Twelve monthly installments.
A present to celebrate my discharge.
There's still a place that copies and sells these.
Where is the place? So I would go and arrest them.
To my sorrow, it's genuine.
My bloody money.
Isn't it a knock-off?
Genuine?
Look at how fast you are.
OMG. Bae Man.
Bae Man!
The bags must be happy.
Women like them that much.
OMG.
When you're about to finish your service term,
I see you have become a proper filial child.
I'm done now with struggling.
Bae Man. When you come out of the army,
will you change this every season?
Depending on your behavior toward me.
Rice.
Oh, right. A military prosecutor came to our station a while ago about the incident.
- A military prosecutor?
- That's what I said.
Do you know how much I restrained myself from asking if she knew Military Prosecutor Do Bae Man?
There are a lot of military prosecutors. I'm not interested in the least.
Now I'm not even going to pee in the military's direction.
Is that so, civilian?
- Rice!
- I forgot.
Management Personnel Record
Period / School List and Major Degree
There's no record for three years after she dropped out of Stanford Law School in the US.
There should be an answer to this three-year gap, Cha Wu In.
Yes?
Are you Military Prosecutor Do Bae Man?
Who is this?
I'm calling about my military service project.
Where are you now?
The Military Manpower Administration determines exemptions from military service?
That's right.
Is that possible when the body is so healthy?
Compulsory military service is basically a net that only the big fish escape.
It's just like court!
It's a strange net that only the small fry get caught in.
Make sure you get a medical certificate.
I'll personally take care of it so that you get the decision you want.
I'll pay for the net at a price you won't be disappointed with.
I don't need money. I want something else.
What is it? Tell me.
My medical school classmate committed a medical mistake.
He's been indicted in your division.
The division I'm in?
If a military prosecutor makes up his mind to create a criminal,
even if searches and seizures in dozens of places are conducted and the bill of indictment is changed,
he can make you the worst criminal.
Of course, the opposite is also possible.
If the military prosecutor intentionally loses at trial, my friend can be acquitted, right?
As if nothing ever happened.
How close is a friendship that you would dare to make a deal with a military prosecutor?
It's amazing.
Friendship, my foot.
In a little while, my service term will end.
If I want to get a job at the hospital where the punk's father is the director.
- I need to show at least some sincerity.
- Is it because of employment?
After I see the outcome of the trial, I will take care of the enlistment issue. Bye.
Hey.
Are you certain your friend committed a medical mistake?
Yes.
How are you so certain?
He shouldn't have become a doctor in the first place.
The Private First Class Hwang Cheol Seung Medical Incident Case
Let me brief you on the Private Hwang Cheol Seung medical incident.
Private Hwang Cheol Seung enjoyed good health since he was born.
While playing soccer at a military training ground, he suddenly developed paralysis.
He was immediately transported to a military hospital.
The diagnosis was limb paralysis.
What was the cause?
The day before he collapsed, he had visited a military clinic with mild spinal disc symptoms.
It seems the treatment he received was the reason.
He is a quadriplegic.
The military doctor who was indicted stubbornly denies the charges.
Captain Jeong Wi Chan
Okay.
Let's start the investigation. Let's hear the victim's statement first.
What? Are you taking charge of the case?
I thought Cha Wu In is the prosecutor.
I'll do it because it's my first case since I was commissioned as a military prosecutor.
I'll wrap up my tenure as a military prosecutor with this as my last case.
Why? What is it? Is there a problem?
All right. Then you take over with me next to you.
Where is Private Hwang now?
He couldn't trust a military hospital so he is in a civilian hospital.
Jeongmundae University Hospital
Mom.
I'm sorry.
Don't cry, Mom.
I'm not crying.
I am going to stand up.
Don't worry.
I'm Prosecutor Cha Wu In from the 4th Division's Military Service Office.
Prosecutor, please help my son.
Can you give a statement?
Yes.
There was an argument between a military doctor and a military nurse.
Doctor, are you drunk?
What are you talking about? Of course, I'm not drunk.
You are drunk. How can you see a patient?
How can you be nagging me?
I can do it alone without you. Get out!
- What's your name?
- Private Hwang Cheol Seung
Roll up your sleeve.
Ethanol
Military doctor drunk
Are you saying a military doctor treated you when he was drunk?
Yes.
We need to get the nurse's statement.
I'll see you again.
It's true that I wasn't in the doctor's office at the time.
We didn't have an argument over the doctor being drunk.
Private Hwang's statement is different. He was certain that he smelled alcohol.
I'm sure that was some sort of misunderstanding.
Could he have confused the smell of alcohol with the hospital's alcohol?
Yes, right.
Why did you leave the clinic?
Since you didn't have an argument with the doctor?
I'm certain you went to another clinic because they were understaffed, right?
Yes.
Military clinics lack both equipment and personnel.
The number of sick soldiers is overwhelming.
You know that obstructing the investigation by perjury increases the severity of the crime, right?
There was nothing wrong with the doctor.
He gave routine treatment.
Did you answer... properly?
I did as I was told.
Good job.
You drank and administered treatment that day, didn't you?
No, I didn't. I can't drink a drop of alcohol.
I lack the enzyme to metabolize alcohol.
Private Hwang made a statement.
Do you believe what a quadriplegic patient says?
Before the symptoms are fully manifested, it starts with the sensory organs.
Look here. A normal soldier became a quadriplegic because of your treatment.
What is this? You're painting me as a quack when I'm doing volunteer service?
Hey. Calm down.
Because this is the army, even if you do your best for the country,
we will pick up and check even a small mistake.
What are you saying right now?
This prosecutor knows something.
I mean all patients are like that. They don't know their own condition.
In the first place, he had serious disc symptoms. I am sure it was irritating his nerves.
So, the disk condition was left untreated and the nerves became paralyzed, right?
- Without any treatment.
- Yes. That's exactly it.
There are many people who look normal but are internally sick.
Such patients are bombs. Bombs.
If you treat them without knowing it, you'll be all blamed like me.
Is that what you want to say as a doctor?
Is a doctor some kind of god?
How can I foresee abnormalities occurring within a patient's body?
No matter whether you fly or crawl,
can you predict the results of your next trial?
You don't know.
I don't know. I don't know. That, I don't know.
I don't know that.
Are you trying to investigate or are you provoking me?
Our Prosecutor Cha needs to learn how to look at the big picture.
You have to predict in advance the opposing lawyer's next move to prevail in court.
So in the interrogation room, did you play your role as a military doctor's lawyer?
I mean, in front of the doctor, you couldn't get a word in.
Why are you taking it out on me?
At that level, can you fight with a defense attorney?
That's why I said I would take charge of this case, my friend.
If you aren't confident, don't come to the trial.
General Court for Armed Forces
Prosecutor, begin your examination.
Private First Class Hwang Cheol Seung
How did this happen to Private Hwang,
who visited a military clinic for treatment of a herniated disk?
The reason is right here.
One vial contains a contrast agent and the other contains ethanol.
The contrast agent is used for nerve block surgery.
It's a drug that makes your tissues and nerves visible.
The ethanol is a liquid to prevent steam from forming on medical devices.
Could the defendant distinguish between the ethanol and the contrast agent?
There are no labels on identical containers.
That's very possible.
Oh, is that so?
Contrast medium and ethanol have different viscosity,
so you can distinguish between them with the naked eye.
The feeling is very different when you inject either into a patient with a syringe.
Then, could you possibly distinguish between them if you were very drunk?
If you are not completely sober, what is the probability of exchanging ethanol for contrast medium?
A nurse who was at the scene at the time
is testifying that the defendant did not administer treatment while drunk.
I will submit the statement of the nurse.
Then I will submit my records too.
It states that the level of ethanol detected in the victim's body was above the standard level
There are many cases in which alcohol is detected in the body.
Alcohol is also detected in bread or health supplements fermented with yeast.
It cannot be evidence that it is the cause of the mishap.
Judge
The evidence is admitted.
Defendant
Prosecutor
I heard from my client friend.
- Yes.
- Then, please be gentle.
I was a little nervous because you came on stronger than I expected.
If you're going to cheat, you have to cheat properly. A trial is not a joke.
That's true.
I've set up a witness. It will be all over if you set the tempo to moderate.
You will surely receive the winning payment too.
The witness?
I understand.
Then, please take good care of us until the end.
Judge, I'm requesting a witness.
Which witness? A witness will not be allowed.
I didn't know a witness was requested for today by the military prosecutor.
The witness just contacted me that he would testify.
What do you think, defense attorney?
Of course, I can not accept that. I didn't get any prior notice.
As difficult as it was to persuade the witness, who must risk his position,
it wasn't easy for the witness to make his own decision.
Lawyer, what do you think? Should we allow the witness?
Judges' Bench
All right.
Witness, please enter.
There won't be a problem.
That prosecutor is very meticulous.
Trial in session
Witness, please introduce yourself.
I'm serving as a military doctor in the Military Manpower Administration.
- What's your relationship to the accused?
- We were close classmates in medical school.
- Then, did the two of you have drinking parties often?
- Yes.
Did you meet the defendant early on the day of the incident?
I met him.
After meeting him then, did you drink alcohol with him?
Yes. We drank together.
The defendant denied that he drank on the day he treated the victim.
You're offering completely contradictory testimony.
I'm positive. He drank with me.
Hey, what are you saying, bastard?
I object. The witness is committing perjury.
I'll submit evidence to show it is not perjury.
It's four hours before the incident.
When I asked the bar, they drank two bottles of liquor and four bottles of beer.
I hereby submit the receipt for the bill provided by the witness.
If we divided by two, the blood alcohol concentration per person is 0.3.
At that level it is difficult to stand properly.
It takes twenty-one hours to break down alcohol in the human body.
The two left the bar at 4:30 a.m.
Private Hwang was treated at 9:20 a.m.
It's not enough time for a doctor to treat a patient after drinking alcohol.
The cause of Private Hwang's paralysis is because the drunk defendant
mistakenly injected him with ethanol.
Due to the defendant's unbelievable error,
a strong Korean soldier will be bedridden
for the rest of his life.
Have you no conscience?
Please answer.
Hey, what are you doing now?
Do you have it or not?
In order to relieve one soldier's resentment,
as a doctor who saves lives, the witness came here after thinking for a long time.
Please take that into consideration.
Lawyer, do you have any further defense?
There is none.
Why don't you try to put the lid on the coffin and nail it down for your military doctor friend?
I clearly told you to make him innocent.
While investigating the incident, I unearthed the relationship between you two.
You were a talented resident,
but unexpectedly there were records of several medical accidents.
On the other hand, the military doctor friend's accident record was clean.
Then, there's only one answer.
Reverse the accident records. You were used before.
It wasn't a friendship, but a master-servant relationship.
If you enter his father's hospital, you will have to continue to live as you do now.
Anyway, I can't go into another hospital without connections.
The VIP you are working for is
Chairman No Tae Nam. He will send you to a much better position.
Chairman No of IM Defense?
But I can't testify.
Then I'll force you to be on the witness stand.
Did you forget that I'm a military prosecutor?
You tried to buy a military prosecutor to cover up your friend's crimes.
You said that first.
I told you.
The role of the prosecutor in this country is to make anyone they want into a guilty person.
Add to that the military as well or more.
Just what made you change your mind?
Chairman No should be exempted without any problem.
But your friend is annoying.
If you can be stabbed in the back anytime, that's tough.
Just state everything exactly as it happened.
If you make even just one mistake,
you will be the first to be abandoned.
You arranged a witness without a word to me.
He wasn't on the investigation list. Aren't you going to explain?
We won. What more is there to explain?
Military Prosecutor Do Bae Man, are you a righteous prosecutor or
are you a clever prosecutor?
Righteous?
I hear that question often nowadays.
Are you confident you can distinguish between right and wrong?
Isn't a prosecutor a defender of justice?
No. If you're on my side, that's my definition. Okay?
It sounds just like Military Prosecutor Do Bae Man.
Did you just find out?
It was very unusual that a military court in a trial involving medical malpractice on a private
to sentence the defendant to 4 years and 6 months in prison.
Meanwhile, the personal history of the military prosecutor who was victorious at trial is a hot topic.
Do Bae Man recently investigated the son of a Gusan Bank for receiving emperor service.
He's been in charge of several such incidents...
Is that the military prosecutor who wants to get an exemption from the draft for Tae Nam?
It is.
He's my subordinate.
Aide Yang!
Schedule a meeting with the chief of the division's legal office and Military Prosecutor Do Bae Man.
Yes, I will.
What are you intending?
He must be warned.
Find the videos first.
I will.
Please save us.
Save us!
What is this place?
Kang's Solution
Leaving the parking lot at the estimated time of the incident, there was only one 9-passenger van.
Who is the owner?
It was in the name of a company. It's a defense contractor called Kang's Solution.
Kang's Solution.
Got it.
How many floors up is she going?
Thirty.
The CEO's name is Kang Ha Jun.
He is an up and coming very competent businessman
in his late 20's in the mobile industry at a young age.
Are you still wearing that watch?
It saved my life.
I exchanged it for my life.
New York 7 Years ago
What did the boss tell us to bring, anyway?
I don't know.
Looks pretty expensive, isn't it?
No, no, no, no. What's inside is expensive, you idiots.
Excuse me.
Hey, you're just making a gambling program with such a smart brain?
While getting a scholarship from my dad?
- Yo!
- Huh?
Are you this dog's chick?
What?
Well, I hadn't met him before, but he's not my type at all.
You're my type, baby.
For the record, I'm no match for you guys.
You guys are a team, but I'm just by myself.
And...
Hit 'em hard. You never.
Do I?
Take care.
Damn, it's all screwed up.
Do you know how expensive that program is?
- Hey, are you feeling sorry for yourself?
With that smart brain, are you going to live by writing a program to look at other people's cards?
I was trying to earn money to start a business.
Then you can get it from my dad.
What?
He told me to bring you. He will invest in that smart brain.
I'm thinking about the chairman. I miss him more today.
I'm sure he has seen us cleaning the trash, hasn't he?
It's over. Come and clean it up for me.
What about him? Has there been any progress?
I was certain that he is someone I need for my plan.
I can't respect him, but I can't help but be amazed at him.
Cleaning the trash...
Did Kang Ha Jun help kidnap Allen?
- Sang Gi?
- Yes, Military Prosecutor.
I think I matched all the puzzle pieces of Allen's kidnapping.
Kang's Solution
The incident happened around 10 pm the night before the 12th.
It was at Cartel, the club in Gangnam.
No Tae Nam and Allen were drinking.
Allen brought a girl called Han Se Na there.
Se Na was raped.
She then headed over to the police all beaten up to report it.
The person Se Na asked for help from was...
Se Na!
Cha Wu In.
Allen played cards with his friends the next day.
- Fifty!
- He didn't give a second thought about what he did day before.
But then...
an unexpected visitor came by.
Cha Wu In can beat up a bunch of thugs with a windshield wiper.
Five drunk guys would've been a piece of cake for her.
In the process of moving the unconscious guys, an accomplice appears.
The identity of the accomplice
is Kang's Solution's CEO, Kang Ha Jun.
Cha Wu In and Kang Ha Jun
know each other through her father.
If we dig into Kang Ha Jun deeper,
I think we'll learn something about Cha Wu In.
This is everything I figured out...
about Allen's kidnapping case so far.
The results came out one hour ago.
The conclusion is that Cha Wu In's red hair wig matches the hair at the scene.
In the end, it happened because of Han Se Na.
She dealt with this way too disproportionately.
Or...
there may be other reasons behind it.
So what do you intend to do now?
What else?
I'll have to arrest Cha Wu In
so that there are no setbacks to my discharge.
Are you searching for this?
Who are you?
It seems like you have bad soundproofing.
Let's keep things down.
We've met before, so don't be too surprised.
I am Chairman No Tae Nam's Lawyer.
Get out.
Get out now. I'll report to the police.
I know you didn't call your mother on purpose because you were afraid of causing harm to her.
It's been a while since you heard your mother's voice, right?
You should give her a call now.
Aigoo, Se Na, I'm surprised you called.
You never call me first.
Mom...
Are you eating well?
Did something happen?
I'm just... curious how you are doing.
I barely do anything, I'm starting to feel bad.
They might think I'm a chair warmer.
I'll call you again, Mom. I'm sorry.
What are you sorry for? I know you're busy.
I love you, Sweetie.
Do you have the video?
I don't.
Even if you don't have the video,
it'd better not...
see the light of day.
Your mother's life depends on your choice, Se Na.
Goodbye then.
Attention. Salute.
- Unity!
Down.
Major Seo Ju Hyeok.
Captain Do Bae Man.
At ease.
I've received the report on the big medical accident case you solved.
Captain Do Bae Man will be discharged soon.
It's a shame we'll lose a talented man like him to civil court.
What's your plan once in the civilian world?
I plan to work as a lawyer at a civil law firm.
Lawyers nowadays need to be specialized in a field to make it.
I'm sure your experience in the military will be useful.
Yes, ma'am.
I heard in the civilian world, there are lawyers who help with evading the draft.
Meaning as lawyers, they do something illegal brokers do.
Tell me, are you possibly interested in doing that too?
As a soldier and prosecutor of the 4th Division,
I have seen and learned many things.
My body may be leaving, but I won't forget my esprit de corps.
I'm just deeply saddened that I won't be serving you.
All right.
I'll see you when you report your discharge, Captain Do Bae Man.
My client...
I'm in a meeting, so why don't you wait outside?
Will you be okay with me talking here?
Because I don't mind.
What shall I do?
Man, I haven't seen your face like that in a while.
You had the same expression when I first brought you here.
I'll report three matters which concern Chairman No Tae Nam.
Fine, go ahead.
First. I've obtained information
on the suspect who drove the car that kidnapped Allen.
I think I can find Allen by today.
- Okay.
- Second.
I'll be meeting Chairman No Tae Nam at Cartel today.
He told me to tell you not to join.
- What's the third matter?
- Third.
It's my last report.
After this day,
I will not be making any reports to you after today.
Do you mean you'll be cutting ties with me from now?
That's correct.
What's your reason?
You shouldn't have told Division Commander of all people.
The fact that I'm in charge of Chairman No's draft evasion project.
Are you that unhappy about me gaining Chairman No's confidence?
Did you think General No wouldn't find out even if I didn't tell her?
I'm going to join hands with Chairman No Tae Nam now.
Directly without a middleman.
So it's all my fault
that our business is over?
I guess I gave you a good excuse.
Fine, I can accept that.
But let me give you a heads up.
You've messed with the thing General No Hwa Yeong is most sensitive about.
That method will never gain you my position.
My gosh.
How many of you peed your pants?
Sorry I'm late. I left right away from the station.
It's okay.
We can't get in contact with Se Na, so I was about to call you anyway.
I asked to meet because of that also.
It's the video they filmed from that day.
I just received it from Se Na.
It won't be difficult
getting an arrest warrant for Chairman No Tae Nam.
Cartel
I left the key inside.
I looked into cars under Kang's Solution and found Allen.
These guys look a total mess.
All right, good job.
I arrived at Cartel to meet with Chairman No.
Bring those punks safely to Seoul.
I found Allen.
I knew you could do it.
Come here and have a drink.
Oh, okay.
It's an honor, sir.
About my draft evasion project—
Even with the Division Commander watching, if you want it done, I'll make sure it happens.
That's the spirit! I didn't ask to be born as a general's son.
Why do I have to go when everyone isn't?
That's exactly what I'm saying.
Don't worry. We just need someone to approve it.
And I've already found the person for it.
But...
Allen dislocated his shoulder. I don't want to use such an unsophisticated method.
I'm too scared to even go to the dentist.
The medical issue is only for document purposes.
You'll get free passage, Chairman.
I really like the way you work. You're different from Lawyer Yong who's always worrying about Mom.
But...
I heard 'Gunbari' means,
"dog that protects the country."
Yes, that's right.
Doberman. A faithful dog that'll rip into anyone for his master.
That's exactly you. Your name is Doberman too!
All right.
You're aware
that my IM Defense is the best in the defense industry.
You must always be in need of someone who knows the ins and outs of the military.
I can't leave it to my mother's shadow, Lawyer Yong.
On top of that, he reports everything about me to Mother.
Gosh, you have a lot of hardships too.
- Which is why...
- Yes.
I'm thinking of having you take over my company's legal team.
Chairman. Thank you. Thank you, sir! I'll do my best.
Here.
Don't get ahead of yourself.
It's under the condition that you succeed in making me draft exempt.
Yes, of course!
Please, pick up. I'm going to go use the bathroom.
Hyung Tae Nam. It's me, Allen.
A red-haired wench beat me up and took the video!
You're still there, right? We have to find the video.
If it's leaked, it'll be over for both you and me. Do something!
Anything is possible with you, right?
The red-haired wench has the video?
Yes. The red-haired—
Lawyer Yong Mun Gu
I'm hanging up.
The police are going to raid Cartel soon.
What did you say?
Team A will go this way and Team B that way. Let's go.
- Yes, ma'am!
- Yes, ma'am.
What's going on?
I tailed after Do Bae Man but there are a bunch of cops.
What in the world is going on?
There are so many.
Auntie. Damn.
What the hell?
- We're executing our duty. Get the dog out now!
- Executing your duties?
Do you not know who I am?
We know you very well, No Tae Nam.
This is an emergency arrest warrant.
We've received a video reporting you. Come with us.
Hey, Bolt. Bite them. Quickly, go!
My gosh.
Hey, you punk! Where do you think you're going?
- Cuff him.
- Yes, ma'am.
You. I'm going to remember your face. You just wait.
- Take him.
- Okay.
Let me go!
Hey, you! Stop there.
Come here for a second.
That bastard!
Oh, thank you!
- Stop right there!
- Catch him!
- What are you doing? Why aren't you stepping on the gas and chasing him? Get going!
- Yes, Hyeongnim.
♫ Hey, watch out y'all. I'm a little out of control ♫
♫ Just follow, me follow on my roll ♫
♫ Even if I hide it, It's an obvious trick to me ♫
Get closer to him.
♫ Top of Beast that will judge everyone. Too wild to be tamed ♫
♫ My zone. My zone. My zone. My zone ♫
Stick to the car. Stick to it.
♫ 'm going to bark viciously ♫
♫ Get out of my way please, please, please ♫
♫ See? See? It's useless  ♫
♫ I'll going to teach you a lesson, more, more, more  ♫
Stop coming after me. Please stop chasing, Aunt!
♫ Bye bye, it's over. Stop making excuses ♫
♫ Everyone has a hidden past ♫
- Stop the car!
- Damn it!
Hey! Stop the car, you bastard!
Do you want to die? Stop the car, you bastard! Stop it!
- Stop the car! You bastard!
- Damn it!
♫ I'm going to bark viciously.  ♫
♫  Get out of my way please, please, please ♫
♫ See? See? It's useless ♫
♫ I will teach you a lesson more more more ♫
♫ I'm on my way. ♫
♫ All sorts of things, Mayday Oh ♫
♫ Step out of my zone. My my zone. My zone ♫
Damn it.
Damn.
♫ My zone. My zone. My zone. My zone ♫
♫ Give it a try try in my zone ♫
Go! What the hell!
♫ Step out of my zone. My ♫
♫  My zone. My zone. ♫
Let's go. Come on.
What's happening?
What's going on?
Cha Wu In.
The red-haired girl.
I knew my instinct was right.
It wasn't a coincidence...
that I found the wig in your car, was it?
It was bait.
Most people think you make your own decisions in life. But that's wrong.
Even those decisions are a part of your fate.
That's because from the start,
you had no freedom to refuse your fate.
Military Prosecutor Do Bae Man. You can't get discharged.
You'll have to stay and fight with me.
That's your fate, Prosecutor Do.
♫ This time won't be the last and same like that before ♫
♫ Do whatever you want. Yeah I don't care ♫
♫ It's obvious that I'm holding my breath. ♫
♫ What you gonna do ♫
♫ I'm on fire like I'm gonna burn down ♫
♫ Cuz you know there's no way to stop ♫
Military Prosecutor Doberman
♫ My style without hesitation, you can't stop me ♫
♫ No chance, you can't get away now ♫
Tell me. Why did you try to kill me?
I'm waiting for you to wake up from oblivion.
Don't spit in the water you're drinking.
Do Bae Man ran by himself, that military bastard.
Chairman No Tae Nam will be dropping all of his titles related to IM Defense.
- IM is my everything.
- Don't fool yourself.
Unfortunately for you, you have lost everything because you betrayed me.
I'll start over from the bottom.
You'll figure out why we have to fight together.
♫ Even if you try to stop me ♫
♫ Oh there's no way to stop ♫