♫ This time won't be the last and same like that before  ♫
♫ Cuz you know there's no way to stop ♫
♫ Feels like I'm losing control ♫
♫ My style without hesitation. You can't stop me ♫
Military Prosecutor Doberman
♫ When this light gets dark ♫
♫ I'll ignite ♫
♫ In this long night alone ♫
♫ I who am wandering. 	Let this madness stop ♫
♫ Oh I will try ♫
♫ Light up the surrounding darkness ♫
♫ Turning around I walk silently ♫
- Dad.
- Yes?
By the way, why is our company's name IM?
It's named after you, my daughter.
- But my name is Wu In.
- What?
My Wu In, do you know how to write the roman alphabetic initials for your name?
W and I.
That's right. Here. Take a look.
Here. Wu In initial is
W and
- I, is it right?
- Yes.
Turn it upside down.
Voila.
Wow, my dad is the best.
Now, if you do this.
Wu In, right? Turn it over, IM
- Dad company's name, IM.
- Right, right.
WI
Aw, you are pretty.
What did you draw? Oh...
Did you draw well?
Dad's company.
It's really shiny.
Cha Wu In.
Episode 2
She's definitely suspicious.
Don't you think we should be prioritizing IM Defense over
Military Prosecutor Cha Wu In?
IM?
- No Tae Man's company?
- Yes.
Because I resemble you, I can't restrain myself about something I'm curious about.
I've done some research.
Founded 30 years ago, IM Defense was a medium-sized defense company.
It was considered the best of the best among the other mid-size businesses at the time.
It was famous in the industry. Now, they create not only defense equipment,
but also security systems for aircraft, engines, and robots. They have expanded.
The scale has increased.
If its focus is the defense industry, they must have contacts in the military, right?
Of course, they do. No Tae Nam's mother is
General No Hwa Yeong.
The superwoman who cut through the glass ceiling.
The first woman in South Korea's history to become a two-star general.
I heard it is her eyes, not guns, that can kill.
That's just how intimidating she is.
So his mother is General No Hwa Yeong.
Who General is No Hwa Yeong.
This is interesting.
But how is a young guy like No Tae Nam the president?
This well-established company suddenly leaked military secrets and manipulated market prices.
As the embezzlement scandal erupted, the stocks plummeted.
The former president was arrested.
- Was the case trumped up?
- Yes.
The company was stripped naked by a short-selling hedge fund
and went into receivership. At that time,
IM defense was acquired at a dirt cheap price.
- The leading actor was none other than—
- No Tae Nam.
But there's a rumor that No Tae Nam is just a puppet.
There's someone behind him.
What about the prior owner? What happened after the company was taken away.
From this point in the story, things become extremely fishy.
Mysterious accident of President Cha Ho Cheol
An issue arose with the personal safety of President Cha Ho Cheol, who was on trial.
2012-12-21
IM Defense President Cha Ho Cheol Dies from Car Accident
President Cha Ho Cheol died at the scene of a car accident.
The family members in the passenger seats were said to have been seriously injured and fell unconscious.
So why is this fishy?
The prosecutor in charge of the case
was none other than Yong Mun Gu.
If a judgment depends on how much money parties have,
what good is the law that should treat everyone equally?
Our prosecutors are concerned about the defendant, Cha Ho Cheol,
who has deepened the public's mistrust in the judicial system.
We promise he will receive severe punishment.
Do you acknowledge all claims to be true?
Do you admit the corruption allegations?
The fact that Yong Mun Gu, who was a young novice prosecutor,
caught a big fish became a hot topic.
No Tae Nam and Yong Mun Gu.
This is the same strategy we used to get rid of the Gusan Bank President.
Strategy?
One, there is an enemy who needs to be removed from the business.
Two, create a crime he did not commit and blame it on him.
Three, force his burial through socially ostracizing him even before going to trial.
Four, No Tae Nam replaces him,
and Yong Mun Gu is compensated with any leftover crumbs.
That's correct. As soon as Yong Mun Gu took off his prosecutor's uniform,
he set up Law & One.
No Tae Nam set it up for him.
After all, Yong Mun Gu helped him swallow up a whole company.
But, what do you find so suspicious about
Military Prosecutor Cha Wu In?
Instinct?
The instinct so deeply ingrained in my bones.
Let's just say it's the side effect of having been so conscious about people around me ever since I was young.
It trained me before I even realized it.
I don't know what it is,
but there is something. That sort of instinct.
The fact that doubt has begun,
means that belief has begun.
This is because as long as you pass through the long, dark tunnel of doubt,
doubt turns into strong belief.
No matter how firmly you have established your belief,
the moment doubt creates its cracks,
the belief shatters like glass.
And the shattered glass shards become knives.
Se Na
- Eonni.
- Se Na. How are you feeling?
I have a request.
I'll head over to the hospital right now.
A few days ago.
Se Na.
I couldn't bring myself to...
call home. I could only call you.
It's okay.
Nothing more will happen. I'm here now,
so everything is okay.
Hello. I'm Detective Do Su Gyeong from the Violent Crimes Unit.
I am Cha Wu In. Please tell me what happened.
According to Han Se Na's testimony, she was sexually assaulted.
Has she identified the perpetrator?
Not yet. It looks like she knows who it is, but is scared to speak.
Anything else?
It looks like she was anesthetized with a drug,
and it was at a club called Cartel in Gangnam.
Did you just say Cartel?
Yes.
Se Na said you were a close friend. So you are a prosecutor?
Yes, a military prosecutor.
Military prosecutor?
- Which divisio—
- Let's get Se Na to a hospital first.
Yes. If you give us the contact information of the hospital—
I'll contact you again.
I understand.
Se Na.
I think I've done something pointless, reporting it to the police.
I was filmed.
They used their phones to film...
What do I do now? What if they blackmail me?
What if they upload it to the internet?
Just thinking about it is driving me crazy.
Se Na.
Eonni, I have a favor.
You said you are a military prosecutor, right?
If you say you are a prosecutor, don't you think that would scare them?
That video. I have it.
- What?
- Nobody can see that video.
I didn't tell the police about it yet either.
How do you have that video?
It's difficult for me to tell you now. I'll tell you when the time comes.
Right now, the most important thing is that this video
is needed by both you and me.
For you as well?
Without this, we cannot start a trial.
But the decision is up to you.
Whether you want to cover this up so that nobody in the world knows about it,
whether you want to make those punks pay for what they did.
I just want to bury this. I don't even want to think about it again.
Alright.
If that is your decision, let's do that.
If I don't make an issue about this,
I can hope they will leave me alone, right?
I will protect you. Don't worry.
Idol star Allen's concert, which was scheduled for tomorrow, has been canceled.
According to his company, Allen has cut contact with everybody and has disappeared.
As backlash from the fans...
- Yes.
- Have you seen the news?
- The news?
- Allen has disappeared.
We cannot reach the person you are calling. Please wait until you are connected to voice mail...
We cannot reach the person you are calling. Please wait while you are connected to voice mail...
What's with this bastard?
We cannot reach the person you are calling. Please wait until you are connected to voice mail...
You still can't reach him?
He's not answering.
You know it's that punk Allen's natural specialty to disappear like this. He was probably stressed out by the upcoming concert.
He has disappeared from time to time, but every one of those times,
he answered when you called him.
That's true. Since he knows my personality.
This is not a mere disappearance.
What happened that day at Cartel?
Why is Cartel relevant?
That has nothing to do with this.
Until now, I have been preventing all of your incidents and accidents before they happened.
So much that even I call myself your legal bodyguard instead of your legal representative.
I make sure problems are resolved before we reach the courtroom.
Hey,
as expected of a former special division prosecutor, you really push me to the edge.
I liked it when you were doing work for me,
but being on the opposite end of such interrogation feels like sh*t.
This is related to the female college student who was there with you that night, isn't it?
Did you film a video this time too?
How much of my personal life am I supposed to share?!
Hey. You have a scratch on your face.
What?
Hey! Are you crazy?
Hey. Don't you know that he has a concert in a few days?
How can you call yourself a fan and scratch him, you b*tch?
And you call yourself an Allen fan, you crazy b*tch?!
That hurts.
Don't do this.
Hey. Her expression is showing.
Give me your phone. We need to film it now.
- Are you filming?
- Yeah.
Did you intentionally film it with Allen's phone?
You told me not to leave anything on my phone if possible. You're always nagging me.
You shouldn't have started it to begin with.
We're good now, right? I've told you everything.
Now you do whatever you need to do.
So Allen has disappeared together with the video.
I will start by looking for Allen.
Why don't you ask him?
Who?
That soldier who did the "emperor treatment" case. He was pretty skilled.
Why? You don't want to?
A military prosecutor is still a prosecutor.
Allowing Do Bae Man to enter your personal sphere is not good.
So just do it.
It's because sometime soon I will order him to do something. Within my personal sphere.
Sixty-seven. Arms, please.
You can put them down now. One-hundred seven. Oh, your build is just...
One-hundred five.
It looks like I'll be able to make a masterpiece.
When will you be wearing this?
I have a hunch that
there is going to be a need for it sometime soon, so I am just preparing in advance.
- Could I have your autograph—
- Hey!
Oh, I'm sorry.
How can you suddenly ask a customer for his signature?
Yes, Lawyer Yong.
Come to my office right now.
Yes, I will.
Chief Lawyer Yong Mun Gu
- I ran over immediately. Is it something urgent?
- Do you know Allen?
An idol singer.
Allen... I have heard his name before.
He's gone missing. Well, it's a little early to conclude that yet.
Let's just say we cannot make contact with him for now.
There is a place Allen and his friends go to play cards. Go check out this place first.
Yes, I will.
Aren't you curious about why you need to find him?
You mean, why you have come to me instead of going to the police when a man has disappeared?
Yes.
A soldier merely follows orders. He does not question.
More importantly... well.
I'm not curious at all.
Sang Gi, I am so curious that I am going insane.
What is it? I know my prosecutor can't stand holding in what you're curious about for even a minute.
Do some background research on an idol singer called Allen.
Allen? The current hot star Allen?
Personal life, people around him, especially relationships with females.
Find everything you can about him until this past month.
Yes. But why does your voice sound so excited?
I think Allen is No Tae Nam's person.
Lawyer Yong Mun Gu is hiding it, but you can't fool my instincts.
I'll look into it immediately. Your loyal worker.
Yeah. Total loyalty.
There was a report of a fire in the middle of the night that day, so it was crazy.
Evacuating civilians and watching firetrucks arriving. It was chaotic.
A report of a fire?
I'm not sure if it was a joke or a mistake,
but after the incident was resolved and we returned,
the CCTVs were all erased.
Yes. Except for one spot.
Where was that?
Camera 8, towards the hallway on the 20th floor.
Could I take a look at the footage?
That'll be a bit difficult.
A celebrity lives there, so without a special reason, we can't.
I see.
Make up an acceptable reason.
Wow.
Blood.
This is it. Red hair.
Are you looking for something in particular?
It's for a superior at work. Do you have any recommendations?
- A superior at work?
- Yes.
Is he perhps someone you'll be making into your boyfriend soon?
I take offense at that.
I'm sorry.
I'll give you recommendations for something practical with a slick design.
Thanks.
I'll take this one.
You... want me to accept this?
This isn't a gift, but a bribe.
Why would I bribe someone who's going to be leaving soon anyway?
In return for you saving me during the interrogation.
I don't like being indebted to others.
Of course, it's okay to express your feeling with something concrete,
but this is a bit...
I wasn't sure of your style preferences, so I picked one to my liking.
You picked the right one for me.
I'm heading out to practice shooting, then.
Wait, wait! Take the watch with you!
She gave you a watch. An expensive one, at that.
This is more than a simple gift to a superior.
This is something you'd gift to a boyfriend or f-f-future husband!
What— What could this mean? Let's see.
Right? Right? You thought the same thing as me, right?
Something is... itching here. What is this, the start of love?
It's not the start of love. You're itchy because you didn't bathe.
- Out of the blue?
- Hey, you too. Get out. Wash up.
Don't touch it.
- Prosecutor Cha!
- Temper tantrum.
That's right. Right.
Cha Wu In.
Where are you going?
You said you're going to the shooting range. I'll finish my assignment too.
Sure.
I also want to give a gift which would be of equal value to the watch. What do you need?
If I receive something in return, that'll make my gift meaningless.
I don't need anything either.
Really?
Oh, my.
I won't see you once you're discharged.
I'll be grateful if you treat it as a part of you and wear it 24/7.
Military Prison
Reform
I...
I'm not someone who can come and go because you ask me to.
As you can see, I can't leave.
Do you even know what I do for a living?
I heard you can make those
who refuse to speak, desperate to do so.
That's right.
I guess news circulates well in here too.
But why is someone like you in here?
You know this bastard, don't you?
Of course.
There's an old saying for the relationship he and I have.
I'm not interested in such sayings.
Refusal to live under the same sky.
An archenemy so great you don't want to exist in the world together.
That's why you're the right person.
With this opportunity, you can put an end to your ill-fated relationship.
It's only ill-fated when we're bad for each other.
I'm a victim, so it'd be upsetting for us to be considered ill-fated.
But the flow of the conversation is a bit awkward.
What is it you're trying to say? Do you want someone to be reshaped to crap?
Kill Do Bae Man.
25 m Pistol Target
Jeez.
If only I had more time before leaving, I'd train you properly.
You're unlucky.
I guess so. How unfortunate.
Are your reactions always so flat?
No matter what I say?
It's not like we're going to war anyway.
Let's approach it as a sport.
In all sports, good form is basic.
One, relax your upper body.
Legs spread just a bit more than shoulder-width apart.
Slightly bend your elbows and knees to form an isosceles triangle.
That stabilizes your aim and minimizes gun recoil.
Like that.
The most important is the second point.
Think of someone in place of your target.
Someone you want to pull the trigger on right now.
Try shooting.
25 m Pistol Target
Wait a minute.
Kill Do Bae Man.
- They'll hear you.
- Scared?
This is different from an ordinary prison.
How am I supposed to kill a prosecutor?
If you take care of this, we can become well acquainted.
What do you think?
Where shall I take you?
Tell all the bros in the group chat to gather.
All of them?
I-I understand.
I can confirm that Allen was with his friends at the hideout.
None of the friends who play cards with him contacted him.
I've searched through CCTVs but the footage has been deleted.
I secured this from a camera independent of the general security servers.
This is the only guest from that time frame. Do you know who it is?
- Is this all?
- One more thing.
I found this on site and ran a DNA test on it.
The results?
It's Allen's blood.
The scale is too large for this to be a simple loss of contact.
Don't rashly jump to conclusions.
Yes, sir.
- Just find Allen.
- I understand.
I'm sure the puzzle pieces will come together with more evidence.
Hello?
We've found a coordinate.
- For where?
- Have you heard of the club, Cartel?
Cartel?
Cartel
They say Allen was here two days ago with a woman.
I mean, it's the same. The same.
- Excuse me, may I ask something?
- How can I help?
This is the singer Allen's usual club, right?
Why are you asking that?
I wanted to know who is the woman who was with Allen two days ago.
- Leave. Leave.
- Wait a minute.
Aren't you the military prosecutor who investigated the emperor service case?
- You recognize me?
- Of course.
Unity.
At ease.
Captain, I served as an operating strength soldier in the 4th division at headquarters.
I've been discharged for about a month now.
Oh really?
Leave. He's a prosecutor.
What are you curious about?
The woman who came with Allen. And...
was this person with them that day?
As expected, it's got something to do with No Tae Nam.
Now all I need to do is find Allen...
Where is this bastard?
Suffer for the suffering you caused.
Have you reflected on your actions?
What?
What are you saying?
Where is this?
I wonder where this is?
Somewhere you'll never go, the military.
Huh? Military?
What are you saying?
How much are these shoulders worth?
According to a speciality hospital in Gangnam, you're suffering from an unstable multi-directional shoulder.
Simply defined, there was a shoulder dislocation surgery.
Leave. Go away!
Someone save me! Someone save me!
What's the appropriate amount?
As much as the surgery or
would you like to pay as much as you earned in the 18 months of military service you were medically exempted from?
Help! Save us! Save us!
What is that?
- Sleep a bit more
- Don't come!
until I'm back.
- ... as it was.
- Huh? You!
Unity.
Cha Wu In, your eyebrows...
Is it makeup? Semi-permanent?
Or is it a tattoo?
They're my natural eyebrows.
Oh, natural?
Then you're fine.
However, your haircut is quite
messy.
If you're talking about my hairstyle,
I don't think it's bad because it doesn't interfere with wearing my uniform hat.
Captain Do, at the defense ministry, what is the substance of Article 24?
You shouldn't wear a wig or dye your hair, etc., if it interferes with military discipline.
For short hair, the ends of the hair at the back of your head should not touch the collar.
If you have long hair, tie it or put it up with hairpins or a hair net. That's what it states.
You know it very well!
But while you know it, look at this. It's almost touching. It nearly reaches.
I mean, you are a military prosecutor. Do you intend to violate the rule?
There were internal military regulations so that until 1988
a female military officer could not give birth.
Military regulations which are outdated should be updated.
What?
I'm sorry. She will be corrected.
I haven't done anything wrong.
Shall I give you a piece of advice?
In the military smart officers are liked,
but I really dislike soldiers who are smart and self-righteous.
And do you know who is the worst among them?
A soldier who is smart, self-righteous, and female.
That is precisely you, Cha Wu In.
Waste of words.
How dare she to her superior officer?
Smart-mouth answers to my questions.
Oh, really. That woman bugs me.
Here, here.
I am sorry.
Even if I have to delay my discharge, I will make her a proper soldier before I leave.
There's no way you can prune a decaying tree.
You should discard a decaying tree.
Because she will continue, when there is another occasion,
should I transfer or discipline her?
I will do it even if it's a dishonorable discharge.
Nice.
Who will do this for me when you are discharged?
From my mom who also has a wild temper
to that female soldier Cha Wu In.
I'm scared. I don't like them.
Nowadays you can't reveal your inner thoughts.
What you said to Captain Cha before was very dangerous.
I don't know if they are trying to ruin military life.
Now the newly installed division leader is a female general.
Who is it?
General No Hwa Yeong.
Really, in the battle of the stars, she blew away all the males.
She got promoted to that position. Just that alone
shows she's not a normal woman.
What is it? You don't like it either, right?
No, I don't. It's not right.
Anyway, what do you care since you're being discharged.
Oh, I like that!
I'll be grateful if you treat it as a part of you and wear it 24/7.
For Cha Wu In too, if I gather all the clues, I will put the puzzle together.
Lawyer Yong Mun Gu
Yes.
Two girls are linked to the process of searching for Allen.
One is the unidentified woman in the red wig I told you about.
The other is Han Se Na.
It was reported to the police that three days ago at Club Cartel,
something nasty happened to her caused by Allen and his company.
Are you saying reported?
I guess you knew about Han Se Na.
Yes.
Then, who is Allen's company?
You don't need to know that.
I know he is Chairman No Tae Nam.
Did you ask a question for which you already knew the answer?
Since I found out, please tell me the details.
Wouldn't that be helpful to you, too?
I think it's an urgent matter to you.
Han Se Na dropped the charges. She's hospitalized now in a general hospital in Gyeonggi Province.
I think I will find Allen soon also.
If I am to do that, I need some reward.
What do you want?
I want to meet Chairman No Tae Nam.
You have an appointment with Chairman No tomorrow.
Just remember it is just a pro forma meeting.
I am nervous about the transition to civilian life.
Wouldn't be it better to just be in the army for life?
Thanks to Lawyer Yong Mun Gu, I've been eating well and living well for the damn last five years.
My life is going to be even better now. Just watch, Sang Gi.
No. Will you be really okay?
I think I have to go with you too.
You know my instincts well, don't you?
I throw myself into the wave that is No Tae Nam who is running toward me.
Every other punk may have drowned, but not me.
I'm going to make sure I ride that fateful wave.
He's looking. Please stop.
I'll wait for you in the car.
Today you are wearing a civilian suit as well.
You look like you made an effort to meet with President No.
Also, an expensive watch?
Is it an expensive watch?
I got it as a gift.
Is it possibly from a woman?
I have many things to do, how would I have time for it?
Let's go.
Stay.
I'm Military Prosecutor Do Bae Man.
It's my honor to meet with you.
That name is unique. Let me think.
It sounds similar to someone. Do Bae Man?
Do Bae Man?
Doberman.
My Bolt is also a Doberman.
Since I was a child, it's been my nickname, Doberman.
You must've been teased a bit because you have the same name as a dog breed.
I was never teased.
I threw out all the punks who had the potential to tease me
regardless of whether they were a student or a teacher.
Let's get to the point since I'm busy.
Yes, Chairman.
It's your job to lock up guys who try to evade the draft, right?
If the guy is a soldier, then yes.
Is there someone you want to report?
- I can immediately—
- Get me out of the draft.
Yes?
I just really don't want to serve in the military.
It's very you, Chairman.
Who would expect you to ask this favor directly to a military prosecutor?
Chairman. If it's about that, I'll look into it separately.
Lawyer Yong. Stay out of this.
Then let me word it differently. I want to see how capable you—
You're saying you want to test me.
Don't cut me off.
If you feel offended by the word 'test,' think of it as an opportunity.
This opportunity is to see if you can be on my team.
Opportunity, you say.
I don't judge opportunities.
The opportunity will judge me.
Do Bae Man. This isn't an offer to accept rashly.
That chance, I'll definitely grab it.
I didn't know that you are indeed that kind of person.
I can't believe you're surprising me from the start.
You're truly a soldier, our Military Prosecutor Doberman.
How could you accept it so easily?
You are just a military prosecutor. Do you have a way?
A way?
I don't have.
But you still agreed to it?
It won't be easy.
But did you ever see me go on a paved path?
The road was always paved after I walked it.
I plan to pave my way this time too.
What? Don't say
you are worried that I'll succeed with the opportunity?
I'm going.
Good job, sir.
You should've discussed this issue with me first.
Are you on a mission to get on my nerves these days?
Military issues are not that simple!
You want me to go to the military and live with some random punks?
You want me, No Tae Nam to do that?
You might as well tell me to go die.
I will tell you just one thing.
If your mother finds out, she's not going to just sit back and watch.
I'll start my monthly report for Law & One.
There are currently 23 cases we are working on.
Seventeen of them are civil cases and five are criminal cases.
Don't say
you are worried that I'll succeed with the opportunity?
That ungrateful punk.
All right. Today's the division commander's inauguration ceremony.
Make sure you're dressed properly and attend on time.
- That's all.
- Yes, sir.
And you...
Nothing.
Unity.
I've arrived at the hospital.
But how do you know Se Na is in this hospital?
Do Bae Man told me.
That military prosecutor doesn't disappoint.
At this age, it's going to be a big problem if she reports you.
Keep that in mind and make sure you don't browbeat her.
Yes, yes.
Han * Na
Se Na!
You are here.
I looked for you everywhere.
Take it.
Please.
I heard you went to the police station.
You know...
just because a person got stepped on accidentally,
doesn't mean they can have the other person's foot cut off.
Don't you think so?
Please.
Please don't do this.
Allen disappeared.
But it's not Allen I'm looking for.
It's the video.
Don't tell me you planned this with Allen to screw me over?
But what have you been clutching so tightly since before? Open your fist.
Please go. I'll shout.
Where have you hidden the video?
I said, where is it?
Division Commander is waiting for you.
Why is Mother here?
That bastard, Yong Mun Gu.
I'll escort you to the car.
Get in.
Mother. I will explain everything to you.
I heard everything from Lawyer Yong. Let's talk on the way.
We'll be arriving at Division Headquarters at 14:41. I'll depart now.
You know the Staff Judge Advocate is watching you, right?
Your military life is screwed once you get on his bad side.
I'll keep that in mind.
- Are you all right?
- Yes, I'm fine.
What punk—
That bastard.
Do you know him?
His name is Seol Ak. His father pocketed military supplies
and money earned by soldiers he sent off to construction sites.
Which is why I sent him off to prison.
That punk's gotten even bolder.
It's dangerous, so wait in the car for just a bit.
Yes, sir.
I guess it's time for me to warm up.
Shyster! I missed you so much!
My gosh. Do you get laser treatment on your skin?
Your skin is glowing, soldier.
What about your father's private meals? Have you been serving them to him well?
If you want to continue doing that, you have to become successful.
You little bastard.
He was an administrator for 20 years, so he'll have to serve the same amount of time in prison.
Don't worry. I am going to go see my father,
after I kill you.
Good. Visiting often is the best gift a son can give him.
Wait, no. Maybe reuniting with him in prison would be the best gift.
You dress trendy but you don't act it.
We're in a world where a self driving car is at level four.
But you brought lumber?
No matter how much AI changes the world,
it can never replace us.
No, it can't.
Hey, brothers. What are you waiting for?
This military shyster bastard. Finish him off right now!
Yes, Hyeongnim.
Hey!
- That's right!
- It hurts.
- You, come here.
- You come.
Go!
This is an expensive watch.
Hey!
Amazing.
Hold on.
Shyster Do. It's time to say goodbye now.
Goodbye, my foot. You don't even know how to spell it.
What time is it?
Hey, Cha Wu In. Don't come out, it's done.
Go on in. It's done. I'll be done soon.
What is she doing?
What is it, soldier lady? Are you going to spank us?
The division commander's inauguration ceremony will start in 20 minutes.
I really hate being late.
- What's with the tough guy act?
- Is that so?
- I'll volunteer to get hit.
- All right.
Hit me. Give it a go.
What are you doing? How much can a girl's whipping hurt?
Who is this little kid?
Get her!
♫ Hey, watch out y'all. I'm a little out of control ♫
♫ There's nothing surprising ♫
♫ Oh so pity. I can't help but gape ♫
♫ Just follow me, follow me on my roll ♫
♫ Even if I hide it, It's an obvious trick to me ♫
♫  That will judge everyone. ♫
♫ Cuz I'm the queen in flush alright ♫
♫ My zone. My zone. My zone. ♫
Cha Wu In. I knew my suspicions were correct.
♫ I'm going to bark viciously.  ♫
♫  Get out of my way please, please, please ♫
♫ See? See? It's useless ♫
♫ I will teach you a lesson, more, more, more♫
♫ I'm on my way.  ♫
♫ All sorts of things, Mayday Oh ♫
♫ Step out of my zone. My ♫
♫  My zone. My zone.  ♫
♫ Bye bye, it's over. Stop making excuses ♫
♫ Everyone has a hidden past ♫
♫ My, oh my look in my eyes ♫
♫ I'm coming after you ♫
♫ Your joker better be high ♫
♫ Cuz I'm the queen in flush alright ♫
♫ My zone. My zone. My zone. My zone. ♫
♫  I'm diggin' diggin' My zone ♫
♫ I'm going to bark viciously.  ♫
♫  Get out of my way please, please, please ♫
♫ See? See? It's useless ♫
♫ I will teach you a lesson more more more ♫
♫ I'm on my way.  ♫
♫ All sorts of things, Mayday Oh ♫
♫ Step out of my zone. My my zone. My zone ♫
♫ 'm going to bark viciously ♫
♫ Get out of my way please, please, please ♫
♫ See? See? It's useless  ♫
♫ I'll going to teach you a lesson, more, more, more  ♫
♫ I'm on my way.  ♫
♫ All sorts of things, Mayday Oh ♫
♫ Step out of my zone. My ♫
♫ My zone. My zone. ♫
Where did you learn this from?
Do you think it's strange for a soldier to beat up thugs?
You do the driving. It's been a while since I got some action. I need to rest.
Okay, sir.
♫ This time won't be the last and same like that before ♫
♫ Do whatever you want. Yeah I don't care ♫
Cha Wu In. You... what are you?
- I'll get going.
♫ I'm on fire like I'm gonna burn down. Yeah I'm losing my mind ♫
♫ Cuz you know there's no way to stop ♫
♫ Feels like I'm losing control ♫
Military Prosecutor Doberman
♫ No chance, you can't get away now ♫<
♫ You can't find your way out. You are the prey in my hand ♫
I am tracking Cha Wu In's real identity.
I was certain that he is someone I need for my plan.
You dare ask a military prosecutor to get you exempted from enlistment?
I really don't want to go to the military.
Because this is the army, we will pick up and check even a small mistake.
What are you saying right now?
I really like the way you work. You're different from Lawyer Yong who's always worrying about Mom.
There's a bunch of cops.
He must be warned.
Stop the car! You bastard!
Have you no conscience?
Do you have it or not?
♫  You've gotta pay for that ♫
♫ I'm not struggling hard any more. ♫