Die.
Hong Ji-a.
It's dangerous to stab
everywhere like that.
I told you, you have to stab it
in the heart in one go.
Let's try again.
Great job, my daughter.
Come on. That's too boring.
Mom, I don't want to become an exorcist.
Then what about vengeful spirits?
They can just stay in this world.
Staying in this world
as a spirit without a body is equivalent
to standing outside only in underwear
when there's a snowstorm
in the middle of winter.
If it's that cold, why stay?
That sounds foolish.
Because they can't leave behind
unfair things that happened to them.
That's why we need to help them leave.
We can help them forget
about their grudges
and be happy in a warm place.
Help me.
How did your mother pass away?
She died because of me.
You should go now. I'm tired.
You said I was special earlier.
Why don't you team up
with this special psychic?
Why would I?
I refuse to work with a fraud.
Didn't you beg me to do a case with you?
And we did just now.
Ms. Joo, please wire
Oh In-beom 20 million won.
Tell her your bank account number.
You think 20 million is chump change?
What's wrong with you?
Just do it. Why did you come here?
Mr. Oh, we Daebak Realty pays a psychic
two million won per gig.
She must've been out of her mind
and added another zero.
She said at least three times
that she'd pay me 20 million,
and I almost died
after being dragged upstairs.
-You went upstairs?
-Dragged?
You went up on your own.
And don't whine about passing out
for a few minutes.
He went up on his own?
To the room on the second floor?
So let's do as I said earlier.
You can pay me in installments.
I'm willing to work with you
until I get all the money.
I told you, I don't work with a fraud.
I've heard enough from you two.
I'll think it over favorably and call you.
You should leave for today.
I hope you make a reasonable decision.
-You know my number, right?
-I deleted it.
Then I'll call you. I didn't delete yours.
-Hire him as your psychic.
-Are you insane?
He uses spirits to scam people.
But he made it upstairs.
Look. Don't you see
how the salt has changed color?
Have you ever seen this glow so blue?
Well, I haven't.
What good is that if he can't help my mom?
But he gives you warmth
and absorbs vengeful spirits' memories.
It's not easy to find a psychic
who can make up for your weaknesses.
-I have no weaknesses.
-You have many.
I've been doing well
singlehandedly until now.
I never said it out loud,
but do you know how anxious I get
whenever you suffer from hypothermia?
-Nevertheless, I've been fine.
-Have you forgotten about Gonjiam?
You almost died there.
I almost died.
I didn't actually die.
Tell me the truth.
Is it me or Daebak Realty?
Hey, are you going
to abandon me and join Daebak?
I'm not abandoning you.
I just need to look
into something personal.
Aren't I your only personal matter?
You have neither parents nor siblings.
What personal thing?
This.
What?
How did you fix this?
-Did you glue it together?
-It's not mine.
Ms. Hong gave it to me.
But it looks the same
as the one your uncle gave you. How?
That's what I'm trying to find out.
What the relationship
between Daebak Realty
and my uncle was.
I thought it'd work this time.
You must've been startled.
I'm really sorry.
Next time,
I'll find a proper psychic, not a fraud.
You trust me, right?
DAEBAK REALTY
His spiritual energy is powerful enough.
I wonder why he wasn't
possessed by your mother's spirit.
-Maybe he isn't a virgin.
-He is.
He was possessed back at Dream Officetel.
He could've met a woman after that.
That quickly?
-We should look into that first.
-Yes.
Who is he?
He's the driver.
Make me the co-CEO.
And him, the chief.
Is he your plus-one or what?
We're not going to pay him.
Deal.
Ms. Joo, please show them the contract.
He's included, right?
Yes. My name is Heo Ji-cheol…
I'm your plus-one?
What?
What is this?
I must stay a virgin
until the contract ends?
Did you sleep with anyone
after the Dream Officetel incident?
-What?
-She's no joke.
Why must I answer that?
This is an invasion of privacy.
I'm not interested in your personal life.
I can only hire you as a psychic
once I confirm that.
What nonsense is this?
The harmony
between yin and yang is crucial.
If the psychic's yang is tainted,
they can't possess
a vengeful spirit with strong yin
and may end up dead.
He didn't sleep with anyone.
I've been by his side
ever since that incident,
so I can confirm that.
But I wasn't there
when he was with you, Ms. Hong.
-Did you two--
-Are you crazy?
Calm down.
So…
In any case…
Since it's been confirmed
that you're a virgin, let's seal the deal.
A virgin?
-I'm not.
-You are.
No, I'm not.
Don't say anything.
What? I didn't.
-Don't.
-What?
I said, don't.
Accommodation.
I found accommodations for us.
You virgin.
That little…
WE SERVE BREAKFAST AT 6:30 A.M.
CHANGHWA RESTAURANT
LODGING AVAILABLE
50 YEARS OF TRADITION
DIFFERENT MENU EVERY DAY
Don't tell me this is it.
Go inside first.
It's easy
to keep an eye on them from here.
And the chef will cook
whatever we want for us.
Hey, this is the room. Look.
There's underfloor heating as well.
Nice. Hey, come take a look.
Ta-da!
Well, this looks nice.
But this is so not my style.
DAEBAK REALTY
Thank you for the food.
Enjoy.
Wait.
This is for our next month's meals.
We're always grateful.
And please let us know
if your new tenants do anything shady.
And tell us what they do
when they don't do something shady.
Don't worry.
Bye.
Did you inhale that?
How can you inhale ribs?
Okay. Now.
Yes?
Now?
Okay.
Darn it.
Gosh. That was so close.
She was almost there.
-Yes.
-How did it go?
She didn't get to see it.
Should we try the secretary again?
But it didn't work last time.
Lee Eun-hye must see it with her own eyes.
Where are you now?
We're checking
if a building is haunted or not.
I can't believe I'm doing this.
Why don't you just perform an exorcism?
Why do you have to check?
Hey, partner.
Ms. Hong.
I asked you a question.
Why won't you answer it?
I told you earlier.
To perform an exorcism,
I need the name of the vengeful spirit.
Listen.
If you need the name,
check the name on the lease.
Why go through this trouble?
It's a reasonable question to ask.
The tenant lived here without a contract
and paid the rent upfront in cash
for a year.
This tenant was never here on paper.
A man who lived like a ghost
died and became a spirit.
Didn't what I just said sound
like a line from a poem?
Oh In-beom.
-I'm a CEO.
-What?
Don't call me by my full name.
Call me Mr. Oh.
Show some respect to your partner.
Hey, Oh In-beom.
Unless you're going to keep quiet,
just go home.
Gosh. The way you talk is quite hostile.
No partners start off on the right foot.
Don't you remember what Ms. Joo said?
You need me, Ms. Hong.
This special psychic.
A special psychic, my foot.
That's a load of nonsense.
By the way, what did she mean
by I'm like your heat pack?
Why am I your heat pack?
I'd rather strap
a heat pack on me instead.
By the way,
why do you keep looking around?
Whenever spirits move,
they leave traces like footprints.
Gosh. To find out who that guy was,
you should go through his garbage.
Goodness.
He had instant rice.
And he also drank.
It looks like he drank alone
without any friends.
Goodness.
He had a lonely life.
Why are you looking at me?
Well,
you should be careful.
You might end up dying alone too.
Says a virgin
who doesn't even have a house.
It's you who might die on the streets.
Gosh. I'm not a virgin--
What was that?
She must be insane. What's with her?
Turn around.
Show me your face.
Are you okay?
What are you doing?
Let me hold your hand for a bit.
What's that look on your face?
What?
What look?
You look like you have an ulterior motive.
You're unbelievable.
You held my hand first.
I have my reasons.
Gosh.
-Of course, you do.
-It's not what you think.
Whatever you have in mind, that's not it.
I can understand.
You held my hand,
but you don't want to admit your feelings.
It's not what you think.
When I hold your hand,
my body temperature goes up.
So when you hold my hand,
your body gets hot?
My goodness.
What a bold line.
It's not embarrassing at all.
Let me explain again.
My body temperature drops
when I'm near a vengeful spirit.
When I first started this job,
I almost died from hypothermia.
So when I perform an exorcism,
I bundle up
and try to finish it as fast as I can.
But strangely, when I touch you…
When my body comes in contact with yours,
my low body temperature
comes back up pretty quickly.
Does that only happen with me?
Not with other psychics?
-Why is that?
-I don't know either.
Anyway, to me, you are…
A special psychic.
Let's say I believe that.
Forget it. Let's go.
I'm exhausted today.
Yes, Ms. Joo.
I saw his face.
DAEBAK REALTY
-Enjoy.
-Thank you.
What about the art museum? Any progress?
I couldn't show Kwon's spirit to Lee
because she didn't come inside.
I need to try again today.
Right.
While I was waiting for her,
I hacked into Britium's server.
Recently, someone turned off
the security system
and entered the exhibition hall.
Who was it?
Lee Eun-hye.
-Lee Eun-hye?
-Yes.
Something didn't feel right,
so I did some digging.
Her insurance policy says
even if the exhibition gets delayed,
she makes a profit.
What if she staged this whole thing?
No.
It makes no sense to damage the museum's
reputation for some insurance money.
For now,
go through all the recent CCTV footage.
If we comb through all of it,
I'm sure we'll find something.
What?
We ordered hangover soup.
We're out
of cabbage leaves.
Then you should've told us
when we ordered.
Just eat it.
What is this?
It's super delicious.
It really is delicious.
Good shot.
Nice shot, Ms. Lee!
I haven't heard from you,
so I thought you were very busy.
But you don't skip your morning exercise.
Is there any reason
for me to contact you, Mr. Do?
Right.
I did receive a report
about your proposal regarding Britium.
I will go over it carefully
and contact you.
I'm just worried, especially now
that Chairman Kwon is no longer around.
There's a time for everything.
Thank you for your concern.
Did you find out anything
about Ms. Hong's mother?
There's a rumor
that she died while performing a gut rite.
-A gut rite?
-Yes.
But I don't get why she died like that.
Isn't it usually the possessed one
who dies from getting beaten?
Incense.
What?
Ms. Hong lit incense first
when preparing for an exorcism.
Yes, that cool-looking incense burner.
The smoke must cause hallucinations.
That must be
why I lost consciousness twice.
The hallucinating exorcist must've lost
her temper and died of a heart attack.
The client also must've died
from side effects of the hallucinations.
Ji-cheol, we need to draw up a plan.
A plan?
From the outside,
it looked like an ordinary realty office.
I know props are important
in this industry,
but these are just too good.
HANOK SAMGYETANG
Next group, please come in.
Thank you. Next.
This helmet…
What?
She's going back already?
Why isn't he picking up?
Right.
What? What's wrong with this?
I definitely charged it earlier.
Darn it.
The phone is turned off.
Leave a message after…
Why is his phone off?
I got scared for no reason.
By the way, why do I feel so chilly
whenever I come here?
What was that?
She should be more organized.
She has so many pairs of the same shoes.
What?
What's wrong with you?
You can't do this while I'm not home.
You can't make a mess like this, Mom!
-"Mom"?
-You hide after doing this?
I can't believe you! My God.
Why on earth did you take everything out?
I know you don't like these, Mom.
But each one
has its own distinctive detail.
Why did you mix up the pairs?
My gosh.
Ms. Hong!
Are you in? Ms. Hong!
What is it?
Mr. Oh…
-In-beom has gone missing.
-So?
-I was wondering if he was here.
-He's not. Look elsewhere.
I love you.
I fell in love with you at first sight.
The way you talk is so sexy.
And I love how violent you are.
-Go out with me.
-Are you insane?
I am, right?
I must've gone insane.
Gosh, I even have a girlfriend.
Forget I said anything, Ji-a.
I mean, Ms. Hong.
Then…
Goodbye.
Being beautiful is so tiring.
Darn it!
You startled me.
You should've called
and let me know that she was home.
I did.
-Anyway, you got the burner?
-Of course I did.
"Of course I did."
Take it.
Don't joke around. I'm not in a good mood.
What is that?
I swear I checked it
before putting it in my bag.
-It was definitely the incense burner.
-Are you okay?
Maybe there really is a spirit.
-I couldn't even reach you.
-Come on. There is no such thing.
I can't believe this.
DAEBAK REALTY
Couldn't we have met somewhere else?
Welcome, Deputy Director Kwon.
-Isn't the view breathtaking?
-I guess.
Has Eun-hye given you her answer yet?
I offered her half the original amount.
It's natural for her to hesitate.
Isn't half a bit too harsh?
Thirty percent would be
enough to have her step down as director.
You're more of a coward
than I thought you were.
-What did you say?
-In a redeveloping neighborhood,
you'll see houses
that have red flags outside.
Do you know what they are?
They're people
who are against the redevelopment.
I see.
But,
every single one of them
eventually put down their flags.
What Director Lee is doing
is just like putting up a flag.
However,
that won't work against me.
You should relax for the time being.
He's the one I saw in Mullae-dong.
The cause of death
was a cerebral concussion.
But he was already
in the final stage of lung cancer.
And the time of death
is about a month ago.
What's his name?
They can't identify him
because his fingerprints have worn out.
The landlord says he was an artist.
-None of his paintings are…
-Where did they get that file?
Even I couldn't hack into the NFS.
-Just in case…
-I bet someone's on the take.
There's not much.
You two.
If you have something to say,
come here and say it.
Should we?
If you give me that file,
I could look into him.
Really?
Do it then.
-What should I find out first?
-His name.
But how will you find something
that even the police couldn't?
Just leave it to me.
Using just a shadow
caught in a photo online,
I found out that world stars
Jung Jae-hun and Kim Se-hui were dating
when no one could.
-Why is he so enthusiastic about this?
-It's the power of love.
What do you mean?
Yes. What does she mean?
It's all your fault.
Let's end the meeting.
I'll go to Britium
and find his name myself.
See you.
Britium?
CHO HYEON-SEO'S
PRIVATE EXHIBITION
Weren't we working
on the Mullae-dong case? Why are we here?
Because it's the same vengeful spirit.
I don't think so.
Why? Because you two made up
the one here at Britium?
Come on. That's a bit harsh.
You know we couldn't even
get it started properly because of you.
Where did I see this?
Where was it again?
Yes! I saw it in Mullae-dong.
Judging by the accuracy,
the artist must've painted it there.
Did Cho Hyeon-seo
know the Mullae-dong painter?
Or…
Who are they to call me over
at this late hour?
I'm sorry. This is important.
This man right here is
the living legend of Korean art.
Mr. Cho Hyeon-seo, it's an honor.
Thank you.
Gosh, you have smooth hands.
I guess you take great care of them
since you're a great artist.
Ma'am, who are they?
This is Ms. Hong Ji-a, a realtor.
And as you both know,
this is Cho Hyeon-seo.
Please ask him.
What's the name of the model
in that painting of yours?
I know you're a realtor,
but you must know what self-portraits are.
Cho Hyeon-seo.
I'm talking about the real model.
What do you mean?
The real model?
Do you want to get sued for defamation?
Calm down. I'll talk to him.
Ms. Hong!
Is she crazy? It's a priceless painting!
She should've just beaten him.
You…
How dare you ruin my work?
-Do you know how much this is worth?
-I don't care.
Just tell me his name.
Tell me who really painted this piece.
I paint my own work.
I'm Cho Hyeon-seo!
Ask me that question one more time,
and I'll…
Your fingerprints would've worn out
if you finger painted for 20 years.
Yet you claim to have painted
all those paintings?
It hurts. Let go of this.
Tell me who this man is.
I don't know.
You just saw a spirit
in that painting, didn't you?
No.
Will you be tormented
by the spirit for the rest of your life?
Or will you tell me the name
and let me exorcise it?
Kim Byeong-ho.
Well, you see…
He was a temporary assistant of mine.
I didn't know that bastard had drawn it
under my painting like that.
I believe your assistant's painting
is the best one you've had.
-Ms. Lee…
-But then,
that painting will never
be shown to the world.
Right.
I'll take full responsibility
and take care of it.
Of course, you will.
And as for all of my paintings
in my studio,
I'll give them to your museum.
Of course,
the contract requires you to do so.
You must retire.
Pardon?
What do you mean?
When people find out
that you had a ghost artist,
the reputation of my museum
will be destroyed
as we've been sponsoring your work.
You are the fraud.
Why must my museum suffer the loss?
I'm the great Cho Hyeon-seo.
This is just a minor mishap. How--
You deceived me.
How dare you call it a minor mishap?
Just focus
on your special exhibition for now.
Afterward,
you will retire
quietly with your honor intact.
DIRECTOR LEE EUN-HYE
How dare she tell me to retire?
She's no more than a lowly businesswoman.
Damn her.
Darn it. Why isn't this working?
What's this? What's happening?
Oh, no. What's happening?
How did you know that there was
another painting behind the painting?
Don't tell me you could see through it.
What?
Whatever I find out on the job
is strictly confidential. That's my rule.
I see.
Just like how doctors and lawyers
keep information confidential?
I see. So you're a professional
like those people.
If you exploit the information
you found out today,
you might die.
Why do you keep making death threats?
Fine.
Okay. I won't.
God…
The ghost artist's name is Kim Byeong-ho.
Cho Hyeon-seo confessed everything.
Gather any evidence you can find.
I think we hit the jackpot.
Are you coming?
I'm coming.
-Did you look into it?
-Yes. I did.
Cho Hyeon-seo has two cell phones
under his name.
-Two?
-Yes.
So I tracked his phones.
He carries one with him.
And the other stays in only one location.
Yes! Hello.
-Take the food already.
-Okay.
What? We ordered soft tofu.
Do you know how heavy
the pots for soft tofu are?
My restaurant is right there.
Why did you make me deliver the food?
What a hassle.
Wait. But…
She didn't say anything
when we ordered it.
Wait a second. This smells awesome.
-All right. Let's eat.
-Let's eat.
-Here.
-Okay.
Nice.
All right.
So Cho Hyeon-seo has two phones
under his name?
One of the phones never left Mullae-dong.
That must be it.
That's the phone
the ghost artist was using.
Videos were automatically backed up
to the cloud from that phone.
VIDEOS
There are over a hundred videos.
I don't think Cho Hyeon-seo knows
these videos exist.
If he did, he would've already
deleted them. They're the proof.
Goodness. The ghost artist must have taken
the videos to blackmail Cho Hyeon-seo.
But he ended up dead
before he could do that.
Then I should do
what the late painter couldn't do for him.
This place is grand.
-Oh, no.
-What is it?
Nothing. Let's go inside.
Darn it.
That darned jerk.
Is this all?
You will get the remaining 113 videos
once you pay us.
This is odd. It seems less
than I was expecting.
Is it just me?
I'll give you
the rest of the money
once you get rid of all the spirits here.
I heard that you guys
get rid of spirits. Right?
I see.
That's why this place
became a melting pot of religions.
But that's too bad.
The lady you saw the other day,
Ms. Hong, handles exorcisms.
Then, get her here now.
Call her now.
Call Ms. Hong over now.
Seeing how you're going back on your word,
I guess you're okay
with the videos going viral.
Let's go, Chief Heo.
He's back again.
Don't go. Don't leave me.
Do something before you leave!
I'll give you all the money.
Please don't leave.
Really? I should sit down, then.
What are you doing? Sit down.
It's mine.
All of them!
They're all mine.
In-beom.
Hey, In-beom!
He's coming.
What?
-How are you here?
-I told you you might die.
What?
Gosh. What's going on?
Gosh. What just happened?
YONGIN POLICE STATION
So when you arrived,
the incident had already happened?
But how did you find that place?
My client asked me to go there.
-What's your client's name?
-Director Lee Eun-hye of Britium.
Lee Eun-hye.
Britium?
Just let her go.
What?
You can go.
I spoke with Britium's
legal representative already.
Wrap it up.
Wait, Ms. Hong, what about us?
Ms. Hong!
Don't bother. We didn't do
anything wrong, so we'll be released soon.
I doubt that.
-Why did you hit Cho Hyeon-seo?
-Come on. That wasn't hitting.
We were negotiating, nice and gentle.
Are you really going to keep lying
when we have evidence?
Evidence?
What is this?
What? When was it torn?
The woman who works there
saw it and even made a statement to us.
Chief Heo,
say something.
But I passed out,
so I don't remember anything.
Why are you trembling?
-Ji-cheol.
-Yes?
Earlier, when I…
I'm sorry.
But you were really scary earlier.
You were like someone else.
Stop him.
Hey, are you all right?
He's bleeding. Are you okay?
-What am I doing here?
-Are you crazy, kid?
Did you do this?
-No, it wasn't me.
-Then who was it?
-Look at him.
-How dare you lie to us!
Where are your parents?
You little…
Grandma.
Are you a psychic?
If you were born a psychic, this must've
happened often since you were little.
You are special.
Am I really a psychic?
I've been really possessed by spirits?
That's absurd.
My goodness.
I know In-beom is blinded by money,
but how could he go
into that dangerous place?
Once a fraud, always a fraud.
I'll kick him out
as soon as this exorcism is over.
What will you do
about the exorcism anyhow?
Did you find a way to lure it?
I'll lure it in with his work.
He is obsessed
with his own artworks, after all.
Then we'll have to do it
at Cho's studio or Britium.
Britium has taken
every single piece of art
that was in Cho Hyeon-seo's studio.
Lee Eun-hye moved fast.
So that just leaves Britium.
I'm sure Lee will never allow us
to do it where the artworks are.
I don't need her permission.
The exorcism will be performed
at the Mullae-dong studio.
The spirit has been unable
to leave this place.
It means there is another painting
hidden here somewhere.
Ms. Joo, I found the painting.
I'll take care of the rest.
This is Dongfang meiren.
It's excellent quality.
When I became Director of Britium,
you gave it to me as a gift.
To this day, it remains my favorite tea.
I thought you'd love it, and I was right.
How long has it been? Ten years?
I've been hearing news
from Chairman Han once in a while.
Chairman Han of the Masan investment firm?
Not only is he a VVIP of Daebak Realty,
but he's also our secret salesperson.
He appears to have great faith
in Ms. Hong's skills.
Yes, as you'll soon
see for yourself, ma'am.
Does that mean
you will take on the sale of Britium?
It is the sale of Korea's
finest art museum. Of course, we should.
However,
would you be willing
to grant us just one small favor?
Out. You're being released.
Get in.
-No.
-Thank you.
Wait, what about me?
I'm not in the car yet.
What are you doing?
Chief Heo didn't get in.
It's too dangerous for ordinary people.
Dangerous? Are we going
to do an exorcism right now?
I absolutely refuse.
Then you'll go to jail
for attempted murder.
Are you threatening me?
Turn the car around!
I'd rather go to jail.
You believe now, don't you?
That you're a psychic.
Please. Of course not.
When we signed our contract,
you didn't believe you were a psychic
or that vengeful spirits existed.
And that's why
you didn't hesitate to sign it.
Isn't that right?
That's right.
And I still don't believe it.
There's no such thing as ghosts.
Then why are you refusing to do this job?
If there are no spirits
and all my exorcisms are fake,
why are you suddenly
so scared to work with me?
What are you doing?
Hostage negotiations
to lure the vengeful spirit out.
Blackmail, in a way.
You just stand there,
and when I say so, take your necklace off.
If I
take this off…
I'll take care of the rest.
He came quickly.
Now. Take off the necklace.
Hurry!
Why are you trembling?
-Where are your parents?
-Where are they?
I can't do it.
I don't want a spirit
-to take over my body again.
-Hey.
We don't have much time.
You were right.
It's happened to me
a lot since I was little.
Now I know
that was spirit possession.
Do you know how many times
I woke up with bloody hands?
I don't want that…
to happen anymore.
Is this what you made your psychics do
to make money?
That's assault!
That's exactly why
you should've taken it off.
Due to that artist's memory,
I become teary-eyed all the time.
Ask Director Lee to return
one of his paintings.
He's already dead.
What are you doing? You're scaring me.
No way! I just painted
one of Cho Hyeon-seo's pictures.
The greatest painter of all time.
Oh In-beom is here to sell the painting.
Oh In-beom, that little…
-All your clients' requests are here?
-Why do you ask?
We're dealing with spirits here.
Does that mean neither the client
nor the exorcist is safe?
Mom, I'm sorry.