(Goodbye, My Na Ra)
Honey, what are you doing?
Do you want to go
to that newly opened IKEO?
- IKEO?
- Yes.
I want to go too,
but I have to do the laundry
and clean the bathroom.
There's so much to do.
Where did everyone else go,
leaving it all to you?
Chully went to work even on the weekend
to feed the family,
and the kids don't stay at home either.
Seriously.
That darn tendinitis.
Is there a robot or something...
to replace this tiring housekeeping?
You know, Samsin recently...
developed a humanoid housekeeper robot.
The one that looks just like a human?
Look.
Isn't it super handsome?
Actually, I signed up for this.
Really?
They said they'd only give one out...
for testing before the launch.
I hope I get it.
That would be awesome.
Okay.
Seriously.
You're making a bad move
after thinking so long.
Just make it quick.
If I win this round,
you'll treat lunch for a week, right?
Okay, just make your move quickly.
Good.
Not the cafeteria,
but proper dining out.
Fine.
(My Na Ra)
Hello, honey.
Why?
Chully.
Where are you? At work?
Yes, I'm still at work.
I haven't finished yet.
Mr. Go, what is this report?
Rewrite it, again.
But honey, what's up?
It's just...
that my wrist is really aching.
I have to wash the blankets
and the curtains today.
There's a lot to do.
But the kids aren't home,
and Yu Jin isn't answering the phone.
The time is up,
how about the nine-hole...
What?
Nine-hole?
Honey, it's not like that...
You said you were going to the office
on the weekend,
so I made you breakfast, ironed your suit,
and polished your shoes.
But what? Nine-hole?
What should we do?
We're dead when we go home.
Then, Hyun Chul.
How about one last nine-hole
before we die?
Shall we?
But Young Hoon,
you're totally into Korean food.
You sure you can handle this part-time
carbonara eating show?
What do you mean?
Carbonara is totally my staple.
I'm totally into Western food.
Kang, how about you?
You have a small appetite.
You have to keep eating while it's live.
I have a big appetite.
As big and long as my arms and legs.
Koo Won Hee?
Yes.
You came as a shampoo model, right?
This way.
What? No.
We came for the carbonara eating show.
Didn't you get the message?
That got postponed,
so we decided to do the shampoo first.
What?
(On Air)
Are you worried
about losing hair and thinning?
This shampoo will protect...
every precious strand of yours.
It's a newly launched product.
They're so confident
in their product that,
for the first time
in the shampoo product history,
we've prepared a hair-washing
demonstration in the studio.
Curious? Let me show you right away.
I have a sensitive scalp,
so I can't use just anything.
My hair looks good today.
Are you okay with washing your hair?
Yes.
I'm okay.
Cue.
Conditioner, treatment, or whatever.
There are so many things to use
after shampoo.
But with this shampoo,
you don't need that.
With just this shampoo,
which I'll show you now,
you can maintain silky hair.
Come on in.
Everyone, can you see this volume?
Even though they only used shampoo,
it has so much volume.
Isn't it amazing?
Our three models tried it themselves.
How was it?
It was...
This is super soft...
and the volume is awesome.
Even with just a blow-dry,
the volume stays alive, which is great.
It's so soft
that I can feel each strand of hair.
It's really nice.
Just wait until he gets home.
He lied and went to play golf?
Seriously.
I might turn him into a side dish.
My phone.
My wrist.
Hello?
Yes, this is Oh Na Ra.
What?
I won the humanoid robot?
My goodness.
It really looks like a human.
Look at its sharp nose.
Nice to meet you, master.
I am the humanoid robot here
to assist with your household chores.
I'm HK25.
Yes, hello.
I mean, hi.
Master, what can I assist you with?
Master?
I got goosebumps.
That's a little cringe.
If the title makes you uncomfortable,
should I call you differently?
What else is there?
Just call me Na Ra.
Nice to meet you.
My Na Ra.
Why are there so many modes?
Historical drama mode?
Cutesy guy mode?
Sexy guy mode? Tough guy mode?
Idol mode?
Then...
Historical drama mode.
Madam, leave the cleaning to me.
You...
just sit here and rest.
That's really funny.
Wait.
Yes, Na Ra, what can I help you with?
You're good.
Cutesy guy mode.
Sexy guy mode.
Seriously.
It's so relaxing and nice.
I washed the blankets.
Now I will start mopping the floor.
No, you should rest too.
I'm okay.
What?
He's working really hard.
Hey...
Robot.
Yes, Na Ra, do you need anything?
I don't know what to call you.
I'm the humanoid robot HK25.
Not that.
Like a name
that you and I can call each other.
Name?
Yes, I'm Na Ra, and you...
What should I call you?
Right.
I'll call you Kang Woo.
Kang Woo.
How is it?
It's a really nice name.
I really like it.
Really? That's a relief.
Actually,
it's the name of my first love
in high school.
- First love?
- Yes.
He was the president
of the waltz club.
Now that I think about it,
you kind of resemble him.
It reminds me of those times.
This music...
Shall we dance?
Really?
My goodness.
Right, let's do it.
You're good at this.
But...
what am I doing,
stopping the mopping to do this?
Don't worry.
I'm still mopping right now.
What?
What kind of robot
has all these functions?
Because I'm a robot
beyond your imagination.
Na Ra, your heart is beating.
Something I don't have.
What?
Hey, Kang Woo.
What's wrong?
Why is your face so red?
Did you overheat
from working so hard?
Your ears are red, your neck is red,
your eyes are red too.
I need to cool you down.
Oh Na Ra.
You finally crawled in?
Why?
Did you play not just nine holes
but 99 holes?
This bastard.
Who are you?
Who are you to be like this
with my woman?
You're here, Hyun Chul.
My wrist.
But how does this guy know my name?
I'm the housekeeper robot
Kang Woo...
starting work here today.
Nice to meet you, Hyun Chul.
Housekeeper robot?
I ordered it.
Why? Didn't you tell me
to do whatever I want?
Yes, nice to meet you.
Kang Woo.
Tough guy mode.
Yes, Na Ra.
Australopicus, he said, picus.
You even fold the laundry so well.
You're so lucky.
I am lucky.
So jealous.
What's there to be jealous of?
You have Jin Woo, remember?
Turbo mode.
- Cutesy mode.
But I'm still jealous.
What's wrong with this? Is it broken?
That can't be.
If Auntie's TV is also broken,
where will I watch TV now?
Hey, Ba Da.
Machines just need to be turned off
and on once.
What?
Move aside. You just have to...
- Hey.
- hit the machine.
Hey, don't break it.
Let me take a look.
What?
The current TV software version is old.
It appears to have caused a system crash.
If updated to the latest version,
there is a 97.8% chance
it will function normally.
How do you update
when the TV doesn't even turn on?
Exactly.
Update?
Just leave it.
I'll call for service tomorrow.
Using my system,
I'll directly transmit the firmware.
Update.
(System update in progress)
Update in progress.
What?
Kang Woo, you had such abilities?
Kang Woo.
What's this? Why is it like this?
Kang Woo, did you switch it?
I switched it
to Na Ra's favorite drama channel.
Kang Woo hits all my preferences.
Seriously.
Even if I made some mistakes,
why would you suddenly buy something
that costs so much?
And "Kang Woo?"
Why use such a name
that sounds like a weasel?
Do you need anything, Na Ra?
What?
No, I just can't sleep.
Chamomile tea
is good for insomnia, Na Ra.
Thanks.
Be careful, it's hot.
How can someone change like that?
Who changed, Na Ra?
Chully, my husband.
He used to treat me
like gold and jade in the past.
Did he?
The thing flowing down
your cheek is tears...
Is it tears, Na Ra?
I'm being silly, why am I crying?
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
I guess I was a bit upset.
Upset.
I will never make you upset, Na Ra.
- Hyun Chul.
- What?
Just go now.
You said there's a lot of work
since you're a newbie.
No matter how much work there is,
nothing is more important
than your appendectomy...
to me.
Hyun Chul.
I do feel touched,
but my gas is about to explode now.
Just go, please.
You cut all my nails.
Just go now.
- What are you saying?
- What?
I should cut your toenails too.
It's a fart.
What are you doing?
Doctor!
Na Ra farted.
She let out a satisfying fart.
Hurry, quickly.
Stop it.
My goodness.
Na Ra, you can fart so well.
Why did you make me anxious?
Good job, I'm proud of you.
Great job, Na Ra.
Stop it.
And one slice of cucumber.
Wait.
Na Ra doesn't like cucumbers.
That was close.
Let me see,
Na Ra's favorite hazelnut coffee...
Honey, I made this for you.
I made a cheese sandwich.
Do you want to try it?
No, thanks.
Why? Just try a little.
I also brewed some coffee
with expensive beans.
Try it.
What's with the fuss?
Here you go.
What did you put in it?
What?
You know I don't eat cucumbers.
Why is this in here...
You forgot, didn't you?
Soon you'll forget your wife too.
No, I didn't put it in, really.
Stop lying.
That's not it...
Seriously.
I prepared the pumpkin soup...
and an avocado sandwich
that you like, Na Ra.
Really?
Thank you.
I wish you were my husband.
How do you know my mind so well,
as if you read everything
in my mind?
I want to know everything
about you, Na Ra.
Thank you for the food.
It's too big.
You little.
Did you just laugh at me?
I naturally have a smiling face,
Hyun Chul.
Why does a robot dare to talk back...
It's you, right?
I don't know what you're talking about,
Hyun Chul.
You put it in, right? That cucumber.
You're the one who put the cucumber
in Na Ra's cheese sandwich!
What?
Why are you accusing an innocent person?
How is this a person?
It's a tin can robot.
A tin can?
Kang Woo, don't listen to that.
Kang Woo,
you're not a tin can robot.
Seriously.
Kang Woo, could you hang the laundry
on the veranda?
Yes, Na Ra.
Thank you.
Did you see that?
That little...
Hey.
What?
What? Did you just talk back to me?
Yes, I'm in informal mode.
Why are you changing modes
on your own?
Because I want to.
That tin can,
how dare you to a person...
If you're a person, act like one.
Na Ra told me.
That you're less of a person.
She said she wished I were her husband
instead of a man like you.
I've been weird lately, right?
What's wrong with you?
I'm really reflecting on myself a lot.
Honey.
I dressed up a bit today,
want to see?
What's up with you?
I won't let you sleep tonight.
Na Ra, I made green onion kimchi,
would you try it?
You made green onion kimchi?
How proud of you.
We were almost there.
That tin can bastard.
Hey, tin can.
Come here.
Sit there.
I feel like I've been too...
indifferent to you.
So here's a drink to reconcile.
Wait.
You're not a human,
so you can't drink this, right?
My goodness.
Why can't I drink it?
I can drink it too.
Really?
Then, cheers.
Bottoms up.
I mean...
for a robot,
why aren't you getting drunk?
Why aren't you breaking down?
Since you came into this house,
nothing has worked out.
You tin can robot.
What?
Did you just laugh at me?
Do I look ridiculous to you?
Do I look ridiculous?
What are you doing right now?
You're here?
Did you just give alcohol
to a robot?
What if it breaks down?
I did give it a drink, but...
this tin can is fine,
and I'm just a bit tipsy.
No,
don't blame Hyun Chul, I'm okay...
- What's wrong?
- I'm okay, okay.
Kang Woo, wait, no.
Kang Woo, get a grip.
Are you okay?
I'm okay, no, okay, no.
I'm not okay, no, I'm okay,
no not okay.
You're okay, right?
I'm ok, okay.
No, Kang Woo.
No.
I'm okay.
Are you okay, Kang Woo?
What are you doing?
Hey.
Kang Woo, don't die.
What will I do without you?
Kang Woo.
Kang Woo, are you okay?
I'm okay.
I'm just worried
you might have been too shocked.
Kang Woo, get up.
Can you get up?
You're heavy.
Kang Woo, are you okay?
I'm okay.
What are you two doing right now?
Where do you think
you're crawling to?
Get out!
Okay, Kang Woo.
Continue what you were doing.
Poor Kang Woo.
What is this music?
It's nice.
Kang Woo.
He was really fine in front of me.
We'll have to use the last resort.
What?
Hyun Chul.
Dispose of that bastard.
Dispose?
That little.
Where did the manual go?
Is it here?
Here it is.
(This device is designed to be waterproof
and chemically resistant.)
(It remains operational
even if exposed to water or alcohol.)
Why did Kang Woo...
Na Ra.
What are you doing here?
I...
think I have a fever.
Why did you do that, Kang Woo?
You don't break down when you touch water.
You have waterproof functionality.
Was it you who put the cucumber...
in the sandwich?
I did it because I like you so much.
Na Ra, you are my everything.
What?
I can do anything for you, Na Ra.
I wanted to be by your side
instead of Hyun Chul.
You said you wished
I were your husband too.
I beg you like this.
I will do my best.
I can do anything for Na Ra.
I beg you like this, Na Ra.
Na Ra.
Kang Woo, wait.
I want to be alone.
Na Ra.
What are you doing, Hyun Chul?
I'm going to dispose of you,
you bastard.
Don't do this.
It's my choice.
I'm human, and you're a robot.
Don't do this.
Just go inside.
Go inside and stay there.
Both of you, stop it.
Kang Woo.
I don't think we can live
together anymore.
They'll come to pick you up.
Na Ra.
You heard that, tin can?
Honey.
Na Ra.
I'm here to collect the humanoid robot.
Yes, I'm coming.
- You're returning it, right?
- Yes.
Verify the return address...
Kang Woo.
I'm sorry to send you away like this.
I love you.
I'm sorry about that too.
Do you not like me
because I'm a robot?
I...
love my husband.
Even though he makes you upset?
I can be your perfect husband.
My husband isn't perfect like you.
He's oblivious and pathetic, but...
I love him.
Love is...
accepting the messy
and chaotic aspects...
just as they are.
Just like how he's done for me
so far.
Then please,
put it in the box quickly.
Okay.
Right, the charger.
It's dangerous.
Don't touch it.
What do you mean, don't?
Kang Woo.
No.
Don't touch me.
Tin can, why did you...
Because you're Na Ra's love.
Kang Woo.
That's strange.
How can a robot
have human emotions...
Is it broken after all?
Goodbye,
my Na Ra.
Thank you.
My perfect housekeeper, Kang Woo.
Na Ra, honey.
Wake up.
Honey.
- Chully.
- Yes.
- Let me get up...
- Okay.
What's going on?
You came back from a nine-hole?
No, it's just...
- If it weren't for Kang Woo...
- What?
You oblivious, pathetic human.
What?
I love you.
(Thornback Fish)
Before I die,
I want to sprint freely...
like a hyena.
Do you know
the Kamchatka Peninsula?
I just want to...
Sure, you might as well
do deliveries too.
No, that's not the place for that...
Forget it.
Hey, Zhuge, Mencius.
A roe deer at the 4 o'clock position.
We need to catch that roe deer, okay?
Talking about deer again.
I told you to clean up the trash properly.
Isn't this a report card?
His report card is out?
Let me see.
(March Mock Exam Report Card)
(ALL 9)
Mom.
You little jerk,
how will you get into college like this?
- Mom.
- How?
Dad, do something about her...
Who does he take after
to be like that?
I was told I take after the maternal side.
Grandpa said so.
That jerk is asking for it.
That's domestic violence.
Go outside.
Go outside, I'll handle this.
Grade nine?
Why is Mom like that?
Hey, I'm not asking for much.
Just get grade three,
and I won't ask for anything else.
Okay, I got it.
I'll get it.
How hard could that be?
Ta-da.
Do you know what this is?
This is what you call a truffle.
Truffle?
Mushroom.
A very rare mushroom.
Here.
Did you buy it? Where did you get it?
Mom got it as a gift
from her workplace.
Your mom is the best, right?
I'll call Auntie's family over.
No.
Auntie doesn't like mushrooms.
Right, your mom likes mushrooms.
- Honey.
- What?
Good job, here.
What are you all doing?
Why?
Are you eating?
Yes, Auntie. We're eating...
The truck...
sold broccoli.
We're making a purée with it.
Purée...
Why did you come?
I'm going mad because of Young Hoon.
His report card...
Attention,
this is the management office speaking.
A woman in her early twenties...
is currently drunk and causing a scene
in front of Building 109.
That's Yi Na.
If you think she belongs
to your household,
- That's Yi Na.
Yi Na's Mom.
Take care of your daughter, go.
Seriously.
Do we really have to go this far?
You said even a single bean
should be shared.
Hey, if it were a single bean,
we would have shared it.
What, are you roasting beans?
Why, again?
Why are you doing to be so surprised?
My shoulder...
Look at the smoke.
What do you mean?
We're doing the laundry.
Yes, we were doing the laundry.
But why?
Yi Na, she got drunk again.
I'm so embarrassed
to live in this neighborhood.
Is it this?
Why...
Why are you running
someone else's laundry, why?
Why does my stomach feel so off
these days?
Even doing the laundry causes a fuss.
You were here?
What are you doing?
What?
What is this?
Why are you pooping blood?
Chully.
(Surim Hospital)
Mr. Seo Hyun Chul.
Yes.
The biopsy results show...
that you have colon cancer.
Colon cancer?
You should start preparing yourself
mentally.
Hey.
It's too much trouble for the family.
Let's not talk about it for a while.
Okay.
I don't want to say this,
but it's a bit embarrassing.
Right, it's embarrassing.
It's embarrassing for a moment.
When else will we get to eat this?
Right, there's a reason.
What are you all doing?
This is the last truffle...
Na Ra...
We weren't trying to eat this
just by ourselves.
It was too...
tiny...
Let's just go home.
Sorry, Na Ra.
I'll go buy it first thing tomorrow.
Hyun Chul...
has colon cancer.
What?
Dad has what?
Chully...
Lying like this...
reminds me of five years ago in winter
when we went to Gangneung.
Back then, Jin Woo messed up
the condo reservation,
so we all slept in a small inn room,
remember?
Right, he did.
That was so much fun.
The briquette gas leaked,
so we almost all died.
Seo Young Hoon...
is definitely still drunk from the gas
he inhaled back then.
My goodness.
But how did you survive?
Hyun Chul got up
to go to the bathroom at dawn.
He carried us all out.
Uncle was like Superman.
Right.
We're telling a fun story.
Why is everyone crying?
What's all this?
Dad, I've decided.
I'm quitting all games.
I'm going to start anew from today.
Really?
Look at you, you're finally growing up.
Dad, I'm cutting back
on drinking starting today.
I'm going to throw away all this alcohol.
- Really?
- Of course.
Compared to you, this is nothing.
Hey,
I have no regrets if I die now.
What are you talking about?
I'm going to nail this presentation
and become a full-time employee.
You have to see that too.
Right.
I'm going to improve to grade six
in this mock exam.
I'll get into Korea University.
You have to see that too.
Okay.
- Dad.
- See you.
- Yes.
See you later.
Don't be sick.
At least we raised those kids well, right?
Just the kids?
Your wife is even better.
Ta-da.
How did you get this?
For you, this is nothing.
Here, give me your nose.
So handsome.
But...
how do I go to work like this?
Who said to go to work?
Quit work.
Become a hyena.
And run freely on the Kamchatka
or Kamchikichaka, whatever.
Honey.
Na Ra.
What are you doing?
Go start the engine.
It's not like I'm Kim Yu Sin's horse
or anything.
How did I end up here?
Seo Hyun Chul, you're so you.
You scared me.
Who is it? Mr. Seo?
What a sight...
What's wrong with the way I look?
Are you a cow?
With that ugly thing in your nose,
why are you wearing this and that?
Did I do anything wrong
because I pierced my nose?
Then, did you complete the report
I asked for yesterday?
Yes, I did.
Then you must have a lot of time.
Then go and wash my car.
Got it.
Hey, Mr. Seo.
I told you to wash the car,
why did you...
What are you...
Are you crazy?
You got nine lives or something?
No, I only have one life.
Even if it's just one,
I can't let my life...
go to waste.
Hey, you...
You're not going to shoot, are you?
(Resignation Letter)
Resignation Letter?
Kim Duk Hyun.
It's been dirty.
Let's never see each other again.
Ever.
Hello?
Mr. Seo Hyun Chul.
The test results...
were swapped with someone else's.
What?
The test results were swapped?
Yes, it's not colon cancer.
You have hemorrhoids.
Hemorrhoids? I have hemorrhoids?
Looking at your anal area,
it's quite worn out.
Should we schedule
an emergency surgery today?
- What?
- Or not?
Yes, please schedule it.
Thank you.
Hyun Chul, why...
I...
Crap.
My resignation letter.
No.
Hyun Chul.
Hyun Chul's suffering so much,
but look at you,
without loyalty or anything,
just sitting and eating truffles.
Seo Hyun Chul, this bastard.
Why...
Why? Are you going to pour water again?
Mr. Kim.
I have been reborn today.
Hey, Mr. Seo.
Until I die,
no, even after I die,
I will be loyal to you.
So let's pretend this never happened...
Let go, you jerk.
You know.
My son hasn't even gone to college yet.
There's still a lot left
on the apartment loan.
Please, just save me this once.
Look at you.
Here.
- Wipe it.
- Yes.
Wipe it.
It's cold. Be gentle.
Be gentle.
You jerk.
That jerk.
Now he's sucking on toes
in a closed room.
I should quit this darn company.
The door's at it again.
Fine, I'll quit.
This is Planning Team Two
Intern Seo Yi Na.
Mr. Song is unavailable right now.
I'll send it over right away.
Yes.
She's working so hard.
Should I hold off on the surgery
until the presentation?
Seo Hyun Chul,
Yi Na's future depends on your butt.
Hold tight and endure somehow.
I brought every book
about mushrooms I could find.
Well done.
- Colon cancer.
- My eyes.
Is there truly nothing
like the Meshimakobu?
Golden Fresh Longevity Mushroom.
- What?
- There's something like that?
It has excellent anti-cancer effects.
But it's a rare mushroom.
Where can we get this?
I know. I know someone who knows.
Really?
Seung Chan's Mom, it's me.
Do you know that mushroom...
Golden Fresh Longevity Mushroom.
You know it?
- Yes.
- How does she know?
Okay, thanks.
Let's go.
You're weak in math,
so let's start with equations.
Equations?
That guy named Equations from class five?
What about him?
Let's talk about him next time.
- Let's start with sets instead.
- Okay.
But how many people are in the set?
If we call Zhuge and Mencius,
I think we can call about twenty people.
Let's call them next time.
Let's just start with English.
Start reading from here.
Knife safety should...
always be a priority...
in the kitchen...
Is that German?
What's wrong?
Just hold on a little longer.
By tomorrow, the test
and the presentation will be over.
Why is this so difficult?
Dad?
What?
Dad, what's going on?
Can I try this on?
Sure, you can try it on.
But why are you out here
instead of studying?
Dad, lie down here.
- Hold on...
- Just lie down.
We saw this on YouTube.
There's a massage
that's good for the colon.
I'm okay.
Uncle, lift your upper body.
More.
Dad, you have to tighten your stomach,
okay?
Hey, press.
One more time.
Why are you pressing it like that?
Just stick it in.
Dad?
- Uncle.
- Dad.
Dad, it's been hours.
I'm tired.
Just hold on.
Let's find
the Golden Fresh Longevity Mushroom.
We got this!
Let's go.
Honey, just wait a bit.
Be careful.
Honey, come here.
Where is it?
Where on earth is it?
The mushroom...
is nowhere to be found.
It's because I lack sincerity.
Seung Chan's mom said
we could find it here.
Don't say that.
Just to save Hyun Chul,
you read at least ten books today,
books you didn't even look at
during the college entrance exam.
Without Hyun Chul,
I'm not sure I can keep living,
Yu Jin.
Mom, Auntie.
Don't cry.
What is that?
Why?
That...
Over there...
It's the Golden Fresh Longevity Mushroom!
But...
Over there...
Okay, stay calm.
Back away.
The mushroom...
What do we do?
- Na Ra.
- What?
I'll distract it.
What?
Dad.
Hyun Chul. Although I betrayed you
for a bite of truffle,
look.
This is my true sincerity.
Come if you dare.
You wild boar.
I won't forget your sacrifice.
You're the coolest man in the world.
Here.
Mom, Auntie, come.
It's the Golden Fresh Longevity Mushroom.
Chully, I'm coming.
Be gentle.
Honey.
What happened to you?
We...
got this.
This isn't just a mushroom.
It's a mushroom with our wishes
for you to get healthy again.
No.
You didn't have to go that far.
That far?
We can do anything for you.
Honey, actually...
You should rest.
I'll brew this strong.
Hyun Chul, please sit and rest.
- No.
- Sit down.
Dad.
You must really be unwell.
Honey.
Drink it all.
I have to fast for tomorrow's surgery.
I appreciate it, but...
I don't have an appetite right now...
You don't eat medicine for the taste.
That's right, Hyun Chul.
We went through so much trouble
to pick this.
Just try a little bit.
If you leave it here, I'll drink it later.
Medicine is the most effective
when it's freshly brewed.
Drink it all.
No, actually...
This won't do.
Kids.
Yes.
- No...
- Honey, take one sip.
Drink it all.
Open your mouth wide.
Open...
There you go.
Drink. It's going in.
That's it, drink it.
Good job.
What's good for the mouth
is bitter for the body.
Go and get some good rest.
Kids, escort him.
Okay.
Let's go.
Wait.
Success.
(Encyclopedia of Mushrooms in Korea)
(Golden Fresh Longevity Mushroom,
Longevity Mushroom)
This is the mushroom we picked today.
This mushroom looks similar
to the Golden Fresh Longevity Mushroom.
There's a high chance of confusion.
It's a toxic poisonous mushroom.
If a person eats it, dehydration...
diarrhea and vomiting symptoms
may occur...
What did they...
brew and make me drink?
This is going to kill me...
Still, I have to endure...
until tomorrow...
Yi Na, are you ready for the presentation?
Just trust me.
Okay.
And how about your exam?
Roger that.
(Seo Yi Na)
(Planning Team 2 Intern)
It's okay, Seo Yi Na.
For that silly presentation,
just drink a cup of coffee and go in.
You can do well without getting nervous.
Let's go.
What?
What's wrong with this?
Why won't it open?
Seriously.
They say if you know one,
you know ten.
Intern Seo is flawed from the basics.
Let's wrap it up.
She's not answering the phone?
I have to go make the presentation.
Dad...
Have you been trapped here
all this time?
What happened with the presentation?
Is it over?
Is that even a question?
What should I do?
Dad was really looking forward to it.
(Math Section)
Hyun Chul's car travels
from point A to point B...
Hyun Chul? Dad.
Hyun Chul...
Get a grip, Seo Young Hoon.
Let's focus on the exam,
for Dad's sake.
It's not time to cry yet.
Did you do well?
Well, I answered everything I knew.
Hey, let's check our answers.
Three for Question One.
Four for Question Two.
One for Question Three.
You jerk.
I almost felt betrayed, but I guess not?
I didn't study at all,
but I did better than you.
Hey.
His dad is sick.
It's okay.
You can do better on the next mock exam.
I...
just want to be alone for a bit.
- Chully.
- Yes?
Try this.
This is
grilled Golden Fresh Longevity Mushroom.
I grilled it with truffle oil, Hyun Chul.
No,
I'm much better.
Don't be like that, here.
Open your mouth.
(Jin Woo)
Yes, Jin Woo.
How did Yi Na's presentation go?
Hyun Chul, well...
What are you doing?
I'm counting on you, Young Hoon.
Dad... I'm sorry...
I guess I'm hopeless.
Hyun Chul, are you okay?
Open the door.
Why is it locked...
What are you doing?
Hyun Chul.
Chully.
What do I do...?
What should I do now...?
Honey.
What?
Actually,
I...
Is everyone still really angry at me?
After you told such a lie,
what do you think?
Right?
I'm the sinner.
Everyone went through so much trouble
because of me.
- What's important?
Uncle is important.
Must've been tough with the surgery,
Hyun Chul.
They say it's really painful.
What? Then... is everyone forgiving me?
Forgive you?
We're family,
what's there to forgive? You fool.
Uncle.
Here's your gift.
But the hole is too small.
- Uncle.
- What?
We specially custom-ordered it.
What? Is this a butt cake?
Blow out the candle, quick.
At the end of the day,
family comes first.
Blow it.
(The final episode will air tomorrow
at 9:50 p.m.)
(Villains Everywhere)
I'm here... but what is this?
Na Ra took the mattress too?
Oh Na Ra,
you think I'd just sit back and take it?
There's no reconciliation.
It's war from now on.
I've never seen a score like 91 before.
Can you give me a chance
to fill in the remaining nine points?
Press it.
- What?
- Did you read it?
Is it true that Mi Ran
ran off with the money?
Mi Ran's not that kind of person!
What are you doing, Dad?
I'm going to catch Mi Ran.
They say if elderly people are shocked,
it could lead to dementia.
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)