♪I wrote a stroke♪
♪About you and me♪
♪You pass like the wind♪
♪I follow like a leaf♪
♪But just you and me♪
♪Had no happy ending♪
♪Perhaps it was just a chance encounter♪
♪I turn memories over with great care♪
♪Afraid to lose the past♪
♪Tears fall quietly with the plot♪
♪Shattered with no response♪
♪The wind once♪
♪Through layers of mist♪
♪And snowy scenes♪
♪Gently cradled the leaf in my palm♪
♪But♪
♪Winds will cease♪
♪Leaves will wither♪
♪Our meeting was too fleeting♪
♪It's an unavoidable fate♪
♪I too once♪
♪Walked through♪
♪A sea of people♪
♪Unafraid of how far it is♪
♪Racing under stars toward you♪
♪But♪
♪Time is heartless♪
♪You never yield♪
♪Let love remain♪
=Spring Night=
=Episode 7=
Mai Tian,
go help me chop the herbs.
Mai Xiang.
Come here.
I'll ask you something.
Go ahead.
Answer me truthfully.
Okay.
While I was away doing corvée labor,
did your sister have a secret affair?
Secret affair?
Don't understand?
I mean, was she involved
with another man?
Wuming,
your jealousy is showing!
Yes or no? Answer me.
Whether there was or not,
a real man
should be broad-minded.
Nian.
We remain
a disgraced official's children.
Once I'm recommended
by the Prime Minister
and enter the court,
I can clear Father's name.
Then we'll be reunited openly.
May Crown Prince find peace
and smooth sailing
in the next life.
If so many things hadn't happened,
we probably
would have been married by now.
I wouldn't have made
such a grave mistake.
We meet again.
If you don't mind,
let's share a drink.
I don't know why,
but even though I don't know you,
every time I see you,
you feel strangely familiar.
I always end up sharing
what's on my mind.
Cheers.
People gather and part.
Life vanishes like bubbles.
Since we have this fleeting encounter,
what troubles you?
I'd be glad to hear it.
You're right.
After all, it's just a chance meeting.
Just listen, then forget it.
What happened?
Well,
I had an old friend.
We grew up together
and were practically betrothed.
But fate was unkind.
He died
while still young.
The absurd thing is
that I don't even know how he died.
But you know what?
Right now,
I kind of envy him.
Death is easy.
Life is hard.
My childhood friend died.
My long-lost elder brother.
I finally reunited with him.
But I...
But we...
I can't tell you.
Mai Tian.
Ye Wuming.
I've looked everywhere.
Going out drinking without inviting me?
You poured for me.
Here.
No more drinking.
You want a drink?
Come to me.
I can hold my liquor.
What are you doing?
Ye Wuming!
You're insane!
I have a high tolerance.
Stop trying to act tough.
You two know each other well?
We're complete strangers.
Then what are you doing now?
A chance encounter.
A chance encounter?
Once is happenstance.
Twice is coincidence.
Three times? Still coincidence?
I may have amnesia,
but I'm not stupid!
You've been pestering my wife, right?
You're overthinking it.
Absolutely not.
It must be you.
You want to have two men at once.
Nonsense!
How can you say that?
He defends you so fiercely.
You say you're strangers?
I don't buy it.
It's a marriage of chance.
Believe what you will.
Yes.
It's a marriage of chance between us.
Mai Tian.
If when we married,
you already loved another,
I won't play the villain
who tears lovers apart.
It's not like that. He and I...
(Right now,)
(to divorce him,)
(I can do anything.)
(Forgive me.)
(I'll use you.)
Fine.
Then let's divorce.
You want to divorce me?
Because of him?
(Best if they divorce.)
(No more trouble.)
I'll ask one last time.
In your heart,
who matters more?
Me or him?
♪Tears fall quietly with the plot♪
(My brother, I know you're in pain.)
(But we can't keep making mistakes.)
♪The wind once♪
♪Through layers of mist♪
♪And snowy scenes♪
♪Gently cradled the leaf in my palm♪
♪But♪
♪Winds will cease♪
♪Leaves will wither♪
♪Our meeting was too fleeting♪
♪It's an unavoidable fate♪
Fine.
♪I too once♪
♪Walked through♪
♪A sea of people♪
I've been presumptuous.
♪Racing under stars toward you♪
You've made up your mind.
♪Time is heartless♪
♪You never yield♪
Then let's divorce.
♪In the past♪
♪The wind once♪
♪Thought of stopping♪
♪The leaf denied its withering♪
♪But such was this life♪
♪But♪
♪Time reminds us♪
♪All is ordained♪
♪Below zero, ice must form♪
♪Vows weigh too light♪
♪I too once♪
♪Had moments♪
♪Of love♪
♪But I never could♪
♪Melt destiny's iron heart♪
♪I can only♪
♪Return to the past♪
♪To undo the regrets slowly♪
♪The wind drifts alone and free♪
♪Through seasons, none asks of me♪
♪Spring fades, and autumn wails♪
♪Only the waning moon
lights my solitude♪
♪Love arose with the wind's sigh♪
♪On a cold night,
a swan's shadow flashes by♪
♪You're deeply devoted♪
♪Yet spring wind betrayed your heart♪
♪I miss you so much♪
♪I never forget you♪
♪A brief period of love-sickness♪
♪You won my heart over♪
♪Why did we first meet♪
♪Seeking spring's song
and night whispers♪
♪Long autumn comes,
and wild geese southward fly♪
♪The azure clouds know my name♪
♪I remember you, and you understand me♪
♪Watching the sun set♪
♪Autumn departs, and beauty fades away♪
♪To lean on you once more someday♪