Your leg still hurts.
I can give you a ride.
It's okay.
I can get home fine.
Can't you go a little easier on me
Miss Pat?
I'm not being difficult.
Taweerath's case is serious.
This time the cops won't go easy on him.
You can quit worrying now,
even about me.
I know
what you're thinking.
Stop trying to read people's minds,
especially mine.
Don't worry about me.
I'm not.
I'm more worried about myself.
Don't let your past mistakes
and your fear of the future
stop you from being happy in the present.
If we're sincere with each other,
there's nothing to fear.
Yes, Kiki?
Hello, Pat.
I just had some work come up.
You had work come up?
Yeah. Can you get home on your own?
Um…
Sure. I can go home on my own.
Don't worry. Okay.
Kiki can't give you a ride now.
You might want to come with me.
Fine.
Here, I'll take those.
- I got it.
- Your leg still hurts.
Come on.
Your bag too.
Let's go.
So even Ingdao can fall.
The light that burns others
gets put out today.
Having fun talking about Aunt Dao?
Did you forget I work here too?
I'm screwed.
Do we have to cancel today?
Wait, Ava! What's the matter this time?
I don't have the heart to work.
I'm leaving.
Everyone's gossiping about Aunt Dao!
Hey, calm down. You can't do this!
This is your last shoot.
And we have no idea
how it will go with the new drama.
You're not a superstar yet,
so don't be problematic. Got it?
So if you're famous,
you can do whatever you want,
is that right?
No one's talking to you, nosy!
I didn't mean to be nosy.
But since we're shooting a scene together,
I just wanted to come and tell you
to focus on your work.
Don't mix your work
with your personal life.
Ava's a professional.
She doesn't need you to teach her.
If she really is a professional,
she wouldn't be crying to go home
when her job isn't done.
Or,
did you learn from your aunt
to believe you can cause trouble
if you're a superstar?
Are you insulting her? Huh!
Isn't it true?
Both you and your aunt
create chaos for everyone.
But she probably can't do anything now
since she has a case to fight.
Hey!
If you're responsible enough,
get back to work. Everyone's waiting.
That Pu girl sure is horrible.
Do your best, Ava.
Let's go.
Pat! Pat!
Please listen to me. Pat!
What is it, Som?
You want her to be the leading lady
instead of Ingdao?
Yes. I'm sorry about last time.
But please help me out here.
Dao's being charged with a crime.
Even if she's bailed out,
I wouldn't know what to do.
I have work to continue. Please?
Som,
you're the one
who fired her on the fitting day.
Come on now.
That was long ago.
Why would you bring it up, Kiki?
Dear dear!
Think of it as a fresh start for us.
Please? Please?
Please? Can we start again? I beg you.
Please help me.
Please?
Fine then, Som.
Thank you, Pat.
Thank you.
Then I'll go tell the reporters
that Pat's the leading lady.
Sure, go right ahead.
No more changes, okay?
No more changes.
Now,
I’m not only caught up in your case,
but I also lost my leading lady role.
How will you take responsibility for that?
You told me it wouldn't affect me.
Don't worry.
We'll be okay no matter what.
What about my career
and reputation?
Just 'okay' isn't enough.
Everything will turn out fine.
Are you sure
you can handle this case?
You can trust me.
I promise.
Ingdao gave an interview to the reporters.
That means Taweerath's off the hook too.
Nikorn told me
that guy found someone
to take the fall for him.
His money, power, and connections
sure are something.
No matter what, I won't stop here.
A guy like Taweerath
has plenty of dirty secrets.
There’s definitely more
I can use against him.
Just be careful,
because he's definitely looking into this
to find out who informed the cops.
I'm more worried about Miss Pat.
Now that Ingdao's off the hook,
she might be back on set.
Up there a little more.
That's good.
- Fabulous.
- Thank you.
Dao, you're back!
How are you? I was so worried.
Sorry for all the trouble, Som.
No worries.
Why is Dao here, Kiki?
For the shoot of course.
But isn't she under investigation?
Didn't you see on the news? Here.
She just got out.
See?
Something unexpected happened.
So naturally,
we had to make a few changes.
Would Dao be able to take it, Som?
She was a leading actress,
but now she's a supporting actress.
It's fine, Som.
After all, this isn’t the first time
I’ve had to give someone
my leading lady role.
Dao's such a nice person.
She's got a good spirit.
And now
she's taking the supporting role
so someone else gets the privilege.
Well, who told the leading lady
to do something so risky?
Thank God she didn't go to jail.
Who knows how much the bail was?
Kiki, are you trying to get sued?
Come on now.
What I meant was
she's spent so much money making merit
to ward off bad luck.
Don't look so guilty--
Sorry, I mean,
don't misunderstand me.
I don't have a problem, Som,
as long as work can go smoothly
without any issues.
I agree with Pat.
But who knows,
anything can happen.
You should take a break.
- Just you wait.
- Check out my leading lady.
Don't mind them. Let’s go. This way.
Thank you for helping me.
I promise I'll make it up to you.
Okay.
So you're the one
who filmed me that day?
Do you know
how much trouble you caused me?
Please don't hurt me.
I was hired to do it.
- Who hired you?
- Mr. Tham.
Hurry, go!
That was it for your shoot. Are you tired?
I'm not. It was just a few scenes.
Really? Wanna go home now?
Wait,
or are you waiting to see someone?
I'm not.
Are you sure?
Then I'd better
go change so we can head home.
Noom! Mr. Tham got shot!
In the parking lot.
Mr. Tham!
Pat, wait for me!
Yes, Mr. Rath?
He got away.
Was it Rath's doing?
I'm not sure.
But if you ask how many enemies I have,
there's just one.
It's because you got involved
with my issues.
I'm telling you,
it had nothing to do with you.
Even without you,
I would have done the same.
I have to pay Taweerath back
for Fah's sake.
But because you got involved with me,
you had to show your face
and reveal that you're his enemy.
Sooner or later,
with or without you,
I would have done the same.
This still would have happened.
But I don't want you
to risk yourself like this again.
I'm ready for the risk
if it will make that scumbag
pay for what he did.
Both to Fah
and to you.
And this is not just revenge.
I also want to protect you.
I thought you were hurt.
Why are you standing up?
It's small, so it doesn't hurt much.
The doctor said I could leave
in a couple of days.
Then I'm relieved.
You have a guest, so I should go home.
Miss Pat, wait.
I heard from Tham
that now
you and Taweerath are already divorced.
Yes.
Although he fooled you,
you're luckier than my daughter.
I've heard quite a bit about Miss Fah.
Now that you're
off the hook and out of his life,
you should start your life over.
After all, you were born lucky.
You were once a famous celebrity,
and your father is well-known in society.
So you wouldn't be expecting anything
from my nephew, would you?
I'll leave it at that.
I hope you understand.
It's not so hard to understand.
And no matter
how difficult my situation is,
I'd never think to rely on someone else.
Whatever it is you're worried about,
please forget it.
And I only came here today
as an acquaintance of his.
If you'll excuse me.
In the end,
you did mess up.
But I got him hurt pretty badly, Mr. Rath.
But I wanted him dead.
Mr. Rath, don't!
You're so useless!
Now that he got away,
he won't stop! Damn it!
Rath, Rath!
Are you killing your worker?
Get out.
I was just pissed he messed up.
What did he mess up to get you this angry?
It's about Tham.
What about him?
You should go.
What if Mr. Rath or someone sees?
Why did you have to let him
hurt you this bad?
What about you?
Why did you give up your reputation
and your life
for a guy like Mr. Taweerath?
About that,
you should know best, shouldn't you?
I found out everything.
About…
our child.
I have nothing left.
Not my child,
not my career.
The leading lady role that was once mine,
somebody else has it now.
It's not your fault at all.
You're right. It's Patchanin's fault.
It's all because of her.
If you're unhappy,
you should quit the industry.
I'll take care of you.
No.
I can't let our child die for nothing.
They have to pay
for what happened to me and our child.
We can't fight them.
Let's not mess with them, Dao.
See? It's because you're a coward!
That's why
we always have to hide like this.
You have no money
and not even any courage.
Who can you take care of?
I won't let anyone
trample over me anymore.
I'll take back whatever's mine.
Mommy's sorry.
Mommy really tried her best.
Is it because of me
that you're letting him
treat you like this?
I do it for the money.
Since the day we broke up,
I learned just how important money is.
But even till now,
you're no different than before.
Dao,
what if I am different now?
I know all of Mr. Taweerath's secrets.
Whatever he can give you,
I can give you too.
So can we get back together like before?
You?
Have it all like Taweerath?
There's just no way.
But if you still miss what we once had,
I ask just one thing.
Don't try to get in my way.
You said you'd head back.
I'm just grabbing my bag.
I saw you talking to Pumeth.
Don't tell me
you worry about him.
It's what people who mess up deserve.
That's exactly why
I was talking to him.
I don't want him to mess up again,
or it'll cause me trouble too.
Is that it?
Also, I didn't leave yet
because I just had an idea
on how we can get back at our enemy.
How will you get back at Tham?
As for the CSR activities
and the Family Stability Association,
Mr. Wiwat ordered you
to handle them specifically because
they have to do with our company's image.
Perhaps because of
the news about me from before.
Yes, something like that.
The association's already here.
It will be an easy deal for you.
Good afternoon. I'm Tham.
It's our pleasure
to be working with your association.
Sorry, but we have to leave.
Hold on,
we haven't talked yet.
Did we do something to upset you?
Our association promotes
honesty and morality,
which are important basics of a family.
Working with a company
whose executive behaves immorally
isn't what we do.
Me?
Behave immorally?
You should see the news about you
before you invite people
to work with your company.
Wait.
Hold on!
Mr. Tham.
WHY THEY DIVORCED
Hey!
Someone posted the news and videos
defaming you and your company.
Should we sue?
That would lead to more news about us
and upset my uncle even more.
The shareholders and board of directors
want you to write a letter
to explain about the news.
If you can't explain this,
it will affect your position.
But I bought the videos that day.
How did these get out?
There's you carrying Pat too.
Someone else must have secretly filmed us
besides that reporter.
Just hurry and leave.
I'll take care of the reporters.
I don't want to run away.
We're not running away.
We're just getting back on our feet.
Please don't see them yet.
I got so screwed the last time you did.
Let's go, Miss Pat.
Ah!
- Are you here to shoot news?
- Yes. Is Pat on her break yet?
She finished her shoot this morning.
That's not true. We still see her car.
It's probably not hers.
Maybe it's another car.
Did you remember correctly?
Guys, there's Pat!
Wait, wait, wait!
Ugh!
Pat!
Pat.
Let's go.
The video I secretly took
is like killing two birds
with one stone, isn't it?
Well done, my niece.
Are you okay?
I'm alright.
And don't worry about my medication.
I always consult my doctor.
I've had my fair share
of bad news about me,
so a little more won't hurt.
I'm more worried about Mr. Tham
who will go down with me.
I heard quite a few of his CSR activities
were canceled
and he had to write an explanation letter.
He's in trouble because of me.
I shouldn't have gotten into his life.
It's not your fault.
This must be their doing.
They're constantly harassing
you and Mr. Tham.
I think so too.
But no matter what,
I won't stop going after them.
See?
I can help you get your revenge too.
I guess I should thank your niece too.
That's right.
Ava's reward, as you asked.
That's it?
And this
is for you.
I hope this is not
some cheap diamond necklace
that belonged to Patchanin
and kept in a box like last time.
I bought a new one just for you.
Thank you.
Actually,
for me,
this isn't enough to get him back.
Don't worry,
I'll help you break him into pieces
just as I'll take everything away
from your ex-wife.
Dao, one day you'll see
that I can do everything I promised you.
Quit sponsoring the show.
I can't.
The recent scandal alone is bad enough.
And if we keep sponsoring the show,
they'll further believe that you
were seeing Patchanin
before they divorced.
But I already explained in detail
in my letter to the board of directors.
The board members
are still giving you a chance
because of your past performance.
But the outside world won't do the same.
It will damage your reputation even more.
Don't forget,
all the shareholders and board members
also have the right
to remove you from your position.
Or are you ready to quit being CEO?
But if we quit sponsoring the show,
they'll think we got scared away
by the news.
And we're a large company.
It will look bad if we break a promise.
Then hold a press conference.
Tell them it's not true.
And bring Patchanin along
so she can confirm
that there's nothing going on
between you two.
Then I'll have to ask her first,
to see if she wants to.
Whether she wants to or not,
it doesn't matter.
What matters is
what you can do to make this go away
as soon as possible.
Got it?
You hiding from me
is not making things any better.
But seeing you now
will just make things worse.
At the hospital,
my uncle said something to you, didn't he?
Let's just say he worries about you,
and you should follow his advice.
And why should we believe
in what goes against our feelings?
Why can't we be sure about our feelings?
Especially my feelings for you.
I believe you feel it too.
Otherwise, at the hospital
you wouldn't have…
It's all in your head.
Wait.
Before you go,
I want you to hear my offer
if you still want to defeat them.
The script got changed?
The writers edited the script,
so I brought it for you.
But why is there just Miss Pat's?
Well, everyone else's script
stays the same.
But for the leading lady,
we needed quite a few changes.
Must be because of the recent news.
I saw lots of people
leaving angry comments on your Instagram.
Hmm, or did you change it
so that the leading lady
dies right from the start?
If the leading lady dies,
people may stop watching.
But if the villain dies in agony,
people might like it.
- Hey!
- Stop it.
Right now!
Ugh!
I hope you understand.
And you two,
keep that same energy
when you fight in a scene.
Go, go.
Come on, come this way.
Now!
Ugh.
You're the leading lady,
yet so many of your lines got cut.
So are you really one now?
Should we just back out?
We haven't done that many scenes.
That will just please whoever
spread the news about me and Mr. Tham.
Aw.
But to work for someone
who doesn't respect you,
I don't think it's right.
But I do understand Som.
Look, I'll go talk to Som myself
so I could do as she pleases.
Miss Pat.
There's a gift for you.
Apparently, it's from a fan.
Aw.
See, Pat? There are still so many
who love and support you.
I bet
it's a gift to cheer you up.
Aw.
Should I open it?
SLUT!!
My god! Who sent this?
This is going too far!
Since you've invited me
to your parties a lot…
If you'll really invite me, then I'll go.
NEXT EPISODE
As soon as these two
stop being useful to each other,
they'll probably kill each other.
Everyone can start again.
Especially me.
You really think
anyone would still believe
a scumbag like you?
No!
- Pat!
- Let go!
Subtitle translation by:
Ramil Natnitiwitaya