So do you care about Mrs. Pat,
or do you hate her?
Didn't you say you wouldn't
be soft-hearted for her anymore?
But last night,
you seemed worried about her.
You know…
In order to make someone listen to us
and do as we say
without any doubt,
what do we have to do?
What?
Make them suffer the most,
be the weakest,
and then give them a hand.
This is the perfect time
for me to use her,
to get revenge on Mr. Taweerath.
So you're saying that
last night was just an act
to make Mrs. Pat let her guard down,
thinking that you helped her,
so that she would trust you
and eventually go along with your plan?
You're really bad, man.
I'd rather be a bad person
if it means that
the worst person gets their Karma.
That woman stole Fah's happiness.
What she had to go through
was well deserved.
But are you sure
that Mrs. Pat will agree to work with you?
She is not a fool, you know.
Mrs. Pat.
Were you okay last night?
I'm fine, Pu.
Thank you for yesterday.
Then let's see
if she will work with me.
Think wisely, man.
I don't want you
to go any deeper than this,
okay?
I had people search the entire bar,
but they couldn't find the kid's phone.
How could it be gone?
At the time, it was in my shirt pocket.
And how did Mrs. Pat act?
Nothing.
When she woke up, she seemed fine.
Just complaining about being tired.
Then it means the kid
is still afraid to tell her anything.
Anyway, if there is no evidence,
she wouldn't believe the kid's words.
Did you make your decision last night?
I haven't decided anything yet.
Why?
I don't know exactly what you want from me
to make that offer.
You already know
the whole truth about your husband.
Are you going to just let it go?
Or are you going to stop him
from doing what he does to you
behind your back?
Women…
Women?
So what?
Don't women have the right
to take their time making decisions?
Don't you ever think about doing anything?
I don't think about anything at all.
Even last night,
I didn't know if you were sincere or not.
I don't want to think or do anything
while I'm still not in my right mind.
Then you should go back
and get yourself together.
Try to think carefully
and differentiate between
your current status as husband and wife.
Are you still important to him
or just useful to him?
That's why he's still with you.
Then we can come back
and talk about this again.
Try to think carefully
and differentiate between
your current status as husband and wife.
Are you still important to him
or just useful to him?
That's why he's still with you.
Oh!
Mrs. Pat!
What's wrong with you, Mrs. Pat?
I'm feeling dizzy.
Excuse me.
Oh, you're burning up.
Do you have a fever?
Please sit down.
I'll go get you some medicine.
Okay.
I had a suspicion
that you were sick.
I've noticed you look tired
for the past few days.
Hello, Mr. Rath.
Hi, Pat.
I went to see Ya,
she said you weren't feeling well,
so she wanted me to bring you some soup.
Pat.
I think you are really sick.
I think…
you should cancel your dinner
with your friends tonight.
I have to go out to a meeting anyway.
It's okay.
I will feel better
after taking some medicine.
I will order food from the hotel instead.
Since you're already here,
let's have dinner together.
Or…
do you already have a date with someone?
Actually, I do have an appointment,
but since you invited me
to stay, I'll stay.
Here's the medicine, Mrs. Pat.
Taking medicine
on an empty stomach is not good.
Why don't you eat something first?
I'll go warm it up for you.
Here.
You go call and order
at the address I gave you.
Tell them to be here before 6 p.m.
Yes, ma'am.
Go now, or we won't make it in time.
I'll give the soup to Pat myself.
Yes, ma'am.
Jaew went to order food,
so I brought soup instead.
Thank you, Dao.
Hurry up. It's warmed up just right.
Eat some, darling,
so you can take your medicine.
I must be really sick,
that's why I feel
the soup has a foul smell.
Or maybe
Jaew didn't wash the bowl properly.
Or maybe,
the hand that held the bowl
was dirty and smelly,
so the smell stuck to the bowl.
I will go rest in my room.
I've been good to your wife.
But look at what your wife said to me.
She's been having mood swings lately.
I don't know what's wrong with her.
Please be patient with her.
Sure,
since I'm already here tonight,
I'm not going to ruin your wife's dinner.
When you're done with the job,
send the money to me as promised.
Then please pay attention to the child,
in a way that is worthy of
the money I'm going to send.
Pat is here.
Pat.
I brought Ava and Chat with me.
I hope you don't mind.
Sure,
the more the merrier.
Let's go.
Oh, Rath.
Are you not going to the meeting today?
I already canceled the meeting.
I'd rather stay
and help you with the guests.
Good.
It's even better if you are here
because there should be
a lot of fun things this evening.
Uh, by the way,
have you been busy recently?
You haven't been to the casino--
I mean the golf course.
Yes.
Mr. Rath doesn't have much free time.
There's a meeting every day.
Well, something like that.
But you canceled it today
to come and be with…
all of us.
Wasting the whole day like this.
I guess you'll have to have a meeting
from morning until night tomorrow.
Yeah.
It seems like you care more
about Mr. Rath than Pat.
She cares about everyone.
Even with Mr. Tham,
she still cares about him.
Wow Dada, did I miss something?
What's going on between Dao and Mr. Tham?
Really?
Are you talking about me?
Please have a seat.
At the Star Sea contest,
I saw Dao and Mr. Tham.
They seemed very close.
Especially,
in the dressing room.
So I invited Mr. Tham to come as well.
Thank you
for inviting me to dinner.
I am very happy
to see you all again.
The gossip news must be coming.
And the initials will be in there too.
Wow, Aunt Dao, your ring is so beautiful.
I can still see the sparkle
of the diamonds from here.
Who bought it for you?
Directly to the point?
It's a secret.
Wow!
You're really good at keeping secrets.
Even though I'm your manager,
I've never suspected anything.
Pat!
I've never seen a real one.
It's so beautiful.
Oh, the diamonds are dazzling!
For Dao, it's just a ring to wear for fun.
But for me,
it's a wedding ring.
Is that the one
Mr. Rath used to propose to you
on the day of the award?
Exactly.
Mr. Rath…
proposed to me in front of the press.
The reason I'm wearing this ring today
is that I haven't worn it for a long time.
I'm afraid people will forget
that we are not dating
and got married openly,
not hiding in the shadows.
But sometimes, hiding and sneaking around
can be quite exciting,
especially for those
who are tired of the old,
bland tastes.
Then, those who enjoy that kind of thing
should drink plenty of water.
Because if they are sneaking around,
I'm afraid they might choke to death.
But maybe
he doesn't want it for the taste,
perhaps he wants it because it's free.
Uh, I think we should eat.
Oh, good!
I'm hungry now.
It looks delicious!
Tham! Tham!
It's a beautiful ring!
Your boyfriend
must have spent a lot of money on it.
It must be quite expensive too.
It doesn't matter how expensive it is,
what matters is who gave it.
He secretly asked to be engaged first.
Don't tell our father just yet.
You called, and I rushed here
thinking I would get some kind of answer.
So, this is your answer, right?
You don't want to work with me,
but you plan to use me
as a tool against Ms. Ingdao.
You were the one
who told me to get myself together.
Now that I'm fully conscious,
I'm doing my best
to bring my family back to normal.
This must be the way of thinking
for a conscious person.
Yes.
Because people who aren't conscious
will try to destroy
their own happy family.
So, am I wrong
to keep it
and not let anyone take it away?
If that's your decision,
don't expect me to be a pawn
for you to use easily.
And the things you took from others
will also be taken back as well.
Whoever wants to take something, go ahead,
but I will never let anyone
take my happiness away.
The dishes are delicious today.
Agreed.
Well,
speaking of which, Pat and Mr. Rath
have been married for a long time, right?
That's right.
Didn't your anniversary just pass?
It's been six years, right?
That's right.
You two have been married for a long time.
Why don't you have a child yet?
Or do you have some problems?
If it were other men,
they would have found a woman
who could fulfill them a long time ago.
As for women with problems,
they shouldn't blame
their husbands either.
Oh, Pat. Don't take this the wrong way.
I didn't say it was you.
I'm talking about someone else.
But I think that
men who use this as an excuse
to be with other women
are probably just trash.
As for women who know he is taken
and still think about pursuing him,
I don't really know
what to call them.
I think you just said it to sound cool,
like someone who has no experience
with family matters.
I've seen many families
where the wives accept it.
Their families seem happy.
You are very correct.
People must know their own shortcomings
and learn to blame themselves
before blaming others.
Don't you think so, Pat?
Pat.
Pat…
what about Dao's food?
It's just in time.
It seems like there are a lot of guests,
so there wasn't enough food.
So I asked Jaew to make some more.
Why don't you try it?
Wow, Pat.
You've prepared
only good stuff for us today.
The berries and meat are delicious.
Hello?
All right…
How is it?
The soup you brought me,
is it delicious?
In yours,
it was just house slippers.
But for me,
I use my favorite
brand-name shoes just for you.
What happened?
Aunt Dao, are you okay?
Uh, maybe…
is it too hot and burned your mouth?
I'm so sorry Dao.
Aunt Dao!
Jaew.
Could you clean up the mess?
I think the soup is too hot.
Please continue.
Is that soup really hot?
You don't need to know.
You don't have to tell me.
I never thought
Pat could make you look like this.
I think tonight
definitely won't end here.
Let me take a picture and post it.
-So beautiful.
-Right?
Dao.
Are you okay?
Yes,
but I must excuse myself.
Where is Ava?
Uh, I think she's in the bathroom.
But don't go just yet.
I ordered a cake
from that famous shop that you like.
Let's stay and eat first.
That's right.
Should I…
cut a piece of cake for you to take home?
I'll take care of it.
Dao, have a seat.
Come here.
Then I'll cut the cake for everyone.
Good.
Thank you.
Did you throw up?
I'm so sorry, Dao,
for teasing you too harshly,
but to be honest,
I don't really like using such low,
dirty methods like you.
Did you just trick me?
Don't even think
that what you did to me will end here.
I don't plan to end it here either.
Oh!
Pat, what are you doing?
I was just joking around.
I see that everyone is bored,
so I'm trying to do something exciting.
I think you went too far.
Did you do it on purpose?
I think it's better to calm down a bit.
That's right. Calm down everyone.
She was just joking around
like someone who pulls pranks, right Dao?
Exactly. Like clickbait content.
Yeah.
Pat is like that.
I don't mind.
If I have any content like this,
I'll come and try it on you.
Sure, Dao.
I'm always ready.
Give it all you've got, I like it.
What are you doing?
Why did you come in here?
I should be the one asking you,
but it seems like that isn't necessary.
It's obvious that you're trying
to steal Mrs. Pat's stuff.
I caught you red-handed.
Let go of me! I said let go!
Let go of me!
Let go!
You have such a habit of stealing.
Even in Mrs. Pat's house,
you still have the nerve.
Do you lack something?
I see, it must be a lack of warmth?
A lack of guidance, right?
You!
-Ow!
-Come here!
-Stop it!
Let go of me!
Stop it!
What did you do to Pu, Ava?
You should ask that girl
what she's doing here.
That's right.
How did that kid get into our house?
Aunt Dao!
I asked Pu to help me in the kitchen.
But she came in
and stole things from your room.
When I saw her,
she attacked me.
You're such a blatant liar.
This kid really came in
and went through your things.
It wasn't me.
Ava is the one who did it!
I walked in and saw her,
so she went crazy.
And she even used the same old tricks.
Who would take a word from someone
as ill-mannered as you?
That's right.
She's just lying to get by.
There's no way
I would do something like that.
What are you doing?
I'll take a stubborn thief
like you to the police.
Rath, stop it!
If Ava didn't do anything,
I'll take her home.
Go.
Come here.
Let go of her!
It's because of how you are
that this kid could trick you.
You asked her to be in the kitchen.
If she wasn't here
to steal something valuable,
why would she be in here?
Or were you the one who let her in?
I sent Pu to find you.
So, it was you.
But this kid
came in and stole
something valuable anyway.
I was the one who looked through things.
I planned to come back and clean up
after we finished eating.
Then Pu happened to come after you,
so everything ended up like this.
Is that right, Pu?
Yes.
You can go now.
Then, I'll leave.
I'll walk you out.
Why did you hit me, Mom?
I knew right away that it was you
who stole their stuff!
It's a good thing
you didn't get caught,
otherwise it would have been
a total embarrassment!
But I said Pu was the one who did it.
Mr. Taweerath still believed it.
If you didn't have
your aunt to protect you,
who else would believe you?
Do you even have a brain?
Or there's not much going on
between those ears!
Why are you so stupid?
Like mother, like daughter.
Did you just call me stupid?
Come here!
Mom, no!
Mom! Stop it!
Stop it!
Mom!
Ouch!
Why did you get in the way?
Are you satisfied?
Or if you're not,
you can take it out on me.
Since I've already been hit as well.
Well, she did something wrong
and still argues back to me!
How could I not get mad?
If you're still angry, you can leave.
Once you've calmed down,
then come back and talk to your kid.
If there's a next time,
I won't let you live!
Ava.
It's fine.
She will be in a better mood.
She's always like this, right?
Aunt Dao.
I'm so sorry.
I just wanted to look at her bag.
But when I saw it, I couldn't help myself.
Ava.
Listen to me.
If your aunt
gets married
and goes public with Mr. Rath,
whatever you want,
I will find it for you.
Don't worry about it.
You don't have to steal from others,
understand?
Yes.
Aunt Dao…
If Mom loved me
as much as you do, it would be great.
Shut it!
Where is my niece?
Inside.
Ava!
Hey, what did you do to her?
She's lazy.
I sent her to sell garlands,
but she only brought back a little money.
It wasn't even enough to buy food.
When she grows up,
I'll send her to work at a karaoke bar!
With a face like this,
I'm sure she'll make a ton of money.
People like you shouldn't be mothers!
Why?
Suddenly developed a maternal instinct
after your miscarriage?
You're yelling at me,
despite the fact that
you were also knocked up!
Even if I didn't know I was pregnant,
if my child was born,
I will take good care of him or her.
I surely won't do what you did.
I'll take care of Ava myself.
If I leave her with you,
you'll definitely use her for money.
As for you studying acting here,
I will find a suitable class for you.
But right now, our school is facing
an ongoing problem.
I didn't want to bother you, Pat.
But I have to talk about it.
What's the matter?
Our school has been open for three years.
The classrooms are old and run down.
We are losing students
because we don't have the budget
to advertise and promote our school.
So I think we might need
to increase our funds…
I was just about
to talk to you about this.
Here it is.
You know that Ms. Jarinya
is addicted to gambling.
If you give her the money just like this,
she will probably end up
spending it at a casino.
I already know that.
I want it to be like that anyway.
Don't worry, Pu.
Whatever I pay for,
I will definitely get it back.
Let's go. I will give you a ride.
It's okay. I can go by myself.
I'll stop by to see my brother
before work. Goodbye.
Whatever you want.
Stop!
Woah! Let go!
Let go of me! Let go!
Pu!
Ouch!
Go!
Pu! Pu!
Let go of her! I said let go!
Let go!
Help! Help me please!
Pu!
-Mr. Tham…
-Pat, are you all right?
Careful!
Hello, officer. Please help!
There are gangsters here
at TJ's acting school.
Go!
Pat, are you okay?
I'm fine.
Mrs. Pat, are you all right?
I'm fine, are you?
That wedding ring
that you are so proud of,
it used to belong to Fah.
Or do I have to die
before you believe me?
I've already sent all the clips
from the casino to Mrs. Pat.
Your image of a good husband is gone.
NEXT EPISODE
If you're willing to help,
whatever you want me to do…
You can go wait for me in this room.
Are you sure
that taking me to this room
won't cause any problems with your wife?
You hurt my feelings
and made me feel ashamed.
Please go ahead and have fun with her!
Subtitle translation by:
Khathathong Thongtumlueng