[Gaus Electronics]
[Kwak Dong Yeon]
[Go Sung Hee]
[Bae Hyun Sung]
[Kang Min Ah]
[Baek Hyun Jin / Heo Jung Do]
[Go Woo Ri / Jeon Seok Chan / Baek Soo Jang]
[Gaus Electronics]
[The names and titles in this drama are fictitious]
Credits
- Hello!
- Me?
- Thank you.
- Please take a good look.
- Have you tried this before?
- Yeah. Wait! Thank you.
- Are you okay?
- Thank you!
Hold on.
Hold on!
Hold...
Hold on. H-Hold on!
Hold on! Hold on! Hold on!
Thank you. Thank—
Thank you.
- Did you just press the close button?
- Sorry, I didn't see you.
I was ready to accept your apology,
but you have no intention of apologizing at all.
Why should I?
I'm the one who was contemplating whether I should accept your apology or not.
Please see me for a minute.
Who is he to tell me to see him?
How outrageous.
I don't have time, so make it quick.
Do you know what you've done to me?
It's not left on "seen." It's just "not seen."
Hae Young has been denying me since yesterday.
She's someone I don't really know.
You haven't misunderstood, have you?
Yup.
She just replied.
"Yup"? Just "yup"?
She said, "Yup."
What's the problem?
There's no "ha."
(Korean consonant to mimic laughing, like "haha.")
Hae Young, who always adds "Ha" too much just messaged, "Yup."
"Yup," that's it!
In the past five years, I've never received a message as dry as this.
Do you still feel nothing after looking at this, Senior?
You don't feel sorry, one bit?
Senior, are you a sociopath?
I mean, what do I need to be sorry for?
You made her misunderstand!
Because you made excessive physical contact with me!
Hae Young!
Wow! All right.
I'm sorry if I was being excessive. Happy?
Explain everything to Hae Young, Senior.
That you coincidentally live next door, and that you're the one who came into my house.
And that we absolutely do not have a relationship together!
Do it yourself. Why would you involve me in your relationship?
- There's a spider behind you.
- As if!
I knew it.
Are you even truly scared of spiders?
Forget it. I need some time to myself.
Hold on.
Are you saying I did that on purpose?
I'm really, totally, absolutely scared of spiders.
I'm so scared of them I couldn't even watch the "Spiderman" trailer!
Yeah, yeah! Thank you for telling me something that doesn't interest me at all.
Yeah, right. You'll be interested.
- Look.
- God.
Should I request a diagnosis?
Go ahead. Go ahead and request one and
explain everything to Hae Young
that there's nothing going on between us—
Oh, my!
I'm sorry.
I-It's not what you think... Hae Young!
H-Hae Young, there's nothing between us, nothing! Hae Young!
- What?
- Did you just see Hae Young?
Why did you have to...
Did you see her and do it on purpose?
And why did you move in next door?
Senior... do you like me?
You're insane...
- Senior—
- You little...
Wait, Senior. Senior!
Senior!
[Episode 3: Drink cold water and get a hold of yourself. Gaus Water Purifier]
Excuse me!
Father, it's Ma Tan.
Starting today, I'm going to start my day
by riding a bus like an ordinary employee.
If I had stayed under your shadow,
I could never even imagine a life like this.
I wouldn't have known what sound this stop bell makes, either.
Young Boss, please stop pressing the bell.
It's already the twelfth time.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't help it because it sounded nice.
Young Boss?
It was a mistake.
- Assistant Kim?
- My goodness, my mistake.
Anyhow, your mother was quite surprised
that you'd ride the bus to work and that you live in a studio.
She should accept it now
that my determination to start from the bottom was a sincere one.
The tent bar rental,
and the damages cost 800,000 won.
Cost of dry cleaning and mending, 5,200,000 won.
My monthly pay is 2,800,000 won,
but rent is 400,000 won and living expenses are 300,000 won,
maintenance fee is 60,000 won,
the phone bill is 70,000 won,
student loans are 300,000 won,
the apartment deposit is 200,000 won...
I guess I should starve.
Could I last one week on this?
What the?
Huh?
Hey! Hey, no!
Hey! No, no!
Hey! Shoo, shoo!
Shoo, shoo, shoo! No!
This is my survival rations!
I wanted to resolve this with words, but...
you little!
To be sparring with pigeons first thing in the morning...
She's diligently training even on her way to work.
Please let me know if you need guarding.
I'll arrange it for you.
What's this?
W-When did I ever say I needed these?
Gosh, how ridiculous.
Geez, you said you didn't need any, but
the smell of the pain patches could reach the live octopus restaurant across the street, Senior.
You think I used them because I wanted to?
Forget it and let's do this.
You should explain it to her, not me.
What would I say?
"Hae Young, there's no need for you to misunderstand at all.
Senior Cha Na Rae is too busy to even glance at me,
and she's very popular and has high standards.
And she already has a boyfriend."
How could I say such nonsense, Senior?
Who would believe that when everyone in Gaus knows about your nasty temper?
Shit, you're going to make me curse again, you little...
Senior!
How about just cursing in front of Hae Young like that?
I don't think Hae Young would misunderstand if she knew your true nature.
Should I rip the fudging soles out of your shoes and flatten you to a sheet with them?
Do you really want me to rip your mouth for you? Should I?
"Fudging, sheet, rip your mouth." I just took note of everything.
- Stop, you want to die? Stop it.
- Say some more.
- Erase it. Erase it.
- "Stop it, I'll erase you from the world—"
That's enough, you two.
This is an office!
I'm sorry.
Senior just kept cursing at me.
You're dead later, I mean it.
"You are dead."
"I truly mean it."
- "Today, I will make sure to—"
- Were you two sworn enemies in your past lives?
But, Senior, past lives still haven't been scientifically proven...
I'm sorry.
This is Baek Ma Tan's job application I got from a colleague in HR after some bullshitting.
Let's take a look.
[Job Application]
Huh, what the?
They're all blank.
Even his family relations.
This guy is totally suspicious.
How can this be possible? It's not like he's a secret agent.
I'm going to have to do a little digging on him
with my potato-digging skills from childhood.
Did you call for me?
Yeah, Manager Seong.
Cancel all of today's schedule.
We don't have anything scheduled today.
It's chewy, but soft.
Spicy, but sweet.
This saltiness at the tip of my tongue
is asking me for white rice.
This savory taste...
continues to remain inside my mouth.
He's using his fork to swirl the jinmichae?
(Dried squid)
Jinmichae...
Even its name is divine.
Hey, Newbie.
Hey, Ma Tan.
Yeah, Ma Tan. I memorized your name.
I'm smart despite how I look.
I have a question.
Have you been living abroad with your parents?
I did go back and forth.
Oh, then are your parents...
diplomats? Expatriates? Or do they do business abroad?
I have no desire to tell you.
Did I ask you something difficult?
Tell me honestly.
Which line did you ride here?
I don't know what you're saying.
Line, Ma Tan. Like a subway line.
Hey, you moron! Do you think that's what I meant?
I'm talking about your back.
Background!
We didn't even have any open positions in Gaus.
But how did you obtain a position and
end up eating here like this?
Tell me.
It's difficult for me to tell you.
Oh! I guess it could be.
Are your parent NIS? CIA? Or are they
the head of a major company or the president?
What the heck is so difficult to say?
I'll get up first.
Look at him!
Did you see that? That rudeness?
And why did he just leave without cleaning up?
It does seem like he has a personal reason.
Personal reason, my foot.
He's like that because he has something to hide.
You might fool everyone else,
but you can't fool me.
I read the letter you gave me yesterday.
- What is this?
- The money you requested.
I put in what I could repay for now,
but could the remaining 5,500,000 won
be repaid in installments?
It will be too difficult to pay it off at once with my monthly salary.
To think that amount is too difficult...
Pardon?
I understand your situation.
- Oh, then—
- I'll give you until tomorrow.
Yes, all right—
Tomorrow?
What the?
What are you two doing here?
Oh, I was just giving him stuff he needs.
Should I let you in on what you really need?
No.
When it comes to coffee, Latte hits the spot.
Back in my days...
(Sounds like "Latte")
Wait, you finished your military service. Right?
I was exempted due to a health condition.
That's right.
I knew it since you left your tray on the table.
The military is the same as work.
If you want a good social life, you just need to excel in one thing.
Kissing your superior's ass.
Are you talking about the anus located on their bottom?
To think I'd have to go that far...
This crazy bastard.
I'm not actually telling you to kiss it. It's an analogy! An analogy...
Is he taking my advice or what?
Where was I?
Oh, yes. Who's there in our department?
Whose ass do you think you need to kiss?
Is there anyone else, but General Manager Gi?
Look carefully. General Manager Gi is the one who runs those vending machines.
If you buy expensive coffee from outside,
all you're asking for is more criticism about how well-off you are.
So just buy three drinks from there at least three times a day.
Sail smoothly with Manager Gi, okay?
More criticism...
Do I already have a target on my back?
No, no, no, yes, yes, no.
No, not yet.
Geez, so many dragon flies.
Get out before you get another earful.
Senior, there's some data you need to take a look at.
What is it?
I prepared this...
to simply brief my situation to you.
[Analysis of the Reason for Failure to Confess and Lee Sang Sik's 10th Confession Plan]
What is this?
What is all this?
It's embarrassing, but this is a record of all my failed attempts to confess to Hae Young.
During the past five years,
there were nine attempts,
but I've never once succeeded.
Like everyone else,
if I made a heart with candles, it would suddenly rain.
And if I stayed up all night to practice singing to her, I'd get a sore throat.
The day I wrote a message on an LED display and tried to confess,
there was a sudden blackout.
I also tried the rose bouquet confession, but...
[Three years ago]
As I said,
I'll deposit your payments 10 minutes later.
Go, go, go, go!
Oppa!
When did you prepare all this?
In the end, I just helped out another guy get lucky.
Hey, Jin Soo!
[Two years ago]
So...
I gave up and just intended to tell her straight up, but...
If you drink that,
we're dating.
I mean, if you failed this many times,
don't you think the universe is trying to tell you something?
Yeah.
The universe did give me a sign.
What?
It did let me know.
It told me that today is the day.
"I've been disrupting your plans for this day."
"I'm sorry."
Failure is an option.
If things are not failing, you are not innovative enough.
A failure is just an option!
"If things are not failing,
that just proves you were not innovative enough." Elon Musk.
According to Musk's resolve that you must keep at it,
no matter what tragedy or adversity you face,
Senior, today I will...
make a very innovative confession.
Innov... what?
An innovative confession!
Today is the day
Jupiter and Saturn are the closest in 400 years.
So, the couples that are formed today
will experience a love that's been blessed by Jupiter and Saturn.
Wow!
"For small creatures such as us,
the vastness is bearable only through love." Carl Sagan!
If I miss this chance, I have to wait until the year 2080.
Senior, please. Please.
Please! Please.
Please help me secure success just this once, Senior.
- Senior, just this once.
- Why should I?
Do you want your name to be recorded as the 10th reason for my failure?
Please...
He's...
totally suspicious even at a glance.
You just wait to get caught, you punk.
What the?
His wallet is so shabby.
He must not have any money.
[50,000 won bills not accepted]
What's with him?
He didn't put in any money.
Is he trying to get a free drink from my vending machine?
What kind of discipline did he get from his parents?
Father! Mother!
I'm doing well!
So please don't worry...
about me and rest in peace!
Well, I mean...
Frankly speaking, just because his parents aren't around,
does it give him the right to do that? Is he a thief?
General Manager!
W-What?
Go inside and work.
So stop surveilling me!
Assistant Kim, you stop, too!
Is he looking at me? We've been caught! Hide! Hide!
What?
Hide...
Hide the drone.
Yes, I'll hide the drone.
Gosh, this really won't do.
As I thought, you're perfect.
I can't explain the specifics,
but if something happens to me at work or I'm in a predicament,
would you be able to help me?
I'll make it a condition to write off the debt.
Then... per case...
- Per case?
Well, fifty...
Fifty? 50 won?
Gosh. 50 won is being a bit stingy...
It should be at least 50,000 won,
so I have the desire to help you.
- Will you be fine with that?
- Of course!
Then, 50,000 won!
Please take good care of me!
Sure.
- Please get rid of this.
- 50,000 won?
[Public Relations Division]
W-What brings you here?
This is my office.
- Oh, right.
- Are you here to see me?
No, I was just passing by.
Oh, but Hae Young.
- Yesterday and this morning...
- Yes.
- You didn't misunderstand or anything, did you?
- Misunderstanding?
Sang Sik. Sang Sik and I have nothing going on between us.
The fact that we live next to each other is also just a coincidence.
Of course, I know. I know Sang Sik's style.
Sang Sik likes the cute and petite type. Like me.
But you're... the big, strong, and scary type.
Me? I am?
Moreover, there are things Sang Sik said about you until now.
So how could I misunderstand? I really didn't.
What might that bastard have said specifically?
Unni, Sang Sik makes it really tough for you. Right?
Does he think I have nothing to say?
He must've eaten his tact when he was eating something because I can't find it anywhere.
You know he's really nosy, too. Right?
Yesterday, he even consulted his roommate about my future dating life.
That's all part of Sang Sik's charm.
He's unexpectedly sensitive to details.
- Not narrow minded?
- He's pure-hearted, too.
Oh, gosh. His brain is pure.
He gives his all on something once he becomes fixated. But he's always wrong.
Exactly. He always heads in the wrong direction.
Same goes for what happened this time.
If he does well, he's Elon Musk,
but in reality, he's closer to being Heo Kyung Hwan.
(Korean comedian)
But Sang Sik is still cute.
I see...
It's a relief to see that you two are on the same page.
But why did you suddenly leave last night?
That's why he worried.
That's because my boyfriend suddenly said he has time.
You have a boyfriend?
Of course.
- What about Sang Sik?
- Sang Sik?
Sang Sik is just a good senior.
As a boyfriend, he's...
You know. He's the best caring guy,
but as a lover, he's a bit...
Is Sang Sik aware of this, too?
Of course.
If he failed that many times, he must know by now.
Oppa! When did you prepare all this?
Do you know how many times I friend-zoned him?
You probably wouldn't know.
How difficult it is to be confessed to all the time.
I'm not totally oblivious or anything.
Anyway, Hae Young wants to get along with Sang Sik.
Sang Sik is a really good person.
He buys me food and coffee all the time.
So, Hae Young doesn't even need to bring her wallet.
He's good at sorting my garbage and discarding my trash.
He's also good at cleaning my dog's poop.
And if we order chicken, he only eats the neck.
Neck...
This is it. I'm not going to get involved between you two again, so keep that in mind.
Yes, of course. I wouldn't want that, either. It has all been resolved now, right?
There wasn't anything to resolve.
Hae Young isn't bothered by it at all and you're overreacting on your own.
Oh, so she just forgot to include an "ha." Thank God.
Do you not understand what I'm saying, Sang Sik?
Hae Young has zero interest in you.
Hae Young is always a bit aloof.
Anyway, you did a good job.
Wait! So you're still going to confess?
I'll take care of that on my own.
Wait!
Have you ever thought that your idea of "some"
(Flirting)
might differ from everyone else's?
Senior, I think you told me about 47 seconds ago that you'll no longer get involved.
I won't, I won't, I won't. Geez, it's not like I'm concerned.
This is the end!
Senior!
Anyhow, I really thank you.
I think I'll do well this time, thanks to you.
My innovative confession.
Wait...
You know Elon Musk, who you really look up to?
Don't you think Elon Musk gave up on certain things, too?
He could've given up on something that didn't work out and ended up creating Tesla.
Wait. I'm going nuts.
Why do you keep trying to prevent me from confessing?
I mean, I was really going to stop suspecting you now, but...
Senior, do you really have feelings for me?
Forget it.
You don't, right?
- I'm going now.
- Fighting.
Senior, you too! I'm going!
Oh, my god.
Whatever.
Whoa, it's restocked.
A penny saved is a penny earned. A penny saved is a penny earned.
I must store it away when it's available.
Three-layer embossed tissue is the best,
but the company is being stingy and doesn't use it these days.
Isn't that Ma Tan?
His posture is so unecessarily upright.
Will he be able to fit in at work when he's that upright?
I figured it would be difficult for you to unpack on your own, Young Boss.
- Let's do it together.
- No. It's fine.
It's fine.
It was your mother's earnest request.
Let's go.
It's really fine.
But please do me a different favor.
Huh? Why is he giving him money?
Please change all of this to coins.
I want to try buying a drink from the company's vending machine.
Wait! Did Ma Tan borrow money from a loan shark?
All right, but we'll take you home. Please don't decline.
We've also prepared the van you wanted to ride, Young Boss.
- Let's go.
- I'm fine.
- Your mother is very worried.
- Shit!
- Please, get in.
- Hold on! Hold on.
Sorry, excuse me.
Hold on... The timing is now!
Don't look back! Don't look back!
Hey, it's getting cold and soggy. What are you waiting for?
Dig in.
Why are you staring at the food as if it's the first time you're eating snack food?
Snack food?
It's my first time trying snack food.
Exactly just how impoverished was his childhood?
Wait a minute. Is he saving the food for later?
Wait! Geez, you punk. Just eat the whole thing!
I'll eat it myself.
Huh? Sure.
Your address was in the middle of nowehere in the countryside.
Do you have someplace to stay in Seoul?
I got a studio near the company.
I finished moving and I just need to unpack tonight.
There's no need to be dispirited or anything because you live in a studio.
I went to and fro work from a study dormitory.
(A space with just enough room for a desk and a single bed.)
But after 20 years,
I bought a 32-pyeong apartment in Seoul!
(1 pyeong=35.5832 sq ft.)
You can do it, too!
Hey, but you ordered some black bean noodles on your moving day, right?
No, I couldn't.
What? This punk doesn't even have enough money for black bean noodles?
Ma'am, please give us two jjajang ramen.
Okay.
Hey, you can make a hole in my wallet today!
Bang!
It rocks, huh?
Hey, why do you have your wallet out?
If your senior buys you food, you just need to say thank you, punk.
I see.
Thank you for the food.
But what's with your wallet? It's all worn at the sides.
My son's old cow leather wallet is laying around at home.
Do you want to use that one? You want it?
This is a one-of-a-kind wallet in the entire world. Is it ugly?
It was handed down to me from my father, but I guess I should change it.
That's why he held on to that shabby wallet...
Follow me.
Here. They're box tissues, but you can have them.
I don't give this to just anyone. Here, here.
Take it and go inside.
Here's one more.
Punk.
I'm so cool today.
Hae Young...
Jupiter and... Jup...
Sang Sik.
What is all this?
Hae Young, can you continue to be together with me?
Oppa...
I'll always be by your side.
Just like how I have been all this time.
Hae Young, look at the sky.
In order to bless our love, Jupiter and Saturn
have also become one like us.
Oppa...
This is a no-smoking area...
Gosh, whatever.
Yes, Mother.
Assistant Kim said he'd help me, but I declined.
I'm not the Baek Ma Tan who always relied on someone anymore.
It's just a studio, so I can take care of this much.
Don't worry.
I'll hang up now.
Power.
Kang Mi?
What is this?
It's so pretty!
But who...
By any chance...
Hae Young!
Why did you come out?
I told you to wait in the car.
You said the person you're meeting is dear to you.
I wanted to meet him and ask him to take good care of you.
But he's not here yet?
What's this?
- Are you Sang Sik?
- No—
Huh?
Oh, are you selling this?
How much is it?
80,000 won...
Can't you go a bit lower?
- No?
- That's not what I mean.
Why isn't Sang Sik coming?
[Sang Sik]
Sang Sik?
Oh, the ring.
What the?
You are Sang Sik.
Sang Sik!
- Oppa!
- Excuse me!
- Excuse me! Take your money!
- Oh, seriously!
HY and SS?
Hae Young...
Sang...
Wow, Ma Tan, you're really rich.
Anyway, you're writing off 100,000 won for this, right?
You did a great job.
Then I'll be off now.
The sound of thunder...
was coming from you.
I didn't even use that much energy.
Would you like to eat something before you leave?
Are you going to ask me to pay for the meal?
I'm not that shameless.
Old habits die hard.
You must have had a lot of mosquitos at your old house.
Is there anything you want to eat?
[Basakana Chicken]
Well, I'm on a diet,
so I'll just eat the chicken breast.
I'll prepare some forceps for you.
Hey,
chicken tastes best when handled with bare hands and ripped into.
I actually had a heavy dinner.
Please enjoy it, Kang Mi.
No, you should have some, too.
I don't like oily foods—
It's really good.
Is that also chicken breast?
I'll just treat today as chicken day.
M-Ms. Kang Mi...
I'm sorry, but could you wipe your mouth, please?
I don't really like it when things are messy...
Oh, my... is it messy?
Stop, please!
I'll wipe it for you myself.
Okay.
Could you wipe the cheek area, too?
- Ma Tan...
- Mother...
It's still—
Thanks to you, I think I can really pull this off.
An innovative confession.
That's really too harsh...
What is?
Jupiter and Saturn have feelings, too, so she should've at least heard him out.
I mean, she said he was attentive and pure-hearted.
Isn't that enough then?
If you're with him, he buys you coffee and food,
takes out all the trash, eating only the radish when eating chicken,
and he even takes care of the dog poop.
Can't she give him a chance at least once at that point?
Why are you angry all of a sudden?
Who is it? A person like that...
There's somebody... Things don't work out for him even when the universe is helping.
♫ I hope that it was you ♫
♫ The person who'd be next to me when my life is shining ♫
♫ That one person ♫
♫ The person who'd stay with me after enduring the rough wind ♫
♫ The only person in this world ♫
♫ That's enough for me, I'll be satisfied ♫
♫ Then, in front of whatever life brings me, ♫
♫ I won't be afraid ♫
♫ because we'll be together for all of time, hey! ♫
♫ Because I love you ♫
♫ I want to tell you, only you ♫
♫ I want to show you everything, even before you ask me ♫
♫ Hurriedly to your ears, I love you ♫
♫ Because I love you ♫
♫ And every day if I'm holding you ♫
♫ I'm fine with living just for a day ♫
♫ Just stay by my side ♫
♫ You don't need to do anything ♫
♫ You are, you are ♫
Who was it?
Who's the one who abandoned you?
Did they throw you away because they got a new doll?
They should've cherished you a bit longer.
If they took a good look, they''d see that you were really great.
♫ That's enough for me, I'll be satisfied ♫
♫ Then, in front of whatever life brings me ♫
♫ I won't be afraid ♫
There's no one to hold an umbrella up for you...
♫ because we'll together for all of time ♫
You and I... we're both alone.
♫ Because I love you ♫
♫ Even before you ask me, hurriedly to your ears, ♫
Why are you sitting in the rain...
♫ Because I love you ♫
...so pitifully?
Senior...
♫ I'm fine with living just for a day ♫
♫ Just stay by my side ♫
♫ You don't need to do anything ♫
♫ You are, you are ♫
Credits
[Marketing Team 3's Sang Sik!]
[October 7, 2022]
[Gaus Electronics Break Room]
When confessing to the person you like, up to how many times would you be able to try?
How many times?
If you did it once and get rejected, then you make a reverse.
The story I'm going to tell you today...
This is the story of the day when a man, who was
rejected nine times by a woman that he had a
crush on for five years, confessed for the tenth time.
Wait, wait.
Nine times in five years, but he's doing it again?
Yes.
This man is quite headstrong.
So did he succeed?
No.
The tenth time, unfortunately, didn't succeed either.
[Shocked]
My, my.
Why, why, just why?
When he was confessing, the woman's real boyfriend came out.
Whoa, wait a minute...
So... So what happened?
Today's story...
Today's story ends here.
What? Why?
What?
[That man was mistaken]
He was mistaken.
What... The story is so critically anticlimatic.
What's your thought after hearing about that day's story?
Well...
[A person]
A person needs to drink...
Drink! Needs to drink good water.
That's why Gaus prepared this with much difficulty!
W-What? What is it?
[Gaus Water Purifier, Launching Soon]
So that you can calm his insides with cold water,
a gift presented for you.
Gaus Water Purifier.
[Gaus Water Purifier]
Gaus' present.
Gaus Water Purifier.
Everyone drink!
[Gaus Water Purifier]
- Great job, everyone.
- Thanks for your work.
Oh, okay. Thanks.
This is a story about Mr. Sang Sik, right?
What? N-No it's not.
Come on, what do you mean, "no?"
[Gaus Electronics]
Please forget whatever you heard yesterday.
Even if your cover gets blown, I don't think I'd be the cause.
Let's make some power!
I got the power. We got the power!
Then I'll give it a try.
You're finished eating?
Are you trying to announce you're a wealthy Young Boss?
Are you avoiding Hae Young?
- I'm not avoiding you.
- Then talk with Hae Young.
What a humiliation this is!
There's no such thing as getting off work in your lives anymore.
What the hell does he want us to change and how?
Hae Young likes Oppa.
So there's something you need to know, Oppa.
What?
What are you doing?
Gosh, what are you doing?
Senior!
Sen—
Senior...