[How dare you!?]
[Episode 30]
You.
Take him away.
And you.
Move!
Get out.
How is it going?
-It's freezing out here.
-This one.
-Come out.
-Take him away.
And you had to come out here
and go through this with us.
Are the higher-ups not planning
to promote you anymore?
Are you blind?
Alright, alright.
Sorry.
And you!
You,
come out.
Take him away!
You!
Take him away
for inspection.
Move.
Move!
Take him away!
Turn around.
What are you doing here?
Search carefully!
You,
go over there!
What's inside?
"Surprise."
You.
-What?
-Come out!
"Surprise."
Speak clearly.
Supplies.
Food!
Alright.
Go do something else.
I'll watch this cart.
You,
-come here.
-Go.
What are you doing?
-Move the supplies out quickly.
-Take him away!
So much trouble every day.
Get in!
Relax. It's me.
Why did you push me?
What rank am I and what rank are you?
Power-abusing wretch.
I've been roughing it outside,
and when I get back I still have to
take crap from you Imperial Guards!
Exactly.
If you don't give us an explanation today,
the Central Army will make you pay for it!
Yeah!
Arresting people for no reason—
what right do you have to do this?
Stand still!
Once Lord Cao finishes the verification...
Listen.
You'll be released!
Since you know how to steal,
you should know
how to do the opposite, right?
What are you doing?
What's taking you so long?
It's too heavy. I can't move it.
You brat!
Don't think I'll go easy on you
just because you're from my hometown.
What are you doing?
Do you know what this is?
I do.
Do you know its power?
If you dare call for help,
your emperor...
will send you to your death immediately.
I promise it will be grand.
Emperor?
Your Majesty, haven't you...
I have a bad temper
and love killing loud people.
You know that.
I do. I do.
You also shouldn't be this quiet.
Yes, yes.
I mean,
if you ever need me for anything,
I will do everything I can,
even at the cost of my life.
My legs are numb from standing.
Yeah.
Move!
Are you done yet?
Be polite.
Hurry up.
Watch your hands.
It's all orders from above.
Cut us some slack.
Are we done?
Exactly.
Seize him!
This isn't mine!
You're framing me!
Let me go!
Lord Cao,
this was found on him.
Report it to Prince Duan.
Yes!
This isn't mine!
You're framing me!
Tear off his face.
What are you doing?
My Lord,
This person isn't wearing a disguise.
Take him away.
Wait, Lord Cao!
Lord Cao,
what is the meaning of this?
We are investigating spies within the army
under Prince Duan's orders.
We ask for your full cooperation
so that no important matters are delayed.
Lord Cao,
the person you've arrested
is my cousin,
Li Wang, a centurion
of the Central Army.
If you say
he is a spy,
does that make me one too?
Or the whole Central Army?
Or even
the Three Armies?
Deputy General Li,
I never meant that.
It's just that the item found on him
is something used by that demonic consort,
Yu Wanyin.
I'm only bringing him back to ask
a few questions
to avoid any misunderstandings.
Ask questions?
Li Wang!
Here!
Is this yours?
No!
I asked.
He said it's not his.
Well...
Release him.
Release him!
You...
Are you trying to rebel?
It's the Central Army!
I saw it!
It came from the Central Army's side!
Let's go!
Go!
Your Majesty,
you're getting better with guns.
You're wrong.
It's a crossbow.
Nine Heavens Mystical Fire
Sleeve Crossbow.
Mr. Bei named it.
Don't call it by the wrong name.
Let's go!
Flower!
You go first.
Where is His Majesty?
Your Majesty!
Xiahou Dan!
I'm here!
Everyone entering the palace
must be searched again.
Generals,
please understand.
There was never any search
when we entered the palace before.
Now you keep
making things difficult for us.
What exactly is your intention?
I'm only following orders.
Please, generals,
forgive me.
Eunuch An,
it's not that we are being difficult.
After a forced march
of thousands of miles,
the troops are already on edge.
Could you ask Prince Duan to come
and clarify this in person?
If I remember correctly,
Eunuch An,
you serve at His Majesty's side.
Why is it that now,
when Prince Duan is in power,
he still uses the Emperor's old servant
to send messages?
Deputy General Lin, I...
don't quite...
understand what you're implying.
Could it be that
His Highness is being controlled by you?
Report!
The Central Army is staging a rebellion!
What?
What's going on?
What exactly is happening?
Report!
Commander Lei!
The Imperial Guards
asked us to provide support!
Shall we go?
Report!
The Central Army sent a message,
also asking us for help!
Shall we go?
This...
Come on...
How would I know?
Aren't we on the same side?
Commander, what should we do?
Well...
Come here!
Hurry up and go to the Right Army!
See what they say!
Yes!
Hurry! Go, go, go!
His Majesty said
our goal is to put
the situation under control
as quickly as possible
and minimize casualties.
Do you all understand
what to do?
Yes!
Defensive unit, step forward!
The rest of you,
grab your weapons
and follow me!
Yes!
Report!
What did the Right Army say?
They said that
since they abandoned us
after getting what they wanted,
we fight!
♪ Who stakes a claim? ♪
Well...
He's right, Commander.
♪ In the end,
whose hands will destiny fall into? ♪
Deputy General Zhou
went into the city alone.
♪ Treading through fire ♪
♪ Who dares to probe these truths? ♪
They're taking advantage
of our lack of leadership!
♪ Relying only on my courage ♪
♪ I roam this world ♪
Commander,
do we fight or not?
♪ Bright light exposes the evil ♪
Which side should we attack?
♪ Let me break through ♪
♪ The gap on this path to the underworld ♪
The Imperial Guards, of course.
♪ Thousands of lights
illuminate layers of mist ♪
♪ Forged in blazing fire,
I steel my bones for battle ♪
Let's fight!
Kill!
♪ Turning the world around,
the empire resounds ♪
♪ In the chaos,
shadows linger in every corner ♪
♪ Truth or lies, the more you hide,
the more it shows ♪
♪ Messages come from all directions,
like a game of hide and seek ♪
♪ Players in the game
wear masks as they clash ♪
♪ Ghostly flames and loyal hearts,
who will load the first shot? ♪
Kill!
♪ Stamping approval in cinnabar ♪
♪ Yet the ink
doesn't always mark the truth ♪
♪ In the rolls of fame ♪
♪ Not all deeds are genuine ♪
♪ Even with
a petition signed by 10,000 people ♪
♪ You may never make it
onto the merit list ♪
Kill!
♪ In the box of merit ♪
♪ It might not be the Bodhisattva's face ♪
♪ What a world,
each step full of schemes ♪
♪ Danger hides everywhere,
and life's like gambling ♪
Kill!
[Capital of Xia]
♪ See through the tricks,
truth and lies entwine ♪
♪ Betting on black or white,
what harm if you bet right? ♪
♪ What a Jianghu,
every blade cuts the heart ♪
♪ Every move a chain, and each may fail ♪
♪ Unmask this half-true,
half-false disguise ♪
♪ In this game within a game,
you and I are both in line ♪
[Capital of Xia]
♪ For every pure thought ♪
♪ There are as many
who trade their conscience blind ♪
♪ For every loyal and righteous heart ♪
♪ There are as many stained hands ♪
♪ Firearms blaze, piercing the sky ♪
♪ Divine machines break armor,
soaring high ♪
♪ Life-and-death contracts,
countless in sight ♪
♪ Secret orders arrive,
just a few echoes in the night ♪
♪ False or true, good and evil mix ♪
♪ Who will break through
the wheel of reincarnate tricks? ♪
♪ Power and schemes are execution
grounds for tens of thousands ♪
♪ Who will claim the crown
in this chaotic world? ♪
♪ What a world,
each step full of schemes ♪
♪ Danger hides everywhere,
and life's like gambling ♪
♪ See through the tricks,
truth and lies entwine ♪
♪ Betting on black or white,
what harm if you bet right? ♪
♪ What a Jianghu,
every blade cuts the heart ♪
♪ Every move a chain, and each may fail ♪
♪ Unmask this half-true,
half-false disguise ♪
♪ In this game within a game,
you and I are both in line ♪
♪ Firearms blaze, piercing the sky ♪
♪ Divine machines break armor,
soaring high ♪
♪ Life-and-death contracts,
countless in sight ♪
♪ Secret orders arrive,
just a few echoes in the night ♪
♪ False or true, good and evil mix ♪
♪ Who will break through
the wheel of reincarnate tricks? ♪
You...
♪ Power and schemes are execution
grounds for tens of thousands ♪
♪ Who will claim the crown
in this chaotic world? ♪
♪ What a world,
each step full of schemes ♪
Eunuch An!
♪ Danger hides everywhere,
and life's like gambling ♪
Eunuch An!
♪ See through the tricks,
truth and lies entwine ♪
Eunuch An!
It's alright now.
Here.
♪ Betting on black or white,
what harm if you bet right? ♪
♪ What a Jianghu,
every blade cuts the heart ♪
♪ Every move a chain, and each may fail ♪
♪ Unmask this half-true,
half-false disguise ♪
♪ In this game within a game,
you and I are both in line ♪
Kill!
♪ Who will claim the crown
in this chaotic world? ♪
♪ What a world,
each step full of schemes ♪
♪ Danger hides everywhere,
and life's like gambling ♪
♪ See through the tricks,
truth and lies entwine ♪
♪ Betting on black or white,
what harm if you bet right? ♪
♪ What a Jianghu,
every blade cuts the heart ♪
♪ Every move a chain, and each may fail ♪
♪ Unmask this half-true,
half-false disguise ♪
♪ In this game within a game,
you and I are both in line ♪
His Majesty is here!
Surrender now!
His Majesty?
Isn't His Majesty dead?
So...
So it's the Right Army
who's staging the rebellion!
No!
If that's really the Emperor and Empress,
then
we'll be the rebels.
His Majesty has passed away!
They...
must be imposters sent by the Right Army!
Your Majesty.
At a time like this,
you should show yourself
to display your imperial authority.
I've never seen such a shameless person!
A crippled dog,
daring to stand before my army
and bark madly!
Xiahou Bo, the traitor,
[Capital of Xia]
intended to murder
the Emperor and Empress!
Now that
the truth has been revealed,
he deserves to be executed!
Since you all
were unaware of the truth,
today,
those who switch sides and surrender
will not be punished!
His Majesty is here!
Surrender now!
-His Majesty is here!
-I, Deputy General Li Zhong
-Surrender now!
-of the Central Army,
-His Majesty is here! Surrender now!
-pay respects to Your Majesty!
His Majesty is here!
Surrender now!
Long live the Emperor!
[Memorial Tablet of Emperor Xiaohewen
of Great Xia]
Your Highness!
I just received word
that the Emperor and Empress Yu
have taken control of the Three Armies.
Lord Jia and Lord Cao have...
Now,
the Right Army
has surrounded the bedchamber.
They are armed with
a large number of firearms.
This...
Your Highness,
hear me out.
Where there is life, there is hope.
Let's...
surrender.
S-Surrender?
Why do you still not understand?
Everything I've done
is for the future of Great Xia.
The victor is king, the loser a bandit.
It is the will of Heaven.
At worst,
I will die.
Luckily,
I have you guys to accompany me.
Minister Yu,
you really raised a good daughter.
Mother...
Medic!
Here!
Take him and tend to his wounds!
Your Majesty!
We
were deceived by Prince Duan
and deserve death!
I am determined to lead the Central Army
and swear loyalty to you to the death!
And I am determined to lead the Left Army
to redeem myself,
and swear to serve Great Xia
with all my loyalty!
I will not pursue past wrongs.
But from today on,
the swords and spears
of Great Xia's soldiers
must only be aimed at invading enemies,
not used as tools
for treachery and power plays.
Your Majesty, you are magnanimous.
We are willing to shed
our blood and give our lives
to live up to your trust!
Your Majesty,
the Central Army
has suffered heavy casualties.
The Left Army's losses are lighter,
but many soldiers
were shaken during the battle just now.
As for how the two armies
should be settled going forward,
we await your instructions.
The Commander-in-Chief of the Three Armies
is now the Empress.
It depends on her decision.
General Lei,
report the Left Army's casualties
as soon as possible.
If needed,
you can ask the Right Army for assistance.
Yes!
General Li,
the Central Army's morale is unstable.
You must come up with a solution quickly.
If this affects border security,
I will hold you responsible.
Yes!
Generals,
set up camp outside the city immediately
and ensure the soldiers
are properly reassured.
Yes, Your Highness!
Yes!
Your Majesty!
Your Majesty,
Your Highness.
Prince Duan
is hiding in Your Majesty's bedchamber.
He's holding the Crown Prince
and the Imperial Father-in-law's family
as hostages.
General Lin dares not act recklessly
and asked me to seek your approval
on whether
we can take that shortcut
straight into the palace.
Do it.
Yes!
Pack up.
It's time to go home,
my Empress.
This... this...
No wonder Her Majesty could still be seen
in His Majesty's palace
after being sent to the Cold Palace.
Turns out there's
such a spacious secret passage here.
It wasn't
this wide before.
If His Majesty had spared
even a fraction of the care
he gave to Her Majesty,
Prince Duan would have been dead long ago.
We wouldn't have waited until today.
That's why you're still single, General.
You don't understand romance.
Such a shame for that handsome face.
Why are you everywhere?
Huixiao.
Cut off their heads one by one
and put them
right here.
Your Highness,
Huixiao
is gone.
That impostor not only deceived me,
but also killed your only good brother,
Huixiao.
So what are you waiting for?
Do it!
Your Highness!
Leave my family out of this!
Your Highness Prince Duan,
surrender now.
His Majesty is magnanimous
and benevolent.
He might spare your life.
I don't need him...
to spare my life!
Take him to the water dungeon!
This...
Where have you been all day and night?
There's a war going on outside.
Do you want to die?
Yeah.
We woke up and everyone was gone.
Where is Cen?
I took him home.
Cen is sick. Why did he go home?
What happened?
A notice in the city announces
that His Majesty and Her Majesty
have defeated Prince Duan
and returned to the capital.
Really?
That's great news!
I knew my half-baked fortune-telling
was inaccurate.
It kept showing bad omens.
Look at...
Er Lan...
Where is Jintian?
Jintian...
He...
This is the cloak I gave to Cen.
Why?
He entrusted me
to return this to you.
Li?
How could this happen?
[Yongyan Hall]
Your Majesty,
you have finally returned.
Thank you
for these past few days.
As long as I can see you
return safely,
I'm willing to do anything.
Where is General Lin?
General Lin...
found the body
Prince Duan used to impersonate you.
So,
Your Majesties,
please go and see it for yourselves.
Alright.
[Yongyan Hall]
Your Majesty.
I originally planned
to carry the body out
and expose the disguise
in front of everyone
to avoid any future rumors.
But...
after seeing that the mask
had already been removed,
I took a look myself first.
Is this some kind of joke?
Mr. Bei,
my head hurts so much.
I want some sweet porridge.
Mr. Bei?
How could this be?
He had clearly left back then.
His martial skills were so high.
How could Prince Duan
possibly capture him?
At first,
I didn't believe it either.
But,
Physician Xiao came and told me something.
Your Majesty,
please hear him out.
That day,
Prince Duan ordered me
to treat someone in prison.
We've used every torture method,
but His Majesty
refuses to write the edict.
How about we
let Physician Xiao take a look?
But when I entered the prison, I found out
that the person Prince Duan
wanted treated was actually...
Your Majesty.
Your Majesty!
Silence!
There is no "Your Majesty" here,
only the late emperor.
Treat him.
His Highness wants him alive.
Physician Xiao...
At that time,
Mr. Bei disguised himself as Your Majesty.
It wasn't just his appearance.
Even his mannerisms
were copied perfectly.
No one in the palace
noticed anything amiss.
Prince Duan
didn't suspect anything either.
It's just that...
What?
It's just that at the time, Mr. Bei
was seriously injured
and on his last breath.
From his pulse,
he had taken a deadly poison.
He was in very bad condition.
Impossible!
When I parted ways with him,
he didn't have a single scratch on him!
Your Majesty.
Mr. Bei's injuries...
were not caused by anyone else.
I'm not her child.
I'm just a lone soul living in this body.
Everything I said before
was a lie.
Dan,
you'll have to
walk the path ahead on your own.
I...
can only accompany you this far.
The only person in the world
who could harm Mr. Bei this badly
was himself.
To avoid revealing any flaws, Mr. Bei
even took a deadly poison
to prevent Prince Duan from
discovering it through his pulse.
So, even though I
did my best,
I could not save him.
No need to bother treating me.
My time is up.
Mr. Bei.
This is how it was meant to be.
I'm already satisfied that I could
buy Dan a few more days.
Dan...
I leave Dan's illness...
in your hands.
Mr. Bei, rest assured.
I will do my best.
I still have some internal force left.
Later,
I want to see Xiahou Bo again.
By then,
you must hide far away.
Later, after I left the prison,
I saw Prince Duan
rushing over.
So I found an excuse
to stay for a moment.
Watch out, Your Highness!
But unfortunately,
a secret guard by Prince Duan's side,
named Huixiao,
blocked Mr. Bei's strike.
In the end, he failed to kill Prince Duan.
How could this happen?
Mr. Bei,
how could you...
He knew I wasn't her son.
Why did he still sacrifice
his life for me?
Mr. Bei had very little to live for.
Perhaps in his heart,
you were already his child,
the family he wanted to protect.
Actually, I returned to the capital
to keep you safe.
But I worried that
you might not need protecting.
Now that we've cleared everything up,
there's no need for more words.
Since Nan
said so,
if I were to abandon you,
who else
in this world
could keep you safe?
Nan's child
is my child too.
I have no family in this world.
The reason I protect you with all my might
is not for any grand cause
of the country or family.
If you dare risk your life again
for this darn throne,
I will tie you up and take you away!
Do you understand?
No!
No. My head hurts.
Your Majesty.
What's wrong?
Your Majesty!
-Your Majesty!
Mr. Bei once entrusted me
-to take care of His Majesty
-Your Majesty!
-whenever his illness flared up.
Please go back, Your Majesty!
Your Majesty!
Servants!
Er Lan.
You haven't left yet?
I'm...
writing a memorial.
I have an audience
with His Majesty tomorrow,
so I'm organizing my thoughts.
I'm afraid I'll get too excited
and forget something.
So I'm
rewriting it.
Are you...
feeling better?
I'm fine now.
That's good.
Good.
Are... are you hungry?
This is the food I made.
It's still warm.
Why don't you...
try some?
I'll get you chopsticks.
Chopsticks...
Where are the chopsticks?
I'll get... I prepared... I'll get...
I remember I got them.
Chopsticks.
Er Lan,
it's my first time cooking.
I don't know
how it tastes.
Taste...
it for me, will you?
Thank you.
Have you eaten?
I have.
Eat with me.
I'm not hungry.
Eat.
Where is Yang?
He was called away
by the Ministry of Personnel.
I stayed because I was worried about you.
I...
was worried about you.
You know what?
The Ministry of Revenue
doesn't know we're hiding here.
They're probably
searching everywhere for us right now.
They...
Tomorrow,
we're going to see His Majesty together.
We must pull ourselves together.
You...
should eat something.
Cen's...
greatest wish...
was for the people to eat well.
You are one of the people,
and more importantly, you are our friend.
Have a bite.
Thank you.
Eat well.