[How dare you!?]
[Episode 17]
If you don't believe
Yu Wanyin would say something like this
to Xie Yong'er,
that's fine.
I'll ask you in a different identity.
How...
Are...
You?
Answer me!
How are you?
You too?
Yes, I am.
I'm tired.
Let's put our cards on the table.
I don't know what you're talking about.
You already know very well who I am.
Stop talking!
How long are you going to
keep running from this?
I'll ask you that same question again
right now.
Do you dare answer it?
Answer what?
Your Majesty.
Consort Yu has gone crazy.
She keeps saying strange things.
I'm really scared.
Is that so?
Let me answer it for you.
Fine.
Thank you.
And you?
You too?
[Kunyu Palace]
Why are you here?
Is everything with the envoy delegation
settled?
More or less.
I muddled through it
without any real trouble.
I heard
the Empress Dowager gave you a hard time.
I managed to muddle through it as well.
You're awake.
So you two, like me,
are also transmigrators?
Yes.
Since we're all the same kind...
Since we're all the same kind,
why didn't you tell me earlier?
Did you have to watch me from the shadows
and see me make a fool of myself?
Right.
Watching you cheat on me the whole time—
pretty thrilling.
Then...
Then why are you telling me now?
Why not just kill me?
Just tell the public that Xie Yong'er
died from childbirth complications.
This way, Prince Duan
wouldn't suspect anything.
Wouldn't that be even better?
Indeed.
Wanyin, why did you tell her?
Well...
Why not just kill her?
Yong'er,
look,
we've already reached the point of
miscarriage
and framing each other.
If the plot keeps developing like this,
it'll be a fight to the death.
Since we're all the same kind,
isn't there another possibility for us?
Stop being so hypocritical.
You never intended to tell me the truth
from the start.
Now that you see me
in this state,
you come telling me we're the same kind?
Haven't you had your fill of the joke yet?
If we had told you
right after we transmigrated,
would your first reaction
have been to cooperate?
At that time, you had already
sided with Prince Duan.
Suddenly finding out
that I was a wild card,
you'd probably
have gone straight to Prince Duan
and told him
to take me out
while I was still weak.
Am I wrong?
Makes sense.
But
is there anything wrong with
me wanting to survive?
Don't you two want to survive?
Of course we do.
Yong'er.
I don't think you're wrong.
It's this darn situation that's wrong.
If possible,
I hope you, me,
the three of us
can all make it to the end.
Then we
can have hotpot together
and play a few rounds of
"Fight the Landlord."
It would be so much fun.
Stop with your act.
If the roles were reversed,
I believe your choices
wouldn't be any different from mine.
But the difference is huge.
If Wanyin had been as ruthless
as you were when you framed her,
you wouldn't even be alive now.
Come on, bro.
Are you determined to sabotage our plan?
That's not the case at all.
Actually, Yong'er
is not as cruel as he imagined.
Right, Yong'er?
Come on, get up. It's cold on the floor.
What are you doing?
I don't think
there's anything more
to talk about with her.
Let's go.
Why were you constantly
undermining my efforts just now?
Xie Yong'er is emotionally vulnerable
right now.
I was trying to turn her.
I know.
I was working with you.
What kind of "working with me" is that?
I intimidate,
you entice.
She cheated on me, all right?
Even if I was just putting on a show
for the Empress Dowager,
it's reasonable for me to be
a little harsh on her.
Xie Yong'er is a real villain.
Forget about turning her.
Do people who've made mistakes
not deserve a fresh start?
She probably didn't intend to
harm me today.
It was just a stress response to
the Empress Dowager.
I just happened to
have a higher ground than her,
and I met you,
which allowed me to seize the initiative
and even appear justified
in everything I did.
Everything I did was just
to protect myself.
The only reason I wanted her to survive
was because I'm worried
the story would get cut short.
So essentially, I'm not really
any different from her, am I?
You are.
Have you never thought
that keeping someone alive
can be done in many ways?
Chop off her legs,
imprison her for life—
so long as she doesn't die,
the goal
is still achieved, isn't it?
You can't even think of that,
and you dare call yourself a villain?
If it were Xie Yong'er,
she'd definitely think of it.
She's just a 2D character.
She's as wicked
as the plot requires her to be.
You...
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Wanyin, you left in a hurry.
Did you eat enough?
I'm okay.
I'll just ask the servants
to heat up something
for a late-night snack later.
That's thoughtful of you.
Dealing with the Empress Dowager,
guarding against the Yan State envoys,
and still remembering to bring me food.
No way.
Getting moved so easily,
"great villain"?
All right, I'll stop teasing you.
Eat up, or I'll have brought it
for nothing.
By the way,
what kind of person were you before?
Just an ordinary guy.
No real skills, no connections,
and... Okay-looking, I guess.
So modest, huh?
What about you?
Me?
I was also ordinary.
Working nine to five every day,
serving one client after another.
When it got busy,
I didn't even have time to wash my hair—
completely different from how I look now.
No need to put yourself down.
You must have been good-looking as well.
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
Well,
I'll head back to the palace first.
Aren't we still putting on that whole
"chasing-your-wife-after-screwing-up" act?
Get some rest early.
As soon as the banquet ended,
His Majesty immediately
went to Consort Xie's place
and tightened the security
around her chambers.
From what I can see,
His Majesty is quite attentive to her.
It doesn't look like he was
the one behind this.
Then this
really is suspicious.
Could it be
that I overthought it?
You may leave now.
Yes.
Your Majesty.
His Majesty has always kept out of
state affairs.
Why is it that this time, he repeatedly
stepped in to smooth things over
for the envoy delegation?
We
truly cannot make sense of it.
It seems His Majesty's wings
have grown stronger
and he's begun to form ideas of his own.
If the peace talks succeed
and the borders are secured,
Prince Duan's power
will swell completely,
and we'll be left on the back foot.
So what do you suggest?
His Highness Crown Prince
is wise and benevolent,
and he carries the bearing of
a wise ruler.
These Yan people can't even
manage a proper sentence
in the official tongue.
Walking around the capital,
frictions with the Xia people
are bound to happen.
A bunch of barbarians—
one wrong word
and they might start throwing punches.
Blades have no eyes.
Before you know it,
there could be bloodshed.
I'll see to it right away.
Your Majesty.
Killing envoys during a conflict
between two states
could very well spark a new war.
That's right, Your Majesty.
The safety of our state
is something we officials
cannot afford not to consider.
What's there to worry about?
Even if the Central Army is defeated,
we can still deploy
the Left and Right Armies.
Then we can just sit back and
watch the Yan people and Prince Duan
wear each other out.
But...
Crown Prince.
What's your take on this?
If Grandmother believes we should fight,
then we should fight.
Exactly!
If the Crown Prince says
we fight,
then we fight!
Thanks to you, Yang,
that I get to enjoy such fine wine today.
I won't stand on ceremony then.
Come on.
It's rare to see you
drinking so heartily, Li.
I'll join you.
It's been ages since the three of us
got together.
Why are you drinking tea?
Switch to wine.
I'll pass.
I'd like to stay alive a bit longer
to tend my fields.
Don't drink alone.
Come on, let's drink together.
Come on. Cheers.
Yang, since you got here,
you've barely said a few words.
Aren't you usually the chattiest one?
Why so quiet today?
You seem to have lost weight, Yang.
Has something happened?
I never want to talk again
in this lifetime.
You two
both got what you wished for—
you joined the Ministry of Revenue,
and you get to keep studying farming.
Do you know what I'm in charge of
after entering the Imperial Observatory?
Divination.
Reading the stars for omens of
fortune and disaster, rise and fall.
I spend my days spinning stories
for people.
And you think I can just make them up?
No.
If His Majesty wants this reading
to foretell misfortune,
then I have to couch it
in grand, arcane phrasing—
pacing the constellations,
plumbing the mysteries of change—
so that even bad news
sounds ornate and eloquent.
Is my literary talent
really meant for this?
Let them leave.
Enough with the dance.
You all,
get out.
Get out.
All of you, get out too.
-Let's go then.
-Let's go.
Hurry up.
What kind of rubbish dance is that?
Nowhere near as good as
the dances of our Great Yan.
And this wine and these dishes—
too delicate.
Not satisfying at all!
Ever since we came to Great Xia,
I haven't felt at ease for a single day!
At the Grand Longevity Banquet,
the Empress Dowager
was clearly targeting us.
I just can't
swallow such insult!
Enough.
We've long known
how insidious and cunning
the Xia people are.
What's most important now
is keeping our composure
and waiting for the right moment.
As long as Xiahou Dan agrees to
meet us alone,
we can kill this dog of an emperor
without losing a single soldier.
That old Emperor of Yan
is counting his chickens too early.
Let's put in some effort
and make sure he spends his old age
thoroughly engulfed in the flames of war.
Speaking of which,
we pulled a switcheroo
and took
the real envoy delegation's place.
Do you think
Zhaluowahan
has realized by now?
And what if he has?
He's nothing but
a toothless old wolf now.
He's probably eagerly waiting for
the outcome of the peace talks.
Alright.
Come on.
Cheers.
Alright.
It's time for the Xia people
to pay the blood debt they owe us.
I, Yang Duojie,
with my ten years of diligent study
and exceptional talent,
actually ended up
becoming a fortune-teller.
Keep your voices down.
Yang.
Didn't His Majesty say
that, for now, he needs you to write
those mystical, mumbo-jumbo pieces
to fool people,
and he'll transfer you elsewhere
after a while?
Allow me to say something
downright treasonous—
do you believe that?
I do.
I believe it too.
Therefore,
you should also have
more faith in His Majesty.
His Majesty also told me
to keep compiling the land registers
from various regions,
saying they would be useful someday.
That counts as the Emperor's promise,
doesn't it?
That's not what you said when you
first joined the Ministry of Revenue.
So you don't mind
Er Lan being so socially adept
and rising through the ranks with ease
anymore?
I don't see him that way now.
Then why didn't you invite Er
along today?
You're the host—
shouldn't you be the one to invite him?
But you both work in
the Ministry of Revenue.
Yes, we do.
I even nodded to him
when I saw him earlier.
I thought he was heading here.
That's on you.
Besides, he's probably swamped with
work now. Able men are always busy, right?
How would he have time to come out
for our little get-together?
Well said—"able men are always busy."
You're all so steadfast.
Turns out I'm the only one still wavering.
Take Wang Zhao for instance.
He was supposed to return
with the envoy delegation,
yet now he's been kept in Yan State.
I fear the worst for him.
And His Majesty, fully aware that
the Yan people came with ill intent,
still lowered himself
to curry favor with them.
I can't understand
what he's really thinking,
and I don't know
-what he takes us for...
-Stop there!
-What's happening?
-What do you want?
They're from the Yan State, right?
-You haven't paid yet. You can't leave.
-Looks like it's those Yan fellows.
Speak of the devil.
Six dishes, four jugs of wine—
you even gave us two coins in change.
That only covers the food and drinks.
You didn't pay for the songstress.
What songstress?
She came in and sang on her own,
and she barely sang a couple of lines
before we sent her away.
Everyone knows that
Miss Miaoying is a star on our street.
So many people spend a fortune
to hire her, yet can't.
How is it that with you Yan folks,
she came performing for you on her own?
How much do you want?
You're quite straightforward.
50 taels.
They're deliberately giving us trouble.
We can't pay this money.
Don't forget the purpose of this trip.
We can't risk the big picture
over small matters.
That should be enough.
It's not enough!
This isn't just a matter of money!
They... They even tried to
take advantage of me.
That's pure slander!
Who tried to take advantage of you?
Him! It was him!
Me?
Yes, it was him!
Everyone, look!
He even left his handprint right here!
-You don't think this situation...
-I didn't take advantage of her!
Is going to escalate into a fight, do you?
Don't jinx it. Just stop talking.
It was him!
-How could you hit her?
-Let's go.
How could you do that?
Stop there!
Brother, they're the ones who bullied me!
You bullied my sister
and think you can just walk away?
Beat them!
We can't kill them.
But, Your Highness...
If we kill them, we'll be charged
and arrested.
Something's not right.
These people's fighting skills
don't seem like those of
ordinary laborers or commoners.
You go first.
We'll stay here and deal with them.
No.
We must leave together.
Who was it?
[Zuixiang House]
Run!
Are you crazy?
Do you know how much
that jug of wine is worth?
You're the crazy one!
At this point, you still care about money?
Stop arguing, you two.
They clearly came prepared.
Who knows
if they're the Empress Dowager's people.
Here's what we'll do. Yang,
hurry into the palace
and report this to His Majesty.
Li, let's follow them
and see if we can help.
Follow them? I just hit them.
They don't know it was you.
Besides,
the envoy delegation's safety
is crucial to stopping the war.
Let's split up.
You're right.
Yang!
This way.
Do we have to sneak around like thieves?
Stop!
Stop there!
Block them!
There's a path behind the wall.
Climb over!
Okay.
Let's go!
Stop! Don't run!
Get down here!
Easy!
Behave yourself!
Move!
Thank you for the timely report, Mr. Li.
We'll take these criminals back
for thorough questioning.
Those Yan State envoys
should have left safely.
They actually dared carry out
such bandit-like attacks
in broad daylight.
It seems
the Empress Dowager is really going to
show her real colors.
The crisis in these peace talks
is still unresolved.
Let's hope His Majesty
can make preparations soon.
Where's Hawugu?
Those people who came to kill us
must have been sent by
the Empress Dowager.
That woman targeted me
back in the main hall.
I suppose she couldn't think of
any other tricks.
Those soldiers arrived pretty fast though.
It was probably the person
who threw the jug
who notified the soldiers.
Could it be the Emperor's men?
Not likely.
I don't think
they're with the same group as
the ones who told us to
climb over the wall.
So there's internal conflict in Great Xia
as well.
Let's go.
I left right after giving the signal.
As Your Highness instructed,
I didn't show my face in front of
the envoy delegation.
Did you discover anything else?
That Haqina in their group
doesn't seem to be the real leader.
During the fight,
I heard him call that burly attendant
"Your Highness."
I also found that bearded man
very suspicious.
He seemed to be deliberately disguised,
and he kept reminding those around him
not to provoke conflicts.
I remember now.
There was indeed such a person.
At the Grand Longevity Banquet,
you said he was a master fighter,
right, Mr. Bei?
That's right.
That man's internal force
is extremely profound,
far superior to Haqina's.
So here's the question:
why would a master fighter
disguise himself as an attendant?
Those Yan people
have probably never
been truly seen by
our Great Xia's people before.
There's supposed to be no need for them
to hide their faces.
Since he's in disguise,
he must be someone familiar to us.
The occasion where our people
would recognize his face...
Could it be...
The battlefield?
With his skills,
he could indeed live up to the title of
top fighter of the Yan State.
He's Tu'er!
[Prince Tu'er]
With the beard, they do look
about 70% to 80% similar.
But it's long been rumored that
Tu'er and the old Emperor of Yan
are at odds.
So how could he have been sent
as part of the envoy delegation?
Could it be...
The envoy delegation is fake.
No wonder!
No wonder Wang Zhao
didn't come back with them.
Your Majesty,
they must be carrying many schemes
on this visit.
Please be extra cautious, Your Majesty.
I understand.
Here's what we'll do.
Mr. Yang.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Send the Ministry of Rites to
the envoy delegation's inn to apologize.
The more ceremonious the display,
the better.
Apologize?
But shouldn't we...
Yes, Your Majesty.
Dan.
Those Yan people have not come
with good intentions.
You should make preparations early.
If we want peace talks,
we have to take risks.
Besides, in a way,
Tu'er and I should have met long ago.
Then should we
tell Wanyin about this matter?
No.
The matter with Xie Yong'er
is already troubling her enough.
I don't want to add more pressure on her.
[Prince Tu'er]
[Beautiful Lady Shanyi]
[A few years ago]
[Yixuan Restaurant]
This is a gift sent by
the Great Xia Emperor,
saying it's compensation
to our envoy delegation
for what happened during the day.
All they know
is how to apologize.
I noticed there are more guards
on duty today.
It's said they were specially reinforced
to prevent the criminals
from striking again—
to protect us.
Whether they're trying to protect us
or keep an eye on us
is hard to say.
You know, years ago,
when the Emperor of Yan
fought against our country,
he didn't just get shot in one eye—
he was actually hit in another part
of his body as well.
That's why he has no children of his own
and only has Tu'er as his nephew.
Zhaluowahan may not have been
especially close to Tu'er,
but he dutifully taught him
how to ride and hunt.
Who would have thought
those two had such affection
as uncle and nephew?
In the blink of an eye,
Tu'er grew into a valiant young man,
surpassing the Emperor of Yan
in riding and archery,
and the number of subjects supporting him
gradually increased.
As Tu'er became the Yan State's
top fighter,
calls for the old Emperor of Yan
to abdicate
and give the throne to Tu'er
grew louder by the day.
Truly, raising a nephew
turned out to be the uncle's hardship.
Beautiful Lady Shanyi
was originally Tu'er's lover,
but was sent to Great Xia
as a gift by the Emperor of Yan.
She later died in the palace
after a failed assassination attempt.
However, afterward, the Yan people
not only denied the assassination attempt,
but even accused Great Xia of killing her
and used this as an excuse
to wage war against us.
So Tu'er must hate the Emperor to death.
This time,
could he be trying to imitate Jing Ke,
changing his name and disguising himself
to infiltrate the envoy delegation?
Risking his life seems unnecessary.
The Emperor is already in a weak position,
and the expert by his side is dead.
And this time, Tu'er has brought
a whole group of Jing Kes with him.
Your Highness,
do you think we should
reveal something to the Emperor?
I didn't expect that you, Mr. Cao,
would be so concerned about the Emperor.
I'm thinking entirely of
Your Highness's interests.
If Tu'er really kills the Emperor,
war will break out
between our states again.
By then,
we won't have resources
to deal with the Empress Dowager.
I was thinking the same thing earlier.
But then I realized something.
Since the person coming is Tu'er,
with his skills,
when carrying out the assassin
like Jing Ke,
accidentally killing
the Empress Dowager too
shouldn't be difficult, right?
With no one at the helm,
formidable enemies outside,
and the Crown Prince still young,
someone would have to serve as regent
to manage state affairs.
As for the war,
since we're all aware of it now,
we can prepare in advance,
so we won't be caught off guard
by the Yan State's surprise attack.
Therefore, we need not inform the Emperor.
When necessary,
we can even lend Tu'er a helping hand.
[Ten years ago] [Emperor of Yan]
[Ten years ago]
Your Majesty, this is Tu'er.
Un... Un...
Uncle.
Does it hurt?
No, it doesn't.
What's this?
It's a Camel Bell flower.
It's really pretty.
Shanyi!
Is it pretty?
Yes, it is.
I'm about to leave for the Great Xia.
Has our Yan State run out of men
that we have to send a woman
as an envoy?
Because I'm the holy maiden
chosen by the people of Yan.
Naturally, I must go and dance for them.
This is a dagger I made myself.
Take it for protection.
It's really pretty.
Even engraved with Camel Bell flowers.
I wanted to go with you,
but Uncle insists I stay
to handle state affairs.
Please be extra careful on your journey.
Don't worry.
I'm going for peace talks, not war.
There won't be any danger.
Shanyi, hurry up!
We're all waiting for you.
Coming!
Tu'er.
Wait for me to come back.
I have something to tell you.
Uncle.
Why hasn't Shanyi returned?
She's the holy maiden.
She should have returned with
the envoy delegation.
Uncle.
What happened to Shanyi?
That Emperor of the Great Xia...
He was impressed by Shanyi's dancing
and actually tried to
take advantage of her
right there in the main hall!
Shanyi
refused to be humiliated
and fought back fiercely,
but that Emperor...
He actually killed Shanyi!
Zhang San's Diary.
[Rockery]
[1-3 AM]
It's her.
She's here.
[1-3 AM]