[How dare you!?]
[Episode 23]
Lord Chen.
Please.
Good morning, Lord Chen.
Hello.
So many new faces around.
Indeed. We thought
when the Empress Dowager fell,
we'd be in trouble.
But unexpectedly,
we've risen to prominence.
Now we're riding high on success.
I haven't been sleeping well these days,
afraid
it's all just a fleeting dream.
Lord Chen.
Don't you get it yet?
We thought Prince Duan was formidable,
but now we realize
the more ruthless one
is above him.
Lord Chen is right.
Who gets promoted
and who loses their life—
it's all within
the Emperor's control.
Do you think
His Majesty will seek to
settle scores with us later?
What scores would there be?
The Emperor
and the Empress Dowager are family.
All these years, we've diligently
served His Majesty.
If anyone would have scores to be settled,
it should be
the other faction's.
Did you see that?
They avoid us like the plague.
A bunch of opportunists.
His Highness hasn't summoned us for days.
What should we do?
We're completely in the dark.
It's better not to be summoned.
His Majesty is displeased with us now.
This is for our protection.
That's not right.
I saw Lord Mu
enter the Emperor's residence yesterday.
His Majesty arrives!
Long live Your Majesty!
Rise, all of you.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Where is Lord Mu?
Your Majesty,
I am here.
The personnel evaluation records
of the Ministry of Personnel
that I ordered you to submit—
why aren't they completed yet?
Your Majesty,
over the past decade,
the changes in the court officials
have been complex.
The recording work
is enormous and tedious.
It cannot be completed overnight.
I humbly request Your Majesty
to grant me a few more days.
These personnel evaluations
should be organized annually.
Isn't tracking changes
a simple matter?
Look at our Ministry of Revenue.
The changes we have to track
are the changes in land and population
across the country.
The workload is hundreds of times greater,
yet we still completed it.
That's right.
Indeed.
Exactly.
Your Majesty,
recently, there have been
frequent personnel changes in court.
In my ministry alone,
including the Left Vice Minister,
we are short five officials.
I have been searching for
suitable candidates
to fill these positions.
But unfortunately...
Your Majesty.
I do not agree
with
Lord Mu.
If we're talking about
having difficulty looking for candidates,
it's obvious that the Ministry of War
has it the most difficult.
Although the court
has suffered serious losses recently,
many talented
young officials have emerged.
Lord Mu,
why not promote them?
Lord Mu, you mustn't
let your personal feelings interfere.
Your Majesty, you are wise!
I... I would never dare do such a thing!
My ministers, you all make valid points.
I can understand
Lord Mu's difficulties too.
But this matter must be resolved.
How about this?
Is there anyone willing to volunteer
to help Lord Mu with this urgent matter?
I,
Yang Duojie!
Am willing to help Lord Mu.
Isn't this Lord Yang
from the Imperial Astronomer's office?
The Imperial Astronomer's office
has nothing to do
with the Ministry of Personnel.
Your Majesty...
Is this appropriate?
Since I joined
the Imperial Astronomer's office,
I've calculated calendars,
established seasonal divisions,
observed celestial phenomena,
and divined fortunes.
All these duties
require coordination and cooperation
with various ministries
and attention to every detail.
Therefore,
I think I am
the best candidate
to extend help
to Lord Mu.
Lord Yang previously saved us
at Mount Bei,
and now takes the initiative to help
the Ministry of Personnel—
he is truly a talented young official!
If my Ministry of Revenue
weren't running so smoothly,
I would want to ask Lord Mu
to transfer him to me.
Indeed!
I second that.
-I also agree.
If that's the case,
I promote Yang Duojie
to Vice Minister of Personnel
to quickly compile the records I need.
As for Lord Mu...
Your Majesty.
You've been overworked lately.
You should rest
at home for now.
Your Highness.
By all accounts,
I'm openly aligned
with the Empress Dowager's faction.
Yet he not only
doesn't try to win me over,
but puts me on the hot seat repeatedly.
I've been thinking hard,
but I don't think
I've shown any flaw anywhere.
Please understand, Your Highness.
Lord Mu, you misunderstand.
I don't mean to blame you.
This is just like
the recent failure at Mount Bei.
We know for sure
the strategy was sound,
but there were just
some unexpected variables.
Variables?
The first one
is the strange firearms they possess.
Its destructive power is terrifying.
The other one is
that the expert we met
on the pleasure boat
is not dead.
Noble Consort Yu deceived us?
Even if she deceived us,
if no one had tipped them off
and handed over our undercover agents,
along with Lord Murong,
as gifts of surrender,
I believe the Emperor
wouldn't have made it down
Mount Bei alive.
The one who knew
the entire assassination plan
and was aware
of all the personnel involved...
It's Consort Xie!
That wretched woman...
Hot pot?
Two soup bases too!
We've been waiting for you.
Come sit down.
If I'd known you lived like this,
I would've switched factions long ago.
It's not too late now.
After we finish eating,
let's play some mahjong.
You know what?
Rumors are spreading among the people
saying
I harmed the Empress Dowager.
And that thunderstorm
was divine punishment
for my misconduct as ruler.
Eat this.
This is clearly a rumor
spread by Prince Duan's faction.
Prince Duan values
having a legitimate cause.
Those rumors
are all groundwork
for his future rebellion.
Put it in the spicy soup base?
But the problem is
we can't prove our innocence either.
Who's spreading these rumors?
I'll go kill one of them
as a warning.
No!
Why not?
Suppression will only backfire.
What should we do then?
Fight evil with evil!
Evil?
Which sect is it from?
I've never heard of it.
I'm from the Devil's Castle.
Anyway,
if Prince Duan calls you a tyrant,
you call him a hypocrite.
If he says you harmed the Empress Dowager,
you say he hired assassins.
If he says you were struck by lightning,
you say as the true Son of Heaven,
you can summon 81 thunderbolts
with a wave of your hand
to strike down on all the other assassins.
Isn't that too exaggerated?
Seems quite dramatic too.
What do you two know?
Let me put it this way.
If you excitedly share
with other people this:
"Jeez!
I learned something from a book today."
Would you be sharing about things
like the Pythagorean theorem, functions,
prime numbers,
or that pi equals 3.1415926?
Of course not!
Because you can't even remember that.
But
if you go tell others,
"Oh my God.
That tyrant
just waved his arm
and summoned 100,000 thunderbolts,
killing all the
darn assassins."
Would you go around telling others that?
That makes some sense.
Throughout history, Emperors,
to win people's hearts,
would even make up stories
about hiding books in fish bellies.
The key is that
people actually believed them.
Not bad, Xie.
You've got skills.
Prince Duan has lasted this long
all because of your support.
Him?
That bastard.
He's no fun to play with.
I'm done with him.
But
I must warn you.
Public opinion battles
are just the first wave.
The real attacks come after.
You better be careful.
He wants legitimate reasons.
He won't make a move inside the palace.
That's right.
Xu Yao's book also says
he'll only make his move
when you leave the palace.
I've been meaning to ask you.
You mentioned before
that the plan in Xu Yao's book
was different from my original plan.
How did you know that?
I only told Xiahou Bo.
After Xu Yao switched sides,
he told me everything.
He discussed all the suggestions you made
with Prince Duan before.
That makes sense now.
I got it!
What?
What's wrong, Mr. Bei?
What did you get?
Evil!
Braised egg.
I didn't get that right.
Let me go again.
Living in ancient times,
not having a bathroom heater is fine.
But not having a hair dryer,
that's the real trouble.
Who told you to bathe every day?
After hot pot, I smell all over.
How can I sleep?
That's true.
You smell so nice.
What are you doing?
Let me go.
No.
If you keep fooling around,
I'll make you take medicine.
Why take medicine?
I'm not sick.
Quick!
Let go—
Mr. Bei.
What is it?
Dan.
Li Yunxi delivered a letter.
What does it say?
Cen Jintian's condition has worsened.
He might not make it through this winter.
[For the Emperor's personal attention:
Cen Jintian's health is deteriorating.]
[I'm afraid he can't make it
through winter. He has compiled]
[the planting of Yan millet in a manual.]
How could this be?
[He hopes Your Majesty can go
see him one last time.]
In the original story,
he at least survived until the drought.
How did it push forward by so much?
That's because
he was hanging on
hoping to see the harvest.
Now he knows the people
will survive the drought,
he has nothing to worry about anymore.
For him,
it's a satisfying ending.
How can this be considered
a happy ending?
We clearly promised him before
that he would live to see
peace and prosperity throughout the land.
But you know,
when we used those words
to gain his loyalty,
there probably wasn't enough time.
That vision...
can only remain a vision.
He says
he wants to see you one more time.
I can't leave the palace now.
I know.
-So I can—
-You can't.
Why not?
It's too dangerous out there now.
Prince Duan's spies are everywhere.
I'll be careful.
And I have secret guards to protect me.
We lost so many men
at Mount Bei.
These are all we have left.
And some must be sent
to protect Xie Yong'er.
What about Wang Zhao's funeral?
Are we not attending that either?
Let those scholars represent us
and build a cenotaph for him.
But...
Wanyin.
Don't forget.
They are 2D characters.
If you forget this,
you'll be dragged down.
But when you heard about Wang Zhao's death
at Mount Bei,
you didn't react like this.
That's why I remind myself
never to get too emotional.
Wanyin.
You must listen to me on this.
If anything happens to you,
I can't go on living.
By the way,
your father sent a message
saying he wants to see you.
I guess
he's not doing well with Prince Duan
and sees an opportunity here.
He wants to use your influence
to find a new path for himself.
Do you want to see him?
No.
As long as I don't see him,
he'll forever remain just a 2D character.
Your Majesty.
The Ministry of Revenue's Lord Chen,
the Ministry of Personnel's Lord Liang,
and the two ministers
from the Ministry of Justice
have all requested leave
saying
they cannot come for an audience today.
Die?
Capture?
Kill?
Is Her Majesty asking for water?
Water?
Water, water!
Quickly, get some water!
Yes.
Ma'am,
the path is rough here. Please be careful.
It's fine.
Everyone,
are you all my son's colleagues?
We were Wang's closest friends,
here to see him off.
Thank you
very much.
My son mentioned
he worked for an official
who treated him very well.
But I didn't know who that is.
I wanted
to come
and thank him in person
for taking care of my son.
Li!
Please wait a moment.
Wait for what?
The auspicious time you divined
is almost passing.
Well...
They probably won't come.
There are too many eyes watching.
They must be in a difficult position too.
Right now,
if Prince Duan's spies discover them,
it be big trouble.
Her Highness usually has so many ideas.
What now?
She has no more ideas?
Li, please don't be upset.
The court is in turmoil now,
and the confrontation with Prince Duan
hangs in the balance.
His Majesty and Her Highness are not
the type to discard loyal servants.
Right now,
they must be heartbroken
that they cannot attend.
If our Wang knows from the afterlife,
he would surely understand.
Of course I know
that His Majesty and Her Highness
are not heartless people.
But when Wang died,
he was all alone,
thousands of miles away.
Today at his burial,
we don't even have his body,
and we dare not carve his name
on the tombstone too.
Yet those he trusted completely
and gave his life for
cannot even see him one last time.
I feel it's so unfair to him.
I feel such pity for him.
We are here to see him off
on his final journey,
so he is not alone.
Where's Lord Cen?
Your Highness!
I'm sorry.
I'm late.
Not at all!
The auspicious time hasn't passed yet.
Your Highness,
this is Wang Zhao's mother.
Ma'am, please accept my condolences.
This is the State Ceremonial Bureau Chief
court robe bestowed by His Majesty.
It was meant for Lord Wang to wear
upon his return.
Thank you, His Majesty.
Please don't, Ma'am.
What Lord Wang did
will be remembered for generations.
It is our failure
that we cannot publicly praise
his achievements
and record his name in history.
This unmarked grave in the outskirts
is truly an injustice to him.
My husband
died in the war.
Since Zhao was little, he always said
when he grew up,
he wanted to be a good civil official
and come up with many solutions,
and that we can't let people
fight wars anymore.
We must
bring peace and prosperity to the nation.
My son...
You've really done it!
[State Ceremonial Bureau
Wang Zhao]
With mountains and rivers as your hall,
sun and moon as your torch,
and plants and trees as your beams.
Wang...
[Tomb of the nameless]
You're home.
Fate willing, we'll meet in the next life.
I hope then
the world will be at peace,
and we
will serve a wise ruler together.
Soul, return home.
Do not journey east.
The sea storms have not subsided,
a lone boat
cannot cross the vast ocean.
Soul, return home.
Do not wander west.
Desert sands obscure the sun,
dried bones everywhere bring sorrow.
Soul, return home.
Do not go south.
Miasma fills the mountains and forests,
and venomous snakes coil on narrow paths.
Soul, return home.
Do not go to the northern frontier.
Ice and snow
freeze the world,
and the western jackdaw
cries in deep sorrow.
The river waters are deep and clear,
and above the banks, the maple trees grow.
Gaze out across a thousand miles,
as I grieve by the coming of spring.
Soul, return home.
Lament for the south.
That was our only encounter.
What kind of person was Wang Zhao?
What were his life's ambitions?
Did he have someone he loved?
Before dying,
when he gazed towards Great Xia,
[Tomb of the nameless]
what was he thinking?
I know nothing.
And now all that remains
is a journey to the end of the world
and an unmarked grave.
Cen, I brought—
Why won't you listen to me?
It's so cold today.
I'm fine.
Her Highness is here.
Please, no need for formalities.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Your Highness,
you were able to bid
Wang a final farewell,
but I couldn't.
I feel deeply ashamed.
Wang Zhao was
free-spirited and unrestrained.
I imagine he wasn't one
to care about empty formalities.
Your Highness,
I've documented the methods
for cultivating Yan millet
in various field types in this manual.
Thank you.
With proper methods,
it can be cultivated
in forest land,
[Great Xia Agriculture 9]
dry land,
[Sweet potatoes
have high requirements for water]
as well as
[Sweet potatoes prefer warm climates]
paddy fields.
Tu'er has promised that
once he enters Yan State,
he will first transport the seeds here.
The Salt-for-Services Policy is also
being implemented as per usual.
By next spring,
farmers across the country
will be able to plant Yan millet.
That would be perfect.
Besides planting,
transportation and storage
are equally important.
Yan millet is different from other grains.
It needs to be dehulled before storage.
With the right method,
it can be
preserved longer.
Got it.
I'll have
the Ministry of Revenue follow the manual
to inspect granaries across the country.
That will give us a clearer picture
for future disaster relief allocation too.
With that,
there's only one thing left.
After the drought,
we still need
to adjust crop varieties
in different regions.
This way we can prevent future disasters.
[Yan Millet Storage]
However,
this is just
hastily written.
It still needs to be adjusted
during practical implementation.
[Agricultural Distribution Map]
In just a few months,
you've accomplished what would
normally take two to three years.
I feel truly ashamed
for not visiting you sooner.
I am...
I am just a humble subject
of this little use.
Your Highness,
how is His Majesty doing?
Yang feared I would worry
and didn't tell me about Mount Bei before.
Otherwise, I wouldn't have asked Li
to deliver a message
and trouble His Majesty at such a time.
Please don't blame yourself.
This is Physician Xiao from the palace.
His medical skills are unmatched.
His Majesty specifically ordered me
to bring him to treat you.
His Majesty also instructed
that you should rest and recover well.
Next year,
when the Yan millet ripens in the fields,
we'll go see it together.
Sure.
I will
do my best.
This person suffers
from an incurable disease.
He was likely born with this affliction.
Having not done anything until now,
it's beyond medical help.
The man inside
is a benefactor to everyone
in Great Xia.
Please, Physician Xiao,
help him live a little longer—
even if just to see one harvest.
I
will do my best.
[Agricultural Distribution Map]
[Yanwu Reserve Method]
Don't worry, Your Highness.
Since Physician Xiao is staying behind,
he must have a way to save Mr. Cen.
Let's hope so.
[Agricultural Distribution Map 3]
The men I promised to lend you
will be waiting at the border.
Though not many,
they are all elite soldiers.
After this succeeds,
I hope our two nations
will remain allies forever
and never wage war again.
Are you so certain
that I will be the victor?
Of course.
We are the same kind of person.
You were forced
to become the prince of Yan State,
while I
reluctantly took the throne of Great Xia.
Those around us commit all manner of evil,
yet we have become
puppets despised by thousands.
I once almost wanted to give up too.
But then I met someone very important.
She made me understand
what an emperor
should truly do.
As well as what
"heaven gave birth to the people"
and ordained their fate" means.
The way you Xia people speak in circles
is beyond my understanding.
But you are a good emperor.
That's why I must win.
And you must win too.
People in our positions
bear too many responsibilities and hopes.
We cannot be villains.
We may not become friends,
but as long as I remain in Great Yan,
Great Yan and Great Xia
will never become enemies.
Your Highness, someone's approaching.
Hold on tight.
Assassins!
Protect our master!
How insolent!
How dare you defy the law
and attack people here?
After them!
Yes, Your Highness.
My Lady.
It's getting late
and your carriage is damaged.
May I offer you a ride?
May I ask where
your residence is, My Lady?
Your Highness surely knows how to jest.
Please escort me back to the palace.
I happened to be here on business today.
If anything were to happen
to Your Highness,
His Majesty would be furious,
and we wouldn't be able
to bear the consequences.
At this point,
Prince Duan,
just be straightforward
with your mockery.
You're quite favored in the palace now,
unmatched in prominence.
I'm simply happy for you.
My relationship with His Majesty
could hardly be something
you'd be happy about or anticipate.
Unless perhaps
if I were to win his true affection,
I would be of greater value
to Your Highness?
After all, controlling me
would give you better leverage
over His Majesty.
Yu Wanyin.
Do you realize what you're saying?
Xiahou Dan.
The person you said
is very important to you
is the Noble Consort, right?
You must protect her well!
Don't ever let her
become another Shanyi.
Your Majesty!
Your Majesty.
Bad news.
The officials who haven't taken sides
have fallen ill
or died.
He fears your spies
and dares not leave the palace.
He knows you intend to kill us,
yet still sends me, a mere woman, to go
just to demonstrate
that he is a wise ruler.
So you mean
your trip outside the palace
was His Majesty
sending you to win people over for him?
And that his favor toward you
isn't genuine either?
That's quite a statement.
Are you any different?
Since I entered the palace,
everyone claims their heart belongs to me,
but deep down,
isn't it all just manipulation
and exploitation?
You have a point.
But for someone as clever as Wanyin,
couldn't you find a way to refuse him?
Why should I refuse?
This is my best opportunity
to scout an escape route from the palace.
You want to
escape?
Your Majesty!
I've already sent the Imperial Guards
to rescue Her Highness.
-Your Majesty, you can't go!
-She's in danger. I need to save her.
Dan!
-Let go!
-Your Majesty.
Dan!
You don't know martial arts.
If you leave the palace,
I fear I cannot protect you.
What if something happens to her?
Let go!
-Your Majesty.
-Dan!
Dan!
Mr. Bei.
You go.
Only you can save her.
Please, will you go?
If I go,
who will protect you?
But Mr. Bei...
You cannot go!