[How dare you!?]
[Episode 27]
Your Highness,
His Majesty prepared these clothes
beforehand
for us to conceal our identities.
Let me help you change.
When did he start planning all this?
Your Highness,
please eat something.
We need to hit the road soon.
I'm not leaving.
We'll return to the palace
at the crack of dawn.
By His Majesty's decree,
if Your Highness asks to return,
we can use our lives as leverage.
He knows I won't take an innocent life,
so he devised this tactic for me.
Fine.
You are all free now.
Let's part ways here.
Your Highness!
What?
Are you going to tie me up?
Your Highness...
Upon departure,
His Majesty left me with this letter
and asked me to give it to Your Highness
after we escaped danger.
But now I'm taking the liberty
to present it
ahead of schedule.
Your Highness, please read it over
before making a decision.
To my dear wife Wanyin:
My real name is Zhang San.
Laugh if you want.
In the past, I was often asked
why my parents gave me
such an unremarkable name.
But the reality was quite the opposite.
From elementary to middle school,
I was always the first student
whose name was remembered by the teachers.
[Zhang San]
However,
except for this unusual name,
everything about me
actually seemed lackluster.
[SOS]
I was only an average student.
At this point, you might start wondering
why I keep talking about my time
in junior high school.
That's because my life
in the world we're from ended there.
In ninth grade,
when I was fiddling with my phone
in class,
ia pop-up add
sucked me into this book.
It has been 16 years and 8 months
since then.
Come to think of it,
I've been playing the role of Xiahou Dan
for a longer time
than I spent on being Zhang San.
Long live Your Majesty!
In the past two years,
sometimes a doubt would cross my mind—
did that world outside the book
truly exist,
or was it just an illusion
created within my sick brain?
You know what's funny?
When I first arrived,
I felt like I was trapped
in a never-ending nightmare.
But now in retrospect,
I can barely recall the name
of my junior high school.
It all changed when you asked,
"How
are
you?"
I finally realized my past was true,
and that I had
had a real life.
I once had parents,
friends,
and a future.
I'm such a despicable man.
You saved me at that very moment,
yet in the next second,
I devised a plan to deceive you,
to gain your trust,
to become your ally,
and to use your knowledge of the script
for my own benefit.
Only through that
could I achieve victory in the surest way
and retaliate on the Empress Dowager
and Prince Duan.
Don't worry, CEO Dan.
We're in the same boat to begin with.
I'll stick with you till the very end.
In front of you,
I've not only glossed over my past,
but also carefully watched
my manners and speech,
trying to act like
a modern person you're familiar with.
So what if you're the Emperor?
Can you protect her from harm?
That I can do.
Then can you guarantee
that among all the women in the world,
she'll be the only one you want?
That's also easy.
As Zhang San,
loving you seems to be a matter of course.
But as Xiahou Dan,
it's practically insane.
I can't tell
when exactly I fell in love with you.
The only thing I'm sure of
is that I became more afraid
of exposing the truth thereafter.
Wanyin,
believe it or not,
only when I reverted to being
Zhang San from Xiahou Dan in front of you
did it occur to me, little by little,
that how far I had drifted
from my original identity.
You came here too late,
Wanyin.
♪ Tell me ♪
♪ Why so many laments echo in the wind ♪
There isn't a fellow of yours
waiting for you.
You have to stuck with me,
♪ Walk past me ♪
a crazy dying man.
♪ Like an aloof passerby ♪
Those who are drowning
♪ Don't watch me as the rain falls ♪
all wish for a piece of driftwood.
♪ Love burns too hot as it passes ♪
But when they are too far from shore,
they're destined for doom.
♪ Even a lifetime of war
cannot be extinguished ♪
By holding onto the driftwood,
they will only end up dragging it
down into the water too.
You shouldn't let love
♪ Blame me ♪
cloud your judgement.
♪ For the frailty of fate ♪
She's driftwood to me, a drowning man.
I hope I can
♪ Hide me ♪
at least keep your hands free of blood.
♪ With light snow or thick ink ♪
In this living hell,
there should at least be a place
♪ We met in the crowd ♪
for you to have a sound sleep.
♪ There's no mistake in this life ♪
[Taiji Hall]
All I beg for
is to delay facing
♪ I only regret being clumsy in words ♪
the fear and wariness in your eyes.
♪ And shrinking from speaking it out ♪
I wish for nothing
♪ Even when destiny mocked me, hurt me ♪
but to see you always thriving
like burning fire
♪ Destroyed me, or trapped me ♪
and shining like the moon.
♪ I never yielded ♪
We need to play
♪ But why ♪
a game of survival overtime.
I hope you will remain to be the brave
♪ Can't I bear to see
even a single tear in your eyes? ♪
and fearless young lady
who I met in the first place.
Punch the Empress Dowager
♪ But we once fell in love, went wild ♪
and kick Prince Duan!
Even if he were truly a god,
♪ Split up, and lost each other ♪
I would never surrender!
♪ They are
all unforgettable memories to me ♪
Let's get him!
I am not alone on this path!
♪ The first time I met you ♪
Wanyin,
I no longer have a place to call home.
♪ It felt like something suddenly
lit up my soul ♪
But in you, I've found my home.
If you ever fear and waiver,
or need support from a fellow of yours,
I'll gladly play that role
till the day
my life is over.
I beg you, Mr. Bei,
to treat her
as you'd treat me.
Please ensure her safety at all costs.
♪ Blame me ♪
What I didn't expect
was that this day would come so soon.
♪ For the frailty of fate ♪
I will try my best tomorrow.
♪ Hide me ♪
If I succeed,
♪ With light snow or thick ink ♪
the burden on you
will be lighter.
If I fail,
♪ We met in the crowd ♪
do as the final page says.
♪ There's no mistake in this life ♪
You should be able to make an escape
that way.
♪ I only regret being clumsy in words ♪
Then you will have to
♪ And shrinking from speaking it out ♪
tread the road ahead alone.
♪ Even when destiny mocked me, hurt me ♪
♪ Destroyed me, or trapped me ♪
It's going to be a long
♪ I never yielded ♪
and dangerous journey.
♪ But why ♪
Be extra careful.
♪ Can't I bear to see
even a single tear in your eyes? ♪
I'm sorry for not being
a good enough person.
♪ But we once fell in love, went wild ♪
Though I've lied to you many times,
♪ Split up, and lost each other ♪
♪ They are
all unforgettable memories to me ♪
this apology
♪ The first time I met you ♪
is genuine and true.
♪ There was once light ♪
You're the bravest
♪ In my soul ♪
and the most formidable person
I've met in my two lives.
You'll definitely have the last laugh,
fighting your way
to a bright new world.
♪ Even when destiny mocked me, hurt me ♪
By then,
♪ Destroyed me, or trapped me ♪
should you have forgiven me,
♪ I never yielded ♪
just enjoy a hot pot
on holidays and festivals,
♪ But why ♪
♪ Can't I bear to see
even a single tear in your eyes? ♪
as if I were there with you.
♪ But we once fell in love, went wild ♪
From: Zhang San.
♪ Split up, and lost each other ♪
♪ They are
all unforgettable memories to me ♪
♪ The first time I met you ♪
♪ It felt like something suddenly
lit up my soul ♪
Hurry up.
His Majesty suddenly fell ill.
Physicians, please be quick!
Sure, sure.
Got it.
Move faster, physicians.
My leg!
Hurry!
It's not His Majesty.
This...
is not His Majesty.
Say that again, I dare you!
What are you all waiting for?
Come fix my leg right now!
Yes, yes.
Quick!
Your Highness,
Chu Si scouted the gate tower at night
and found the Imperial Guards
to be led by Prince Duan's men.
Now,
the city gate is surrounded
by border troops.
As for where we should go,
it's up to Your Highness.
How are your injuries?
These minor wounds
amount to nothing.
Let's leave the mountain
for an inhabited area.
Or we can't receive news
about the capital.
I'm here to protect Your Highness
by imperial order.
There are many uncertainties now.
The troops from three border regions
arranged by Prince Duan
are closing in on this place
to suppress the Imperial Guards
and help him take the throne.
These troops
are coming from the north, east and south.
I suggest
we find a way out
before they join forces.
Let's head south.
Your Highness,
the Right Army is coming from the south.
We'll head south
to Peiyang.
That's what His Majesty wants.
Clothes were prepared beforehand, right?
Put them on now.
Then we'll set out.
Yes.
Sir,
did you sell fish in town today?
Yes.
The business wasn't good,
so I came back early.
Ma'am,
is your husband home?
Yes, he is.
There's a huge manhunt in town now.
It's said to be complete chaos.
How weird and creepy.
Why would so many people die
during the Empress Dowager's funeral?
Could it be possible that Her Majesty
tried to take people with her
to the nether world
so she could have servants there?
But as I heard, it was
the demonic consort
who murdered the Empress Dowager
and planned to kill
the Emperor too during the funeral.
Is that true?
There are wanted posters for her
at the city gate now.
-Really?
-It can't be fake, can it?
Excuse me.
My sisters and I are heading
to the capital to meet our kin.
We just overheard your conversation.
Is it safe to go
to the capital now?
At a time like this,
even a strong male like me
dare not enter the capital.
Young ladies, I suggest
you make a second plan.
Right now, entry to the capital
is allowed, but exit is denied.
My husband went there to sell fish
early in the day,
and is still trapped within till now.
But this gentleman here just said
the manhunt was for the demonic consort.
Why are even males
forbidden to leave the capital now?
Who knows?
Come on. Let's go home.
Could it be
that Xiahou Dan has escaped?
-Your Highness.
-Your Highness!
Your Highness!
Are you alright?
You're burning up.
We can't go any further.
Her Highness needs to take a rest
somewhere.
I'll check out on that house.
Don't.
Commoners dread strange men most.
And there are so many of us.
Chu Wu, you do it instead.
The two of you,
go hide somewhere.
Take care of Her Highness.
Sure.
Let's go.
Sir,
we plan to visit our relatives
in the capital.
Yet our money was stolen on the way.
Now, the lady of our house is sick.
This is all the money we have on us.
Could you kindly give us some food?
We're all suffering souls.
Come on in.
Let's go.
Thank you.
Why is your wife...
burning that?
To mourn her brother
who lived near Mount Bei.
Yesterday,
while he was taking a peek
at the Empress Dowager's funeral,
unexpectedly,
Prince Duan rose in a rebellion
and caused many deaths.
My wife's brother somehow lost his life.
Prince Duan started a rebellion?
Was it a success?
W-We...
have no idea at all.
He who delivered the bad news to us
just said many people died,
most of which were Imperial Guards.
He didn't know much other than that.
The dead were mostly Imperial Guards.
There was either an internal fight
within them,
or that Prince Duan veiled his armies.
In either case,
CEO Dan must've got in grave danger.
My Lady.
Sir,
we shouldn't bother you
at a time like this,
but the lady of our house is severely ill.
Could you make her a bowl of noodles?
Wait a moment.
My love,
make some noodles now.
Let's go.
Here you are.
Have some noodles.
Thank you.
Take it.
Thanks.
Your Highness,
at least have a bite.
A long journey awaits us.
That's right.
Travel takes physical strength.
Please eat something.
You're right.
I can't fall now.
He's still waiting for me.
You should eat too.
Yes.
Alright, stop crying.
It's bad for your eyes.
I just pity my unfortunate brother.
That heinous Prince Duan
is beneath contempt!
Keep it down.
First,
the Emperor killed the Empress Dowager.
Then, Prince Duan rebelled
and tried to kill the Emperor.
These...
are all royal affairs.
How could we have foreseen those?
It's true I don't know much,
but my brother
told me...
that the Emperor ordered
equal land distribution
and tax reduction.
His Majesty also executed
many corrupt officials!
Isn't it enough to put
these corrupt officials in jail?
Why execute them?
If I am to have the people's support,
I must first give them hope.
Execution is a just desert
for these vile officials.
It gives hope to the people.
Back then,
I thought he was just acting over the top.
Little did I imagine
that after living for 16 years
in this world,
he had already seen
the harsh truths of life.
Sacrificing one person
to ensure others' survival
is sometimes unavoidable.
Don't you forget
they are 2D characters.
I would also remind myself
not to get too emotionally involved.
Do you really think you are a tyrant?
I am a tyrant,
as I have always been.
But the man who claimed to be a tyrant
and to have no regard for others' lives
is actually spending what little
time and life he has
to protect
all those irrelevant 2D characters.
Your Highness,
don't cry.
What's with this lady?
Perhaps she's missing
her family in the capital.
Life hasn't treated us well.
Dear,
let me get you some more soup.
You won't feel homesick on a full stomach.
Thank you, ma'am.
But I can't eat anymore.
Why is your face so red?
She's running a high fever.
We need to get her a physician now.
Honey!
I'm fine.
I'm just tired from the journey.
Could we stay here for the night?
We don't mean to turn you down,
but the authorities have issued a notice
forbidding residents
from housing strangers
overnight.
Although you're not bad people,
ladies,
we common folks
dare not go against the authorities.
How about...
In that case,
we'll take our leave.
Thank you for the noodles.
Thank you.
That...
What's going on?
This...
Well...
Quiet down!
My Lady,
she was just climbing
through the kitchen window
when I caught her in the act.
Sir, ma'am,
take a look. Are these your belongings?
We saved this meat for the New Year.
And that hairpin...
It seems to be Wang's.
Right.
Easy on her, Chu Wu.
She's just a kid.
Yes.
Sir, ma'am,
we bid you farewell.
This thief is yours
to deal with.
Miss,
I wanted to say this earlier,
but this old fool stopped me.
The authorities did issue a notice.
But our village is quite remote,
with the nearest inn
situated over 30 li away.
It's not safe for you three ladies
to stay out there.
Yes.
Things have taken a turn.
They caught a thief for us.
Ladies, if you don't mind,
please stay here for the night.
You may leave tomorrow morning.
Yes.
Good idea.
Thank you.
Come on. Get in the house.
Get up!
Move.
Your Highness.
Your Highness?
When I escorted the thief to the woodshed,
she struggled too hard
and made much noise,
drawing some villagers over.
Our host returned the lost items
to his neighbors.
Now, about five to six households
are aware of our stay.
Your Highness,
if we kill all those people
under the cover of darkness,
we can frame the thief for it
and then cover our tracks.
No.
Let's go.
We should leave
for Peiyang now.
Your Highness,
you're in no condition to go anywhere.
You need a good night's rest.
Chu Yi and Chu Si are keeping watch
on the roof.
We don't have to run
until anyone reports us.
Fine.
I'll sleep a bit more then.
Wake me up in four hours.
Yes, Your Highness.
We found him!
We found him,
Centurion.
Let me see.
It really is him.
Shall we notify the Imperial Guards?
Are you stupid or what?
He was caught by us, the Central Army.
Bring a few men with you
and escort him to His Highness.
Yes!
Take him away!
Move!
CEO Dan,
wait for me.
I'll be with you soon.
Your Highness.
Your Highness!
Your Highness,
there are soldiers here now.
Search carefully!
Move!
-Officer, are you mistaken?
-Darn it!
Officer...
They got to this place so soon.
Move!
Cut the crap. Get a move on!
Be quick!
Search the house!
Confess now!
I don't know anything.
-Walk faster!
-Report the household
with suspicious lodgers
immdiately!
The reward is10 tales of silver!
Officer!
Your Highness!
-We're innocent!
-Your Highness!
Move!
Use the rear door here.
Let's go.
Go there!
And you!
-Hold on.
-Move!
Quickly!
Confess now!
There are soldiers here.
Run for your life.
Don't steal again.
This way.
Check over there!
Go!
Open the door!
Open up!
Who is it?
Open the door!
Now!
Search!
Nobody's here.
Where is she?
Did you tip her off and let her go?
Officer, we're innocent.
Officer,
we don't know who she really is.
She only asked to spend the night here.
-Officer, please spare our lives.
-Don't hurt us.
Guys, go!
Split up and search the village.
Go, guys!
Hurry!
This way.
It's a dead end.
We need to first find an anchor up there
and pull Your Highness up with a rope.
It's too late.
The soldiers will be here soon.
Besides,
how are we supposed
to find a long rope right now?
We'll lure the soldiers away
to buy you as much time as possible.
No.
You escaped by the skin of your teeth.
Going back
is no different than suicide.
Only I am their target.
You should leave.
I can't drag you down with me.
Your Highness...
Just leave.
Don't worry, Your Highness.
We'll use the trees for cover,
take out some soldiers,
and kill ourselves before capture.
We'll make sure no clue is left.
Exactly.
Chu Wu, Chu Qi,
think of a way
to help Her Highness out of danger.
Wait.
What are your names?
We don't have names.
"Chu Yi" and "Chu Si" sound good enough.
Take care, Your Highness.
Do come back alive!
Your Highness,
death is almost certain.
Might as well take a gamble.
Chu Qi, stay alert.
I'll go find an anchor up there.
Your Highness,
let's take a rest over there.
I've been a liability to you all.
Don't beat yourself up, Your Highness.
Who's there?
Your Highness,
that hole's too small
to fit more than two people.
If she tries to harm you, I won't be able
to rescue you in time.
She could've reported me for the reward,
yet she risked coming back for me.
I trust her.
You have great lightness skills.
Hide on the cliff face now.
Be careful.
Got it.
I saw them heading to the woods.
Should we keep looking?
Of course we should.
If we catch her,
we'll receive a thousand taels of silver
and be set for life.
That woman's quite good at hiding.
How many villages have we searched?
I don't even get to enjoy the New Year.
Don't be afraid.
That's why she's called a demonic consort.
The higher-ups
told us to catch her,
be she alive or dead.
If she falls into our hands,
let's take her to bed
like the Emperor did!
-Let's go!
-Go!
Check over there!
Go, guys!
You're unable to speak?
Now I understand
why you steal for a living.
Xiahou Dan.
Calling my name already, huh?
"Being ill,
the late Emperor felt
death was drawing near.
This edict was therefore made
to pass the throne to the Crown Prince.
But given the latter's minority,
Prince Duan is vested
the power to govern as regent."
Honorary titles
are mere vanities.
Pick whatever you like, Your Majesty.
All is fine by me.
Why don't you dress up
as the Empress Dowager
in women's clothes?
Xiahou Dan!
I forgot it.
You're scared of her.
What did you just say?
You knew clearly from the beginning
who harmed your mother
and you.
But you had no choice
but to turn a blind eye
and a deaf ear to the truth.
You decided to vent all your anger
on an innocent person.
Why?
Because you were too weak.
You had to direct your hatred to someone,
or you couldn't have lived.
So,
you picked a soft target—
a headache sufferer,
and a mere puppet.
Luck was the entire reason
that he ascended to the throne.
Given that, you, Xiahou Bo,
feel the urge to tell the world
that you,
Prince Duan,
are better than him in every way,
and that only you are
meant to be the ruler.
As a defeated loser
behind bars,
you're still talking tough.
You're saying all this to provoke me,
aren't you?
It won't work, Xiahou Dan.
Stop struggling.
I've hit a nerve with you, right?
Shut up!
Your Highness,
I'll finish him.
No need.
Make sure you rough the late Emperor up.
Remember
to spare his right hand, though.
He needs it to write his final edict.
Yang, I...
I...
T-T-This is inappropriate.
Er Lan, well, I...
I...
I didn't mean to intrude.
I thought I entered Yang's room.
This room is more spacious,
making it easier to attend to Cen.
So I swapped rooms with Yang this morning.
Cen...
Cen has arrived?
Not yet.
Yang has set off to receive him.
Li, do you ever consider
stop standing in the cold wind
by the door?
We've been through life and death
together.
Just forego the formalities.
Were you just saying
you had news about His Majesty?
Yes.
I waited at the palace gate all morning,
but still couldn't get in.
Nonetheless, a young eunuch
guarding the gate said
Prince Duan summoned all ministers
to attend court tomorrow morning.
He's just a prince.
What right does he have to do that?
I actually think it's a good thing.
Hell no!
My apologies, Er Lan.
I...
I've got used to it.
I keep forgetting that you are...
In fact, I somewhat miss the time
when you treated me like a man.
We voiced our opinions
and argued till we were red in the face,
with the one and only focus
on offering counsel to His Majesty.
But now,
Wang is gone.
Her Highness is missing.
His Majesty's fate is unknown.
Given that,
though this is not a fair request,
I still have to ask you, Li,
to continue to conceal my identity
for a while.
Just treat me the same as before.
Sure.
I got it.
I'll try my best.
It has been
three days since the Mount Bei incident.
The city gate is sealed,
and so is the palace gate.
We have no access to any news.
So, our only chance lies in
tomorrow's morning court session.
Yes.
You m-made a good point.
But you're injured now, Er Lan.
You shouldn't risk attending court
tomorrow.
Just leave it to me and Yang.
What is with you, Li?
After just promising to keep my secret,
you're giving it away now?
I-I'm not.
I haven't disclosed it to anyone...
If I were a man,
would I make a fuss
over a minor injury like this?
Yes.
Right.
Although you
and Her Highness
are women,
you two are incredibly formidable.
I admire both of you.
I tip my hat to you.
Who am I to be compared with Her Highness?
I wonder
where Her Highness is right now.
Your Highness!
Your Highness.
Your Highness,
we made it back alive.
Chu Yi, Chu Si.
Why are you dressed as Imperial Guards?
That gave me quite a fright!
You're injured?
If I hadn't knocked out
two Imperial Guards in the chaos
and put on their armor,
he would've lost his arm.
Could those lousy fighters have wounded me
if I hadn't took
that blade for you?
You...
Cut it out.
What's the situation like?
Not good.
People are searching everywhere
for Her Highness.
We absolutely cannot take the main roads.
But the distance between here
and Peiyang is over 500 li.
What route can we take
if not the main roads?
After living in the palace for so long,
we're not familiar with the roads outside.
Do you mean...
you can be our guide?
You know the way?
Terrific.
But...
you might get in danger
for sticking with us.
Will you still join us?
You want payment?
Chu Wu,
give her some food.
By the way,
I don't know your name yet.
You don't have a name?
Why do none of you
have names?
Well...
How about I give you a name?
Let me think...
We'll call you
"Flower."
What do you think?