[How dare you!?]
[Episode 10]
Which company are you the CEO of?
What does this company do?
When was it listed?
What was its market cap
before you came here?
I should just tell her everything.
Who exactly are you?
But if I tell the whole truth,
that fragile bit of trust and closeness
she has with me
will probably vanish.
Between letting her doubt me
and breaking her heart,
I would rather let her keep doubting.
I don't remember.
If you don't want to tell me,
I won't ask again.
Your Highness!
Wake up! Wake up!
Your Highness,
stop sleeping.
The Empress Dowager
is here to check your homework.
What the hell?
What am I wearing?
How did I wake up here?
Where am I?
I think earlier
I was sneaking my phone in math class
and accidentally clicked
on a cheesy web novel
called...
Oh right.
It's called "Transmigrated:
The Devil's Beloved Consort"!
The Empress Dowager has arrived!
Your Majesty.
How is the Crown Prince's study today?
Your Majesty,
today the Crown Prince studied
the Thousand Character Classic
and learned about astronomy, geography,
and social customs.
-Devil's Favorite Concubine?
-He is a quick and eager learner
-Favorite Consort?
-and has already
grasped much of the material.
So it really is a story
set in an imperial palace.
It's just that...
Oh no.
How do I get back?
It hurts so much?
Here,
let me massage it for you.
Here.
Don't touch me, Mr. Bei.
Why did it flare up all of a sudden?
It might be a brain tumor.
Impossible.
I checked your pulse.
You don't have that.
I need a CT scan.
Wh-What T?
Never mind.
Mr. Bei.
I want sweet porridge.
Okay.
I'll go make some right now.
Just wait.
Your Majesty, Mr. Bai sent another letter,
urging you to get rid of
the demonic consort as soon as possible.
She is not a demonic consort!
No need to reply to that!
Yes.
Your Highness,
His Majesty didn't summon you today.
Is it appropriate for us
to go there directly?
It's precisely because he didn't summon me
that I must go.
Why?
I don't understand.
I, Xie Yong'er, am the chosen one.
In this world, I was supposed to
have everything go my way.
But I've been in the palace for so long.
Not only have I accomplished nothing,
but I have also been treated
like an outcast.
An outcast?
Now, although he says he believes me,
he hasn't summoned me
to attend him even once since then.
Don't you think something's off?
So, you mean...
Ling, remember,
in this harem,
one careless step can cost you your life.
Tonight,
I must see His Majesty
and get to the bottom of this.
[Yongyan Hall]
Eunuch An, I need to see His Majesty.
Please let His Majesty know.
Your Highness,
His Majesty's headache has flared up.
It's not convenient for him to see anyone.
Eunuch An,
if His Majesty is unwell,
then all the more reason for me
to go in and attend him.
Your Highness, please go back.
His Majesty is seeing no one tonight.
Please,
don't make things difficult for me.
[Yongyan Hall]
Having everything go my way?
Is this how you treat the chosen one?
Why is she here?
And she looks even more miserable than me.
Oh right.
She's fallen out of favor
with His Majesty.
Then let me make things
even worse for you.
Go back first, Ling.
Okay.
Sister, why are you here alone?
Are you enjoying the rain?
Yong'er?
Why are you here?
I just went to see His Majesty,
but I didn't even get through the door.
It seems his headache flared up
and he's not feeling well.
His Majesty is ill?
You didn't know?
Sister.
I know you and His Majesty are in love.
I think this is the perfect time
for you two to patch things up.
Why don't you give it a try?
Since that's the case,
I'll go take a look.
Thank you for coming
to tell me about this.
Go now.
His Majesty said he's seeing no one.
You're just going to hit a wall.
[Yongyan Hall]
Dan.
Dan?
Wanyin is here.
The porridge is ready.
Thanks, Mr. Bei.
Well...
You two talk.
Let me feed you.
Let's talk.
There's no rush.
You should rest now.
You guessed right.
I'm not actually a CEO.
Before I came here,
I was a third-rate actor.
I played bit parts for years
and never made it big.
If that's all,
why did you lie to me?
I didn't mean to lie to you.
You first guessed that I was a CEO.
You're not one of those
legendary alpha bosses, are you?
I just went along with it.
Why did you do that?
I...
have always had bad luck,
and I don't seem
to have any real talent either.
I thought I would die here.
Then,
you showed up,
like a savior from the heavens,
holding the script
and determined to win.
When I looked at you,
I finally felt
that there might still be hope for me.
You're a little...
different from how I imagined.
I thought
you were carrying some deep, dark secret.
Now you know.
I don't have much of a chance.
Even if Prince Duan is a 2D character,
he's 100 times more capable than me.
So that promise
still stands.
If you want to leave,
I completely understand.
I won't stop you.
Even if you don't act pitiful,
I won't leave.
You need to get better soon.
Our future plans
still need your acting skills.
Why are your clothes all wet?
I just got caught in a bit of rain.
I'll go back and change.
Why don't you
take a hot bath here?
If you catch a cold,
who's going to take care of me,
the patient?
[Xiao Tiancai]
Which palace are you from?
Don't stand in this heavy rain.
Go into the flower house and take shelter.
What are you waiting for? Go on in.
Hurry up.
Wait until the rain lets up
before you head back.
Take this umbrella.
Don't get caught in the rain again.
If you catch a cold,
at best you'll get a fever,
and at worst it could affect
your internal organs.
That would be real trouble.
This is mugwort.
Take it back and smoke this spot,
the Fengchi point.
It helps dispel cold and dampness.
It's best not to get sick.
What is this?
This is called danggui.
It grows along the northwestern border.
Some time ago,
the Imperial Hospital wanted
to compile a catalog of medicinal herbs
and study their effects
and growing conditions,
so they had people bring back
a few plants from the northwest
and planted them here.
They were fresh and lovely at first
and grew a lot in just 3 days.
But for some reason,
after they bloomed, they began to wither.
The same species can be very different
in different environments.
The northwest is cold.
If you plant it here,
it surely won't survive.
That's not entirely true.
Plants are like people.
They have strong vitality
and will try hard
to adapt to different environments.
Dandelions take root wherever they land.
Wild grass grows back stronger
after burning.
Sometimes the price of survival
is not being as lush as before,
or bearing fewer fruits,
but that's the law of survival.
Look at that.
Lilyturf.
It's also known as the "immortal herb."
Whether it's dry or damp,
warm or cold,
it survives just fine.
That's easy for you to say.
With a flick of your fingers,
you decide whether it lives or dies.
But has anyone ever asked
if it was willing?
Maybe death is its way of protesting.
It... it's just a plant.
Miss, can you tell me
how you know whether it's willing or not?
I just feel
it shouldn't have been taken away
from home
to grow
in this completely unfamiliar place
and wither here.
What did it do wrong?
Why should it go through all this?
You have a soft heart.
It pains me deeply
that they didn't survive.
I come every day
to mist them and cool them down.
I even prepare ice every day
to recreate a cold,
damp environment for them.
Though they suffer greatly,
they aren't alone,
nor are they facing all this
by themselves.
If,
as you say,
they truly
have thoughts of their own,
then seeing someone watch over them
and make an effort for them
might give them a bit more will
to keep going.
Even a herb has someone watching over it,
going through hardships together.
Yet I have always been alone.
Are you feeling better?
I ate something,
and I'm better now.
Well,
if there's nothing else,
I'll go back now.
♪ A letter, a line of words ♪
♪ Picking up the pen again and again ♪
What's wrong?
♪ A cup of tea, a glass of wine ♪
Is your head hurting again?
♪ Drinking alone, hard to get drunk ♪
It's starting to hurt again.
♪ Words unspoken ♪
Why don't you stay?
♪ Shyness unhidden ♪
Your hair is still wet,
♪ Walking down a street together ♪
and it's raining outside.
♪ Shoulder to shoulder ♪
♪ Raising my head, lowering my eyes ♪
But...
But I'm supposed to be playing
the out-of-favor role right now.
♪ Blushing slightly ♪
♪ A face flushed red at first sight ♪
It wouldn't be appropriate for me to stay.
Then let's just treat it
♪ A smile like a flower in my heart ♪
as a day off.
Forget about the tyrant
and the demonic consort.
♪ Whose longing lingers day and night? ♪
Forget about Prince Duan
and the Empress Dowager.
♪ Piling up stories
and countless thoughts ♪
Just for one day.
♪ Walking through once, taking a glance ♪
Okay?
♪ All lingering and wandering ♪
♪ How many rains, how many winds? ♪
♪ Looking back, it's all like smoke ♪
♪ Watching the hazy world ♪
♪ Who still guards that yearning? ♪
♪ Still unchanged ♪
♪ Even if months and years
pass in a blink ♪
♪ One thought for a lifetime ♪
♪ Waiting for someone to appear ♪
Then let's stop thinking about anything
and have a good sleep.
♪ Whose longing lingers day and night? ♪
♪ Piling up stories
and countless thoughts ♪
♪ Walking through once, taking a glance ♪
♪ All lingering and wandering ♪
♪ How many rains, how many winds? ♪
♪ Looking back, it's all like smoke ♪
♪ Watching the hazy world ♪
♪ Who still guards that yearning? ♪
Goodnight.
♪ Still unchanged ♪
♪ Even if months and years
pass in a blink ♪
♪ One thought for a lifetime ♪
♪ Waiting for someone to appear ♪
That fire in the library last time
was terrifying.
Although it's being renovated now,
safety isn't guaranteed.
If you ask me,
My Lady, you shouldn't have come here.
It's fine.
Isn't Madam Bei at the door?
It's absolutely safe.
The history of Yan State is so convoluted.
And it has nothing to do with us.
My Lady,
be careful not to strain your eyes.
It's fine.
My eyesight is excellent.
My Lady, are you even listening to me?
Take a break.
Look at the scenery.
My Lady, look.
The hydrangeas in the field
are blooming beautifully.
What's...
going on?
-Beautiful, right?
-SOS?
It's just that the arrangement
looks a bit strange.
Mei.
Do you know
who planted these flowers?
I don't know.
Put the book back.
I'll go take a look.
Wanyin!
Wan...
Mei!
Get the umbrella!
Go!
[SOS]
This...
Could this be planted by a transmigrator?
In Devil's Favorite Concubine,
there is absolutely no such plot.
Could it be that before we came,
there were others like us?
If it really was left by a transmigrator,
there must be other clues nearby.
[SOS]
Noble Consort？
The rain is so heavy today.
Why aren't you using an umbrella?
Crown Prince?
Why are you out here alone?
Your Highness.
I'm here to enjoy the flowers.
Could he also be...
Crown Prince.
In front of my house are two trees.
One is a date tree.
What is the other one?
"Before my bed, the moonlight glows."
Do you know the next line?
-"It looks like frost..."
-Your Highness!
Your Highness!
Greetings, Your Highness.
Your Highness,
I've been looking everywhere for you.
The Empress Dowager is waiting for you.
Your Highness,
I will take His Highness back
to his palace now.
CEO Dan!
Guess what I found in the library.
What?
SOS.
SOS?
Yeah.
That distress signal.
I had always been on the 2nd floor before.
Today, I went up to the 3rd floor
to look for books about Yan State.
Through an inconspicuous window,
I happened
to catch sight of an open space
beneath the library.
Someone had planted flowers
spelling out a huge SOS.
So there must be
another transmigrator here
like us.
Could it have been Xie Yong'er?
That's what I thought at first.
But everything she says and does
is written in the book.
There's not a word about asking for help.
It must be someone else.
We've been here for so long.
If there had been anyone strange,
we would have noticed long ago.
What if that person
has been trying hard to hide themselves?
They don't know who to trust,
so they have to use this
subtle way to call for help.
Exactly.
I need to find out
who planted this flower field.
Wait.
Don't rush.
You think it's an SOS signal.
Maybe
the person who planted it
intended it to be
"Two Dragons Playing with a Pearl."
I know.
But what if
there really is someone calling for help?
Just like I was back then.
If I hadn't met you,
I would be so scared struggling alone
in this other world.
Use your imagination.
If we really find that person,
we can play poker.
Do you think
this person is a man or a woman?
Would they like hot pot?
Would they become friends with us?
What's wrong?
I asked around.
They all said
in recent years,
no one has touched that flower field.
See?
I told you.
You were overthinking it.
From a distance,
it really looked like
a miraculous SOS signal.
Then here comes the problem.
These flowers have just started blooming,
and will bloom for a long time.
What if Xie Yong'er passes by one day,
and just like you,
sees the
"Two Dragons Playing with a Pearl"
as an SOS signal?
Guess
what she would think.
She'd also suspect
there's one of her kind nearby.
She might have a sudden epiphany
and suspect us.
Then...
Then we can't keep this field.
Can we find an excuse to remove it?
Please.
Do I need an excuse
for renovating a garden?
What?
Just call it my wild imagination.
I'm still thinking,
what if there really was someone
like us who went through
so much trouble planting all those flowers
to ask for help,
only to get no response at all
and even have the flowers pulled out.
Should we bury something there instead?
Like...
a note or something?
There's a risk Xie Yong'er might find it.
True.
Anyway, the person who planted them
doesn't need them anymore.
What?
I said,
you look so pretty today.
[Promoting Yan millet]
[Commoners: Food]
[Ministry of Revenue: Money]
[Empress Dowager: Power
[Prince Duan: Opposition]
Still thinking about Li Yunxi's method?
I thought he explained it pretty clearly.
There's nothing wrong
with the method itself.
What worries me
is whether it can actually be carried out.
What do you mean?
Look,
back when I was an editor,
for a project to launch smoothly,
it had to satisfy several groups' needs.
The producers want to save money,
the screenwriters want credit,
the directors want artistic freedom,
and the platforms want ratings.
Different positions, different demands.
Only when everyone's needs are met
could the project move forward.
Go on.
So, by the same logic,
to promote the planting of Yan millet,
we have to satisfy several groups at once.
You mean...
The Empress Dowager wants power,
[Empress Dowager: Power]
[Dignity]
so the decree can't come from me.
[Ministry of Revenue: Money]
[Chen Danian]
The Ministry of Revenue has no money,
so the funds must come from elsewhere.
[Commoners: Food][Why plant?]
Prince Duan opposes me,
so I can't be the one benefiting.
Not bad, CEO Dan.
You catch on fast.
This is a place where the finest energies
of heaven and earth converge,
where yin and yang merge.
The dragon veins, surrounding hills,
and water are all perfectly aligned.
The terrain,
momentum,
feng shui, and qi
all are auspicious.
This is...
In other words,
this is the best place
to build a mausoleum?
Exactly.
The Empress Dowager has been
working tirelessly for the state.
Your Majesty,
your wish to build a mausoleum for her
is truly moving.
For many years,
we've been unable to find a suitable site.
Now that the Empress Dowager's birthday
is approaching,
the Imperial Observatory
has identified Mount Bei
as an auspicious location.
I am deeply gratified.
Ministry of Revenue.
Is there enough money?
Well...
Your Majesty,
could you please tell me why?
Did I do something wrong?
Are my eyes playing tricks on me,
or am I seeing a ghost?
Aren't you already...
Your Majesty.
The f-former...
The former Minister of Revenue was my...
twin brother.
It seems the position
of Minister of Revenue
is run by your family.
No, Your Majesty.
It's not like that.
It's just that...
everyone in our Chen family
is willing to serve Great Xia
to our last breath, Your Majesty.
Don't panic.
I won't punish people collectively.
As long as you raise the funds to build
the Empress Dowager's
mausoleum,
I will even reward you.
Forgive me, Your Majesty.
Allow me to report!
Speak.
The mausoleum project is massive,
but the treasury is tight at the moment.
Unless...
Unless what?
We raise taxes!
Raise taxes?
How can we do that?
Indeed.
The Ministry of Revenue
proposes raising taxes again this year.
What do you all think?
Well...
Since none of you has reached a decision,
stay here
and discuss it until you reach
a conclusion before the court ends.
Your Majesty.
I heard
that His Majesty
plans to build a mausoleum
at Mount Bei for you as a birthday gift.
I'm both happy and helpless.
How so?
I'm happy
because His Majesty and Your Majesty
share such a deep mother-son bond.
It makes everyone envious.
And the helpless part?
I am helpless because...
the gift from His Majesty is so grand
that anything we give
will seem insignificant.
Flatterer.
Building a mausoleum
wastes money and manpower.
Those who know
see it's the emperor's filial devotion
acting on his own.
Those who don't
might think I
do not care about the people.
The Ministry of Revenue is short on money.
Let's put
this matter aside for now.
Your words are mistaken, Your Majesty.
In every dynasty,
the Empress Dowager's mausoleum
isn't just a tomb—
it represents the royal prestige
and is the highest honor
for women of the harem.
Our Great Xia thrives
and the people prosper
thanks to Your Majesty's
careful management.
Do you
want to be outshone
by the previous Empress Dowager?
You certainly are bold.
I only said
what others want to say but dare not.
The construction of the mausoleum
is known by the whole court.
Stopping it now
would be truly disgraceful.
Your Majesty,
we absolutely can't do this.
Really?
Yes.
Yes, indeed.
Right.
Then tell me,
how should this mausoleum be built?
I...
Make way!
Irrelevant persons, stand back!
Your Majesty!
What are you doing?
Your Majesty! I demand to see you!
Your Majesty!
How dare you!
Startling His Majesty
is a capital offense!
I'm dying anyway!
Your Majesty!
Please show mercy!
Otherwise, I will die
with my grievances unresolved!
-Drag him away now!
-Your Majesty!
-Hurry!
Your Majesty!
Stop!
Wait.
Let him go.
Let him go!
I am here. If you have any grievance,
tell me everything in detail.
Your Majesty,
please show mercy
and leave us a way to live.
How is there no way to live?
Your Majesty,
you live in luxury within the palace.
Do you know what kind of life
the common people are living?
A single vegetable like this
sells only for one coin,
but taxes take up more than half of it.
After deducting costs,
the actual profit
is less than a tenth.
All my fellow villagers
toil from
dawn to dusk.
Yet after all that labor,
the grain left at year's end
is only enough to stave off hunger.
My...
My younger brother and sister
were born into a year of poor harvest
and starved to death.
They didn't even get the chance
to see this world.
These lines...
My younger brother and sister
were born into
a year of poor harvest
and starved to death.
Your Majesty,
my family
is already struggling to survive.
Now that taxes are rising again,
I fear even my elderly parents
won't be able to survive.
This is driving the common people
to a dead end!
What are you doing?
The mood is just right.
Why did you stand up?
They are driving us to our deaths!
Yes, Your Majesty!
No more tax increases!
Your Majesty, no more tax increases!
How can this be?
Bring the Minister of Revenue to me
at once!
Yes, Your Majesty!
Your Majesty, Chen Danian,
the Minister of Revenue, is here.
Your Majesty!
I am innocent!
Why is the Ministry of Revenue
raising taxes again?
Well...
Didn't Your Majesty want to build
the Empress Dowager's...
Yes.
It was me.
I thought that
building the Empress Dowager's mausoleum
must not be done carelessly,
but...
but there weren't enough funds.
So...
No money?
And with no money, you think you can
take our lives as payment?
Let go!
In that case,
our family has no choice
but to cut off our heads
and offer a bowl of hot blood
to Your Majesty!
"The ruler relies on the state,
and the state relies on the people."
Such a simple truth,
and yet you, the Minister of Revenue,
don't understand it?
I want to ask you,
why are the funds for the mausoleum
not taken from the state treasury?
Well...
I was wrong.
I was wrong!
Take me to the state treasury!
Your Majesty, you cannot go there!
Today, I must...
I must give an explanation
to the people of Great Xia!
Your Majesty is wise!
What is it?
Why the panic?
The Emperor publicly berated
the Minister of Revenue
over the tax increase.
Now he's escorting him
to the Ministry's treasury.
He has an ulterior motive.
I knew
building the mausoleum wasn't that simple.
It seems our Emperor
is going after the Empress Dowager.
Since they're putting each other
over the fire,
I might as well
add fuel to the flames.
Zhang San's Diary.
Are there other transmigrators like me?
Wait.
"Yuanfang,
what do you think?"
My name is not Yuanfang.
"I simply cannot do it!"
I...
I am just a servant!
"Imperial Jade Wine.
180 for a cup."
Spare me, Your Highness!
You may go.
Yes.
Where is the female lead
who transmigrated into this book?
I have to find a way
to leave a noticeable mark.
One that only my kind would notice.