Do you know what other relief centers did?
Either they exploited the local businessmen,
or used grassroots or bark as food materials instead.
And suppressed by their military force,
the victims dared not to say anything.
My father was the most foolish,
visiting wealthy locals one by one,
But he couldn't make threats,
so he reaped very little.
So he put up all his own assets,
even the fields and mansion Your Majesty granted him,
and he sold them all!
He even sold
the homestead in his hometown!
That was a homestead passed down generation to generation!
When the victims aired their grief,
my father wouldn't use military force.
He was afraid to harm those bare-handed victims.
But they almost beat him to death!
Because the victims’ violence angered the soldiers,
causing the casualty later.
It’s not that he is incompetent.
He couldn't bear it, he just couldn't.
I know.
Your Majesty.
I know you are in a difficult position,
so I don't dare to ask for forgiveness.
But on the account of his devotion,
please spare his life.
Your Majesty.
I have only begged you once in this life.
Spare him. Please!
Your Majesty.
I'm begging you.
Alright.
I
won't kill him.
Rise.
-Your Highness. - Empress.
Prince He of the First Rank!
May I talk to you?
Your Highness! You are not recovered yet!
Don’t stand in the wind.
I know you have with you the royal decree
to go and spare my father.
Empress.
I’m useless.
I couldn't wash away Lord Naerbu's wrongful accusation.
No.
You have tried everything you can to look for evidence.
And you had many people offended because of my father’s incident.
I’ll remember your kindness.
It’s my pleasure to do something for you.
I need you to do me another favor.
Zhen'er.
This is?
My father will be exiled to Ningguta which is a bitter cold place.
I prepared clothing and medicine for him.
His leg is injured.
There will not be any good doctor on the way.
And he has no time to nurse the injury.
I just hope these medicines can come to use.
Empress, don’t worry.
I will surely bring these to him.
Is there anything else
you'd like to tell Lord Naerbu?
Tell him that I feel so sorry
that I can't send him off personally.
Please let him take good care!
Yes.
Your Highness, let's return.
Zhen'er.
Do you think the clothing we prepared for Father
will be thick enough?
Your Highness,
you prepared leather and fur for winter.
Of course they are thick enough
But Ningguta is really cold.
Very cold.
Open up.
Lord Naerbu.
Lord. His Majesty spared you from death
and changed it to exile.
Hurry and thank the grace!
Lord?
My decree was late.
I already sent an order
to prepare a good funeral.
If you want to arrange it personally,
I can agree to it too.
Did Your Majesty kill my father?
No.
Then it was Empress Dowager's doing.
Empress.
Your father
Committed suicide!
My father was loyal and foolish.
But he was a human and he cherished his life.
In order to live,
he once laid down his pride to come beg me.
Now he was clearly falsely accused.
why would he
commit suicide?
Empress,
he has already left.
There's no point in pursuing this.
Your Majesty.
My father was wronged and became
the most corrupted official in everyone's eyes.
In the prison, he committed suicide.
Should his daughter tolerate this
without saying anything?
You clearly knew that he wasn't corrupted
and used all he had to make up for the deficit.
In the end, he still needed to pay with his life.
He worked hard being a great leader
for more than twenty years.
In the end, he lost his reputation
and was cursed by everyone.
Is there still justice in this world?
Empress,
I know that you are very sad.
You can blame and hate me
but not Empress Dowager.
Your Majesty,
do you think that Empress Dowager is unselfish?
Empress.
No matter how sad you are,
you shouldn't be rude to Empress Dowager.
Empress Dowager’s nephew also participated in the corruption.
Before my father was arrested,
Empress Dowager's elder brother and his wife came to the palace to plead for clemency.
Once this is investigated,
it will implicate the family of Empress Dowager.
Hence, Empress Dowager, without any hesitation,
made my father a sacrificial lamb!
Are you done?
Your Highness, don't say anymore.
Will His Majesty dare listen to
what I’m going to say?
At this point,
what else wouldn’t I dare listen to?
Your Majesty.
The palace officials are mediocre, incompetent, greedy and cunning.
It's the same in the seemingly lovely harem.
Everyone's acting,
chanting out a tune of a world in prosper with justice and clarity,
and ganging up to lie to you and trick you.
Even if you are diligent and hard-working,
you still can't protect your subject who is falsely accused.
And you can't eliminate all those greedy corrupted officials.
Li Yu.
The Empress is sick.
Ask the Imperial Doctor to treat her.
Yes.
His Majesty doesn't dare to listen anymore?
Your Highness, I'm begging you. Stop talking!
Empress.
The world is far from being satisfactory.
You are overly-aggrieved today.
I can forgive you this time.
If you speak and do anything recklessly again,
I will not spare you.
Chamberlain Li,
the Empress isn't ill.
Nonsense.
The Empress contracted hysteria.
She's already started raving, how is she not ill?
But I took her pulse.
She's really very lucid.
If she were fine,
how would she contradict and offend His Majesty?
His Majesty feels guilty
so he pardoned her.
So I should treat it as hysteria?
Yes, do that!
Your Highness,
in order to investigate this case,
you haven't slept in days.
Now that It’s resolved,
you should go home and take a rest.
Resolved? Clearly they killed him because
they were afraid that the secret would be revealed.
The person is gone.
There’s no point to reinvestigate the case.
Your Highness should take care.
It was not your business in the first place anyway.
Zhen'er. What are you doing here?
Prince He of the First Rank.
I am…
I am heading to Imperial Household Department to retrieve something.
You are always tending closely to the Empress.
How come you were sent to run errands?
Prince He,
I really am going to Imperial Household Department
according to the Empress’s order.
Please let me through.
Prince. The palace gates will be locked soon.
Let's leave now.
Wait for me at Gate of Divine Prowess.
I still have things to do.
Your Highness? Your Highness?
Wait! Your Highness!
Prince, what are you doing?
What happened to the Empress?
Tell me!
You don’t have to pretend in front of me!
Prince He, Her Highness the Empress disappeared.
I’ve looked all over Palace of Receiving Celestial Favor and Imperial Garden.
But no sign of her!
I dare not tell others.
So I can only search alone.
Let's split and look for her.
We must find the Empress
before others notice.
Your Highness!
You're here.
What are you doing?
Come down now.
Do you think
I’d jump off from here?
Empress.
Come down now.
What are you trying to do?
I’ve spent the whole day here,
looking at the scenery afar.
Suddenly I wanted to know how Fuca Rongyin
felt when she stood up here that day.
So I came here to experience it.
Are you really crazy?
Fuca Rongyin and I
entered the mansion in succession.
She was the Primary Consort who was gentle and tender,
and I was the Secondary Consort who was prudent and cautious.
We had a lot in common,
but we were also so different.
We both
gave our true love to our husband.
But she jumped off from here,
while I became the Empress on high!
It was so long ago.
Why do you mention it again?
You're not Fuca Rongyin.
Yes, I am not Fuca Rongyin.
Because even if I stand here,
I never think of jumping off from here.
Do you know why?
Because I can’t accept it!
I thought I was in charge of the Imperial Harem.
I was the head of the country,
so I’d never be bullied by anybody,
and I’d never have to be cautious again! But I was wrong!
The then Consort Xian couldn't protect her mother and younger brother,
the current Empress still couldn't protect her father!
Because my power is too limited.
Too limited!
No. It’s not true!
It's because
you trust and admire His Majesty.
You want to be a good Empress.
Your Highness.
Please come down!
Your Highness the Empress.
My heart is straight toward my lord,
to the top of the clouds brushing away the blue sky.
It's time to return.
Empress.
If you need my help,
just let me know.
I want to do something for you.
Respectfully greeting Your Majesty.
How is the Empress?
Her highness was in deep sorrow upon losing her father
and accidentally offended Your Majesty.
She feels very sorry about that.
If she knows Your Majesty is here, she'll be so happy.
Allow me to inform her of your visit.
No need.
Take good care of the Empress.
Your Highness the Empress.
His Majesty didn't pursue your loss of composure.
Why are you still being so cold?
Don't worry.
His Majesty won't blame me.
Why?
Because he feels guilty.
Your Highness.
You think I really went mad?
Even if the entire world goes mad,
I will still be very lucid.
If I still acted like nothing happened
after losing my father.
Then do I still have a heart?
Your Highness, you mean..?
A disciplined person
can only win His Majesty’s heart
by occasional misconduct.
As long as His Majesty remembers my grievance
and my frustrated fury,
the entire Imperial Harem will remember too.
Empress,
His Majesty had Chamberlain Li send this.
Put it down.
Your Highness.
Emperor Chongzhen and Empress Zhou had a conflict once.
Empress Zhou went on a hunger strike and disobeyed.
So Emperor Chongzhen sent an old leather mattress to her.
The two thus reconciled.
Now His Majesty sent these old clothes to me
to tell me
that he remembers my grievance,
and he cares about me.
Then you sent me to go see Prince He?
Prince He
appears to be licentious and unruly. But in actuality, he is passionate and righteous.
If I want to subdue him,
I need to at least put some thought into it.
Your Highness.
Are you really not sad?
At this point, grief won’t do anything.
I’d rather think about how to take advantage of this incident
to benefit myself the most.
Alright. You may leave now.
Greetings to Mother Ling. May you have peace and longevity.
Rise.
In a blink of eye,
the Fifth Prince has grown up.
Yongqi.
When you were first born, you were golden yellow from head to toe.
Everyone thought you were a monster.
Thanks to your Mother Ling who protected you with her life,
or you might not even be alive today.
Thank you, Mother Ling, for saving me.
When I grow up,
I will surely be filial to you.
He’s such a young kid,
yet speaks like an adult.
Rise!
Rise, please!
Come here.
Mother Ling, does it hurt a lot?
Yes, it hurts a lot. But I can bear it.
When my Mother got hurt before,
she was clearly in so much pain that her eyes were red.
But she told me it didn't hurt.
Mother Ling, you are different than my Mother.
Yongqi.
Don't talk nonsense.
Fifth Prince.
If she clearly got hurt but she forced herself to endure,
it's because your mother was worried about you.
Your mother
regards you as the most precious treasure in the world.
In the future, you must be very filial to her.
I will be filial to Mother,
but can I be filial to you too?
My master will have her own child to be filial to her in the future.
We don't need to trouble you, Fifth Prince.
Mingyu, watch your mouth?
Last night, I kept hearing strange noises.
I was wondering
how come the yellow weasel is already here when it’s not New Year’s yet.
Mingyu.
Mingyu’s temper
hasn’t changed at all
over the years.
Who's laughing?
What’s going on?
Why are you so angry?
Just a traitor!
Why should we be nice to her?
Who is a traitor?
Yingluo is crazy, isn’t she?
Can’t believe she forgives Consort Yu!
But she also can’t confront her openly.
Don't forget.
It was Consort Ling who preserved the Fifth Prince's life.
She can't bear to watch such a little child
lose his mother.
Yingluo's changed.
Before, she was never hesitant to do anything.
Now, she's a different person,
talking happily with her enemy!
She's grown up.
Mingyu. You too though.
Me?
With this situation in the past,
you would've expelled Consort Yu and the Fifth Prince
out of your Palace by now.
But I am still stubborn and immature.
That's not stubborn and immature.
You are just not good at pretending.
Consort Ling has her reasons to do things.
I am guessing
she is getting close to Consort Yu,
because she wants to find a way to expose Noble Consort Chun.
The closer you get to your enemy, the easier to find.
Right?
Silly girl!
Now go back. Don’t let Consort Ling worry!
I am a month older than you!
How did you know?
I…
You looked into my age secretly.
I don't care about you.
Easy, Your Highness.
Even though the cast is removed,
you have to
move carefully.
I will prescribe another medicine for you.
Take it on time and take good care,
so that you can recover soon.
How is it? Feel better?
Thank you, doctor Ye!
I take my leave then.
Are we still mad at me?
No.
If you're not, then bring my tag
and go to the Imperial Household Department
and get something for me.
Here, to the left.
Yes, to the right.
Mingyu. Turn.
Keep turning!
That's not what Teacher Yin said.
It’s the other way!
This way! That’s right!
Slow down!
I give up! I can’t do it!
Mingyu.
Try again.
Yes.
His Majesty.
Greetings to Your Majesty.
Rise.
What are you doing now?
This Western item gets so dusty at the Imperial Household Department.
So I asked Teacher Yin
and he showed me
a dance.
I had the French technician stay in the Forbidden City
to work on calendars and firearms,
not to entertain you.
Do you know how to dance, Your Majesty?
I'll teach you.
I'm not interested.
I am not interested in horseback riding either,
but I learned it anyway for you.
To be fair,
Your Majesty has to learn how to dance too.
You are just messing around.
Step your left foot.
There you go.
One!
Two!
Left!
Keep your eyes straight ahead!
Your Majesty.
Dancing is fun, isn’t it?
That foreigner also put his arm around your waist?
Teacher Yin and the junior eunuch
showed it to me like this.
Your Master is really something.
His Majesty is unhappy these days.
But now he’s cheered up so quickly.
Something’s wrong!
What's wrong?
Wait.
I heard when the foreigners dance,
man should arm around woman’s waist.
Wei Yingluo, you're teasing me again.
Did I hurt you?
I was trying to cheer Your Majesty up.
By teaching me the woman's steps?
Then we'll switch.
Don't be mad anymore.
Step left foot.
Like this, right?
Your Majesty, so you know how to dance.
You knew how to dance.
You were tricking me!
Your Majesty is upset again?
Yingluo.
If one person must be killed,
what would you do?
Kill him.
What if he was falsely accused?
Release him.
What if he was falsely accused,
but he must be killed
for the big picture?
Either kill him or release him.
What does that mean?
Announce his death sentence in public,
but find someone
who is on death row with similar appearance,
and do a secret switch!
That’ll work, right?
You think the Ministry of Justice is the vegetable market?
You have to ascertain someone's identity before you behead him.
Your Majesty is indeed talking about Lord Naerbu.
But you did want to kill him.
Nonsense. I’ve never thought of that.
Even if you granted the Empress your grace,
exiling her father instead of beheading,
but would he be safe one the way?
There's no one the Emperor cannot spare in the world.
Your Majesty didn't want him to live after all.
Will Your Majesty kill me
as I just told the truth?
Your Majesty!
So you're scared of death too?
Was I right?
You were right.
Naerbu didn't take the disaster relief.
But he did make two mistakes. One, he kept information from me,
two, he is incompetent.
Many places in Eastern Zhejiang
face similar situations.
But they didn't have any revolt
or deaths of disaster victims.
Sometimes, an incompetent officer
will do harm just the same as a corrupted officer.
I sentenced him
to exile
only on the Empress' account,
giving him an honorable death.
I had no idea Empress
Dowager would take an early action.
Yingluo,
do you think
that I am a cruel monarch?
I do.
So what?
Your Majesty always wants to be perfect,
but there’s no perfect person in this world.
The greedy officers will hate you if you kill them.
The useless officers will resent you if they are killed.
Just let them hate or resent.
Since it’s already done, then don’t regret.
You pushed yourself again, didn't you?
Last night you insisted on dancing.
When an officer is ill,
he still needs to attend court.
When a consort is ill,
she still needs to cheer up the Emperor.
This is called duty.
You're so full of bizarre logic.
I'll go find Doctor Ye.
Don't move.
Why is it hurting so much suddenly?
Because you overestimated yourself!
Give me your hand.
Brother!
How come you are here?
Your Highness Consort Ling.
You're a ranking consort now.
Don’t call me brother anymore! I’m not worthy of it.
No matter what, you're still my brother.
Alright, Consort Ling.
Take a seat.
Gently.
You deserve it!
Brother, be gentle, my bone was injured.
So comfortable.
I’m still angry.
I’ve been angry with you for the past six months.
The stuff you sent me has piled up,
but you never showed up.
I was afraid I'd make you angrier.
You promised me
that we'd shoulder trouble together and enjoy fortune together.
I’ve thought about it.
You're Consort Ling now.
I will stay at your Palace
and be your chamberlain.
Okay?
Sure!
Consort Ling,
don't call me Brother in the palace.
Others will hear it. Understand?
Just call me by name.
Knowing you is truly my misfortune.
Knowing you
is a luck for me!
Your Highness the Empress!
Empress, be merciful and save me!
I am dying,
Empress!
Your Highness the Empress, forgive us.
This servant is unruly and needs to be taught.
Hupo, how dare you to stop Her Highness!
Do you want to be whipped?
Empress,
I used to work at Palace of Eternal Spring.
Because I made one mistake,
I was sent to Slave House and suffered a lot.
Empress. May Your Highness be merciful
and save me!
Your Highness the Empress! Save me!
She is..?
Your Highness,
she's Hupo who used to work at Palace of Eternal Spring.
Hupo?
I remember now.
How did she become like this?
Empress,
she was supposed to be assigned to Palace of Everlasting Joy.
But she offended Consort Ling,
and she was sent to the Slave House to do hard labor.
But she can't endure any hardship.
Empress, don't worry,
I will teach her properly!
Empress.
May you be merciful and save me!
Shut up!
She's the late Empress' old servant,
so she should be treated well.
Yes.
Assign her some easier chores,
and don't whip her anymore.
Yes.
Let's go.
Empress.
Empress! Empress!
Your Highness!
Hupo.
Stop daydreaming.
Your Highness!
You offended Consort Ling.
Even the Empress can’t save you!
Your Highness!
Shut up!
Your Highness.
Greetings to Mother Ling.
Yongqi heard you can get up now.
So I came to bid you wellness especially.
Mother Ling, I don't think Sister Mingyu likes me.
True.
Usually,
Mother Ling would say
it’s all a misunderstanding.
Why would I deceive you?
But everyone in the palace does that.
Mother Ling doesn't like that.
Sit here.
Thank you, Mother Ling.
Go ahead.
You clearly want to eat it.
It's by your hand, so why don't you take it?
Mother said
taking something without asking is not proper.
Enjoy!
I’ve agreed.
Is it good?
Yongqi.
Since you're coughing,
you shouldn't eat sweet things anymore. Got it?
The tea is cold.
I will go switch it.
This.
Give them to me.
Shush!
What are you laughing about?
I'm laughing that you're a fool!
Don’t you see that
she stole two chess pieces from you?
Yingluo! You're too much.
Last time you stole two chess pieces from His Majesty.
His Majesty was so mad that he ignored you for two days.
Now you're doing it again?
I like seeing him mad.
It makes me happy!
You're so weird.
I don’t know why,
but I like to tease serious people.
So silly!
Yingluo, Yingluo!
Chamberlain Li. What brings you here?
Consort Ling, His Majesty invites you to go to Palace of Eternal Peace.
Palace of Eternal Peace?
Why now?
Please come with me right away.
I will accompany you.
No!
I will accompany Your Highness.
Mingyu.
You stay here.
Don't be nervous.
Nothing will happen.
Your Majesty, Her Highness Consort Ling is here.
Greetings to Your Majesty.
Is the Fifth Prince ill?
What are you trying to do!
Consort Yu,
what was that for?
Your Majesty.
Yongqi is so young!
Can’t believe she poisoned him!
She is so evil!
Poisoned him?
What does that mean?
Consort Ling.
Did the Fifth Prince go to your Palace today?
Yes.
Consort Yu told him to come visit me
and bring lucid ganoderma and deer antler to me.
Did he eat a snack there?
He ate a piece of lotus cake.
There it is then.
Doctor Liu.
Consort Ling,
the Fifth Prince has been coughing lately.
I am treating his illness mainly with fritillary bulb.
But fritillary bulb has a peculiarity.
It cannot be taken together with aconite
such as wolf's bane, monkshood, devil's helmet.
They should all be avoided.
If they were taken together, what would happen?
To reply you, Your Highness,
if taken together,
it's very likely that due to the medicinal properties clashing, one would be poisoned,
causing paralysis, unstoppable pain,
even death.
When I took the Fifth Prince's pulse,
I found out that he had signs of being poisoned by wolf's bane.
Only Consort Ling knows
If her lotus cake contains wolf's bane!