[English subtitles are available]
[Story of Yanxi Palace]
[Episode 45]
Your Majesty!
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Get up.
Why are you here, Your Majesty?
It seems a long time...
since my last visit.
Over the last month,
you've only called for
Concubine Ling to serve you.
I haven't seen you for a long time.
Don't you blame me?
If you visits me,
I'll welcome you with smiles.
If Your Majesty doesn't visit me,
I'll wait for you.
Noble Consort Chun,
do you know what I like about you?
What?
Whenever...
I see you,
you're always gentle, caring,
and considerate.
Her Majesty is virtuous.
Concubine Jia is adorable.
Imperial Concubine Shu is passionate.
Noble Lady Qing is innocent.
-In this Forbidden City,
-Your Majesty, please.
among all the beauties,
I feel most relaxed...
when I see you,
because you never ask anything from me.
I have nothing to ask for.
The only thing I want...
is to make you happy.
I heard the victory against Jinchuan...
has spared you a big concern.
Why are you frowning?
By the way, you should tell
Concubine Ling this good news.
She'd be happy to hear it.
Why would she be happy?
While she was in the Changchun Palace,
Fu Heng always took good care of her.
He then went to war.
I'm sure Concubine Ling
has been worried about him.
Now that he's safely returned,
she will feel relieved.
Your Majesty, what's wrong?
Nothing.
It's late.
Go to bed early.
Take care, Your Majesty.
Let's go to the Yanxi Palace.
To the Yanxi Palace!
Lower the sedan!
Head back to the Yangxin Hall.
Sister Ming Yu.
-What's wrong?
-I saw His Majesty passing by our palace.
He left without getting off the sedan.
Why?
-Really?
-I saw it with my own eyes.
His Majesty left
without getting off his sedan.
-Is that true?
-I don't know.
I heard they all saw it.
-We'd better stop talking about it.
-It's true.
Have you heard?
Concubine Ling and
Lord Fu Heng seem to have...
Ying Luo, something is wrong.
Go and ask around.
Yes.
Is it true? Their relationship
may not be normal.
Stop talking nonsense.
Mistress, you're no longer grounded.
You should go out for a stroll.
What can I do out there?
Let that vixen laugh at me?
You're not the laughing-stock.
It's Concubine Ling herself.
What?
Mistress, we've been
staying in our palace.
Hence, we didn't keep ourselves updated.
There's rumours flying around the palace.
Good!
I'll skin that vixen alive.
Your Highness,
His Majesty said that he won't see you.
You can't keep kneeling here, can you?
Does His Majesty...
despise me now?
I was wrong, Your Majesty!
[Yangxin Hall]
And I came to ask for your forgiveness!
Your Majesty!
Your Majesty,
if you don't forgive me,
I'll keep kneeling here...
Your Majesty!
Supervisor Li,
Your Highness has always been good to you.
Please beg for leniency
from His Majesty on her behalf!
Well,
I'll give it a try.
Your Majesty,
Her Highness has been kneeling
out there for two hours.
She has a delicate build.
If she keeps kneeling,
I'm afraid her body
won't be able to take it.
Let her in.
Yes.
Your Majesty,
I know I was wrong.
I really do.
You really do?
Your Majesty, ever since
Concubine Ling entered the palace,
you've stopped favouring others.
Who am I?
I'm just a little woman who knows nothing.
You're the only one
who has a place in my heart.
But you always spent time with her.
I got so upset.
My anger got the best of me.
And I made a mistake.
I punished her by making her kneel.
I know I was wrong. I really do!
Your Majesty, I dare not
make things difficult for her again.
Does that mean...
you've figured it out?
Yes, I have.
Your Majesty,
you do know...
that everyone gets jealous.
If you can share with me...
a little part of your kindness
to Concubine Ling,
I'll be satisfied.
Do all women get jealous?
Of course.
As long as they hold Your Majesty
close to their hearts,
they'll get jealous.
Unless...
What if someone...
never cares if I visit her or not?
It can only mean that...
she doesn't hold you close to her heart.
Your Majesty,
you're not angry...
with me anymore?
Get up.
Thank you, Your Majesty!
I'll stay to chat to you then.
Your Majesty,
are you drawing a new courtyard?
I plan to...
bestow on Fu Heng a new house
in the Dongan Gate.
And I shall name this courtyard.
But I haven't figured out its name yet.
What about...
Yujing Garden?
Why?
Flowers in Shu have faded.
Gardenia is blooming.
Its colour is as beautiful as cajuput.
Its fragrance is like of
the goddess in the moon.
The phrase Yujing...
comes from this poem.
Yujing?
It praises gardenia?
Yes.
I heard that Lord Fu Heng...
ordered the servants to look for
rare gardenias everywhere.
I think he loves that flower very much.
Isn't Yujing Garden a very suitable name
for his courtyard?
Get out.
Your Majesty.
Did I say anything wrong?
You thought I didn't realize that...
you're indirectly...
defaming Concubine Ling?
Your Majesty!
I truly love you.
But you don't cherish me.
You hold the unfaithful one
close to your heart instead.
Even if you'll kill me today,
I must tell you the truth!
Concubine Ling,
she's done you wrong!
Get lost!
It's game over for that vixen.
But it's clear that His Majesty was angry.
You know nothing.
His Majesty was just venting his anger.
He is...
powerful and above everyone.
His favourite consort
is being coveted by his subordinate.
How can he swallow his pride?
But isn't it  too risky...
for you to do that?
So what if it's risky?
His Majesty used to...
dote on me the most.
I won't allow that vixen
to steal His Majesty.
If she's gone,
His Majesty will
return to my side for sure!
Just wait and see.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Empress,
rumours have been going around lately.
Have you heard?
Rumours?
Are you talking about
Concubine Ling and Lord Fu Heng?
Even you've heard of it.
It seems that they've
been spreading those rumours.
You've been favouring Concubine Ling...
and other consorts got jealous.
It's inevitable that they've been
gossiping about her.
Don't worry, Your Majesty.
I'll look into it thoroughly...
to deliver justice for Concubine Ling.
So...
you believe she's innocent?
Lord Fu Heng was
on the campaign all the time.
And Concubine Ling has been
staying in the palace.
It's normal for them to have a chat
if they bump into each other.
Concubine Ling used to be
the late empress' trusted maid after all.
Their relationship...
is different from others.
Relationship?
You've misunderstood me, Your Majesty.
I meant...
it's all in the past.
Since the late empress passed away...
and Concubine Ling stayed
at the Yuanming Garden,
she's never seen Lord Fu Heng.
Concubine Ling is now your consort.
She's cautious and obedient.
She has no fault.
You're magnanimous, Your Majesty.
You've never cared about...
a trifle like this.
From now on,
whoever talks about it...
will be flogged to death.
-Your Majesty.
-That's all I wanted to say.
You'll take care of...
the rest.
Your Majesty, what do you think of it?
I've never seen His Majesty...
care about a woman so much.
What trick did Concubine Ling use?
Maybe His Majesty finds her unique.
He's never seen
a woman like her after all.
He may find her not attractive
anymore after some time.
It seems that Noble Consort Chun...
has met the biggest foe in her life.
I've looked into it.
The rumours about you and
Lord Fu Heng are going around.
Some are saying you've been together
since your days at the Changchun Palace.
Some are saying Lord Fu Heng
offered you to His Majesty...
for the sake of promotion.
Some are saying
you're still in a relationship.
Every rumour is full of details.
They're all talking nonsense.
In that case,
it makes sense.
Do you mean His Majesty doesn't
come to Yanxi Palace anymore...
because he believes in the rumours?
What other reason could there be?
It's true that...
His Majesty hasn't summoned you lately.
Ying Luo, what should we do?
The wise does not buy into rumours.
I didn't expect that...
even His Majesty would believe in them.
Your Highness, we've been out for so long.
Let's head back now.
No,
I can't go.
If I leave now,
they'll say that I have
a guilty conscience.
But…
Ying Luo,
I want to talk to you.
Let's talk here then.
Why?
I didn't want to be
a palace maid anymore.
Why didn't you wait for me?
I could have...
You could've made me your concubine?
No.
I'd rather be His Majesty's consort...
than being your concubine.
At least it's a higher rank.
Ying Luo,
I won't believe...
what you're saying.
Fu Heng,
do you know about the rumours about us?
They're saying that
we're having an affair.
You're an esteemed official
with military merits.
Of course His Majesty
won't make life difficult for you.
But he's venting his anger on me.
Therefore,
please stay away from me.
Get it?
I just want to see you.
I just want to help you.
You can't help me.
You may get me into trouble instead.
Do you mean what you're saying?
Do you still remember that snowy day?
You and Er Qing stood together...
like a match made in heaven.
From then on,
I swore to myself that...
I would broke ties with you...
and become a stranger to you.
A stranger?
Yes.
Hence,
please stay as far away as you can.
What if I say...
I can't do it?
I can't stop thinking about you.
I can't stop caring about you.
For me, you're not
His Majesty's Concubine Ling.
You're the Wei Ying Luo of my heart.
You're the Wei Ling Luo who's stubborn...
and full of sense of justice.
Justice?
You're a noble-minded gentleman.
And I'm a petty person who seeks revenge.
We're never of the same kind.
I'm very touched...
by your compliment.
What did I say?
Playing chess somewhere else
is a change of mood.
It'll cheer you up soon.
Place the chess at that gazebo.
Your Highness,
the gazebo is occupied.
Isn't that Concubine Ling?
Who's beside her?
That's Lord Fu Heng.
Your Majesty,
Concubine Ling used to be a maid
at the Changchun Palace.
Surely she knows Lord Fu Heng well.
They're talking at a public place,
with a palace maid in attendance.
They're acting respectable.
Since they're acting respectable,
there's no need for you to explain it.
Your Majesty,
I am afraid you'll blame Concubine Ling,
since she's quite young after all.
She's ignorant of the palace rules.
An occasional misconduct is...
understandable.
Her Highness will be upset
seeing you like this.
Okay, Zhen Zhu,
-Stop crying.
-The entire palace is talking about it.
Surely Her Highness knows about it.
Stop crying.
What happened?
Mistress,
I accidentally tripped
and hurt myself today.
-Who did this?
-I tripped.
You did this to yourself?
You think we're fools?
Zhen Zhu,
tell me the truth.
Today, I went to the Imperial Kitchen
to fetch some snacks.
And I ran into Lan from the Chuxiu Palace.
They're the snacks made for you
by the Imperial Kitchen.
But Lan said that the Chuxiu Palace
needed them urgently.
And she took them away.
Everyone at the Imperial Kitchen
defended her.
Okay, stop crying.
I'll send you a bottle of ointment later.
We need to avoid scarring.
Where's the other bracelet?
Ying Luo, now isn't the time
to water the flowers.
Didn't you see Zhen Zhu getting bullied?
What should I do then?
Go to the Chuxiu Palace and
beat the young Concubine Jia up?
You need to stop the rumours.
Your Majesty favoured you...
for only a few days.
Yanxi Palace has now become a cold palace.
Even your servants are in deep water.
I can't stop thinking about you.
I can't stop caring about you.
For me, you're not
His Majesty's Concubine Ling.
You're the Wei Ying Luo of my heart.
You're the Wei Ling Luo who's stubborn...
and full of sense of justice.
Ying Luo!
Greetings, Concubine Ling.
De Sheng, what can we do for His Majesty?
What are you doing?
Concubine Ling,
His Majesty said...
that the smell of the chamber pots
at Yong Alley is too strong.
We need your gardenias to cover it.
How can you do that?
My mistress picked all these flowers.
And you're going to use them
to fumigate the Yong Alley?
Don't move them!
Leave them be.
Concubine Ling,
His Majesty is mad at you.
When he calms down,
everything will be fine.
I'm just doing my job.
Please don't blame me.
Concubine Ling, I'm taking my leave.
That's going too far!
Hurry up...
Why are they taking them all away?
Has the mistress lost
His Majesty's favour?
When the mistress was favoured,
His Majesty had
the most precious variety sent here...
upon knowing that
she loved gardenia the most.
And now they've been taken away.
They'll be used to
fumigate the Yong Alley.
He's shaming the mistress.
Ying Luo,
why did His Majesty do that?
Go find out...
if His Majesty went to
the Imperial Garden today.
Oh no.
He must have seen
you met with Lord Fu Heng.
He did all this...
to warn me.
-How beautiful these flowers are.
-I know, right?
They're from the Yanxi Palace.
They smell quite nice.
Sister Ming Yu?
It's late. Why are you lingering around?
I'm on duty tonight.
But I've got a stomach ache
all of a sudden.
-I need to go relieve myself!
-Wait!
What's in your arms?
I can't hold it anymore.
Sister, I'm leaving!
You're the thief!
Concubine Ling,
I was wrong.
I stole them...
because I was confused.
I was wrong!
Your Highness, please spare my life!
You're not confused.
You knew I lost the favour...
so you tried to steal the valuables
from my palace...
and sell them off.
Your Highness,
You may beat or scold me.
But please don't send me to
the Bureau of Internal Affair!
If you do so, they'll kill me!
If I hadn't found out,
you wouldn't have admitted your crime!
Everyone is bullying us.
And you're acting like an ingrate.
Where would you sell...
the mistress' stuff?
Well...
If you don't tell me,
I'll send you to
the Bureau of Internal Affair.
Your Highness,
I'll tell you.
It's common for eunuchs to steal.
Even those serving at
the Qianqing Palace and Yangxin Hall...
often do so.
As long as the masters don't find out,
there're ways to get them
out of the palace.
With the help from
friends at Glass Street,
stolen items can be sold off very quickly.
-Really?
-I'm telling the truth!
If you spare my life,
from now on,
I'll do anything for you...
without complaining!
I can spare you.
But don't you ever forget...
what you just said.
Thank you, Your Highness...
Leave them here!
No one ever pays attention to these items.
He's stolen so many without our knowledge.
Ying Luo,
why did you let him off?
He said...
he'll do anything for me.
You believe the words of such a rogue?
Yes.
They found out about it?
You're such a good-for-nothing.
Miss Lan, please calm down...
It's all Ming Yu's fault.
She's too vigilant.
It's my fault as well.
I was being careless.
But don't worry.
I got away with it...
by saying that I stole them.
Concubine Ling will never
find out about it.
What's the point of it?
What my mistress wants is gone.
Miss Lan,
I'm capable.
I'll never let you down.
Give me what you promised me.
Thank you...
I'm leaving.
Miss Ming Yu, you're here to see me?
I came to say thank you...
for helping me.
I didn't help you with anything.
Can I call you Hailan Cha?
Of course you can.
Come and find me if you ever need my help.
What are they doing?
It's Noble Consort Chun's instruction.
She's preparing a special gift
for Empress Dowager.
Special gift?
It's supposed to be a secret.
But since you're not an outsider,
I'll tell you then.
Suzhou Street?
Here comes our opportunity.
Empress Dowager, be careful.
It's so bustling.
I can't see anything.
Noble Consort Chun,
what have you got for me?
Empress Dowager, listen.
Hurry. Take it off.
Take it off...
Look.
Noble Consort Chun, what is this?
Empress Dowager,
you've always yearned for
Jiangnan's scenery.
There are no small bridges or rivers
in our Forbidden City.
Relying on my childhood memory,
I've instructed the eunuchs and maids
to dress as the commoners...
and open this palace market.
Even though there are
no swaying willows...
and flowing rivers,
we have flying wine flags...
and crowds of pedestrians.
I hope it can amuse you, Empress Dowager.
Noble Consort Chun,
you're thoughtful.
that's very clever of you.
But this isn't real after all.
I've decided...
to build Empress Dowager a Suzhou Street
in front of the Wanshou Temple,
along the banks of Imperial River.
Once it's built,
Empress Dowager can enjoy
the beautiful scenery of Jiangnan.
Emperor,
that's too costly.
As long as you're happy,
I think it worth it.
Empress Dowager,
do you want to go down there?
Sure.
-It looks good.
-I know, right?
Amazing...
Awesome.
I like this fabric.
Empress Dowager,
Noble Consort Chun is smart indeed.
In my opinion,
since the palace market is open,
we shouldn't just look around.
We should put it to use instead.
How?
The war against Jinchuan
has just subsided.
Although we won,
it's incurred many casualties.
The pensions received by
families of the injured...
and deceased soldiers are very limited.
Widows and orphans lost their homes.
I suggest all consorts take the lead...
and donate some jewellery
and treasures for charity sale.
Since it's a charity sale,
we shouldn't just do it in the palace.
We can place these stalls
outside the palace gate.
The money received can be used
to compensate bereaved families.
Empress, you're very compassionate.
That's indeed a great idea.
In this case,
we can make this palace market...
prepared by Noble Consort Chun
more meaningful.
Since both Emperor and Empress said so,
we shouldn't build
a Suzhou Street for now.
Let's use the money...
to help those in urgent need.
Empress Dowager.
When the imperial treasury
has enough money,
we'll then build a Suzhou Street.
Empress Dowager, I thank you...
on behalf of all Great Qing soldiers.
Your Majesty is indeed thoughtful.
I only thought about
making Empress Dowager happy.
I didn't think beyond that.
In that case,
I'll make a donation too.
You don't have to do this.
-A small donation will do.
-Come and buy the liquor!
A decree from Empress Dowager...
-and all the court officials...
-Come and buy the liquor!
will follow suit.
Come and buy the liquor!
Thank you.
Why are you here?
Sir,
do you want some liquor?
Try it.
Sir.
Sangluo liquor.
Xinfeng liquor.
Chrysanthemum liquor.
Zhuyeqing liquor. Red Daughter liquor.
Sir, which liquor would you like?
Concubine Ling?
Who do you dress up as?
I'm not Concubine Ling today.
I'm a liquor saleswoman today.
These are all rare good
liquors in Jiangnan.
You should try them.
You've dressed yourself
as a liquor saleswoman.
I can't contain my laughter
at the sight of you.
Only she could figure out
such an odd idea...
and execute it.
Empress Dowager.
If you don't buy it now,
I'll sell it to someone else.
Twenty wen for one pot of Sangluo liquor.
Forty wen for one pot of Xinfeng liquor.
Thirty wen for one pot of
chrysanthemum liquor.
Twenty wen for one pot of
Zhuyeqing liquor.
Twenty-five wen for
one pot of Red Daughter liquor.
Come and buy them!
What accent is this?
Your Highness,
you grew up in Suzhou.
That makes you the native speaker
of Suzhou dialect.
She's showing her slight skill
in front of an expert.
Try it.
Concubine Ling, you're really something.
I can't even remember...
my native dialect.
Come and buy the liquor!
Concubine Ling is so clever.
Look at her clothes.
It looks pretty amusing.
Are you stupid?
Don't you see she's seducing His Majesty?
Look at His Majesty's eyes.
He's attracted by her.
It's because she's tactful.
Even if someone else
could think of such an idea,
they wouldn't be able to
swallow their pride and do it.
What liquor is this?
I think it's Dukang liquor.
Sangluo and Zhuyeqing liquor...
are from Shanxi.
They're not from Suzhou.
If you want to sell liquor,
you should check the market price first.
Who would dare buy your liquor?
Come and buy the liquor!
My liquor ladle!
It's mine!
Give it back to me!
This liquor is undrinkable.
Pay for the liquor.
Here's my payment.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Hey!
Come here.
Don't you know the rules?
His Majesty is here.
Tell your mistress
to come out and greet him now.
My mistress said...
His Majesty will pass by and not come in.
So she won't come out.
She's acting like a smarty-pants again.
Is your mistress...
trying to scheme against
His Majesty again?
What are you talking about,
Supervisor Li?
My mistress only tells the truth.
You're pretending...
I'm telling you.
His Majesty is angry.
Although Concubine Ling
has lured His Majesty to visit her,
it may not be a good thing.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty!
I treat you well with all my heart...
but you're fond of that vixen...
and always ignore me.
My anger got the best of me...
so I targeted her on purpose.
Your Majesty,
even if I have many flaws,
that's all because I love you.
Concubine Ling likes gardenia.
Lord Fu Heng too likes gardenia.
What a coincidence.
I think...
both of them are having an affair.
She doesn't deserve your favour.
Concubine Ling...
deserves to die.
Wei Ying Luo,
what are you doing?
Concubine Ling and Lord Fu Heng
have been knowing each other.
They bumped into each other...
and had a chat.
Even if they're in a relationship,
it's all in the past.
Now that she's entered the palace,
the past is not important anymore.
I believe...
she's not a shameless woman...
who would betray you.
You...
Your Majesty, don't worry.
As the head of the harem,
I'll find out who has been
spreading the rumours...
to deliver justice for Concubine Ling.
You haven't been
in the palace for very long...
but you know each one of them...
so well.
What you said is similar to
what they told me.
As if you actually heard them saying it.
I know women...
way better than you.
You knew what they'd say behind you.
Yet, you dared meeting
Fu Heng in the garden.
If I had turned around
and left right away,
they would've said...
Concubine Ling...
turned around and left right away
as soon as she saw Lord Fu Heng.
It's clear that she has
a guilty conscience.
Your Majesty,
rumours tend to confuse people.
If a lie is repeated often enough,
it'll be accepted as a truth.
I hope...
you can give me more trust...
while favouring me.
Or else,
even if I were made of bones of steel,
I would be reduced to tofu.
In this harem,
you're the most mischievous among all.
You always tease me.
Do you like me, Your Majesty?
I...
like a bad woman like you.