[English subtitles are available]
[Story of Yanxi Palace]
*[Episode 2]
The newly-selected concubines and consorts
will enter the palace in a few days.
If you are ill, get well soon.
Those who are not ill, buck up.
Don't let those newbies outperform you.
-Yes, Your Highness.
You may leave now.
What? His Majesty is retiring alone again?
Noble Consort Gao,
there are many reports that His Majesty
has to go through tonight.
He doesn't want everyone
to wait for him in vain.
Let's go. What are we still waiting for?
Farewell, Noble Consort Gao.
After going through the elimination round
and embroidery training,
you are now officially palace maids.
From now on, you will be under me.
We are new here and are still
unaware of the rules.
Please take good care of us, Madam.
Here, no one can take care of anyone.
Just pray for yourselves.
Madam, what do you mean by this?
Don't be anxious. You will find out later.
Ying Luo! Come over here.
I reserved a nice spot for you.
Let's go.
Ying Luo, thank you very much for today.
You are welcome.
Are all the palace maids here new?
Yes. What's wrong?
Nothing. I just wanted to ask more
about the palace rules from...
palace maids who came in earlier than us.
I think someone is trying to
curry favours with Madam.
-If you say so, so be it then.
-You!
-Stop it.
-Why should I?
Yes. She is the best one here.
The most outstanding person!
We are all bad people here.
You are the only good person!
Ji Xiang, do you really
think she was helping you?
Let me tell you. She just wanted to
showcase herself in front of Chief Eunuch.
-You are spouting nonsense.
- If you don't believe me, ask her then.
Wei Ying Luo, you make a hit today.
Did you do it for yourself?
Fine. You want to ignore me?
Jin Xiu, what are you doing?
Stop splashing water on her bed!
You dared ignore me, right?
This is the consequence.
She deserves it for
stealing the spotlight.
That's right. You shamed us all.
Remember not to steal the spotlight again.
Don't be so eager for success.
Ying Luo, let's share a bed.
Jin Xiu, what are you doing?
Why did you wet her bed?
-What if the Madam finds out about it?
-Will she dare complain about it?
There are so many of us here.
Why should we be afraid of her?
Wei Ying Luo! What are you doing?
Ying Luo, are you crazy?
-Let's go and report this to Madam.
-No!
Ying Luo was just acting on impulse.
She didn't do it on purpose.
Ying Luo, say something!
This is too much.
Why did you wet all of our beds?
-Have you caused enough trouble?
-Trouble?
It's clearly you who is
causing the trouble here!
It would be rough for Ji Xiang if she
couldn't finish her embroidery piece.
And now, you are jealous because
I helped her and received a compliment.
You didn't want to her and
you forbade others from helping as well.
Is that logical? Initially, I didn't care.
Because I didn't enter
the palace to make friends.
But let me warn you today.
I, Wei Ying Luo,
has an ill temper and
I'm not someone to be trifled with.
If any of you want to target me again,
I'll have a way to deal with you!
You are arrogant and despotic!
-Wei Ying Luo, release me!
-You wanted to see Madam, right?
-Let go of me!
-I'll go with you.
Let's tell her what happened just now.
Ying Luo, release her. Aren't you
afraid that you'll be punished?
Do you really think that she is so free...
to seek justice for you?
We are all living under the same roof.
If we cause troubles,
we will all be kicked out.
Do you believe that?
Fine. Let's go now. Come on.
-Ying Luo, release her!
-Let her go.
It's too late to wake up Madam now.
Do you want to die?
-I was wrong. I was wrong, okay?
-Let her go.
I won't mention it again.
I don't want to be kicked out.
Why are you causing so much noise
in the middle of the night?
Madam Fang, I accidentally
overturned the tea pot just now.
Our beddings are wet now.
No need to cause a ruckus.
Just flip the beddings.
Don't make any noise again!
Stop right there.
Wei Ying Luo, what else do you want?
Flip my bedding for me.
Ying Luo, you are so amazing.
Besides being kind,
we should learn to protect ourselves.
Remember this.
Shut up. Go to sleep now!
[Ying Luo, are you crazy?]
[Get away from the coffin.]
[Ying Luo, come to your senses.
Your sister is already dead!]
[Everyone said that...]
[she died from an illness.]
[Now, I can prove that...]
[she didn't die from an illness.]
[She was strangled to death.]
[Shut up!]
-[Take a look for yourselves, all of you!]
-[Ying Luo.]
[Ying Luo!]
[There are bruises on her neck,
she was murdered.]
[She was murdered!]
-[She was murdered!]
-[Stop it!]
[Wei Qing Tai, your daughter opened
the coffin and disturbed the dead.]
[She'll be punished.]
[Yes. Ying Ning tainted herself and
was expelled from the palace.]
[That's why she committed suicide.]
[This kind of unchaste woman...]
[brought shame to the family!]
[Now, Wei Ying Luo is spouting nonsense.]
[Do you want us to punish her
according to the rules of our clan?]
[No, Clan Leader.
Ying Luo is too immature.]
[Everybody here, please forgive her.
I will discipline her!]
[Ying Luo, kneel down and
apologise to them now!]
[I lost my mother when I was young.]
[It was her who raised me.]
[Although we are all...]
[from the same clan,]
[I've never eaten their food before,]
[taken a single sip of water
or received any help from them.]
[Now, my sister died in injustice.]
[They failed to differentiate
right from wrong...]
[and criticised her for staining
the graveyard of Wei clan.]
[They won't even give her a burial spot.]
[You want me to apologise to them?]
[For what?]
[Why can't you let this matter drop.
What do you want?]
[My sister...]
[died for no reason at all.]
[I will enter the palace...]
[to investigate the truth of her death.]
[If you enter the palace,
you will get into trouble.]
-[Do I have to expel you from the family?]
-[I don't care!]
[Father. Even if you expel me
from the family...]
[and Wei clan,]
[I will still seek justice...]
[for my sister.]
What's wrong? Who hit me?
Madam, what's wrong?
What's wrong?
Look at the way you sleep.
You are exposing your bellies and
salivating in your sleep like toads!
This is the Forbidden City.
There are rules for walking and sitting.
You can't just act as you wish!
Madam, how should we sleep then?
Legs! Lie down!
Hurry up!
Your legs.
You! You should sleep in
the same direction! Turn over there!
Remember this position. Don't forget it
even when you are asleep!
Go back first and
let them sleep for a while.
Wake them up in an hour's time.
Your Highness, what's wrong?
Something is not right.
Your Highness, it's not daybreak yet.
Did you have a bad dream?
Idiot.
Something must be going on
with Concubine Yi.
Next.
What is this?
What are you doing?
Yan, help me think of a solution.
Sister, calm down.
How can I calm down?
Noble Consort Gao must be suspicious
of me now. She already suspects us.
What should we do now?
We should think of
a countermeasure against her.
Noble Consort Gao is here!
Hurry up and leave through the back door!
Fang Cao.
Greetings, Your Highness.
Noble Lady Yu, I heard that you are sick.
So, I came to visit you.
Imperial Physician Liu,
check her health for her.
-Yes, Your Highness.
-Noble Consort Gao.
What's wrong? I kindly brought along
the imperial physician to check on you.
And you don't appreciate it?
It's just a cough. I don't need to be
treated by the imperial physician.
Imperial Physician Liu.
Noble Consort Gao! Let me go!
-Greetings, Concubine Yi.
-Ming Yu, I need to see Her Majesty.
She is not feeling well and has
excused herself from today's greetings.
Concubine Yi, what brings you here?
This is an urgent situation.
I need to see the Her Majesty!
I already said that
she's not seeing anyone now.
Please come back later.
Your Majesty, help!
Concubine Yi, this is Changchun Palace.
How dare you make a ruckus here?
Your Majesty!
Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, I beg you.
Please save Noble Lady Yu!
Please save Noble Lady Yu, Your Majesty!
This is mine!
Palace maids are not allowed to bring
anything with them. Take your hands off.
Tell me what's in here.
I was afraid that I'll miss home. So,
I took a handful of dirt from my home...
and put it into this jar
and brought it here.
This is not against
the palace rules, right?
You look so nervous.
I'm going to check if this is soil or not.
Madam!
How impudent.
Noble Consort Gao,
please spare my mistress!
-I beg you, Your Highness!
-Stop!
-Please spare my mistress!
-Let go of me!
Your Majesty.
Noble Consort Gao, what are you doing?
Noble Lady Yu is sick.
So, I brought the imperial physician
here to check on her.
Imperial Physician Liu, what are you
forcing Noble Lady Yu to drink?
Her Majesty is asking you a question.
Tell her the truth.
Your Majesty.
When I was diagnosing her illness,
her left pulse is deep and wiry while
her right pulse is beating strong.
Her liver is unwell and
there is phlegm in her lungs.
She's suffering from a cough.
To relieve her coughing,
I specially prescribed a cough medicine...
to be taken with loquat jelly.
You are spouting nonsense!
She is pregnant.
She's not having a cough!
How dare you, Concubine Yi!
What did you say last night at Yanxi Hall?
You said that Noble Lady Yu
is just having a cough.
Today, you say that she is pregnant.
Did you deliberately lie to me?
Your Majesty, I haven't been having
my period for quite some time.
So, I discussed it with Concubine Yi
because it's about a royal heir.
I couldn't confirm it. I planned to report
to you after I get the confirmation...
from the imperial physician
in half a month's time.
I have no intention to hide this
from you, Your Majesty.
-Please forgive me, Your Majesty.
-No.
I am afraid that...
she will be harmed by others because
she's pregnant with a royal heir.
That's why I lied and said that
it was just a cough.
Harmed by others?
Who would harm her?
Concubine Yi, are you pointing at
a certain someone?
It has been proven that...
my speculation is not wrong.
This bowl of medicine...
is the evidence that
you were trying to poison the royal heir!
How presumptuous!
Whether it's poisonous or not,
we'll know once we check it.
Physician Zhang.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, this is indeed loquat.
That's it?
Yes, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty.
You heard it.
Noble Lady Yu herself said that it's too
early to confirm that she is pregnant.
It's common to have a wrong diagnosis.
She is the one who kept it hidden
because of her paranoia.
I kindly brought the imperial physician
here to treat her.
But she accused me instead
for harming her.
Concubine Yi is even more outrageous.
She accused me for trying
to kill a royal heir.
A low-ranking concubine...
defaming a high-ranking noble consort.
This is highly disrespectful!
Your Majesty, this is all my fault!
What is this?
I already told you that it's dirt
from my hometown.
Why did you taste it?
Wait for me, Madam!
Ying Luo, she probably thought that
it is sesame and walnut powder.
Some palace maids hid it from her before.
When she found it,
she confiscated all of their powder.
She must be blind.
This is really dirt from my hometown.
You brought dirt into the palace?
You're really a silly girl.
Sister. I'm sorry.
Noble Consort Gao, Concubine Yi
acted like this out of panic.
Could she speak without reservation
just because she panicked?
Your Majesty, the rules of
our ancestors are crystal clear.
Concubine Yi accused me
without any evidence.
If she's not punished severely,
she'll set a bad example...
and this kind of bad influence will
totally ruin the morale of the palace!
Noble Consort Gao, this is not
as serious as you said it is.
Concubine Yi did it because she is
worried about Noble Lady Yu's royal heir.
Your Majesty, going against your superior
is unforgivable.
You're the mistress of the six palaces,
the mother of the nation.
You have to set a good example
and be fair and square.
But if you insist on taking her side,
I can do nothing about it.
But if you are biased and
handle this unfairly,
everybody will question...
your ability to govern the six palaces.
How impudent!
Your Majesty, I was...
too impetuous and offended
Noble Consort Gao.
I was wrong.
I will always remember your
generosity and kindness.
No need to trouble yourself
with this matter anymore.
Noble Consort Gao,
it was a slip of tongue.
You can punish me however you like.
As for Noble Lady Yu,
please forgive her considering that
she is pregnant...
with a royal heir now.
Noble Lady Yu is very delicate right now.
I won't make things difficult for her.
As for you,
Are you really at my disposal?
No.
-No.
-This is not up to you!
Noble Consort Gao, this is...
all my fault.
I conducted myself wrongly!
You can punish me however you like.
I just hope to appease your anger.
How are you all alone here?
Where are the others?
They went to eat breakfast after
they are done with their work.
Why didn't you join them?
Today is my first day.
So, I wanted to be early.
You're quite sensible.
Madam Zhang, I'd like to
ask you about someone.
Who is it?
You've managed the Embroidery House
for so many years.
Have you ever heard of Wei Ying Ning?
No.
She was assigned to the Embroidery House.
Why wouldn't you know?
Other than some talented embroidery maids,
we also hire some skilled embroiderers
from the outside.
We just keep our heads down when we work.
We don't know who is who.
Her embroidery skill was outstanding.
She wouldn't have gone unnoticed.
So what if she is talented? It's nothing
when this palace is full of them.
There's another thing that
I need to remind you.
The person who you just mentioned...
has the same name as Noble Consort Gao's
maiden name for the third character.
Every palace maid has to avoid using it.
-Avoid using it?
-Yes. The servants are not worthy...
to use the name of the imperial consorts.
The person you mentioned must have
changed her name already.
So, don't ask around with her name
anymore after this.
If someone hears you,
you will be punished.
Madam Zhang.
I was wondering why you skipped breakfast.
So, you are bothering Madam Zhang here.
What were you two talking about?
Alright now. Since you are both here,
let's not idle around.
Make a trip with me.
-Yes, Madam Zhang.
Palace maids are not allowed
to loiter in the palace.
If you have no reason to come out,
just stay at your assigned palace.
You are embroidery maids.
You often have to our mistresses'
body measurements.
You must remember the paths well.
You don't want to be
delayed with your work...
because you got lost.
-Yes, Madam Zhang.
-Chief Wu has issued an order.
Noble Lady Yu is pregnant.
The embroidery house has to
make new clothes for her.
When you enter Yonghe Palace,
pay attention to me.
-See how I...
-Please spare her!
Please spare her.
Concubine Yi, I'm asking a question
on behalf of Noble Consort Gao.
Why am I slapping you?
I defamed Noble Consort Gao and
disrespected my superior.
Please spare her! I beg you!
Noble Consort Gao also asks you this.
Will you be careful with
your words from now on?
Yes.
-Louder!
-Your Highness!
I'll bear it firmly in mind.
Stop hitting her!
She made a mistake because of me.
If Noble Consort Gao wants to
punish someone, punish me! Hit me instead!
Noble Lady Yu,
you're pregnant with the royal heir.
You are very valuable now.
Of course we won't hit you.
But you made the same mistake as
Concubine Yi. You better stay out of this.
Yan, go back now.
Are you asking me to just let them
humiliate you like this?
I won't leave you.
I'm fine. Go back now.
Noble Lady Yu,
if you harm the royal heir...
by being so emotional, we won't be able
to take the blame for it.
Go back now. Yan, go back!
Are you all logs?
Hurry up and drag Noble Lady Yu away.
-Noble Lady Yu.
-I won't leave you!
-Sister!
-Go back!
I beg you, don't hit her anymore!
-Stop hitting her!
-Let's continue.
Fifteen more slaps left.
Madam Zhang, this...
Concubine Yi offended her superior.
She has offended Noble Consort Gao.
Noble Consort Gao punished her
to be slapped in public.
But Concubine Yi
is the head of a palace too.
So what? You have to see who she offended.
The rule of the palace is to
hit the body, never the face.
Now, Noble Consort Gao...
clearly chose this to humiliate
Concubine Yi completely.
Sometimes, even if they are
a consort or concubine,
even the lowest-ranking
palace maid is better than them.
Noble Lady Yu, what's wrong?
Your Highness.
Your Highness, why have you
slimmed down instead?
She couldn't eat or sleep lately,
of course she'll slim down.
The loquat jelly is poisonous.
Why couldn't they realise that?
-Why?
-Your Highness, stop thinking about it.
Physician Zhang has outstanding
medical skills. He wouldn't be wrong.
She wants to kill the baby in my womb.
Why couldn't they tell that
it was poisonous?
Noble Lady Yu, stop it. I beg you.
Old loquat leaves aren't poisonous.
But the young leaves are poisonous.
Ying Luo, what nonsense
are you talking about?
What did you say?
Ying Luo.
Don't you know the rules? Don't talk
recklessly about what you don't know.
Repeat what you said.
-In the past, I...
-Ying Luo!
When I young, I loved loquat.
But once, I accidentally ate the pit.
I had trouble breathing
and I kept vomiting.
Later, a travelling physician
told me that...
that physicians prescribe medicines
according to The Canon of Medicine.
According to it, they can only use
old loquat leaves...
to make the loquat jelly.
But most people don't know the reason why.
After that,
he discovered by chance that...
old loquat leaves are not poisonous,
but the new leaves and pit are poisonous.
If they are eaten in an excessive amount,
your life will be at risk.
The loquat jelly sent by Noble Consort Gao
must be made with young leaves.
The poison must be so faint that
Physician Zhang cannot detect it.
Even if he did discover it, she could just
blame the Imperial Apothecary for it.
So, this is the truth.
Come with me to meet Her Majesty
and repeat what you said.
Your Highness, you can't do that.
How can anyone believe the words
of a petty palace maid?
Could she be more accurate than
Physician Zhang?
Ying Luo, how dare you speak
without care like this!
Do you want to die?
She had experienced it before.
She knows the truth.
-Let's go.
-Your Highness!
Your Highness.
She is new to the palace.
She knows nothing.
Please be magnanimous...
and spare her.
Alright.
I won't make it hard for you.
I will go and expose the truth myself.
Your Highness.
Your Highness!
You brat. You've caused a huge disaster.
Noble Lady Yu, Her Majesty is having
a headache ever since she got back.
She's still not awake.
You won't be able to see her today.
Miss Ming Yu,
I have an urgent matter to report.
Please announce me at once.
Close the gate!
Miss Ming Yu!
Open the gate, Miss Ming Yu!
I have an urgent matter to report,
Miss Ming Yu!
-Look at her.
-Ling Long.
I thought Madam Zhang admired her.
Why did Madam Zhang change so quickly
ever since they got back.
She spouted some nonsense and
angered Madam Zhang.
-I wonder what she did.
-That's right.
What did Ying Luo do wrong?
Alright. We'll stop here for today.
All of you are dismissed.
Look at how haughty she usually was.
Now, she's punished. She deserves it.
Keep up with your arrogance.
Ji Xiang, what are you doing?
Aren't you afraid that
Madam will punish you?
But...
Alright now, if you're too late,
I won't save you any food.
-Alright now, don't mind her. Let's eat.
-Time to eat.
-She has been out here for so long.
-Yes.
What are you looking at?
All these hours,
2,080 clouds had floated by.
Three hundred and two of them
were sunset clouds...
and the rest were all white clouds.
Looks like you are in a leisure.
Are you so aloof from this world?
In the past, I always wondered...
why couldn't I embroider sunset clouds?
But after today,
I will be able to embroider them.
Stop talking about the clouds.
Let me ask you this.
Have you thought it through?
Do you know what you did wrong?
What did I do wrong?
You've been kneeling here for a day and
you still don't know what you did wrong?
Do you think...
I shouldn't tell Her Highness that...
the young leaves of loquat are poisonous?
Do you know your status?
Young leaves of loquat are poisonous.
And the royal physicians
don't know this, but you do?
Nonsense.
Are you trying to kill yourself?
What are you laughing at?
Yes is yes, and no is no.
I don't feel guilty about
every single word I said.
Yes, you are not guilty
towards your conscience.
But what about your parents?
What about me who are worried for you?
I know you punished me to kneel here...
because you are concerned about me.
That's why I am kneeling here now.
-Why don't you admit your mistake then?
-They are separate matters.
Why do I have to admit my mistake
when I didn't do anything wrong?
Forgive me for not being able to do it.
Let me show you
the consequence of speaking bluntly.
Be careful.
Madam Zhang, what brings you here?
We left something here yesterday.
I came to retrieve it.
This isn't a clean place. Hurry up
and leave after you retrieve it.
Thank you, Chief Wu.
We will leave right away.
Let's go now.
Why didn't you wait until
I go and beg Her Majesty?
-Why are you so foolish?
-Your Highness.
She's already gone.
Stop talking about this nonsense.
She's not gone yet.
-Your Highness!
-You know the truth.
Tell everyone about the truth.
Noble Consort Gao wanted to kill
the baby in my womb.
My sister wasn't spouting nonsense.
-Go and tell everyone the truth! Let's go!
-Your Highness!
-Your Highness! Fang Cao.
Your Highness is too upset
and is not in her right mind.
Hurry up and escort her back to rest.
Let's go.
Your Highness, stop making a fuss.
Let's go back.
-I beg you. Let's go.
-Fang Cao.
Did you hear it?
The young leaves are poisonous.
They are poisonous.
Stop looking!
Did you see it clearly?
Concubine Yi was humiliated in public
and lost her dignity.
Noble Consort Gao wanted her dead.
What you said can't change anything.
This time, you are lucky.
If Noble Consort Gao
finds out about it next time,
you won't be able to save yourself.
Why did Concubine Yi commit suicide?
If she didn't die,
she could still fight back.
-What did you say?
-Concubine Yi was too weak.
Why did she have to die just because
she was humiliated?
Why?
She was a concubine and
was slapped in public.
How could she keep a foothold
in the palace after that?
If she doesn't seek death, is she supposed
to live and court shame upon herself?
If it were me,
I would be able to endure it...
even if I was humiliated by everyone.
Even if I was forced to kneel and wait,
I would still wait...
until the day when the truth is revealed.
You can't fight against the situation.
How can you break a rock with an egg?
You are wrong.
I am not an egg.
I am that stinky rock.
If you really had to face it one day,
you would know how scary it is.
I will fight tooth and nail for it.
The worst thing that can happen
is just to die.
You are forbidden to use that word.
Stubborn donkey.
Why did my sister die without any reason?
Why did Concubine Yi hang herself?
Why is the world so unfair?
Why? Why? Why?
How dare you attack the
spiritual cypress tree?
Why are you hiding? His Majesty is here,
why aren't you kneeling?
Hurry up.
Hurry up!
Greetings, Your Majesty.
How dare you harm
the spiritual cypress tree.
I'm sorry but I don't know what
a spiritual cypress tree is.
You brat!
This is the spiritual cypress tree.
It once provided shade to His Majesty.
So, he named it spiritual cypress tree.
Even its name tag is hanging there
so clearly. Many came to worship it.
And you dared harm it?
Drag her away and cane her thirty times.
I'm new to the palace and didn't know
about this spiritual cypress tree.
But I did this for a reason.