[English subtitles are available]
[Story of Yanxi Palace]
[Episode 35]
I hate my teacher.
He once showed me kindness.
But at the moment of life and death,
he pushed me out without any hesitation!
How could the respected Consort Xian...
do something so lowly?
Scoundrel! How dare you steal
from the palace in secret!
I didn't do anything wrong!
-Still deny it? You are doubly guilty now.
-I didn't do anything wrong!
And I hate this evil heaven more.
This laughable world.
What did I do wrong?
Why do I have to suffer so many hardships?
I have the same noble blood
as all of my other brothers.
Each and every one of them lives
a lofty life. But what about me?
I had to endure...
the greatest insults in this world...
and be the lowliest servant.
I have to crawl on the ground.
So, Ying Luo,
the ways of the heaven are unfair...
and the ways of the world are cruel.
If you don't want to become the prey,
you have to become the hunter.
But it's okay.
I'm your brother.
Sister,
I, Yuan Chun Wang, swear that...
I will protect you.
Because...
Because we are one.
You are me...
and I am you.
Consort Chun.
Yu Hu, go and keep guard outside.
Yes, Your Highness.
Your Highness, why did you ask for me?
Why are you marrying Er Qing?
-This is His Majesty's edict.
-No!
You agreed to this marriage...
to save Wei Ying Luo...
and clear her name.
Just for a servant in Labour House.
Is it worth it?
This is my personal matter.
No need to concern yourself with it.
Fu Heng!
You really don't remember me?
Consort Chun, what are you talking about?
Your sister and I are close friends
even before we got married.
In the past,
I had always gone to Fuca Mansion to play.
[Jing Hao, what do you want to eat later?]
[I'll ask the kitchen staff
to prepare it.]
[Mung bean pastry!]
-[What about snow fungus soup?]
-[Sure!]
[Jing Hao.]
[Miss.]
[Fu Heng!]
-[Sister.]
-[Accompany me to...]
[the tea house at Zhengyang Street
for an opera tomorrow.]
[I also want to go to the jewellery store
at Xiceli Street.]
[Don't forget about it. Another thing.]
[Let's go for a horse ride
the day after tomorrow.]
[Later, go to the stable
to check on Comet for me.]
[I remember.]
[Look at your pendant.
It's so old already.]
[I'll make you a new one tomorrow.]
[Jing Hao, let's go.]
My sister had a lot of close friends
before she was married.
I don't remember you.
I don't believe it.
If you don't remember me,
why do you keep wearing
the pendant I gave you?
Wasn't this from my sister?
[Miss, let's go.]
[Hold on.]
Your Highness,
if there is nothing else,
I'll take my leave now.
Your Highness,
Fu Heng is an unfaithful man.
Why can't you forget about him?
Yes,
No matter how good he is,
you have already entered the palace
and became a consort.
You should focus on being in His Majesty's
favour and stabilising your position.
But instead, you keep defending...
Her Majesty for him...
to the point of avoiding His Majesty.
But what did you get in the end?
He has never placed you in his heart.
Everything that you did is meaningless.
Shut up!
I really can't take it anymore.
Even if you don't want to hear it,
I have to tell you about it.
You're an intelligent person.
But why are you so foolish
when it comes to him?
Stop being sad for him.
Stop doing stupid things, okay?
I asked you to stop! Get out!
Stop right there.
Your Highness.
Where's that letter of mine?
Back then,
I asked you to give Fu Heng a letter.
[Remember. You must personally
hand this letter to him.]
I did it for your sake.
All this time, I thought that...
he accepted that pendant...
because he had feelings for me.
But because I went into
Prince Bao Mansion...
and became a princess there,
he deliberately distanced himself from me.
But all along,
that love letter of mine...
has never reached him!
Why?
Why did you do it?
-Tell me, why?
-Your Highness!
Master had long decided that...
that he was going to marry you
to Prince Bao.
You were always destined to enter
the prince mansion.
If I gave that letter to him,
it would have destroyed you
and the Su family!
So, you just watched...
while I fell deeper and deeper
into this sinkhole...
and kept on deceiving myself!
And then, you watched while I...
lost all of my dignity
in front of him, right?
Your Highness.
You were so obsessed with Fu Heng.
You even refused to enter
the prince mansion...
at the expense of your life.
Only when you knew that Miss Fuca
would be married to Prince Bao...
did you agree to enter the mansion too.
You said that you'd
accompany and protect her...
on behalf of Fu Heng.
I saw how you pulled yourself
together again.
How could I bear to tell you the truth?
I just wished for you to feel
the same way as I do for you.
Then, you wouldn't disappoint me
for the affection that I have for you.
I saw him...
wearing that pendant every day.
I thought that...
he had some feelings towards me too.
Yu Hu,
I didn't ask for much.
I didn't even need him to love me.
I just hoped that...
he would remember
and think about my love for him.
And that would be enough.
But,
since the very beginning,
Fu Heng didn't know anything.
He didn't understand anything!
All the protections that I had given
to Her Majesty all these years...
and my infatuation for so many years...
are just a joke!
Do you know that?
Your Highness.
Do you know how painful my heart is?
Do you know who much pain am I in?
You don't know!
This kind of delusion...
is the greatest kind of humiliation!
Your Highness.
I only mean well for you, Your Highness.
My name can be easily changed.
But no one has ever cherished your heart.
You've been foolish for ten years.
It's time to wake up.
Greetings, Noble Consort Xian.
Your Highness,
quickly wipe away your tears.
You mustn't let anyone notice anything.
Your Highness,
even if it's not for yourself,
think about Su family and your siblings.
Consort Chun, what important matter do you
have that kept me waiting for so long?
Noble Consort Xian.
We are sisters who get along well.
No need to be bothered with
this pretentious etiquette.
Just address me like how you used to.
Yes, Your Highness.
Why are you here today?
Why are you looking at me like this?
Bring her in.
This old servant is such a greenhorn.
She blurted out everything
after just a few beatings.
Consort Chun,
do you want to know what she said?
Your Highness,
vile slaves like her often
slander someone over measly things.
But when they are interrogated,
they can't wait to blame others for it.
You can't believe any words she said.
Yu Hu, don't deny it.
Consort Chun is the one who
ordered me to frame Wei Ying Luo.
-This is really Consort Chun's doing!
-Rubbish!
Her Highness has no grudge
against that palace maid.
Why would she frame her?
You were clearly instructed
by someone else.
But you are accusing Consort Chun instead.
Consort Chun, what do you have to say?
Sister,
this is slander.
I know very well
what kind of a person you are.
I won't allow you to slander Consort Chun!
Guards!
Cut off her tongue.
No!
Servant like her who speaks evils of
another and slanders her mistress...
should be punished severely
to serve as a reminder to everyone.
From now on,
no one will dare disrespect
their superiors,
speak nonsense and slander
their mistresses anymore.
Thank you for your trust in me.
Why are your hands so cold?
Did I scare you earlier?
Take her out!
Sister, your body have always been
weaker and you are afraid of cold.
Now, the weather is getting cold.
You must take good care of your health.
Yes, Your Highness.
She has changed.
Noble Consort Xian has changed
into another person.
Your Highness.
No matter what,
we've safely survived it.
No.
She knows.
I have an intuition that...
she knows everything.
It's true.
What is she doing?
I don't know. Let's go and have a look.
-You scared me!
-What are you doing?
-Getting ready to ridicule someone.
-What?
You don't know yet.
Wei Ying Luo has gotten really hurt
for trying to climb the social ladder.
I'm waiting to watch her cry.
What are you doing?
She said that she's here to ridicule you.
You!
Let go of me.
-What are you doing? Let go of me!
-Don't you want to laugh?
Sure. Let me help you.
-Laugh!
-You're hurting me!
Wei Ying Luo, let go of me!
Wei Ying Luo, let me tell you.
Lord Fuca is about to marry
another woman soon!
Just continue acting tough!
Before you laugh at me,
try rubbing your own stomach.
Isn't it empty?
It's already noon now.
If our chief finds out that
you are all loafing on your job,
there'll be no lunch for you.
You can't even fill your own stomach, yet,
you have the leisure to ridicule others.
Let's go now!
Let's go.
You're really a cold-hearted woman!
Yes.
I'm indeed cold-hearted.
Do you still want to laugh?
I'll help you.
Laugh!
Let go of me! You crazy woman!
What are you laughing at?
I wonder who was the one
that cried so much yesterday...
and has to wash her eyes
early in the morning today.
Are you afraid they'll find out that
you cried from your swollen eyes?
I cried because I was upset.
But by letting others see me cry,
I'll just get a cold shoulder.
It's meaningless.
Are you not upset anymore?
I still have to work and eat
even if I'm upset.
After I'm done being upset,
I should do what I should.
I wonder who was the one that cried
to the point of fainting yesterday.
Was it you?
Those who abandoned me
are just a past to me now.
We should never hold on to the past.
No matter how upset I am,
I have to tell myself that...
it's fine.
Because one day,
I will definitely have something better.
Great! That's the spirit.
Brother Yuan,
I know who killed Noble Consort Gao.
Her Majesty is awake.
Her Majesty is awake!
Guards!
Your Majesty!
Yu are finally awake, Your Majesty!
I want to get up.
Ming Yu.
My legs.
-Calm down, Your Majesty.
-What happened to my legs?
I'll call for the imperial physician
at once. He will be here soon!
Don't call for the physician.
Ask Fu Heng to come here.
I want to see him.
Tell him to come here.
All of you,
come over here.
Do you know that
Jin Xiu ran away last night?
Ran away? She actually ran away?
The Forbidden City is heavily guarded.
-Where can she escape to?
-That girl is too bold.
-Isn't she afraid to die?
-Listen to me carefully.
If you have any news about her,
you have to report it to me.
Or else, you will be punished
for being her accomplice.
Alright now. End of discussion.
Go back to work.
That girl is so audacious.
-Doesn't she want to live anymore?
-That's right.
Brother!
Look for her over there first.
Go.
What is it?
Has Jin Xiu really gone missing?
When did I say that she has gone missing?
She ran away last night.
If she had planned on running away,
why weren't there any signs before this?
Moreover, Forbidden City
is heavily guarded.
She doesn't have wings.
Where can she go?
How is that your business?
Look at the wounds on your hand.
Your hands are soaked in water every day.
Your wounds will only get worse.
No.
I can't let you stay here anymore.
-Go to the Heating Department instead.
-Heating Department?
The Heating Department
is under the Fuel House.
They are in charge of supplying fuel
to all palaces.
It's not yet winter.
They don't need to supply the charcoal.
So, they might have a lighter workload.
Use this chance to rest.
Don't be so diligent
in your work from now on.
You must learn how to slack off. Got that?
Fine. I got it.
-Jin Xiu...
-Stop mentioning her. Come.
Remember to apply the medicine
I gave you every day.
You mustn't skip it for even a day.
Do you hear me?
As for those matters that
don't concern you,
no need to be bothered with them.
Let's go.
Your Majesty, you're finally awake.
I was really worried.
I could hear everything you said...
all the time.
I just...
couldn't open my eyes.
It was like...
being trapped in a dark nightmare.
I couldn't wake up.
Now,
everything has passed.
Your Majesty.
You need not worry.
Ye Tian Shi already said that you can't...
move your legs because
you were unconscious for too long.
But you'll be able to recover
for sure after some time.
Sister!
Greetings, Your Majesty!
Your Majesty.
I still have state affairs to attend to.
I have to return to Yangxin Hall.
I'll accompany you again at night.
-Fu Heng.
-Yes, Your Majesty.
-Keep your sister company.
After talking to her,
come to Yangxin Palace to see me.
I still have a task for you.
Her Majesty just woke up.
Don't exhaust her.
Sister.
Where's Er Qing?
You are so foolish!
If I didn't agree with the marriage
bestowed by His Majesty,
I wouldn't be able to save Ying Luo.
With Ying Luo's personality,
she would rather
go through death with you.
Do you know that...
from the moment you said yes,
she will never forgive you?
Are you really ready...
to part with her forever?
This matter is too unfair...
for you,
for Ying Luo...
and for Er Qing.
No matter how high a price I must pay,
I will beg His Majesty
to take back his decree.
Sister,
the decree has been promulgated.
Er Qing has already left the palace
to prepare for the wedding.
There's no going back.
If you beg His Majesty
to retract his decree,
you'll just destroy
the reputation of Fuca family...
and Er Qing will lose her dignity.
You'll force her to death.
Besides, she agreed to this marriage...
just to help me.
In terms of friendship and righteousness,
I can't do this to her.
At first, I thought that...
at the very least,
you and Ying Luo...
could find your happiness together.
I never thought that...
the ending is still the same.
-Sister.
-Leave.
-I don't want to see you.
-Sister.
Just leave.
Fu Heng!
This is about your lifetime of happiness.
Have you really made up your mind?
Yes.
I'm really worried about you.
You will regret this
for the rest of your life.
Sister,
everyone must take responsibility
for their own decision.
Please forgive me.
Greetings, Your Highnesses.
Her Majesty just woke up.
The imperial physician said that
she can't receive any visitors yet.
I will inform Her Majesty
about your kind visit.
Please go back first.
Her Majesty doesn't want to
see me either?
I thought that the rumours are fake.
Looks like they are not
groundless rumours.
Rumours?
Haven't you heard?
Her Majesty is against the marriage
of Imperial Guard Fuca.
She is gloomy all day long.
She doesn't even want to see
His Majesty now.
But no matter what, this is
a familial matter of Fuca family.
It's right for Her Majesty to be worried.
If you are free, why not spend
some time with me at my palace?
I would love to do that.
Your Majesty, eat something.
Your Majesty!
Leave us.
No matter what is
your reason for being angry,
you shouldn't punish your body for it.
-You're here.
-Yes.
I'm here.
But it's very obvious that...
your mind...
is no longer here.
Your Majesty.
Can you tell me...
what is it that you are thinking about?
Your Majesty,
I'm begging you.
Can you cancel the marriage
that you've bestowed in Fu Heng?
Impossible.
Since you've already said no,
I have nothing more to say.
Your Majesty,
I don't understand.
Er Qing is elegant, composed,
good-looking and intelligent.
Her grandfather is the minister
of the Ministry of Justice.
I even raised the status
of her whole family.
No matter it's in terms of
personality or status,
she is not unworthy of Fu Heng.
Everyone is happy about it.
Why are you the only one
who is upset about it?
Everyone is happy?
Your Majesty.
Do you really think so?
Isn't that true?
Your Majesty,
you are the ruler of this empire.
Every word you speak
is as precious as gold.
No one would dare disobey you.
I've been attending to you for many years.
I want to...
ask you one question.
Why do you have to break apart...
Fu Heng and the woman he loves?
I already said it many times.
She's not worthy of him.
Your Majesty. Fu Heng doesn't even care...
whether she is worthy or not.
But why do you care?
One must choose a virtuous wife.
Fu Heng is the right-hand man I chose.
He will be of great use in the future.
I won't allow him...
to have a sinister and manipulative wife.
I'm protecting him...
from being seduced by a vicious woman...
and committing
the biggest mistake in his life.
What are you laughing at?
Didn't you do it out of
your own selfish motives?
What selfish motives do I have?
Perhaps...
you've taken a liking to Wei Ying Luo...
and wants her for yourself.
Your Majesty, have you been
unconscious for too long...
until your brain is fuzzy now?
Let me tell you.
This is just your delusion.
A crazy delusion!
Your Majesty!
-Your Majesty.
-I beg you.
-This will never happen.
Your Majesty, Fu Heng is not someone
who can have a change of heart so easily.
Or else, I wouldn't have interfered.
I'm his sister. I know him.
Your Majesty. You are wealthy
and do not lack any women.
I'm begging you.
Can you be magnanimous...
and let him marry the one he loves?
Your Majesty!
Get the Imperial Academy of Medicine
to treat her.
She has to recuperate from her illness.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, why did you do it?
There's no turning back now.
Fu Heng is my most important
family member.
I thought that...
at least the both of them could be happy.
But...
Your Majesty.
Miss Ming Yu, what do you want?
Her Majesty is so heartbroken
because of Imperial Guard Fuca.
But he is totally indifferent.
-How could he do that?
-This marriage is bestowed by His Majesty.
What do you expect him to do?
Go against the decree?
I...
What is it? You have
no retort for that, right?
Stop giving him a hard time.
You men are all useless creatures!
How could you just kick me?
You didn't give me any warning at all.
Miss Ming Yu,
why are you crying over
Fu Heng's marriage?
I'm angry.
I'm sad.
Why are you angry and sad?
I'm angry because Fuca Fu Heng
didn't fight harder for it.
I'm sad...
because I regret being
infatuated with him in the past.
What are you laughing at?
-Come with me.
-Where are we going?
We are almost there. Be careful.
Where are you taking me?
Come here, Miss Ming Yu.
Miss Ming Yu, take a look.
No matter what worries you have,
climb to a high place
and take in the view.
It'll make you feel better...
and all of your worries will be gone.
What do you know?
People in a bad mood might
want to jump down from here...
to end everything.
Didn't you want to die?
Let me fulfil your wish.
Why are you holding on to me so tightly?
You are a lunatic!
I was just citing an example.
Just an example. Understand?
I don't like Fuca Fu Heng now.
I won't kill myself just because
he's getting married.
Looks like a woman's heart
changes very quickly.
Before this, you even
gave him a perfume pouch.
You don't like him now?
I just feel outraged for Ying Luo.
How could Fuca Fu Heng have
a change of heart without any signs?
I just feel outraged for Her Majesty too.
She's trying so hard to help her brother
until the point of defying His Majesty.
But in the end, no one is grateful at all.
Miss Ming Yu.
As humans, is love
the only thing worth pursuing?
A good man should aspire
for greater things.
Why should they be tied down by love?
You sound so righteous.
What do you want to do then?
Me?
I want to fight on the battlefield.
I want to make contributions
to the nation.
I want to go down in history.
-You don't want a family of your own?
-Yes, I don't.
One can die at any time
on the battlefield.
If I'm alive, my wife will have to
live alone for years and years to come.
It'll be even more terrible if I die.
She will become a widow.
Dead or alive,
it'll still be a disaster.
I want to live happily all by myself.
One day, I will lead hundreds of thousands
of mounted and foot soldiers...
to bring victories to Great Qing.
Miss Ming Yu,
don't be sad for what you have lost.
When you look back at it ten years later,
it will just be a minor thing.
Smile and everything will pass.
You are right.
-What are you doing?
-You pushed me and I stepped on your foot.
We are even now.
Smile and everything will pass.
You are really something.
You are not young anymore.
You should start planning for yourself.
Life is lonely in the palace.
If you have a son...
No, a daughter will be good too.
You'll lead a happier life.
When you wake up...
and hear your child's laughter or cries
every day, even a bigger palace...
will become very lively in an instant.
I know you are loyal to Her Majesty.
But there aren't many offsprings
in the harem.
And Her Majesty is...
What's wrong with Her Majesty?
Physician Zhang said that
Her Majesty has ruined her health.
So, it'll be even harder for her
to bear any child again.
Why did I talk about this.
I have caused you to worry.
Yong Cheng.
Come, this is for you.
You like this one?
The fourth prince is really
lively and adorable.
Come. Over here.
Your hair is messy.
Let me comb it for you.
-Zhen, take Yong Cheng out.
-Yes, Your Majesty.
You are beautiful,
outstanding and talented.
If you are willing to work on it,
it'll still not too late for you.
No matter how well Her Majesty
treats you and how lenient she is to you,
she still can't live your life for you.
You are young and beautiful now.
But year after year,
if...
beautiful women continue to
flood the palace,
your beauty will wane along with your age.
One year,
ten years, twenty years.
We are trapped inside this palace...
and have to live a lonely and boring life.
If...
you don't have a child of your own,
your life in the future
will be cold and lonely.
You might not be able to accept
what I'm saying now in the past.
But now...
Did I hurt you?
Remember this.
Pain will wake you up to your senses.