Over here! Over here!
Come over here and give me the baby.
Hurry! Hurry!
Thank you!
I lost my baby.
I thought you knew what kind of man Lee Hoon Seok is,
and yet, I thought you recommended me for that position.
That's why I wanted to take revenge on you.
That's why I did that.
I'm sorry, Sunbae.
I'll take...
that baby.
I heard you're being chased.
Why don't we...
protect that baby?
So the child that Cha Min Joon brought back from Canada
is Chairman Kim's son?
After Dr. Park stopped by Chairman Kim's residence,
he rushed a DNA test.
And if you look at the page after that...
It's a form to request a change of paternity rights that Mr. Cha submitted.
I took care of Cha Yi Yeon and the baby.
It means he didn't get rid of them then.
How is Chairman Kim handling matters regarding the child?
He's making sure no one leaks information on the child.
He's not ready to make the news public.
Don't leave anyone out and let me know who Chairman Kim meets with.
Yes, ma'am.
Hae Ra, are you here?
Gosh, where did she go?
Kang Hae Ra, where are you right now?
What?
Director Kim Tae On...
must be pissed off at Chairman Kim and you.
What are you going to do now?
Now that Director Kim is fuming,
she'll loosen up her dogs.
I'll catch that dog then.
There's trouble.
Hae Ra saw Mr. Hong's accident video clip and went to meet Kang.
I recorded you.
Damn it!
It's no use.
I'll tell the world that you killed Mr. Hong.
I should've...
finished you off then.
Crazy bastard.
Are you okay?
I'm sure Kang was recorded on the CCTV.
Before he gets rid of it first, hurry up and get the recording.
Why are you so reckless?
What if something happens to you? How about Ga On?
I said...
I said I'd wrap up everything!
I'm begging you. Please be careful.
Do you know how scared I get whenever you do this?
When I'm feeling this way,
what about Mr. Cha?
What about Mr. Cha?
"What about Mr. Cha?"
Forget it.
If you're not concerned about Mr. Cha worrying about you,
fine then, Ga On.
Consider Ga On and please...
How did it go?
The investigation will go on with assault and attempted murder charges.
I mean...
even after you told them that
Kang is the culprit and tried to stop me from uploading the video?
Since the truck driver already turned himself in,
just because he was at the accident scene
doesn't provide direct proof.
Then what kind of proof do we need to provide?
I'll look into it further.
We'll make sure to lock up. Don't worry.
The two of us are together.
And I'll put this next to her pillow.
I think we should install extra alarms.
Oh, I'll call someone for that early in the morning.
It's late. Go home and get some rest.
Okay. See you tomorrow.
I'll text you a list of security companies.
Call me if anything comes up.
Okay. Be careful going home.
You still don't get it?
Get some rest.
My gosh.
- Yes.
- We're ready for the meeting.
Okay.
Let's begin.
Chairman Kim of FB Life personally visited insurance agents who got into the accident
- and gave compensation money—
- Just go with that.
Next.
If FB Group companies switch over as holding companies,
how about we talk about the synergy that will affect—
Did we get all of our stories from the FB PR team today?
Well, not all of them...
Then you didn't get rid of them both.
No, I definitely got rid of them.
If you got rid of them, how could Cha Yi Hyeon's child be alive?
- I definitely...
- Chairman Kim found Cha Yi Hyeon's kid.
And Kang Hae Ra had raised that kid all this time!
Damn it!
Hyungnim.
Around Gusan Agency's building,
the security tightened, and more CCTVs are installed.
I don't think we can enter easily.
And last night,
that lawyer bastard came with cops
so the building manager had to turn over the CCTV video.
There are more patrols around the building as well.
Kang Hae Ra, I should've gotten rid of that wench then.
Where are you going?
Huh?
To the restroom.
Aren't you going to the law firm for a meeting?
My gosh, no way.
I'm going to the restroom.
With your notebook?
I'll go with you.
Hae Ra.
After we posted the video clip of the insurance agents
and thanks to your news appearance,
FB Life withdrew the right of indemnity lawsuits
and gave them compensation money.
I think you've done enough on that.
Including what happened yesterday, I'm worried about you.
As for compensation, the agents got what they deserved.
But nothing on Mr. Hong has been resolved.
I heard Kang works for FB Life.
Didn't you quit working on the FB case because of Ga On?
Mr. Hong's death is a separate matter.
If his death was intentional,
I can't let it get buried this way.
And if Chairman Kim was behind it,
I can't let him be around Ga On.
What's wrong with you guys?
Shouldn't I do anything from now on?
Do you think Gusan Agency is a safe place?
If Kang wanted to,
he can break into anywhere he wants to.
And Hyung Sung. He was able to come in looking for me.
Geez, why bring me up?
I wasn't really trying to hurt you then.
I know.
You were trembling then.
What?
You were trembling?
No, I wasn't.
No, I didn't tremble.
"Yeah, Kang Hae Ra, I won't let you off easy."
"I'm from hell to take my revenge on you!"
Were you like this?
No, I didn't.
The police are out to get him,
and Prosecutor Jang is working on the case, not just us.
You don't have to step forward, Hae Ra.
What you did last night was enough.
We couldn't catch him at the organ auction.
He won't be afraid just because his identity was revealed.
More than anything,
he's like a demon who caused an accident to kill someone.
I can't let him off this way.
Then we'll work on the ground.
Why don't you back us up from the office?
While working on the content on Kang.
I'm so worried about you.
You fought off Kang last night,
and you revealed his wrongdoing on VTube.
I'm afraid he won't leave you alone.
I feel the same way about that.
If you're working on the ground,
I'd be worried and won't be able to focus.
If you're all so worried about me,
I'll work on video content on Kang.
But be sure to share with me your progress on this case.
Then let's begin our meeting.
The police are investigating, and since he's committed a crime,
I think they'll try to smuggle out of the country.
I know someone who knows a smuggling broker in Incheon.
I'm thinking of going to Incheon.
He ran away all of a sudden.
He could stop by his office or his home.
Eun Hye, I think you should stake out in front of Kang's office.
Do you think he'd come back?
They say, "The foot of the candle is dark."
As Mr. Cha said, he ran off all of a sudden.
It's highly possible that he'll come back.
Then I'll stake out in front of Happy Credit building.
If they notice anything in Incheon, I'll ask him to call me.
I'll call you right away when I hear from him.
Okay.
I know where Choi might show up.
I'll go around the area.
The list of credit agencies that Kang runs.
I'll get it soon.
Please monitor that area, Hyun Sung.
Okay.
I'll monitor one of those places.
Okay, let's move then.
I'll rattle Director Kim from the inside.
You keep your eyes on her movements.
I'm sure she'll meet up with Kang again.
Okay.
But you won't tell Gusan Agency people
about Director Kim Tae On, will you?
I don't want anyone else getting hurt or victimized.
Get Gusan Agency people's help while keeping them out of danger.
Let's take care of Kang ourselves first.
Okay.
I know Assemblyman Kim.
Who's this again?
His name is Bae Young Tak. He's from the Shipping Association.
Someone from the Shipping Association?
Meeting Assembly Kim and someone from the Shipping Association means...
And Chairman Kim wants to see you in his office.
Yeah.
Sit down.
I called you in because I wanted to talk to both of you.
I'd like to talk about switching over to holding companies,
and I think...
we should restructure the group governance.
Director Cha had some good ideas.
I thought we'd hear him out together.
Director Cha's good ideas?
Go ahead and tell us.
Okay.
FB Group's Financial companies
are pretty solid overall.
The problem is with the general affiliates.
Among them, distribution affiliates especially need restructuring.
I was wondering if you could take charge of restructuring distribution affiliates.
I also heard about it just now.
I think it's a pretty good idea.
So I was thinking...
why don't you check out the Chinese market, Tae On?
For the past ten years, FB Distribution
has invested over one trillion won in the Chinese market.
If you withdraw like this now,
FB Group will have to take all the loss.
While all the Korean corporations are withdrawing,
you want me to go to China now?
That's why now is a good opportunity.
While other corporations are withdrawing,
why don't you go there and make the distribution business a success?
This is a great opportunity for you to show off your ability.
Why don't you go for about two years?
I'll do that then.
The Chinese market is important.
In return, the Global Strategy team leader position.
Please appoint Seung Woo oppa for the position.
I'll make him turn himself in.
Please work with the Prosecutors' Office
so that he won't be arrested during the investigation.
Aunt is thinking of selling off FB Life shares she owns.
At this point, if her share is sold off,
the outsiders will think that
there are internal conflicts
due to switching over to holding companies.
It's not like I haven't thought about it.
Global Strategy team leader...
I guess Seung Woo will be good for the position.
I can send away Tae On to China.
Oh, yeah.
Sungmyung Shipping.
They got their business license this year.
Are you trying to import vessels?
But...
they're all used vessels.
What if...
they were all new vessels, how much more would I need?
Make that document...
worth 100 billion won.
He's turning secondhand vessels...
into new vessels?
Is this really our building?
I said yes.
Can't you tell by looking at the paperwork?
It says "Goo Sung Chul" as the owner right there.
Wow!
Then you're a "lord."
Lord?
A landlord.
Lord!
Wow, daebak!
Yes, Uncle, it's me.
I was wondering if you looked into what I asked about last time.
To find out who the building was auctioned off to,
do you need the building number?
I have a copy at the office.
Yes.
Can I take a picture of it with my cellphone and send it?
I'll do that right away then.
Okay.
Yeah.
Hi, are you at the office?
Can I ask you a favor?
Yeah, what is it?
Inside the black cabinet in the pantry,
somewhere in there...
there's a copy of building ownership paper.
Can you find that and take a picture
of the building number and send it to me?
Okay, got it.
Was it about ten years ago?
When a huge lawsuit landed on him,
he lost this building and our house.
It took only a moment for that energetic man to crumble.
October 19, 2009?
Welcome.
What brings you here?
I was going to visit you because I was worried.
But Eun Hye stopped me, so I was holding back.
Are you okay?
What's this?
Where did you get that?
It's that place, right?
Then, because of that incident,
you lost your house and Gusan building?
Why didn't you tell me?
It's all been taken care of.
I heard you went through a lot.
Everyone's life has ups and downs.
Don't tell Eun Hye.
She'll just be disturbed.
Chairman Kim started the shipping business again.
Did he ask you to fabricate the document?
If things go wrong, Chairman Kim
turns over only the people who are involved and get them arrested in his place.
I hope you don't get too deep into this.
I must find out everything on how he committed
his corruptions and
how he managed to cover them up.
That's how I can destroy him.
But still. What if you can't get yourself out of it?
Did you talk to Prosecutor Jang?
It's not easy to find the fugitive only with CCTV,
so he ordered stakeout at a few offices that Kang visits often.
When they catch Kang, along with the video on Kang Hae Ra's camera
and the CCTV from Happy Credit,
they should be able to get to the bottom of the accident Kang caused, right?
We'll have to make sure we do that.
Why don't you check out the Chinese market?
Why don't you go for about two years?
- Did you get him on the phone?
- Yes.
- It's me.
- What's up?
Turn yourself into the Prosecutors' Office tomorrow.
What?
You can't hide out forever.
This is all your fault.
Chairman Kim told me to go to China.
So I suggested your return to headquarters.
The team leader of the Global Strategy Team.
Once you turn yourself in,
I asked him to make sure you're not investigated under custody.
We can't keep taking it like this.
And...
we should pay back Cha Min Joon, too.
The Global Strategy team leader is
an executive position.
Do you think that sly Chairman Kim would do that?
So just in case...
you have to prepare something for me.
What is it?
The leash Aunt has...
on my father.
Here's the document we discussed.
Mom didn't want to give it to me saying, it's her leash on Chairman Kim.
But I managed to convince her. It was tough to get it from her.
By chance...
you're not planning on exposing the shipping industry scandal, are you?
Mom and aunts...
There's a reason why they're turning a blind eye.
Don't worry.
I won't burn down the house
just to catch a mouse.
Then why do you need this document out of the blue?
Chairman Kim...
is importing vessels again.
I'm sure they aren't good vessels this time, either.
Why would he?
As for 11 years ago, he needed money
to buy shares to become the chairman.
He doesn't need to do that anymore.
All the assets he owns...
he won't be able to spend everything until the day he dies.
Why would he take such a risk now?
There's no way that Chairman Kim...
is after your shares
that are tied to the foundation, is he?
No way?
It's checkmate.
I lost.
Who taught you chess?
My mom.
I see.
Ms. Tae On is here.
I'll take Ga On upstairs.
Tae On is here?
No.
They'll meet at some point.
Your older sister will be here soon.
- Noona?
- Yeah.
What's going on?
Say hi.
Your younger brother.
Your older sister I told you earlier.
Say hi.
Hello.
Who is that kid?
Cha Yi Hyeon had a son.
My son.
So you want to bring him into the family?
Yeah.
Why?
Sit down.
My neck hurts.
I now know why people want a child
in their older years.
The kid...
sure has me wrapped around his fingers.
He even has cuteness that
I couldn't even see in you, as a daughter.
I guess he takes after his mom, who wrapped her legs around anyone.
Do you even know Cha Yi Hyeon?
Do I have to see her to know her?
This is a good thing for you, too.
A good thing?
That child...
is your younger brother.
If you get along with him,
he'll help you out later,
and you'll be able to depend on him.
Depend on him?
I'm saying he's a thousand times better than
your mom's side of the family
who want crumbs off of you.
I'll raise him well...
so be good and depend on each other.
Be a good example as his older sister.
So be good.
Gosh, I'm tired.
I'll get some rest now.
It's late.
You should get going now.
I heard Cha Min Joon is Cha Yi Hyeon's younger brother.
People's connections are so interesting.
I had no idea then that woman's younger brother will be working for you.
So when it comes to relationships,
you can never burn the bridge
nor can you trust someone too much.
And without that child,
you would've been played by Cha Min Joon.
And you would've endangered FB Group.
If you don't stay alert from now on,
even if you're my daughter,
remember that I can't trust you with anything.
- That's all. Thank you.
- Thank you.
- Sure. See you again.
Call Kang.
Yes, ma'am.
Pardon?
Including that lawyer?
Then talk to the police and...
release the cops staking out...
After the sloppy job you've done,
are you asking for me to clean up after you?
Get rid of Kang Hae Ra and Cha Min Joon right now.
Right now!
There are cops everywhere.
Under the circumstances, getting rid of Kang Hae Ra and that lawyer
is impossible.
I think that lawyer has a connection at the Prosecutors' Office.
She doesn't have our backs, yet asking us to do this...
Do you think she's making us take the fall?
If we get caught doing this,
she'll make us take all the blame for everything.
So I was thinking...
how about we lay low for a while?
You said that Director Kim is off the rails.
I think we should run away for now.
I'll find out...
if we can smuggle out of the country tonight from Incheon.
Mr. Cha.
I got a call from a friend in Incheon.
He got a call asking to smuggle out two adult men to China.
But the people who called him are in the money lending business.
I'm pretty sure it must be Kang.
At what time?
At 2 a.m.
I'll call Prosecutor Jang and ask him to send his team over.
You never know. I'll go to Incheon.
What?
What if you bump into Kang there?
You don't stand a chance.
I was just...
He's worried about you.
He's so skilled at speaking not so nicely.
If you're that worried, go with him.
Should I?
Then you two go together.
Kang can come by to pick up his car or stop by his office.
I'll go to the Happy Credit office.
Okay.
Bastard...
Hey, what the hell is with you?
I'll show you where you belong.
Damn it!
The police will arrive soon.
Tell me where Cha Yi Hyeon is before then.
Who? Cha Yi Hyeon?
Cha Yi Hyeon you chased off to Gunsan.
Oh, that... that Chairman Kim's second woman?
Why? Was she yours to begin with?
Tell me what happened to my noona!
Your sister...
Why are you looking for your sister now?
Okay, okay, okay!
Your sister...
Damn it!
Get in here!
I didn't think you'd be like this.
I had no idea you'd run off abandoning your kids.
That's not it...
The police are everywhere right now.
I was going to take care of them after things calmed down.
Dad?
Dad.
Yeah, yeah.
Princess!
Yeah, I'm fine.
Your mom and your sister are well, right?
But just a moment ago...
- your friend brought us a gift.
- What?
My friend?
Just a moment.
Your friend wants to talk to you.
Keep your eye on them for a while.
I'll call you if there are any changes.
Even if you have to leave,
you should wrap up everything.
Isn't that right?
What are you going to do now?
Hyungnim.
I think...
that lawyer has Kang Hae Ra's back.
You think I don't know that?
What I'm saying is...
I think Kang Hae Ra exposed Happy Credit
plotting with that bastard.
The police and Prosecutors' Office raided us at the scene.
Kang Hae Ra couldn't have that kind of power.
All the local police were on our side.
Kang Hae Ra isn't working alone...
but they're working as a team.
That tall girl from Gusan Agency and...
that blond hair and the lawyer's guy.
I think they're a team.
Gusan Agency?
Yeah.
What? They're not coming?
All right.
Eun Hye sunbae got a call from the smuggling broker.
Those two men who were to be smuggled said they're not leaving.
Then I'll turn the car around.
Drop me off around here.
Wouldn't it be better to go back to Gusan Agency?
If Choi didn't smuggle out,
he might show up at one of the offices.
I'll continue to stake out.
- See you later.
- Hey.
Be careful.
You be careful, Hyung.
Yes, Hyung. Where are you?
What?
Stay there. I'll be right there.
Hyung.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine. How is it going with Kang?
We got a call from Goo Eun Hye
saying that they canceled all of a sudden.
Where are Gusan Agency people?
Hyun Sung went looking for Choi.
Goo Eun Hye is staking out at Happy Credit.
Kang Hae Ra is probably at the Gusan Agency office.
By chance, did this guy stop by?
No.
All right.
Thank you.
Geez, let me go to the restroom.
Hey, rookie.
I heard you were desperately looking for me.
I missed you so much, too.
Since we desperately wanted to meet, here we are.
What the hell are you talking about?
Your face...
You keep snickering, not knowing your place.
I wanted to make sure you can't go around with your head up.
You're dead meat today.
Won't he come by the office?
Why?
You were waiting for me so desperately.
Happy to see me?
Your dad, Goo Sung Chul.
Your dad is so worried about you.
If you have time to chase other people,
be good to your dad.
What?
Why don't you call your dad?
Dad.
Eun Hye, where are you?
Dad, what's wrong?
I heard you got hurt and is in the hospital.
Tell me which hospital. I'll be right over.
I guess he wants to come running since it's about his daughter.
Are you ready?
Yes.
I'll run him over as soon as you tell me.
What are you doing right now?
Eun Hye, what's wrong?
Are you okay? Huh?
Dad. Dad...
Dad! Dad!
What?
Should I run him over?
You crazy bastard!
If I see you one more time,
I won't be polite as to explain like this then.
That scum bag.
Hyun Sung, what happened?
Where did you go?
I thought something had happened to you, too.
This happened to him while chasing after Choi.
Let's go to the ER first.
It's okay.
I know myself.
What's wrong with you?
I think I should visit my dad.
Kang found out Dad's number somehow and had him come out...
- Eun Hye!
- Dad.
What happened? Are you all right?
Dad, what happened to you?
This...
What the heck is this?
Your dad is dying trying to pay off his debt.
Yet the daughter is playing detective.
If I see you one more time,
forget his debt.
I'll turn over your dad to the lumber yard.
Just know that.
I thought you paid off all the debt.
You still had more?
You don't have to worry.
How can I not worry?
Do you know how cruel that Kang is?
Of all people, why Kang?
Actually...
the warehouse that caught on fire belonged to Kang.
Even after turning over the building,
I still owed Kang.
I had no choice but to write that note.
What?
That warehouse was...
Kang's warehouse?
What are you talking about?
That warehouse belonged to Kang?
That's why Kang filed the right of indemnity lawsuit against you?
Wait a minute.
What fire?
Eleven years ago, I asked Mr. Goo
to go to Gunsan to look for a sunbae.
He said he found her, so I went there, too.
But Sunbae was trapped inside a warehouse on fire.
That's when I met Ga On for the first time.
Because of me, Mr. Goo...
went to that warehouse.
Then...
the client...
back then...
was you, Hae Ra?
I'm sorry...
for not telling you sooner.
Hae Ra also found out this afternoon that I was sued for
the right of indemnity over that fire.
At the time, Hae Ra couldn't afford to pay off the lawsuit.
She wanted to tell you about it.
But I told her not to disturb you.
Then...
the woman and the baby were trapped inside the warehouse.
And they set the place on fire with them inside?
I don't know if they started the fire intentionally.
But it's true that the woman and the baby were trapped inside.
Sunbae was trapped inside a warehouse on fire.
That's when I met Ga On for the first time.
I hadn't heard from you yet...
so I was wondering what was going on.
Chairman Kim will release news on the shipping contract insurance in the near future.
Please run that story extensively.
The news about Chairman Kim?
And along with that, I'd like a relevant article to spread.
It's about shipping insurance from 11 years ago.
Why did you give me this?
Eleven years ago, a shipping company imported vessels
and signed up for insurance with Sangil Fire Insurance.
Sangil Fire Insurance signed up for another insurance with FB Fire.
But a vessel from that shipping company got into an accident.
So when the accident occurred,
FB Fire must've paid off Sangil Fire Insurance.
That's right.
FB Fire Insurance that was covering for Sangil
paid quite a large sum to them.
The real owner of Sangil Fire Insurance
was Chairman Kim.
The shipping company responsible for the accident
was Chairman Kim's paper company.
You're saying the insurance compensation paid by FB Fire
ultimately ended up in Chairman Kim's pocket.
But not too long ago,
that shipping company changed its name and opened for business
and started importing vessels.
You're saying that company
recently signed up for insurance with FB Fire, right?
Is there any document related to the shipping company?
For now, I'd like the insurance scandal to go public.
This is the document you gave me last time.
You did a good job.
We have time for paperwork.
But I wonder if we can get past the customs.
You don't have to worry about that.
I have someone else for that job.
While Tae On is in China,
you just have to make sure things are moving smoothly.
Yes, I understand.
But...
Director Song Seung Woo. He'll be helping Director Kim.
Will you be okay with that?
The Global Strategy team leader is an executive position.
Director Kim's leave for China might not happen.
Do you think Seung Woo and her aunts
will stop Tae On from going to China?
When they find out Tae On is leaving for China,
they'll shout hooray with their arms raised.
Tae On's mom's side of the family...
might seem like they care about her.
They're circling around Tae On
to get something for themselves.
And she has no idea.
She thinks her maternal side is on her side
and teams up with Seung Woo.
Geez.
I want to split them up,
and that's why I'm telling her to go to China.
So you're doing that on purpose for Director Kim's sake.
In any case...
she's my daughter.
Tae On and Ga On both...
In order for them to survive this jungle,
they need to have power.
If not...
those hyenas will...
rip them apart...
and devour them.
All right. Shall we begin?
What?
I'd be offended even if Deputy Chief Ahn came in.
A low-level prosecutor like you will interrogate me?
I'm curious about that, too.
Why did I get assigned to this case out of the blue?
I went in because Deputy Chief Ahn summoned me in a hurry.
And he gives me this case.
What are you trying to pull right now?
I tried to talk him into it.
But your case was such high profile that they can't let you go that easily.
They said you can't avoid being placed under arrest.
My gosh.
I had no idea it will turn out this way.
What?
You had no idea?
You tried to get the document on Chairman Kim from me.
You rambled on about going to China and my going back to headquarters, huh?
Do you think I'll sit back and take it like this?
Geez, she can't even handle it, yet she's all over the place, not knowing her place.
You have to bring down that Tae On while you're at it!
If Chairman Kim switches to holding companies,
we're all screwed!
Geez, come on now!
Don't let the calls from my maternal side through for now.
Yes, ma'am.
Where is Chairman Kim?
He's at the office.
Open it.
Are you really giving this to me?
You can use it right away.
Really?
I can make a call right now?
You must have someone you want to call.
You should keep an eye on the press from now on.
If any issues come up before switching to holding companies,
it will affect other things,  too.
Okay, that'll be all.
Go on and get back to work.
Yes, sir.
She can't find Ga On.
What?
Director Kim Tae On stopped by earlier.
He's been missing since then.
Find out where Tae On is.
Yes.
Hurry!
Did you see Eun Hye?
She went to drive Mr. Goo home last night.
She's not back yet?
Yeah.
Are you feeling better?
I'm okay.
Don't worry about me.
I'll go out for a moment.
Are you going to look for Choi?
I have to look into something else.
Be careful.
Okay.
I was curious from the get-go.
Kang...
Who does he work for?
He's working for Director Kim Tae On.
Yes.
Mom, it's me.
Ga On.
Whose phone is this?
Mom, I got a new cellphone.
Is your workplace Gusan Agency?
What?
Yeah.
Ta-da!
- Are you sure she went there?
- Yes.
Ga On.
Ga On, how did you come here?
- Is this the place?
- Yes.
We found the right place.
Good job.
Hae Ra!
♫  I will walk through rough life  ♫
♫  You and I will stand in the midst of it all  ♫
Watch Kang Hae Ra closely and see what she's up to.
Find out the real owner of the warehouse
as well as the current owner.
Did you come to work here to get me and FB Group?
Don't you dare touch even a hair on Ga On.
I'll kill you.
I'll have to let him finish what he started.
They share a long history.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Mr. Cha.
Eun Hye!
♫  I will walk through rough life  ♫
'