Our life has been shaped differently
based on the type of boss we have.
So every time you meet a new boss,
you start exploring to see
if the person will get along with you
or if you'll have to adapt to the person.
BRANCH CHIEF CHOI JONG-HUN
-Cheers.
This is so invigorating.
I guess that's why people eat sea eels.
Gosh.
Right, the new branch chief
is coming tomorrow.
Is it okay for us to be relaxed like this?
Chief Nam told me
he didn't want the inauguration ceremony.
-I see.
-Really?
Hwang Hak-min's case caused a stir
throughout the prosecution,
so he'd want to keep a low profile.
I heard the new branch chief is a bumajok.
But you're not a bumajok anymore, Mr. Cho.
BUMAJOK: PROSECUTORS WHO ROSE
TO HIGHER POSITIONS THANKS TO IN-LAWS
Apparently, his father-in-law
used to be a district chief.
-Is that so?
-Hey.
It only counts
when the father-in-law is in his post.
Their influence doesn't last a year
once they retire.
Commoners like us just want
to stay warm and put food on the table.
I just hope he won't be so demanding.
I hear he does care
about the performance of the branch.
I guess everyone is like that
at the beginning.
Anyway, they say he's young at heart.
-Right.
-He is?
Regardless of your position,
he's the type
who likes to interact with his employees.
I see.
Just like me.
Right? Don't you think we will hit it off?
I heard he went to Yonsei University.
-I see.
-Yonsei University?
Why? Are you trying
to use your school ties
so you can team up
with the new branch chief?
You guys don't look after your juniors.
But we do.
-Prosecutor Hong, try this tail.
-Gosh, thank you.
-Eat this and work harder tomorrow.
-Sure. Thank you, sir.
It wouldn't be so bad
to have something in common with him.
Come on.
Don't learn bad things from them
and just work hard.
Here, try this.
Why is it bad? You all do the same thing.
My gosh.
Mr. Cho, don't you think
you should give him a call?
It'd be awkward to meet him
tomorrow for the first time.
You think so?
Mr. Choi, nice to meet you.
I'm Nam Byeong-jun.
Hello, Mr. Nam. Nice to meet you too.
I'm Choi Jong-hun.
Nice to meet you. I'm Cha Myeong-ju.
Likewise. Shall we have a seat?
We're honored to have dinner with you
like this before you take office.
Don't say that. I'm taking you out
to dinner to get along with you.
How was your trip to Jinyeong?
Not bad. It was a little far though.
Right, it is quite far.
I know you already refused it,
but I thought we should hold
a small inauguration ceremony.
No. I really don't like the idea
of an inauguration ceremony.
Young people these days hate that.
Aren't I right?
-Mr. Nam
-Yes, sir.
-Can I speak casually?
-Of course, sir. If you wish.
I went through the names
of the prosecutors from the branch.
You're the only two people
that are worth working with.
So I wanted to meet with you in person.
Excuse me.
Hello?
Hello, sir.
This is Division Chief Cho Min-ho
of Criminal Division 2.
Oh, hello. Mr. Cho.
Nice to talk to you.
Yes, Mr. Choi.
Welcome to Jinyeong.
Thank you.
I should've treated you to dinner
or something.
I feel burdened.
No worries.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Yes, sir. I hope you'll have
a comfortable night.
I'll see you tomorrow, sir.
All right. Thank you for calling.
Goodnight, sir.
-He says, "Thank you for calling."
-I see.
And his tone sounds nice.
See? Things are a lot better now
after you gave him a call.
You sure know how things work here.
You'll be successful.
You all are just like politicians.
Don't be like that.
All right. Go ahead and pour me a drink.
Allow me to pour you a drink.
Sure.
Please lead us well.
I look forward to working with you.
-Here.
-Yes, sir.
Here.
Pour him one.
Prosecutor Cha.
You went through a lot in Seoul
before coming here, right?
Here. Let me pour you one.
If you work hard,
good things will happen for sure.
Okay?
-Shall we drink a toast?
-Yes, sir.
Welcome, sir.
Thanks.
-Let me give you a refill.
-Yes, sir.
-Prosecutor Cha.
You greet him here on his first day?
You are brilliant.
Watch and learn.
You know how animals grow attached
to the first thing they see
as soon as they're born.
Humans are no different from them.
This is how the world works, you know?
But Chief Nam doesn't seem to care.
I know.
I doubt he knows stuff like this.
Actually, this is like the basics
of how to get ahead in the world.
That silly brat.
Those from Seoul National University
are such nerds.
They are out of touch with the world.
-On the hill of Namhae
-Oh, he's coming.
-He's here.
This way, sir.
Why did he…
get off this car?
We should hurry and follow him in.
Okay.
CONGRATULATIONS ON YOUR INAUGURATION
Yes, District Chief.
I just got to the office.
Yes. It's all right, sir.
I will take over my duty
without an inauguration ceremony.
My priority is to get the ball rolling
without a skip.
Yes, sir. Thank you.
Yes. Goodbye, sir.
All right. Stay seated.
I didn't recognize you earlier.
It was you, Mr. Cho.
Yes, sir. I wanted to welcome you
on your first day here.
There's no need.
I don't want such empty formalities.
Let's focus on working.
What's most important now
is for us to restore the public's trust.
-Yes, sir.
-Don't worry about me
and just focus on your work.
Yes, sir.
Mr. Nam, did you look into the thing
I mentioned yesterday?
Yes, sir.
First, I'm thinking
about arranging a meeting
with the community leaders
and councilors this week.
No, I'd rather meet them individually.
What can we talk about
when they all get together?
Yes, sir. Individual meetings.
There's no better way than this
when you want to learn how the city works.
Going to a local market
and having some rice soup with people
won't get you anything.
Keep that in mind.
Yes, sir.
-Oh, right.
-Yes, sir.
Unless it's something urgent,
you can send your reports by email.
I'll approve them in the evening,
so send them before 5 p.m.
Isn't this how
young people work these days?
Reporting face-to-face at set times
will only hinder your work efficiency.
We have phones too.
-Yes, sir. So…
-By the way,
how about the reports from each division?
-Let's do it right away.
-Yes, sir.
-How would you like for lunch…
-No worries.
I have plans.
I see. The thing is,
there's a good eel restaurant in Jinyeong
for your stamina.
We can go there next time.
-You're here.
-Hello.
Say hello. This is
Prosecutor Lee Seon-ung.
Hello.
Hello. Who is this?
She's Ms. Choi Sin-yeong.
Assistant Sung Mi-ran's successor.
I see. Nice to meet you.
You look quite young though.
I know.
So how old are you?
I'm 25.
Are you 25?
You look really young for your age.
The meeting with the new branch chief
will take place in the conference room.
Okay. I heard that too.
Go sit at your desk.
Go ahead.
Mr. Nam got the start on him.
He's quite shrewd in this.
Mr. Cho seemed very flustered.
He wouldn't be so harsh on us
on his first day, would he?
I hope so.
People either love or hate
the new branch chief.
One of my old colleagues
used to work with him in Cheonan.
He'll leave you alone
as long as you meet the performance quota.
But another colleague of mine
from Gwangju says
He's a jerk that doesn't
look after his subordinates
since he's too busy looking after himself.
Both can be true at the same time.
He might be very nice
to those with good performances.
But he would completely neglect
those who don't stand out.
-Why are you looking at me?
-What about you?
-Look at you.
-How dare you?
-My goodness.
-Gosh.
Gosh, this is unbelievable.
Thanks.
MONTHLY REPORT, HONG JONG-HAK
OF CRIMINAL DIVISION 2
MONTHLY REPORT, CHA MYEONG-JU
MONTHLY REPORT, LEE SEON-UNG
OF CRIMINAL DIVISION 2
MONTHLY REPORT, OH YUN-JIN
MONTHLY REPORT, LEE SEON-UNG
OF CRIMINAL DIVISION 2
Is Prosecutor Cha the only one
who's working in Criminal Division 2?
Well…
The division was managed
in an unusual manner,
but it was agreed
with the former branch chief.
So Prosecutor Cha took most of the cases…
I don't care what the former chief said.
That's not my concern.
Yes, sir.
Who's the lead prosecutor here?
It's me, sir.
MONTHLY REPORT, HONG JONG-HAK
OF CRIMINAL DIVISION 2
What's your role here?
You're supposed to serve
as a model for your division.
But your performance is the worst of all.
Do you have any authority
over your juniors?
What would they think of you?
Tell me.
My goodness.
MONTHLY REPORT, LEE SEON-UNG
OF CRIMINAL DIVISION 2
And what is this?
Lee Seon-ung.
Yes, sir.
You have the overwhelmingly
lowest arrest rate.
Actually, you've been at the bottom
for the whole year.
Is it that you have a conviction
about indictment without detention,
or are you just not good enough?
What is it?
Back in my day,
those with such poor performances
would voluntarily resign in shame
or at least take on night duty.
Okay?
You.
-Yes, sir.
-If you aren't going to quit,
you'll be on night duty
until your arrest rate goes up.
Well…
-Next, Oh Yun-jin.
-Yes, sir.
Your high acquittal rate isn't
the only problem here.
Why is the perjury rate so low?
Is it that
the citizens of Jinyeong never lie?
Or are you just too naive
to distinguish a lie?
Answer me.
Mr. Cho.
-Yes, sir.
-Listen.
We can barely call your division
a prosecution organization.
It's more like
a neighborhood get-together.
From now on,
submit a weekly performance report.
Along with the report,
I will need you to submit
your work plan for the next week.
On which day would you like us to report?
It's due at midnight every Friday.
Send it by email.
I don't even want to see your faces.
-Yes, sir.
-You can barely keep up with Division 1
thanks to Prosecutor Cha.
Among the prosecutors
of Jangwon District Prosecutors' Office,
Prosecutor Cha holds
the second-best performance.
-Mr. Cho.
-Yes, sir.
Were you aware of this?
Were you?
Tell me.
Answer me.
Cheer up, Mr. Cho.
I've misjudged him.
Young at heart, my foot.
Is there any way to make up
for the bad start we got off?
You all remember the weekly work report
due Friday, don't you?
Write it up well.
Don't make him call me to his office
on a Monday morning.
-Yes, sir.
For the time being,
the cases that require an arrest will be
assigned to Prosecutor Lee.
I can't let you go on duty every night.
You don't have to do that, sir.
No worries.
All right. Do you all agree?
-Yes, sir.
Hold your chins up.
We just need to adapt.
Everyone is like that at first.
He'd want to tighten up on discipline.
I'm sure he will
loosen up over time. Okay?
Hang in there.
-Yes, sir.
All right.
Let's eat.
-Yes, sir.
Oh, dear.
Please let me pay.
-Thank you for the food.
-Thank you.
HOMEMADE LOTUS LEAF TEA
My gosh.
I miss him even more today.
You should know that, okay?
Yes, sir.
Oh, gosh.
Congratulations on your inauguration,
Branch Chief Choi Jong-hun.
Thank you, Mr. Choi.
This is Reporter Ha Jae-ho
of Gwanghae Daily.
Nice to meet you, sir.
I'm Ha Jae-ho from Gwanghae Daily.
I'm Choi Jong-hun.
Mr. Ha has been working as a reporter
in this town for over 20 years.
He has connections throughout the city.
I believe he will be able to help you
get the hang of things
in your jurisdiction,
-so I asked him to come.
-Is that so?
Actually, I was going to ask you
to introduce someone like Mr. Ha to me.
I guess you saw through me already.
-Please have a seat.
-Please sit here.
Okay.
The best seat.
I'm sorry we started drinking without you.
It's no problem.
All right.
Honestly, I was surprised
that you wanted to have lunch with me
as soon as you got here.
You've been in the city for a long time,
so I had to pay you a visit first.
You really know how things work here.
Oh, right.
I recently met with District Chief Jung
and Deputy Chief Park.
And they kept saying
so many good things about you.
You know they don't praise people often.
I see. Are you familiar with the two?
My gosh.
We go golfing together twice a month
and often drink together.
Mr. Ha, you also meet them
quite often, right?
Sure.
Mr. Choi, I hope we will get along well.
-I'll appreciate your guidance.
-Gosh.
There's no need to be so formal.
-All right.
-Sure.
By the way,
there's something
that gives me a headache these days.
What is it?
My brother-in-law runs
a small business in Jinyeong.
And he recently got caught up
in some trouble over nothing.
Is that so?
Park Seon-u, male, 42 years old.
He lives in Jinyeong
and runs a small construction company.
He's already got caught
driving drunk twice this year
and got his license revoked.
But last Saturday, around midnight,
he was caught driving his friend's car
with a blood alcohol content of 0.24.
Let's request
a preliminary arrest warrant.
I'm being blamed
for the low arrest rate now.
This will do.
That's right.
Pardon?
What do you mean exactly?
Are you saying I'm a prosecutor
who can't make arrests?
Is that it?
What? Ms. Choi! Why are you…
What are you doing here?
Well…
What?
I'm on duty tonight. So earlier today…
I see.
Okay.
You can switch with me.
The thing is,
I have plans tonight. I'm sorry.
Mr. Yang Se-hwan. You've been arrested
for stealing a money container
at Jinyeong Pollack Restaurant
in Jungang Market last Wednesday.
Do you admit the charge?
Yes.
Your probation was over a week ago.
Sir, why did you do such a thing?
I was so hungry.
I'm sorry.
Is it true
the container had 100,000 won in it?
Yes.
You spent 50,000 won of it.
Where did you use it?
I used it to buy some food for a few days.
Gosh.
He has 12 previous convictions,
and they are all small amounts.
Like 50,000 won and 100,000 won.
The largest one is 1,200,000 won.
He stole a bag of money
from a car with its windows open.
Most of them are opportunistic thefts.
Even this time,
he spent only 50,000 won on food.
I think he did have
financial difficulties.
What did the victims say?
I called them,
but they're too busy for an interview.
They reported it in a rush,
but they also felt bad,
so they asked us to show him mercy.
Where does he live?
He has no fixed residence.
What about his family?
He has a son who's a sailor,
but I can't get a hold of him.
CAMULUS
My Lord.
It's about time you form a guild.
Isn't it boring to wander around with me?
Why? Are you bored?
It's not like that.
I'm just afraid
something might happen to us.
If you're that anxious,
you should find yourself a new lord.
CAMULUS
Wait.
Why do you talk down to me
when we chat in the game?
I use honorifics.
I'm your lord, and you're a stableman.
She talks a lot only in the game.
CAMULUS
Darn it.
SOLDIERS OF DARKNESS
Please help me!
CAMULUS
Branch Chief Choi.
What are you doing here?
I have something to tell you.
Then you could've
talked to me at the office.
-Come on in, anyway.
-Yes, sir.
When is your wife coming?
Maybe next week.
-I see.
-Have a seat.
Yes, sir.
Sir, you can speak casually to me now.
When I'm ready.
Yes, sir.
Have a seat.
Well…
-I hope you will like it.
-What is this?
You can take just one dose a day.
It's red ginseng.
You don't have to do this.
-Thank you, anyway.
-You're welcome.
What did you want to tell me?
Oh, well…
It's nothing specific.
You're newly appointed here,
but I wasn't well prepared.
I'm sorry to have worried you.
I just wanted to say I'll try harder and--
So…
What is it you want to say?
Please teach me a lot.
I will be sure to assist you well.
You know,
I don't need anyone's assistance.
I just want you to do your work.
Don't try to do something for me.
That's not what you're supposed to do.
-Okay?
-Yes, sir.
PERSONNEL RECORD SUMMARY
MOODY, MAKES OTHERS UNCOMFORTABLE
WITH STRONG WORDS
ADMINISTRATIVE ASSISTANT CHOI SIN-YEONG
The ribbon…
Why is the HR division doing this to us?
She's a total newbie.
Am I to blame again?
Is this because of you?
BRANCH CHIEF CHOI JONG-HUN AIMS
TO MAKE A SOCIETY WHERE LAW IS RESPECTED
He's busy already.
Since when was Gwanghae Daily
interested in the Jinyeong Branch Chief?
-Don't you think so?
-I see.
All right.
JANGWON DISTRICT COURT
JINYEONG BRANCH
I guess having you go on night duty
as a penalty works already.
You're even requesting
a preliminary arrest warrant.
That's because of the nature of the crime…
I know.
I was joking.
Yes, sir.
NON-INDICTMENT DECISION
They say the affluent are generous.
Prosecutor Cha
had the indictment suspended.
This man has some criminal records though.
Yes. But he's old, and the amount
he stole is only 50,000 won.
It was an accidental crime
due to financial difficulties.
What?
This is Jinyeong Pollack Restaurant.
Their food is really good.
We haven't been there in a while, right?
Yes. Would you like
to go there for lunch today?
Sure.
Then we should hurry.
Then I'll report this
and catch up with you.
You go first and order.
You don't have to share this with me.
Mr. Nam, you may leave now.
Yes, sir.
Thank you for this, Mr. Choi.
Sir, we have two cases here.
NON-INDICTMENT DECISION
PROSECUTOR CHA MYEONG-JU
REQUEST FOR ARREST WARRANT
PROSECUTOR LEE SEON-UNG
Division 2…
does everything backward.
Pardon?
-My gosh.
-Hello.
-It's been such a long time.
Yes.
Seon-ung,
it looks like you've lost weight.
That's not true at all.
And you've become
a lot prettier than before.
-Gosh, stop it.
-What?
They've known each other
since he was little.
-Auntie.
-Yes?
I heard there was
a theft case here recently.
That's true.
I was really shocked that day.
It was right after
I opened up in the morning.
An old man came in and had some noodles.
Then he suddenly ran away
with my money container.
You must've been startled.
My heart almost stopped.
I heard he got caught a few days later,
so I went to see him.
Then I found out
what he was going through.
It wasn't much money,
so I wanted to let it slide,
but it was too late.
What will happen to him?
We won't indict him
and keep an eye on him.
-I see.
-She's the prosecutor in charge.
We'll wait and see
if he should be punished or not.
I'm so glad to hear that.
Please let it slide this once.
It's good that it happened in the morning.
I mean, your restaurant is packed.
It would've been bad
if it happened in the evening.
Stop it.
That's enough of the joke.
-Go ahead and eat. Please enjoy.
-Okay.
-Yes.
Tell me if you need anything.
-Sure.
-Thank you.
Thank you.
Oh, Mr. Cho.
-Sir.
-Hey.
The food is ready.
-We just got it now.
-Let's eat.
It looks delicious.
Please enjoy it.
-All right.
-Thank you.
Are you not well?
He wants you to indict him
without detention.
What?
And he wants you to arrest him.
What are you talking about?
Maybe he confused them.
What's his reason?
As for Prosecutor's Lee case,
he is showing remorse,
and a petition has been turned in.
So he shouldn't be arrested.
As for Prosecutor Cha's case,
he has past records.
And his probation was just over.
He's showing no sign of remorse,
so he can't allow the suspension.
He wants us to arrest him.
So what did you say?
Did you just say yes?
Just meet the defendant
and investigate the case for now.
Things might be different
when you actually talk to him.
He's trying to tame us.
Did you eat?
I was at fault. I'm sorry.
The flower-shaped item is quite expensive.
Why don't we start complimenting
each other's items from now on?
I just said that
out of loyalty
because I wanted you to aim high.
I'm so sorry.
If you give me
another chance to serve you--
At 7 p.m. on Friday.
I'll give you that chance
at the Windy Hill.
ADMINISTRATIVE ASSISTANT SUNG MI-RAN
The Windy Hill?
WINDY HILL
I was talking about the game.
Does she want to see me personally?
Come this way.
Prosecutor Kim Jeong-u.
Yes, Mr. Choi?
Do you have some time?
Yes, sir.
Go ahead and drink.
It's always nice to see someone
from my university in prosecution.
-Yonsei University?
-You guys don't look after your juniors.
But we do.
-Prosecutor Hong, try this tail.
-Gosh, thank you.
I see.
Nothing's troubling you?
Yes, sir.
When were you appointed?
It's been over ten months now.
I see.
Then you will go on your own soon.
Make sure to invite me
to your celebration party. Okay?
Yes, sir.
You might think a branch chief
and a rookie prosecutor are distant,
but they say extremes meet.
We might hit it off well.
-Don't you think so?
-Yes, sir.
-You're with Prosecutor Cha, right?
And with Prosecutor Lee before.
I heard you two are still roommates.
-Yes.
-I see.
Then you must know
both Prosecutor Lee and Cha very well.
What are they like?
They both are hard-working and upright…
No, that's not what I'm talking about.
To be honest,
Prosecutor Lee seems
like a rebellious type.
And Prosecutor Cha seems quite cold.
Isn't it hard to get along with them?
Yes, just a little.
Like how?
I'd like you to keep an eye on them
and tell me if there's anything unusual.
You can report directly to me.
I know you work for Mr. Cho,
but that means
you work under me after all.
Don't you think so?
Yes, sir.
-Branch Chief signed these.
-Okay.
Thank you.
NO PRELIMINARY ARREST WARRANT,
INVESTIGATE WITHOUT DETENTION
PROSECUTOR LEE SEON-UNG
Hello. Have you been doing well?
Hello. You're here early.
Yes.
-Mr. Park Seon-u.
-Yes.
Last Saturday at around midnight
near Jinyeong Market,
you were caught
driving your friend's Mercedes
under the influence.
Is that correct?
Yes. I guess.
You refused to take a sobriety test
and crashed into a police car once.
While checking your alcohol level,
a police officer suffered injuries
that require over two weeks to recover.
Are you aware of that?
I don't remember.
I was a little drunk that night.
Mr. Park,
Stop smirking.
The sobriety test showed that
your blood alcohol level was 0.24 percent,
which is a state of inebriation.
And this is your third time
getting caught.
Your license was already suspended,
so it is considered unlicensed driving.
Do you admit the charge?
This is the letter of apology he wrote.
And this is
a petition signed by 141 people
that asks for favorable arrangements.
It wasn't a big accident,
and no one got seriously injured.
Mr. Park's company has
more than 100 employees.
If the CEO is arrested,
what will happen to all the employees?
As you can see,
the mayor and some city councilors
signed the petition.
So please take a careful look.
It doesn't matter who signed the petition.
If he was responsible for all the people,
he should've been careful.
INVESTIGATE WITH DETENTION
PROSECUTOR CHA MYEONG-JU
Is this Busan City Hall?
This is Prosecutor Cha Myeong-ju
of the Jinyeong Branch.
REQUEST FOR ARREST WARRANT
PROSECUTOR LEE SEON-UNG
Park Seon-u's brother-in-law is
Reporter Ha Jae-ho of Gwanghae Daily.
And he's close to a few city councilors.
-Mr. Cho.
-Yes.
Are you showing me an attitude?
Gosh. It's not like that, sir.
Prosecutor Lee.
-Yes. sir.
-I think
I made myself clear
about the arrest warrant.
But you requested it again
after a few minutes of the interview?
Did you find anything new
after the interview?
According to the traffic laws
revised last June,
the offender of such a serious DUI case
is supposed to be arrested.
And when I met the defendant,
he showed no sign of remorse.
Are you saying you can read into his mind?
And what makes you think
this is a serious case?
Do you think I'm blind?
If he has a residence
and has no risk of destroying evidence,
aren't we supposed to free him
from custody?
-Mr. Cho.
-Yes.
Must I teach a prosecutor stuff like this?
-No, sir.
-I don't know
why you're being generous toward
this offender specifically.
What?
What did you just say?
Lee Seon-ung, how dare you talk
to the Branch Chief like that?
Don't you have
any respect for your superiors?
Apologize to him right now. Immediately.
It was a slip of the tongue.
I'm sorry, sir.
-Mr. Cho.
-Yes.
Don't submit documents on this case again.
If you do,
I'll consider it insubordination.
This is my last warning.
Yes, sir.
And why hasn't Prosecutor Cha
requested a warrant request yet?
Tell me.
Can't you take care of it before I ask?
-Please.
-Yes, sir. I'll get it done.
Prosecutor Kim, is everything going well?
PROSECUTOR CHA MYEONG-JU
Yes, Mr. Choi.
What is Prosecutor Cha doing?
Will she not request a warrant?
I'm not sure, sir.
What do you mean you don't know
what your senior prosecutor is up to?
-Well…
-Yes?
How are you going to handle
the case about the pollack restaurant?
Why do you ask all of a sudden?
If you plan to request an arrest warrant,
it should be taken care of today.
I'll take care of it.
Yes, ma'am.
She says she'll take care of it.
What about Prosecutor Lee Seon-ung?
PROSECUTOR CHOI JONG-HUN:
WHAT ABOUT PROSECUTOR LEE SEON-UNG?
He and I rarely talk about work.
I'm sorry, sir.
HE AND I RARELY TALK ABOUT WORK
I'M SORRY, SIR
It's tomorrow.
Of course!
Which Windy Hill are you talking about?
In the game,
I don't see a hill that's named…
Oh, right. The place is
famous for its cake.
So it's in real life.
My flight tomorrow evening got canceled.
Can we meet at seven?
We haven't met before,
but I feel like we're old friends.
You'll come this time, right?
FROM JI-HYE
Jeong-u, find out what Prosecutor Lee
is up to and get back to me.
I want to sit where we can see the sea.
Who is it?
Mr. Cho.
Whatever you do,
I'm the only one
who really cares about you.
You should just relax and listen to music.
Why do you have so much work to do?
People might think I'm slaving you away.
You said I had no respect for my boss,
so I was trying to work hard.
Don't be absurd.
I'm on duty now,
but what's with all the alcohol and meat?
It's all right. If you drink
with your boss, it's part of your work.
-You think?
-Take this.
Yes, sir.
-Here you go.
-Thank you.
-Let me.
-It's okay.
All right. Let's drink.
Cheers.
Who is…
Jong-hak.
Prosecutor Hong.
Mr. Cho, you got here before me.
-All right.
-My gosh.
You make me want to cry.
You're just saying that.
Look at this drumstick. Gosh.
-It must be hot.
-Try this before it gets cold.
-Seon-ung, you should eat this.
-No.
-Beer or soju?
-Soju.
-Here's your glass. All right.
-All right.
-Thank you.
-My pleasure.
This is nice. True friendship.
-Let's drink.
-Yes, sir.
-Cheers.
Who is it?
-Seon-ung.
-Gosh.
Hey, Prosecutor Oh.
Oh, my.
What are you guys doing here?
-What is it?
-All right.
Here it goes.
-Okay.
-That's nice.
-My gosh.
-Nice.
-Cheers.
Seon-ung, you're so lucky.
Don't you think?
You have a cool boss like me
and these loyal colleagues.
-Aren't I right?
-Yes, sir.
Hey.
However obnoxious the new branch chief is,
as long as we stick together like this,
we can get over anything.
-Right?
-Yes, sir.
Sure. All right. Pour me a drink.
Yes, sir.
-Go ahead and drink it.
-This is nice.
Oh, my.
-My gosh.
-Who is it now?
It must be Prosecutor Kim.
Gosh, this is truly a touching moment.
Is that you, Jeong-u?
Or is it…
Cha Myeong-ju?
Come on. That's ridiculous.
What? You're so childish.
Seriously.
My gosh.
This is so good.
How many kids does Prosecutor Oh have?
Was Prosecutor Hong
Mr. Cho's junior in school?
Is Mr. Cho still in touch
with his ex-father-in-law?
We haven't met before,
but I feel like we're old friends.
You'll come this time, right?
I'll give you that chance
at the Windy Hill.
HELLO, BRANCH CHIEF CHOI,
I'M CHO MIN-HO OF CRIMINAL DIVISION 2
TO BE HONEST, I'VE ALWAYS…
DEAR BRANCH CHIEF CHOI…
PROSECUTOR LEE SEON-UNG
Did you write a lot?
I'm almost done writing two pages now.
I'm on my third page.
You must have a lot to apologize for.
Why? Do you not have much?
If I'm allowed to say drinking
with my boss is part of my work,
I think I can write about four pages.
Don't be absurd.
Hey.
-What are we doing right now?
-Do we have to apologize like this?
It's not like we're school kids.
Anyway, we just need to put this
on Mr. Choi's desk by tomorrow morning.
Let's go.
-My gosh.
-What is it?
This is sea squirt risotto.
It's a special menu.
I ordered it.
All right.
I like the color.
My goodness.
So they can make this with sea squirt.
-It tastes good.
-I like it.
There's a drink
that goes perfectly with sea squirt.
For sea squirt…
This is so good.
It's tasty.
All right.
Slow down. How will you
go to work tomorrow?
Forget it.
I'm not going to work tomorrow.
I can't stand
the sight of that Branch Chief.
He looks just like a rat.
"Criminal Division 2 is…"
I even hate his voice.
I know you'll be the first
to get to work tomorrow after saying this.
What?
Seriously, I'm not going.
You think I'm joking?
Mr. Cho, it's not like we're working
as prosecutors for Branch Chief's sake.
You've been through hell and high water.
We've seen a lot worse.
No.
This one is the worst.
Right.
By the way,
I wonder what he is doing now.
BRANCH CHIEF KIM IN-JU
What?
Sir.
-What?
-Mr. Cho, how are you?
It's been a while.
Yes, Mr. Kim. Have you been doing well?
-Yes.
-I'm here too, Mr. Kim.
-Hey, it's you, Prosecutor Lee.
-Yes.
Why did you send so much lotus leaf tea?
I won't be able to finish them
until my term is over.
I see.
It's just that they all wanted
to send one with me.
Is everyone doing fine?
-Yes.
-Sure.
What is the new branch chief like?
I believe he's a good person.
Well…
The thing is…
He's…
He's what?
a son of a bitch.
-Mr. Cho.
-Stop it.
It's not like that, sir.
I guess things are tough for you.
Yes, sir.
You will always be
my last branch chief, sir.
Sure thing.
That jerk who came after you
is not the branch chief, you know?
I'm flattered,
but stop calling me the branch chief now.
Then…
how do you want me to address you?
I mean,
can I call you by your name?
Will you?
-In-ju!
All right. I appreciate your hard work.
In-ju!
I miss you, In-ju.
I miss you too.
In-ju!
I miss you so much, my friend.
I should go home now.
I'll be sure to take him home.
-My gosh.
-Seriously.
You should call a chauffeur service.
What if you get caught again?
It's all right. No one in Jinyeong
can mess with me.
You're right.
A letter of apology solves everything.
You sound so confident.
Sweetheart, go home safely
and visit us again.
Sure. I'll see you later.
See you.
Bye, sweetheart.
Come again.
-Bye.
-Drive safely.
My gosh.
See you.
Darn it.
In-ju.
Some jerk just ditched me.
It really hurts, In-ju.
Prosecutor Cha.
I told you to arrest him.
But I haven't got
the request for the warrant.
What happened?
I think I was mistaken.
I wasn't sure why you wanted me
to arrest a criminal
with financial difficulties at first.
But I finally realized what it meant
after giving it a lot of thought.
The winter is coming.
If we have his indictment suspended,
he will commit another crime for sure.
So you thought it would be better
to let him stay at a detention center.
I misunderstood your intention
when you were seeing several moves ahead.
I'm so sorry.
So what?
What did you do?
There was a facility
for people like him in Busan.
Instead of indicting him,
I sent him to the facility.
Thank you for your wise guidance, sir.
BUSAN HOUSE OF HOPE STATUS REPORT
SHELTER FOR THE HOMELESS
All right.
I'm glad you understood my intentions.
Make sure to think carefully
when you make decisions.
Yes, sir.
-Yes.
-This is Choi Tae-jung.
Hello. I'm sorry,
but I'm in a meeting now--
It's about Reporter Ha Jae-ho's
brother-in-law
I told you about before.
I just heard a preliminary arrest warrant
has been issued.
What's happening?
What?
Yes. I'll get back to you soon.
Lee Seon-ung.
-Yes.
-Did you request
an arrest warrant without my approval?
Yes.
"Yes"?
Are you insane?
Do you think I'm a fool?
You know this is insubordination
and against the law.
It's not against the law.
According to the Criminal Procedure Code,
any prosecutor can request a warrant.
What did you say?
I already had enough grounds for arrest,
but I even confirmed that
there was a chance of an additional crime.
-An additional crime?
-Yes.
Last night,
I saw the defendant drive
under the influence again.
Where? Who?
Near Jinyeong Market, at around 1 a.m.
I witnessed it myself.
About how I left the office
and drank while on duty,
I will be penalized.
Penalize?
Do you think this is just about a penalty?
Mr. Cho.
-Yes, sir.
-What's with you?
I don't know what he saw
after drinking all night.
What were you doing
when he was betraying the prosecution?
Were you aware of this?
Yes. I was.
What?
I told him to request
a preliminary arrest warrant.
This is an act of insubordination.
What was I supposed to do?
You say everything we do
is insubordination.
We had no choice but to defy the orders.
Fine.
I'll show you what happens to those
who defy the rules of the organization.
Is this the Inspection Division?
I'm the Jinyeong Branch Chief.
Is the head
of Inspection Division 1 in office?
A lot of things change
when a new boss comes.
Yes.
Park Seon-u's case has been
reassigned to our division.
The arrest warrant has been issued,
but you still have a habeas corpus,
so you don't have to worry.
Some people say
it's best to adapt to the changes.
You just saw what your seniors did, right?
I will never let this slide.
What is Lee Seon-ung's private life like?
Do you know anything?
Mr. Choi.
-Yes.
-Lee Seon-ung and Cha Myeong-ju.
I respect them both as my seniors. And…
Hang on.
And I'm a prosecutor
of Criminal Division 2.
BRANCH CHIEF'S OFFICE
But some people improve
by resisting such changes.
Some people adapt to the changes
and protect themselves.
DECISION OF DISCIPLINARY COMMITTEE
CHO MIN-HO, LEE SEON-UNG
And some people refuse
to be tamed after all.
CHANGE IN ASSIGNMENT
OH YUN-JIN: TRIAL TO INVESTIGATION
LEE SEON-UNG: INVESTIGATION TO TRIAL
Prosecutor Oh,
can you brief me on any urgent trials
and pass me the materials
I would need tomorrow?
No. I'll go over to your office.
My gosh.
WINDY HILL
-Here.
-Okay.
I'm planning to form a new guild.
I see.
My Lord.
No.
Don't call me that anymore.
Then…
Mi-ran.
I want to serve you online only.
I'll fulfill my duties as a servant.
Anything more than that…
So they have no work to do.
They all were here
when they were drinking.
PROSECUTORS' OFFICE
Is he still there after going against you?
Don't let her get any cases.
Have all the cases
in her office reassigned.
I know it's hard for you,
but you should go meet him again.
If you drink too, who's going to drive us?
Even my pride is hurt.
-You take care of that case.
-Me?
Schedule an interrogation
and help out Prosecutor Kim.
Ms. Cha isn't the only prosecutor here.
I'm a prosecutor too.
Do you not even care what I say?
I'm sorry.
I need some courage.
After all, I'm a stableman,
and you are my lord.
Park Seon-u has been released.
You got penalized
and became the trial prosecutor,
but the defendant is released on bail.
What is it you want to say?
The branch chief told me
to attend the trial.
-Do you have anything to add?
-No, Your Honor.
I can't lose this case to her like this.