The flower of the prosecution
and the star of the prosecution.
The dream of all prosecutors.
These expressions are used
to describe a district chief.
Although a district chief is
only one level higher than a branch chief,
becoming a district chief is
a lot harder than a branch chief.
Do you have any connections in Jeonju?
DISTRICT CHIEF
Not really.
BRANCH CHIEF
Actually, I served in Jeonju
as a military service officer.
Then you must be familiar with Jeonju.
Let me make it easier to understand.
Let's say there are
300 prosecutors in one class.
Among them, about 200 prosecutors are
promoted to division chief.
And about 30 of them are promoted
to deputy chiefs and branch chiefs.
And finally,
only about three of them make it
to district chiefs.
Only the top 1% of them
can rise to the position.
Only those who are blessed
can enjoy the honorable position.
That's the district chief.
DISTRICT CHIEF
WHEN YOU COME TO JEONJU
Jeonju…
Mr. Oh Jeong-bae.
You've been charged
with trespassing into 2K Motors
on the 3rd at 10 p.m.
and stealing about a million won in cash.
You worked at 2K Motors
until about two months ago.
Yes.
You were fired before
your three-month apprenticeship was over.
Yes.
Did you do this because you harbored
a grudge against them for firing you?
I felt mistreated.
I got fired for asking a few questions.
PROSECUTOR KIM JEONG-U
What questions?
I asked why the suppliers
sent us only the sales statements
without providing us with the parts.
Isn't this something worth asking?
But they said I was slow-witted.
Ignorance is not a sin.
-I just didn't know because I was new.
-I see.
Anyway, you admit the charge, right?
Did something like that happen often?
A BC case?
Yes. According to Mr. Oh Jeong-bae,
who was an apprentice,
the parts supplier often sent them
sales statements
without shipping the actual parts.
And many customers
often complained of malfunction
after they had their parts replaced.
But we can't start investigating 2K Motors
only with the testimony of an apprentice.
What's this?
A list of complaints about
2K Motors' fraud in the last 5 years.
The victims dropped their charges
and suffered slight damage,
so there hasn't been
a proper investigation.
But seven of them seem to be BC cases.
BC: BASKET CASE
DIVISION 2 CHIEF'S OFFICE
PROSECUTOR CHO MIN-HO
Mr. Lee.
What is a BC case?
It's a kind of insurance fraud.
When there's a car accident,
you go to a repair shop.
They fix your car and charge the fee
to your insurance company.
CAR, INSURANCE COMPANY, REPAIR SHOP
So the repair shop uses cheap
or faulty parts to fix your car
and claims the expenses for expensive ones
to get more money
from the insurance company.
BC: BOGUS CLAIM
It is called BC in short.
I see.
Then why did Mr. Cho seem so serious?
Because this is about 2K Motors.
What about 2K Motors?
Kang In-sang is the CEO.
Who is Kang In-sang?
Kang Jun-mo's son.
Assemblyman Kang Jun-mo?
Even you know about Kang Jun-mo.
If you mess with Kang Jun-mo,
you become public enemy number one.
Darn it. Branch Chief needs
to keep a low profile now.
Why did we just walk all the way here?
Because we had long lines.
I don't know much about cars,
so I just went to a famous place.
They say 2K Motors has many branches,
and I saw their ads on TV.
So I trusted them.
Their office looked quite fancy,
and the employees were neatly dressed
in uniforms, so they seemed trustworthy.
I had to get the joint replaced,
so they recommended a German product,
which was a bit pricey.
But I had no choice.
It was for my car, so I went with it. But…
After about ten days,
the warning light was turned back on.
I took my car to another repair shop,
and they asked
when I last had my car checked.
And they said it needed an overall repair.
I was flustered.
So I went to 2K Motors and complained.
They claimed they had nothing to do
with it, so I filed a suit.
Then they finally admitted
that there had been a mistake.
I said all this to a prosecutor last year,
but the whole thing fizzled out
and the case was dropped.
I lost a lot of hair because of this case.
-I was so stressed out. Take a look.
-It's all right.
I've never taken my car
to 2K Motors since then.
I put together the statements.
We will reinvestigate the case.
Make sure to look into 2K Motors
as well as all the businesses
who are involved with them
in the bogus claim cases.
-Okay.
-We'll find the ledgers first.
Draft a search and seizure warrant.
Okay. Should we search 2K Motors first?
No. We'll search
all the businesses at once.
Okay.
MURYANG MOTORS
We're from the Jinyeong Branch.
As of November 11th, 2019,
we'll proceed with the search and seizure
of Muryang Motors.
We're from the Jinyeong Branch.
We will execute
our search and seizure warrant
-as of November 11th, 2019.
-Who do you think you are?
We're from the Jinyeong Branch.
As of November 11th, 2019,
we will execute
our search and seizure warrant.
Get the main computer.
2K MOTORS
We're from the Jinyeong Branch.
As of November 11th, 2019, we will execute
the search and seizure warrant.
Please give us the ledgers, Manager.
The company officials are part
of the search and seizure.
Please remain seated with your IDs.
-Confiscate their phones.
-Here.
You're not allowed to use your phones now.
Confiscate the phones here.
2K MOTORS CEO KANG IN-SANG
Dad.
CEO'S OFFICE
What?
We're from the Jinyeong Branch.
BRANCH CHIEF KIM IN-JU
Yes, Kim In-ju speaking.
Yes.
The office filled
with blue search and seizure boxes
reminds me of the beach of Kota Kinabalu.
Ji-hye, you must be flying in the sky
which is bluer than the ocean.
Although my nights are sleepless,
I work hard day by day
thinking of you.
Here.
This is from one of the suppliers.
This is the only ledger with bogus claims.
JINYEONG AUTO-PARTS COMPANY
Jinyeong Auto-parts Company?
That's not for 2K Motors.
And it's from two years ago.
Look. You wrote this down to split up
the insurance money with the supplier.
Prosecutor Kim,
could you please let this slide?
Please. This is from two years ago.
We didn't make any bogus claims
last year and this year.
You can see that everything in here
is from two years ago.
It's just that we didn't find the ledgers
from last year and this year.
I'm telling you. We didn't do that
last year and this year.
Actually, we didn't even have a chance.
I put the shop up for sale
half a year ago.
You made so many bogus claims
two years ago.
I can't believe that
you stopped doing it last year.
-Damn it!
-You startled me.
It's 2K Motors who took all the money!
They conspired with the towing companies
and auto-parts companies.
Can you explain that in more detail?
Come in.
DIVISION CHIEF CHO MIN-HO
So…
-Is everything going well with the case?
-Yes.
We got a testimony
that 2K Motors has been monopolizing
the bogus claims in the last two years.
I'll prepare the search
and seizure warrant
for Kang In-sang's home.
I see.
Prosecutor Cha, the thing is…
Come in.
Hey.
Well…
About this case.
It's been reassigned to Prosecutor Lee.
-Pardon?
What's the reason?
There have been complaints
about how you pushed ahead with the case.
It's true you failed to find any ledgers
after you raided all the offices
of 2K Motors and their suppliers.
Am I wrong?
Prosecutor Lee. I need you
to be more careful with the case, okay?
Yes, sir.
All right. You may leave now.
DIVISION 2 CHIEF'S OFFICE
PROSECUTOR CHO MIN-HO
FOR APPROVAL
Here it is, sir.
-Goodbye.
Don't.
Let's just go.
The District Office called?
Yes.
Why do you think
the District Chief called and told him
to reassign the case?
He must have a lot on his mind now.
Make sure you behave yourself.
So you won't stand in his way.
But why does it have to be Lee Seon-ung?
Who knows?
Apparently, Deputy Chief Park
specifically recommended him.
What connection is there between them?
That's strange.
Oh, right.
The brass ruler.
PROSECUTOR LEE SEON-UNG
This is Lee Seon-ung
of Criminal Division 2.
Prosecutor Lee, this is
Deputy Chief Park Jeong-gon.
Who again?
DEPUTY CHIEF PARK JEONG-GON
Deputy Chief Park Jeong-gon
of the Jangwon District Office.
Yes. Hello, sir.
Don't tell me
you got up to answer my phone.
Well… Of course not.
I'm sorry I didn't recognize you sooner.
Why have you kept
your head down all this time?
You should've told us about it.
Oh, yes.
You've never even attended our gatherings.
-Pardon?
-Anyway,
I'll go visit you in Jinyeong soon.
I'll treat my fellow member
of the Brass Ruler Society to a nice meal.
-I'll see you then.
-Sir, actually…
Hello?
-My gosh.
-What's wrong?
Hey, Prosecutor Cha.
-Are you going home?
-Yes.
Oh, right. I heard you got
your case taken away.
That must be upsetting.
There's not much you can do
when the Brass Ruler Society
wants to have its own league.
Common prosecutors like us
should just put up with that.
-Pardon?
-Did you not know that?
Mr. Park is backing Prosecutor Lee up
because he received the brass ruler.
I guess you didn't know.
See you.
Where did you get the brass ruler?
I received it.
What did you say? I can't hear you.
I received it from Professor Park.
Why are you acting so clueless?
Clueless?
As if you don't know
anything about interrogations.
Think of the numerous defendants
you have interrogated so far.
No, let's say you're a defendant now.
Imagine that you will be put behind bars
if you get caught lying.
-Mr. Cho, please.
-There you go.
Try again with that innocent look.
Where did you get the brass ruler?
I got it from Professor Park Dae-cheon
when I graduated.
Why didn't you come to
the Brass Ruler Society gatherings?
Because Prosecutor Lee isn't
the type of guy
to be interested in
making a fuss over a mere metal stick.
Prosecutor Lee.
-Yes.
-We're already
past the point of no return.
Now that we're at this,
you have to pull this off.
If you get caught, not only you and me
but also our Branch Chief…
No.
Everyone in Jinyeong Branch
will be put to shame.
Do you understand?
-It's really not that big a deal.
-What?
Wouldn't it be more humiliating
to get caught later on?
We won't get caught.
Professor Park passed away last year.
This is all up to you now. Okay?
This is our plan
for the brass ruler, all right?
This is the last chance
for the Branch Chief.
If he fails this time,
he may go to the High Prosecutors' Office
and work under his juniors
or he might have to resign.
You know that?
-All right then.
-Yes, sir.
Good job today. I had fun.
-Let's stay in touch.
-Yes, sir.
Please get in.
Goodbye, sir.
Bye.
Mr. Park, come with me.
-Pardon?
-I'll give you a ride.
-Let's go for another drink.
-Yes, sir.
Goodbye, Mr. Kim.
-See you.
-Yes, sir.
Let's go.
PERFECT CARE GUARANTEED
2K MOTORS
Deputy Chief Kim.
I should be calling you
Branch Chief Kim, right?
-I'm still used to calling you a deputy.
-I see.
You know it's most dangerous
when a plane takes off and lands.
Things have been noisy in Jinyeong.
You need a soft landing.
Wrap things up nicely.
-Yes, sir.
-All right.
PERFECT CARE GUARANTEED
2K MOTORS
Let's go.
It's chilly today.
-It's cold.
-I know, right?
The weather is already…
The door is closing.
-Hello.
-Good morning.
-Oh, gosh.
-Be careful.
-Are you all right?
-I'm fine.
-What?
-What was that?
Let me carry it for you.
No, thank you.
Please let me do it.
It's okay.
It's Prosecutor Kim's wish.
Just let him carry it once.
This is my job.
Please.
What's with him?
Is it love?
It's loyalty.
Shall we go?
Oh, dear.
I sent the files to your office.
-This is a summary for your quick review.
-Okay.
2K MOTORS AUTO-PARTS FRAUD CASE
Prosecutor Lee, don't you have
a lot of cases to handle now?
Yes.
I do have some urgent issues.
What could be more urgent than this case?
She's right.
This is the most important.
So I need you
to investigate it more carefully.
-Got it?
-Okay.
Take your time with it.
I've done everything
that requires caution.
Now, we should be bold.
But the evidence we have is
statements from an apprentice
and rival repair shops.
They all are harboring
grudges against 2K Motors.
They'd say anything to make their case.
Don't you think so?
If your superior denies the evidence
a prosecutor in charge has found,
the investigation can't be conducted.
Do you agree with him, Prosecutor Lee?
All right.
Are these for the bogus claim case?
Yes. I'm sorting them out.
We can check them together.
Put them aside for now.
Okay.
There's a suspicion that a prosecutor is
involved in the hotel sexual favor case,
which has shocked the public.
Hwang Hak-min, the Chief
of the High Prosecutors' Office…
Gosh, why would he do that?
We have a reporter
at the Supreme Prosecutors' Office now.
Doesn't he have any pride as a prosecutor?
This is humiliating.
Cha Myeong-ju
got on my nerves this morning.
It's not like we're not investigating.
We're just lying low
until Branch Chief's promotion.
But she acts as if it's a heinous crime.
You know she is a woman of principle.
Then are you saying
I'm violating principles?
That's not what I meant.
He didn't mean anything like that.
It's just Prosecutor Cha is…
She's a little uptight and inflexible.
Right.
So I'm a spineless pushover.
Let's just eat.
Gosh, things will be crazy
at the prosecution for a while.
-Darn, this is so humiliating.
-Tell me about it.
I'm humiliated too.
I didn't say I wouldn't do it.
I'm just putting it on hold.
You know it's most dangerous
when a plane takes off and lands.
Things have been noisy in Jinyeong.
You need a soft landing.
Wrap things up nicely.
PROSECUTOR LEE SEON-UNG
What is this?
We have a case of unnatural death.
A car accident?
CASE REPORT
PHOTO OF INCIDENT
This didn't happen
from trying to avoid another car.
He just crashed into the guardrail.
Was he dozing off? I wonder
why he didn't step on the brake.
Maybe he did step on the brake,
but it didn't work.
I see.
Did you ask his family
if he visited a repair shop
for maintenance recently?
He was living alone,
supporting his family who are abroad.
So we're having trouble reaching them.
I see.
Excuse me.
Hello?
Oh, really?
They found a receipt from
a car repair shop in his belongings.
-Is that so?
-Yes.
Which repair shop is it?
It's 2K Motors.
PROSECUTOR LEE SEON-UNG
This is the last chance
for the Branch Chief.
FATHER
Hello, Dad. Did something happen?
Do I only have to call you
if something happened?
Just tell me.
Do you not even care
if your dad is dead or alive?
I mean, we both live in Jinyeong,
but you never come to visit me.
I've been busy with work.
Is everything fine?
I had a car accident,
so I'm at a repair shop now.
What? Why? Did you get hurt?
Hurt?
If I were hurt,
I wouldn't be calling you like this.
So which repair shop is it?
I'm at a shop in the neighborhood.
It's not 2K Motors, is it?
You can't go there.
You darn fool. Which one is this?
This is Seogwang Motors.
Hey, why would I go to a shop
that Kang Jun-mo's son runs?
-You silly thing.
-Right.
Aren't you coming to visit me?
I'll stop by this weekend.
Okay. I'll see you then.
-Bye.
-Bye, Dad.
Come in.
Yesterday,
I went to examine a car accident victim.
He was a father who lived alone.
And he recently
had his car repaired at 2K Motors.
And my father called me last night.
He was at a car repair shop.
And before I knew it,
I was telling him not to go to 2K Motors.
I was fortunate to tell him that,
but even at this moment…
Prosecutor Lee.
Have you been on a plane?
They say it is most dangerous
when a plane takes off and lands.
I don't know
because I rarely take a plane.
I'm not a fan of floating in the air.
If I was meant to be there,
I would take a train or a bus,
or I'll reach
the destination even on foot.
Even if it takes longer.
I was going to write an email,
but now that you're here, I'll tell you.
Proceed with the search and seizure
of Kang In-sang.
PROSECUTOR LEE SEON-UNG,
2K MOTORS…
JANGWON DISTRICT PROSECUTORS' OFFICE
JINYEONG BRANCH
DIVISION CHIEF
You must find something no matter what.
-Okay?
-Yes, sir.
Actually, I'm afraid
you might find something.
Anyway, we can think about that later.
What we need to find are
the ledgers of bogus claims.
They weren't in the office,
so they must be kept
somewhere in his house.
-Shall we?
-Yes.
-Let's split up as we go in.
-Okay.
Do you really have to do this?
I only keep clothes there.
Here.
Be careful.
My gosh.
Gosh, what's all this?
Take it easy with that, will you?
Gosh.
Stop throwing things around.
-My goodness.
-They are my watches.
They eat good stuff.
It's not here.
It won't be easy.
He must've hidden it
somewhere we can't imagine.
But it definitely must be
somewhere in the house.
With all your knowledge and experience,
you must find where the ledgers are. Okay?
-Yes, sir.
All right. We have to see some results
of this search and seizure.
-Yes, sir.
Then should we try the thing
where we say, "found it"?
-That.
-Sure.
-I like that.
-Okay. Who would do that?
I'll do it.
-I'll say it.
-Okay.
What?
Gosh, it's taking so long.
Let's hurry and find it.
Did you check the basement?
What? You found it?
Where?
Where is it?
-Yes!
-We got it!
I found it!
Great job!
BRAKE LINING, BRAKE PAD, BRAKE FLUID
BRAKE PAD, BRAKE LINING, BRAKE FLUID,
AUTO-PARTS MAINTENANCE
There it is.
What?
The car accident victim.
They used faulty parts for his car too.
I see.
We, Criminal Division 2,
recognized the bogus claim cases
of 2K Motors two weeks ago
and launched an investigation.
After raiding the office
and the CEO's house,
we found the ledgers
as pieces of key evidence.
Excuse me.
It's Deputy Chief Park Jeong-gon.
May I take this call?
-Hello?
-Lee Seon-ung, are you out of your mind?
I was being nice to you as a fellow member
of the Brass Ruler Society.
But you're about to let me down.
I thought I made myself clear.
-Sir…
-I won't say much.
Drop the case immediately.
I'll arrange a meeting
with Assemblyman Kang and his son,
so you can come and apologize.
Do I have to spoon-feed you
everything like this?
I hope you can live up to
our society's reputation.
About the brass ruler…
I picked it up.
What did you say?
I didn't earn the brass ruler.
I found it.
The day I was appointed to this office,
I found it stuck in my desk drawer.
I didn't even know
what the brass ruler meant until recently.
I've never even spoken to
Professor Park Dae-cheon.
And I had no idea that there was…
a Brass Ruler Society.
So it's understandable
that you're disappointed in me.
But I will take care of this case
within the bounds of common sense.
I'm not a member
of the Brass Ruler Society,
but I'm still a prosecutor.
So I believe you'll understand.
You darn crazy punk.
For your information,
you're on speakerphone now.
So…
we raided CEO Kang In-sang's house
and found the ledgers.
Can we take a short break?
You picked it up?
Yes. The thing is…
You must've had a lot of fun.
It wasn't fun at all. I was so distressed.
Then you should've told the truth
when I first mentioned the brass ruler.
I didn't even know
the metal stick was called a brass ruler.
I had no idea what you were talking about.
You didn't know about the brass ruler?
How does that make sense?
Did you not go to school?
That's not… We went to the same school.
Maybe I didn't know
because I was hung up on charity work.
Africa?
Yes, I went to Africa.
Is that why I didn't know?
I just don't get it.
Anyway, now that this is out of the way,
so I want you to stop
talking about the brass ruler.
I will. My curiosity is finally satisfied.
So it's clear that you're not
a person worthy of the brass ruler.
PROSECUTOR LEE SEON-UNG
What is this? Is it for me?
Thank you.
I heard you gave the Deputy Chief a blow.
Is it going around already?
It's not just going around.
I believe it will make a mark
on the history of the Jinyeong Branch.
"The Rebellion of Lee Seon-ung."
It's not like I'm a historical figure.
It's embarrassing to name it like that.
Why don't we…
just call it
the Brass Ruler Declaration Day?
That's so catchy.
I know. All right then.
All right then.
Let's go after Kang In-sang.
Yes!
I HEREBY REQUEST AN ARREST WARRANT
FOR KANG IN-SANG
2K MOTORS
Is Mr. Kang in there?
You can't go in.
What?
Where's Mr. Kang?
INVESTIGATOR JANG MAN-OK
Yes, Ms. Jang.
He went abroad?
Bye.
-Make sure you behave.
-Okay.
I think she's here.
Prosecutor Cha, welcome.
She's Prosecutor Cha Myeong-ju.
Hey, come on in and have a seat.
Sit over here.
All right.
It was you who first took the case, right?
-Yes, sir.
-I should've done this sooner.
Then this wouldn't have happened.
It was pointless to have reassigned
the case to another prosecutor.
It only hurt Prosecutor Cha's feelings.
Mr. Park.
-Yes, sir.
-Why did you do that?
It was my mistake.
Prosecutor Cha,
I heard you and Mr. Park go way back.
That's true. When I was
at the Eastern District Office,
she was in the office next to mine.
Mr. Park says
you were outstanding
compared to your fellow prosecutors.
And you two were on the same wavelength.
Many people are paying
attention to this case.
Those from the Gwacheon Office
are concerned too.
If you step up
and take care of it,
they all will be grateful.
All right. Let me pour you a drink.
Yes, sir.
Prosecutor Cha.
It's about time you went back to Seoul.
He's here.
-Hello, sir.
-I'm sorry I'm late.
You're here, Mr. Kang.
Hello, Mr. Jung.
-It's been a long time, sir.
-Mr. Park.
-Hello.
-Hello, Mr. Choi.
This is Prosecutor Cha Myeong-ju
of the Jinyeong Branch.
Nice to meet you. I'm Kang Jun-mo.
I'm Prosecutor Cha Myeong-ju.
Please have a seat. Over here.
Thank you for coming all the way here.
You must be busy.
BRANCH CHIEF KIM IN-JU
Hello?
Yes.
Welcome.
-Good morning.
-A double shot Americano, right?
-Yes.
You come here often.
Are you sure you don't want a stamp card?
Yes. I won't be here for long.
I see. Just a second.
You lost Kang In-sang after all the fuss?
Do you think that makes sense?
After poking around all you want,
you got no results.
Prosecutor Lee, I must say
you don't finish things well.
I'll ask Interpol for cooperation.
Yes.
Prosecutor Cha, have a seat.
The 2K Motors Case
has been reassigned to Prosecutor Cha.
Pardon?
But why?
Dear Branch Chief Kim.
Prosecutor Lee Seon-ung's father is
Kang Jun-mo's sworn enemy.
So Prosecutor Lee is
highly likely to hold a grudge
against Kang In-sang, Kang Jun-mo's son.
That makes Prosecutor Lee
unsuitable for the 2K Motors Case.
I got this anonymous letter.
And the District Chief
received the same letter.
This is not true.
I checked it myself,
and it wasn't completely ungrounded.
He's right.
I heard your father competed against
Kang Jun-mo for a nomination.
Why did you not tell me that?
You mean he hid
this important fact from us?
Are you out of your mind?
This happened over ten years ago.
I understand how you feel,
but little suspicion and doubt
can lead to public distrust.
And it will end up
sabotaging the investigation.
I know it sounds sudden,
but just consider that the case
went back to its owner.
What should I do with this?
Are you done?
If you're done, please give it to me.
Next line can start entering the office.
I think I'm done.
The witnesses are here.
Shall we start with the employees?
Send all of them
to Prosecutor Cha's office.
The case has been reassigned.
What?
The interviews have been canceled.
You may leave now.
When should we come back?
-You don't have to come back.
-What?
-Are you sure we can go?
-Can we go now?
-No, please wait for a bit.
-Why not?
-She just told us to go.
-It won't take long.
-What?
-I'll get back to you soon,
-so please remain seated.
-My gosh.
Why aren't they coming back?
Don't tell me you're going to stop now.
Prosecutor Cha.
Will you stay out of this?
I'm in charge now.
Is this why you took it back?
It's been reassigned to me
because of your father.
Taking it out on me
would only make you look ridiculous.
Prosecutor Cha, it's you
who looks ridiculous here.
Mr. Lee, send him out.
-Pardon?
-Is it the District Chief?
Did he ask you to listen to him
saying he'd give the case back to you?
No, you're very calculating,
so you wouldn't cave in with just that.
What did he offer you?
Did the District Chief
promise you a favor?
Or did he say he'll send you to Seoul?
I see. Maybe he promised to get you
the brass ruler you were dying to have.
Excuse me, Prosecutor Lee.
If I'm wrong, just say so.
Just tell me
you'll continue the investigation
and catch Kang In-sang.
You can't, can you?
I knew it.
You told me this before.
That I'm not worthy of the brass ruler.
Before you say such a thing to others,
you should reflect on yourself.
Ask yourself if you are a prosecutor
who deserves the brass ruler.
Have you no shame?
An APB was out for Kang In-sang, right?
What? Yes.
-Withdraw it.
-Pardon?
Yes, ma'am.
I was told to leave.
Yes. And I don't have to come back.
Yes, the female prosecutor.
Then the male prosecutor
showed up and made a big fuss.
They were fighting and everything.
It was a total mess.
Yes.
Right. Mr. Kang will be taken off the APB.
I guess the case will be closed soon.
All right. Good job.
Bye.
ATTORNEY CHOI TAE-JUNG
Hello, Assemblyman Kang.
INVESTIGATOR JANG MAN-OK
Gosh, the soup looks so refreshing.
Seon-ung.
Why are you eating alone?
-What?
-What's with him?
Hey.
Hey, you've had enough.
I recommend you apply it
after learning the procedures.
Lastly, I'd like you
to make your best effort
for the Winter Team Workshop next month.
That'll be all.
WARM ADMINISTRATION, HAPPY CITIZENS
That punk.
The Rebellion of Lee Seon-ung.
There are about 25,000 parts in a car.
If one of them doesn't function properly,
it can lead to a fatal accident.
And a prosecutor is
no different from a car.
If there's a prosecutor
who doesn't fulfill his duty properly,
society can suffer a serious wound.
POLICE ARE SURE IT IS HWANG HAK-MIN
CEO KANG IN-SANG OF 2K MOTORS
He's here.
-Mr. Kang.
-Hey.
-Sorry about that.
-It's nothing. I was just on a trip.
-Welcome back.
-Thanks.
Where's the car?
It's in the parking lot.
Let's go.
Oh, dear. I got a lot of text messages.
I just can't take some time off.
I have an appointment for a drink already.
All right. I should drink.
What are you doing? Let go of me.
Get off me! Who are you?
Mr. Kang In-sang, you're under arrest
for committing an economic fraud crime.
You have the right to explain yourself
and the right to an attorney.
Excuse me.
I'm off the wanted list now.
You don't know anything.
It's you who doesn't know.
We can still arrest you
even if you're off the wanted list.
Let's go.
Wait. Let go of me first.
It hurts. Just get off me already.
What are you doing?
Let go of me!
How could you do this
to an innocent businessman?
Get off me!
Please keep it down.
Right, I'll keep it down.
-But don't you know who my father is?
-I don't care.
-That's why I'm telling you.
-Shut up.
People would think I'm a serial killer.
-Seriously.
-Let's move quietly.
Hey, what are you watching?
-I want an attorney. That's my right.
-Kang In-sang?
Just stay quiet.
I can't believe this.
-Just stop it.
-My gosh.
Do you know who I am?
Do you even know what you just did?
How could you do this to me?
How can you stab me in the back?
I'm sorry, District Chief.
I didn't know the junior prosecutors
would take such extreme action.
Yes. I'll take full responsibility.
Yes.
CRIMINAL DIVISION 2 CHA MYEONG-JU
Hello?
Mr. Kim, I have something to tell you.
Do you have time to talk?
Yes.
I'm on my way back after meeting
with Assemblyman Kang Jun-mo.
Even the District Chief is in on this?
Yes. They want me to take over the case
and cover things up for them.
The District Chief will call me soon then.
What are you going to do?
Why don't we use this
to our own advantage?
Use their strategy to our own advantage?
Let them reassign the case as they want.
Instead, we will go after
Kang In-sang who's on the run.
The 2K Motors Case
has been reassigned to Prosecutor Cha.
DEAR BRANCH CHIEF KIM
I will reluctantly reassign the case
to Prosecutor Cha,
and she will pretend to close the case
as the District Chief ordered.
The case has been reassigned.
What?
The interviews have been canceled.
You may leave now.
When should we come back?
You don't have to come back.
To make them fall for that…
An APB was out for Kang In-sang, right?
Withdraw it.
We can still arrest him
after withdrawing it.
We will be arriving
at Incheon International Airport soon.
-All right.
-Please fasten your seat belts.
Thank you.
Relieved, Kang In-sang will return.
INVESTIGATOR LEE JEONG-HWAN
Investigator Lee Jeong-hwan speaking.
Okay.
Kang In-sang is on the passenger list.
We'll get him at the airport.
Let me sit by the window. I get car sick.
And Kang In-sang will be in our hands.
We shouldn't tell Prosecutor Lee
about this, right?
I don't think he can act.
Of course not. He just can't.
Let's keep it to ourselves
so nothing will go wrong.
Yes, sir.
DISTRICT CHIEF JUNG YUN-HO
Hello, sir.
BRANCH CHIEF KIM IN-JU
THOUSAND YEARS OF JEONJU
A GUINNESS RECORD
How could you do that
when I made myself clear?
I can't face Assemblyman Kang now.
No, it's not like that.
I don't need your apology--
The District Chief is called the flower
-I'm sorry.
-and the star of the prosecution.
-But what we shouldn't forget is
-I'm so sorry.
that it's not the flower or star
that makes the prosecution work properly.
It's numerous prosecutors
who fulfill their duties quietly.
PROSECUTOR HONG JONG-HAK
Drink this.
Thanks.
Well, Prosecutor Cha.
About what I said before.
I said that without knowing anything.
So don't take it personally.
I wouldn't have said that
if you told me in advance.
I'm sorry. You should go now.
You always
make excuses.
What?
That's because you didn't know?
You wouldn't have said that if you knew?
Well, I beg to differ.
You really thought
I was the type of prosecutor
that would conspire with an assemblyman
and hide away defendants.
Why are you pretending you didn't?
You don't have to do this every time.
You can stop
giving me excuses from now on.
I'll just let things slide.
Well, I mean…
Please enjoy your meal.
Why don't we get up?
You fell for that?
-You fell for it, right?
-Mr. Cho, please.
You should've at least told me.
-Tell you what?
-You could've given me a heads-up.
About what? Enjoy your meal.
Enjoy it.
I'm sorry, Mr. Cho.
Eat a lot. All right.
Stop being bashful and just laugh.
You seemed pretty dejected.
I know. He did.
Do you want more meat?
I'll have some instead.
Jeez.
Enjoy your food.
-You can have mine.
-Okay.
Gosh, you caught a good one.
Everything goes better on a full stomach.
AMBULANCE
This isn't a military facility.
Why are you so startled?
They say a burnt child dreads the fire.
-Please enjoy it.
-Okay.
-What will happen to the Branch Chief?
-He's resigning.
I'm not sure if we served him well.
Do you remember Kwon Du-pil?
Now that you're retiring,
do you miss the old days?
We're prosecutors, not torturers.
We're in the top 1%.
If we're wrong, who is right?
-He's a streamer.
-He's an attention seeker.
Is he crazy?
He's here for a crime.
What makes him so proud?
-Mr. Hong, a new video is up.
-What?
Did you not notice he was filming this?
Threaten to sue him for slander.
Do what you can to make him take it down.
Darn it!
Who do you think is responsible
for the Branch Chief's resignation?
It's because of Prosecutor Cha.
We have nothing to apologize for.
If we apologize for that,
how would we work as prosecutors?
I won't apologize.
Thank you for everything.
Jinyeong Branch has
the lowest indictment rate.
I, Choi Jong-hun, will make things right.