♪Moonlight on the surface of the sea♪
♪Dances with wind♪
♪Amid the torrent of the secular world♪
♪I find my heart♪
♪In this chaotic time♪
♪You’re thinking of me all the time♪
♪Though this love could have no result♪
♪Your figure with a sword in hand♪
♪Blurs in my dream♪
♪Once impetuous and ambitious♪
♪I find joy back♪
♪Under the disguise of sea♪
♪I follow your steps♪
♪And shut the surging waves
off my heart♪
♪You know I’m proud, joyful♪
♪And loyal, and I never despair♪
♪Ride a gallant steed♪
♪And go out to the vastness♪
♪Every slightest feeling of love♪
♪Blooms in my life♪
♪Melancholy♪
♪But wonderful♪
=Novoland: Pearl Eclipse=
=Episode 18=
Get out of here!
You showed up
just as Lord expected.
Here you are
while your master is long gone,
leaving you as bait
to distract others.
Lackeys like you
don’t get to know who we serve.
Leader,
did Master leave without us?
Master...
Master would never
abandon us.
You want a name?
Fine.
I’ll tell you.
It’s Manager Ju Qiqi at Fabric Office.
All this
is her plan.
Oh, no!
Fabric Office!
Unbelievable!
How dare they
murder a house of maids
right under my nose!
Unless
someone has eyes and ears
all over the palace
and assets under deep cover
right next to me!
What do we know so far?
Your Majesty,
I’ve traced those assassins
back to their leader, Wu Qi,
who kept them
for years.
All of them
and members of Fabric Office
were killed by the same poison.
That’s it?
I don’t need that!
What I need
is the name of the mastermind.
Your Majesty,
one embroiderer at Fabric Office
had very little poison
and could still breathe
when I found her.
She’s being treated as we speak.
Once she wakes up,
she’ll give us more leads to work with.
Check everyone in the palace.
Bring all Wu Qi’s accomplices
to justice!
Yes, Your Majesty.
Your safety is guaranteed.
Guards have been replaced
to tighten the security.
You can trust
everyone around you.
Jianming,
we should’ve never
been lenient.
You’re up!
Master,
I’m too tough
to die.
We’re all worried sick about you.
I’m glad you’re awake.
Master,
I don’t regret it.
What do you mean?
When I was half-awake,
I vaguely heard you saying
I would’ve regretted running into you.
You should know
whatever happened to me
has nothing to do with others.
Meeting you
is one of the few best things
that have ever happened to me.
Master,
I’d never regret it.
I didn’t,
I don’t
and
I’ll never regret meeting you.
You could’ve died.
Don’t say that.
All the more reason
to let it out now
when I still can
before it’s too late.
Master...
Relax.
I’ll be right back.
Here’s Young Master Haishi’s medicine.
Got any word from Zhuoying
or Zhang Chengqian?
No, Lord.
Not yet.
Put the word out
that Mr. Fang is awake
and he’s stable.
Yes.
Your wound is still fresh. Don’t move.
Take your medicine.
Are you all right? Is it too hot?
No, just bitter.
Master,
you’re frowning again.
I’m sorry
for letting Earlji go
and worrying you all so much.
Don’t do that ever again.
I never said
to save others with your life.
Finish your medicine.
I’ve learned my lesson.
(Postal Relay Station)
Let’s drink.
- Here. Fill the cup.
- Fill it.
Come on.
Mr. Su won’t be back
anytime soon.
Let’s drink, guys!
- Yes! Cheers!
- Cheers!
Where’s Su Ming?
Officer,
what’s this about? Don’t hurt us.
Who are you
to ask about Mr. Su’s whereabouts?
Don’t make me ask again.
Uh... Mr. Su
had the boat ready yesterday.
He and his five assistants
are heading to Shangzhou by water.
Your Highness! Your Highness!
Your Highness!
What’s the emergency?
Bad news, Your Highness!
Bihong is arguing
with a few eunuchs at North Garden Lane.
It’s our lost kite.
It got out from Yu’an Palace.
(Flowered forehead is from last night.)
Look, it’s inscribed!
Miss,
please don’t make it hard for us.
Eunuch Mu
asked us
to deliver this kite to His Majesty.
How dare you
try to intercept it!
I mean, it’s just a kite!
“Just a kite”?
It’s...
Bihong,
you were supposed to come back
after collecting things
from the Storehouse,
yet here you are bickering with others.
Your Highness,
they found our kite.
I asked them to return it
but they refused to.
(Flowered forehead is from last night.)
(Behind the screen window she smiles brightly.)
That’s not ours.
It’s just a kite.
Don’t make a fuss
about it.
Behave yourself
or you’ll be punished!
But...
Let her finish.
- Your Majesty.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
What’s this all about?
Show me. Let me see.
You three, come over.
But what?
I’m giving you a chance
to finish your sentence.
Your Majesty, that kite
flew away from Yu’an Palace.
We made the body
and Consort Shurong colored it.
It took us a while to finish.
Look,
there are characters on it.
Stop lying,
you troublemaker!
Can you even read
the characters of Dazheng?
I can’t
but I know
what they say.
“Flowered forehead is from last night.
Behind the screen window
she smiles brightly.
We first met when peonies bloomed.
Yet we had to part too soon.”
Is that correct, Your Majesty?
I’m sure it’s your kite.
I found it by accident.
That poem is well-written.
I wish I could’ve read it before.
And?
What’s the other half?
I know too little
to finish it.
You don’t have it?
Or are you keeping it from me?
If you are,
I incline to think
your maid lied to me.
That’s a serious offense.
The other half is,
“I could share my feelings with no one.
The moon and flowers
are my only company.”
“With...
With no one.”
(Flowered forehead is from last night.)
(Behind the screen window she smiles brightly.)
(We first met when peonies bloomed.
Yet we had to part too soon.)
Spot on!
It’s a genius idea
to have your kite
find its way to me.
I’ll take it.
I haven’t seen you for a while.
Maybe
I’ll summon you to Jincheng Palace
when I need someone to grind the ink.
Your Majesty...
Your...
How’s Mr. Fang doing today?
The panacea worked.
I heard he’s recovering
after taking it.
That’s great!
God bless him!
It’s worth it
as long as he can recover.
Mr. Fang!
What are you doing here, Mr. Fang?
Staying indoors all day
is boring.
I came out
for a walk.
Thank you
for taking care of me these days.
I’ll repay you
for that.
You’ve saved me more than once.
That’s the least I should do.
Without you,
the Jiamanese
wouldn’t have survived this long,
let alone have driven out
Lord of Right Pudun.
Would you like something to eat?
Are you hungry? I can get you some food.
No, thanks.
Those red decorations
are still over the place.
When you were sick in bed,
we were too worried
to do anything else.
Now that you’re getting better,
we’ll find time
to remove them all.
But not today.
Maybe tomorrow.
No rush. That can wait.
Have you seen my master?
Lord Qinghai just went out
to the market.
Good day.
Greetings, sir.
Take a look.
Do you have any sugar?
Basic supplies
are still lacking
after the chaos in the city,
not to mention rare goods like sugar.
I’m the only one in town
selling it.
Brown sugar
may seem rough,
but I assure you it’s clean.
There’s no sand at all.
Have a look.
It’s the best sugar
money can buy here.
I’m sure
it’s of top quality.
You know better, sir!
I’ll take it all.
Sure! No problem!
All right. Thank you! Thanks a lot!
- It’s not...
- Let’s go.
See you, sir!
Let go.
You’ve barely recovered.
Better put on more layers.
The wind
can give you a cold.
I’m good.
Liar.
I’m fine, Master.
It’s like ice.
How could you feel warm?
I feel
your hand
is colder than mine,
but holding it
makes me feel warm inside.
Nonsense!
Master,
would you like some sugar?
Pass.
This brown sugar you bought
is even better
than osmanthus sugar.
It’s so sweet that it overpowers
my bitter medicine this morning.
Taste it, Master.
It’s windy. Come.
Gentlemen,
may I offer you some clothes?
My fur coats
are the best in the city.
Good choice!
That one is made of the fur
of snow fox on Red Plain.
Is this for me?
It’s windy.
What do you think?
It looks thick enough.
What’s so funny?
I’m too slow to realize
that someone
isn’t as smart
as he seems.
I’ll take it.
Thank you. Thank you, sir.
Have a nice day.
Thank you, sir.
You’re welcome.
That’s mine! Give it to me!
I will if you can catch me!
Are you going to follow me around
all day?
Why ask?
I have something for you, too.
What is it?
I can’t tell you now.
(Happiness)
Master.
Are those candles
for me?
You were
working all day
in the dim light.
These candles
will make your eyes comfortable.
Don’t you know red candles
are only for one occasion?
What...?
♪Suits us well♪
If you don’t like them,
I’ll put them away.
Go to bed.
♪Beneath the tranquility the world sees♪
♪Sacrifices♪
♪Playful and simple I am♪
♪Hate to stay neutral and forbearing♪
♪And waste life♪
♪Time roars past♪
♪Still I follow♪
♪Men of loyalty and integrity♪
♪To think of you♪
♪I don’t need your response♪
♪Or company♪
♪It’s the blooming season♪
♪The best time of a year♪
♪Why sit alone♪
Aren’t you going to sleep?
I am.
♪As in a city in wash painting♪
♪A man saves every possible stroke♪
♪And refuses to reunite♪
♪Heart and soul♪
Lord.
Did you just come back?
Yes.
Su Ming got ahead of us
and headed to the Left Tribe
in Hanbei through the Lax Sea.
I failed to
intercept him halfway.
Please punish me.
That’s fine.
Don’t blame yourself.
Su Ming is cunning and scheming.
He blocked the information
when the Left Tribe of Huku
raided Well Town.
And now,
he’s rushing to their territory.
They must’ve been in cahoots
since long ago.
It’s too risky for Young Master Zhuoying
to go to Hanbei alone.
Also,
I’ve got news from the capital.
About what?
Su Ming’s men
failed to
snatch the spy away
and poisoned themselves
before making Fabric Office
the scapegoat.
Manager Ju
died of poisoning
along with all members there
except for one embroiderer
who is in critical condition
and under treatment day and night.
She may or may not survive.
What?
Lord...
Don’t say a word to Haishi.
Lord,
an envoy came from Huangquan Pass
with His Majesty’s edict,
waiting for you at the main hall
of the Governor’s Mansion.
Lord Qinghai.
Mr. Fu.
This is His Majesty’s secret edict.
Thank you, Mr. Fu.
(Come back immediately. Xu)
The wind is too strong.
Don’t stand at the window for too long.
I’ve heard about the bloodbath.
Are you going back?
It’s His Majesty’s order.
Manager Ju had a tough life.
She died a horrible death.
Could you burn incense for me
when you get back?
Sure.
I’m sorry for your loss.
I’m ordered to leave immediately.
And I’ve asked
the Governor and Zhang Chengqian
to look after you.
Don’t worry about me, Master.
I’m fully capable of
taking care of myself.
When we meet again,
I’ll be
as good as new.
We won’t be able to see each other
in a long while
after I leave.
I can live with that.
For what it’s worth,
I know we’re only one step away.
One step?
Yes. One step.
Emotionally speaking.
I was
afraid of you.
I didn’t want to upset you
or disappoint you,
so
I was scared
to take that step.
But now, I’m different.
I’m no longer scared.
However far
you’re away,
I’ll find you.
Lord,
we’re ready to leave.
Let’s go!
(Lanzi)
Mr. Zhang.
Lord asked me
to take care of you.
Thanks.
He should be
back in the capital by now.
We’d better
leave and return to Huangquan Battalion
as quickly as possible.
It’s too soon.
You’re still too weak
to travel that far.
I suggest you rest for a few more days
in Lanzi
before going back.
Mr. Zhang,
it’s not my condition
but the condition back home
that concerns you, right?
Nothing can get past you, Mr. Fang.
What’s the status there?
After that spy Song Dian
lured you to Mount East Piluo
on your way to
tracking down those people of Huku,
Lord discovered
moles among us.
Then he rushed over,
which reached
Lord of Right Pudun’s ears instantly.
Given the speed,
that message must’ve gone out
from Huangquan Battalion.
Meaning
Su Ming’s men
are still there.
That’s what Lord thinks, too.
The only one
dumb enough
to go to such great lengths
to kill Master
can be none other but Su Ming.
Now that he’s defected,
his men inside
are lying low.
Mr. Zhang,
those moles
aren’t as important as
Huangquan Battalion’s stability.
Under this circumstance,
only if the border is secure
will Master
be able to focus on traitors.
The longer we’re away,
the riskier things get.
We should go back
right away.
Sure.
I’ll have them get prepared.
(Lanzi)
Lord,
did you leave anything behind?
General!
(Wu Qi and everyone else are gone.)
Wu Qi and everyone else
are gone.
They were homeless
before you took them in.
It was their honor
to die for you.
Ju Qiqi’s death
is far from enough!
How far are we
from the Left Tribe of Huku?
A little over 15 kilometers.
I’ve sent them a message
last night.
Lord of Left Pudun
will have his men pick us up.
Good.
We’ll be able to rest
in a few hours.
You’re from Jifeng Pavilion.
Nice to meet you, General Su.
All these years,
you’ve been
coming at us
and targeting our members
one by one.
You must be proud of yourself.
Have you ever expected
that you’ll be the target one day?
General,
go back with me
or meet your death here and now.
Fang Jianming is fast.
But the thing is
you’re on
Lord of Left Pudun’s territory.
Do you have a shot
at seizing anyone on your own?
Kill him!
Go, General!
You are...?
General Su,
show your respect
for Lord of Left Pudun!
Greetings, Lord.
Kill him!
Princess Hongyao’s badge!
Are you Su Ming?
I am.
Do you know the man
after you?
He’s with Jifeng Pavilion.
Fang Jianming’s chief disciple,
Fang Zhuoying.
Fang Zhuoying?
Su Ming has gone over to the enemy
but his followers are still in the city.
I want you to track down all of them.
Detain and question
every suspect.
Don’t let
anyone get away.
Yes.
Is Lord Qinghai on his way back?
Yes, Your Majesty.
He’s been traveling
day and night
ever since your edict arrived.
He should be here
very soon.
Good day, Your Majesty.
Your Highness,
why bother sewing
the shredded fur?
You might prick your finger again.
His Majesty’s edict has arrived.
His Majesty’s edict is as follows:
His Majesty
hasn’t seen Consort Shurong for a while.
You’re summoned to Jincheng Palace.
Yes.
Your Majesty,
Consort Shurong has arrived.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Rise.
Yes.
Have a seat.
Why are you following me around?
I can grind the ink for you.
No need.
I’m not reviewing any reports.
They’re too lengthy
and giving me sore eyes.
Your kite
is over there.
I can pour you tea.
Don’t.
There are servants for it.
Read it.
You have a beautiful voice.
Read word for word.
I wouldn’t dare.
Interfering in state affairs
is a capital crime.
You’ve provoked me more than once.
I thought
you’re bold.
Why are you getting cold feet now?
I’ll do it.
Do what?
Read the report.
Oh?
You aren’t afraid of death?
I’m not.
The world is under your feet.
If you want someone dead,
even if they’re innocent,
you can find dirt on them
or cook up charges.
People get wronged
all the time.
I could be found guilty
whether I read the report
or not.
But I know
a great emperor like you
would never harm the innocent,
so I have nothing to fear.
By that logic,
if I punished you,
would you call me a bad emperor?
I wouldn’t dare.
You aren’t too dull.
Read it.
I,
Prefect of Yuanzhong,
pay respect to Your Majesty...
(Tianqi)
(Dinghe Gate)
Shaozi!
Shaozi,
is it Fabric Office?
Are they
all dead?
(Dinghe Gate)
Greetings, Mr. Fang.
Miss Zheliu can’t see.
I’m sorry.
Miss... Miss Zheliu,
I’m sorry for your loss.
Thank you, Mr. Fang.
The first seven days
of mourning aren’t over
and I’m still in my mourning dress.
It might
bring you bad luck.
Please excuse me.
(Fabric Office)
Aunt,
His Majesty has allowed you
to go back to Liushang.
I know
kapok was your favorite,
so I made this pattern for you.
With this cover,
you’ll feel less cold.
Rest in peace, Aunt.
I swear
I’ll do my best
to take your blind embroidery
even further
and restore Fabric Office.
I’ve prepared gifts
for your friends and family back home.
With them there,
you’ll be in good hands.
You’ll never
be forlorn again.
Aunt,
I miss you!
I’ll forever
remember you.
Aunt,
I...
I’m sorry
that I can’t be there with you.
Farewell.
May you
rest in peace...
♪Kiss me with all your heart♪
♪This unacceptable true feeling♪
♪Suits us well♪
♪Sweeping across the moon
and the vermilion gate♪
♪Cool wind finds its effort vain♪
♪Beneath the tranquility the world sees♪
♪Sacrifices♪
♪Playful and simple I am♪
♪Hate to stay neutral and forbearing♪
♪And waste life♪
♪Time roars past♪
♪Still I follow♪
♪Men of loyalty and integrity♪
♪To think of you♪
♪I don’t need your response♪
♪Or company♪
♪It’s the blooming season♪
♪The best time of a year♪
♪Why sit alone♪
♪In freezing wind and moonlight♪
♪As in a city in wash painting♪
♪A man saves every possible stroke♪
♪And refuses to reunite♪
♪Heart and soul♪
♪The rest of your life♪
♪Will be a lonely journey♪
♪So do not try to heal♪
♪The part with me in♪
♪The way I paved for you♪
♪Mists in my eyes♪
♪And becomes a vivid token♪