Twenty-five years ago,
I was ten years old.
Fifteen years ago, twenty.
Five years ago, thirty.
And then,
five more years passed.
But I still feel like a ten-year-old.
Why am I still such a child?
You're not a child.
A real child would say that he's an adult.
You really seem to be
a lot cooler than what I thought at first.
What a sight.
You two look great together.
Did you just figure that out?
Ra-im, were you supposed to meet him?
No.
He should've gotten the clue by now.
He must be either really dumb...
or love me to death.
It must be one of those two.
What? "Dumb"?
Why are you wearing
a women's undergarment?
What? "Undergarment"?
You never learn, do you?
This outfit doesn't deserve
that kind of treatment from you.
A French environmentalist designer sewed
this flower pattern stitch-by-stitch--
I'll be heading in.
Drive home safely, Oskie.
I'll see you in my dreams, Ra-im.
Be careful on the stairs.
What about me?
Where's my goodbye? I drove here too.
You should watch yourself at night.
Do I look like I need
to watch myself at night?
The night should watch out for me!
Hey! Ra-im!
What the heck is he thinking?
Who are you calling, "Oskie"?
You've never called me by a nickname!
We're four years apart,
the perfect age gap for dating.
Hey! How could you slam the door
in my face like that?
Why can't you be considerate
of my prominent nose!
Hey! Gil Taeng-ja!
I wish I could take that down.
Is someone outside?
Just a barking dog. I told it to be quiet.
What kind of dog barks, "Gil Taeng-ja?"
-Did you hear that?
-Was it President Kim?
Why was he here?
I don't know.
Why didn't he come in
if he came all the way here?
By the way, you got a package.
They deliver so quickly nowadays.
What is it? A book?
Yes.
I went to someone's house
and he had a huge library full of books.
It made me wonder
if that person had read
every book on there,
and which ones he liked.
I wondered about what he had thought
and felt as he read those books.
I got so curious.
Is that why you bought
the same book that he's reading?
Yes.
I wanted to know what he's thinking.
What part of his heart did I miss?
Who knows? I might be able to find it.
You're right.
There comes that moment when you want
to know what someone truly thinks.
Why did you follow me in?
-Would you rather follow me outside?
-You're being awfully hostile.
It seems like
you did something to deserve it.
Not yet.
But seeing the way you act,
I can't guarantee that I won't.
I don't intend to meddle
in your love affairs,
but answer me this honestly.
Did you mean
what you said to Ra-im?
I said it, so, obviously I meant it.
What else would it mean?
-You shouldn't mean it.
-Why not?
Do you really like Ra-im?
Can you be responsible for those feelings?
"Be responsible"?
You're not fit to ask that.
Have you been responsible
for every girl you've met?
No, but I've taken the heat for it.
And the girls I see
would never carry around
a tattered bag in front of guys like us
and not understand how we would react.
They'd never be that innocent.
Why are you bringing that up?
See? If you can't even handle that,
how will you manage?
Could you give up everything?
-Do I have to?
-You don't.
You can just lose the girl instead.
It's simple.
Do you know what makes our mothers
different from other rich women?
They'd never hand the inheritance
over to us in their lifetime. Why?
Because that's the only way
we'd listen to them.
Can you defeat your mom?
I have no right to defeat her,
so, how could I?
You have no right,
but you don't have a reason either.
To you, marriage is just business
like mergers and acquisitions.
Isn't it?
That's why
you should just meet someone like you.
Don't make Ra-im suffer.
You don't deserve her.
Also, what was holding Seul's
hand in Haenam all about?
I'm telling you, that wasn't me.
Then, who was it? Was it a ghost?
Just what is your intention?
You want to marry someone like Seul,
but you want to enjoy puppy love
with Ra-im and then dump her?
You're a jerk.
Lay off on both of them.
They're both
too good for you.
You have no right,
but you don't have a reason either.
To you, marriage is just business
like mergers and acquisitions.
Just meet someone like you.
Don't make Ra-im suffer.
You don't deserve her.
MR. NO-GOOD JOO-WON'S HOUSE!
COWARD
THIS MINOR MELANCHOLY
HE WALKS AT THE SPEED OF REMINISCENCE
ALICE IN WONDERLAND
LIKE A FAIRYTALE
A NIGHT WHERE
ONE GALAXY CROSSES ANOTHER
A BAD BOY STANDS
THIS MINOR MELANCHOLY
HE WALKS AT THE SPEED OF REMINISCENCE
Hold it! Hand me the script.
Yes, sir!
-Here, sir.
-Okay.
Here in this scene,
you're not fighting your lover to death.
There has to be a sense of sadness.
You're all brute strength.
You're going to slaughter your lover.
I must've gotten too excited
over the thought of working again.
Hello. Have you eaten?
-Hello, Director.
-I'll eat soon.
Here.
What is it?
You'll see when you listen to it.
-Can I listen to it now?
-You're lacking discipline.
Listen to it after training.
All right.
Director! She's listening to it
without permission!
She's just undisciplined. Discipline her.
When did you record all this?
Thank you so much!
How should we discipline her?
Should we have a muster call?
Let's make her do some PT exercises.
Just make her mop.
-Five, six, seven, eight!
-One, two, three, four!
Hurry or we'll be late.
Hurry up and get dressed.
I've told you before.
An entertainer is a miserable job,
existing to only entertain others.
I can understand being on TV,
but how does a fan signing event
make sense in this situation?
I could talk to each fan and apologize,
but how can I sign autographs?
I don't have the courage
to face them right now.
Would you rather announce
that your agency is in a crisis?
Get dressed already!
Are you really all right?
Is U-yeong insane or what?
-How could he suspect you?
-Lower your voice.
But,
did you really not do it?
Do you wish that it was me?
I just want to be sure.
You're good at keeping it together though.
You're even getting your hair done
at a time like this.
Other than when the nation has fallen
or when your parents have passed away,
a woman should always have her hair done.
There is only one thing a woman should
protect, especially in a crisis.
Her beauty.
I'll wash your hair now.
Yes, it's me.
Did you find him?
Is he Korean?
What?
Are you sure that's his name?
No, it's just...
This is interesting.
Excuse me.
What shampoo is she using?
That? It's an imported shampoo.
It's popular because of its fragrance.
Director Yoon only uses that one.
Wash my hair with that too, please.
OSKA FAN SIGNING
-What's your name?
-Jin-ju.
TO JIN-JU, OSKA
Here you go.
-What's your name?
-Min-ju.
Thank you.
-What's your name?
-Lee Jin.
Lee Jin.
-It's okay!
-Be strong, Oska!
Oskie, it's okay!
We believe in you!
Don't pay attention to them.
Be strong! I love you!
You have us! We'll protect you!
Oskie!
Who's protecting who?
I'm going to protect you!
Trust me! I'm not someone who plagiarizes.
I might go off-key sometimes,
but my conscience is as clear as daylight!
-Got that?
-Yes!
-It's okay! Be strong, Oska!
All right. I got it, so, get in line.
You, over there!
The adorable one.
Yes, you. Don't cut in line.
I will sign today's autographs
not as the singer Oska,
but as the human being, Choi U-yeong.
TO BO-RI, CHOI U-YEONG
Thank you.
-Hello!
-Hello.
What's your name?
Okay.
-What's your name?
-Seon-ju.
TO SEON-JU, CHOI U-YEONG
-What's your name?
-Hye-su.
Listen to your mother.
Watch the road and your weight.
And look me up on the Internet. Got it?
-Okay! Stay strong!
-Stay strong!
What's your name?
I don't believe in you.
You don't believe in me either, right?
But I'm still your fan.
Please write,
"To Yoon Seul, with my eternal love."
To Yoon Seul.
Thank you for loving me so much.
December 2010, Oska.
Excuse me, but do you know
how much these seats cost?
I paid 250,000 won. Why?
Then,
did she pay 250,000 won too?
-Excuse me?
-Because I did.
Please take her.
Then, these seats are all...
Yes. All three of these seats...
are mine.
I like having both armrests to myself.
How was the opera?
I couldn't focus.
Book it again.
Get the entire row this time.
-The entire row?
-Some woman placed her bag on my seat.
After talking to her, I realized
I wouldn't have had to speak to her
if I had booked the entire row.
For most, that would be
a difficult realization.
But I'm special.
What is it that you had to tell me?
This is the data for tomorrow's
Bisong Resort VIP presentation.
That's tomorrow?
Why didn't you tell me sooner?
Your brain must be on a break
because I've been lenient lately.
Oh, my goodness.
You even confirmed the schedule...
Why are you upsetting me?
I'm upset too.
Hearts in my signature?
I shouldn't have said it.
Now, she actually
thinks she's Kim Tae-hee.
Up until now, resorts have been centered
on a leisure concept like skiing, golfing.
People go to rest,
but end up being more tired.
That is why I thought,
"Isn't there a resort
for true relaxation?"
One that provides rest
just at the thought of going.
And for this reason,
Bisong Resort, which will renew history,
has been built on a hill,
surrounded by forests and valleys.
That doesn't mean we tampered with nature.
We left it as is.
We made sure that not a single tree
or rock was touched.
More specifically,
I made sure.
I will show you the rooms.
He's all bark and no bite.
He's always had a way with words.
They say the chairman has arrived.
What? Out of the blue?
As you can see, the interior
has been built with the finest materials.
You can trust me.
Every doorknob and spoon was handpicked.
By who? By me.
I'm sure you are all tired from walking,
so, I will keep this short.
We always keep it short.
Your soon-to-be villas
and my soon-to-be villa.
The stargazing, moonlight walks,
and the breeze await us.
A truly eco-friendly rest
will await you every day.
To wrap up,
we trust that you will love and support
our new healing resort.
We want to thank you all
for attending today.
-Thank you.
-Thank you for coming.
Okay. Bye.
Where is the chairman? Did he leave?
Yes. He just left.
He looked very satisfied.
Did he?
I've always been quick on my feet.
And
I found out who the CEO's physician is.
Did you?
President Kim is taking a walk.
I know. I've spoken to him.
If you need anything else...
I'm fine. Thank you.
Have some tea while I wash up.
I'm sweaty from the walk--
No, me first.
It'll only take five minutes.
What? Stay for dinner.
I have plans.
I just came to check up on you.
Don't you need a medicine refill?
My medicine?
I haven't been taking medication lately.
-You haven't?
-How did I do that?
How did I survive sleeping
in that tiny room without any medication?
-Did you go somewhere?
-What I mean is...
Never mind.
You might think I've really gone crazy
and institutionalize me.
Anyway,
I guess I don't need
the medication anymore.
But I have a question.
Usually, do people give up things in order
to get something that they really want?
Yes, because it's usually
something they don't deserve.
No way. Then, are you saying
that she's too good for me?
"She"?
This woman...
Does she always have to act
so tacky and cliché?
Do you even know how difficult it is
for a woman who has nothing
to be tacky and cliché like this?
Most women would've taken it and left.
I told you. She's too good for you.
-Is it true?
-Yes.
I just got off the phone
with Reporter Park from Star Sports.
That fraud sent in a letter of apology,
confessing that it was all his fault.
That idiot.
Why did he send it to them?
Are they releasing a seventh album?
Are they a Korean Wave star?
My scandals keep that
newspaper company in business.
It looks like you're back to life
since you're shooting your mouth.
The article will be up in a few hours.
You've been through a lot.
Yes. They say when you're young,
suffering is worth the experience.
But I'm too old for all this.
He looked like he was never
going to come clean.
Why did he give in all of a sudden?
Did my fans dox him?
I'm sure he has a conscience.
Anyway, this is good.
Release a statement about your experience.
Let's find a good composer
and do this seventh album right.
All right. You take care of that.
And you, find out where Han Tae-seon is.
I should have apologized to him.
It seemed that
he was going to leave Korea.
If he's still in Korea,
tell him that I want to see him.
Where are you going?
Home.
I'm expecting a package.
It must have been hard
these past few days.
I'm Yoon Seul. Nice to meet you.
How did you find me?
You're the original composer
of Oska's title song,
the one with the plagiarism issue, right?
You wrote it for your friends from London
who fed you and gave you a place to stay,
and a Korean composer plagiarized it.
You wrote it
under the nickname, "Sun", right?
You researched my background thoroughly.
I have many, many connections,
so, I can obtain information quickly.
I called you to offer you a contract deal.
I brought the contract.
Would you like to see it?
It includes a house, a studio, and a car.
Let me know if you want more.
I don't have the stomach to endure
business people like you.
If you'll excuse me.
You can pay for the tea
since you called me out.
Do I look like
I'm in business to earn money?
I like your music.
And I have a lot of money.
Create the music that you want.
I will help you.
Why?
Why would you help me?
Maybe you're too young to know,
but it's not easy to find someone
who knows your true value.
That's why you tried to leave Korea.
Isn't it?
Up until now, no one recognized
Han Tae-seon's music.
No one even knew who Sun was.
But I have recognized you.
Isn't that
reason enough?
What is that?
This?
It's a game console.
Is this where Choi U-yeong lives?
What?
The new one came out? When?
Just a few days ago. Mr. Choi is
the first person to own one in Korea.
Should we put it over there?
No. Load it back up.
-Pardon?
-This isn't Choi U-yeong's house.
Hey!
-Hey.
-Get off right now!
I waited three months for this.
Then, wait three more for another one.
Why would I do that?
I'm going to have it moved tomorrow,
so, don't touch it and get off.
Fine.
Do as you wish.
Just make sure to avoid Dong-gyu.
What do you mean?
You know how exact I am about being fair.
As soon as you take this,
I'll send your photos with Park Chae-rin
to Dong-gyu.
You evil jerk.
If you leave this here,
I'll give you the originals
in three months.
Do you mean it?
-Do you promise?
-Of course.
I saw that you cleared up
the plagiarism issue.
Of course.
I've been a good man all my life.
God may test me,
but he won't let me suffer for long.
And the truth always prevails.
So, you should watch out.
-What about me?
-Don't pretend like you don't know.
Your current infatuation with Gil Ra-im.
If you have any true feelings for her,
stop with the act,
and come back to your normal self.
That fits you, not this.
I've already decided.
I'm going to break up with her.
-Really?
-Except that
I'll do it later.
Not right now. I can't now.
Why not now?
I've thought about it from all angles
for the past few days.
I like her.
So, I'm going to see her
as if I have no pride.
What?
I may find her novel and interesting now
but if I keep seeing her,
I'll certainly grow tired of her.
She'll be like any other woman.
She'll be neither hot nor cold.
I give it three months.
Nothing will happen to my fortune
just because I see her for three months.
Jerk.
-I'm going to tell Ra-im.
-She already knows.
That all she can be is the Little Mermaid.
With her personality,
I don't think she'll get clingy.
You're being very clingy right now
in my eyes.
I am?
What do you want?
-Pay up.
-What?
-I gained weight.
I had very clear-cut abs
before we had our bodies switched,
but where are they now?
My clothes don't look good on me anymore
without my abs.
So, give them back.
Psycho.
These are the ones you washed.
Just keep them.
Why would I?
I think they'll fit perfectly.
Get rid of them.
And I never wore this one.
I'm sorry. That got mixed in there.
Anyway, keep them,
since they're better
than the ones you have already.
Psycho.
Take responsibility.
-What now?
-Me.
I'm constipated.
What did you feed me?
Why can't I push them off?
It's completely blocked up.
What are you going to do about it?
Do you have proof that it was me?
Evidence? Should I bag it up and bring it?
Pervert!
What now? What do you want?
My department store stocks went down.
Maybe they found out
that the CEO is crazy.
Are you going to say that's my fault?
You think it wasn't?
I told you not to sign anything.
What were you thinking?
You never dreamed
that with each signature,
you're affecting the stock market,
did you?
That is my status,
and that is what
your juvenile heart signatures are worth.
Do you understand what you've done now?
What was I supposed to do?
Mr. Kim said that I had to do it.
-So, I'm going to fire him.
-What? That's not fair.
Should I not?
Fine, then I'm going to come and go
as I please.
And every time, you must greet me
with love, joy, and gratitude, okay?
In your dreams.
I can greet you
with violence and profanity.
Do you want a preview?
Are you okay with Mr. Kim being fired?
Jerk.
I dare you.
Get mad at me!
What did my clothes ever do?
Psycho.
See.
Why are girls like that?
They don't do it
when they're with each other.
But when they're with guys,
they get foam on their lips
and pretend not to know about it.
Gross.
Come here.
What? There are no napkins.
I can't use my jacket.
"Stitch-by-stitch", remember?
I'm warning you,
don't use violence towards me from now on.
If you do so, this is how I'll react.
-Get in.
-Yes!
First day of shooting!
I can't wait.
This is great.
Ra-im, what are you doing?
Excuse me?
I'm sorry.
Let's roll.
-What?
-I'm going too.
Do you even know where we're going?
Get lost.
Anywhere is fine.
I said get lost.
Let's go.
What are you doing?
I told you to watch out
for my prominent nose.
What's the matter? I told him to come.
-Get in.
-He's never even received proper training.
I'm not the type to fail at things.
I'm a fast learner.
All we're doing today
is running and falling.
Or, he can just stay in the car.
Who are you to stop him, anyway?
Get in already. The director is waiting.
What the heck!
-What are you doing?
-It's so cramped.
Let's go.
Can't we go separately though?
It's so uncomfortable.
If you speak, you're getting left behind.
Even me?
He spoke. Leave him so we have more room.
Hey--
You heard what she said.
Why is he here?
I thought he gave up,
but he keeps hanging around Ra-im,
so, I brought him.
Ra-im is so clueless.
She keeps driving him away,
so, I'm playing Cupid.
It'd be good for Ra-im.
He can make things easier for her.
I'll head off first. Bring the rest.
Yes, sir.
Is everyone ready?
-Yes.
-One minute.
Where's my spear?
-Here you go.
-Thank you.
Hey.
Yes, Mr. Money-maker Joo-won. What is it?
I think something went wrong.
It's been switched, right?
What has?
Take it off. That's my costume.
What?
Get him!
-Get him!
What happened?
I told him that if he does well today,
I'd let him come to our workshop.
What are you doing?
The ground's all muddy!
Get them!
Hey!
You! What do you think you're doing?
He's on your side!
Are you a spy?
Come on.
-Sorry.
-"Sorry"?
I apologize. He must have been confused.
Were we on the same side?
I didn't know.
Weren't you an Arab spy?
Or a Middle-Eastern oil merchant?
Goodness. He's your leader. Pay attention.
We're allies?
-He's a piece of work.
-Oh, gosh.
Okay. Next scene.
Is everyone ready?
Wait.
Get ready, martial arts team.
-Yes, sir!
-Hey.
-My goodness.
-Yes?
-You know the scene we just did
where we ran and got shot by arrows?
-Let's take a look at the footage.
-Excuse me?
I'm actually a cameo
on the same level as Jang Dong-gun.
I just need to quickly check
how I looked--
Where did this screwball come from?
Out of my way.
Is the martial arts team not ready yet?
I'm sorry. We're ready now.
You don't look too bad.
Director Lim will be out soon as well.
Okay. The martial arts team is ready.
We'll start shooting in five minutes.
There is a disorder known
as Alice in Wonderland syndrome.
It is a fascinating and sad disorder
in which one's perception is distorted
as if one is looking through
a telescope upside down,
causing one to live in a fairytale world.
I am certain that I have this disorder.
Otherwise, why would every moment
with this average girl
feel like a fairy tale?
-Good work, everyone!
-Good work!
-Thank you.
-Good work.
Why aren't you eating?
-Sir?
-I don't eat food
unless I know exactly where it came from.
Don't eat it. Eat something warm later.
I still have scenes to shoot.
Where is Director Lim?
Did he go somewhere
to eat something better?
He's gone to shoot
a horseback riding insert. Why?
That's what I mean.
Why are you doing this ridiculous job
where you have to shoot an insert
while starving?
Just eat your food.
I just don't get it.
It's not good money, there's no fame,
you could get seriously injured
or even lose your life.
So, why do you do this job?
"The pride of being a stunt actor"?
No one will recognize you.
They only remember the leads.
Who cares about pride?
Am I wrong?
You're right.
However...
this person remembers me.
This person remembers me.
And I remember all of them too.
Sure.
But it's only a few people.
How does that change anything?
"A few people"? What about you then?
How many friends do you have?
How many of your friends would
get injured in your place
and be glad that it wasn't you,
and laugh it out together?
This is why I told you not to come.
I don't understand
why you laugh at what we do,
but it's what we chose.
This is what we're most passionate about.
That's why we do it.
Who are you to judge our work?
What gives you that right?
Thank you for the food!
Great work today.
-You should eat.
-I am.
Ra-im was awesome today.
Director, you were great today too.
Good job today.
Great work, guys. Eat up!
-Thank you!
Eat up.
What about me?
You can't eat this stuff.
You said that only perverts eat it.
It's up to me whether I eat or not.
You're holding the tongs,
so, you have a duty to not discriminate.
You said you want discrimination.
Being set apart and treated differently
are the principles you people live by.
You can't eat this?
How do you call yourself a man?
Who said I can't?
And this has nothing
to do with being a man--
You said you wanted it. Eat.
I am eating it.
It tastes so...
Chew it.
Chew it and swallow.
No! I'm going to melt it.
What?
Why am I here?
Did we switch again?
Are you still drunk?
-Wash your face.
-Why am I here if we didn't?
Why do you think?
Think hard.
I asked you because I don't know.
Why am I...
My head.
Great work today.
You all did great.
Gosh...
I'm going to eat breakfast
with Ra-im tomorrow.
Are you crazy? What's wrong with you?
Good!
It's game over if you do.
Says who?
You can't!
Over my dead body!
Right.
You shouldn't.
What are you talking about?
I slept at her house
so many times.
You have no idea,
and yet you keep going on and on.
Hey!
Why are you going in there?
Don't ever go in there.
Let me go.
This is my home.
I lived here.
I've worn her underwear...
I've bathed her,
and I've brushed her teeth
three times a day.
Shut your mouth.
Do you seriously want me to kill you?
It's been a while since I've been hit.
I could've dodged it.
Ra-im,
why is he being such a pain?
Tell him to go home!
Director Lim, you be quiet too.
-Move.
-I have to go in first.
Director Lim.
Seriously!
What's going on?
Director Lim? President Kim?
I'm sorry. I couldn't stop them
as you can see.
I'm going to sleep on the bed!
Go ahead.
I'm going to sleep next to Ra-im.
Hey!
What's this? Why are you here?
Where are we?
Is this your home?
So, you've never been here, have you?
Of course, not.
My head.
Your head hurts, right?
The shame will come in five minutes.
That's where I'm at now.
That was quick.
Do you need any help?
Sit. You need to relieve your hangover.
Okay.
Did you get rid of my toothbrush?
Why would we have your toothbrush?
Give me the blue towel. I like that one.
He must still be drunk.
Ra-im!
What are you doing here?
I wanted to surprise you,
but what are they doing here?
Did you guys play poker all night?
What are you doing here?
I came to kidnap Ra-im.
You weren't picking up your phone.
I was a bit preoccupied this morning.
It's okay. Just know that you're
the first girl to not pick up my call.
I met you on Jeju Island, right?
This is perfect.
I was going to ask Ra-im to be my mentor
for a while. Is that all right?
"Mentor"?
Do you need action training?
Something like that.
I'll take that as a "yes."
Shall we go? What a sweet
and courteous kidnapping, right?
That's my charm.
I'm asking because I'm actually curious.
Do you laugh
because you actually like this,
or because it's pitiful?
It's the latter, right?
May I go?
Go ahead.
Hop in.
-Goodbye.
-See you.
How could you send her like that?
Then, why didn't you do anything?
You could've taken physical action
with your training,
and I could've gotten you an attorney.
Are we on the same side right now?
"The enemy of my enemy is a friend."
Don't you know that?
Why not? That's a famous Arabic saying.
A commercial?
Why are you so surprised?
Are you wondering what kind of nutjob
would give me a commercial?
-Is that it?
-Of course, not.
I'm just happy
because it's been a while for you.
The plagiarism scandal is over
and you got a commercial deal too.
I thought that
things were finally starting to look up.
Right?
You're really the best.
This isn't good.
When people understand me this well,
I start thinking about them at night.
Which night?
Tonight? Tomorrow night?
I want to know
so that I can think of you too.
At this rate,
we'll be dating in five seconds.
Are you being cautious of me?
I was joking.
I know.
But you caught me red-handed.
To be honest,
I am being cautious.
I'm starting
to grow fond of you.
Let's talk about work.
The commercial is for outdoor clothing,
and it's a rock-climbing concept.
But in my eight years of being a singer,
I've always been at the top.
So, I've forgotten how to climb up.
You can help me, right?
Although, your beauty might distract me.
It would take several months
to learn properly,
but you're pretty athletic
and you're not doing this professionally.
So, ten days should be enough.
You said, "yes", okay?
How should we schedule the training?
Whatever works for you is fine with me.
I'll call you once I confirm my schedule
with the team.
Excuse me.
Hello?
Yes, this is...
Right now?
Did you receive the money that I returned?
What money?
Didn't Joo-won return it?
Did he say that
he would return it for you?
Haven't you received it yet?
Are you kidding me?
Was that amount not enough?
Or, do you really want monthly payments?
You are really indecipherable.
Why should my son pay back what you spent?
Is he your wallet?
That isn't what I meant.
I know this is difficult to believe,
but it wasn't me who received that money.
Really? It wasn't you, you say?
Why? Did you leave your soul at home
when you came out to take money?
I assumed that you had no pride, but that
you'd keep your promise, at least.
Why are you still seeing Joo-won?
Do you have such a beggar's mentality
that you have no pride or shame?
You should've either taken the money
and left or asked for more.
Don't you have any business ethics?
You're a little out of line.
I am, aren't I?
Only in words though.
I'm sorry.
It was out of instinct.
I'll go again.
What in the world?
Oh my. What are you?
What are you doing?
Can't you see?
I can't just sit around and do nothing.
Why? What for?
You have no reason to treat her this way.
Kim Joo-won.
What are you doing to me
in front of this tramp?
You're wasting your energy, that's why.
I never said that I would marry her.
Why are you turning this
into some third-rate soap opera?
If my life starts to depend on her,
then, you can intervene. Stop me then.
This is temporary for me.
Can't you even wait that long?
Subtitle translation by Serena Lee