♪On the clouds, I drift in the wind♪
♪How vast is the world?♪
♪Overwhelming humans are crazy♪
♪How sensible are they?♪
♪Even in the mortal world, I'm immortal♪
♪I hate mortal rules♪
♪Way too many and complicated♪
♪I'm what I am♪
♪Absurd and haughty♪
♪That's usually me♪
♪Anything identical differs♪
♪Changing all the time♪
♪I wave and ride away♪
♪Staying for nobody♪
♪Among all the people in the world♪
♪Who'd stay together?♪
♪I watch the stars and drink wine♪
♪No one can understand♪
♪The whole world is free♪
♪Wind blows and water flows♪
♪You smile and I'm around♪
=Love In The Desert=
=Episode 11=
Is anyone on the hook?
Everything has been peaceful.
Nothing happened.
It doesn't feel right.
Enlighten me, My Lord.
What is not right?
The lantern fair
was heavily guarded.
But the bandits broke in.
These days,
why do they not do anything?
Bandits are arrogant.
Maybe they think
the most dangerous place
remains the safest.
My Lord,
shall we transfer the soldiers
from the Library and the Prayer Pavilion
to the Mortuary Temple?
The Mortuary Temple is unobstructed.
Once the bandits appear,
we can hunt them down.
Go get it done.
Yes.
The other piece
should get moving, too.
How can we win with such ordinary dishes?
She can do many tricks.
If she wins His Lordship's favor again,
I'll lose my position.
My Lady,
what do we do?
Go write a letter to my father
and ask him for help.
Ask him to send me
all the chefs from my tribe.
Yes, My Lady.
It will be done.
Did I offend him?
Who did you offend?
His Lordship?
That'd be terrible.
You don't know anything.
Don't say that.
Yepei.
Lianhuan.
In Enaqi,
did you learn to cook?
I can make ordinary dishes.
But dishes in Enaqi are rather simple.
I don't think His Lordship will like them.
Yunpei is rich in resources.
And there are many kinds of food.
- Lianhuan.
- Here.
Go to the kitchen
and ask about His Lordship's preference.
Yes.
(No worries.)
(You've learned the Herb Volume by heart.)
(I believe understanding the Dune Volume)
(is just a matter of time.)
(After you succeed,)
(I'll give you a big present.)
(What do you say?)
(The Desert Scroll)
His Lordship is too busy to be disturbed.
My Lady, please go back.
I'm here for something important.
Please tell His Lordship, Mr. Zhu.
It's not that I don't tell him.
Don't give me a hard time.
If I have to be scolded,
I really...
- You know we...
- Get her in.
There you go, My Lady.
Greetings, My Lord.
You don't usually
come to see me.
I'm here to ask for punishment.
Punishment for what?
The needlework competition.
Do you mean
the armor made of root bark?
That is a great contribution.
What is wrong?
To win the competition,
I bragged, regardless of the truth.
Armor made of the root
can make our soldiers invincible.
But large-scale planting won't work.
Why?
First,
trees in Yunpei don't have strong roots.
Less productive.
All the root bark in my house
is only enough for a pair of wristbands.
Second,
the climate in Yunpei is unpredictable.
Different from that in the north desert.
You mean this kind of tree
doesn't grow very well in Yunpei,
right?
Not really.
After I read the two volumes together,
I've learned a lot.
I get to know
where this kind of tree grows
and what kind of soil is the best.
I should keep reading.
But I don't have the Climate Volume.
Within a short time,
I'm afraid I can't advance.
You can't advance?
Yes.
For now,
I've tried many times
to solve the climate and soil problem
with the volumes I have.
Be patient.
After you
totally understand the Herb Volume,
I'll give you the Climate Volume.
You have the Climate Volume?
Of course.
Why would I lie?
(Just as I predicted,)
(Na Zhan has the Climate Volume.)
You've been watching the key all day long.
But you don't tell me
what it is used for.
Weird.
On the register, there are over 100 girls.
Why are there only 30
in Zuixiang Brothel?
You love this place?
Not really.
I'm just curious.
And...
I have a new mission.
What is it?
None of your business.
Why don't you just stay here?
Don't leave me behind again.
Come on, man.
Without a woman around,
you can't even comb your hair.
So shaggy.
You look like a beggar.
Don't try to be strong anymore.
- Don't move.
- I'm talking to you.
Worried?
Chief.
I don't want you to be a burden.
Chief, we checked it out.
In Yunpei, there are four arsenals.
They're located in four directions.
Qin Duo is the supervisor of the east.
Every morning, the watchmen change shifts.
Then the arsenal is weakly guarded.
We can sneak in at that time.
Get more men with us.
We'll do it tonight.
Yes.
Tonight, you'll snatch Yunpei's weapons?
Keep combing.
You just talk tough.
Do you want to go?
It's men's work.
I'm not going.
Besides,
I have bigger fish to fry.
If you dare, make this place
where we can always stay in Yunpei.
Can you?
Chief,
more soldiers are sent
to the Mortuary Temple today.
It's uncovered.
I can detect nothing.
The Temple is for ancestors.
Extra soldiers are indeed weird.
Except this place,
we should check
the Library and the Prayer Pavilion.
They're guarded by very few soldiers.
It's hard to know Na Zhan's crafty plan.
Give up on the Temple now.
Yes.
(Zuixiang Brothel)
Cheer up, girls.
Smile. Smile.
Mr. Wang, come in, please.
- Come on.
- Welcome.
- Come in.
- Entertain them.
Gentleman, come in.
You're always welcome.
Give them a good time.
- Chief.
Is it done?
- Yes. Don't worry.
- It's done.
After we took away the weapons,
we put back the empty boxes
where they used to be.
Within a year or two,
no one would know
we ransacked the arsenal.
Oh, boy.
You've finally used your brains.
Fox, watch and learn. Use your brains.
But Chief,
the Mansion is more heavily guarded.
Shall we fall back now
and sneak back in when it blows over?
Yeah.
Is she really that important?
Do you have to risk your life?
I never know what danger is.
Her eyes make me uneasy.
To invade Masui
and guard against Yunpei,
we have to get prepared.
- But...
- No buts.
Wait for me outside the Mansion.
Chief,
if Princess Xinwei asks
where you have gone,
what shall we say?
You're clever, aren't you?
Why do you even have to ask?
Figure it out.
- How to reply?
- Clever, aren't you?
Show off again, huh?
I...
Tell me how I can rely. Come on.
(Jade Restaurant)
Fancy pendants.
It's so heavily guarded.
I don't stand a chance to sneak in.
Yes.
This is where His Lordship lives.
Common people like us can never get in.
What's wrong, sir?
Get lost.
Waiter.
Sorry. Sorry.
Be right there.
Gentlemen, the same old food?
- Yes.
- Here.
Your boot is dirty.
Let me wipe it.
Wait a minute.
Let's do a good job
and take back the chefs from Zhenqu soon.
Lady Youjia will greatly reward us.
This time,
we'll make a fortune.
So soon?
Yes. I set off
upon receiving your letter.
What about the men I sent to get you?
Men?
I didn't meet them.
Did my father send you alone?
Do you think...?
Oh, no.
My Lady, do you think I'm not enough?
No, of course.
It is too hasty.
I thought Father
would send me at least three chefs.
It makes sense.
Forget it.
Since you came alone,
you must have some skills.
Show me.
Step aside and watch.
If I cut off your head,
I'll make soup with it.
You've got quite a temper.
Well done.
Does it satisfy you?
Impressive.
Father sent me such a good chef.
Xiaolian, take him
to the kitchen to register.
My Lady, in the competition,
we will win.
Before you taste some,
I have something to say.
First,
if it's delicious, tell me honestly.
If it's not, tell me honestly, too.
Second,
however it tastes,
give me your opinion.
There you go.
Taste this.
How does it taste?
Delicious.
Tastes great.
Which tastes best?
All the dishes.
Yeah. All the dishes.
Be specific.
There are vegetables and meat.
Neither too salty nor light.
Yepei.
Lianhuan.
This competition
is about getting the oasis.
Be serious.
The meat smells fishy
and isn't palatable.
This dish is overcooked.
Too oily and mellow.
But Your Grace,
I really think they taste great.
They're better
than what we ate in Enaqi.
In Enaqi, there was
no fresh fruit or vegetables.
We mostly eat the meat of beasts.
It's either boiled or roasted.
Nothing special.
Yeah.
Before I came here,
I never knew
there were so many kinds of food.
In Yunpei, I've gained a lot of weight.
Enaqi will have an oasis.
Just like people in Yunpei,
they can eat anything.
But our top priority
is to win the cooking competition.
How about
we get a local chef to teach you?
His Lordship always eats here.
Even if I learn something,
it won't be impressive.
I need a recipe.
Recipe?
Where can we get one?
From the Library, of course.
I'll go take a look.
If you like the dishes,
eat them up.
Don't waste food.
Let's eat.
I've wanted the meat.
It must be delicious.
You eat more, too.
I will.
(In the 310th year of Yunpei,)
(Lady Su was exiled
for a terrible mistake.)
(Nobody knew she was pregnant.)
(So, the Lord's son was missing.)
(After many search attempts,)
(Biographical Record)
(blessed by God,)
(in the 320th year of Yunpei,)
(Lady Su's son Na Zhan
returned to Huayu Mansion.)
(It's hereby declared)
(that Na Zhan will be the heir.)
(The fire in the Library that year)
(burned for three days and nights.)
(But this record has survived.)
(Such a counterfeit.)
(Library)
(Yunpei Recipe)
I thought you had left.
What are you doing here?
What about you?
- My Lord.
Let's hide.
Come on.
What did you just say?
You...
I asked if we should torture him.
Do you think an old man like him
can survive  a night of torture?
But except that,
we don't know what else to do.
Let me think about it.
Why did you bite me?
Have you been too busy lately?
What do you want?
Where have you been?
What do you mean?
I didn't go anywhere.
The cooking competition is coming.
You haven't cooked anymore.
I suddenly want
some stewed mutton of my tribe.
Go cook some now.
Give it to me tonight.
Where's the mutton?
There's a lot in the kitchen.
When you're done, I'll come get it.
Make three more dishes
and some soup.
Light soup.
Her Ladyship has had too much heat.
I'm talking to you.
Do you hear?
Then why does she want mutton?
None of your business.
You have good taste in food.
Who's that?
Aren't you busy?
To what pleasure do I owe this?
You left something in the Library.
(Yunpei Recipe)
Wait.
I left before you.
How come you got here first?
I can climb up walls.
Don't you remember?
What are you looking for?
There's a passageway, right?
These days,
did anything happen?
Or is it because I...?
You what?
Did I mess with you?
No.
Never mind.
I shouldn't have asked.
Thank you for today.
You may leave.
You shouldn't have come.
Don't come anymore.
Huang Beishuang!
I have a bone to pick with you.
- Ruo Wen?
- How did you get in?
Ruo Wen.
Hide in here.
I'll go stop him.
Do you want everybody to know
I hide a man in my chamber?
Ruo Wen is a danger.
What if he kidnaps you?
Whatever.
None of your business.
Don't interfere.
Get out of the way.
You've got something.
You managed to sneak in.
Huang Beishuang,
get packed and leave with me.
I don't want to be rude.
If the two of you
want to come, come along.
You can serve us.
Don't brag.
Go look in the mirror.
I'll go with you.
You're just in time.
When are we setting off?
Your Grace.
Huang Beishuang, what are you up to?
What?
Don't dare to take me away?
Who said that?
Since I met you last time,
I've never forgotten your eyes.
Why's the mystery in your eyes?
The answer is right in you.
You have to go with me.
Desert Rankers have lost their den.
Go with you?
Where can we go?
Huang Beishuang, you reminded me.
You blew up my den.
I'll get you back for that.
Don't make a move.
Who's actually making a move?
Ruo Wen,
you killed dozens of my clansmen.
Even including my old wet nurse.
I blew up your den
just to take revenge.
We're even.
I killed a lot of people.
Your men follow you.
You're not a decent man.
That's why your men are malignant.
Stop arguing
over this meaningless stuff.
Check over here.
This is Huayu Mansion.
You can't do whatever you want.
You may leave.
He has left.
Why do you still hold your dagger?
So, will you go with him?
You were eavesdropping, weren't you?
What?
Didn't catch that?
Ruo Wen is complicated.
You can't easily deal with him.
None of your concern.
I can solve the problem.
Stop having a tantrum.
Huayu Mansion is always dangerous.
Now, Ruo Wen is here.
You can't be too careful.
You coax me
and you remain indifferent.
Sometimes, you care for me.
Sometimes, you ignore me.
I understand.
You're a changeable man.
Some is true and some is false.
Now, what is this about?
You're my best friend in need.
I don't want you to be hurt.
That's all.
You should worry about yourself.
Don't come anymore.
Yepei, Lianhuan.
Here.
Your Grace.
There's a passageway in this room.
Find it and seal it.
Passageway?
Passageway? Where is it?
Your Grace.
I found this in the corner.
It looks really old.
Maybe it belongs to the previous owner.
What is this?
Put it away.
Idiot.
Why are you always careless?
I'm not.
(Library)
Since we parted in Tiandu,
it has been 15 years.
I've never been to Tiandu.
I've never seen you before.
Mr. Rong Huo.
Come on. Leave with me.
Move.
- No!
- Come on.
Boy,
listen to me.
Forget what happened today.
Don't tell anyone about it.
Never tell anyone
what happened
in the Lord's Mansion of Yunpei,
not even your name.
Understand?
Only in this way
can you survive.
We have to go.
Hurry.
Mr. Rong Huo,
can't you stay?
If I stay with you,
you'll be in danger.
Boy,
remember.
You have to live.
Will we meet again?
When you're well prepared,
come get me.
Where can I find you?
I believe
you will find me.
Qingyun?
It's really you.
These days,
you've had a hard time.
Oh, boy.
What took you so long?
I thought
I could never see you again.
Now, you've grown up.
Even if I die,
I'll have nothing to regret.
Mr. Rong Huo,
let's not talk now.
Let's get out of here.
I'll take you out.
- All right.
- Let's go.
Come on.
♪It always begins with grudges♪
♪Tears pierce the darkness
and light up the other side♪
♪I used to be too plain♪
♪I walk into the desert to be reborn♪
♪The soul fire burns me all the time♪
♪Asking me what I want♪
♪What I actually want♪
♪Give me God's wings
to conquer in the distance♪
♪When I look back, my heart burns♪
♪It gleams and lights up the night sky♪
♪Tears roll down my face
when my heart blooms♪
♪Old hometown and blossoming wishes♪
♪What was in my dream comes back to me♪
♪Turn all sorrow into infinite hope♪
♪I look up at the stars
and light up the night sky♪
♪Old hometown and blossoming wishes♪
♪What was in my dream comes back to me♪
♪Turn all sorrow into infinite hope♪
♪I look up at the stars
and light up the night sky♪