♪On the clouds, I drift in the wind♪
♪How vast is the world?♪
♪Overwhelming humans are crazy♪
♪How sensible are they?♪
♪Even in the mortal world, I'm immortal♪
♪I hate mortal rules♪
♪Way too many and complicated♪
♪I'm what I am♪
♪Absurd and haughty♪
♪That's usually me♪
♪Anything identical differs♪
♪Changing all the time♪
♪I wave and ride away♪
♪Staying for nobody♪
♪Among all the people in the world♪
♪Who'd stay together?♪
♪I watch the stars and drink wine♪
♪No one can understand♪
♪The whole world is free♪
♪Wind blows and water flows♪
♪You smile and I'm around♪
=Love In The Desert=
=Episode 17=
So, is she the Ninth Princess of Masui?
No.
She's Lady Beishuang.
She isn't our princess.
Our princess is easygoing
and generous.
She's in no way like Lady Beishuang
who is so proud
and indifferent.
You're lying!
You're complicit!
All of you!
Enough!
You tell me.
Who are you?
Huang Beishuang,
the princess of Enaqi.
Lady Beishuang
of Yunpei.
Confess.
Who's behind you?
What I said is true.
No one is behind me.
No one?
Then how did you get in here?
Confess.
It's...
It's Zhen...
- Somebody.
- Yes.
Take away this lying woman.
Execute her.
- Yes.
Mercy, My Lord!
What I said is true.
Lady Youjia, save me!
Lady Youjia, help!
My Lord, I...
- If it gets out...
- Lady Youjia, help!
Everybody here
won't get away.
Lady Beishuang.
What?
The banquet is just over.
Rushing back to your chamber?
After what happened,
I felt tired and unfit.
I don't want to upset you, My Lord.
Can't you even bear a mere joke
of Lady Youjia?
This case is nothing to me.
I don't care who you really are.
All I want is you,
Huang Beishuang.
Thank you, My Lord.
I didn't uncover Lady Beishuang.
Stop threatening me with my mother.
Keep this.
Your mother worries about you.
Ruo Wen will occupy your city.
Na Zhan will not aid Masui.
How can I trust someone
who threatened me?
Believe it or not,
I just try to tell you
a new ruler may not be a bad thing.
Being reborn,
Masui will only improve.
It's easy for you to say.
But our people have to pay the price.
Maybe not as bad as you think it is.
Don't do anything silly.
I'll have my men get your mother here.
My Lord,
I have some confusion.
Lady Youjia,
keep your voice down.
You must not yell
in His Lordship's study.
Get her in.
Yes.
My Lord,
why do you always
take Huang Beishuang's side?
You love me most, don't you?
What I said is true.
You think Huang Beishuang lied to me?
Yes.
What about you?
Me?
Do I have to remind you?
Ruo Wen.
How dare you?
And you...
I should reexamine you, too.
My Lord, let me explain.
I really didn't know that.
He...
He deceived me.
- Zhu Jun.
- Here.
- My Lord.
- Send her back to Yufu Pavilion.
Without permission,
she must not come out.
- Don't.
- Yes.
Don't, My Lord.
Don't ground me.
My Lady, let's go.
My Lord, I beg you.
- Lady Youjia.
- No. Don't do this.
Somebody! Take her away!
My Lord!
Hurry!
My Lord.
- Go.
Don't discard me, My Lord!
My Lord!
Ruo Wen.
My Lord,
when I followed Zhan Bie,
I found someone suspicious here.
Trying not to alert him,
I followed him to a rockery
outside Yunfang Pavilion.
Then, he disappeared without a trace.
Yunfang Pavilion?
Can he travel through the ground?
I guess
there are secret passageways.
Did you see that man clearly?
He's about my weight.
Fair-skinned.
He has a mole on his jaw.
Hurry. Get me
the portrait from our spy in Tiandu!
Yes.
My Lord,
it's him.
Huo Qingyun, Lord of the North.
My Lord, it is my duty
to perform for you.
I don't deserve a reward.
I'm just very thirsty.
May I ask for a cup of tea
Her Ladyship just made?
Look at the guards under your command!
They don't function at all!
The rebels came and ran away
whenever they wanted, huh?
Calm down, My Lord.
I did my job so poorly
that the bandits broke in.
One is the princess of Masui
and the other is the Lord of the North.
Interesting.
There's fun to see.
(South Gate)
Get up.
(Heyan Mansion)
- Chief, look.
- Whoever resists
will be executed!
- Yes.
Yes.
You guys...
Come on, guys.
Here.
- Search carefully.
- Yes.
Let go of no one.
Yes.
Go check over there.
Let's go.
Wait for me.
I'll go with you.
When we fight fiercely,
I can't protect you.
So what?
I'm not scared.
(Cheng'en Pavilion)
Watch out for poison.
Bad guy.
There isn't poison.
But a dozen guys.
Show yourselves.
Where?
Where are they?
Put down your swords.
You can be allowed
to see your family.
Bandit!
You're bumptious, indeed.
Put down your dagger.
Otherwise, this is where you'll die!
That's some tough talk.
Fine.
I'll play with you.
Ruo Wen, my dagger.
Darn it.
There you go.
Ruo Wen!
Ruo Wen...
Ruo Wen, darn it.
Ruo Wen, you're terrible.
Don't come to me.
Stop running.
Help!
♪I was a rock monkey in the world♪
♪Waiting to travel to the West by fate♪
♪Unexpectedly, my life is worth my while♪
♪I've known a confidante like you♪
♪We've met for the first time♪
♪But we're destined
to spend the rest of our lives together♪
♪I'd wait for you for another 500 years♪
♪Name you the Monkey King
and travel with you♪
♪I want no mercy from the Buddha♪
♪I just want a reputation in my dream♪
♪People in the desert love and hate♪
You said you wouldn't protect me.
I'll leave you alone, then.
You can't do that.
♪Having fascinated the travelers♪
♪Love and hate♪
♪People keep changing♪
Madwoman,
good martial arts.
My man,
you have strong arms.
And a strong waist.
♪A girl once grew flowers for you♪
♪A girl once sang for you♪
♪The blue sky meets the desert♪
♪It meanders, far, far away♪
♪Far, far away♪
♪We've met for the first time♪
♪I just want a reputation in my dream♪
♪I'd wait for you for another 500 years♪
♪Name you the Monkey King
and travel with you♪
♪I travel freely and fearlessly♪
♪I get drunk for my confidant
and never regret it♪
♪Everybody in the world dies♪
♪We just can't be together anymore♪
♪Sand moves and wind blows♪
♪Burying many loyal couples♪
♪Hate for fate but no regret for it♪
♪After all this trouble,
my heart burns to ashes♪
Warlord Ruo Wen,
the ruin of Masui
is its destiny.
Warlord, I beg you
to spare my life.
I'll give you the seal of my city
to prove my loyalty.
Please spare my life.
I will...
I will follow you.
If I had an afterlife...
What?
Would you be a slave?
You beg for mercy
in front of your ancestors.
How do you have the face to live?
What if your descendants laugh at you?
Under such circumstances,
I don't care about that.
You're the Warlord, after all.
Spare your life?
Let me think about it.
This useless seal...
I don't need it.
Fox,
see if it can be made into a bedpan.
Chief,
it can serve not only as a bedpan
but also a stepping-stone in the latrine.
Who'd want this kind of stuff?
You'd better
take it into your coffin.
Mr. Ruo Wen, if you don't mind,
I'll take orders from you
and follow your lead.
Don't move.
Let me go.
Or I'll kill this woman.
You get the wrong hostage.
She isn't as important
as you think she is.
This can't be right.
Isn't she your niece?
Niece?
I don't even know her.
Don't take me as a fool.
I won't capture anyone
who means nothing to you.
Nonsense!
You usurped power
and hunted my mother and me.
I won't let you go!
Don't struggle.
My dagger has no eyes.
I can always recognize
Ge Xinwei and her mother.
Liar.
Who'd believe a cheater like you?
Be patient.
A dying man speaks kindly.
I want to hear this story.
There's no point in it.
Let me kill this guy.
Keep him alive.
He may be useful someday.
Ruo Wen.
Masui was broken into.
Everything has gone according to your plan.
But why are you...?
Her parents are avenged
and she must be happy.
But to her, it's only the beginning.
Are you worried
her next target will be Tiandu?
But she's a powerless woman, after all.
She's powerless?
Is that what you think?
She can't stay in Yunpei.
Mr. Rong Huo was
secretly taken out of town.
He'll get to Tiandu before us.
(To Huang Beishuang)
(Masui was broken into.)
My Lord.
My Lord,
Desert Rankers broke into Masui.
Really fast.
What do we do?
Bandits have occupied a city.
The north desert will get chaotic.
Chaotic?
What's so bad about it?
My Lord.
I didn't know there were
so many secret passageways
under the ground.
Na Qida,
you were indeed wary of me.
It's been 15 years.
I've never known
about this secret passageway.
My Lord, come this way.
My Lord,
what happened that year...
Back then,
how much more was kept from me?
(Father,)
(with your blessing,)
(Masui was occupied.)
(You can rest in peace.)
(In this chaotic world,)
(someone helps, protects,
values, and loves me.)
(He saved my life several times.)
(I love him)
(and don't want to leave him.)
We should go.
Can I settle on you?
Do you remember what I told you
when you were badly sick?
On the oasis,
you'll take Enaqi people and me
to sow the first seed.
Brick by brick,
we'll build our own house
and embrace the first wisp of smoke.
We'll hear
the baby's first cry.
Such a fantastic dream.
It's the life we wish for,
isn't it?
It is.
Go with me.
I'll give you the life you want.
I'll give you an oasis now.
As long as you approve,
I'll have my men travel across the desert
and bring all Enaqi people here.
From this day on,
no one will dare to target Enaqi
or this oasis.
(Oh, I see.)
I will protect you
and Enaqi.
I give you my word.
As long as you approve,
you don't need to take risks anymore.
Whatever you want,
I'll get it for you.
Qingyun,
have you made up your mind?
If you're with me,
you'll be against Yunpei
and Tiandu.
Tiandu?
My mother died
at the city gate of Tiandu.
It's a blood feud.
I can't forget it
or let it go.
(My top priority is to take you away.)
(Back in Tiandu,)
(I'll explain everything.)
I don't fear Yunpei
or Tiandu.
When you're with me,
I won't be scared
of anything in the world.
When I'm with you,
I won't be scared, either.
I'll go with you.
You will?
Then let's leave now.
Tomorrow, we'll meet
at Juyun Pavilion.
All right.
Tomorrow,
let's meet there.
From our journey for marriage
to our life in this mansion,
without the two of you,
I couldn't have got away from danger.
Take the money
and find somewhere peaceful
to live a good life.
Na Zhan may blame Enaqi.
But Boa Agents will protect them.
You should protect yourselves.
Your Grace.
Wherever you go, we'll follow you.
Qingyun and I
will move around
without settling down.
Instead of living this kind of life,
why don't you live alone?
Your Grace.
Yepei and I won't go
until you leave.
In this way,
if His Lordship suddenly returns,
we can buy you some time
to get out of town.
Protect yourselves.
Your Grace.
All right. Stop crying.
Your Grace, I don't want to leave you.
(Yun, Shuang)
♪We're born in an invisible cage♪
♪Under flaky feathers,
I'm thirsty for freedom♪
♪Who will hug me in the dark?♪
♪Who will reach out and save me?♪
♪Then I hear you calling me♪
(Juyun Pavilion)
♪We're twin birds in the dark♪
Qingyun!
Beishuang.
Beishuang!
Qingyun!
Time crawls when I wait for you.
The Lord of the North,
when will you stop lying to me?
Don't be scared.
I know what you want.
And I know where you're going.
I won't stop you.
But before you go,
I have to tell you something.
One year ago,
Ge'er Jinqin wrote a letter to me.
If the Lady of Masui
and her daughter came
and I killed them,
he'd surrender to me forever.
I don't know
if Tiandu also received this letter.
Soon afterward, I heard
the Ninth Lady of Masui
was shot to death
at the city gate of Tiandu.
Under the command
of the Lord of the North.
I guess
you don't know yet.
The Lord of the North
seems to be
Huo
Qing
Yun.
Since you know it,
I'm finally relieved.
Huo Qingyun,
you've been using me all the time.
Everything is just your trick.
I know you hate me.
Nothing I say will change that.
But today, you have to go with me.
If you don't want to see me anymore,
after you're out of here,
you can go anywhere you want.
Go with me.
Don't touch me!
After you're out of here,
you can cut me into pieces.
I'll let you take revenge.
In the north desert,
you pretended you would die
and tricked me of the Herb Volume.
You deliberately got close to me,
so I helped you save Rong Huo.
You colluded with Masui
and got my mother killed.
How can you let me take revenge?
Shoot!
Protect Her Grace.
Congratulations.
You avenged your mother.
Do you bear to watch him die?
He's a sworn enemy for killing my mother.
I stabbed him twice.
That is mercy.
You made the right choice.
You killed him for me.
You deserve
a reward.
What do you want?
Think of it and tell me.
I betrayed you.
You don't blame me?
I can pretend
nothing happened.
We can still be partners
just like always.
Do you still believe
I'll keep helping you
with no distractions?
I bet you will.
Do you still love him?
Will my love
influence your decision?
You haven't answered yet.
I have.
Let's drink.
What are you thinking?
I think what Ge'er Jinqin said is weird.
Cheers. Fill your cups.
Ge'er Jinqin...
Well done.
He's senile.
He plays rascal tricks
just to live.
Fancy wine.
You're a great man.
You can control everything.
Let's drink.
Come on, guys. Don't drink alone.
Let's propose a toast to Chief.
- Sure.
- Come on, Chief.
- Cheers!
- Drink it up!
The first toast to Chief.
He's so righteous
and gives us a fortune!
So, we no longer
need to wander in the desert!
- That's right!
- Cheers!
A toast to Chief, too.
I pledge my life to follow you, Chief.
I live for Desert Rankers
and I die for Desert Rankers!
Today, we've taken Masui.
Someday, we'll march with Chief
and take Yunpei!
Take Yunpei! Take Yunpei!
Guys,
let's drink it up!
- Cheers!
We'll enjoy a great life with Chief.
If anyone rebels,
I won't let him be!
Yeah. We'll follow Chief.
Let me say something.
We shouldn't call him Chief anymore.
We should call him My Lord.
Not now.
I have this city for someone else.
But...
Chief,
we've just occupied the city.
We wait to see you be the Lord.
Will you...?
Terrible man.
My Lord,
the pond of Juyun Pavilion
has running water.
We did the salvage but found nothing.
I had my men search along the river
and found something unexpected.
Juyun Pavilion
is the hub of Boa Agents.
Boa Agents?
I didn't know he had another identity.
Get him to me, alive or dead.
Seal the passageways.
Let no one know
about them.
Yes.
♪It always begins with grudges♪
♪Tears pierce the darkness
and light up the other side♪
♪I used to be too plain♪
♪I walk into the desert to be reborn♪
♪The soul fire burns me all the time♪
♪Asking me what I want♪
♪What I actually want♪
♪Give me God's wings
to conquer in the distance♪
♪When I look back, my heart burns♪
♪It gleams and lights up the night sky♪
♪Tears roll down my face
when my heart blooms♪
♪Old hometown and blossoming wishes♪
♪What was in my dream comes back to me♪
♪Turn all sorrow into infinite hope♪
♪I look up at the stars
and light up the night sky♪
♪Old hometown and blossoming wishes♪
♪What was in my dream comes back to me♪
♪Turn all sorrow into infinite hope♪
♪I look up at the stars
and light up the night sky♪