ALL LOCATIONS, PEOPLE, ORGANIZATIONS,
INCIDENTS IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS.
Hey, why did you tell me to record
Reporter Seo's whereabouts?
You know why.
Keep an eye on her, see if she meets
the woman in the wine-colored coat
while I'm in Mueon.
Just in case something happens.
Looks like you should
keep an eye on her yourself.
She's in Mueon now too.
MUEON
-What?
-If that woman
really is the culprit, it'll be dangerous.
Isn't that why you told me
to keep tabs on her?
Maybe she's going to Mueon
to meet that woman.
Give me real-time updates
on exactly where in Mueon she is.
Who are you?
Who are you? What do you want?
What are you doing here?
That's my question, exactly.
Why are you here?
What are you after?
Why did you come all the way to Mueon?
What about you?
Don't tell me you came all the way here
to tail me.
This is your warning.
Don't tail me again
unless you're going to arrest me.
Did you know that someone
was secretly questioned
as a witness in relation
to the Cha Eun-sae case?
Who's this person?
The thing is,
rumor has it that it was
your husband's friend from school.
Is that right?
I'm going to Mueon High School tomorrow.
If you find out the name, let me know.
Who are you? What do you want?
MUEON HIGH SCHOOL FESTIVAL
MUEON HIGH SCHOOL
Yes, Tae-heon.
While I visit Jin Myeong-suk's
ex-husband's family,
track where Seo Jeong-won goes
after Mueon High School.
VICE PRINCIPAL SON DU-IN
You said you were making
a promotional video
for the foundation yourself.
Yes, it's my gift to my husband
on becoming chairman.
It'll be a surprise.
Woo-jae will be so touched.
Here, look.
He looked much more handsome in person.
SEOL WOO-JAE
YOO YUN-YEONG
Do you know Yoo Yun-yeong?
I met her through my husband,
and we're quite close now.
Yes. I know Yun-yeong.
I know her well.
She was one of our best students.
I heard she became a doctor.
She and Woo-jae were close, right?
They were close?
I had no idea.
Well, Woo-jae was very popular.
He got along very well
with almost everyone at school.
You're here to collect
some impressive stories about him, right?
Well…
I want the video
to showcase his history as it is,
so any story, even if it's not special.
Then, I have to tell you
about how he got into Hankuk University
and suddenly moved to the US.
He left in a hurry in February
and missed the graduation ceremony.
-He did?
-Yes.
Kim Min-cheol is the friend
who was questioned.
I guess it's someone I shouldn't know.
Like Cha Eun-sae.
Kim Min-cheol.
We went to high school together.
I lent him some money.
Sir, by any chance,
do you remember a student
by the name of Kim Min-cheol?
Yes, I do. He was a real troublemaker.
EUN-SAE'S SHOCKING AFFAIR
WITH SEOL WOO-JAE
CHA EUN-SAE WAS IN AN INAPPROPRIATE
RELATIONSHIP WITH SEOL WOO-JAE.
The father of Cha Eun-sae's baby
is me.
EUN-SAE LOVED SOMEONE ELSE.
THE FATHER OF CHA EUN-SAE'S BABY IS ME.
He said the girl he had a crush on
was ignoring him and hurt himself.
My gosh. It was really dangerous.
Was that girl okay? She didn't get hurt?
No. Thankfully, nothing serious happened.
Hold on. Come to think of it,
Woo-jae was the one
who saved Na-ri that day.
"Na-ri"?
-You just said "Na-ri," right?
-Yes.
By any chance, was this girl Na-ri?
Yes, that's right.
I guess you know Na-ri too.
-What's her surname?
-Lee.
Please excuse me for a moment.
Hello?
LEE NA-RI
KIM MIN-CHEOL
SEOL WOO-JAE
YOO YUN-YEONG
I'm a fan of Woo-jae's novels too.
Do you know
what Lee Na-ri is up to these days?
Sorry? You said you knew Na-ri.
Don't you know what happened to her?
What is this?
After that incident,
we planted that tree in memory of her.
What incident?
In 2009, a fire broke out at a plant.
The fire killed a number of people,
including Na-ri.
Are you talking about the fire
at the Bongto plant?
Yes, that's right.
DONATED BY PRESIDENT SEOL PAN-HO
OF MUJIN CONSTRUCTION
CHAIRMAN SEOL WOO-JAE
MUJIN WELFARE FOUNDATION
-Do you have it?
-Yes.
A photo of your wife's necklace
found at the crime scene.
Cha Eun-sae had the same necklace.
Are you sure it was Jeong-won's?
Yes. The serial number in the sales record
is a match.
Do one more thing for me.
Look into Detective Kim Tae-heon.
Everything about him
from his family to his finances
and his past relationships.
GANGHA POLICE STATION
LIEUTENANT KIM TAE-HEON
How random.
Why's a detective from Seoul
asking about the past?
Families of the deceased
would've given you a hard time.
Yet you stayed here.
My brother set fire to the factory,
not me.
Your sister-in-law Jin Myeong-suk,
did you know she was murdered?
Just once, about three years ago,
she called late at night, very drunk.
She said it was true
that Jin-su wasn't the culprit.
Instead of saying,
"He wasn't the culprit,"
she said, "It's true he wasn't?"
Did Jin Myeong-suk ever give you money?
What money?
As soon as she got her monthly pay,
she made a cash withdrawal.
I wonder if you have any idea
what the money was for.
One thing I can say for sure
is that it wasn't for anything bad.
She was frustratingly kind and generous.
She volunteered regularly too.
I believe Park Jin-su
was in a coma for a week before he died.
Did Prosecutor Mo Hyeong-taek
visit during that time?
As if that punk would visit.
I went to see him.
14 YEARS AGO
They keep mentioning some valve,
and talk as if my brother set the fire.
He worked at the Bongto factory
for over 25 years.
He's not the culprit, sir.
Well,
Park Jin-su is a victim just like others,
so I'll make sure
he isn't treated unfairly.
Hey, you!
You said you'd make sure
he wasn't treated unfairly.
Why did you go back on it?
You can't act like this.
Why is Jin-su the arsonist?
He's a victim too!
He's at death's door!
Because he's at death's door,
even though he's a suspect,
he gets to rest
instead of being questioned.
"Rest"?
He's in a coma
and you call that "rest"?
How could you say that?
Since that day, whenever I see him on TV,
I curse him.
Hello.
I'm Detective Kim Tae-heon
from Gangha's Violent Crimes Unit.
-Hello.
-I heard Seo Jeong-won was here,
and she asked to speak with you.
CHICKEN AND WHELK
Address of the place Kim Tae-heon was at.
-Thanks.
-Enjoy yourselves.
-Welcome.
Hello. I'm Seo Jeong-won, a reporter.
From Nothing Uncovered?
That's you?
A detective from Gangha Police Station
was here, wasn't he?
Tae-heon's here on Jin Myeong-suk's case,
not Cha Eun-sae's.
There has to be a connection
between the two.
"Yoo Yun-yeong."
YOO YUN-YEONG
Where did I see that name?
DIRECTOR YOO YUN-YEONG
YOU AND ME NEUROPSYCHIATRIC CLINIC
This woman…
So she knew Seol Woo-jae personally,
not Seo Jeong-won?
-What?
-Ms. Seo scares me.
-How so?
-That woman,
she was at Park Jin-su's
sister's beer joint.
She knew you'd been there.
I think she knows Jin Myeong-suk's
connected to the Bongto factory fire.
Where is Seo Jeong-won now?
I warned you not to tail me.
You tailed me too.
How was Mueon High School?
The foundation PR video was an excuse.
You looked into your husband's past.
-Why do you care?
-I have to care.
Unlike how you defended him
when he had an affair,
you're secretly doing
a background check on him.
Anyone would think it's suspicious.
Why are you so frustrated?
Are you angry I looked into your partner
but turned a blind eye
to my husband's affair?
The case was closed when he died.
Don't jump to conclusions.
Will defending him
cancel out what he did?
Yes. On the outside,
I'm defending my cheater husband,
and in secret, I looked into his past,
but unlike you, I don't ignore reality
and dwell in the past.
The woman in the wine-colored coat…
It's Yoo Yun-yeong, isn't it?
Seol Woo-jae's high-school friend
and Seo Jeong-won's psychiatrist.
I can't say.
You're always like this.
You never want to take a loss
and always want to use me.
You're the one who used me.
Did I want to know
about a wine-colored coat?
Why should I tell you
if I found her or not?
Are you stupid?
If we identify her,
-you'll be dropped as a--
-That's a joke.
Let's say you're right and Yoo Yun-yeong
is the woman in that coat.
What's weird about her entering her clinic
around the time of the murder?
If you identify her, are you sure
I'll be dropped from the suspect list?
No. You'll suspect me all the same.
I don't want to move the way you want.
I won't answer anything.
Think whatever you want.
You're right.
I have to keep suspecting you.
Because I think you lied.
The day Cha Eun-sae was killed…
you went to the scene, didn't you?
Just like when Jin Myeong-suk died.
I said no when you questioned me.
I should believe you if you say no?
I can't.
I want to believe you!
But I can't.
When did you ever believe me?
Believe whatever you want.
That's what you always did.
3 YEARS AGO
COMMISSIONER
OF THE SEOUL METROPOLITAN POLICE
REST IN PEACE
WE OFFER OUR CONDOLENCES
I told you to stay away.
Didn't you hear me?
I was close to him too.
You got close because of me.
You approached me to get to him.
If the officer suspected of bribery
were you and not him,
I'd have done the same.
Before he died, he told me
that you had deceived me.
That I should stop being a fool
and let you use me.
Say something.
Come on.
Please?
Why won't you say anything?
Why can't you give me an excuse
and tell me you weren't using me?
If I say so,
will you believe me?
If I tell you I didn't approach you
on purpose to investigate Detective Cha,
will you take my word for it?
This just shows
the extent of your trust in me.
Believe what you like.
Admit that blaming me
makes you feel better.
You're something else.
-Udon and a bottle of soju, please.
-Sure!
Another bottle of soju, please.
You were taken to hospital for cirrhosis.
You've had enough.
You said the same thing to me
both three years ago
and earlier today.
You told me to believe
whatever I wanted to believe.
Why do you keep saying that to me?
Are you implying
I've got the wrong idea about you?
Say what you want to say.
You and I
shouldn't have met.
That's where it went wrong.
There were other detectives too.
Why did it have to be you?
You've already seen me at my lowest.
Do you know how awful it feels
to hit rock bottom with you watching?
MUEON BEACH
MUEON STALL STREET
I'm in a worse place than you are.
I'd rather see you
living a luxurious life without me.
Seeing that miserable look on your face
is annoying.
It upsets me.
Meeting you again…
I know.
You're angry.
I'm angry…
and sad.
And…
Is he all right?
-Could you give us another room?
-Sure. This way.
Gosh.
Just like you said…
I don't think you can kill someone
in the same way
your father was murdered.
MY HUSBAND
So…
help me believe you.
Hello.
Sorry. I tapped the wrong button
and hung up.
I see.
I heard a man's voice just now.
Someone was walking by.
Where are you?
Aren't you at your accommodation?
I just arrived. Why did you call me?
I was wondering
when you'd arrive tomorrow.
I won't be too late.
Okay. Call me when you leave.
Sleep tight.
Who is it?
Thanks for inviting me.
Gosh.
-What are you doing here?
-I'm visiting you.
Your wife wanted to invite me
to your house too.
Ms. Seo, I'm here!
Hey, Jeong-won went on a business trip.
Get out.
I know she went on a business trip.
That's why I'm here.
Will you keep acting impulsively?
-Are you trying to drive me crazy?
-Come on, this is nothing.
What if I were to leak the photo
of her shirt, stained with blood?
There's a photo?
Let me see it.
You two don't sleep
in the same bed, right?
-Do you sleep in separate rooms?
-Hey.
Hey!
Hey, open the door.
Get up.
Get up!
You…
-You'd better not do this again.
-Why do you think I do stuff like this?
You only look at me
when I bother you like this.
Yun-yeong…
I consider you a good friend.
To me,
you're a jerk I want to kill.
When you love someone to death,
you can actually kill a person,
whoever it may be.
That's why I killed Cha Eun-sae.
What's with that reaction?
I can't even crack a joke with you?
How could you say such a thing?
You look like you're about to
hit me with that.
Why?
Wasn't she just a fleeting distraction?
This is why
your wife wants to throw you
into the fiery pit.
If anyone
threatens my wife, I will throw them
into the fiery pit myself.
You're only making me not want to give up.
Actually, no.
This means you're bothered by me,
which is a good thing. Right?
I'll be leaving, then.
Right.
I almost forgot to give you
your surprise gift.
You'll like it.
Hop in. You're not fully sober
so you can't drive.
You don't know where I'm headed…
Enjoy.
You need to eat something first anyway.
-Is it too spicy? Do you like it?
-Yes.
Since I found out
my husband cheated on me,
I haven't been able to taste anything.
That woman in the wine-colored coat,
it was Yoo Yun-yeong.
I saw her at the kick-off ceremony.
I bet you invited her on purpose,
to see how your husband would react.
The bigger goal
was to buy enough time to copy
the video of Cha Eun-sae's session.
Cha Eun-sae was her client too?
I watched the video
of Cha Eun-sae's last session
before she died.
In the video,
a girl named Na-ri is mentioned.
Na-ri?
I came here to find out who she was.
Wait.
Who is Lee Na-ri?
One of the people who died in the fire
at the Bongto plant.
So every person
we tried to track down in Mueon
died in that fire?
Mo's housekeeper who died
is Park Jin-su's ex-wife?
Detective, weren't you the one
who handed him over to the prosecution?
Back then, Prosecutor Mo hounded me
into handing over the case
with the decision to indict him.
What is this?
That.
It was one of the victim's belongings
found at the scene.
-The fire broke out at 9:00.
-Correct.
Do you still have this stored as evidence?
EVIDENCE, MUEON POLICE
It's here.
Was there no battery in this watch?
Was there no battery?
Right. We returned it
to the victim's family,
but they refused to accept it
and told us to reinvestigate.
Reinvestigate what?
They said it was odd that the strap
was broken and there was no battery.
They were adamant
that someone had hurt the victim.
Who was this victim?
Does the family still live in Mueon?
No, the whole family
moved to a different country.
Why do you ask?
By any chance,
is Lee Na-ri this victim
you're speaking of?
She was in her third year
at Mueon High School.
What? How did you know?
MEETING ROOM
There were pictures of several items
found at the scene.
Why did that watch catch your attention,
of all things?
The watch had stopped
at the time of the incident.
What's up with that?
There were a number of victims.
Why Lee Na-ri's watch?
I want to ask the same question.
Why did it have to be Lee Na-ri?
Did the culprit start the fire
to kill her?
What do you mean?
Does the watch have something to do
with the incident itself?
I guess it does.
How did you know that
by just looking at that watch?
There was a stopped clock
at the other scene.
Cha Eun-sae's office?
I wouldn't say this
if I only saw it twice.
You saw it at the scene
of Jin Myeong-suk's murder too?
In other words,
are you saying the same signature
was found at the scenes
of the three cases?
So they were all done
by the same person?
My necklace that was found
at Cha Eun-sae's murder scene,
it would've been easier for Yoo Yun-yeong
to get her hands on it
than for Mo Hyeong-taek.
It's possible my husband gave it to her.
What if it's untrue that she has
no connection to Jin Myeong-suk?
What if we simply haven't found it yet?
Are we being tailed?
Stay in the car.
Are you okay?
Of course, I'm not.
Someone tailed a detective.
And in Mueon of all places.
I apologize.
I was extra cautious but…
ASSEMBLYMAN MO HYEONG-TAEK
GANGHA POLICE STATION CHIEF HONG
Hello, Chief Hong.
It's me.
I almost forgot what you look like.
Drop me off here.
You have a suitcase. I'll take you home.
I don't want to give the wrong impression.
Bye.
SEOL WOO-JAE
WITH MY JEONG-WON
HONEYMOON
Dear Nothing Uncovered viewers,
let me introduce my sweetheart,
Seol Woo-jae!
Hello.
Do you know how angry my fans were
after I announced we'd marry?
I promise to uncover Seol Woo-jae for you.
Here you go.
Here's some extra information.
This place is where
Jeong-won and I first met.
-That's right.
-Do you feel bad?
Here's more. Last night, we spent
-a passionate--
-Are you mad?
Are you happy now?
-Don't!
-Listen up!
Seo Jeong-won belongs to Woo-jae now!
-I love you, Jeong-won!
-I love you!
-I love you as much as the ocean's wide!
-I love you too!
It's beautiful out here.
I didn't hear you come in.
Are you tired?
Where did you go on the trip?
Did you drive?
Did you have dinner?
YOO YUN-YEONG
KIM MIN-CHEOL
LEE NA-RI
You should knock.
We're the only ones who knock
when we're living together.
Is it that hard to answer?
This is torture, not a chance.
Don't you see I'm flailing
because I'm glad for a chance
and trying to win you back?
How long will you ignore me
after giving me hope?
You ignored me first.
Cha Eun-sae and…
And what?
I know
you put a GPS tracker on my car.
Jeong-won…
if you'll give me a chance,
make it a real one.
I regret saying I'd give you a chance.
I can't stand seeing you try so hard,
and seeing you watch old clips.
Everything you do annoys me,
and I hate it.
Do you feel better now?
Thanks for being honest.
We live together
and see each other every day.
And I still miss you.
I wondered why that was.
I don't remember when you last smiled.
That's why I watched the clip.
Even if I annoy you and you hate it,
I'll keep trying and flailing.
I won't give up on you.
I can't do that.
-Hi.
-You were right.
The victims of the Bongto fire
received a donation
in Jin's name every month.
It's the amount she withdrew.
That's one mystery solved.
But another one popped up.
-What's that?
-The donations were delivered in cash
by a man in his 20s or 30s.
That means someone
was close to Jin Myeong-suk.
-The CCTV footage is gone?
-Yes, two months ago.
Shall I get a worker who saw him
help draw a composite?
Yes, do that.
SECRETARY GONG
-Hello.
-Detective Kim Tae-heon.
He went to Mueon two days ago
and returned today.
Did he?
Thanks.
So…
make me believe you.
My gosh.
You're so desperate to win.
That means it's not a simple bet.
You get it because it's a trick
you used as a prosecutor.
Back then, you made me do a lot of things.
Why bring up the past?
The tables turned long ago,
and now you're way above me.
I couldn't remain a politician
without your help.
Our circumstances changed
because times have changed.
Yes. What do you want done now?
I'll tell you when I'm done sketching.
COFFEE VILLAGE CAFE
2 ICED AMERICANO, $10
ZEUS
You were sleeping uncomfortably,
so I was wondering
if I should wake you up.
I need to talk to my source.
Okay. I'll prepare breakfast.
Jeong-won
was in Mueon yesterday.
You must find out why she went there, Dad.
You must have heard some bad news
this early in the morning.
Yoo Yun-yeong is the director
of You & me Neuropsychiatric Clinic.
Can you look into her?
You're basically asking me
to find dirt on her, right?
COFFEE VILLAGE CAFE
2 ICED AMERICANO, $10
Sorry.
I was on the phone with my dad.
I didn't get to ask you yesterday,
what happened to your hand?
I broke a cup and ended up with a cut.
It was sneaky and petty of me.
I won't do this sort of thing ever again.
I went to Mueon on my business trip.
I see.
For what?
I publicly announced that
I would expose Cha Eun-sae's killer
on my show after a month.
I went to investigate.
I obtained a lot of useful information.
Is that so?
Can I ask what kind of information
you found?
It's completely confidential.
You'll find out soon enough.
Did you go
on a business trip alone?
Yes.
LOCATION:
CHEMICAL PLANT IN MUEON CITY
You were right.
This is the killer's signature.
But… why a stopped clock?
The killer stopped it
at the estimated time of the murder.
So it must be like a trophy of victory.
The killer must have been euphoric
after taking the victim's life.
In a way, that makes the killer
an even bigger pervert.
By the way, the culprit must have no idea
that we obtained this crucial lead. Right?
First, let's widen the search
for Jin's murder suspects.
Run Yoo Yun-yeong's license plate.
Check if her car was on any camera
in Owol-dong on the day of Jin's murder.
Okay?
The program is bound to go down anyway.
Do you all want to go down with her?
I'll let you join my program.
Just jump ship.
I have exactly two openings now.
One for a cameraman, another for a writer.
-Do you mean it?
-Let's be honest.
You know she won't last the year.
Does she think she's a police officer?
How is she going to catch the culprit?
Besides, how will she air this on TV?
This kind of behavior is
putting your jobs in jeopardy.
Don't go down with her and be humiliated.
Cut ties with her already.
Okay?
PRESCRIPTION
Are you not well?
Ae-na…
will you join Mr. No's team?
I understand.
The newbie told me everything.
Why you defended your husband
in front of the reporters.
You were so good to me.
I feel awful that I misunderstood you.
How could I leave you?
You couldn't possibly understand
what I wanted to do.
I couldn't possibly understand you.
So don't say that.
Hold on.
MY HUSBAND
-Hey.
-You're at the TV station, right?
Yes.
Dad wants to have lunch with us.
I'm on my way there.
I'll call you once I arrive.
Okay.
What's going on?
Just the man I was looking for.
The top drawer was locked.
Could you open it?
You have to tell me
why you're searching my stuff first.
Isn't it obvious?
Someone reported you for bribery.
You know the drill. Cooperate with us
so we can get this over with.
Have you gone mad?
You were the one
who inspected Detective Cha, right?
Do you think this kind of cheap trick
can bring me down, like it did Cha?
Your boss ordered me
to inspect Detective Cha.
You shouldn't call it a cheap trick.
You're a mere subordinate.
Detective Kim.
I was the one who ordered them
to investigate Detective Cha.
It came from a trusted source.
The day I got the report,
Ms. Seo also heard about it,
so that says it all.
When did you get the report?
-What?
-When were you tipped off
about Detective Cha?
THE LATE SEO SANG-GYEON
I didn't know there exists a man
who looks better than me.
To be precise, you should say "existed."
He's gone now.
My name is Kim Tae-heon.
Your daughter kept hitting on me.
She won me over in the end.
I'm also without parents.
My mother was a single parent,
but she died of an illness.
You probably hoped that your daughter
would date someone
who had parents and siblings.
I'm sorry.
Since I'm all on my own too,
I sure know how lonely it is
to have to get through life
with no parents.
I'll make sure Jeong-won
never feels lonely.
I'll always put her before myself.
I'll be good to her.
Please watch over us, Father.
I guess you received a tip.
It must be something big.
-I'll be right back.
-Okay.
She received the tip when we were dating.
She didn't play me.
Why didn't she say so?
371N 3386
Plate 371N 3386?
That's him.
371N 3386
Seo Jeong-won!
-Hey.
-Tae-heon, I found Yoo Yun-yeong's car
on a speed camera in Owol-dong
the day of Jin Myeong-suk's murder.
I'll send you the image right away.
OH MYEONG-SOO
33M 6859
What were you thinking,
coming to the broadcast station?
What were you thinking, ignoring my calls?
It's so hard to have a meal with you.
What are you, the President?
Do you remember the boiled pork restaurant
behind the Bongto plant?
I found a place that makes boiled pork
that tastes just like that.
How's boiled pork for lunch?
Good idea, right?
I came up with your nickname
at that restaurant.
Mr. Bribe, because there's nothing
you love more than taking bribes.
I bribed you most generously, didn't I?
What do you want?
There's only one reason
I had you join the group.
Keep an eye on those servants
so they don't waste our money
or do anything funny.
They're all your enemies.
You belittle all the board members
and think they're our enemy.
I didn't know it went with your motto,
"Put talent first."
You have the nerve
to talk back to your father?
Why did you get anxious
because your wife went to Mueon?
He was worried you'd packed up
and left again using work as an excuse.
You're too weak.
Hello.
-The doctor is inside, right?
-Yes.
Detective!
How was the work trip?
Was it fruitful?
I am asking if you've figured out
who did it.
Not yet.
You said you'd reveal the real culprit
on your show.
Sounds like it'll take forever.
I'll find the culprit as soon as possible.
Detective Kim Tae-heon.
Right?
If you can't find the culprit…
create one.
I must be destroyed
to destroy you, Father.
Don't do anything to my wife.
I emailed you the information
you'd requested on Kim Tae-heon.
-Did something bad happen?
-No.
Someone from the security office
filed a report saying Min-cheol did it.
Did you kill Cha Eun-sae?
No! Why would I kill Eun-sae?
I loved her so much!
Someone you know well has been arrested
for the murder of Cha Eun-sae.
Who? Don't tell me…
Go home. It's an emergency,
so I have to work.
You need to meet the detective in charge?
You're a reporter,
but can you try to play it safe?
I helped. Why are you mad
when you should be thanking me?
You really don't know why I'm mad at you?
What are you two doing here?
-I'm covering the investigation--
-Do you really
have to do that
at your ex-boyfriend's place?