Bring it on!
My reinforcements have arrived!
You're doomed!
Light the torch!
Kill!
The Great Yan reinforcements!
Yanyun!
[Slay them!]
[Charge!]
By Your Highness's side,
there may be loyal and upright men,
and there may also be treacherous sycophants.
But the ones like Lord Ye
must never be near you.
What kind of man am I?
You're a man
consumed by despair.
Sir.
You shouldn't call me Lord.
Jinxian is your cousin,
yet my own nephew.
You should call me uncle
like he does.
It's not so easy
to take advantage of me.
If you ask me,
that face is all you've got.
Or with your nature,
who would like to marry you?
What happened?
What are you doing?
Grab me like this?
May lightning strike me dead
if I tell a lie.
And may lightning strike you dead
if you lie.
Meeting you
is already my doom.
Gu Jinzhao, how dare you!
Do you truly not understand,
or pretend not to?
I do all this
for your sake.
[Your mother was murdered.]
[Who did this?]
I will kill them for you.
[You have so many carriages,]
[yet only a handful of guards.]
You're clearly sitting ducks.
With them guarding you,
I can rest easier.
This is...
A bracelet.
It came from a raid,
but it's now legally cleared.
Don't worry.
If you think it's filthy,
just toss it.
Gu Jinzhao!
What a coincidence!
Fancy meeting you here.
Sir!
How is Yanyun?
Rest assured.
He just woke up.
He is fine.
Keep him company for a while
[Gu Jinzhao,]
[if you are reading this letter,]
[there is only one possibility that]
[I am done for.]
[Do not feel guilty.]
[I march to the borderlands this time]
[not only for you,]
[but also for myself.]
[Doc told me that]
[my heart ailment is severe,]
[and I have less than three years to live.]
[Rather than fading away in lethargy,]
[I choose to die boldly and fiercely.]
[In the past,]
[My dad is always yelling at me that I can't learn martial arts,]
[can't command an army,]
[and can't even hold up the reputation of Marquis's.]
[But this time,]
[I've commanded an army,]
[fought battles,]
[and shall die]
[on the battlefield.]
[When we meet in the netherworld,]
[I will stand tall and proud,]
[and tell him face‑to‑face that]
[I, Ye Xian,]
[have brought no shame to Ye.]
[Are you crying?]
[Do not cry.]
[You ought to be happy for me.]
[It's not that]
[I have no regrets.]
[My mother still lives,]
[but I can't repay her filial piety.]
[Please look after her]
[and my sister for me.]
[My brother‑in‑law is good‑for‑nothing.]
[But my sister is proud,]
[and keeps her sorrows]
[bottled up inside.]
[She likes you.]
[So please visit her often.]
[Then, Xue Qinglan.]
[Such a good girl,]
[yet she fell for me.]
[How foolish of her!]
[When she marries,]
[send her a wedding gift on my behalf.]
[Oh, and]
[Baopu the cat.]
[Such a lovely cat,]
[whom I never once praised.]
[Please praise it for me]
[in the future.]
[As for Chen Yanyun,]
[that scoundrel,]
[who always outshines me,]
[even secretly stole your heart from me.]
[I shall never forgive him.]
[They say good men die young,]
[while villains live long.]
[With all his]
[schemes and tricks,]
[he will probably live to grow old with you.]
[If so,]
[that is the only decent thing he has ever done.]
[Still,]
[now that I die in battle,]
[you will never forget me]
[for the rest of your life.]
[To live in your heart]
[in this way,]
[that's one win over him.]
[Just thinking of it makes me glad.]
[Make sure]
[you tell him this part]
[Keep that in mind.]
[Oh,]
[one more thing.]
[If I die,]
[keep the name of the Ye Army]
[if they wanna keep using it.]
[It is a pity to waste such military merit,]
[but it doesn't matter.]
[Consider it my gift to him.]
[Well.]
[That's all.]
[I shall take my leave first.]
[To have met you in my life]
[is the greatest fortune of mine.]
[Farewell.]
I led
two thousand light cavalrymen,
marching day and night,
yet still arrived too late.
Otherwise,
Lord Ye would not have perished.
This time, I swear to
escort you safely back to the capital.
I am not
planning to return yet.
Before I came here,
the Governor‑General repeatedly ordered me
to escort you safely back
to the capital in person.
Are you afraid that
after your return,
Fu Hailian will harm you?
I fear not for myself.
Right now,
Shi City and Men Plateau have fallen.
Though Yi County is guarded by ten thousand elite soldiers,
the Northern Barbarians
keep amassing their troops.
The imperial court must
immediately dispatch
elite troops from the Capital Garrison
to Yi County to resist the enemy.
Yet all military deployments
require mediation
from the Grand Council,
and demand united efforts from officials
both in and out of court to be carried out.
If I return to the capital now,
the truth that Fu colluded
with the Chunyuan Sect
will surely be exposed.
By then,
the court will plunge into chaos.
Not to mention resisting the enemy,
even
dispatching troops
may be impossible
due to the
court turmoil.
Go report this way
to Yanzhang.
He will not blame you.
I've said it before, you civil officials...
What should we do?
Unless
I truly die here.
Mom!
Mom insisted on coming here,
and I could not stop her.
Mom...
this place is unsafe to linger.
Let us
return to the Manor first.
Let's go.
Mom...
Yanyun,
you sacrificed for the Great Yan.
Upon hearing this,
I'm overwhelmed with grief.
Mrs. Chen, please
send Yanyun's coffin
to Xuanmiao Temple
for all officials to pay their respects.
What if I refuse?
That can't be allowed.
I refuse.
Insolence!
I don't believe
you dare to incur universal condemnation
and force the widow of a loyal minister
to death so boldly!
Nor do I believe you wish to die.
I advise you not to provoke me.
Yanyun died a heroic death
on the battlefield.
As his wife,
I fear no death.
Okay.
Go back to the Manor!
Sir,
by now, the lady
should have reached the capital.
Judging by the days,
she ought to have arrived.
I wonder if she
can secure reinforcement troops.
I...
I am rather worried.
She will make it happen.
I believe in her.
I see you zoning out.
Are you tired?
Let me massage you.
I used to do this
for my grandma.
I was thinking
if there is a way
to keep you from
taking such great risks.
What risk am I in?
I'm just going back to the capital.
Do you really fear
Fu Hailian will bite me?
I just worry about you.
You need not worry about me.
Yi County has tall city walls,
easy to defend yet hard to attack.
Six months ago,
the walls were reinforced again.
The Northern Barbarians know nothing about siege warfare.
In the short term,
they can do nothing to us.
So according to you,
we are both safe.
It's for you.
What's this?
This is brought by Qingpu
from Pingyang Prefecture.
I won't need them
after I return to the capital.
If you miss me,
have one.
How many are there?
Guess.
From the feel of it,
I could finish all of them
in two hours.
Don't you have anything
to give me?
Behind the painting in the study,
there's a box.
Inside it are
my most precious belongings.
If I...
Just keep them as a memento.
Don't talk nonsense.
What memento?
I only want you.
Clear?
Clear.
Wait for me.
I will find a way
to persuade the court to send troops.
Sending troops matters,
but to me,
your safety matters far more.
In my whole life,
I have put the court, the nation,
the realm and the world
above everything else in my heart.
But this time...
I want you.
Don't risk your life
for any cause.
I want you to live,
okay?
Miss Gu.
Jinzhao.
My condolences.
Are the ones of Daxin Ancestral Clan here?
Not yet.
Hurry back to Daxin Manor,
and invite Grandma and the others
to pay their respects.
Make sure Auntie comes as well.
Okay.
Go now.
Let's go.
Mom,
sister-in-law,
I have something to tell you.
Mom,
in fact,
Yanyun is still alive.
What?
It's true.
Mom,
it is all my fault.
I did not
tell you beforehand,
causing you such grief.
It is my mistake.
Please forgive me.
I once thought
it was merely
my wishful thinking.
Mom.
Yanyun is alive.
You should be happy!
Mom.
Yes, I am.
Yet I hate myself.
Since I
thought he was gone,
every night,
the moment I close my eyes,
I can see him as a little boy.
He was mature from childhood.
Among all my children,
he was the most sensible.
But that's why
whenever
his brothers quarreled,
I never judged who was right
and I always scolded him first.
But I forgot that
he was just a child too.
Later,
he grew up,
becoming the most accomplished
among his brothers.
Yet I felt he
grew distant from me,
telling me nothing.
And I kept
burdening him with everything.
I made him plan
for Yanzhang's future,
and
clean up
Yanwen's mess.
To the outside world,
he was my
proudest son.
But at home,
I never once
praised him from my heart.
I was wrong.
Terribly wrong.
All these years,
I wronged him endlessly.
If I could start over,
I would never do this again.
I would...
I would treat him well.
I know.
I know, mom.
He's still alive.
When he's back,
you can tell him all this.
Okay.
Help mom up.
Come mom.
Thank you.
My good girl.
It is my duty.
Sister-in-law...
Then...
who lies
inside the coffin?
Miss Gu.
Grandma and Auntie
have arrived.
Sister-in-law,
please do me a favor.
Look after mom
and my grandma.
Okay.
Tell Auntie to
come to the study.
Okay.
Jinzhao,
what happened?
You asked Lan
to invite me here for the condolence.
Has something happened
to Ye Xian?
Auntie...
Ye Xian...
What happened to him?
At Huxiao Gorge,
he encountered the Northern Barbarians.
He...
He died.
Before his death,
he said not to tell others.
He wanna keep using the banner of the Ye Army
to resist the Northern Barbarians.
That's why
I could only bring him back in secret.
Where is he?