The remaining nine
are governed by your men.
No one's spoken to me like that
in quite some time.
Pardon my frankness, my lord.
When a man
has just cheated death,
he finds
he has very little left to fear.
Did you imagine
those words would
cost you your life?
No.
Quite the opposite.
You have served me well.
I value a man who
tells me
what I don't
want to hear.
You're
exactly the kind of voice I need.
Truly!
Now get well.
The reforms
are underway.
The empire needs you.
So do I.
His Majesty has ordered
a full inquiry into the case.
Should Wang Xuanfan
prove to be the hand behind it,
no office, however high,
shall bring him to justice.
Gratitude, my lord.
See that you rest.
I shall take my leave.
Safe travels, my lord.
I saw
Lord Fu leave just now.
His expression was grim.
Was there discord between you?
He bade me
put aside my grudge against Wang.
I refused him plainly.
I had thought
he might intercede on Wang's behalf,
yet I did not foresee,
he would shield him
to such a degree.
I told him plainly:
six of the regions
where corruption took root
are governed by Wang's men.
His reply? Merely that they had
"gone a little too far."
It beggars belief.
Was that
truly worth
the confrontation?
I had to test how far
he would shield Wang.
And the test has yielded
its answer.
His bonds with Wang run deeper
than I ever reckoned.
Then we must
remain vigilant from now on.
Not only your affairs at court,
but my dealings as well.
Nothing can be
left to chance.
I should send word
to Grandmother
and Yao at once.
Perhaps
we should return to Tongzhou.
Ungrateful cur!
He dares rebuke me to my face!
He'd lay the blame for those breaches
at my feet!
Such insolent words!
Has he forgotten his place?
It was a threat.
If I do not remove Wang,
he will unleash an investigation.
And when he does,
it won't just be Wang who falls.
Half the court gets buried.
My lord, please...
He holds the purse strings.
Should he choose open war,
I have no means to stop him.
Zhang Qi!
Lord Fu asks that
you withdraw for now.
Return home and lay low.
When the storm has passed,
we shall arrange your return.
If that is
Lord Fu's wish,
I shall comply.
Mind your step.
So many crates.
What's
inside?
Records from
the bureau,
though they date back ten years now.
When Prince Chengqing rebelled,
he sought leverage over the officials.
So he bribed his way
into the bureau
and had every record of conduct
seized and shipped away.
The Cabinet had pirates
seize the convoy.
I managed to move
everything here.
Can records so old
still serve any purpose?
They can.
A man's deeds
always leave traces behind.
When Lord Fu
entered the Cabinet,
he was
an idealist.
But
these files
taught me
something else about him:
he prizes results
over integrity.
Why is it
scarcely half full?
I've read all of Lord Fu's records
and retained what I require.
I presume you've studied
Wang's files as well?
Not a single minister of note
has been left untouched.
How do you intend to proceed?
Whatever Wang
holds over Lord Fu
must be truly damning.
Nothing less could drive him
to protect Wang this far.
Treason?
Could Lord Fu have been in league
with Prince Chengqing?
It's possible.
But everything here
only covers Prince Glorian.
I studied
his records
before I dealt with
his heir.
Right about here.
There.
Jingning Era, Year twenty fourth,
Li Zhi summoned the Soulguide Liu Heng
to pray for his late mother.
In attendance were
Zhou Feng,
steward to Prince Chengqing,
and Wang Nianen, steward to Wang Xuanfan.
Afterward,
Wang Nianen sent prayer beads,
tangerines, pears
to the residence of
Grand Secretariat Fu Hailian.
Who is
Liu Heng?
Have you heard of
the Chunyuan Sect?
Someone cast a stone
over the wall.
This spell was tied to it.
You think it's Wang Xuanfan?
Who else would it be?
He's getting reckless!
Men with power
rarely let go of it gracefully.
My lord, my lady,
word has come from the palace.
His Majesty has summoned Ye Xian
to lead the investigation
into Chen Yanyun's assassination.
My lord,
Ye Xian has never
shown us any goodwill.
[By His Majesty's decree:]
[the investigation into]
[the assault upon Lord Chen]
[is now entrusted to Ye Xian.]
[Ye Xian is to return]
[to the capital forthwith.]
Faster!
Valuables are
to be packed separately!
Mind the fragile pieces!
Careful!
Stop dawdling!
- You brought this on us!
- Faster!
You and your obsession
with destroying
Chen Yanyun!
Say something!
This has nothing to do with us...
Have you quite finished?
Don't you raise your voice at me!
You want to
blame someone?
Blame yourself!
Take your rage out on someone else!
Hold your tongue!
Good heavens!
What did you find?
Hey!
What's that for?
So the wound is real after all.
It's nothing.
Thought you might be
faking it.
Enough.
Tell me,
how many are dead?
Three.
The Wangs,
and their steward.
Wang Nianen?
How did you know?
Take me there.
The Wangs
succumbed to charcoal fumes.
But the steward
was strangled.
He clearly
fought for his life.
They all died
between
midnight and dawn.
Any clues
on the steward?
Your intuition is keen, my lord.
Behold.
The steward caused
the Wangs' suffocation.
Yet, he himself
was murdered.
Any other findings?
Why is there
a cut?
My lady,
this appears
to be a nail scratch
from his own thumb.
How odd…
Why would he scratch himself?
And
in that exact spot, of all places?
Now I recall…
He was found
sitting on the ground
with his left hand
clenched in
a rather peculiar pose.
Moving the body
must have disturbed it.
Can you replicate the pose?
It was...
sort of like this.
The Chunyuan Sect!
The Chunyuan Sect...
Have you searched
the entire estate?
Every corner.
You have a lead?
I suspect as much.
But I need to
prove it.
Lord Chen attacked,
the Wangs dead
in their own manor!
These men were the pillars of my throne.
Has the capital
fallen into such chaos?
Your Majesty,
it's more than a failure of law.
Continue, my lord.
Lord Wang
was my aide
for years;
Yanyun
is my protégé.
The mystery
runs deep,
and many fear to tread here.
Let me
take up this burden myself.
Lord Wang!
My lord?
You uncovered that
Wang Xuanfan had
Chen Yanyun shadowed,
correct?
Yes, my lord.
The man confessed that
Wang feared Chen would
expose his ties
to Prince Chengqing.
He was ordered
to monitor
Chen's every move.
Did you interrogate Wang yourself?
He was defiant
and refused to see me.
Speak your mind,
my lord.
I believe
these two incidents
are connected.
They are one and the same!
If Wang truly
sought Chen's life,
then who has
a greater motive
for revenge
than Chen
himself?
Unthinkable...
It has the ring of truth...
A treacherous turn...
Aye.
Your Majesty,
for an ordinary man
to slay Wang
would be a feat of gods.
But Chen holds prestige rank
and dark,
deadly skills.
The suspicion points
solely at him!
This crime is a stain upon us all.
Your Majesty,
let justice be
swift and merciless!
We implore Your Majesty,
justice for
the fallen!
I...
Your Majesty,
I implore you.
Order his arrest at once.
To purge the rot
from the court.
Lord Chen has arrived!
Greetings,
Your Majesty!
Rise, my lord.
Gratitude.
Ought you
not be abed at home?
Why have you come?
Your Majesty,
the tragedy
of the Wangs reached me.
I felt
compelled to attend.
I'd hate
for a knife
to be stuck
in my back.
The nerve of the man...
No shame, truly...
Spare us
your barbs, my lord.
I am merely curious,
you were
gravely wounded,
yet you stand before us
looking quite hale.
You visited my estate
just days ago,
offering
prayers
for my recovery.
Now that
I am mending,
you seem… disappointed?
I merely raised a reasonable doubt.
No need for such cutting remarks.
A doubt?
Or an accusation against Lord Fu?
My lord,
you brought a royal healer
to attend to my wounds.
Is Lord Su disputing
the healer's findings,
or your own, my lord?
I... but...
Enough.
Cease this
petty bickering.
Yanyun,
the Wangs are dead.
Suspicion
trails you.
You must
submit
to an inquiry.
How so,
my lord?
You told me yourself that
you
lacked proof of
Wang's collusion
with Prince Chengqing.
I advised you
to let it rest.
You kept your silence.
Now, Wang
lies dead.
Can you
truly claim
you had no hand in this?
My lord,
I am unjustly accused.
I kept silent because
my bitterness
was beyond words.
What bitterness?
I fail to understand.
I laid the proof
of Wang's
corruption
before you.
Why do you
defend him with such fervor?
It seems
Wang's words held truth after all.
What did he say?
After the bran scandal,
Wang and I shared a drink.
He boasted that
he had done far more for you
than I ever did.
That scheme
to swap
grain for bran?
It was your strategy
to topple Fan Chuan!
He pocketed
the bribes
for you,
and you
repaid his service
with a prison cell.
You bring tavern-talk
in front of His Majesty?
You have grown truly arrogant!
Tavern-talk is unworthy of belief?
Then
by what right
do you accuse me,
based solely on a past grudge?
You twist words like a snake!
Lord Fang!
Present, my lord.
Lord Li!
My lord.
Lord Wen!
At your service, my lord.
I demand the Court of Judicial
preside over this case.
The Ministry of Justice and the Censorate shall assist.
Chen's guilt
is plain as day!
Your Majesty!
Lord Ye Xian requests an audience!
Your Majesty,
I have secured
the Wang manor
and questioned all within.
We have a significant lead.
What is it?
Present it at once!
Your Majesty...
The session should be over.
Where is him?
The Chunyuan Sect?
Yes, Your Majesty.
This is their symbol,
"The Fearless,"
an oath of unwavering,
fatal devotion.
I found this very mark
upon the Wangs' steward.
But as I recall,
they were crushed
when the prince's coup failed.
They were
meant to be eradicated!
Your Majesty,
though
the majority were,
many fled to the north
and took refuge
with the barbarians.
Unbelievable!
Why would they
harbor such cultists?
Many of those
who fled were
learned men,
scholars
of rank.
The Northerners
have
co-opted them
into their service.
Then why
would Wang
employ a Chunyuan fanatic?
Your Majesty,
they're merely
a broken ghost
of the past.
A few desperate remnants
that pose
no danger
to your throne.
I advise
a discreet
investigation.
We must not let
their whispers
poison the minds
of the people.
Wise words, my lord.
And
what of Lord Chen?
Let him to
withdraw and recuperate.
Your Majesty,
state affairs require my attention.
I beg your leave.
Um...
What is it, my lord?
Did you know
the Wangs' steward
had the "Fearless" branded
onto his own skin?
Who told you such a thing?
It was uncovered by Ye Xian.
It cannot be!
Our sect teaches that
our flesh must
remain pristine.
We do not mar our skin,
let alone brand it
with our marks!
Did someone stage it?
Gods.
We've been played!
Ye Xian!
My lord.
You must be
famished.
I brought meat pies.
Not hungry.
His Majesty has kept me.
Leave.
He kept you?
A guard would
have told us.
But you came here yourself.
Worried I'd lose sleep?
I'm here
for Li Xianhuai.
Right, yes...
You and
your pride!
My lord!
My love,
all well?
Rest easy.
Why did you come?
I could not remain home while
you faced danger.
A man as crafty as he?
Danger is his playground.
Ye Xian,
must you always be
so venomous?
Then stop pulling him
into your games!
Stay out of this!
Why?
Every time they face ruin,
you're the one caught in the fray!
You're married!
Can't you leave him
out of your schemes?
Let's go home.
See.
Cat's got their tongues.
Ruixiang,
why do I find that
surly nature of his so charming?
You have an eye for a rare soul.
What is this?
A message from Ye Xian.
An audience
with His Majesty.
Greetings,
Your Majesty.
No formalities.
Gratitude.
Gratitude, Your Majesty.
We meet again, my lady.
You have a remarkable gift,
making two of
my finest lords
jealous over you.
Your Majesty,
the streets
are no place
for a sovereign.
You should return at once.
Lord Chen speaks wisely.
I shall escort you back.
Not yet!
It took great effort
to sneak out.
Fine! I won't speak
another word
of
your little triangle!
You two, withdraw.
I'll speak with Lord Chen alone.
My gratitude for recalling Ye Xian.
It was the only way
to make Lord Fu yield.
The credit is yours.
Had you not
traced
that steward
back to
Lord Fu's recommendation,
I would still
be blind to
my Chief Councilor's ties
to the Chunyuan Sect.
Perhaps there's
a misunderstanding.
Spare me his defense.
A man as shrewd as him
does not
recommend a man
without knowing his origins.
I believe
he knew
that steward's
identity
perfectly well.
He's been
a pillar of the empire,
and I have honored that.
But he overreaches,
spinning his webs
of influence
as though
the throne
were his to claim!
Now,
to find him
conspired with cultists?
He is surely
plotting something far darker.
I'm lucky
to have you and Ye Xian,
men willing to
stake their lives for me.
It is my duty, Your Majesty.
I have no more titles
to award Ye Xian for now;
it must wait until I'm truly in command.
But you,
I have spoken with Mother.
You shall be elevated.
Your Majesty...
She has consented.
With her approval,
Lord Fu has no grounds to protest.
I accept it
with all humility, Your Majesty.
Get well.
I need you
fighting-fit
for the battles ahead.
Yes, Your Majesty.
I never imagined
the Emperor would reach out to you.
Without him,
I'd have to
bide my time for years
before I could challenge Lord Fu.
And without Ye Xian and me,
His Majesty
would never seize true power.
It is
a strange destiny.
But mark my words:
our sovereign is
coming into his own.
What if
Fu Hailian suspects
the mark
was
your handiwork?
It is possible.
But it changes nothing.
The tie between us
is severed;
there is no going back.
But if
the sect
is truly at his command,
he will never stop hunting you.
Precisely why
I must drag
this conflict
into the light.
Better to face him
in the open
than to
have him plotting
in the shadows.
My hands are tied.
His eyes
are everywhere.
I'm sending
Qingpu to Shanxi.
Those cultists
fled north,
which borders Shanxi.
I've long had trade
established there.
I'll send her
under the cover
of managing my trade,
but she
will be tracking
the sect's shadow.
She is
as skilled
as she is discreet.
What do you think?
A clever gambit, truly.
Take your time.
I have work to attend to.
Of course.
[I've been to the border markets]
[twice.]
[I've spotted a barbarian merchant]
[keeping a Yan translator]
[who reeks of secrets.]
[He performs rites daily;]
[when I pressed him on his faith,]
[he turned evasive.]
[As you instructed,]
[I have kept my distance.]
Wang Nianen was
introduced to Wang Xuanfan
by Fu Hailian himself.
I've followed that trail
to the end,
yet I have found
nothing.
The Chunyuan Sect is
crawling all over this city.
They are far from subtle.
He is a low-level lackey;
how could he
possibly
vanish from your sight?
You should have
found something by now.
Why are your hands empty?
Are you suggesting
someone is obstructing us?
But Wang Xuanfan is dead.
Could it be Fu Hailian?
We shall see.
But you already
suspect him, right?
Fu is
too sharp to
let a man of
unknown origins
into Wang's house.
He must have known
Wang Nianen was a cultist.
But then,
if he knew,
why
place him there
for all these years?
It seems
Fu is inextricably
bound to the sect.
Those are theories,
not facts.
My men are under surveillance;
I can't make a move.
I must rely on you.
So, you're finally begging me?
Beg? Not at all.
Feel free to quit.
You know,
the one I truly wish to investigate
is you.
You seem to know
every detail
of the sect;
how are you so well-versed
in their darkness?
Maybe
read a book once in a while.
I'm starting to think
you're one of them.
By all means,
investigate me then.
Don't tempt me.
His Majesty sent word.
He Wenxin's away on leave.
Fu is officially pinning
the Wangs' murders on the sect.
Even the attempt on your life
is conveniently pinned
on Wang Xuanfan.
To cross you,
Wang Xuanfan truly
invited his own doom.
My lord,
the royal messenger is here.
Ah, the decree
for your promotion
is finally here.
My congratulations!
I suppose His Majesty's plan
to break Fu's grip
rests on your shoulders now.
Mercy or lash,
all is grace from the throne.
By Imperial Decree:
Chen Yanyun, for his
unwavering loyalty
and
exceptional governance,
is promoted to
Senior Grand Secretary
and named
Guardian of the Crown Prince.
So it is decreed.
I am humbled by this honor.
Long live the Emperor!
Our trade bureaus,
shipyards
and the weaving bureaus
are all in dire need of funds.
The cabinet has agreed
to divert
thirty percent
of our frontier defense funding
to bolster these institutions.
If the cabinet has reached
a consensus...
Your Majesty,
I must object.
Lord Fu is pushing to
cut frontier defense budget,
despite the opposition.
We have been
locked in war
with the barbarians
for two decades;
the truce is barely a year old.
By what right does he
gamble with our borders?
Unless he knows,
with absolute certainty,
that they won't invade us.
How could he be certain?
There is but one answer:
he has eyes
within the enemy's ranks,
a network unknown
to our generals
the court,
or even His Majesty.
Which makes them
his own private hounds.
I'm going to see His Majesty!
Choose a more
discreet place next time.
Fear not.
I shall be as a shadow.