[Mistaken Love]
[Episode 6]
You're crazy!
Those who pretend to be deaf and mute
are the ones who are truly crazy inside.
Your Highness, please don't be worried.
How am I worried?
Why should I be worried?
What do you know?
It's okay.
You may leave now.
Yes, Your Highness.
Conghuan.
Where have you been?
I...
I suppose after we got married,
you've been cooped up in the palace and feeling bored.
As it happens,
the annual Flower Shadow Festival of Qingshuo is coming up.
I'll have the maid take you to see it.
The Flower Shadow Festival?
That sounds wonderful.
Bravo!
I didn't expect Qingshuo to have such a grand event.
[Li Conghuan's Secret Guard, He Lianxuan]
Ninth Princess?
Let's go.
Have you found out anything about
the poisoned dart that killed my mother?
I've traced the dark iron
used to make the poisoned dart.
Give me a bit more time,
and I'll surely find the person in black who used it.
He survived both times I poisoned him.
What? He didn't die?
I think the poison wasn't strong enough.
Could it be that he has a powerful protector?
I'd better stay here to help you.
Otherwise, I'll be too worried.
I will carefully consider
my options for ways to kill him.
You continue to investigate the person in black
who used the poisoned dart.
Alright.
Why is He Lianxuan here?
Why are you here?
I'm here on behalf of my big brother to check
what my sister-in-law is up to outside the palace.
Why are you dressed like this?
Is it to meet He Lianxuan in secret?
He's just my secret guard.
Where did this country bumpkin come from?
How could a lowly person like you be allowed to
attend the Flower Shadow Festival?
Flower Shadow Festival?
You're so ignorant.
The Flower Shadow Festival is our day
to welcome the spring god for the coming year.
From this day on, people start to
look forward to the spring god.
Young men and women also begin to seek their partners.
This is the biggest annual event in our Qingshuo.
I see.
So, you're here to pick a man too, aren't you?
You...
How dare you!
No need to be shy.
In our Zizhou,
it's common for women to look for husbands.
There's nothing to be embarrassed about.
I... You...
Empress Dowager, you cannot leave the palace without permission.
Please return with us immediately.
I'll just play for a while.
I'll go back soon.
Empress Dowager.
The lords of the four kingdoms have offered to our Qingshuo
four peerless beauties despite the long distances.
The first three have already performed.
Now, let's welcome the last beauty to the stage
to showcase her talents.
Everyone, please applaud.
Great!
It's your turn to go on stage.
What exactly do you want?
What did He Lianxuan tell you?
He told me…
to kill you.
Then try it.
Great.
Bravo.
Cunning and deceitful.
Miss, why are you leaving?
You still need to participate in
expressing feelings through writing.
No, I... I'm not...
The person across from you is your destined one.
Just write down your feelings on it, Miss.
Sitting here
was not my intention.
♫The bell rings like questions♫
Strangers are
♫The past is like a dream, sword dance under pear blossoms♫
sometimes more approachable than those close to us.
♫Black hair turned white, yet cannot be severed♫
♫Bound by fate, even to death♫
♫Entangled in promises and vows♫
That's because those close to you know your weaknesses.
♫We see each other every year♫
If they want to hurt you,
they can certainly hurt you more deeply.
♫You're right in front of me; my heart is broken♫
♫Love is hard to say, the hidden hatred♫
I didn't understand these things before.
I once gave my heart to someone,
♫Is it love or resentment from past lives?♫
but she trampled on everything for fame and fortune.
♫The red blood stained the white snow♫
♫If love has turned into a sharp arrow♫
What a coincidence.
I've had a similar experience.
♫It will pierce the heart's desire♫
That person not only betrayed our feelings,
but he also killed my closest family.
♫The wind and snow rage and swirl♫
♫Entangling to redden the eyes♫
I never thought we'd share such a similar fate.
That person who betrayed you,
♫It fell between the eyebrows like fate♫
have you seen him since?
♫The destined cycle♫
More than that.
One day,
♫Gazes across the expanse of time♫
I'll make him pay blood for blood.
♫Love and hate travel through the years♫
♫The lights shine as desired, and we cherish our time together♫
♫The thrill of infatuation remains unspoken♫
Neither of us have control over our fates.
There are still many unfinished matters.
Whoever is behind this gauze curtain
is not important to either of us.
Since that's the case,
-we might as well not see each other.
♫You're right in front of me; my heart is broken♫
♫Love is hard to say, the hidden hatred♫
♫Is it love or resentment from past lives?♫
♫The red blood stained the white snow♫
What a pity.
These two should've been a perfect match.
♫If love has turned into a sharp arrow♫
Why were they unwilling to meet?
Such a shame.
♫It will pierce the heart's desire♫
How long are you going to keep harassing Conghuan?
You don't want your past with Conghuan
to be made public, do you?
I must return with my maid since we came out together.
Where is she?
Crown Princess,
the Crown Prince and the Second Prince are fighting on the city gate tower.
Hurry!
Conghuan told me everything.
You're the only stain in her past.
Shut up!
What you can't give her,
I can provide it all.
No!
Mo Heng!