[Mistaken Love]
[Episode 13]
Why did you bring me here?
Do you remember the archery technique I taught you?
All right.
It's your turn.
You were close to killing it.
Why haven't you mastered the technique yet?
I don't want to master such deadly skills.
But this archery technique
can save your life at critical moments.
I just need to wound the opponent to get a chance to escape.
I don't need to take someone's life.
All right.
It's up to you.
Anyway, in this lifetime,
I'll protect you.
This lifetime...
I later realized
one's lifetime is so long.
No one can truly protect another forever.
Don't even think about dodging it.
Today,
you'll have to master it.
The bow should be close to the arrow.
The arrow should be close to the string.
The string should be close to the face.
These are called Three Closenesses.
Keep yourself aligned with the target.
Keep your shoulders aligned.
Keep your arms aligned.
Keep your feet aligned.
Stay mentally aligned.
These are called Five Alignments.
When facing an enemy,
you only have one chance to get a lethal shot.
So,
you must aim precisely at his heart.
Again.
Start over.
You're not allowed to leave until you master it.
How could you be so unreasonable?
How can anyone master it in just one day?
But I only have one day left.
Miss,
you're a fast learner.
You're the first one to hit the target today.
This is your prize.
Thank you.
This is a special osmanthus sachet from Zizhou.
Since I came to Qingshuo,
I've never smelled this kind of aroma before.
Nine,
I'm sorry.
I can't protect you anymore in this lifetime.
From now on, you're on your own.
They say the gods will help you realize your wishes
that are made while you're setting off sky lanterns.
So, what did you wish for?
I'm not telling you.
What did you wish for?
I hope I can take your life soon.
Then I have to live a long life.
I won't let your wish come true.
Nine.
If...
I mean, if one day I die,
will you cry for me?
If one day you die,
I'll definitely applaud and cheer.
What did you wish for?
Don't just stand there.
Let's go.
It's raining. I'll go find an umbrella.
Wait for me.
The dead are free from all worries,
while the living are burdened with countless concerns.
Who are you?
I'm just
a commoner,
not as noble as you.
But you
will be nothing but a handful of dirt
in two more hours.
[Heart's Blood of Medicine Maid]
Medicine Maid?
Medicine Maid was born with a unique constitution.
She has tasted hundreds of herbs since childhood.
Her blood can be used against poison.
Incorporating her heart's blood
into your medicine as a medicinal material
can detoxify you.
If I take her heart's blood,
can she survive?
Life and death are unpredictable.
It's all up to fate.
This is the only way for you to survive.
She
is just close at hand.
Whether you can survive is in your hands.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Where did that old man go?
What old man?
Let's go.
It stops raining.
The world is so quiet.
I've never seen what it's like outside the Qingshuo Palace.
Mo Jin.
We haven't had a good conversation.
You promised me
you'd tell me everything today.
I'm looking forward to it, yet I'm a bit afraid.
I'm afraid my expectations will be let down.
But I...
Still want to believe you.
Mo Jin.
Mo Jin!
You survived?
Sounds like you're quite disappointed
at the fact that I'm not dead.
But you
will be nothing but a handful of dirt
in two more hours.
You're not allowed to leave until you master it.
How could you be so unreasonable?
How can anyone master it in just one day?
I mean, if one day I die,
will you cry for me?
Liar.
Your life belongs to me.
Without my permission,
you can't die.
Li Conghuan,
since I met you,
nothing positive has come my way.
l want you to stop pestering me.
You should leave.
Do you really want me to leave?
Do you?
Then why did you want me to spend this day with you?
Why did you go to great lengths to arrange all this?
Didn't you arrange all those people?
You're just being overly sentimental.
I've never seen someone as stupid as you.
You have been fooled by others over and over,
yet you're still willing to trust others.
Do you know
why I keep you by my side?
Just to toy with you.
Then why did you take the whip for me?
Why did you save me so many times?
Why do you care so much about the Longevity Lock?
It was all just an act.
You don't really think I still have feelings for you, do you?
Get lost.
Mo Jin.
Look into my eyes.
I just want one answer.
♫Rain falls down in the yard at night♫
Look into my eyes
♫Reflecting on the departure in the world♫
and say it again.
Say it.
♫We meet each other again even when we're apart♫
Say it!
♫What we had was glorious♫
Why did you come back?
You should leave.
♫A sharp arrow pierced through memories♫
I've arranged everything.
At dawn, He Lianxuan will take you back to Zizhou.
♫Love is growing♫
♫The curtain separates love and hatred♫
Leave.
I won't leave.
I won't.
I won't leave you alone.
♫After endless sorrow♫
I won't leave.
♫Love is hard to forget♫