Well said.
Let you go.
Death.
I only know that
someone sent a secret letter to Zhao Yong
to report your Yuwen family's rebellion.
and provided evidence.
We started to handle it impartially.
But later,
Tell me.
Someone came to me later.
But Yuwen family
is a respectable person.
I'm afraid
it'll be hard to explain.
It's really not about money.
You mean our butler?
Wang Tianxing?
Wang Tianxing.
Also,
your brother, Li Siwen's father,
The Master of Dojo.
Li Jian Xing.
You want to kill me?
It's not that easy.
So what?
Since you've escaped,
you should live in Nanyang for the rest of your life.
But now you don't have the chance.
Everyone wants you to die.
You know too much.
No one wants you to live.
If I kill you now,
I can redeem myself.
Choi Young.
Calm down.
Mr. Luo is a VIP from Nanyang.
We have to take responsibility if anything happens.
Hey.
Are you okay?
You two
are indeed in cahoots.
Sir.
Your wine.
Help!
They colluded
to set me up.
Choi Young, what are you doing?
Open the door.
Did you hear that?
Leave now.
Wait for someone to come in.
none of you can escape.
Brother.
Cut the crap.
Do it.
Commissioner, you're here.
Hurry up.
Take a photo.
Why are you here?
I'm afraid you'll be in danger.
But you can't kick him off.
I didn't mean it.
I'm afraid he'll run away.
You'll be in trouble.
It's more troublesome now.
Brother.
They're coming in.
Hit me!
Hit me, knock me out.
Notify everyone.
Seal off the crime scene.
Commissioner Li.
Can we talk?
Mr. Luo.
You're awake.
This is...
This is the best hospital in Southern City.
I happen to know someone here.
You can rest assured, Mr. Luo.
By the way,
My wife
made for you.
Delicious buns.
Try it.
Mr. Luo,
Did you just come to Shanghai?
I'm really sorry.
I just got here.
Choi Young.
He's dead.
When we went in,
Mr. Luo, you passed out.
So...
Deputy Director Wu,
I want to ask you about the details.
Is it convenient?
It tastes good.
The buns your wife made
suits my taste.
Please enjoy.
Mr. Na is awake.
I heard Choi Young died.
That day, Choi Young
took me to the lounge.
Then, there was a fight.
My hands were tied up.
Later,
Then I fainted.
Then I woke up.
It's right here.
How did you know
Choi Young died?
I saw signs of a fight at the scene.
It must be Mr. Na.
during the fight with Choi Young.
with Choi Young.
It's strange.
That waiter
hasn't been found yet.
Mr. Luo.
Do you know him?
We met once.
I heard
Mr. Luo
is back from Nanyang.
overseas Chinese.
Where was Mr. Luo
before he went abroad.
I grew up abroad.
But my parents are Chinese.
It seems that Mr. Luo
from Mr. Luo today.
Actually,
I have an old friend
is also in Nanyang.
Maybe he knows Mr. Luo.
Now that I think about it,
I don't think it's a coincidence.
Just in time.
Today is
is the anniversary of his old friend's parents' death.
It was at Mount Phoenix outside the city.
So, I have to go now.
excuse me.
Let's
another day.
It's been ten years.
I'm back.
Choi Young is dead.
Unfortunately, I couldn't
kneel before you to apologize.
Don't worry.
I will make them pay
I will make them pay.
Brother.
Who is Oh-reum?
Who are you?
Why did you save me?
I'm Wu Tian.
Master Yuwen saved my mother's life.
He is a good man.
He won't betray the country.
My father...
Stay there.
The warden won't be here soon.
Find a chance
I'll let you out.
After you get out,
you can go to Nanyang.
I have friends there.
Remember.
Live well.
Tong.
Go back first.
I have to go somewhere.
I sigh that no one will notice
The intersection is already clouded.
It can connect the ancient and modern times.
Peach Xuxi Red Rain reports the new sun
I have a daughter.
If you get the money,
If possible,
find her for me.
There's a letter
in the bank safe.
There's a poem in it.
was written to my daughter
when she was three.
[I wrote for her.]
It's creative.
This missing person notice
will be published
in the most obvious location.
Make sure everyone can see it.
No problem.
But the price might be...
The headline.
Time.
One month.
Always.
Crystal report, everyone.
Mr. Henry
will be at your command.
Hello.
Mr. Henry.
Do you live here?
I went out for something.
Sir.
Have some water.
He has a sister.
Excuse me, sir.
I'll get you another cup.
You're the missing waiter, right?
Stand there.
Don't move.
Deputy Director Wu.
Explain it.
Mr. Luo.
Explain first.
Explain what?
This must be the waiter Choi Young harassed.
You two are in this together.
and killed Choi Young.
Do I look like him?
No?
Is it?
A waiter.
and my sister.
A face.
How?
Yes.
Just like her.
It's her.
You framed Choi Young together.
The case is closed.
Why are you here?
On the day of the incident,
you had more than one argument with Choi Young.
Before he died,
before he died.
So Sa-wen had a fight with him too?
The waiter is your sister.
She knows kung fu?
Is it illegal?
Why?
What do you mean why?
Why did you come back?
I told you
to live well.
Remember.
Stay alive.
Don't shoot.
[Product]
Beijing Sunu Culture Co., Ltd.
Beijing iQIYI Technology Co., Ltd.
Beijing Fenghai Film and Media Co., Ltd.
Hainan hip-hop Culture Co., Ltd.
Producer
[Joint Producer]
Shi Ke Nan, Uncle Mak.
Li Junxing, Zhuo Huimin, Liu Hui, Zhang Wanlu.
Actors group
as Yenna Lan.
Abu as Li Shiyue
Cui Zhigang as Lao Luo
Zhou Xiaopeng as Li Jian Xing
Gao Guo as Wang Tianxing
Zhang Mingming as Tak Qi.
Bacon Wang as Choi Young
Yoo Ja-rim as Yu-yeon
Yang Bo-seung as Jin Se-chang
[The director team]
Yang Shu Jie.
The script.
[Writer]
Hsu Hui-ting, Sun Bolin
Zhang Jianyong.
Ziye.
Planning.
Life Producer.
[Live Producer]
Wang Dan.
Peng Chaoyu, Han Xiu Xiu.
Team.
Xu Ying.
[Art Group]
Mei Feng Art Instructor.
Xu Huan.
The prop team leader.
Wang Qingming.
Sun Jia, Zhao Lin Fei.
Meng Qing.
Han Dongjin He Jiandong
Focus.
Liang Stick, Feng's, Shi Tao, Li Xinqiang.
Han Bo, the waiting group.
Lighting guidance.
Li Zhenzuo, Zhao Pang, Guo Zhiqiang, Zhang Mingzhe
Li Xiaohu.
Recording assistant.
Jo Sin-ok.
Wu Jian, Chen Shiguang, Qi Sichen.
[The styling team]
styling instructor.
Huacbing.
Makeup focus.
Han Bing, Yoo Gangnam.
Costume Team Leader.
The main focus of clothing.
Zhang Ye and Zoe Jiang.
[Action team]
Action director.
Li Peng Cheng.
Wang Jin.
Substitute.
Yang Hung, Su Feng, Liu Ziqiang, Wang Zili, Gu Bin,
Huang Jintao, Li Longping, Zhang Jinshu, Zhang Ping, Shen Boman.
Mid-film shot.
Cut.
The post-production director.
Wang Rui.
Advanced.
Beijing Gathering Pictures Culture and Communication Co., Ltd.
post-production director.
Producer.
Hongjie Qi Haoxiang
Li Yang.
Voice Instructor.
Yang Shuo.
Liang Xiaojie Zhang Wenyuan
Mixed record.
Wu Wenjuan, Liang Haoyu.
Effect Editor.
Zhang Yixing: Come on.
Voice show.
Zhou Qinghe, Lin Zhaoyan, Liu Shiyuan, Fan Zhenlu. Liu Shiyuan, Liu Yiying.
Break.
Gao Xin.
Arrangement.
Zhang Wenyuan.
Wenkuo.
Music production.
[PR Team]
Yang Bin.
Ming Xie.