Wang Tianxing suddenly bought a lot of shares.
Where did he get so much money?
Good.
Looks like he's moving someone else's cake.
Wu Tian.
send some good news
some good news about the special medicine.
Let's give him another push.
How much is it this time?
12 yuan.
Yes.
I drank too much.
Have some tea.
Ms. Mo Li.
Have you been eavesdropping?
I'm here to deliver tea to Mr. Luo.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Good tea!
Pudong medicine.
100 stocks.
Hurry up.
50 shares.
Sir,
The stock price has risen too fast.
Someone must have maliciously raised the price.
Many big families have entered.
I'm afraid we can't take it.
You know nothing.
You talk too much.
When Miss Mo Li wakes up,
washing and cooking.
What is he doing?
Guess
why I'm not leaving.
On the contrary,
I'm guessing
will leave.
You're right.
I'm leaving now.
Where are you going?
Flowers.
Flowers?
There are so many flowers in my yard.
in my yard.
Remember.
I like Jasmine.
It's not the season for jasmine to bloom.
What a beautiful jasmine flower bone.
I thought you found a new job
after you found a new job.
The flowers
bloom brightly.
And
in the right place.
Really?
Cut the crap.
Any good news?
Henglio asked Manager Qian
to buy
from
in Pudong Pharmaceuticals.
They said they'll take as much as they have.
No cost.
at any cost.
I knew it was him.
By the way,
One night,
a foreigner rushed in
and yelled at him.
What?
He poisoned
while making medicine.
Is that him?
Moving Bei Nan.
This is
It's him.
No wonder.
No wonder he stayed in Henry's house.
There's something wrong.
I knew it.
You're sneaky
sneaking around
[sneaking around.]
Mr. Wang.
Are you...
Did you do something wrong?
Why did you invite Detective Oh?
Well...
Looking for a girl?
It's not a crime, right?
Of course not.
Then no one did it.
You can...
Please leave.
Thank you.
Don't ever think about stepping into the Henry family again.
Where were we?
They had a fierce fight.
Just a fight.
Really?
Pudong medicine will rise.
It's just that the news hasn't been released yet.
So you...
We're out of money again.
What did you say?
I'm out of money again.
Why do I always have no money?
Did you hack money?
How about this?
Give me
the money
to the south city.
Sir.
You're playing with fire.
If we fail,
both of us will die.
What's wrong with you?
You never change.
I lost hundreds of thousands because of you last time.
If you say one more word,
I'll sew your mouth.
Get lost!
Come back.
Help me.
Contact two people.
Where's Jasmine?
She went to buy flowers.
Flowers?
You believe everything she says.
I came to tell you where she went.
She went to inform Wang Tianxing.
What?
That's it.
Luo,
What are you doing?
Wang Tianxing.
I asked you to work with me before.
and gave you a chance to make money.
Now you secretly built the mouse warehouse
and bought all my stocks.
I paid for it.
and made an article with the newspaper.
But you made all the money.
Is this appropriate?
The plague is coming.
There are many people in Shanghai.
Luo,
This is your fault.
You didn't cooperate with me back then.
But I'm not like you.
I'll let bygones be bygones.
I want to introduce some old friends to you.
George.
Anthony.
Come in.
Mr. Wang.
Thank you.
Please.
You...
You know each other?
I don't need to introduce you.
Interesting.
You think my money is dirty?
What?
his money is clean?
Luo,
They are
are my advisors.
Now,
The plague is rampant.
The newspaper is very interested
in Pudong Pharmaceuticals.
So,
I invited them here
to help you.
Wang Tianxing.
Don't go too far.
Me?
You make medicine
while making drugs.
You said I went too far.
You used dirty tricks.
You raise the stock price.
You said I went too far.
Speaking of going too far,
The same goes for you.
have their own lives.
You know everything?
Of course.
Since you chose not to cooperate with me,
I have to find my own way out.
The road is facing the sky.
and go half way.
Let's see what we can do.
Don't report me in the future.
If you do,
let's fight till the end.
Who?
Don't do it.
You...
Please leave.
Okay.
Get out.
This means leaving.
Thank you very much, Mr. George.
Thank you very much for your votes.
Cheers.
Henglio used drugs to make medicine.
It's unpardonable.
You're welcome, Mr. Wang.
It's not just about money.
Most importantly,
is Mr. Wang's character.
You're right.
I am a noble person.
A person
who is out of the low-class fun.
As the old saying goes,
the world is full of joy
is for profit.
The world
for profit.
We businessmen
should be profitable.
But
in life,
you can't go against your will.
You can't go against your will.
If you harm the law of heaven,
will be punished.
Do you think
Pudong.
Tell me.
how much
How much can it go up?
I think
at least 15.
No.
Once Pudong medicine is published,
at least
This amount.
Twenty.
I didn't expect
can dance so well.
A romantic place.
We need to be friends.
Ms. Mo Li is experienced.
How many men am I to you?
I said the first one.
Do you believe me?
If you dare,
if you dare.
Mr. Luo.
What are you going to do next?
Are you talking about tonight
or stocks?
Tonight, of course.
The rest of the stocks.
Ms. Mo Li,
is this a spy?
Why do you say so?
Wu Tian told me
you went to see Wang Tianxing today.
Mr. Wang and I
using each other.
It's just a show.
What about me?
I have something on him.
Can you help me
escape from his control?
What makes you think
I can save you?
I believe
you have the ability.
I'm going to throw away all the medicine for Pudong.
Me too.
Did you throw them away?
No, it's still covered.
Throw it now.
Is he a fool?
But why is it still falling?
Yes, what's going on?
Sir.
14.8 yuan.
Only 15 yuan short.
You scared me.
Sorry, sir.
Now
the stock price is going down.
It's a little unstable.
Many small investors have been discarded.
Why don't we just give up?
Retreat a little.
It's okay.
It's all with me.
How can they compete with me?
It will rise again.
Luckily I didn't throw it.
It finally rises.
Again
It's going up.
I'm glad you didn't throw it away.
I'm really going to send it this time.
F.
It's going up.
Yes.
Pudong medicine is 16 fast.
Do you know what breaks the soul with one knife?
A sword breaks the soul?
You'll lose a lot of money.
The market will open tomorrow morning.
Pudong Pharmaceuticals
to the lowest.
How much?
[Product]
Beijing Sunu Culture Co., Ltd.
Beijing iQIYI Technology Co., Ltd.
Beijing Fenghai Movie and Media Co., Ltd.
Hainan hip-hop Culture Co., Ltd.
Producer
[Joint Producer]
Shi Ke Nan, Uncle Mak.
Li Junxing, Zhuo Huimin, Liu Hui, Zhang Wanlu.
Actors group
as Yenna Lan.
Abu as Li Shiyue
Cui Zhigang as Lao Luo
Zhou Xiaopeng as Li Jian Xing
Zhang Mingming as Tak Qi.
Bacon Wang as Choi Young
Yoo Ja-rim as Yu-yeon
Yang Bo-seung as Jin Se-chang
[The director team]
Yang Shu Jie.
The script.
[Writer]
Hsu Hui-ting, Sun Bolin
Zhang Jianyong.
Ziye.
Planning.
Life Producer.
[Live Producer]
Wang Dan.
Peng Chaoyu, Han Xiu Xiu.
Team.
Xu Ying.
Huang Xinyao, Rongwei soldiers
[Art Group]
Mei Feng Art Instructor.
Xu Huan.
The prop team leader.
Wang Qingming.
Sun Jia, Zhao Lin Fei.
Meng Qing.
Han Dongjin He Jiandong
focus.
Han Bo, the waiting group.
Lighting guidance.
Li Zhenzuo, Zhao Pang, Guo Zhiqiang, Zhang Mingzhe
Li Xiaohu.
Recording assistant.
Jo Sin-ok.
Wu Jian, Chen Shiguang, Qi Sichen.
[The styling team]
styling instructor.
Huacbing.
Makeup focus.
Han Bing, Yoo Gangnam.
Costume Team Leader.
The main focus of clothing.
Zhang Ye and Zoe Jiang.
[Action team]
Action director.
Li Peng Cheng.
Wang Jin.
Substitute.
Yang Hung, Su Feng, Liu Ziqiang, Wang Zili, Gu Bin,
Huang Jintao, Li Longping, Zhang Jinshu, Zhang Ping, Shen Boman.
Mid-film shot.
Editing instructor.
The post-production director.
Wang Rui.
Beijing Gathering Pictures Culture and Communication Co., Ltd.
Producer.
Hongjie Qi Haoxiang
Li Yang.
Beijing Leya Culture and Media Co., Ltd.
Late Voice Instructor.
Yang Shuo.
Liang Xiaojie, Zhang Wenyuan
Mixed record.
Wu Wenjuan, Liang Haoyu.
Effect Editor.
Liang Xiaojie
Voice show.
Zhou Qing and Lin Zhaoyan, Liu Shiyuan, Liu Shiyuan, Liu Shiyuan, Liu Yiying.
Break.
Gao Xin.
Lyrics.
Arrangement.
Zhang Wenyuan.
Wen Kuo
Music production.
[PR Team]
Yang Bin.
Ming Xie.