Timing and Subtitles brought to you by
Sustainable Heartbeats Team @Viki.com
Focus your breathing.
Free yourself,
and feel the moment.
A soft breeze caresses your cheek,
as the smell of greenery...
Smell of...
Something's burning!
Oh no, no, no.
Dad, turn off the stove, please.
You can tell it's burning, right?
Remote marriage...
Remote...
- Dad!
- Huh?
Does concentrating kill your nose?
Is there a fire?
Reheat this curry for dinner, okay?
Oh, it's just burnt curry.
I made it pleasant-smelling.
Few Japanese would consider this pleasant-smelling. After all, pleasant-smelling-
Here's breakfast.
Huh?
Fewer dishes to wash.
We're being eco-friendly.
But not to me. Yoko would-
I'm not Mom.
We're both busy, working adults. Help out for once.
All right.
Urgh, I haven't charged my phone.
Where'd I put it?
Move, I've got a phone to charge.
Is it here?
Ow... Dad, call me.
Again? You're a slob.
- Sloven, I say!
- Just call me quickly.
[Father]
Listen. I left my phone here
while grabbing batteries for you.
You're not helping by covering it with newspapers.
You look for your phone every morning.
And you're always looking for the batteries.
Keep track of them already.
Make sure to fold your own laundry.
Okay.
Straighten up.
You'll look old.
My phone.
Where's my phone again?
Where is it?
There.
Won't they make a word that describes the hunt for one's own phone?
"Remote Marriage..."
to get married online, huh?
I'm off.
At this point, any method will do.
Yoko-san, will this girl ever get married?
Sorry, I'm getting on!
Is marriage that necessary?
Although some people consider this era a difficult one,
I'm glad to have been born in it.
Some people live the very picture of family life.
Others are married, without kids.
Single mothers make do too.
No matter the lifestyle,
I am freer than I would've been in Showa era,
when unmarried women over 25 were called spinsters.
The only flaw of modern freedom?
It's much harder to find someone similar to you.
My current goal is to dedicate my body, brain, emotions,
my everything... to whatever I want to do.
I've got no time for marriage.
[Yoga]
[Vanessa Yoga Studio]
- Good morning.
Good morning.
- Morning, Kenshin Sensei.
- Morning.
- Kyoka Sensei.
- Huh?
- Your shirt's on backward.
- No way.
Breath in, lift your right arm,
and breath out, to the left.
Do not push yourself. Comfort is key.
Keep your gaze on the ceiling.
Chest out and let out a breath.
Yoga is not all about difficult poses.
Maintaining a beautiful body and soul
is another aspect of yoga.
A life of purity is key.
Do not let emotions like jealousy and obsession control you.
[Mikako, Yoga Teacher: Find your new self through yoga. We offer you a wonderful yoga life.]
A smoothie?
"The time you enjoy wasting is not wasted time."
8,647 likes?
- Good work.
- Likewise.
Ouch!
- You okay?
- I'm fine.
If only your students saw your true nature, they'd be surprised.
Hey, I was in a real rush this morning, okay?
If every instructor upheld all the laws of yoga, you'd be a saint.
I try to uphold them.
If I could drink a smoothie every morning, I would.
But if I did, I'd lose out on stretch time.
Wake up that early, and I'd be snacking now.
So you do follow Mikako Sensei's Instagram.
I never specified.
But 100,000 followers? Who wouldn't be jealous?
- Good work today!
- Hello.
Good work out there.
Oh, keep this a secret.
I have to uphold the Mikako image.
Can't disappoint my students... I mean, fans.
But Ahimsa chocolate
(T/N: the teaching of non-violence)
satiates me and my fans.
Ahimsa...
Like, non-violence chocolate?
- I'm off to the Aoyama studio.
- See you.
I wonder why Kyoka Sensei has been packing her schedule.
"The time you enjoy wasting is not wasted time."
What was that?
"The time you enjoy-"
[What makes you unique?]
Unique?
Relax your shoulders. Pull in that stomach.
I work hard at my job and pursue my goals.
No. In reality, I work so hard, I'm a slob at home.
Feel yourself in the moment.
Cleanse your mind and soul.
Ironically, I'm not following my own yoga principles.
Be kind not only to others but to yourself.
But there are times I can't be kind at all.
Wasn't that why I began yoga, though?
Up I go.
"LMAO"...
"Finger-lickin' good"...
"Giving life"...
"Fatcarons"...
[Sanseido Dictionary]
Isn't "gacha" already in our latest dictionary?
(T/N: a luck-based loot box system)
Yes, but the current definition is exclusive to toys and gaming.
Nowadays, it describes any sort of chance occurrence.
It can even mean fate... no, destiny!
Oh, the difference between "fate" and "destiny" from a-
Sensei, that's enough.
I'm sorry.
Just earlier, while I was out researching...
- Insane, right?
- Totally.
- Right?
- Yeah.
My dad totally lost his mind about the sleepover.
Like, really? I'm only going to Erika's.
My parent-gacha sucks.
Wait. He's totally snooping.
- Ew gross!
- Creepy!
- For real!
- Why us?
Gosh, he's taking notes.
Gross!
Why the huge bag too?
They really put me in my place.
Sawada Sensei, please reel in your work ethic.
Otherwise, marriage will be the least of your daughter's concerns.
Really? And it'll be my fault?
Excuse me.
Is there something?
No.
Is that so...
Actually, please just tell me. I won't mind.
Then may I see your back?
- Your back.
- All right.
Pardon me for a moment.
Puff out your chest, and feel your airflow.
My chest?
It's nothing.
Ah, this way.
O-Oh, erm...
[Small Business Seminar]
Good evening. It's nice to meet you all.
Please call me Danny.
My goal is to create a platform within the next few years,
where users can share designs of their own.
Pleased to make your acquaintance.
Up next, let's have our two newcomers
introduce themselves.
At our seminar, we ask that you go by a nickname
to overcome the hierarchical mindset of business.
A nickname?
In that case...
I'm Seita, spelled with the characters for "spring" and "tarou".
It's my actual name, but I'm drawing a blank otherwise.
Nice to meet you all.
My name is Kyoka, as in "apricot flower".
Just as my name says,
I was born on a rainy, spring day.
(T/N: Apricots are in season when it rains)
Nice to meet you all.
The deciding factor of any business is the number of sponsors.
Your magnetism and charisma
will be tested here.
And now, some homework.
I'd like you all to reach out to a stranger by our next seminar.
Any businessperson needs the charisma of a flirt.
A flirt?
And charisma...
Before we go, please open your introduction sheets.
I'd like to ask why you have attended our seminar today.
Let's see...
How about you, Seita-san?
M-Me?
Well, I...
I currently work at a real estate agency.
Two years prior, I was moved to our newer branch.
And... Well...
Do you dislike your current job?
No, nothing like that.
Rather than focus on myself...
I wish to focus on others...
or rather, find a method of work that's kind to my family.
That is why I attended this seminar today.
Others, huh?
Your wife's lucky to have you.
I... have no wife.
Nor do I have any plans to get married.
Thank you.
Who shall we hear from next?
How about you, Danny-san?
In my case, I believe Japanese business...
Excuse me!
I'm sorry for earlier.
Oh, not at all.
To tell you the truth, I'm a yoga instructor.
Ah, so that's why...
Yes, your posture bothered me.
My apologies.
Well then... See you, Kyoka-san.
Magnetism and charisma...
Seita-san!
Do you have time for a drink?
[Is Love Sustainable?]
[Episode 1]
Now that we're settled...
- Nice to meet you.
- Seita-san.
- Kyoka-san.
Adding the character for "rain" to my name reads "Kyoka-u".
It means "springtime rain".
"Kyoka-u"? That's the first time I heard this.
That's natural. My dad's just a word geek.
He makes dictionaries for a living.
Wow, that's amazing.
Anything aside from work is beyond him, though.
He can't even notice the smell of burning curry.
Curry?
My father and I live together.
Our latest argument was about tonight's curry.
Is he a single father?
No, I moved back because my mother passed two years prior.
Really, all we do is fight.
Oh...
Sorry, that must've sounded heavy.
No, it's fine.
I think your father must be glad that his kind daughter is home.
I'm only there for financial reasons.
There was no better way to save money for a startup.
Even my current job doesn't know about this.
Is that what brought you to the seminar?
In short, I'm not kind at all.
- Rather, Seita-san...
- You're kind.
After all, you cook for your father.
I know it's difficult to cook for family
- every single day.
- It's just curry.
But curry is amazing!
All its spices essentially make the curry a herbal medicine.
Licorice, turmeric, cloves...
it even contains coriander, which is cilantro seeds!
I never knew...
Right... Sorry, I just really like curry.
You made that quite obvious.
I'm sorry.
No, it was interesting.
[Parent-Gacha]
"Parent-Gacha".
To lament about not being born to the right parents.
Coined from the term "gacha", used primarily in video games.
[Example : "My parent-gacha sucks."]
My parent-gacha sucks, huh?
Okay, stop.
I don't care about the seminar. Were there any nice guys around?
No use asking Kyoka-san.
Marriage is beyond her.
Hey, isn't that Kazuma-kun's?
Don't blame me if you two fight, and he leaves again.
Your doodling is atrocious, too.
Just break up. It's been four years, and I see no ceremony.
You're wasting your time.
It's more of a waste if I don't get married.
Look. We already spent 10,000 yen on that.
[Marriage Amulet]
10,000?
10,000 to get married? That's nothing.
I'd pay anything for my life's greatest event.
Do we really need to try so hard?
There are plenty of single guys out there.
- Let nature handle it!
- Naive.
Don't you realize you're over thirty?
Nowadays, we women have to take the reins. Nature's beyond us.
I bet Kyoka-san's oblivious to marriage because she's at home.
The opposite, actually.
Looking after my dad
makes me wonder why mom married him at all.
I'd love to ask her
if she regrets her decision.
How's your dad been, anyway?
Much better than when he acted like an empty husk.
I don't blame him. Your mom was amazing.
I remember she won a singing contest by dancing AKB.
(T/N: an idol group)
She used to be an interpreter around the globe, right?
Yeah. But she settled down after marriage.
She was living my ideal life.
I wonder if that's the case.
She might have had other things she wanted to do.
Maybe her dream was to become a mother.
My mom was always the person
who prayed for her family at shrines.
- Same goes for her Tanabata wishing slip.
- I could never.
(T/N: July 7th; write a wish, hang it on bamboo)
Same for me. I'll never live up to my mom.
I mean, how could I prioritize someone else?
My priority now is a personal studio.
One day I'll be doing yoga in the tropics,
and want to fulfill my human destiny.
Anything's better than your previous job. That left you dead.
It sure did.
Does that mean you'll never get married?
I just don't want to force it.
I'd rather fall in love with an ordinary, kind person.
Most "ordinary, kind people" are looking to get married.
Is there any person similar to you?
There is.
A bond of trust...
At least, I think so.
is the very lifeline of all businesses.
Investors are tough to crack.
You must focus on your merits and demerits.
A logical presentation will help garner your investor's trust.
How does this merit you? The investor?
Find the perfect middle ground for a successful negotiation.
- Hey, it's fun!
- Wait!
It's fun.
Oh, good evening.
I was recalling the fun I use to have, frolicking in the rain as children.
I see.
I never realized how soft springtime showers are.
So this is what a "Kyoka-u" feels like.
You've reminded me
that rain isn't so bad after all.
Thank you.
Are you hungry?
Yes, very.
Shall we grab a bite somewhere?
Yes.
Then I've got just the place.
Anyone can make curry, but they'll all taste different.
Family recipes and whatnot, you know?
This store uses an original spice blend,
including one called mace.
Oh no, was it too spicy?
Um, I have a proposal.
Yes?
I think we're quite an unusual pair, no?
How so?
For one, I dream to open my own yoga studio.
Seeing as I have a goal, I have no desire to get married currently.
I... see?
One of my biggest merits is that I'd never pressure a man into marriage.
Right.
As for my demerits,
I'm sloven, messy, and can't take care of myself,
let alone a husband.
If anything, I'd like a wife.
A wife...
Someone who loves to redecorate,
who's good at dividing plastics for recycling,
and organizing.
- That I understand.
- Right?
In other words, my demerits are your merits.
Pardon?
I mean, you have no desire to get married either, correct?
In other words, I see no reason why we shouldn't go out.
Huh?
Would you please go out with me
without marriage in mind?
Excuse me?
Erm...
W-Well... but... I'm...
Uh...
Is that a no?
U-Um...
I get it.
No worries, it's no big deal.
Sorry, I made it sound all businesslike.
- That's not-
- I really overthought this.
Sorry.
I'm a single father.
Huh?
I'm once divorced with a son.
He's in second grade.
So marriage is a bit...
I... see.
I can't focus on my own dreams
or goals like you anymore.
Right now, my son takes priority.
However, working an office job doesn't make parenting easy.
I attended the seminar in hopes of finding a better way
to balance my work and home life.
To focus on others, was it?
Yes...
Or rather, my son.
Therefore, you're wasted on someone like me.
You'd be better off-
Do you pray for your family's health and happiness at shrines?
Yes?
And use your Tanabata slip for them?
I-I guess so.
How lovely.
I'm sure your son adores you.
I respect people like you since I simply can't do the same.
Thank you.
Hearing that cheers me up.
- Shall we-
- Forget everything I-
You first.
Shall we start as friends?
- Friends?
- Yes. Friends.
Friends...
For one, let's exchange Line IDs.
As friends?
As friends.
Here's my ID.
Thank you.
And added.
Text me if you need me.
If I need you?
Or if you just want to.
All right, I will.
[Thank you, Dad]
Dad? Dad, wake up.
Dad!
Your phone's ringing.
Oh, I dozed off.
Thanks.
[Kyoka Sawada: Thank you for inviting me out today. The curry was delicious.]
[Likewise, thank you for joining!]
Work again?
Is it from the department head?
Huh? No.
From an important friend.
Wait... something stinks.
Did you shampoo properly?
I-I did.
No, I'll wash them.
No! You get bubbles in my face!
- No! No!
- I got you, Mister!
- I'm home.
- Welcome back.
What are you doing?
Tried my hand at cooking... no, "prepping" curry.
Either way, what's with your sudden gusto?
I'll do my share of chores,
so feel free to get married. I'll manage.
Huh?
Weren't you home late because of a boyfriend?
Of course not.
- Just leave me be.
- How could I?
So? How about getting married?
How about it?
Dad, what even is marriage?
- Huh?
- What does the dictionary say?
T-The dictionary?
Let's see...
"When a man and a woman get married"...?
That's like describing "idiot" with "stupid".
Dad, how would you define marriage?
I still don't know.
- Still?
- Anyhow, you should get married.
Why are you all about marriage today?
Because if lousy parent-gacha is the reason you don't, how can I die easily?
What are you saying?
Mom's finally living it up in heaven.
Mom's pitiful if you die now.
I've practically died once already.
Stop talking about dying.
You're only convincing me not to marry.
All you do is obsess over words, with no life skills to your name.
Where was your motive to cook while mom was alive?
Jeez, was she happy at all?
Sorry.
But seriously, no more talk of dying.
She's already been gone for two years.
Wait, you called a shrine for her second death anniversary, right?
Uh oh.
Right this way.
Yes, right this way.
Sorry to suddenly push this on you, Auntie Chieko.
No worries. So, are you two getting along?
Similar personalities and all.
Similar? Far from it.
Still, we're getting by.
They were really such a wonderful couple.
I've only known my parents after they were married.
I can't even imagine how my father caught my mother's fancy.
Before they got married, Rintaro-san was only a poor researcher.
Everyone was against it.
But Yoko continued working despite the opposition,
and they married with an income gap.
That's quite a passionate affair.
I never knew the story behind your marriage.
Turns out, mom loved you as much as you loved her.
Well, I guess that's a given, considering you got married.
Then of course you'd still be mourning.
Yoko-san's death isn't the only reason why I'm mourning.
When Yoko-san died,
a part of myself that she discovered died with her.
I liked the version of myself
that Yoko brought out of me.
The meaning of marriage, was it?
Truthfully, I still don't know.
Huh?
But I know I enjoyed meaningless conversations with Yoko.
That was enjoyable.
Dad?
Wait up!
I'm tossing everything, except what you want to keep.
Here, use this box.
Dad, don't push yourself.
Dad!
The material things can go.
I just promised Yoko-san we'd meet in another life.
Dad, here.
[Japanese-language Dictionary]
[Dear Rintaro]
[Divorce Form]
[Divorce Form - Sawada Yoko]
I'm sure this was only a practice run.
No, that's not it.
She was pulling a prank.
Mom was such a jokester-
I need time alone, please.
Sorry, Sir!
Look, I'm saying no one can read your tiny chicken-scratch.
Sir, is something the matter?
- Are you her manager?
- Yes, Sir.
We are really sorry.
Keep at it, okay? You'll be fine.
Could you finish this today?
- Of course. Leave it to me.
- Thanks.
Keep at it!
What's the matter?
You're almost done!
- Let's both keep at it-
- I can't.
Sawada-san, I'd rather not "keep at it" and become another you.
[Wis Kids - Have fun playing, enjoy English]
Thirsty, okay. What's this one?
Yeah, very good, kid. What's this?
- Hello! Higashimura here.
- Sleepy.
You're early today.
My afternoon plans were canceled.
Is that so?
Nijiro?
Nijiro!
Daddy is here.
[Sawada Kyoka: Are you free to meet now?]
Is it from work?
Would you like to extend his stay? I'll be here until closing.
Sorry, could you?
Nijiro, your dad says work calls.
Want to make a giant fort with me instead?
Yes!
All right, Boy.
Have you ever been to the amazon?
Kyoka-san?
Seita-san! I'm so sorry.
- You must've been busy.
- Actually, my day freed up.
Is everything all right?
Oh, this? I was at a memorial service earlier.
You said I could reach out whenever, so...
Oh, right...
Sorry, the funeral getup feels awkward in most places.
That's true...
Welcome.
I won't be ordering, thank you.
All right, shall we go?
Huh? G-Go where?
Let's go.
So... Where are we headed?
I thought it'd be nice to just hop on the first bus wherever.
I see...
Oh, that cloud looks like a turtle.
Huh?
Over there. Below the big cloud.
Turtle, right?
You've heard of sea turtles laying eggs on beaches, yes?
If the sand is above 29.5 degrees Celsius, the baby is a female.
Anything below becomes a male.
Really?
Does that mean global warming will turn all sea turtles female?
I suppose.
- That's depressing.
- Is it?
Of course.
I mean, females as far as the eye can see?
That'd ruin the balance of nature.
We're not on the same page, are we?
While I don't wish to get married,
I do prefer men.
Oh, I assumed...
You knew, right?
- Sorry.
- Don't apologize.
I've been thinking. No matter how long a marriage lasts,
love is never guaranteed to be eternal, is it?
Married couples need to work both ways.
One side's love may last,
but I guess it's difficult to remain mutual.
Well, I'm divorced, so...
- I'm sorry.
- No worries.
Still... the fun I had while married wasn't a lie.
So I look back on it as good times.
Good times, huh?
Let's bet.
If the next man who boards is wearing a pink shirt, I'll buy you a drink.
A pink shirt?
Sounds unlikely.
Unlikely indeed.
Sorry, we ended up in the middle of nowhere.
"The time you enjoy wasting is not wasted time."
Pardon?
It's exactly as I said. Enjoying something isn't a waste.
Profound.
I enjoyed our little bus ride.
I'm glad to hear it.
Woah.
What a beautiful view.
Agreed.
We were mourning my mother today. She died three years ago.
Your mother?
I'm sorry I rambled about nonsense on such an important day.
It wasn't nonsense to me.
Far from it.
You turned my day
into a good one.
When was the last time I even saw a nice sunset?
The free drink makes it all the better.
I'm in the same boat.
Usually, I'm too busy to watch sunsets.
I must've forced you to join me.
- I'm terribly sorry.
- Really, it's fine.
That's what friends do.
I feel like you draw out the kindness in me.
Nonviolence is key.
Did you turn into Gandhi?
One principal of yoga is "ahimsa," the idea of nonviolence.
Indeed, one must not direct violence
towards people.
However, everyone is quick to forget that we're "people" ourselves.
Ask your body and mind this.
Am I inflicting violence upon myself? Am I straining myself?
I want to learn to be kind.
Not only to others but to myself.
Yes.
Chest out, and let's breathe.
In through your nose...
and out from your mouth.
Once more.
Slowly in...
Good morning.
You heard me for once.
I'll make breakfast now.
Huh?
- You made breakfast?
- Yeah.
On that note,
I've decided to begin marriage hunting today.
Cool.
Wait, what?
My marriage counselor recommended me this matchup party.
[Wedding Party - People between their twenties and sixties are welcome. April 11, 10 a.m.]
Hold on, pause.
I know the divorce papers were a shock.
They surprised me too. But don't be hasty.
I'm not being hasty.
No need for a party.
Let nature do the matchmaking.
Do you sincerely believe that'll happen to me?
Well, I don't think so, but...
If I remarry, I'll be off your shoulders.
Not a bad deal, eh?
Wonderful, even.
If this is what makes you happy, good luck.
What? You're coming along.
Sorry? I'm not following.
I RSVP-ed for the both of us.
Huh? We're going as a family?
[To Rintaro-san]
I'm off.
- Ready?
- Y-Yeah.
Wait. Look!
Your pants aren't hemmed!
Well, I can barely open my eyes.
I've got it. Sit.
Ready? Up goes your leg.
Ouch!
Staples? Yoko-san would-
No comparing your new encounter with mom, okay?
Right this way.
May I have your name, Sir?
Sawada Rintaro
- and my daughter Kyoka.
- Yes.
First, keep this tag on you at all times.
Next, fill out this short bio. The men stay right here,
while women head inside.
Thank you.
Welcome!
Please sign in.
Here you are.
Why?
Didn't you want to avoid marriage?
Likewise, Seita-san.
My current place of employment branched out into marriage counseling.
What? Then...
O-One moment.
What is your number, Ma'am?
This sucks.
Right this way.
Kyoka-san, what brings you here?
I'm merely accompanying my father.
Then you're the family who RSVP-ed...
Higashimaru-san! Do you have a moment?
Coming!
It's time.
Men, please move to your right.
- You're a yoga instructor?
- Yes.
That's wonderful. You must be flexible then!
Can you draw with your toes-
I'm not affiliated with the circus.
Yoga's when you meet in the mornings,
and Kamehameha together, right?
(T/N: a special technique from Dragon Ball)
That's more a martial arts thing.
Let's just move on from yoga.
Something other than yoga?
I see your blood type is O. That's good.
You can donate blood to anyone.
It's time.
I feel like I'm eating conveyor belt sushi.
- Hello.
So if we were to get married,
I'd have to live with your daughter?
No, she will move out eventually.
Excuse my bluntness, but does she have a father complex?
Not at all. If anything, she's too strict.
It's time. Please once again move to your right.
Nice to meet you.
Tired as well?
Yes, I'm a first-timer-
Likewise.
The name's Sawada.
I'm Hinata.
[Occupation : Librarian]
You're a librarian?
Yes. I work at the National Diet Library.
I visit it often.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
I go there for research at least once a week.
I see.
Why do I have to see my father get romantic?
What was that?
Oh, nothing.
Really, what a coincidence.
I see you work from home?
Yes, although sometimes I'm at the Diet Library for research.
Kyoka!
This is my daughter.
Wow, she truly is a beauty.
Meet Komiyama-san, a respiratory surgeon,
and Ogawa-san, a tax counselor.
Sorry, I'm going home. Good luck, Dad.
What are you saying? Then my RSVP meant nothing.
If you want to remarry, match make on your own.
I want you to be happy!
And I'm saying you're being a busybody!
- Kyoka-san-
- If I'm not, then who'll take a curry-burning girl like you?
You even stapled up my pants!
Exactly! Marriage is impossible for a woman like me.
Right? You wouldn't marry anyone like me, would you?
If I had to choose...
- The staples are a bit much.
- Do not insult my daughter!
Sir, you said so yourself...
Sure, my daughter's a slob who loses her phone, eats breakfast in a bowl,
cuts corners, and is stubborn to boot.
But she's kind.
She's incredibly kind.
She returned home to keep me company-
Dad?
W-What's wrong?
- What seems to be hurting?
- My hip!
Please excuse me.
I'm actually an orthopedic surgeon.
Weren't you a librarian- Ouch!
- Here, Sir?
- Yes...
While I believe this is merely a strained back,
you should get scanned to be safe.
Yes, Ma'am...
Is there anywhere he can rest?
There's that sofa.
Great. We'll be moving you.
Hold on tight.
Ready, and...
Slowly now.
Kyoka-san, these are your father's belongings.
Thank you.
Where's his health insurance again...
Isn't this...
[To Rintaro-san]
A divorce form?
Oh, yes.
Huh?
"Thank goodness."
"If you're reading this letter, you've prepared to sort through my belongings, right?"
"Sorry I left so much as it is."
Mom...
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by
Sustainable Heartbeats Team @Viki.com
Rintaro-san, thank you for saying "yes" when I proposed.
Every day I spent with you, was brimming with happiness.
You were the one who helped me define "marriage".
So please...
do not feel obligated to stay my husband after death.
This time, I want you to propose. Find someone special, okay?
Don't worry about me. I'll enjoy myself in my own way.
The one I'm really worried about, is Kyoka.
Please support her a while longer
until she finds her happiness.
With love, Yoko.
Mom was the one who proposed...
She really was happy.
My hands falter, but I do my best
To capture you with it
Kyoka-chan?
Huh?
I knew it was you, Kyoka-chan!
I thought so but wasn't exactly sure.
Sorry, you are...
Right, hard to tell I guess.  Honestly, I'm surprised you're here.
Fuwa Sensei? He's my son's after-school teacher.
It's Hayate. Fuwa Hayate, remember?
Huh?
Oh! Hayate!
Long time no see! For... how many years?
Wow, you've grown. I totally couldn't tell.
I've missed you!