♪I woke up in a strange place♪
♪The sunlight here is blindingly bright♪
♪Pages rustle, and I hear a loud voice♪
♪I've become the center of the story♪
♪I must escape this dream♪
♪Yet why does my heart
surrender before you♪
♪Clearly, it's a fake plot♪
♪A fake world♪
♪Yet eventually,
my heart is open to you♪
=My Page in the 90s=
(Adapted from "Bye, Wild Weasel")
=Episode 5=
Chairman Gao?
Let's chat?
I heard Gao Haiming is collaborating
with Yunsheng,
and requested you
to handle the business.
That's correct.
You're the second person to approach me.
No surprise.
Miss Xie came to see me before you.
Alright.
Hand it over.
What?
The check.
Didn't you come here to give me a check
to make me leave your son?
How much do you want?
You business moguls
have such a limited approach
to problem-solving.
Is marrying off your own son
the only way you can solve this problem?
What does my son's marriage
have to do with you?
Just tell me directly.
How much money do you want?
500,000?
Five months.
I need five months.
Because the PR firm I work for
is currently partnering with Letao.
As the liaison,
I'll inevitably have work interactions
with your son during these months.
I'll be doing my job.
No need for concern.
Someone with his brilliant,
towering, perfect image
is beyond my reach.
But I need this job.
Please understand.
I need to make a living in this city.
After that whole speech,
you must want more than that, Miss Lin.
Since I invited you into my car,
it means this is a private conversation.
Just speak plainly.
Stop beating around the bush, okay?
No wonder your son
avoids talking with you.
You're way too paternalistic.
Paternalistic?
What paternalistic or maternalistic?
I am his father, okay?
True.
Forget I mentioned it.
(If I refuse the money,)
(he'll think I have bigger plans
for Gao Haiming,)
(making him more suspicious.)
(Not worth the risk.)
(I'd better)
(take some cash)
(and put the old man's mind at ease.)
How much do you want?
Does it really require
this much thought?
5,000.
5,000?
If you think that's too much,
we can negotiate.
Is that okay?
Well, this is unexpected.
My son is worth
just 5,000 to you?
You misunderstood.
He's not worth a penny to me.
Here's the thing.
Truth is,
even if you hadn't come today,
he probably wouldn't
give me a second look.
But since you're wealthy
and willing to share some generously,
I should know my place.
So whatever amount you offer...
This heavy?
Here's 50,000.
Enough to buy your "knowing your place"?
Is it enough?
Yes. More than enough!
No need to count it.
No need to check.
Every penny is there.
Now, get out.
Right away.
Thank you.
Just go.
Take care, Chairman Gao.
Leave the contract at Yunsheng.
So Lin Huan'er must
deliver it personally.
Then put on a show,
so everyone thinks you're dating.
When the chairman hears about it,
he'll at least realize you have
zero interest in Miss Xie.
Exactly as you planned.
Brilliant, sir.
You're sure Lin Huan'er got
into the chairman's car?
Absolutely. Saw it with my own eyes.
She was thrilled when she got off.
Clearly, she took quite a bit.
You said Lin Huan'er was special before.
I don't see how she's different
from those gold diggers.
But does she still hold
any value like this?
It's fine. We both get what we want.
Will you still go on the date
with Miss Xie?
Of course, I'm going. Why not?
Male Lead's fondness toward you
dropped again.
Currently at negative 50%.
(Dropped again?)
(Alright.)
(Let's see if you can
create more obstacles)
(or if I have more tricks.)
Hello.
Hello. May I ask...
Why are you here again?
I'm here to spend money, okay?
Okay.
Just don't cause a scene like last time.
I'd like someone to help
build the model.
It's fine. You take the order, Haiming.
I'm not picky.
Okay.
New Zealand King Salmon.
Iberian white ham.
Aged roast duck.
Two almond milk puddings.
And a bottle of La Tâche.
Thank you.
Okay. Just a moment.
I saw your father's marriage
announcement about the alliance.
He seems a bit too eager.
He is indeed a bit eager.
I hope you don't mind.
Of course not, Haiming.
Do you know?
Back in school,
you were always first place.
And I was always second.
That always made me so happy.
Why?
Because it made me feel like
you and I were together.
No one was between us.
We were one unit.
Miss Xie, you really have
interesting thoughts.
But work has been so busy.
I've forgotten many things from before.
That's true. Your father also told me
that you are excellent in every way.
It's just that your mind
is entirely on work.
Well, you can't focus
on two things at once.
How can you remember everything?
But it's okay.
Once the arranged marriage is announced,
we'll be one unit.
I'll help you remember things
from now on.
You're right.
A father knows his son best.
I truly am focused entirely on work.
I have no other thoughts for now.
That's good.
Miss Xie,
Mr. Gao asked me to drive you home.
Luo,
what exactly is the relationship
between that Lin Huan'er and Mr. Gao?
They have no relationship.
Are you unwilling to tell me?
They really have no relationship.
Really no relationship?
If they have no relationship,
how could she just whisk Mr. Gao away
from the banquet?
If they have no relationship,
how could Mr. Gao negotiate a deal
with Yunsheng for her?
Trying to hide it from me?
I wouldn't dare.
You know how it is.
Even if Mr. Gao has
some connection with her,
that's his private business.
If he doesn't say,
how could I dare to ask?
Stop giving me excuses.
You've been with him for so many years.
There's no way you know nothing.
I really don't know anything.
Do you know?
Then if I'll tell you,
you can't tell anyone I told you.
I knew it.
Luo.
From now on, whenever you have news,
tell me first, okay?
Don't worry.
About today's matter,
no one will ever know
it was you who told me.
No need to drive me. Thank you.
Mr. Gao,
I told her everything as you asked.
Yes.
But it doesn't seem like
she intends to give up.
Okay, got it.
A flying kick. Flying kick.
It's okay. Put in another coin.
I'm done playing.
Then let me just finish this.
Almost done.
Huan'er, do you remember
that back in school,
Hu Tiehan was really good at this.
Every time we died,
he was the only one still alive.
Why are you always talking about...
Hu Tiehan?
(Wait.)
(Did Hu Tiehan die in the line of duty
at the end of the novel?)
(But isn't he a traffic cop now?)
(What's wrong with my brain?)
(I can't remember anything.)
Why did you stop moving
at this crucial moment?
Mengmeng, do you know...
(I can't trigger a rule punishment)
(for two fictional characters, right?)
Know what?
Nothing.
(Only five chances.)
What is it?
(I'd better use sparingly.)
(Otherwise, I'm done for.)
Let's go. Didn't you say
you want to quit?
Why do you always
leave your sentences hanging?
Let's go home.
What do you want me to know?
Know what to have for dinner.
It happens to be...
(Yunsheng Tower)
(This model has numerous
and complex parts.)
(He assembled it so well.)
(It shows he's very patient)
(and willing to invest time
in his interests.)
(I didn't expect that.)
Mr. Gao?
Why do you have this fighter jet model?
That's strange.
Has this fighter jet model
gone out of production?
No. But you didn't assemble this.
Why wouldn't it be me?
Do you think I couldn't handle
such a precise model?
Then how were
the ink wash stains removed?
Some prefer using an eraser pen.
But I prefer applying nitro varnish
several times first.
This way is more foolproof.
Any problem?
That's odd.
Why would you think
I didn't assemble this?
Could someone really
give away such
a painstakingly assembled model?
Would they?
Miss Lin,
I came today to explain something.
By the way,
which of these three colors
do you find more appealing?
How about we have a talk?
This red one looks best.
I'll use it.
Destroying others' hard work like this
isn't appropriate, Miss Lin.
Others' hard work?
You care deeply about others' hard work?
Then tell me, does my proposal
count as my hard work?
That's precisely what I came to explain.
It's fine.
No need to explain to me.
I'm just thrilled to be recognized
by a boss like you.
Yes. This is exactly my proposal.
Look closely.
It's mine.
The time?
11:07.
If I recall correctly,
you arrived at Letao
in the afternoon, right?
You're not implying...
It may be hard to believe,
but I completed it before you arrived.
Both the concept and the approach
were identical to yours.
I apologize for not explaining earlier.
But since we'll be collaborating,
the misunderstanding shouldn't go on.
So I want to explain to you.
So that's how it is?
So, Miss Lin,
can we find a place to talk properly?
Are you asking me out for business
or a personal date?
A personal date.
Alright.
(The first step to getting closer.)
(Find common interests.)
(Reduce psychological distance.)
What can I get for you, sir?
Miss?
(I remember in the book,)
(Gao Haiming likes a food
with a very peculiar name.)
(I think it's called Angel Hair.)
Miss Lin, what would you like to eat?
Angel Hair.
Will you have the same as Mr. Gao?
Yes.
The same, thank you.
Miss Lin, how did you know
I'd order Angel Hair?
I can read minds. Do you believe it?
You don't believe it?
Then why not let me try?
You attract many admirers,
and are loyal to those you care about.
But...
What?
But you face some obstacles
in your career.
Full of ambition
but with nowhere to apply it.
Am I right?
Miss Lin, you studied psychology?
Then perhaps I should analyze you too?
Alright.
When you were analyzing me,
your eyes unconsciously looked
to the upper left.
Your eyebrows lifted slightly.
That didn't seem like
on-the-spot analysis.
It looked more like
you were searching your memory.
Seems you came prepared.
You own broad interests.
But you only
scratch the surface of each.
Mr. Gao, you studied psychology too?
Just the basics.
Angel Hair is actually very thin pasta.
I just like its name.
But in terms of taste, it can't beat
the classic versions.
Falling for a dish
just because of its name.
Seems Mr. Gao is a romantic like me.
I wonder if assembling models
for others is also romantic?
So you admit that model
was assembled by me?
I'm just curious how you recognized it.
A tailor never fails
to recognize their own handiwork.
Even the tiniest flaw
is known only to them.
Why picked me
to assemble that fighter jet?
Shouldn't you tell me
why you assembled jets for others?
Since you can read minds,
just take a guess.
(Oh, no. What exactly did the book say?)
(How would I know?)
Your mind-reading failed?
It doesn't matter.
None of those matters.
What matters is
the moment I received that jet,
seeing such an exquisite model
made all the day's unhappiness vanish.
It healed me.
Though I didn't uncover
why you assembled jets for others,
I believe
at least others' happiness
makes your effort worthwhile.
What more did you ask for?
You always seem so happy.
As a business elite,
shouldn't you have more freedom?
How could anyone have real freedom?
But you have more freedom
than us, right?
A fighter jet can fly far,
but I can't.
The bigger the empire,
the more constraints.
You know nothing.
Haven't you stared enough
during the meal?
I'm thinking.
The model jet you gave me
is absolutely perfect and beautiful.
I just don't know who to give it to.
That requires careful thought.
Sorry for taking up
your model-building time tonight.
One day's delay is nothing. It's fine.
But you seem very passionate
about PR work.
Trying so hard to understand me
just for a job?
Now that the contract's secured,
shouldn't you relax a bit?
Relax?
Mr. Gao, do you actually mean "give up"?
We've only shared one meal,
and you want me to give up?
So you don't plan to give up.
Do you think I should give up?
I'll tell you next time we meet.
Okay.
How could I be so careless?
Careless?
Since you lives with Miss Zhu,
you could get in even
without a key, right?
Yes.
Since you knew that,
why return it to me?
You started the verse.
I couldn't let the stage
go cold, could I?
Harsh.
You too.
Sir, another bowl of wontons, please.
- Thanks.
- Your wontons.
What? Can't handle hot wontons
with a Western palate?
You seem to have quite the appetite.
You treated me to Angel Hair.
I treat you to wontons.
It's like for like.
Careful, it's hot.
Is it good?
(Wouldn't the fondness shoot
straight up to 50%?)
It's just a set of keys.
You could return them any time.
Yet you chose to come back
specifically at night.
Didn't you just ask me a question?
Didn't you say you'd tell me next time?
Isn't this "next time"?
My answer is...
Don't.
Don't what?
Don't give up.
(Why isn't the fondness changing?)
Mr. Gao.
What's wrong?
You've never had this expression
coming home before.
What expression?
Like you know you're going to win...
Victory is assured...
No, dead set on winning...
What do you want to say?
Don't get mad if I say this.
Spit it out.
Trying way too hard.
Luo, why are you still in the company?
Mr. Gao, I'm leaving right now.
Good night.
Decided to show your face, huh?
Mr. Chairman.
About the innovation
and R&D idea of yours,
Uncle Li already told me.
I waited up to hear your explanation.
What exactly are you thinking?
Mr. Chairman, you know it better.
Letao's current strategy
is far too conservative.
Bringing in foreign capital
is selling out for peace.
We'll never get the terms we want.
I simply can't understand.
There's a clear shortcut
right in front of us,
yet you insist on taking
the long, muddy detour.
Why?
I don't consider marrying
into Fuchuang a shortcut.
Gao Haiming,
what right do you have
to look down on Fuchuang?
Fuchuang is the biggest
domestic distributor now.
It's a blessing
that Wanjun looks your way, you know?
Why else would Fuchuang choose
to partner with us?
Mr. Chairman,
Letao's crisis is born of this era.
Our only way out is independent R&D.
Don't give me that "era" nonsense!
I'm telling you. There's only one way
for you to save yourself.
Dump that unsavory woman immediately,
and marry Wanjun.
We'll discuss everything else later.
Mom.
Stay with me for a while.
Okay.
In my heart,
I've always felt I failed you.
When you were little,
your father and I both fell short.
You've suffered enough.
Now you're grown,
and when it comes to marriage,
I don't want you to compromise
or make sacrifices.
Marriage
is far too important
in a person's life.
Don't you end up like me.
Alright, Mom. I know.
Remember this.
Whatever you decide,
whatever you want to do,
I'll support you.
Truly.
I just want you to be happy.
Just be happy.
That's what matters most.
Luo, follow up on this tomorrow.
Please book a window seat for me
for the Sky Garden
afternoon tea tomorrow.
Archery.
Can I try this?
Sure.
For the two of you?
Yes, two of us.
Thank you.
- Let me see.
- Give it a try.
Like this.
Yes, wedge it in.
Wedge it in.
Arch your thumb.
Thumb.
I can't.
It's too heavy.
Maybe forget it.
No way.
Dare to make a bet?
Let's see who's the better shot.
Truth or Dare.
The loser answers one question
from the winner,
or does one thing the winner asks.
Alright.
You go first.
I'll go first.
Just a hair away from the bullseye.
Your turn.
You got skills and didn't say so.
Hold it. Right.
Then arch with your thumb.
Arch your thumb.
♪I woke up in a strange place♪
♪The sunlight here is blindingly bright♪
Arch it.
Loose.
Who gets credit for that?
You win.
♪I must escape this dream♪
♪Yet why does my heart
surrender before you♪
Right here.
We're eating right here?
Yeah.
You've never eaten
like this here before, right?
Hold on.
Sit.
Here you go.
Thanks.
How is it?
The coffee tastes quite unique.
Unique is exactly right.
I specially brewed this for you.
This coffee's name is
"Coffee on the Left Bank by the Seine,"
"a cup in my hand, savoring..."
The name's that long?
You know nothing.
So have you decided?
Who should I give
my fighter jet model to?
I thought about it.
One shouldn't interfere in others' love.
So you should make the choice yourself.
But how can you count as others?
You're practically an involved party.
♪Timelines, tangled♪
You know about this substance
called a catalyst?
It doesn't undergo
chemical reactions itself.
But it helps other substances react.
Helping others assemble a fighter jet
is a catalyst too.
But it doesn't interfere
in others' love.
First time I heard someone
describe matchmaking so romantically.
So, Mr. Gao, you only want
to be the catalyst in my love life
and don't want to be part of it?
♪Love's time machine,
flies, flies, flies♪
Hair's messy.
♪Entwined worries linger♪
♪My heart is not empty,
yet pain remains♪
♪Now I see what passed between us♪
♪Walking through the crowd to meet you♪
♪Going through surging tides of people♪
♪Until the world's end♪
♪If I could♪
♪Keep loving you♪
♪Hearing two hearts♪
♪Beating together♪
♪If I could♪
♪Stay resting in your arms♪
♪I'd trade the rest of my life for it♪
♪Entwined worries linger♪
♪My heart is not empty,
yet pain remains♪
♪Now I see what passed between us♪
♪Walking through the crowd to meet you♪
♪Going through surging tides of people♪
♪Until the world's end♪
♪If I could♪
♪Keep loving you♪
♪Hearing two hearts♪
♪Beating together♪
♪If I could♪
♪Stay resting in your arms♪
♪I'd trade the rest of my life for it♪