笙ｪI woke up in a strange place笙ｪ
笙ｪThe sunlight here is blindingly bright笙ｪ
笙ｪPages rustle, and I hear a loud voice笙ｪ
笙ｪI've become the center of the story笙ｪ
笙ｪI must escape this dream笙ｪ
笙ｪYet why does my heart
surrender before you笙ｪ
笙ｪClearly, it's a fake plot笙ｪ
笙ｪA fake world笙ｪ
笙ｪYet eventually,
my heart is open to you笙ｪ
=My Page in the 90s=
(Adapted from "Bye, Wild Weasel")
=Episode 15=
笙ｪOld photos, yellowed笙ｪ
笙ｪTimelines, tangled笙ｪ
笙ｪI boarded a rickety time machine笙ｪ
笙ｪHeart pounding, won't stop笙ｪ
笙ｪOld times, pass slowly笙ｪ
笙ｪIn memories, the breeze is soft笙ｪ
笙ｪYour smile is like stars that shimmer笙ｪ
笙ｪLighting up my lonely corner笙ｪ
Any fish?
No.
I was just
resting my eyes.
I wasn't asleep.
I know.
Did I snore?
How could you snore
while resting your eyes?
You're right.
Not a single fish bit?
It moved a few times.
If it moved,
it means a fish was biting.
When a fish bites, you need to reel in.
Just reel it in.
But you were asleep.
No, if this keeps up,
when will we ever catch a fish?
I'm wondering
if our spot isn't good.
We should go deeper.
There's no deeper place to stand.
When will we catch something?
Are there no big fish here?
- It's fine.
- No, we can't just sit around and wait.
Gao Haiming, look.
You...
I asked the resort owner
for a net.
I don't believe this.
Be careful.
You...
I...
Be careful.
Trying to escape?
Got it.
Lucky I caught you.
Thanks!
- Come on.
- Come on. Easy.
The oldest method remains the best.
So?
Realized the lake
isn't so scary after all?
Wasting time can be nice,
but when it counts,
my urgency gets things done.
See? Now we've got dinner covered.
How would you like it?
Let's ask
the resort chef to cook it.
Maybe we could cook it ourselves.
Here.
I didn't expect you to know how to cook.
There's more I can do.
Like what?
Like...
You'll find out later.
I saw you add the vegetables last
when making the fish soup.
That shows you cook often.
Very experienced.
But I am curious,
why would a rich guy like you
need to cook for yourself every day?
My parents were busy when I was young,
so I had to learn to cook.
Here, try some.
Is it good?
It's tasty.
What's wrong?
A man who can cook
is so handsome.
Have more. There's plenty.
Okay.
(Unread Message)
(Mr. Gao, everything's ready.)
(Items arrive around 6:30 PM.)
(Keep your phone nearby.)
Something urgent?
No, just Luo.
By the way,
when can we see the photos we took?
After we get back,
we can load them on the computer.
That's really convenient, huh?
Of course.
Now that we have computers.
Right?
So advanced.
What is it?
A mosquito bite?
Got me before I realized it.
Here, I know a trick.
When I got bitten as a kid,
my grandma
used this method.
The pressing stops itching.
Really?
Well? Still itchy?
Yes.
I-I'll try again.
A cross won't do, right?
Maybe an asterisk.
You need to press harder.
Still itchy?
笙ｪI woke up in a strange place笙ｪ
笙ｪThe sunlight here is blindingly bright笙ｪ
I'm fine. Thanks.
That method works well.
I'll scratch it myself.
笙ｪI've become the center of the story笙ｪ
How about we go back
and transfer the photos?
Sure.
It'll take 30 minutes?
That long?
(Copying 56 items from camera
to computer. 24% complete)
That's very quick.
Be patient.
You'll soon be obsolete.
Of course.
You all will be obsolete too.
Maybe.
Who can say where future tech
will lead?
What do you think
the future will be like?
I've heard some companies today
are already researching
more portable digital devices.
Some even suggest
that future phones might combine
communication, photography,
and even more features.
This talk of yours
would sound visionary
if heard in 1999.
But if people
in 2025 heard it,
they'd laugh at you.
I just browsed online casually.
But you speak as if
you know 2025 very well.
I'm just guessing.
Technology advances so fast now.
What you described
will likely happen sooner.
True.
(New Message)
(Mr. Gao, I left air cans at your door.)
(Take them in.)
Work this late?
No. How could that be?
I need to take this call.
Hello?
Your super deluxe package
is at the door.
Can you come sign for it?
Okay.
I'm coming now.
Well, Luo said
he's delivering documents.
I'll go get them.
Watch this.
Keep it connected.
Okay, go ahead.
(54% complete)
This is so slow.
(67% complete)
Luo Zhou,
I can't believe you.
So that's it.
You could've just asked
for a photo together.
(Fondness: 69.9%)
(Why stuck at 69.9%)
(for so long?)
(If fondness reaches 100%,)
(will I return then?)
(Then I'd never see him again?)
Luo Zhou,
you're good at turning everything
into chaos.
Stop. Give back my air cans.
Hello?
Mr. Gao,
the reservation is for 7:30 PM.
Only three minutes are left.
Hurry over.
Or you'll miss it.
Our booked slot
expires soon.
Anything else?
Boss, you got this.
I'm on standby.
I'm your strongest backup.
We'll talk properly when I'm back.
Wait. Hello?
Hello? Where are you?
I'm by the river.
Come out. You'll see me.
笙ｪOld photos, yellowed笙ｪ
笙ｪTimelines, tangled笙ｪ
笙ｪI boarded a rickety time machine笙ｪ
笙ｪHeart pounding, won't stop笙ｪ
笙ｪOld times, pass slowly笙ｪ
笙ｪIn memories, the breeze is soft笙ｪ
(Is he finally confessing?)
(Why now?)
(Why no system alert?)
Huan'er.
I...
Well, I...
It...
You must've checked
the weather forecast,
knowing
there's a Leo meteor shower tonight.
You turned off the lights
to watch the meteor shower with me.
How romantic.
Yes, because it's easier to see them
when the lights are out.
Right.
Such beautiful fireworks.
Huan'er.
Darling, will you marry me?
- Marry him!
- I do.
I'm sorry, Huan'er.
I wanted to surprise you.
But I ruined everything.
I...
Actually,
perfection is life's biggest taboo.
We can't always chase perfection.
Look at the moon.
Once it becomes full,
it immediately starts waning.
So,
don't always expect
a perfect moment.
I believe
timing trumps ceremony.
Cherish the present.
Actually, every moment
is the best moment.
Don't you agree, Gao Haiming?
Huan'er.
Actually, I...
Answer it. What if it's important?
Hello?
Boss, did it work?
Luo Zhou,
why are you still at the office?
It's better to be important.
Boss, this time,
I do have something important.
Mr. Zhang from Huasheng Supermarket
wants to meet you tomorrow morning.
He's flying to Paris at noon,
so you might need
to come back tonight.
Got it.
Well, about Xinye yesterday,
things are progressing smoothly.
Really?
Good.
You have mints?
Want one?
Sure.
Another one.
Never mind.
Y-You don't eat that.
Then let's listen to music.
Okay.
(I really want to confess to her.)
(But every time I get ready,)
(something comes up.)
(I don't want this either.)
(Sir,)
(you can't even confess.)
(How will you marry her later?)
(I don't want this.)
(I prepared for days.)
(But at the last minute...)
(Here's a song to you.)
(Love Really Needs Courage.)
Well...
I'm so sleepy.
I'll take a quick nap.
I'm good from here.
You can come in late tomorrow.
Get some rest.
You rest early too.
笙ｪEntwined worries linger笙ｪ
笙ｪMy heart is not empty,
yet pain remains笙ｪ
笙ｪNow I see what passed between us笙ｪ
笙ｪWalking through the crowd to meet you笙ｪ
笙ｪGoing through surging tides of people笙ｪ
This is the air of destiny.
There are 33 cans in total.
This is for you.
What is it?
Don't open it yet.
Open it at the right moment.
笙ｪIf I could笙ｪ
(Fate will bring romance and you)
(to me together.)
笙ｪI'd trade the rest of my life for it笙ｪ
(Heart rate: 69.9%)
70%.
(Heart rate: 70%)
(Heart rate: 70.1%)
70.1%.
(Heart rate: 70.2%)
70.2%.
(Heart rate: 70.3%)
70.3%.
(Heart rate)
(Heart rate: 70.8%)
What's happening?
(Fondness: 70.9%)
No way.
(Heart rate)
70.9%.
(This is the air of destiny.)
(Made by the fresh air of Lake Como.)
(It represents the wish of sharing
the same breath of air with each other)
(at every single moment.)
Actually...
Actually, I prepared a lot for today.
72%.
But man proposes, God disposes.
All those air cans
were taken by the cleaning lady.
The LED strip I prepared went off.
It seems everything reminds me
today isn't the right day to say this.
I almost wonder...
I almost wonder
if saying that would bring
the whole building down,
and the moon with it.
But...
But what if?
What if the building stands
and the moon stays put?
Huan'er,
I like you.
笙ｪI woke up in a strange place笙ｪ
笙ｪThe sunlight here is blindingly bright笙ｪ
笙ｪPages rustle, and I hear a loud voice笙ｪ
笙ｪI've become the center of the story笙ｪ
笙ｪI must escape this dream笙ｪ
笙ｪYet why does my heart
surrender before you笙ｪ
笙ｪClearly, it's a fake plot笙ｪ
笙ｪA fake world笙ｪ
笙ｪYet eventually,
my heart is open to you笙ｪ
Huan'er, I...
- I'm sorry.
- I...
No.
(The fondness is rising too quickly.)
(If this continues,)
(the time I can stay here
will get shorter,)
(and I'll never see him again.)
(The air of destiny)
What's wrong?
You returned from the business trip
looking soulless.
It's nothing. I'm sick.
I'm quite sick.
This time, it might be incurable.
You don't have a fever.
You know nothing.
I just mean... I'm really sick.
Are you overtired from work?
Talk to Gao Haiming...
Don't mention that name.
What are you doing?
I'm looking
at this comic I drew before.
The one where you're the inspiration
for the female lead
inhabited by another soul.
I even took your advice.
Made her a time traveler
from the future.
So where is the plot now?
She and her true love
are head over heels for each other.
She's about to confess
everything to him.
That fast?
So they've decided to be together?
Even though
they didn't quite see eye-to-eye before,
and they lacked mutual understanding
on many things,
as they got to know
and trust each other,
they gradually discovered
many precious qualities in the other.
That sparked the most genuine love
between them.
Isn't that romantic?
Then what about the ending?
The ending is definitely
that the female lead stays in this world
and stays forever with the male lead.
What?
So she will just abandon
her family and friends
and her career in her own world?
For a romance
and a man,
she decides to stay here forever?
Is she crazy?
Huan'er, it's just a story I made up.
Oh, right.
Maybe I got too into it.
Let's skip that.
By the way,
that music producer wanted you
to enter that competition, right?
Have you decided?
I don't have much confidence
in that competition.
Mengmeng, you can do it.
Trust me.
I trust you.
But you can't predict the future.
Forgotten?
My predictions are spot on.
Listen.
Whatever the outcome
of the competition for you,
you will achieve your dream
because of the competition.
Then predict for Hu Tiehan and me.
Mengmeng, I really don't get it.
What's so great about Hu Tiehan?
Why are you so hung up on him?
Is he really the one?
I don't know
what's so great about him either.
He's just a silly goose,
a blockhead.
Every time I drop hints,
he seems completely oblivious.
But, Huan'er,
do you understand that feeling?
When he approaches me,
my heart just blooms,
with butterflies taking flight.
Do you get it?
Are you silly?
You've led the way for so long
and taken so many steps toward him.
He's only taken the tiniest step
toward you.
And you think it's all been worth it?
I've liked him for eight years.
If he didn't feel anything
for me at all,
there's no way
I could've lasted this long.
Huan'er,
I can truly feel
his sincerity and hesitation.
But you can't be together.
Why can't we be together?
Because...
(I have two chances left
to share spoilers.)
(But I have to tell her.)
Listen to me.
You will get together.
You'll love each other deeply.
You'll share a time of great happiness
and wonderful joy.
But in the end,
he'll die in the line of duty.
If that's the case,
do you still choose to be with him?
笙ｪEntwined worries linger笙ｪ
If that's truly the case,
then having been happy together
is enough for me.
Warning! Warning!
You can't reveal spoilers
to any characters.
The system punishment
has been triggered,
resulting in time rewinding.
Reminder again.
Don't reveal spoilers
more than five times.
Remaining chances: one.
笙ｪIf I could笙ｪ
I can truly feel
his sincerity and hesitation.
笙ｪHearing two hearts笙ｪ
笙ｪBeating together笙ｪ
Mengmeng,
you will be incredibly happy.
You have my word.
(Letao Tower)
Regarding the issues
everyone just raised,
I'll compile them for Dr. Wei.
Over the next month,
we'll streamline
and upgrade the product.
We aim to launch the new product
early next year.
Okay.
Everyone.
The R&D department's
new project's plan and implementation
require your full cooperation.
All priorities align with R&D's plan.
Anything wrong?
Then execute. Dismissed.
(Huge Sale! Clearance Prices!)
Its texture is completely skin-friendly.
(Sale)
And we've conducted numerous tests.
It will definitely not harm your skin.
All individually wrapped.
Very convenient.
(Tender Care, Angel for Women)
Look.
Then give me a day-use
and a night-use pack.
Day and night.
Okay, no problem.
Can I get a black plastic bag?
Sure.
(Sale! Tender Care, Angel for Women)
Actually, menstruation
is a perfectly
normal biological process.
It shows our bodies are healthy.
There's nothing to be ashamed of.
Right?
Here, two extra.
Thank you.
Check out over there.
Okay, thanks.
Hello, Mr. Gao.
Hello.
Are you here to inspect the work?
No.
Just off work and free.
Thought I'd drop by.
No worries. Sales are good today.
Rest assured.
Okay.
Let's grab dinner together after work.
No.
It's just that I have a lot to do today.
I need to clear some inventory later
and then compile some reports.
It's fine. I can wait.
No, don't.
If you're swamped,
I can have Marketing...
No need, really.
Don't get anyone else.
I can do it.
I don't trust others to.
Some things
j-just have to be done by me.
If there's nothing else...
I am quite busy here.
Okay, I'll let you get back to work.
(Sale! Tender Care, Angel for Women)
Bye, Mr. Gao.
(I just don't want it
to happen so fast.)
(Why can't you get it?)
笙ｪEntwined worries linger笙ｪ
笙ｪMy heart is not empty,
yet pain remains笙ｪ
笙ｪNow I see what passed between us笙ｪ
笙ｪWalking through the crowd to meet you笙ｪ
笙ｪGoing through surging tides of people笙ｪ
笙ｪUntil the world's end笙ｪ
笙ｪIf I could笙ｪ
笙ｪKeep loving you笙ｪ
笙ｪHearing two hearts笙ｪ
笙ｪBeating together笙ｪ
笙ｪIf I could笙ｪ
笙ｪStay resting in your arms笙ｪ
笙ｪI'd trade the rest of my life for it笙ｪ
笙ｪEntwined worries linger笙ｪ
笙ｪMy heart is not empty,
yet pain remains笙ｪ
笙ｪNow I see what passed between us笙ｪ
笙ｪWalking through the crowd to meet you笙ｪ
笙ｪGoing through surging tides of people笙ｪ
笙ｪUntil the world's end笙ｪ
笙ｪIf I could笙ｪ
笙ｪKeep loving you笙ｪ
笙ｪHearing two hearts笙ｪ
笙ｪBeating together笙ｪ
笙ｪIf I could笙ｪ
笙ｪStay resting in your arms笙ｪ
笙ｪI'd trade the rest of my life for it笙ｪ