♪I woke up in a strange place♪
♪The sunlight here is blindingly bright♪
♪Pages rustle, and I hear a loud voice♪
♪I've become the center of the story♪
♪I must escape this dream♪
♪Yet why does my heart
surrender before you♪
♪Clearly, it's a fake plot♪
♪A fake world♪
♪Yet eventually,
my heart is open to you♪
=My Page in the 90s=
(Adapted from "Bye, Wild Weasel")
=Episode 14=
Then my wish is
for smooth sailing
and a swift finish.
Finish what?
To finish destiny's arrangement,
of course.
I'll drink.
It's my turn.
Spade, Mr. Gao.
I... I'd better drink first.
I have no wishes.
- No.
You must say one.
Not following the rules?
I just said mine.
Exactly.
Don't you want to find a girlfriend?
What if I already have one?
Who?
You can only ask one question.
I... I'll draw.
Yours.
I...
I hope that in the future, I will
be braver at work.
And in love too.
Wait a minute.
Tiehan, you need to be more specific.
How to be braver?
For example,
how to be braver with Mengmeng?
Right? Pursue Mengmeng bravely?
Stop.
Tiehan, just be brave and be yourself.
Do whatever you want.
Mengmeng, your turn.
Actually,
I think I'm already doing great.
I have my job
and people I love.
And most importantly, I have you all.
Do you know that on this planet,
the probability of two people meeting
is only 0.00478?
Such a tiny chance.
But we gathered together.
What fate is this?
What fate?
It... it really is fate.
Let's drink.
- Come on.
You haven't drunk this.
I'll drink two.
Mix this in. Mix it.
Mengmeng, want to sing something?
Yeah, Mengmeng.
I won't sing. Why should I sing?
You sing so beautifully.
I remember your high school dream
was to debut as a singer.
You even won a singing contest.
Sing one.
- No.
- Sing one.
- Come on.
- I won't sing.
- Sing one.
I won't sing.
Excuse me.
Sorry to bother you.
Could my friend sing a song?
Of course. Welcome.
Thank you.
Hurry.
This song, Liked You for So Long,
is for everyone.
♪Why won't you look at me♪
♪Why won't you say a word♪
♪Why can't you see what's on my mind♪
♪I don't wanna hide in the corner♪
♪Or do a monologue♪
♪I don't wanna watch you from afar♪
♪Like a fool♪
♪I wanna be by your side♪
♪To lean on your shoulder♪
♪To hold the summer breeze♪
♪And take it all in♪
♪The sunset is so tender♪
♪Melting every afternoon I miss you♪
♪I wanna take a walk with you♪
♪I wanna hold your hand♪
♪Waiting until one night♪
Your girlfriend?
No, a friend.
Your friend
has real potential to be a singer.
Here.
(Chen Yujie, music producer)
This is my card.
Pass it to her.
Okay.
I'll wait for her call.
Who was that just now?
He said he's a music producer
and told me to give this to Mengmeng.
Not a scam, is it?
(It's her career's turning point.)
No, absolutely not a scam.
You must give her this card.
Don't worry.
Okay.
♪I wanna be by your side♪
♪To lean on your shoulder♪
♪To hold the summer breeze♪
♪And take it all in♪
♪The sunset is so tender♪
♪Melting every afternoon I miss you♪
♪I wanna take a walk with you♪
♪I wanna hold your hand♪
♪Waiting until one night♪
♪Beneath a sky of stars♪
♪I'll tell you loud and clear♪
♪I've liked you for so long♪
♪I wanna take a walk with you♪
Tiehan.
Mr. Gao works tomorrow
and must rise early. I'll take him home.
Tell Mengmeng for me.
Okay.
Mr. Gao, let me take you home.
It's too late.
Thank you all.
Not bad at all.
Why did they leave?
They said Mr. Gao
has something tomorrow.
So they left.
Let's go too, Silly Goose.
Hold on.
Mengmeng, this is for you.
He said he's a music producer.
Could it be a scam?
Why are you laughing?
Because your reaction
was exactly like mine.
But Huan'er just said
it's not a scam.
Relax.
Well, since she said so,
it's definitely fine.
Come with me to school again tomorrow.
What for?
Just say yes or no.
Yes.
Let's go. Take me home.
Thanks for today.
Before, because it involved
personal feelings,
it wasn't convenient to explain.
Hope you don't mind.
I had my own motives too.
What?
I helped resolve your concerns.
Now I can go all out to do some things.
I meant work.
65.3 percent, 66 percent...
Why are you smiling?
Nothing.
I just learned a little secret.
What secret?
Secret.
Not sure if it's because
I've been back more often lately,
but I keep remembering things
from the past.
Like what?
Too many.
Too many memories.
Tiehan,
do you remember back in college,
when I came to you?
I remember.
Do you know why I came to you then?
I'm sorry, Mengmeng.
- I...
- Why are you apologizing?
I should apologize.
I only found out later
that something happened
to your dad that day.
I was too immature back then.
Because of that,
I had been mad at you for months,
ignoring you.
But at that time,
you needed company most.
Well...
It was not your fault.
It's okay.
Do you know back then I wanted...
At that time,
we were both too young.
Take Huan'er and Xiaojue's situation.
We used to envy them so much.
Being able to accompany
and support each other,
they were so happy.
But after all these years,
everything has changed.
I haven't changed.
Why aren't you worried at all?
Are you worried?
No, I am just wondering
why you parked so far away.
Just to take a walk.
Sometimes walking
lets your mind go blank
and gives you some breathing room.
I used to like walking as well.
Too bad that I got busy later
and didn't have time.
Then let's walk together from now on.
Sure.
Is this a chair?
It's a seesaw.
A seesaw?
Take that side.
Sit over there.
No way. You're secretly pushing.
No way.
We...
We weigh the same?
Why am I so heavy?
You're not sitting at the end?
Go down. I want to go up.
Sorry, I didn't mean to.
It's... it's fine.
You can go up now.
Didn't you tell me to go down?
Yes, but I want to go down now.
G-Go ahead.
Okay.
I'm fine.
My arm strength is pretty good.
Wait...
See? I've come up.
You can stand up.
Why not say it earlier?
I thought you knew.
What the heck?
It's not fun at all.
Well...
I... I have an appointment
with a distributor in Lvcheng.
I'll go tomorrow.
Will you join me?
I will.
Just the two of us?
Yes, just the two of us.
Well,
why isn't Luo going?
You've always managed Dr. Wei's matters.
You know better than Luo.
That's true.
Indeed, I know a bit more.
If it's for work,
then I agree.
Okay.
I'll go home for dinner.
See you.
Where are you going?
Going home.
Are you going to my place?
Sure.
Come on.
Huan'er.
My colleague.
Hello, I'm Gao Haiming,
Lin Huan'er's colleague.
Not bad. I'm quite pleased.
Come out!
Hello.
Hello, sir.
Then let's start eating.
Wait a moment.
Huan'er, get up.
Move aside.
Sit.
Gao, come on.
Eat the fish.
Thank you, sir.
The one from earlier.
Okay.
And there are ribs.
Sweet and Sour Ribs.
Huan'er and Le'er
love this dish the most.
Eat more while it's hot.
It's enough.
Eat more.
Gao,
I heard you also work at Letao, right?
Yes.
What position?
- Department Manager.
- Department Supervisor.
- Supervisor.
- Manager.
I... I was a supervisor before.
He'll soon be a manager.
Yes.
Good.
The name Gao Haiming
sounds so familiar.
- In a magazine...
- You haven't seen it.
Okay.
Being the manager is good.
A bright future ahead.
Come on.
Eat more ribs.
It's enough.
Being the manager is quite a dedication.
Eat more ribs.
Enough. Don't serve him more.
I haven't eaten any yet.
What's the rush?
I can make it for you every day.
Gao rarely comes, right?
Eat more.
Okay.
Right!
The rice. I forgot to serve the rice.
Well...
It's okay. No rush, sir.
I haven't eaten any yet.
Lin Le'er, I'll hit you.
Take a piece.
Try this. This is delicious.
Say it.
Dad, how about we...
Play mahjong?
Sure. It's been a while since I played.
Mahjong?
I don't know how.
Eight of Dots.
Wait.
Kong.
Kong?
East Wind.
East Wind? Kong.
You kong too?
What are you doing? Let me take my turn.
Red Dragon.
I haven't drawn a tile.
Hurry up.
One of Dots.
- Two of Characters.
- Two of Characters?
Two of Characters? I win!
You win?
I win too.
You too?
Come on.
Food rewards.
And gold coins.
So much. How big was that win?
Let's keep going.
Were you offering them tiles
on purpose today
just to make them happy?
We play for fun, right?
Winning isn't everything.
I never expected
you'd actually know how to play mahjong.
My grandma taught me when I was little.
I haven't touched it since.
Well?
How's our cooking?
Not as good as yours, huh?
Want the truth?
Go ahead.
I think your family's is better.
One particular dish
must've won you over.
Sweet and Sour Ribs? The fish?
Neither.
It's because you have an amazing family.
For me,
having the whole family sitting together
to enjoy a meal happily
is the greatest happiness.
Actually, when I first arrived,
I didn't get along with them well.
But now I agree with you.
They are indeed
wonderful family members.
What do you mean by that?
First...
I first arrived in this world.
Childhood is when we all
arrive in this world.
Right?
Teach me mahjong when you're free.
Then I can join Mengmeng
and Tiehan to win your money.
Okay.
Then
I'll deduct teaching fees
from your salary.
M-My salary won't cover that, will it?
Thanks for today.
I had a great time.
Me too.
Get some rest now.
By the way,
you said Le'er was transferring schools.
Let me know if you need help.
This won't come out of my salary, right?
Good night.
Congratulations.
Male lead's fondness
toward you has increased to 68 percent.
68 percent?
I can go back soon then.
Nothing wrong with going back soon.
Right?
Keep pushing.
Lvcheng.
I'll need a solid plan.
Flower shop has to be 2 PM to 3 PM.
Peacock Lake...
Peacock Lake closes at 4:30 PM.
Huan'er, you have a job now.
Why do you still do homework?
You know nothing.
I'm planning the trip.
Planning? To take down which one?
To take down Haiming?
Lin Le'er, what's going on
in your head?
I suspect you're crushing on someone.
Don't worry.
With you as my cautionary tale,
I'll never make your mistakes.
I made a good cautionary tale.
Huan'er, listen.
Your taste in men was really bad before.
Ou Xiaojue came to see me
just a couple of days ago.
He did? What did he want?
He asked me
to set up a meeting with you.
He asked me to meet him
at a park south of the city.
He seemed a bit off.
So I ran away quickly.
You did the right thing.
With someone like him,
you have to stay vigilant.
If he goes to you again,
come find me immediately.
Understand?
Okay?
Okay.
Huan'er,
to be honest,
I think Haiming is really
a very, very good person.
You have to hold on to him tight.
The way you talk sounds a bit like Dad.
I mean it. If you're with him,
you'll definitely be happy.
Le'er,
I'll give your suggestion
serious thought.
You must think about it.
I got it.
(Yunsheng Tower)
Mr. Gao, please sit.
(Inclusion of Letao products in Huineng)
Thanks.
Inclusion of Letao products in Huineng.
Next,
I will elaborate
on market share,
brand awareness,
and our sales channels.
These three points
are our most important core.
Product line,
process,
sales channels,
and market demand.
Demand for feminine hygiene products
keeps growing.
Boss, which company
are we going to next?
We still have 48 hours to enjoy Lvcheng.
What do you mean?
Sorry.
I thought
we could finish the work earlier.
I didn't expect the schedule
to be so packed.
So I extended the business trip
by two days.
If you can use
the 48 hours well,
the plans can surely be completed.
Where is it?
(No. 24, Old Street, Hanling)
(Forget Me)
We're here. This is the place.
(Surrounded by Flowers, Lost in Dreams)
I want to go.
Okay.
It's so beautiful in here.
Welcome.
Would you like to plant flowers
or buy flowers?
We offer storage and maintenance too.
So the flowers you plant
can grow strong, just like your love.
Customers have
always planted flowers here.
Well, actually we're not...
So we can't plant flowers together
if we're not a couple?
You still can.
But if you're a couple
and come together next time,
we'll have
an extra gift for you.
We are a couple.
Yes.
With so many beautiful flowers,
why choose sunflowers?
Other couples
would definitely choose roses.
Well, I mean,
roses are clearly more beautiful.
But I think
sunflower symbolism is more interesting.
What is it?
I'll browse first.
To browse first? What does it mean?
♪Love's time machine,
flies, flies, flies♪
♪Through centuries, just to meet you♪
♪Love's time machine keeps on turning♪
♪Streaking across the sky♪
♪Just to hold you♪
(Forget Me)
Hurry, only one minute's left.
Hello, two people.
Hello.
We're closed.
(Ticket Office)
We missed it by a minute.
We should've come earlier.
Darn it, such a good opportunity.
They say if two people
come here together,
they will be together forever.
Hinting at me?
No, not really.
I just think this place
is worth seeing.
It'd be a pity not to visit.
It's fine. We can come next time.
There won't be a next time.
Do you think it's easy to take a trip?
Look.
Look at what?
Look at these trees.
No one would see them as scenery.
Even when we first arrived,
we didn't notice them either.
But they're still full of life.
So?
We came all this way
just to look at trees?
They're everywhere.
Like downstairs at home.
But each one is different.
No matter where you go,
you won't see these trees again.
You mean,
no two leaves in this world
are identical, right?
Gao Haiming,
so you're a philosopher.
Alright.
I want a picture with this tree.
Okay.
Come on.
Three, two, one.
Your turn.
Okay.
You're right.
The scenery here is beautiful too.
But the inside must be better.
I just didn't plan well enough today.
If I'd been more thorough,
we could have gone inside.
You
are just too fixated
on reaching a destination
and miss the views along the way.
Isn't that an even bigger shame?
You always seem so emotionally stable.
It's not that I'm stable.
You're always in a hurry.
You're in a hurry to find a place,
to solve a problem,
and to finish a task.
Why are you in such a rush?
Am I? Am I really in a hurry?
Yeah.
Sometimes, wasting time
can be a kind of joy too.
Try it.
Wasting time.
Yeah.
You make a good point.
Then let's go fishing.
Fishing?
Yeah.
Fishing is the best
time-wasting activity.
Fi...fishing? Forget it.
Up ahead...
There's a lake up ahead.
We can fish there.
Since we're here,
let's go fishing today.
We might not catch anything, right?
Didn't you say
the result doesn't matter,
but the views along the way do?
Good.
Fishing is good.
Let's go fishing. To catch a big fish.
We'll eat fish tonight.
Very good.
Come here.
I just remembered.
You're afraid of the sea.
But this is a lake.
Are you afraid too?
What's scary about this lake?
Look, it's very shallow.
The water is waist-deep at most.
Don't you think
what's under the water is scary?
It seems calm on the surface.
You never know what's there.
Is it scary?
Could there be a monster in there?
Got one.
There really is.
It is scary.
Really.
Look.
There are tiny fish in the water.
It seriously hurts
my enthusiasm and self-esteem.
This is scary.
Maybe I'm overthinking it.
Don't overthink.
This tiny fish must've been
overthinking just now
and got caught before knowing it.
It's not grown yet.
How about we release it?
I will.
But not now.
You know?
If we release it now,
this tiny fish will spill the beans
and tell the other fish.
Then we won't catch anything today.
Going home empty-handed is scarier.
So, we need to wait
until we catch a big one
before releasing the small ones.
Are you that sure we'll catch a big one?
Absolutely.
Today, I must treat you
to a full banquet of fish I caught.
Hurry.
Come on.
Bring me the big one.
We will catch a big one.
♪Entwined worries linger♪
♪My heart is not empty,
yet pain remains♪
♪Now I see what passed between us♪
♪Walking through the crowd to meet you♪
♪Going through surging tides of people♪
♪Until the world's end♪
♪If I could♪
♪Keep loving you♪
♪Hearing two hearts♪
♪Beating together♪
♪If I could♪
♪Stay resting in your arms♪
♪I'd trade the rest of my life for it♪
♪Entwined worries linger♪
♪My heart is not empty,
yet pain remains♪
♪Now I see what passed between us♪
♪Walking through the crowd to meet you♪
♪Going through surging tides of people♪
♪Until the world's end♪
♪If I could♪
♪Keep loving you♪
♪Hearing two hearts♪
♪Beating together♪
♪If I could♪
♪Stay resting in your arms♪
♪I'd trade the rest of my life for it♪