(Street Woman Fighter 2)
(This program contains indirect advertisements.)
This is your last interview on Street Woman Fighter 2.
How do you feel?
(Hesitating)
Is this our last one? There's no more?
No, it can't be the last one!
This is actually so emotional.
(7 months ago)
Our ultimate goal is to make ourselves known.
I wanted the challenge.
I wanted to show people that female hip-hop dancers...
have been and will keep trying.
I wanted my teammates to succeed.
I really liked the name of the show, Street Woman Fighter.
This type of show doesn't exist in Japan, so I was envious.
Also, it was for female dancers.
I thought about how lovely it would be to be able to perform...
on such a great stage.
Eight different dance crews have gathered...
to begin Street Woman Fighter 2.
(Street Woman Fighter 2)
In 2021,
this show has brought dance fever to Korea.
(The sensational dance-off between women)
"Street Woman Fighter 1."
In 2022,
this show brought the dance fever back to Korea.
"Street Man Fighter."
And now,
Street Woman Fighter 2 follows.
The first appearance of global crews...
caught people's attention from the beginning.
You're still an eighth-grader to me.
I'm going to show you who is the queen!
From No Respect, Battle with the Weakest Dancer...
that created a number of legendary scenes...
(No Respect, Battle with the Weakest Dancer)
to the Class Mission,
a fierce dance-off for the main dancer position.
And the choreography of "Smoke," the mission song for the leaders...
led the global sensation...
(Trending number 1)
got many superstars to participate in the "Smoke" challenge.
(Many stars joined the "Smoke" challenge.)
This show continued to lead the dancing sensation.
Of all the dance series by Mnet,
Mega Crew Mission had brought the greatest number of dancers.
That's amazing.
They're so cool.
As soon as the videos were released,
they were the top three trending videos.
The video by 1MILLION that placed 1st...
had 10 million views...
and helped them strengthen their position.
The most popular TV show for eight weeks straight.
The top two popular celebrities that weren't on dramas.
With the highest viewer rating of 4.7 percent,
this program broke its own record every week.
Also, two weeks into opening the show,
the show had 100 million cumulative views.
Currently, the cumulative view count is over 520 million,
which proves how influential this is.
People from not only in Korea but also all over the world...
have reacted to our program.
These four crews are finally in the finals.
Finalist, 1MILLION.
From No Respect, Battle with the Weakest Dancer...
to the Class Mission,
this crew has gotten low grades.
But they've brought 100 dancers, the most out of all seasons,
to the Mega Crew Mission.
And released a dominating performance.
I feel like you could show this in the Olympics for our country.
People gave the highest praise, saying that the performance was...
like the opening ceremony to a national event,
and they proved themselves.
1MILLION deserves to be one of the finalists.
Finalist, BEBE.
Their career is being Bada's students.
Others broke their hearts by calling them...
Bada and Girls.
That makes me upset.
With their trendy choreography...
and teamwork,
they became a popular crew.
BEBE was the first crew to become a finalist.
Finalist, JAM REPUBLIC.
The competent, global dance crew...
showed its class from the start.
They turned the unexpected crisis into an opportunity...
and became a finalist...
with the support of viewers from all over the world.
Finalist, MANNEQUEEN.
They created many great scenes in battles with their dance skills.
After that, they had to go through discouraging moments...
as they placed low.
But they survived in their third Elimination Battle...
(They dramatically survived in the third Elimination Battle.)
and became the last finalist.
(MANNEQUEEN became the last finalist.)
And today,
it's the final round to determine the champion crew...
of Street Woman Fighter 2.
The final round consists of 20 percent...
of crew song performance voting...
and 80 percent of live text voting.
The champion crew receives...
a 50,000-dollar prize...
diamond rings to celebrate the victory.
1MILLION is bound to win.
We'll take the championship win.
1MILLION.
Who else would win if not BEBE?
We'll take the final crown.
BEBE.
JAM REPUBLIC is going to win.
And we are going to take that trophy.
JAM REPUBLIC.
We're going to place first, anyway.
MANNEQUEEN will take the trophy.
MANNEQUEEN.
Street Woman Fighter 2.
The live finals to determine...
the number-one dance crew in the whole world.
It begins now.
Ready? Fight.
("Move!" by pH-1)
(Listen to "Move!" by pH-1)
(the song for the opening performance of the finals, )
(on all streaming platforms.)
(To be continued)
(Street Woman Fighter 2, Finals)
Mnet's original dance series.
Street Woman Fighter 2.
Main host, Kang Daniel.
Good evening.
Determine the number-one dance crew in the whole world.
Street Woman Fighter 2,
I'm your host, Kang Daniel.
(Kang Daniel)
In 2023, these amazing eight crews...
including the famous Korean crews...
and global crews,
have been in fierce dance battles...
to prove themselves every step of the way.
1MILLION,
BEBE,
JAM REPUBLIC,
MANNEQUEEN.
Among these four crews, the number-one crew...
in the whole world will take the championship title.
Which crew will take...
the champion trophy of Street Woman Fighter 2?
Before we begin in earnest,
I give you the judges that have been with the crews...
of Street Woman Fighter 2 from the start.
Monika, Shownu, and the special judge, Mike Song!
(Monika, Mike Song, and Shownu)
Monika,
you were a contestant in Season One,
and you became one of the fight judges...
in Season Two. You were here every season.
The final round this time must feel different.
What would you focus on?
This performance is...
the last one on Street Woman Fighter 2,
and I know, for sure, what these four crews will have...
in mind when they perform.
These crews will try to let...
their identities known to the world through this performance.
Winning the title must be their goal,
but it's also a place to shout out to the world...
that their ideas on dance are the correct answer.
Great.
And Mike Song.
You were with us in No Respect, Battle with the Weakest Dancer...
and the Class Mission.
You've returned to honour us once again.
Your tremendous reactions...
as well as your commentary have been sensational,
and it shows how hard you've supported the program.
What are your expectations about the finals?
I'm well aware of the fact that all the crews...
in the final episode have master-level skills.
I think the most important part is...
to show your unique characteristics...
and who you really are.
All right.
Lastly, Shownu.
Please show your support for the four crews...
who will give us the best dance show ever.
You've worked really hard...
to be in the finals of Street Woman Fighter 2,
one of the toughest competitions in Korea.
I should have given you some compliments...
to cheer you up during the competition,
but I feel bad that I couldn't do that.
But I'll enjoy the show even more since it's the last one.
Great work so far.
Thank you for that.
A lot of people...
who love dance have joined us tonight.
Not only in this hall, but also in movie theatres...
all over the country,
numerous people are watching the live finals.
We appreciate the support and respect...
you've sent us for Street Woman Fighter 2.
We hope you enjoy tonight's show with the loudest cheers.
We will now begin the last dance-off...
of Street Woman Fighter 2 to determine the number-one crew...
among the four crews!
(The last dance-off starts now.)
Street Woman Fighter 2,
the final round is comprised of two different missions.
The first mission is the Global Artist Mission.
(Global Artist Mission)
Global Artist Mission.
Among four global artists loved by the whole world,
Ariana Grande, Beyoncé,
Lady Gaga, and Rihanna,
each crew chose an artist.
They must reinterpret the song by said artist...
and complete the best performance...
that surpasses that of the global artist.
And the second mission to finish the finals is...
the End Credit Mission.
(End Credit Mission)
The End Credit Mission is the finale of each crew.
The crews will portray their identities, themes,
and characteristics through dance in the end.
To prove the crew's unique style and world-class skills,
they put everything into this final performance.
So, we ask for your loud cheers,
support, and active participation in the vote.
Tonight, the number-one crew will be...
decided by 20 percent of crew song performance votes...
and 80 percent...
of live text votes.
(Your phone number will be collected and used...)
(for the text voting on this program.)
First, the crew song performance vote is...
a global vote that the whole world can participate in.
The votes from August 22, at 10:00 p.m. to today,
October 31st, 6:00 p.m.,
have been counted through the official platform...
of Street Woman Fighter 2 and Mnet Plus.
The voting has been closed.
Which crew did the global viewers...
love and care the most?
Here are the global ranks of the crew song performance vote.
In the crew song performance vote,
I will only announce fourth place.
Fourth place in the crew song performance vote is...
MANNEQUEEN.
(4th place, MANNEQUEEN, 2,119,971 views, )
(98,816 likes, and 175,192 votes)
MANNEQUEEN has earned 2,119,971 views,
plus 98,816 likes,
and 175,192 votes.
However, the current ranking can always change.
The final rankings of the four crews and the birth of the champion...
will be decided by you, the viewers,
who will watch the final performances...
and take part in the live text vote.
The live text vote that will begin soon...
takes up 80 percent of the total score.
Now, I will tell you...
how to vote for your crew in the live text vote.
Write the name or number...
of the crew that you root for in the text message,
and send it to 0011.
The live text vote will be explained by female fighters,
who have visited Street Woman Fighter 2.
Let's meet them together.
(Street Woman Fighter 2)
(Your phone number will be collected and used...)
(for the text voting on this program.)
(Street Woman Fighter 2 and "Street Comedy Woman Fighter 2")
(Number 1, 1MILLION)
Hey, guys.
Did you know that the voting has begun?
I didn't know.
(Increasing blood pressure)
That's how you want to talk to me?
That wasn't on purpose. We honestly didn't know.
I'll teach you, Lia.
Will you?
Now, text 0011...
1MILLION's name or number 1.
I voted.
I didn't want to embarrass you.
You've never embarrassed me once.
Let's make up.
(A beautiful sight of becoming one with a single text vote)
If you're rooting for 1MILLION,
text the number 1 or 1MILLION's name...
to 0011.
Okay.
("Chilli" for voting)
(Number 1 or 1MILLION)
(No double votes are allowed, but you can vote for more than one.)
- Number one! - Let's go!
- Let's go, number one! - Number one!
(Number 2, BEBE)
I'm going to vote for number two, BEBE.
King Bada, step forward!
(Relaxed)
(Getting interesting)
Bada, you're still number two to me.
What? Number two?
Number two?
- Yes! Keep going! - Don't let her win.
Hang on, guys.
Did you guys vote yet?
Vote?
We talked about it, but it got nowhere.
You didn't do anything.
(Suddenly, there is tension in the air.)
Do you want to remain as Bada and Girls?
No.
You're truly members of BEBE.
(Was I too serious?)
Hurry up and vote.
It's 0011. Vote for number 2 BEBE.
- Is this right? - BEBE.
- Look. - BEBE.
Wait a second.
Did you vote?
I need my phone.
(King Bada was in no place to blame the others.)
If you're rooting for BEBE,
text 0011...
- number two or BEBE! - Please!
Go and vote for us.
- BEBE is number 2. - BEBE is number 2.
- Number 2. - Number 2.
(Number 3, JAM REPUBLIC)
Hi, guys. We are...
- number 3. - Number 3.
(I like number 3.)
Hello.
(Hello.)
Big-eyed Kirsten?
My name is Big-eyed Kirsten.
(Gosh.)
(They love it.)
(The room gets heated when she takes her sweater off.)
(Watch me dance.)
(Audrey loves it.)
Big-eyed Kirsten, timing.
What?
(She can barely breathe.)
Timing?
JAM REPUBLIC, come out.
Come out!
(Let's do this.)
I'm sorry.
It's time for text voting.
If you vote for number three...
Thank you.
Thank you. You are so wonderful.
Gosh.
If you support JAM REPUBLIC,
text 0011...
JAM REPUBLIC or...
- number 3. - number 3.
(No double votes are allowed, but you can vote for more than one.)
- It's number 3. - Number 3, guys.
(Number 4, MANNEQUEEN)
MANNEQUEEN, I am a queen card.
- Excuse me. - Gosh. What is it?
What are you doing? You should be voting.
My goodness.
What do you think you're doing?
We don't need six people.
Come out, Cera.
MANNEQUEEN, I am a queen card.
- Stop it. - What are you doing?
(The relaxed attitude of a winner)
Cera, did you lose?
Don't get intimidated.
Pak Cera.
- Gosh. - Pak Cera.
What?
(She can't hold in her laughter.)
I going to avenge my sister.
My gosh.
(It's Pak Cera versus Yoonji.)
(Pak Cera gets beaten up with dances.)
(Trapped in MANNEQUEEN's jail of dance)
All right.
I'll vote for MANNEQUEEN or number four.
Four.
If you support MANNEQUEEN,
text 0011...
number four or MANNEQUEEN.
- Please. - Please.
- MANNEQUEEN card, MANNEQUEEN card. - MANNEQUEEN card, MANNEQUEEN card.
We will now begin live voting.
Five, four, three, two, one.
(Voting begins.)
Street Woman Fighter 2.
Live voting has begun.
You are allowed to vote for more than one crew,
but you cannot vote for the same crew twice.
Make sure to remember that.
I hope you show a lot of support and text in many votes.
(Text voting 0011)
The profit from text voting...
will be donated to Mapo Foundation for Arts and Culture...
to support artists.
This is the live finals of Street Woman Fighter 2.
The first mission of the live finals...
that will bring forward a fierce and powerful battle...
in attempts to become number one globally.
It's the Global Artist Mission.
The first crew to perform...
is 1MILLION.
1MILLION introduced K-dance to the public.
Everyone agrees they are the best choreography crew in Korea.
They've prepared a special stage with the honour of global K-dance...
on the line. Let's watch it right away.
1MILLION, ready? Fight.
We received zero votes...
for our "Single Ladies" performance for the Global Artist Mission.
So we ended up not being able to perform...
the song of the artist we wanted.
However, do you remember...
when we were eliminated in the JYP match?
(They were eliminated from the K-pop Death match Mission.)
(They were automatically added to the YG match with no choice.)
It ended up bringing us a better result.
I think our crew...
- can use this... - As an opportunity.
Yes, we're a crew that can turn this into an opportunity.
That's right.
1MILLION has choreographed so many of Ariana Grande's songs, right?
- Yes, she's like a cousin to us. - Seriously.
It's hard to find songs better to dance to...
- than Ariana Grande's songs. - Of course.
I am confident we can pull this off.
We have to pick a song.
Should we decide while dancing?
(They dance to a random list of songs to choose one.)
Wait. We need to feel the excitement rising in us.
I want it.
Since it's the finals,
I want to put on a performance we can enjoy with everyone.
(All the members of 1MILLION are having fun.)
We should do this one.
How can we not when we're all so excited?
I think it'd be okay to do two songs.
- Put them together? - Yes.
We couldn't just pick one song,
so we will show off...
the quality of our dance through "7 Rings..."
and create a performance...
that will let the energy within us explode through "Bang Bang."
(1MILLION stretches to warm up before practice.)
My body aches.
(Harimu brings something.)
- What's that? - I need sugar. I'll have a snack.
- A snack? - Yes.
Give it to me.
You know the feeling.
(1MILLION gathers around the snack.)
Nice.
You should stick these on your fingers.
No.
- No? - I'll show you something awesome.
You put these on your fingers and eat them, right?
- This is normal. - I love it.
After putting them on your fingers,
eat like Cardi B.
Like this.
Don't take them off until you're done.
(She even makes facial expressions to imitate Cardi B.)
(She can even feed others without her fingers touching it.)
(Crunchy sounds)
It sounds exactly like "crunch."
- Not "cringe?" - "Cringe?"
This is tasty.
I loved this when I was little.
(Snacks taste better when you devour them.)
Try to look pretty.
(Like me!)
- This is so good. - Yes, it is.
I ate too much.
- Should we practice? - Yes.
(1MILLION focuses on practicing since it's the final stage.)
(Trying hard)
I'm so tired.
- My feet are so sweaty. - I know.
You know you get tired more easily when you sweat, right?
I want to change shoes.
That's a sterilizing shoe rack.
- It's for dancers. - Really?
(Lia Kim's consideration for the dancers of 1MILLION!)
I'll give it a try.
I'd be grateful if it helps my shoes.
(The shoes are wet from dancing.)
- See you soon. - Bye.
Play.
(Standard styling, Preparing steam)
What colour do you like?
- Pink. - Light pink.
- Gosh. - Gosh.
It's done.
Ta-Da.
It feels different.
- You're right. - Right?
I love it because they aren't smelly anymore.
My shoes were wet from sweat on the inside.
Now it's dry.
Really?
Let's run.
I want to put on a performance...
that will let us prove how well we dance in the finals.
I am determined to show everyone...
the true value of 1MILLION.
(1MILLION is the best.)
You're so pretty!
(Choreography by 1MILLION)
You look like dolls.
You look like dolls!
(Lia Kim)
(1MILLION is already number 1. Enjoy it to the fullest!)
We watched 1MILLION's Global Artist Mission performance.
They started with dynamic moves...
and switched to a party vibe.
They were able to show us...
why 1MILLION is known for their choreography.
Fight judge Monika,
what did you think of 1MILLION's Global Artist Mission stage?
They understand the charisma of Ariana Grande.
I think...
she has a sexy side that can enjoyed by people of all ages.
It's a healthy type of sexy...
that won't allow anyone be biased against her.
You were able to display that sexiness accurately...
in various ways through your outfit,
choreography and structure.
It was the best.
Thank you for the compliment.
If you'd like to give 1MILLION,
the living legend of K-pop, the winner's trophy,
text 0011...
1MILLION or number 1.
Thank you, 1MILLION.
Number one.
(1MILLION, Lia Kim)
Global Artist Mission.
The next crew to perform...
is BEBE.
They started out as a rookie crew loved by many K-pop artists,
but now secured a spot among the top crews.
They say they've prepared a performance to win.
Let's take a look.
BEBE, ready?
Fight.
- I'm hungry. - I'm hungry.
- I'm starving. - Me too.
- That looks good. - That looks good.
It looks good.
I want a Spicy Shrimp.
I want a Spicy Italian.
- I want an Italian B.M.T. - That sounds good.
You know it's a popular sandwich, right?
- I do. - Of course.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- Enjoy. - Enjoy.
(Taking a huge bite)
(This is it.)
I just had a shrimp.
It's so juicy and delicious.
Try it.
This is really good.
It's the right amount of spicy.
I like adding egg Mayo...
- to B.M.T. - I see.
(Tatter likes to add ingredients.)
I heard adding avocado is also really good.
- Right. - It's also filling.
Which sauce did you choose?
I chose ranch and sweet chilli.
Chilli?
- Taste like chilli. - Chilli.
- Feel it. - Feel it.
Dilly.
That's right.
The spicy flavour reminds me of the dance.
You're right. We were automatically dancing.
Since we had a hearty meal,
shall we go practice hard?
- Yes. - Sounds good.
Ta-ta-ta.
We will now begin the first...
- Diva Contest. - Bring it on.
(BEBE is excited.)
We held a Diva Contest to create a theme...
for the Global Artist Mission.
When it comes to performances,
we've become known to put on energetic and powerful stages.
We plan to show everyone that we're a true diva.
We'll be sexier than ever.
What is she doing?
(Totally sexy!)
She's so pretty.
(The battle of sexiness has begun. Number 1, Diva Lusher)
(She is still a bit shy. Number 2, Diva Soweon)
(Clean and modern Number 3, Diva Minah)
She's carrying an umbrella.
(Dressed in a classic black outfit, Number 4, Diva Kyma)
(Showing off her charm!)
(What was that?)
(Who is the next diva?)
(The definition of "hip," Number 5, Diva Bada)
(It's Bada, the diva.)
She's a cool diva.
What's this?
(Funky cowgirl, Number 6, Diva Tatter)
- Gosh. - What's that?
When did you prepare all this?
(Bada loves it.)
It's the last.
(Finally, the last!)
(She turns the place upside down.)
- What's this? - Wait.
- Gosh. - Gosh.
(Unexpected charisma, Number 7, Diva Cheche)
(The rebellion of the youngest!)
I don't believe this. Look at our youngest.
What is going on?
If you had that inside of you,
show it to us.
Show us more.
- All right. - Nice.
Nice. I love it.
I personally...
liked the cowgirl concept.
I think we can pull it off.
Okay, we'll go with cowgirls.
- All right. - Okay.
We'll show you how sexy we are.
I want people to ask,
"Why did they wait so long to show us this?"
Since we chose Rihanna,
we'll put on a powerful performance.
Whatever you're imagining,
we'll show you something better.
Let's put on the coolest performance...
for the Global Artist Mission.
One, two, three.
- Let's go! - Let's go!
- Let's go. - Let's go!
(Tatter, Mommy is watching you!)
(Choreography by BEBE)
(You are the best.)
(Let's win 1st place, BEBE!)
We watched BEBE's Global Artist Mission performance.
It was like a festival we could all enjoy together,
and they displayed an unexpected charm with their cowgirl outfits.
Known to be good at dancing in sync and the small details,
they once again put on a flawless performance.
Fight judge Shownu,
from BEBE's Global Artist Mission performance,
what was the most impressive?
First of all,
I liked the overall structure,
and the ending when you paired up...
and sprinkled confetti in the air.
You dominated the stage...
and didn't miss anything from the song, expressing it all.
That was amazing.
One of BEBE's strengths...
is adding trendy moves to important parts of the song.
It's like those parts are embedded in my head when the show is over.
I believe I'll be thinking about it on my way home today as well.
You did a great job.
Thank you for sharing your thoughts.
If you'd like to make BEBE,
the young generation dance crew, the final winner,
text 0011...
with the name BEBE or number 2.
Good job, BEBE.
The next crew to perform in the Global Artist Mission...
is JAM REPUBLIC.
Being a global crew,
JAM REPUBLIC grabbed the attention of people around the world,
and charged forward to the live finals with their support.
They have prepared a performance...
to show us the pride of the Worldwide Avengers Crew.
What kind of performance is it?
Let's watch it right away.
JAM REPUBLIC, ready?
Fight.
The sun is shining today.
Oh, my goodness.
(One cool autumn day)
(Where did JAM REPUBLIC go?)
It kind of looks like a Korean drama.
- It does. - That's fancy.
- "New Zealand Residence." - Yes, it looks like a house.
(New Zealand is where they filmed their Mega Crew Mission...)
(and Kirsten, Ling, and Emma's hometown.)
We're a global team, and represent New Zealand.
So the ambassador for New Zealand that lives in Korea...
invited JAM REPUBLIC over to her house.
- Hello, JAM REPUBLIC. - Hi.
I'm very excited that you are doing so well. Congratulations.
For everything that you've achieved so far.
We've got some New Zealand treats for you.
Anzac cookies, Afghan cookies, and pavlova.
Oh, pavlova. It feels like home already.
It's so nice to have you here.
Kirsten, you popped up on my Instagram feed yesterday...
because I follow Taeyang.
You were doing the "Smoke" challenge with him.
I was like, "I recognize this one."
And there's somebody else. The one with...
HUENINGKAI from TXT?
- Yes. - Yes.
I saw that one too. Yes.
Do you like K-pop?
I'm a big fan of BTS'.
(We're here with an Army.)
And within BTS, my favourite is Suga.
He does that... "Enemy, enemy, enemy."
Oh, my gosh.
You did that, right? Yes, that was great.
Maybe you should've been in that part.
(Chuckling)
So how has it been meeting all these K-pop idols...
and people you've admired from afar?
Is it quite amazing to meet them in person?
It's very surreal.
- Surreal. - Yes.
From seeing them on the screen...
to being able to feel their presence in person?
It's like... Yes, "surreal" is the word for it.
Yes.
And it shows what we can because these missions are quite hard,
and the show is quite challenging.
But it just got more about each other as a group,
and remembering why we're here.
You're doing such a great job representing New Zealand,
Australia, and America here in Korea.
I will be rooting for you in the finals.
I really want you to win.
I'll be your biggest supporter.
- Thank you. - Yes, thank you.
It was lovely that we met. It felt like home.
Our journey has basically been supported by...
not just New Zealand, Australia and America. It's been global.
All JAM REPUBLIC wants to do is give back our love and support...
to our Jammies, to our fans, and to our supporters.
Now that it's Global Artist Mission,
Beyonce is known globally.
She inspires so many...
and gives off that strength.
Global domination JAM REPUBLIC has.
Okay, when you think of Beyonce, what do you think of?
Three, two, one.
- Hats. - Hats.
Do I like this?
Ling-yonce!
(We love you, Ling-yonce.)
This is definitely what comes to mind when we think of Beyonce,
and we wanted to highlight what the world loves about her,
in terms of what she wears for shows.
So this mission is our mission.
We want to show everybody...
why we are the only international global crew in the final stage.
We are going to showcase as JAM-yonce,
so I hope you guys are ready.
Let's go.
(I love you, Audrey.)
("Flawless," "Baby Boy," and "Bow Down" by Beyonce)
You've watched JAM REPUBLIC's Global Artist Mission performance.
Just like what they said about...
showcasing as JAM-yonce for their pride as a global crew,
they opened their performance using hats, Beyonce's signature prop.
It was a special show you can only watch on Street Woman Fighter 2.
Mike Song, our special judge.
What did you think of JAM REPUBLIC's original choreography...
to Beyonce's music?
That was crazy!
You all killed it.
I felt so many emotions.
I think you guys used so many different weapons there.
It was so good.
I feel like in the beginning, using hats...
and then having a flow from cleanliness to strong energy,
to attitude and star quality.
You guys really went on the roller coaster,
and I think that just shows that you guys are high-level...
super experienced and honestly just masters.
I know Beyonce would be proud and just want to give you props.
You guys are always so fearless. Fearless coming on this show,
fearless using props in the final challenge.
It's so difficult to do that there.
I'm so happy for you all. Congratulations.
Mike said they used the props very well,
and their performance...
was memorable and full of different energies.
If you want to give JAM PUBLIC, the worldwide Avengers crew,
the honourable title as the number one global dance crew,
text your vote to 0011 now.
Please text "JAM REPUBLIC"...
or simply number three.
JAM REPUBLIC, great job.
Thank you.
The next crew to perform for the Global Artist Mission is...
MANNEQUEEN.
Waacking, hip-hop, choreography, and krumping.
MANNEQUEEN is a world-class crew of talented female warriors.
I can't wait to see how they combined...
these different genres and created a new performance.
Let's see it right away.
MANNEQUEEN. Ready? Fight!
(MANNEQUEEN's dance studio)
Although Lady Gaga wasn't our first choice,
I think her music...
- is a great fit for us. - That's right. It is.
Lady Gaga is known as the master of performance themes.
I believe we'll be able to give ourselves some flamboyant looks.
- You're right. - Absolutely.
Are you Lady Cera?
- That's right. - I'm Lady Yoonji.
For the days you want to look stylish.
For the days you want to look even more stylish.
(Cautious)
Lady Gaga is known for her coolest sunglasses.
No, it's her costumes.
- Lady Gaga. - Gaga.
- Hey. - Who's that?
Hey. I'm Lady Waackxxxy.
(Waackxxxy copied her makeup.)
(She already looks like a queen.)
I can see with my eyes open,
and even with my eyes closed.
I can see with my eyes open like this.
How many is this?
(Who's the lady in red high heels?)
(It's Buckey, MANNEQUEEN's eldest member.)
I'm a queen.
(Cracking up at her skit)
I'm "Judas" Buckey.
(She's dressed as Lady Gaga back in her "Judas" days.)
How do I look?
You just look pretty.
Is this what we're doing?
Are we doing pretty?
- What about me? - No, it's...
(Come on, next Lady Gaga.)
(Lady Redlic with the biggest ego ever)
Are you an AI character?
What's your theme here?
(Lady Redlic's theme is unclear.)
- Come on, look at us. - Look.
(Together, they look ridiculous.)
She looks the prettiest.
It's like Buckey is Lady Gaga,
and the four of us are just wearing props in a photo booth.
It's like we're in a photo booth.
- Stop that. - Here she comes!
What have you got?
(Her indescribable aura intimidates them.)
I'm scared.
No, don't be intimidated.
What?
- Oh, my gosh! - Yes!
The makeup looks good on her.
She totally looks like Lady Gaga!
(Astonished by the resemblance)
This might give me a nightmare.
- Let's go. - It's party
(Their Lady Gaga dress-up was a success.)
(The end of MANNEQUEEN's Lady Gaga contest)
- It looks good, right? - It does.
We should start practicing now.
Before we do, this will be a good warm-up exercise.
- Yes. - Shall we give it a try?
Here. First,
- you tap on this app. - Oh, my.
- Okay, let's go! - All right.
- Here we go. - I'm nervous.
Nice. Great.
This is so much fun.
(Dancing hard)
Even if you're not good at dancing, it'd be easy to follow.
(Quokka Yoonji is enjoying the game.)
(She got a bad for going to the wrong direction.)
She got it wrong!
(The full version video is available online.)
We're all warmed up now. Shall we begin our practice?
- Let's go! - Yes!
Lady Gaga is...
a revolutionary and daring artist.
A lot of her songs express strong determination.
We'll reveal the part of us that we're hiding inside...
and express our strong passion and our inner selves.
We're going to give you an unforgettable performance...
in the finals.
("Poker Face," "Scheibe," and "Judas" by Lady Gaga)
You guys look beautiful!
(I am going to show you who the queen is.)
You've watched MANNEQUEEN's Global Artist Mission performance.
Their pose during the intro to depict a human dress...
was very impressive.
They showed off their flexibility and technique, their strong suit,
and gave a performance that you can't take your eyes off.
Fight judge Monika.
What did you think of MANNEQUEEN's Global Artist Mission performance?
It was like Lady Gaga was actually here.
Yes.
It didn't feel like a mission. It felt like I was at her concert.
I think Lady Gaga should buy this choreography.
It was truly amazing.
Thank you, Monika.
If you want to give MANNEQUEEN, the great world-class crew,
the crown as the queen of queens,
text your vote to 0011 now.
Please text "MANNEQUEEN" or number four.
(Text your vote to 0011.)
MANNEQUEEN, great job.
All right. You've watched...
all four finalists' performances for the Global Artist Mission.
The four crew have proven themselves once again...
with amazing reinterpretations of the global artists' music.
Which crew will be the final winner of Street Woman Fighter 2 tonight...
and win the title as the number one dance crew in the world?
The live voting is still open,
so make sure to cast your votes.
Now, there are some people in the live audience here...
who would like to express their support to the crews.
Firstly, I see someone enjoying the finals with hearty cheers.
It's the former sports star, Kwak Yoon Gy.
Please give the crews some words of support.
Yes, hello.
I'm Kwak Yoon Gy, the one who danced at the Olympics.
Yes!
Personally, while watching their performances,
I thought that if there was a dancing Olympics,
the competition would be as heated as this.
Their performances were fantastic and extraordinary.
I was touched like it was a sports game.
All right, thank you. It's an honour to have you here.
Now, these days, I enjoy watching...
ZEROBASEONE's performance.
They participated in the "Smoke" challenge...
and expressed their love for Street Woman Fighter 2.
We have some of ZEROBASEONE members joining us in the audience.
It's Han Bin, Matthew, Hao, and Tae Rae.
Could you give the crews some words of support?
Let us say hello to everyone. In 2, 3.
- Hello, we're ZEROBASEONE. - Hello, we're ZEROBASEONE.
Yes.
All of us are big fans...
of Street Woman Fighter 2.
We'll be fully enjoying the crews' passion...
for dancing.
This is the finals, and they must be very nervous.
I hope our cheers will help them loosen up.
Good luck!
- Good luck! - Good luck!
Now, we're joined by one more special guest today.
He's one of my favourite seniors. It's Kim Jae Hwan.
No, I'm not your senior.
- Right. - Yes.
Anyway, you've come to show your support to the crews...
- of Street Woman Fighter 2. - Yes.
Please give them a few words of support.
Actually, I'm so hyped right now...
that I don't even know what to say.
That's how fantastic their performances were.
I got goosebumps all over. That's all I can say.
Also, I'm so grateful to Mnet...
for making such a great show like this.
And all the dancers in the show as well.
I think all their sweat and effort...
have paid off and made their performance so brilliant.
Thank you so much.
- Also, - All right.
Daniel, you make a good show host.
- Sorry? Oh, thank you. - You're a good show host.
Now, Tae Rae, could you say a few words as well?
Yes. First of all, all the dancers...
- just look radiant today. - Right.
Since they've worked so hard so far,
I hope they'll give their all to their performances today.
I'll be looking forward to it.
Great.
Lastly, there's someone...
who's been looking forward to the finals more than anyone.
It's Nam Ji Hyun.
Please give the crews a few words of support.
Hello, I'm actress Nam Ji Hyun.
I've been a big fan...
of Street Woman Fighter 2.
I've been enjoying every episode since August.
It feels like a dream to be here to watch the finals live.
It's such an honour. Thank you.
I sense such great enthusiasm from the audience here.
I'm sure it means a lot...
to all the dancers on stage.
I'll also show them my support as much as possible.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Lastly, we're also joined by the judge of Street Woman Fighter 1,
TAEYONG of NCT.
Please give some words of support to the four crews.
First of all, it feels completely different to watch...
the finals live.
Since the four crews are showing us such great passion,
we'll also do our best to cheer for them. Good luck.
Great, thank you.
I appreciate all your heartfelt messages of support...
for the four finalists.
I hope you will keep supporting them...
with even louder cheers until the end.
You're watching Street Woman Fighter 2.
Let's move on to the last mission, the End Credit Mission.
(Second mission, the End Credit Mission)
(End Credit Mission)
1MILLION, BEBE,
JAM REPUBLIC, MANNEQUEEN.
This will be the last performance they'll be giving on our show.
Which crew will be the first to perform?
It's 1MILLION.
1MILLION's Mega Crew Mission performance...
has now hit over ten million views online.
It's the best record we've seen in all seasons,
and they're making new history.
The finale by 1MILLION,
the crew that started history.
How will their end credits of dance look?
1MILLION, ready?
Fight!
(Lia Kim)
Lia, we're here!
Hi.
Do I look good in an apron?
It's a new look.
(Lia Kim in an apron appears.)
I invited the members at home.
And I wanted to serve them a hot meal...
so that we could spend...
some time together to cheer up.
- It looks so new. - You look so different.
How does my doenjang stew taste?
- It's tasty, right? - Yes.
It's so good that it makes me frown.
It's seriously good.
I've always wanted to cook for you.
Thanks.
Oh, my gosh. Look at this.
I'm so full.
- I'm stuffed. - Me too.
Since day one, a lot of things have happened to us, right?
Share the most memorable mission...
one by one.
The Mega Crew Mission for me.
Right.
We devoted ourselves to it from the meeting to the choreo.
We kept developing and revising it.
There were a lot of conflicts and different opinions.
Although it was tough, we were still...
We were able to make up for each other's shortcomings.
I realized what an actual team was.
So,
we're going to watch our Mega Crew Mission...
to bring back the memories and strengthen our determination.
That sounds fun.
(1MILLION's reaction to its Mega Crew Mission)
Yes.
- Oh, my. - It's so...
We had amazing teamwork.
Let's go.
(Drawn in)
There you go.
It amazes me non-stop...
that I can't close my mouth.
It's still awesome.
- We made it, but it's incredible. - Yes, totally.
It's so...
- Hi, 1MILLION girls. - What?
It's Lia.
(Lia has a surprise message for the members.)
What?
(You can't just move our hearts like this.)
You've done so well.
Yes!
We've all been through a lot.
(Choking up)
I couldn't stop crying,
so I had to keep taking this video over and over.
You guys had my back so reliably,
and that was the only reason I could get through it.
Even when Lia fell for a short time,
we wanted to stand tall...
so that she could get back up.
One more time. Slowly.
I doubt that I would have gotten through this if it weren't for you.
Just performing on this stage with you guys...
will be the happiest moment of my life.
I love you all.
Let's go, 1MILLION!
(Bursting into laughter)
- "Let's go, 1MILLION!" - You got it wrong.
Right.
- Hello. - Oh, my!
(And a message from the members for Lia)
I thought I was the only one!
We've been seeing each other every day for half a year now.
I've seen you more often than I have my mom.
But you're practically...
my Korean mom.
(You're my Korean mom.)
(Shy and touched)
You bought me food,
clothes, and shoes.
So, I'm grateful.
We've had it tough,
and a lot of it seemed impossible.
But we did it.
I hope you never forget...
that we're there for you.
I want to keep dancing joyfully with you.
I was glad to be on the journey of Street Woman Fighter 2...
with you and the other members.
Let's keep going until the end.
Let's go!
(Lia shows tears due to the members' sincerity.)
When Debby said,
"Korean mom," it was so...
Same.
I didn't think I was that nice to her.
Then, call her auntie.
- Korean auntie. - Auntie.
Watching this...
- gave me energy. - Right.
I have a feeling that I can do my best and do it well.
(I'll do my best and do it well.)
We came all the way to the finals.
I want to have so much fun...
- on the stage. - Right.
- Definitely. - I just want to...
At least, in this performance,
I don't want to mind other people's prejudices.
I hope we will show people...
our true colours.
- 1MILLION! - To the champion!
- Whether we win or lose, - Whether we win or lose,
- let's go! - let's go!
(Whether we win or lose, let's go!)
("Natural" by Imagine Dragons choreographed by 1MILLION)
(The performance of 1MILLION's determination to focus on...)
(the present and its true colours to overcome the prejudices.)
(Lia Kim)
That was the End Credit Mission by 1MILLION,
the crew acknowledged not only by Korea but also by the world.
We could feel their explosive passion...
and their conflicting energy...
that was intense yet gentle.
Fight judge, Shownu.
What did you think about 1MILLION's performance?
I'm wondering how many performances...
you came up with in such a short time.
First, one of 1MILLION's strengths is...
its flexibility...
and the talent...
that shows from the facial expressions.
That went well with the explosive show today,
and it was the best performance ever by 1MILLION.
Great work. Thank you for the show.
Thank you for the comment.
1MILLION has shown its end credits through dance.
The leader of 1MILLION, Lia Kim.
How do you feel about finishing your last performance here?
Gosh.
We've finally reached the end.
I doubt that any of the dancers thought...
that I could get through this program.
Now that we've finished our final performance,
I'm extremely glad.
And the members that helped me get here,
I love you all.
I believe that we pulled off out last performance fabulously.
Thank you!
(Lia Kim)
That was the last performance...
by 1MILLION, one of the finalists of Street Woman Fighter 2.
If you're rooting for 1MILLION,
send a text message to 0011...
with 1MILLION's name or the number one.
(Text the number of the crew name to 0011.)
Great job, 1MILLION.
- Thank you! - Thank you.
Tonight, the champion crew will be decided...
by your live text voting.
Your votes will determine the champion,
so please vote for the crew that you're rooting for.
The next crew to perform is...
BEBE.
BEBE is a team of Bada, the hottest choreographer,
and the rookie dancers of the world of dancing in Korea.
In the last mission, the crew placed first...
and became the first crew...
to secure its spot in the finals.
BEBE is acclaimed as the future...
of the K-pop world through Street Woman Fighter 2.
What will their End Credit Mission look like?
BEBE, ready? Fight!
(A Store)
- What is this? - Gosh.
It's gorgeous.
- Bada! - It's Bada.
- Ta-Da! - Ta-Da!
- What are you doing here? - What are these?
We're going to get crew jewellery.
I prepared these for you!
(Make some noise.)
Try on the ones that you like and pick one.
- Yes! - Yes!
- It looks cute. - Check out this necklace.
I want this.
I thought they only sold it on their app.
I didn't know they had an offline store.
- I know, right? - Me neither.
Did you all pick one?
We picked so many.
- Seriously. - How should we pick one?
I don't think we can decide.
- Shall we decide? - Sure.
- I choose you! - In 1, 2, 3.
(We choose you!)
We were thinking the same.
- So, this is our crew ring. - Yes!
(BEBE's new uniform, crew ring)
I was watching, and...
I found the championship ring.
- Oh, my gosh. - They're gorgeous.
Awesome.
- They're so pretty. - It's shining so brightly.
- The colours are brilliant. - Beautiful.
We're going to win, so should we tell them our sizes?
- Sure. - Let's do that.
We'll win the championship and come back for you.
(The second special course by Bada)
It's a theme park!
How long has it been?
I never had time...
to make memories with them during Street Woman Fighter 2.
So we came to a theme park as they all wanted.
Hello.
(The employees say hi with the "Smoke" move.)
- She did this. - I'm glad...
- when they do this. - I know.
- You're so pretty, Tatter! - I love you!
I love you, Bada.
Thank you.
It's weird that they recognize us.
In 1, 2, 3.
(They forget about the mission and have fun today.)
Hold on!
I feel like we've only been running forward.
It was pleasant to spend the day...
without any worries.
I'm glad to share a memory as a team.
What's going on now?
- You're making me too happy. - What?
To celebrate our friendship forever,
I got us roses!
(Sky-blue roses for their long friendship)
When the members of BEBE first gathered,
I gave them roses to promise that we'll forever be a family.
But I never gave the new members any roses.
I wonder when this type of day will come in the future.
I feel like we've formed a stronger bond today.
Right.
I can't believe we're in the finals.
I would never have been able to do it by myself.
(Spotting something)
Surprise!
(The big event that even Bada didn't know about)
It's Mom, Tatter.
(Mom?)
- I told you this would happen! - Are you watching?
(A message from the families of the BEBE members)
You're doing so great out there,
so I'm proud of you and grateful for everything.
I see Minah being on a team with such good people,
and it makes me think about how blessed she is.
I hope you keep doing well.
Your mom and dad will always root for you from behind,
so keep showing your efforts as you've always done...
without minding the result.
Hi.
How are you doing, Soweon?
(Soweon cries as soon as her mom appears.)
I'm enjoying the show.
You liked to dance when you were little,
and I thought it'd only be a hobby.
Now, you're properly showing them on Street Woman Fighter 2.
I just want you to do what you want to do and be happy.
Do whatever you want to do.
Don't forget that I'll always be your number-one fan.
Thanks for letting me be your mom, Kyma.
I love you so much.
My daughter, Lusher.
What are you doing over there?
I know, right?
She was obviously Lusher's mom.
I saw you enjoying the work and powering through,
and I was very proud of you.
Please keep doing your best without any injuries.
(And...)
My mom...
Is that from your mom?
(And a sincere message in a handwritten letter)
But she said she didn't do anything.
(The handwritten messages...)
(hold her affectionate support for her daughter.)
(I love you, Bada. Thank you for being my daughter.)
(Our family will be happy.)
(The warm words...)
(make them all cry.)
Oh, come on!
This is probably a tear trigger for everyone.
- Exactly. - This is cheating.
But it's nice to see our mothers.
Absolutely.
I don't think I'll ever forget today.
Let's keep remembering today until the end of the finals.
Sure. Let's dance hard.
This is only a start, isn't it?
The final round is our beginning.
Let's go and begin our future.
Not the end, but the beginning!
- It's the beginning! - Yes!
(It's the beginning now.)
Let's go!
Go!
("Praise," produced music, and "Run It" choreographed by BEBE)
(Meaning, "Only the prepared may escape from darkness,")
(BEBE portrays its determination to keep on dancing...)
(in a dark manner.)
(Bada)
(Let's go, BEBE!)
(Number 2)
- BEBE! - BEBE!
That was the End Credit Mission by BEBE that turned...
from the youngest rookie crew to a named crew.
Your intense moves using masks were pretty impressive.
They've shown how they'll keep devoting themselves to dancing...
after growing to a whole new level on Street Woman Fighter 2...
in the last performance.
Special judge, Mike Song.
What did you think about their performance?
When I watched BEBE's performance,
I felt that we found a leader of the new generation.
I think you greatly affected the global dance culture.
I'm just so proud to see you guys. I'm happy for you.
Congratulations.
Thank you, Mike Song.
The leader of BEBE, Bada.
How does it feel to finish your last performance here?
Yes. First,
I'm exhilarated that BEBE...
was able to come to the finals.
And I'm glad to have shown you our unique performance.
My heart is full, and it's an honour.
Also, the members who came through with the performance.
Thank you.
Great work.
It was such a happy and fun journey,
and I hope it touched your hearts as well.
Thank you for watching!
That was the last performance...
by BEBE, a finalist on Street Woman Fighter 2.
If you're rooting for BEBE to win,
text BEBE or the number two...
to 0011.
(Text the number of the crew name to 0011.)
Great job, BEBE.
(Number 2)
(BEBE for the championship)
(Bada)
Tonight, the number-one crew in the whole world...
will be decided by your live text voting.
Vote for the crew that you're rooting for right now.
The next crew to perform is...
JAM REPUBLIC.
JAM REPUBLIC is the first global crew in Street Woman Fighter.
A total of 23 countries, including Korea,
helped propel their videos to an unprecedented popularity.
They set a new record across all seasons of the show.
For each mission, they showcased their worldwide talent boldly.
How will JAM REPUBLIC'S ending performance turn out?
JAM REPUBLIC, are you ready? Fight!
(Kirsten)
Hey.
Long time no see.
Hello. I'm LaTrice.
Guys, we're all in different countries.
This is wild.
- I miss you all. - I miss you guys too.
How are we feeling about finals, all?
I can't believe how quick it's coming.
And we're excited! Just waiting to see what comes next.
For the finals, after we perform, and whatever happens,
it's going to be really sad saying goodbye to everyone.
Yes, it'll be sad.
Wait, do you guys remember the first time we met together?
(JAM DROP LING would like to share a memory.)
(During their first meeting with the producers)
Hi, I'm Audrey.
I'm from Washington, America, yes.
Hi guys, I'm Ling.
I'm Emma. I'm from New Zealand as well.
I am from Brisbane, Australia.
Hi, I'm Kirsten.
(Why did you decide to be on Street Woman Fighter 2?)
I really love Korea, and I love K-pop,
so I'm just excited to be in the culture.
I also love the name of the show.
It's like "Street Fighter,"
so it's giving me attacking vibes. I just can't wait to get out there,
and kill the beat, buys.
I think it's a new challenge for me.
"Woman power" is really a game changer.
Dance as well. It's going to be amazing.
(What are you looking forward to the most on Street Woman Fighter 2?)
Different women freestyling.
It'll be interesting to see all the different styles there.
That has me excited.
(SWF2 would like to share a memory.)
(Audrey was looking forward to freestyling.)
(She was able to prove her battle skill in front of many.)
I'm really excited for...
the choreography for the artists that you bring on.
(SWF2 would like to share a memory.)
(The most anticipated Artist's New Song Preview Mission)
(Ling was able to meet Hwasa, an artist she's been a fan of.)
(She was able to receive the highest praise for her dance.)
I think I've seen a lot of Korean dancers...
just on social media.
I'm excited to see how they work in person.
It would be nice to see them firsthand.
(Through Street Woman Fighter 2, JAM REPUBLIC made memories...)
(with other Korean dancers.)
(What side of JAM REPUBLIC will we see on SWF2?)
Everyone in this crew has got their own individual strengths.
Moreover, as the first global crew to enter the competition, the show,
we have confidence.
Everyone here is a beautiful woman.
I think that's going to be something that no one else has seen.
Oh, my gosh, this was five months ago.
We did a lot, right?
We did well, guys.
Good memories.
No regrets, baby.
I have to say, the number of times I'm like,
"I can't wait till it's over," and now I'm like, "aw."
- I'm sad. - Sad.
We have an announcement.
Another challenge has been put out.
- Let me guess. - It's a new mission?
I want to go home.
- Hi Kirsten. - Hi Kirsten.
(A surprise video message from families of the members)
We just want to say how proud of you we are...
for all your hard work on this show. We love you.
- And we can't wait to see you. - Oh, my gosh.
We love you.
- Gosh. - Go, JAM REPUBLIC!
Go, JAM REPUBLIC!
We love you so much.
We encourage you to keep going.
You have so much to give.
Just keep climbing up.
Just have fun...
for the last competition.
And make the most of your time. Enjoy it and have fun.
Hi, Emma.
- Gosh. - Hello from Auckland, New Zealand.
- Go Emma, we love you. - Go Emma, we love you.
- Go! - We love you!
- What's that? - I just want to do my heart.
- That's so lovely. - That's great.
She wanted to do a heart.
- Oh, my gosh. - Like this.
Hi Audrey.
We just wanted to say congratulations...
for making it to the finals.
We're super proud of you and all the hard work you've put in.
We love you and miss you.
That was the best mission.
This was really the first prize.
Throughout this whole journey, we wouldn't be here without you.
And a big shout out to our families.
We love you and we miss you so much.
- This one. - This one.
I'm doing it like this.
For the Ending Credits performance, it's our goal to showcase...
not only who we are,
but also represent the world.
By having the flags on the back of our LED lights...
for JAM REPUBLIC showcases...
who we are, where we come from,
and who we represent.
I think we're going to try our best to put on the best stage...
that we can do. We're not holding back for this one.
This is not the end,
so make sure you stay tuned.
- Let's go. - The finals!
Let's go!
(Would you like to see JAM REPUBLIC'S Ending Credits?)
("Jele" by DBN Gogo, Sino Msolo, Kamo Mphela, Young Stunna, Busiswa)
(A performance highlighting JAM REPUBLIC's identity...)
(as a diverse band of dancers unified to achieve success...)
(and to show how will, toughness, and tenacity overcame adversity.)
JAM REPUBLIC!
JAM REPUBLIC's Ending Credits performance...
reminded us once more this is a worldwide Avengers crew.
Once more, they've boldly showcased...
the fresh, new performance style...
that is JAM REPUBLIC's strength.
They've proven their unrivalled skills again.
Fight judge Monika,
what did you think of JAM REPUBLIC's Ending Credits Performance?
I thought it was incredible, and there's so much I could say.
Right now, I'm a little emotional.
This is what how I'd like to express it.
All of your roots are so beautiful.
They're so beautiful.
Thank you so much.
Thank you for sharing this performance with us.
Thank you for your kind words.
JAM REPUBLIC's Kirsten,
as the first global crew in Street Woman Fighter history,
your crew has made it to finals.
How do you feel, having finished your final performance?
Take your time.
No!
I'm here. Okay.
I just want to say, it's been a journey.
What we wanted to show again on our last performance...
is the journey that we've taken.
We came here to show...
so much, not just one thing.
And I hope you understood...
everything that we did, the story that we told.
And we are so happy...
and proud to be standing on this stage in front of you all.
So thank you very much for this moment.
This is so amazing.
Kirsten told us that she's very grateful...
to have been able to share their journey...
through their last performance.
Street Woman Fighter 2.
The final performance for JAM REPUBLIC is now over.
Viewers who support JAM REPUBLIC,
please text pound 0011...
and send a message saying JAM REPUBLIC...
or the number three.
(Vote for the crew number or the crew name via text.)
JAM REPUBLIC, thank you for your hard work.
Thank you.
(JAM REPUBLIC, you tore it up)
Tonight, the winning crew will take home the trophy.
Which crew will win?
Please vote for the crew you support right now.
The last crew to perform...
is MANNEQUEEN.
MANNEQUEEN has world-class skill and seeks to expand their range.
They are a pioneering crew on the dance scene.
In the recent Elimination Battle, they won an overwhelming victory,
and survived to show you this final performance.
What kind of Ending Credits performance will MANNEQUEEN show?
MANNEQUEEN, ready?
Fight!
We believe the finals will be better after we eat, so let's eat.
It's pizza.
Ta Da.
(A pizza party for the finals)
- This looks so delicious. - It looks insane.
- To MANNEQUEEN's victory! - To victory!
(Taking huge bites)
It's so delicious.
They're so generous with the toppings.
She took such a huge bite.
- Is it crispy? - It's good.
The dough is chewy and delicious.
(MANNEQUEEN enjoys healing time with delicious food.)
It's really delicious.
Now that we're full and feeling refreshed,
let's present what we've prepared.
Let's reveal our Secret Santas.
(Gosh, I'm so nervous.)
Please look forward to what gift I bought.
I'm here to buy a gift for my Secret Santa.
I want to get something a little cuter.
I'll prepare a handwritten letter...
to convey my feelings. I think that's a good idea.
- Try to guess mine. - Cera's?
I didn't drop any hints at all.
- I think it's Buckey. - Ha Eun.
- I really didn't drop hints. - Me.
The reason I chose this gift...
is that I was...
thinking of my friend.
- Friend? - Friend?
It must be me.
My Secret Santa is my friend.
She's crying!
(Already moved)
It's Yoonji!
I wanted to get her a pretty makeup pouch.
Thank you.
This is my pouch now.
Throw that out now.
I like moving things over right away.
This is so nice. Thank you.
She's putting on an act now.
Ta Da!
(Waackxxxy's Secret Santa was Yoonji.)
(Already getting teary)
What is it?
It's your favourite.
(Impressed)
It's perfect.
Doesn't this remind you of me, everyone?
It's a hair mask.
(She even gifted a hair mask to improve her hair.)
I'll have to use a lot of this.
I'm the Secret Santa for Ha Eun,
or Redlic, and I'm on my way to buy her gift right now.
It's silver and has a heart.
I think this one...
suits Ha Eun well.
(Crying)
Gosh.
It's so cute.
(It's so cute that I'm "Sadlic.")
(Cutesy)
That really suits you.
- Thank you. - I was Secret Santa...
- for Buckey. - Gosh!
Thank you.
- I'm going to carry this around. - All right.
This is for the blue-loving Funky Y.
(Buckey was Secret Santa for their leader, Funky Y.)
Our eldest member got gifts for our leader.
It's blue.
Everything's blue.
(An assortment of blue gifts for Funky Y)
It's over now.
- It's a blue envelope. - There's even a letter.
- This is really moving. - Who's next?
Who did Funky Y have?
It was Cera.
Something that's with Cera for 365 days out of a year.
- A cell phone? - A scarf.
Her clogs.
Gosh.
She's always wearing them. She wears them every day.
Since it's the winter, I got her some fur ones.
(Decorating them to be Cera-style)
Here's "queen,"
and a crown that lights up.
(Exclaiming in delight)
I told you I wanted something that lights up!
Try them on, quick.
Please look forward...
to us together,
- Black Swan and White Swan. - Black Swan and White Swan.
Her handwriting is like a professor's.
(Time to read the letters aloud)
"From Ms. Funk, Secret Santa to Cera."
("From Ms. Funk, Secret Santa to Cera.")
- Just cry, since it's the end. - "Dear Cera,"
"I'm glad I'm able to tell you how I really feel"...
"as we prepare for our final performance."
"Even though you don't stand out within our crew,"
"you're the quietest and most reliable."
"Your role was to support the team, Cera."
"That was very precious,"
"and I'm even more grateful you were able to do that, Cera."
"I think it's such a blessing that I met you, Ha Eun."
- Yes. - That's right.
"I can't express in words how precious you are to me."
"We have a special relationship, you and I."
"I'm grateful and happy"...
"that you were there along my dance journey."
"From Cera."
"To one of the youngest members of MANNEQUEEN, our quokka,"
"we first met when we were both students."
"Now, I'm on TV with you and performing with you on stage."
"I'm so happy to be here with you."
"If you weren't part of MANNEQUEEN,"
"I wouldn't have been able to endure until now,"
"and I wouldn't have come this far."
"You went through a lot as the leader, right?"
(Crying)
"Thank you for always pointing us in the right direction gently."
"Every time I see you doing that, I think you're so impressive."
That's true.
She's right.
"I believe this is just the start for us, for MANNEQUEEN."
"I'm looking forward to where you lead us as our leader,"
"and let's do well in the future."
(Love you, MANNEQUEEN!)
You worked so hard.
We experienced a lot of hardship and a lot of adversity,
but it's because we went through all those things...
that we were able to get this far.
With every episode that passes,
we look happier and happier.
We were truly happy while we were dancing.
Ending Credits for MANNEQUEEN...
means a fresh start.
In that case, we want to end...
with our best performances, while we're having the most fun.
Something that will show how MANNEQUEEN will move.
We will show everyone a grand, flashy performance.
In 1, 2, 3.
(MANNEQUEEN, let's win this!)
Let's go!
("Express" by The Beautiful People, "Show Me How You Burlesque")
(This is a real show! A Vegas-style show that's hard to see in Korea)
(A performance showing MANNEQUEEN's diverse styles of dance)
(The end is another beginning! Curtains rise on MANNEQUEEN's show!)
This was the Ending Credits performance for Queen of Queens,
MANNEQUEEN, who are strongest and brightest when on stage.
As befitting a crew encompassing many genres,
their colourful styles created a rich performance.
They have gifted viewers with a happy and enjoyable ending party.
Fight judge Shownu,
what did you think of MANNEQUEEN's Ending Credits performance?
This performance showed what can happen...
when a crew with a diverse range of individual talents...
and personalities can come together.
I think this performance was the epitome of that.
I always tend to root for the ones who grow the most.
I think MANNEQUEEN is the crew that grew the most...
out of all four teams here.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you for your kind words.
MANNEQUEEN's leader Funky Y,
you've finally completed your last performance.
How do you feel?
I'm very happy.
We got to finals with difficulty, so if we got to perform,
we wanted to show a fun, energy-filled performance.
I'm not crying.
We wanted to show a fun, energy-filled performance.
It was an honour to give the ending performance of the show.
The audience's support and cheer...
made our performance very fun.
Thank you.
Street Woman Fighter 2 finalist,
MANNEQUEEN's performance came to an end.
Viewers who support MANNEQUEEN,
please send pound 0011...
a message that says MANNEQUEEN or number four.
MANNEQUEEN, thank you for your hard work.
(The queen of queens, MANNEQUEEN)
So that the crew you are rooting for can be the winner,
vote now.
Street Woman Fighter 2, the live finals.
The four crews' last mission,
Ending Credits came to an end.
Right now, the live text votes...
are being counted in real time.
In about two minutes, the live text votes will end.
If you haven't voted yet, please send...
the name or the number of the crew you are rooting for...
to pound 0011.
The live text votes near the end...
and the passionate support for the four crews continue on.
Apparently, the competition is neck-to-neck.
Not much time remains until the birth...
of the winning crew of Street Woman Fighter 2.
The vote you send...
will make 1MILLION, BEBE,
JAM REPUBLIC, or MANNEQUEEN...
the final winner that ranks first...
in the global dance scene.
The final mission performances of Street Woman Fighter 2 ended,
but things aren't over yet.
For the live finals,
special stages await.
(Special stages will be revealed soon.)
From the song to the dance,
the rookies' cheerful charms will shine.
The rookie class will give a performance of "Twerk."
The middle class will give a performance of "Swipe..."
that resembles a scene from a movie.
The sub-leader class will give a performance of "Click Like..."
with the dancers' charming group dance.
And there will be a song that still ranks high in charts...
and receives a lot of love since the day of its release.
BTS' Jungkook and V,
Taeyang, SEVENTEEN,
NCT, IVE,
ZEROBASEONE, actor Lee Sung Kyoung,
Jay Park, Lee Young Ji,
and many other celebrities participated in the dance challenge.
The leader class will give a performance of "Smoke."
Today, you will be able to check out the performances...
of the Class Mission...
that started the trend of Street Woman Fighter 2 challenge.
After the grand finale of Street Women Fighter 2...
that is the special stages,
the final winner will be revealed.
The final winner will be decided by the viewers' votes.
Which crew will take the throne...
in the global dance scene?
The live text votes will close now.
(The live text votes will close now.)
Five, four, three, two, one.
(The live text votes are closed.)
(TSUBA KILL's Rena took the center of the rookie class.)
(MANNEQUEEN's Waackxxxy and Yoonji led the middle class.)
(JAM REPUBLIC's LaTrice led the sub-leader class.)
(The heroine of the "Smoke" challenge craze, )
(BEBE's Bada led the leader class.)
(With explosive popularity, )
(Class Mission led to legendary performances.)
(Street Woman Fighter 2's legendary Class Mission)
(The special stages will begin now!)
(What does Street Woman Fighter 2 mean to you?)
To me, Street Woman Fighter 2...
is something that motivates me to live my life diligently.
It's a new challenge...
and a happy place.
It's the second life.
It's the last hope that made me shine once more.
Street Woman Fighter 2 is...
a big turning point in my life.
It made me clearly see...
who I was, how I danced,
and what kind of dance I wanted to show.
Once Street Woman Fighter 2 began airing,
I felt like I had received recognition...
as a dancer.
I just love to dance.
I think... That's kind of all I know.
And I love seeing people's reactions.
All I want is to make people feel some type of way...
through my movement...
and through how they feel when they watch me perform.
Yes, that's I want. I just want to make people...
feel some type of way when they watch me dance.
I didn't know there was such a big flame inside me.
Being on Street Woman Fighter 2 made me think,
"This was how much I wanted to dance."
"This was how much I wanted to avoid losing."
"This was how much I wanted to grow through challenges."
I realized that through Street Woman Fighter 2.
Through Street Woman Fighter 2,
I gained the members.
The teammates told each other, "We can do this."
We consoled and supported each other.
"We will do really well." When they gave me courage...
with confidence,
I felt, "So this is how it feels to have someone by my side."
Those moments made me feel that way.
I didn't know...
that I could dance so confidently before people.
I proved that to myself.
It made me so happy.
My cool seniors and colleagues made me realize,
"This is the mindset I should have when I dance."
"This is the mindset I should have toward dance."
I learned how precious dance was.
Also going against the stereotypes of, you know,
dancers being...
just the background people to the artist...
and showcasing that, you know, on Street Woman Fighter 2...
We are not only dancers. We are also the artists...
and the main act. And...
we can hold the stage ourselves on our own.
I think the show made people see...
that dancers could have various charms and talents.
(48 dancers united with their love for dance.)
(As an artist and the main act, )
(the 48 dancers will shine even more in the future.)
(Street Woman Fighter 2 will root for them.)
Find the number one crew in the global dance scene.
Street Woman Fighter 2.
All performances and live text votes came to an end.
There were No Respect, Battle with the Weakest Dancer,
Class Mission, K-pop Death match Mission,
Mega Crew Mission, Hwasa's New Song Preview Mission,
Battle Performance Mission, and the finals.
Thank you for your hard work.
1MILLION, BEBE,
JAM REPUBLIC, and MANNEQUEEN.
Between the four crews, the final winner will be decided...
by 20 percent of crew song performance vote...
and 80 percent of live text vote.
(Crew song performance vote and live text vote)
Let's start with the live text vote.
The total number of votes was 259,783.
We thank the viewers for their love.
Let's go.
Now, I will announce the final rankings...
of Street Woman Fighter 2.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
I will announce the crew that placed fourth.
The number four crew.
This crew showed their perfect skills...
and proved themselves as the master of performances.
With a strong fan base,
they received a lot of love from the public.
Which crew placed fourth?
Thank you for your hard work. It's MANNEQUEEN.
(4th place, MANNEQUEEN)
For the crew song performance vote,
MANNEQUEEN received 2,119,971 views,
98,816 likes,
and 175,192 votes.
They placed fourth in the crew song performance vote...
and received 170 points.
- MANNEQUEEN! - MANNEQUEEN!
(Crew song performance vote: 170 points)
(Live text vote: 650 points Total: 820 points)
As for the live text vote, they received 60,727 votes.
They placed fourth in the live text vote...
and received 650 points. With 820 points,
they placed fourth.
The leader of MANNEQUEEN, Funky Y, I am sure you felt...
many emotions on Street Woman Fighter 2.
Please tell us how it feels to place fourth.
I am very happy.
Until the finals...
I won't cry.
Until the finals, the team members stayed with me.
I want to thank them and tell them that I love them.
We love you.
I wondered when else we would receive...
so much love.
I want to thank the fans...
who love us a lot.
As for our team,
each member wants to say a word. Would it be okay to do that?
- Yes! - Yes!
All right.
Well...
I won't cry.
Firstly, I just want to say...
Without this show, MANNEQUEEN wouldn't have existed.
- That's a lie. - Thank you so much.
I can't stress that enough. Thank you.
Thank you so much.
I am so happy that we placed fourth.
I am so proud. I love the MANNEQUEEN members.
Producers and writers, thank you so much.
(Redlic, smile.)
Let's go.
Come on.
In the end, I cried on every single episode.
Thank you so much.
Thank you so much. Thank you.
All right. Firstly,
I want to thank the audience members who came to root for MANNEQUEEN...
despite the late hours.
And holding the microphone is making me want to cry.
Thank you for everything.
I am going to show you who the queen is!
Yes, you are the queen.
I want to thank everyone.
There is something personal I want to say.
When Street Woman Fighter 1 aired,
a close friend who was like a big sister to me got ill...
and ended up passing.
She told me that she wanted me to appear on this show.
I wanted to invite her here.
I think she gave me...
these five members to take her place.
To my cousin who went up to the sky,
I became a proud sister.
Again, I want to thank the crew members,
judges, and production crew.
MANNEQUEEN, thank you for your hard work.
(MANNEQUEEN is the queen.)
I will now announce the crew that placed third.
The number three crew.
With the explosive and energetic vibe,
this crew gave a strong performance for every mission...
and awed people.
Which crew placed third?
The crew that placed third is...
It's... Thank you for your hard work.
It's 1MILLION.
(3rd place, 1MILLION)
For the crew song performance vote,
1MILLION received 1,808,766 views,
135,209 likes,
and 200,500 votes.
They placed third in the crew song performance vote...
and received 180 points.
(Crew song performance vote: 180 points)
As for the live text vote, they received 61,665 votes.
They placed third in the live text vote...
and received 700 points. With a total of 880 points,
they placed third.
The leader of 1MILLION, Lia Kim.
Congratulations on placing third.
You must have felt many emotions throughout the challenges...
you faced on Street Woman Fighter 2.
Please tell us how it feels to place third.
On this meaningful competition,
we placed third. Members, thank you so much.
Thank you so much.
To be honest,
I have danced mechanically...
for a long time in the past.
I didn't know why I was dancing.
I was lost in that regard...
for a long period of my life.
But through the missions on Street Woman Fighter 2,
I got to know people...
who loved dancing so much.
Witnessing the dancers' passion on the show...
inspired me a lot.
So I earned the strength...
to enjoy dancing once more.
I am very thankful for that.
Thanks to this cool show,
we received an opportunity...
to show our cool performances...
and our cool sides.
So I sincerely thank the production crew...
behind this show.
1MILLION...
will continue to do cooler things...
in the future.
This isn't the end. Through future endeavours,
we will show who we are. Thank you.
1MILLION, thank you for your hard work.
Street Woman Fighter 2.
Now, only two candidates remain...
for the final winner.
They are BEBE...
and JAM REPUBLIC.
One of these two crews will become...
the final winner of Street Woman Fighter 2.
With each mission, they showed...
the best effort and performances.
BEBE and JAM REPUBLIC had a fierce rivalry.
Tonight, only one crew will seize...
the trophy.
Before announcing the result,
I will reveal the difference...
between the two crews' live text votes.
Between BEBE and JAM REPUBLIC,
the difference in the live text votes...
is 13,323 votes.
In the crew song performance vote,
BEBE placed second...
and JAM REPUBLIC placed first.
They had a neck-to-neck match.
Bada of BEBE.
How are you feeling?
All right. Firstly,
it's thanks to the support of many people...
who love BEBE that we had such a good result.
So we wanted to show a good performance.
Was it okay?
- Yes! - Yes!
All right. Thank you for giving us this good result.
Thank you for voting diligently.
Please continue to root for us.
Thank you.
And Kirsten of JAM REPUBLIC,
how are you feeling?
I feel very happy.
We, JAM REPUBLIC, had a really confident final show...
with our last piece.
And win or lose, we are still winners.
And we came here wanting to give you a show.
I hope you were inspired and loved our performance...
because we really gave it our all. And...
thank you for all the loving supporters,
the new supporters, our family and friends.
Thank you.
Kirsten is happy to be here.
Regardless of the result,
she thinks it was a good experience because she received...
inspirations from the dancers.
BEBE is led by Bada, the choreographer...
who is the most loved by K-pop artists.
It's a young-generation crew that captivated the Gen MZ.
In the Class Mission, they started the "Smoke" challenge craze.
By winning the K-pop Death match Mission...
and placing first in Hwasa's New Song Preview Mission,
they finalized their spot in the finals before any other crew.
JAM REPUBLIC is...
a global crew with the best dancers from different countries.
The leader, Kirsten is...
a well-renowned dancer who has taught Justin Bieber,
Rihanna, and Ciara.
Her participation in Street Woman Fighter 2...
became the talk of the town.
Their performance video of each mission...
received attention and love from around the world.
They proved that they were the world-renowned crew.
Now, BEBE versus JAM REPUBLIC.
I will reveal the winner of the two crews.
Street Woman Fighter 2, the final winner...
is...
(The final winner of Street Woman Fighter 2!)
It will be revealed soon.
(To be continued)
You waited a long time.
BEBE versus JAM REPUBLIC.
JAM REPUBLIC versus BEBE.
It's time for the final winner of Street Woman Fighter 2.
The announcement...
will be made by Monika, the fight judge representative.
Dancer who went beyond Korea...
and showed their passion and talent in the global dance competition,
thank you for your hard work.
At this moment,
BEBE and JAM REPUBLIC must be...
very anxious and nervous.
Either one of the two crews...
deserves to be the final winner.
Thank you for your hard work.
All right. I will make the announcement now.
Street Woman Fighter 2!
The final winner is...
It's...
I am scared.
Congratulations,
BEBE.
(The final winner, BEBE)
(BEBE, let's go.)
For the crew song performance vote, BEBE received 2,470,460 views,
195,782 likes,
and 845,026 votes.
They placed first in the crew song performance vote...
and received 190 points.
As for the live text vote, they received 75,357 votes.
They placed first in the live text vote...
and received the perfect score, 800 points.
With the total of 990 points,
they became the final winner of Street Woman Fighter 2.
BEBE received the honour of placing first in the global dance scene.
Congratulations again.
The final winner of Street Woman Fighter 2, BEBE...
will receive 50,000 dollars and a diamond ring.
(50,000 dollars and a diamond ring)
My goodness.
Bada of BEBE.
- Yes. - Firstly,
congratulations on winning.
Please tell us how it feels to be...
the final winner of Street Woman Fighter 2.
Please say a few words.
Firstly,
I prepared...
an acceptance speech.
But... Thank you.
To be honest, I didn't write it as an acceptance speech.
I just wrote it for everyone I was thankful for.
Yes.
So the moment we poured our everything into...
passed.
We are so thankful that we concluded the finals well.
To be honest, I never thought the end would come.
But the end came.
Participants of the eight crews...
LADYBOUNCE, Wolf'Lo, Deep N Dap, and TSUBA KILL too.
We love you.
We also love the four crews that prepared...
amazing performances for the finals.
You worked so hard.
I am very proud of all the dancers.
It was an honour.
Thank you so much.
Looking back, every moment and every performance was precious.
It was really an honour. Thank you.
And the production crew,
thank you so much. Thank you.
BEBE's mom and dad, Producer Da Yeon...
and Writer Ji Young, are you watching this?
Thank you for taking care of the seven timid members...
with a lot of worries until the end.
Since you made this cool stage,
we could dance in a cool way.
Thanks to the production crew and the show,
we are receiving so much love.
We want to thank the production crew of Street Woman Fighter 2.
Thank you.
Now comes the last part.
The ones who raised us to be cool, healthy, and cute women,
BEBE members' parents.
Are you watching this?
Are you watching this live? I hope you are recording this well.
Yes.
We decided to star in Street Woman Fighter 2...
because we wanted to be the daughters...
our parents and families were proud of.
(BEBE, congratulations.)
That was why we starred in the show.
We could keep that promise.
For that, we are really grateful.
And lastly, there are...
so many fans who love Street Woman Fighter 2.
Thank you for loving the crews.
Thanks to everyone who roots for BEBE,
we could dance well...
and win the trophy in the end.
To be honest, I think all the crews are winners.
I agree.
I truly think that.
Thank you so much.
Babies, thank you for following the leader.
Can each member say a few words?
- Yes! - Yes!
Ever since I began to dance, my family members...
believed in me, rooted for me, and loved me. My mom...
and my late grandma,
thank you so much. I love you guys.
I love you guys.
(Victory, come on.)
All right. Firstly,
it was an honour...
to meet and dance with the eight crews...
on Street Woman Fighter 2.
I want to thank my family members...
who rooted for me and supported me.
And...
As the youngest member of BEBE,
I will work hard. Thank you.
BEBE, thank you.
Unfortunately, we will have to stop here due to time.
BEBE, congratulations on winning again.
JAM REPUBLIC placed second.
(2nd place, JAM REPUBLIC)
For the crew song performance vote,
JAM REPUBLIC received 4,042,818 views,
288,529 likes,
and 745,843 votes.
They placed first in the crew song performance vote...
and received the perfect score, 200 points.
As for the live text vote, they received 62,034 votes.
They placed second in the live text vote...
and received 750 points.
With the total of 950 points, they placed 2nd...
on Street Woman Fighter 2.
The leader of JAM REPUBLIC, Kirsten,
please say a few words.
First of all, I just want to say thank you.
This is not a loss. This is a win in our eyes.
I want to first of all, say thank you...
all these amazing girls standing next to me.
We wouldn't have JAM REPUBLIC if it weren't for them.
So first of all, I would like to thank Nick and Ricks...
and JAM REPUBLIC's staff.
I would like to thank JAM REPUBLIC's crew...
that has been on this journey...
and all the staff members on Street Woman Fighter 2.
And again, our families, our supporters, our Jammies.
We wouldn't be standing here if it weren't for you.
Thank you for showing your love and support.
I hope you really felt something from us.
Because again, we didn't come here to win. We came here to show you...
what an international crew is all about.
I hope you take that and feel inspired by that.
So thank you guys so much.
And congratulations, BEBE.
We love you, Kirsten.
- We love you. - Kirsten thanked everyone...
and said it wouldn't have been possible without them.
JAM REPUBLIC, you worked hard until the end. Well done.
And there are people who accompanied the eight crews on their journey...
and gave them advice and respect from the closest place.
The fight judges, Monika, Shownu, and Mike Song.
You worked hard by watching all the missions and battles...
and evaluating them.
We thank you sincerely.
Street Woman Fighter 2 ends here,
but the passion and performances of the dancers who love to dance...
aren't over yet.
On Mnet Plus, the communities...
for 1MILLION, BEBE, and MANNEQUEEN will open.
Please pay attention to them.
A worldwide reality show about global life...
of the crews who commanded the Korean dance scene...
and their unexpected daily life behind the stage,
"Street Woman Fighter 2,"
"Worldwide Log" will be revealed through an OTT platform.
TSUBA KILL's performance for the Mega Crew Mission...
and the members' daily lives can be checked out,
so please look forward to the show.
And the Street Woman Fighter 2 concert, "On the Stage..."
will take place soon.
It will begin in Seoul on Friday, December 1...
and go to Busan, Daegu, Incheon,
Suwon, and Gwangju.
It will be a national tour.
And with the craze of Street Woman Fighter 2,
the dance battle of the female teenage dancers...
around the world will begin.
Among the female teenage dancers who love to dance,
the world-class dancers who will continue on...
the K-dance syndrome will be chosen.
Please look forward...
to "Street Dance Girls Fighter 2."
If JAM REPUBLIC doesn't win...
I am sorry.
Next week,
a show that captures the behind-the-scenes stories...
of the live finals and winning crew,
"Street Woman Fighter 2, Birth of the Winning Crew."
Please look forward to it.
Street Woman Fighter 2, live finals.
The dance competition that began in the hot summer...
came to an end with BEBE's victory.
So that there will be more stages...
that let the dancers enjoy themselves and grow,
so that dancers can shine on those stages,
please give your continuous attention and support.
This is where I say goodbye.
I am Kang Daniel, the host of Street Woman Fighter 2.
Thank you.
(1MILLION: An end is a new beginning.)
(Please look forward to 1MILLION's new beginning.)
(BEBE: It was the most dazzling moment of our dancing career.)
(BEBE will continue to move forward, to look forward to it.)
(Deep N Dap: We got Deep N Dap through Street Woman Fighter 2.)
(This is the beginning!)
(JAM REPUBLIC: We thank our families, friends, )
(and everyone who helped us with our journey on the show.)
(LADYBOUNCE: We became one through this best time.)
(One, two, three, we love you!)
(MANNEQUEEN: Long live the queen!)
(The queens' performance begins now.)
(TSUBA KILL: We cross borders and fought with dance.)
(Every second and every minute made us happy.)
(Wolf'Lo: Even in the future, we will only do what's cool. Wuff!)