(Street Woman Fighter 2, The birth of the winning crew)
(This program contains indirect advertisements.)
(Street Woman Fighter 2 was as fierce as ever.)
(The original resolution)
(Which crew will win and take the trophy?)
(Which crew will it be?)
(The final winner, BEBE)
(It was the birth of the winning crew...)
(on Street Woman Fighter 2!)
(I am jealous!)
(Congratulations.)
(BEBE had the honour of placing 1st in the global dance scene.)
(Again, congratulations.)
(The behind-the-scenes stories that came before this moment...)
(will be revealed now.)
Hello.
It's good to see you.
(The 8 crews meet up for the 1st time in a while.)
(TSUBA KILL came to Korea for the special stage.)
(It's so good to see you again.)
- I missed you so much. - Same.
How do I say, "It has been a while?"
- "Long time no see." - How do I say it in Japanese?
- Japanese? - "Long time no see."
(Peeking)
What? It has been so long.
(The 8 crews are excited to be together after a long while.)
- Hello... - TSUBA...
- Hello, - Hello,
- we are TSUBA KILL. - we are TSUBA KILL.
(We are back!)
It has been a while.
We are happy.
(They wear their name tags and get ready for practice.)
(JAM REPUBLIC and MANNEQUEEN couldn't join.)
It's our song.
It's the rookie class song.
(The cute, cheerful, and charming rookie class'...)
(behind-the-scenes stories for "Twerk" will be revealed!)
(Laughing)
(The rookies are happy looking at each other.)
Let's have an interview for the rookies.
(She suddenly becomes a host.)
Take turns and reveal what you ate today.
Koreans get strength from rice. I had sundae soup.
(Bibimbap)
Good job.
As for me,
I had the spicy pork soup...
and grilled mackerel.
All right.
So tasty.
Tasty.
The rookies will play the first impression game.
- In here... - Let's go.
In here, who will be number one...
- Number 1. - Number 1.
In terms of scariness when she is angry?
How do I say it in Japanese?
(interpreting right away)
(Redy is a great host who is good at interpreting.)
In here.
(Serious)
Three, two, one.
(Everyone picked a member except for Rena of TSUBA KILL.)
(My goodness.)
- She picked Yeni Cho. - Me?
- Me? - It's 2 to 2.
- It's 2 to 2. - It's 2 to 2.
- It's 2 to 2. - Is it 2 to 2?
- Is it 2 to 2? - It's a tie.
- Is it 2 to 2? - Really?
As for me,
I have no respect for you.
I will end all of you.
I am not scary at all.
(Showing a heart)
Round Two.
(The aspiring host moves on smoothly)
- Won't we reveal the reasons? - The reasons.
Things will get messy if we do that.
Okay.
- Next. - All right.
- In here, who is number 1... - Number 1.
in terms of not showering?
(In here, who is number one in terms of not showering?)
(What is this?)
- Three, - Right now?
two, one.
I can't do it.
(Rena doesn't know what to do.)
Look at me.
I am wise. I picked myself.
Hey.
Even if things get messy, I want to hear the reasons.
(Truth lies beyond.)
(The pouting mode is on)
- What? - She is angry.
- I see. - I feel victimized.
I feel victimized.
(The rookies are close as always.)
Shake your hips.
- Do we go out? - Out.
(The sub-leader class is busy practicing.)
(Dancing)
(It's an addictive dance that makes Akanen dance along.)
(Catching everyone's attention)
I got this.
(Glancing over)
(Absorbed)
My glasses are about to fall off.
I really like this dance.
LaTrice is the best.
(Camera zooms in on Biggy who is practicing diligently.)
What?
This is insane.
Don't film her. She is Busy.
She is Busy.
She isn't Biggy.
She isn't Biggy, but Busy.
- I am Busy. - Everyone wears heels.
(Many dancers shy away from the cameras.)
I came without wearing makeup...
because they said there wouldn't be cameras.
This is too much.
- Let's enjoy it. - Let's enjoy it.
Only Bada can do this move.
(Only Bada can do this move.)
(Hopping)
(The short members are jealous of Bada's height.)
I can never hit her.
That's right.>
(Their coolness explodes.)
My goodness.
(What caught the rookies' eyes?)
(Lia Kim and Mina Myoung dance as a duo.)
I am tearing up. What should I do?
My goodness.
What is going on?
(What caught the rookies' eyes?)
(Lia Kim and Mina Myoung dance as a duo.)
I am tearing up. What should I do?
(I am tearing up. What should I do?)
(This is so touching.)
What is going on?
This is too much.
You danced in sync with Lia Kim.
Of course.
- Even with my eyes closed... - You guys looked...
the same from the back.
Even with my eyes closed, I can dance in sync with her.
- Of course. - You guys were teammates.
- So I didn't practice in advance. - Really?
(Laughing)
(They practice the duet dance on site.)
(Years passed, but their bodies remember it.)
(We are all for this combination.)
(They wrap up with the decalcomania dance.)
- We have good teamwork. - How do we have such good teamwork?
(They find it funny.)
I danced with Mina earlier...
for the first time in a long while.
Both of us were surprised because we had good teamwork.
There she is.
- Go ahead. - I can copy you.
- Really? - From the back...
I will copy you.
(Funky Lia's dance move from the past)
- Let's see the original. - Here.
- The original dancer, let's go. - Let's go.
- Let's go. - Let's see it.
She remembers it.
(The dancing machine)
(The past memories make these oldies happy)
You make this facial expression when you do the robot dance.
(Her facial expression is as intense as her dance move.)
When you do the robot dance...
That's right.
She does that.
- She does that. - That's right.
(Doesn't she look the same?)
- That's insane. - She does that.
When the two of you danced,
you were really in sync.
- Really? - Yes.
We need to film this.
- Mina, we need to film this. - What?
Why are you doing this?
It's yoga.
(Why are you doing this?)
It's like you are in the living room.
(Lia and Mina are similar in this way too.)
Excuse me, you will get sick if you sleep here.
- Please don't sleep here. - Gosh.
(The behind-the-scenes story ends with a drunk.)
- Another class. - Excuse me.
- We are a team. - We have a class.
Do you know who our leader is?
It's Baby Sleek.
- Are you jealous? - I suddenly feel reassured...
right now.
- Come on. - Our leader.
- Come here. - She is our leader.
Another class.
(The members with no class stick together.)
(While the classes are practicing)
I am cool too.
- Cool. - Cool.
(They are cool.)
We are like losers.
(A loser)
Let's make a cool dance.
- Let's make something. - Seriously.
Seriously.
- Hello, we are... - Hello, we are...
- New Class. - New Class.
Our leader.
(A new class appears.)
We are New Class.
- New Class. - New Class.
- We are... - We are in another class.
- We are a newbie group. - We are a newbie group.
We will make an Instagram account.
Please give us a lot of love.
- Please give us a lot of love. - Please give us a lot of love.
(Please look forward to New Class.)
Shall we take a selfie?
(A selfie time is a must even during practice.)
Let's go.
(More crew members join.)
- Seriously. - Ahem.
The male version of Capri and Redy.
- The middle-aged man version. - The middle-aged man version.
What do you think?
- Let's see. - What?
I want a photo of the whole group.
It looks like a solo photo of this person.
(Her sexiness captivates attention.)
- Look at her facial expression. - The Gen Z way...
is not looking at the camera.
That's right. They take a photo like this.
You looked at the camera, so you aren't a Gen Zer.
Next.
Since there are many people in here,
I receive energy even when I am standing still.
One, two, three.
Yes.
Hello.
I need to learn Japanese to talk to Akanen.
- I know. You can speak English. - I need to learn Japanese.
I lost my English skills.
(I lost my English skills.)
(The dancers are busy learning Japanese.)
It's a Japanese class.
(These dancers are determined to learn Japanese as well.)
Big sister.
- Big sister. - Big sister.
(Something isn't right.)
Obachan.
- Obachan. - Obachan.
It means "Aunty."
What was that?
(She got attacked in a foreign language.)
Don't do that.
This isn't a mission that comes with rankings,
so I am having fun practicing.
And other leaders...
are having fun practicing.
My goodness.
I think that's the case.
Step and push.
(What are they doing?)
(The slick back challenge is popular among the dancers.)
(The hip-hop style slick back challenge)
(Fancy)
(Everyone tries the slick back challenge.)
(She just runs.)
(The relay slick back)
(Awkward)
(What is this?)
(Baby Sleek's slick back dance)
She is good.
(Fancy footwork)
Everyone is insane!
(Everyone is insane about the slick back challenge!)
(Panting)
I am doing this more diligently than the leader class' performance.
(Here is the result of crazy practice!)
(Did they succeed in the slick back challenge?)
(They gather around and watch the challenge video.)
Seriously.
It's a big mess.
- It's a big mess. - The messy slick back dance.
Thank you for your hard work.
(The rehearsal ends on a happy note!)
(One day before the live finals, the day of pre-recording)
- Hello. - Hello.
HI, guys.
It's game day.
Mum mum mum mah
I wanna hold 'em like they do in Texas, please.
(Audrey Gaga gives a special performance.)
What is a roasted chestnut seller doing here?
(A roasted chestnut seller in BEBE's waiting room?)
My mom gave me roasted chestnuts.
(Roasted chestnuts delivery)
She really was a roasted chestnut seller.
And I will distribute this gift.
(Bada's 2nd gift, multivitamins)
(The baby birds cheer.)
(Bada is busy feeding the baby birds of BEBE.)
(It's tasty.)
(Thanks to Bada, they have a hearty breakfast!)
Go ahead and eat.
That's so funny.
- Seriously, Lia. - What?
You look like 23.
- I look like 23? - Yes.
I love it.
(Lia left behind 16 years.)
(Gazing at the camera)
I didn't know pink and glitter would enter my life.
It's awkward for you to see me like this too, right?
Please support my new attempt.
I am...
wearing a pink fuzzy outfit.
They're all laughing. You're giving them a hard time.
Don't hold your laughter.
Just laugh.
Life is about laughter.
Laughter brings you good luck.
(MANNEQUEEN is focused on practicing.)
- Should we try that again? - Yes.
(The heat of the queens make it look like a real stage.)
I saw this at Doota in Dongdaemun.
I saw a crew performing this at Doota.
(All 4 crews are ready for the rehearsal!)
BEBE, please get ready for the dry run.
- The floor is okay. - It's perfect.
(BEBE checks the floor first so they don't slip.)
I think we should try laying out the mat.
(They prepare the stage so they don't make any mistakes.)
Soweon and Kyma,
you will have to kneel with just your knees on the mat.
(They are ready.)
Let's go. Let's kills this.
Let's go.
(BEBE is on high power mode as soon as the rehearsal begins.)
(Cute)
(They finish the performance without missing a single look in the eyes.)
Okay, thank you.
(The youngest member brings the leader water.)
(But she fails in opening the lid.)
Thank you.
(BEBE monitors the rehearsal thoroughly.)
(Watching closely)
(Focused)
We should be more aware of our facial expressions.
I think Lusher should add something more...
instead of what you just did.
It looks too flat.
Soweon, you can't miss the beat.
You cannot do that. That's a huge mistake.
(Shaking)
(Today's ending fairy is Tatter, who is shaking.)
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - Good job, everyone.
We really put a lot of effort in this performance.
It's the long-awaited finals.
Yes, even in our outfits. We're cowgirls.
Our outfit piques your curiosity, doesn't it?
Guess what our concept is.
Cowgirls.
Next is MANNEQUEEN.
- Can you slightly move to the side? - Yes.
(Carefully)
I love it, Buckey.
One, two, three.
(They constantly practice for a perfect rehearsal.)
(Groaning)
(The queens are already exhausted from the strenuous practice.)
(Funky Y gets smaller.)
(They finally start their dry run after endless practicing.)
(Powerful)
(The energy of a queen explodes on MANNEQUEEN's stage.)
(Lady MANNEQUEEN)
Thank you.
- She passed out. - Thank you.
(The energy of MANNEQUEEN seems to penetrate the screen.)
We look like Science Ninja Team Gatchaman.
- We kind of do. - My hand is so chubby.
I think you should slightly bend it.
- Thank you for the hard work. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- What if we do this? - Let's do this.
- Let's do this. - We can't show our faces.
This is our poker face.
Do you think you will win?
- Yes. - Yes.
We'll win first place if we get our faces ready.
- That's right. - We're the winners.
- Okay. - Let's win.
- Let's go, MANNEQUEEN. - Let's go.
Hey.
Hi, guys. Welcome to our channel.
Please like and subscribe.
This is JAM REPUBLIC's stage.
We're feeling very exhausted, but so excited...
and can't wait for our family, fans, friends, and supporters to see...
JAM-yonce's performance.
So stay tuned.
(Stay tuned.)
(Walking away)
The "W" is so cool.
(JAM REPUBLIC takes photos before the rehearsal.)
My gosh. We have to take a photo right here.
Just go like...
- you're... - Look fabulous.
There you go.
It's going to blow up.
Do you think you could...
Okay, legs.
LaTrice.
(However, they become serious when the rehearsal begins.)
(The hat Beyonce is known for)
(Red fabric)
(JAM REPUBLIC did a good job preparing the props.)
(The energy of the five members fills the stage.)
(Powerful)
That's good. Thank you.
(Emma is still excited even after the rehearsal.)
We've been going through war.
And now we're here in the final war.
We're always winners.
It's cool to see 1MILLION on the screen.
We were...
in Yeoju just a while ago.
- Already... - Already...
- It's the Finals. - It's the Finals.
What happened to your pants?
I must've practiced too hard and burned a hole in them.
It's proof I worked hard.
Today's challenge...
is to make sure this rhinestone doesn't get caught in my hair.
That means I constantly need to control my fingers.
(Watch me.)
("7 Rings" with its alluring charm and restrained dance moves)
("Bang Bang" that shows an unexpected charm)
That's it for the rehearsals.
(It's over.)
What do you think?
How did the rehearsal go?
The rehearsal?
We monitored it,
and I love the outfits, hair, and makeup.
I love it.
It goes well with the songs.
I think our performance will go well with it.
- I'm looking forward to it. - Me too.
Let's go.
1MILLION.
(Cute heart)
(Fail!)
(They leave in a hurry.)
Do I look like a rookie?
I wanted to dress like I did in the music video,
but I couldn't find it.
So I modified the outfit.
(Why is Redy of 1MILLION dressed as a rookie?)
- Hello. - Hello.
(Very excited)
Why do all the members of BEBE look like Haechi Wang?
We're all Haechi Wang.
(Bechi Wang comes together with Dr. Wang's style.)
(I am Minchi Wang.)
What's with your hair?
- What do you have here? - You'll look cuter than I am.
What's this heart?
Excuse me. Why do you look shocked?
It's because you look cute.
- Are you going with the sexy look? - Yes, totally.
- Is this your sexy look? - Yes, I'm the queen.
You're the queen?
I think you need to take more clothes off.
(I think you need to take more clothes off.)
(Squealing)
Oh my gosh.
We're taking a photo. 1, 2, 3.
(They start practicing the special stage where they all become one.)
(They are perfectly in sync.)
Good job, everyone. Watch your step when you come down.
It's spectacular.
I was moved when I saw it.
It's special to end it with a performance together.
It will be a lasting memory.
I wasn't here for a while.
I'm happy that everyone looks like they're in pain.
(This is the relaxed attitude of the person that left.).
Everyone seemed jealous of us.
We're happy we were eliminated.
- It's just the beginning for us. - That's right.
Let's go. You really look tired,
so I hope it brings you that much of a good result.
- I love you. - I love you.
I am rooting for all the crews.
Anyone, win.
(It doesn't concern her.)
Show some love for Deep N Dap.
Let's go.
Go.
- One, two, three. - Let's go.
(The middle-class rule is to pull their hands out in the middle.)
(The performance begins with the cheers of the audience.)
(It starts with the 16 dancers in the middle class.)
(Sub-leaders)
(Rookies)
(Leaders)
(And the final highlight)
(The performance of "Smoke" by all 48 dancers)
(A special stage created as they all came together.)
(This is so exciting.)
(I love you.)
It's over.
That was so fun.
(Global Artist Mission performance, First crew is MANNEQUEEN)
Are you nervous?
I'm always nervous.
But... I'm nervous.
I'll do a good job.
(The queens constantly practice before going on stage.)
(They get excited.)
- This is the last performance. - Let's go.
(They encourage one another!)
- Let's have some fun. - Let's go.
It's the last performance.
(The first performers are nervous as the audience cheers for them.)
(It's time to show the anticipating crowd what they prepared.)
(MANNEQUEEN's reinterpretation of Lady Gaga begins.)
(Their intro pose captivates the audience.)
(MANNEQUEEN's performance adds excitement to the air.)
(MANNEQUEEN did what they always do!)
(MANNEQUEEN doesn't forget to thank the audience at the end.)
(1MILLION runs into MANNEQUEEN, who just finished performing.)
- Good job. - That was good.
That intro was insane.
Lady Gaga.
It was amazing.
(We did a good job, didn't we?)
The audience went totally crazy.
It was the perfect performance to bring out the best in us.
- Seriously. - They're the best.
Bye.
Seriously. This is the final stage. It's our last mission.
- Have fun. It's okay to mess it up. - It's okay to mess it up.
- So just have a blast. - Okay.
It's okay to make mistakes.
(Behind Lia Kim who's watching MANNEQUEEN's performance, )
(Harimu is already getting ready to have a blast.)
(Here's Lady Rimu.)
MANNE Gaga.
(Instead of getting nervous, 1MILLION is enjoying it.)
(Copying the ending pose)
(I'm not afraid of the final stage as long as there's music.)
- I, Lia Kim, am single! - I, Lia Kim, am single!
(Make some noise!)
(1MILLION can be a group of playful zoomers.)
(But they are professionals who become serious on stage.)
(They know when to have fun and work hard.)
(The almighty 1MILLION)
(They finish their performance on a cheerful note.)
(1MILLION)
- Good job. - Good luck.
It felt liberating,
and I was overwhelmed with this touching moment.
It was such a good experience. It was a good experience. Thank you.
What? Bye.
Good luck!
(Tapping)
(This is the sound of BEBE's practice backstage.)
(BEBE's routine before the stage, practicing endlessly)
But we have to burn it up.
Right. Then why don't you come with me for a second?
- Soweon and Kyma should go. - Okay.
- Cheche and I will go on this side. - Okay.
(What is this suspicious object BEBE prepared?)
(BEBE used the coloured powder as their props.)
(They go up to set the stage before their performance.)
(What are they doing?)
(Fidgeting)
(Setting it up thoroughly)
(We're so busy.)
- Hey. - Don't be nervous. Be yourself.
(They beat up their bodies to loosen up.)
This is our final stage. Let's do it. In 1, 2, 3.
- Let's go! - Let's go!
(With their thorough preparation, )
(BEBE delivered a flawless performance.)
(Meanwhile, they enter backstage with an unusual look.)
(They turn the other crew's song into their entrance song.)
(JAM REPUBLIC seems at ease.)
(Although they're performing Beyonce's song today, )
(they're enjoying Rihanna's song as well.)
(Exploding with excitement backstage)
Last time. Love you, girls.
Live your life. Three, two, one.
- Beyonce. - Beyonce.
- Crazy. - Crazy.
We're about to bring it to you.
(They get ready to perform after chanting a diva spell.)
- You ready to go? - No.
- Right now. - Let's go.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
- Love you, girls. Let's go. - Let's go.
- Love you all. - Come on.
(Let's do this.)
(As they're the last to go, they give the audience a festival.)
(With their explosive energy, )
(They finish their performance.)
(Watch the full version on "The CHOOM.")
That's a wrap, baby. JAM-yonce.
I can cry now.
Stay tuned.
(The 4 crews finish recording the performances.)
- Jammies! - They're all from Jammies.
(Making a heart for their fans)
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- It's okay. - Korean Jammies. Love you.
I love donuts.
- Is that my favourite? Tteokgalbi? - Let me see.
(The food has been delivered for the three crews.)
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(Thanks for the food, it's a festival for everyone.)
- Cheers! Let's go! - Cheers! Let's go!
(Harimu's mother and aunt show up.)
You get why I'm so loud, right?
I'm not loud. I just have a booming voice.
I was born with healthy vocal cords.
- You don't have to worry... - Now I know...
- because... - where she gets her booming voice.
(She has her mom to thank for the DNA.)
(They suddenly start competing who has the most booming voice.)
(Rebecca)
(Amy's brother)
I support all the crews.
Good luck!
- Yes! - Go!
Last one!
Good job, everyone.
- You were the best, ma'am. - Thank you.
(Their long day before the final stage comes to an end.)
It's 10:27am now.
It's the day of our final mission. How do you feel?
I'm suddenly doing an interview.
I can't wait until midnight.
(Desperate)
I want to transport through time, so everything would be over.
We've been working hard for the past six months for this.
To think that there's only one day left,
it feels surreal.
Regardless of that, I must do my best...
because we want to win first place.
- We'll win 1st place. - We'll win 1st place.
I wonder if the other dancers are on their way.
Hello.
I'm Yoonji of MANNEQUEEN.
It's the morning...
of the live show for Street Woman Fighter 2.
You know, live broadcasts come with a certain type of pressure.
There will only be one live broadcast.
So it's very nerve-racking.
Let me give you a small spoiler...
regarding our crew's outfit on my way to the TV station.
Take a look. We have rhinestones on our outfit.
And this too. We have more decorations on our outfit.
(She was showing us these pants and this top.)
So our outfit is ready now.
Today is the day of our final mission.
(It's a sunny day too.)
- We have a coffee truck. - It looks good.
They sent us a coffee truck.
Thank you so much.
We really needed coffee. This is the best.
(What else do the dancers need before their final mission?)
(A warm bowl of ramyeon in the morning)
The morning ramyeon.
MR.
(MR means morning ramyeon.)
MR. That's it.
- Has Dohee arrived? - I think so.
Gosh. She's already here.
- Are we leaving now? - Yes.
Just like this?
(Dohee? We're not done yet.)
I'm Dohee.
The members of my crew are sleeping soundly.
I'm going to rest up until we arrive too.
(Bye.)
(How is it going at the studio before the final rehearsal?)
(Kirsten's version of "The Final Countdown" by Europe)
(This is how Playful Kirsten prepares for the final mission.)
Hi, guys.
Today is the Finals.
And I'm feeling excited and mixed emotions.
But it's going to be great...
because we're going to dance for our family, our friends,
our Jammies, and our supporters.
So thank you for being with us on this journey.
And we hope to make you proud.
(Kirsten is excited.)
(Meanwhile, Audrey is trying to style her hair.)
(Shy)
(Step 1: Fix her bangs with a hairpin for a second.)
(She's a bit clumsy.)
(Step 2: Gather her back hair and tie it up neatly.)
(Not leaving a strand of hair behind is the key point.)
(Looking neat)
(Audrey ties up her hair neatly.)
(Step 3: Curve her bangs across her forehead.)
(Step 4: Is she done once she fixes her hair with hairpins?)
Why is it so hard?
(Will her hair stay fixed?)
(Messy)
(Emma fails to hold back her laughter.)
(I will start again.)
Does anyone have hair spray?
(Super focused)
How hard is it to do this simple piece?
It's taking me forever.
(Is she finally done?)
(No! This isn't what I want.)
(She's never satisfied with her hairstyle.)
(Inhaling sharply)
(It's time for the endless battle against the rubber band.)
(It's finally starting to look better.)
(Fixing the wig that she will attach on the back of her head)
(Careful)
(Glancing)
This is confusing.
(Can you help me?)
Can you just give me a plain one?
(Experts blame the tools.)
(She finishes styling the wig with a new device.)
(Step 6: Attach the wig on her hair, and then that's it!)
(She's satisfied.)
(The dessert tastes sweet for those who accomplished their goals.)
(Crunchy)
(Audrey's do-it-yourself hairstyling session is over.)
All right. Let's start JAM REPUBLIC's camera rehearsal.
(Her hair stays fixed despite the intense choreography.)
(JAM REPUBLIC treats their rehearsal like a real performance.)
(They safely finish the rehearsal.)
(They thoroughly check their footage too.)
(They take their performance more seriously than any crew does.)
Even Emma. If you just do one.
(Kirsten goes over detailed feedback for everyone.)
I think it gets better.
The producers all loved it. And it was perfect.
- All of them. - See? We worked together.
Thank you.
- Yes. Thank you so much. - Thank you.
Good work.
Thank you. I was like...
Could you take a photo of us?
(JAM REPUBLIC wants to remember this moment with a photo.)
So pretty.
(Clicking)
Thank you.
It's still on.
(A posing genius)
(After their performance, they become playful.)
(May this journey be remembered as the most passionate days.)
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(Another crew wants to remember this journey with photos.)
This really is our final mission.
(Crying)
- Who will take the rug? - Me!
- Can I take the sofa? - Great.
(How will I say goodbye to the show?)
Bye, hideout.
- Bye. - Bye.
It's been fun.
Let's do our final run-through.
(BEBE prepared a performance using masks.)
(Bada looks uncomfortable.)
(They aren't able to connect their moves smoothly.)
(In the end, they stop the rehearsal for a moment.)
Here's some pain reliever.
- How does it feel? Are you okay? - My knee felt like...
it suddenly twisted this way.
(Her knee joint was strained due to powerful movements.)
(She tries spraying a pain reliever to soothe the area.)
Okay.
- Are you all right? - Yes, I'm fine now.
(Bada doesn't show her pain to keep the rehearsal on track.)
We should get you more knee pads to stabilize the knee.
(She declines the extra pads in case they interfere with dancing.)
Should you ask for emergency medical treatment?
- But it's... - You shouldn't wait to get treated.
(In the end, she wound up leaving to get emergency treatment.)
Thank you.
Oh, no.
(BEBE decides to suspend rehearsal until they see how she recovers.)
(Can BEBE safely complete their live performance?)
- Please come up on stage. - Let's go!
- Hello. - Hello.
Good luck!
She wished us good luck.
- Good luck, 1MILLION. - We're so grateful for that.
Let's warm up, girls.
(How 1MILLION warms up)
(Isn't it easy?)
Look at that angle.
(It's not a deep-rooted tree, but a Harimu tree.)
The headstand is the best warmup for the rehearsal.
(Gathering energy for victory through her toes)
(What did 1MILLION prepare just for this performance?)
You have to put this on your chest...
and do it.
I'll try it afterwards.
(A mysterious, white powder?)
You have to put a lot of it on.
(What is this powder that they're piling on?)
- You lift this up to release. - Let me try.
(An ambitious prop prepared for 1MILLION's final performance)
(Did you see it when it aired?)
(The actual live performance)
(The white powder erupted with a powerful jump.)
(Her nose tickles.)
This performance isn't good for one's bronchial tubes.
I was really worried about how much of the powder would be visible,
depending on the lights and the camera angles.
But they adjusted to us using it, so I think it will come out well.
What do you think? How did it go in rehearsal?
- I think it's good. - I feel like I performed my all.
Just do it like that.
- It's good. - Just do it like in rehearsal.
I think all we have left to do is get our makeup on.
- All you need is makeup? - Yes.
- Compared to now... - It'll help us express ourselves.
Just go all natural.
(This is really all natural.)
- As we are. Born to be dancers. - Right.
(Is there another dusty party on the rehearsal stage?)
- Hello. - Hello.
- We're MANNEQUEEN. - We're MANNEQUEEN.
Today is the long-awaited finals.
(A flashy rehearsal to be performed with feather boas)
(Feathers float in the air.)
(The feathers are proportional to the flashiness of the dance.)
I swallowed so many feathers.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
I have three mics right now, so I'll do an interview now.
Which crew does MANNEQUEEN consider its greatest rival?
Our greatest rival?
Honestly, all three crews are so good,
I just hope we perform well with no mistakes and no injuries.
However, MANNEQUEEN will still aim to win.
(MANNEQUEEN will aim to win.)
- Get it up. - Are you ready?
Samba.
(Waackxxxy also leaves, maybe exhausted from rehearsal?)
(BEBE also finishes their rehearsal after recovering from the injury.)
- Seriously... - We have an hour and a half left.
(Darkness has descended on the studio.)
Oh, no.
I feel weird.
To think Street Woman Fighter 2 ends today...
It seems like a lie.
By tomorrow,
- all of this... - It will all be over.
may seem like a dream.
I was really happy to be here.
I consider it a turning point in my life.
I consider it a huge turning point.
As episodes 8 and 9 aired,
I increasingly felt...
that I didn't want it to end. I kept thinking that.
I wanted to keep doing more fun things.
I think it's too bad that it's over.
I really gave it my all.
I'm happy it's over,
- but I also think it's too bad. - You feel relieved but regretful.
The time just flew by.
- That's true. - The first shoot felt so recent.
Now what will I do?
We rushed here in a frenzy,
and now only the Finals are left.
I find that hard to believe.
But what is this?
Is this for us?
- It's nothing? - It's flipped over in a scary way.
(A suspicious card on the table looks familiar.)
(What is this card?)
(To be continued)
But what is this?
Is this for us?
- It's nothing? - It's flipped over in a scary way.
(A suspicious card on the table looks familiar.)
It's nothing?
(It's nothing.)
Then why did you put it here? It's scary!
Wait a minute.
Is this a new mission?
We just flipped over the card that we gave you earlier.
- I see. - That was good.
- Gosh, seriously. - Imagine getting a new mission.
In one hour...
(Screaming)
Just an hour...
Just an hour before a live broadcast.
(Trembling)
They'll ask us to come up with a new performance.
Street Woman Fighter 2 has made us this way.
- That's true. - Just by putting this here...
- It's not even surprising. - It's just suspicious.
To think we're all scared of this one piece of paper.
Seriously, a piece of paper can mean everything.
You've worked hard to make it all the way to finals.
(Clapping)
- Bravo. - We worked very hard.
Today's totally D-day.
It's almost time.
- Is that why you're trembling now? - I'm so nervous.
She's talking with her leg.
I'm so nervous.
I'm not as nervous as I thought I would be today.
(Buckey's in a different class.)
Instead, I feel...
like a weight's been lifted off my shoulders.
I just want to perform well today.
- You practiced hard, considering. - True.
You'd say, "great job," then practice again.
So I won't make any mistakes.
I think a lot of people came to watch.
- Was it 1,000 people? - Yes.
It's the biggest audience yet in Street Woman Fighter 2.
I think we'll draw a lot of energy from the audience.
- That's true. - For today.
I'm really looking forward to it.
- We're doing what we do best. - That's true.
Let's have a refreshing performance,
and have a refreshing beer after.
Let's wrap up in a refreshing way.
- In a refreshing way. - Yes.
What a journey.
All we have to do is dance once.
It's the Finals.
(It's really the end.)
This is the last interview we'll do.
I'm so happy this is the last interview I'll do.
I'm so bad at interviews.
I think...
(What is it?)
We've been through a lot of stressful things together,
and even though you've all seen me at my worst,
you're still here. You didn't abandon me, and I'm thankful.
(Audrey cautiously reveals her true feelings.)
I always had my little thing.
I like to freestyle. It's whatever.
Literally, when I filled out my paper...
- "It's whatever." - When I filled out...
- "Whatever." - my paperwork...
When I filled out my paperwork, and had to write in weaknesses,
I wrote, "dancing in a group."
(Really?)
I didn't know that this was a group thing.
(The profile Audrey wrote for their first meeting)
("My weakness is that I can have difficulty blending with groups.")
(But after meeting the members of JAM REPUBLIC, )
(Audrey realized working as a group could be precious and bring joy.)
That was very meaningful to me.
- Audrey. - Gosh.
(Audrey, the shy youngest, shares how she feels about the members.)
(Kirsten holds her hands without a word.)
(Kissing back)
And remember, you're 19.
And you're amazing. Incredible.
(Embarrassed)
This is just the beginning.
- JAM REPUBLIC! - JAM REPUBLIC!
(These dancers gathered with the same love for dance.)
Fight!
- Let's go! - Let's go!
(Doing something "together")
(Achieving something they "like" together)
- To our beloved 1MILLION, - To our beloved 1MILLION,
- good luck, 1MILLION! - good luck, 1MILLION!
(Shall we take a look at the shining final chapter?)
(Just 5 minutes before the Finals go live)
(The audience members suddenly start to cheer.)
(The fight judges enter.)
(They're so popular.)
(Judge Monika's refreshing fan service)
(Looking flashy)
(Next up is Mike Song.)
(I can feel your passion, 200 percent.)
(Taking off his jacket due to the heat in the studio)
(Cheering passionately)
(Sending hearts)
(All three fight judges sit down.)
We will now begin our dance battle.
(The live broadcast of the Finals has finally begun.)
They've begun.
(The 4 finalist crews wait in real time in their rooms.)
It's coming on screen.
Okay.
- It's 50,000 dollars. - I want it.
(Another prize, diamond rings)
They look so cool.
- Hey. - Look at that style.
- Now I want to win. - I want that.
I would've worked harder if I knew I was getting those rings.
(Actor Kim Bo Sung was caught on camera.)
(Even the BEBE babies recognize this man of "loyalty.")
- Loyalty. - Loyalty.
- Loyalty. - Loyalty!
Earlier, I took a photo with "loyalty" man's wife.
- Did you like that? - Yes, I did.
He said, "my wife's a big fan."
(The dancers relieve anxiety by laughing a lot.)
Loyalty!
(Back Koo Young came as a spectator to cheer on the dancers.)
(Discovering a familiar face)
- It's Back Koo Young. So handsome. - He's so handsome.
- He really is. - What's he doing there?
(MC Kang Daniel introduces the final performances.)
(The End Credit Mission)
(1MILLION heads backstage.)
Everyone, hands.
(They carefully put on the white powder they prepared.)
- Let's go. - Let's go.
Don't get hurt, since this is your last one.
Yes.
(The experienced MC Kang cheers them on between emceeing.)
(1MILLION shouts their final cheer.)
I love you, 1MILLION.
Let's win, 1MILLION.
Whether we win or lose, let's go!
(The full cam version of 1MILLION's End Credit Mission)
("Natural" by Imagine Dragons, choreo by 1MILLION)
(A performance showing the dancers' will...)
(to focus on the present despite starting on the fringe, )
(breaking the biases dancers hold towards 1MILLION dancers)
1MILLION!
(1MILLION finishes their last dance for Street Woman Fighter 2.)
(The members comfort one another first.)
- You did a great job. - We did great.
Don't be sad.
- You did great. - I'm not crying.
I was so happy while dancing.
I felt so refreshed.
I feel so light now.
(The next crew to go up is BEBE.)
(Her hand is on her prop, and her eyes are on 1MILLION.)
No crying.
(Here, they're trying to control their emotions before performing.)
(They finally shout their final cheer.)
- In 1, 2, 3. - Let's go!
- I love you all. - I love you. Let's go.
(The full cam version of BEBE's End Credit Mission)
Let's go, BEBE!
(Expressing the idea, "only those who are prepared can escape dark,")
(this performance changes "Ending" to "And-ing," expressing darkly...)
(that BEBE's dance will go on.)
(Bada)
- Thank you. - Go, BEBE!
- BEBE! - BEBE!
(BEBE wraps up impressively for their final performance.)
- It's over. - That's insane.
It went by in a flash.
Why are you crying?
(Cheche started tearing up as they walked backstage.)
You all worked hard, and I love you!
- I love you. - Come here.
(Love you, BEBE!)
(The third crew up is JAM REPUBLIC.)
Come on, it's the last one.
(I'm nervous.)
(Squealing)
(Kirsten practices until the last moment.)
- Last cheer in 3, 2, 1. - Put your hands in.
- JAM REPUBLIC, let's go! - Let's go.
Let's go.
(JAM REPUBLIC's final performance for Street Woman Fighter 2)
(JAM REPUBLIC's End Credit Mission, the full cam version)
("Jele" by DBN Gogo, Sino Msolo, Kamo Mphela, Young Stunna, Busiswa)
(A performance showing the identity of JAM REPUBLIC as a crew...)
(with various backgrounds coming together for a common goal, )
(and their tenacity, perseverance, and grit in overcoming hardship.)
(JAM REPUBLIC comes off stage cheerfully.)
We did it!
It's done!
(The leader, Kirsten, tears up for a moment.)
Why are you doing that?
We did it.
(Now that their journey's over, memories flash through their minds.)
In 1, 2, 3.
- JAM REPUBLIC! - JAM REPUBLIC!
(The final crew to go up is MANNEQUEEN.)
- Funky Y. - You look so pretty today.
(Waackxxxy waits for their turn.)
(Tapping)
(Suddenly tapping her rear)
I'm sorry. That was your butt.
- I like it. - I'm used to it now.
- We're so comfortable now. - Yes, totally.
- We're family now. - We're family.
Let's have fun, okay?
- Let's do it! - Let's show all we have this time!
Now, in 1, 2, 3.
- MANNEQUEEN! - MANNEQUEEN!
(Let's go do MANNEQUEEN'S Ending Show.)
(MANNEQUEEN's End Credit Mission, full cam version)
("Express," "The Beautiful People" and "Show Me How You Burlesque")
(A Vegas-style show never before seen in Korea!)
(Showing a happy "ending" with MANNEQUEEN's diverse styles)
("Once the curtain rises, MANNEQUEEN's real SHOW starts!")
(Watch the full versions of the End Credit Missions...)
(on "The CHOOM.")
(MANNEQUEEN dazzled as Street Woman Fighter 2's Ending.)
We won't cry.
- We did a great job. - No, don't cry.
I was really happy.
It was really fun.
We did really well. MANNEQUEEN is the best!
(Everyone shouts the final countdown together.)
- In 5, 4, 3, 2, 1. - In 5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
- It's over. - That's it!
(The live audience voting is over.)
- Let's go! - Let's go!
- Let's go! - Let's do this!
(The dancers applaud the approaching ending.)
- Go. - You did a great job.
- Yes! - Go!
- Jump! - Jump!
- Let's go! - Go!
- It's the last part. - Everyone's so excited.
You're wearing such a pretty outfit.
Can you do "Smoke" in that?
(While the "Special Performance" filmed earlier is being played, )
(the dancers have prepared a live dance for the audience.)
(The "Special Performance" Class Mission Medley, live version)
(Lia Kim)
(After all finals performances are over, including these)
It's MANNEQUEEN.
(MANNEQUEEN comes in 4th.)
(1MILLION comes in 3rd. Once these are revealed...)
- Gosh. - You're here.
- You worked so hard. - You worked so hard.
- You worked very hard. - Thank you. You worked hard.
It's not important that we came in third place.
We still worked hard.
- We were in the top three. - We...
And we tore it up in the Finals.
Please look forward to seeing us in the future.
(These leaders went through the same thing on different crews.)
Don't cry.
- You went through so much. - We really did.
You did such a great job.
(The two of them cheer each other with a warm hug.)
Congratulations, BEBE!
(The long-awaited crew to take home the final victory)
(As soon as the winner is announced, the dancers all congratulate them.)
I'm so proud of you.
- Congratulations. - You're so cool!
BEBE did it.
- They really did it. - They did it.
It's over.
I'm happy!
- Is there something else? - Happy.
You all worked so hard.
- You all worked so hard. - Thank you.
- You worked hard. - You worked hard too.
You worked so hard.
We really went through a lot.
What's wrong? Don't cry.
(Lia Kim bursts into tears at her friend's consolations.)
- It was really great. Don't cry. - Don't cry.
- Don't cry. - Don't cry.
Don't cry. You did great.
- You did really great. - You were great.
- Don't cry. You did well. - You did great.
(After the live broadcast of the Finals is over...)
(Bada is feeling a thousand emotions sweep through her.)
Everyone on Street Woman Fighter, you all worked very hard.
(She shows her gratitude to everyone who has supported her.)
(And they thank and say goodbye to...)
(those who they competed against until the end.)
- Please leave in an orderly manner. - Thank you.
Thank you for your hard work.
(Redy, a member of a competing crew, greets Bada warmly.)
Congratulations.
(A happy ending full of strong congratulations)
(Bada conveys her feelings to her fans as well.)
Bye.
Congratulations.
I knew someone from Daegu would do it.
I knew you could do it.
A congratulations hug?
(The dancers convey congratulations, knowing what they went through.)
It's over!
- It's over! - Yes.
- Congratulations. - Thank you.
We won!
(The youngest, Soweon, shows off their victory rings.)
- Let me see. - Here they are.
What is that?
- It's cute. - It's really pretty.
- It's so pretty. - Let's switch.
- It's so pretty. - It fits her perfectly.
Isn't it pretty?
Thank you to everyone who loved our show.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
I'll never forget this experience.
- LADYBOUNCE! - LADYBOUNCE!
Street Woman Fighter 2 was everything in 2023.
(Everyone was great!)
See you at the concert!
(Putting the days of laughing and crying behind them)
I'm taking the photo now.
In 1, 2, 3.
(They take one last group photo.)
Thank you for your hard work.
(1MILLION returns to their dressing room.)
We tore it up!
I'm so happy!
(A last dance of joy)
(The baby sub-leader, Harimu, is still feeling the after-effects.)
If you want me to be quiet,
you just have to let me end something.
I get really quiet when that happens.
I'll be loud again starting tomorrow.
(Today, she'll cry, and tomorrow, she'll be loud again.)
We're all done.
- Hi. - Hi.
It's Matthew.
I just wanted to say I'm a big fan.
I was wondering if I could get you guys' signatures.
My gosh!
Your accent. You've got a strong...
- Yes. - A Canadian accent.
- I knew it! - You're Canadian?
Yes, I'm Canadian.
In 1, 2, 3.
(They take a nice group photo.)
If it's possible,
can we do the challenge?
- Yes. - Yes!
(Han Bin and Matthew did the Class Mission challenge.)
(They dance together beautifully to the rhythm.)
Let's go!
- That was great. - Thank you.
(JAM REPUBLIC and ZEROBASEONE did a nice joint performance together.)
(Zhang Hao and Kim Tae Rae came to MANNEQUEEN's green room.)
- Make a crown above your head. - A crown?
Crown is actually the theme of our new single.
- Perfect. - That's great.
Thank you!
(They took a group photo while exchanging words of encouragement.)
- Thank you. - I want to do something with Cera.
Me?
- Go ahead. - What is it?
- In 5, 6, 7, 8. - In 5, 6, 7, 8.
(They're killing it with Cera's signature move.)
Awesome!
You did it!
- My wish just came true. - Thank you.
Thank you.
- Thank you. - Take care.
(BEBE celebrates their victory with their friends and family.)
(Nam Ji Hyun came by their green room.)
You guys did such a great job.
It was an honour to watch you dance in person.
- Gosh. - My.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- Thank you for coming. - Thank you for coming.
Congratulations!
(Congratulations on your win, BEBE.)
Go, BEBE!
- Go, Ji Hyun! - Go!
(Everybody has left, and BEBE is alone in the room.)
We've received so much love...
and won a title that's more than what we deserve.
What I really loved...
is that through the series,
we were able to record our growth which will last forever.
I really loved that.
(At the pre-production meeting)
We haven't done this kind of...
competition show before,
and we're worried that we may not be able to survive.
(None of the crews expected BEBE to win.)
(People's critical views and harsh words)
Why are they doing this show?
(They were a crew that seemed to have more flaws than strengths.)
(However, )
(they surprised everyone during the No Respect Battle.)
(They proved their talent during the Class Mission.)
(They pushed their limits during the K-pop Death match Mission.)
(They overcame the crisis together during the Mega Crew Mission.)
(The New Song Preview Mission and Battle Performance Mission...)
(were new challenges for them.)
It's been such a wonderful journey,
and we've grown so much.
We also ended up making such a valuable achievement.
I'm just so grateful.
Cheche, Soweon, Kyma, Lusher,
Tatter, and Minah. Thank you for following my lead.
I couldn't have made it without you guys.
I'll be better.
Stick with me forever.
- Yes! - Of course!
We won first place!
(We won first place!)