Using
the art of Purple Star divination
to fulfill
the Emperor's destined wishes.
I pray for the power of stars to protect our great Tang Dynasty.
I humbly beseech heavenly grace
to grant the Emperor ten more years of life.
Your Majesty, what's wrong?
Your Majesty!
Your Majesty! Your Majesty!
You
must
pay!
The evil concubine has brought disaster to our nation.
She should be forced to become a nun and banished to the Cold Palace.
Order the Imperial Guards
to thoroughly investigate these evil deeds.
Assemble! Assemble!
Hurry!
The case of the stolen Xuanyuan Mirror
must be solved within ten days.
The purpose of this mission
and your identity as Imperial Guards
must not be revealed.
Once you find the Xuanyuan Mirror,
return to the capital immediately
and do not engage in unnecessary combat.
If you fail to find the Xuanyuan Mirror,
bring your heads when you return.
Here.
Dismissed.
Yu Jianying.
I'm here, sir.
Ying'er.
Please speak, Foster Father.
Within the imperial court,
there have always been criticisms about female soldiers in the Jinwu Guard.
If you can accomplish this mission,
you will surely silence those critics.
You must not disappoint me.
Moreover, among the Jinwu Guard,
you are the top expert in tracking and pursuing criminals.
I'm counting on you this time.
I will not fail your expectations.
Guards!
Go check over there.
Yes, sir.
The mirror thief's tracks
disappeared at the entrance of the Governor's mansion.
Could someone from the Governor's mansion be responsible?
Officer,
may I ask why there's such a commotion inside?
Today the Governor is hosting a banquet
to welcome Ambassador Hawule from the Western Regions.
No unauthorized persons allowed inside.
So this is the Governor's mansion.
I've been looking everywhere but couldn't find
my invitation.
Officer, please verify this.
So you're an honored guest of the Governor.
Forgive me.
Daniu!
Miss.
Please.
Thank you.
I've been traveling for days without a proper meal.
Time to enjoy some good food here.
Governor Fang.
I'd like to toast you.
You've gone to such great lengths
to entertain our delegation.
Hawule is deeply grateful.
To you.
It's nothing worth mentioning.
Come,
let's drink to our heart's content today.
Bottoms up!
Cheers!
Come, have another!
I heard the dancing girl you're presenting to His Majesty
is of exceptional beauty
and extraordinary dancing skill.
We've never had the privilege to see such Western beauty.
Might we have the honor of seeing her?
That's no difficulty at all.
At Governor Fang's request,
Hawule wouldn't dare refuse.
Guards!
Bring her here.
Go now!
Yes, sir.
She'll be here shortly.
Look, look!
How graceful!
Indeed!
Such figure!
Truly extraordinary!
Marvelous!
Look, look!
Look at her figure, her hands,
those movements!
Wonderful!
Excellent!
Stop right there!
You brazen thief! Drop your weapon!
There's a path in heaven you refuse to take.
Yet you insist on breaking into hell where there's no door.
Of all places to flee,
you chose Bingzhou.
Today, even with wings, you cannot escape.
Listen, you petty judicial officer,
your monthly salary is just a few taels.
Why risk your life
chasing me for three days and nights?
I only stole 5.4 taels of silver.
Is it really worth all this?
Wu Ming
How dare you!
I am hosting important guests.
And you've brought your thief-catching right into my residence.
Governor, sir,
this man is a serious criminal wanted by the court,
the notorious thief Minglang.
I have been tracking him for half a year.
If I have disturbed you,
please accept my apologies.
Ambassador, please don't be alarmed.
This is Wu Ming, a judicial officer of my prefecture.
This young man is quite talented.
He came to Bingzhou last year.
He has solved many cold cases.
Thief Minglang,
if you don't want to add another charge to your crimes,
release that dancing girl.
Then please order your men to let me go, Governor.
Then I'll release her.
You're still running.
Wolf.
You've been running for three days and nights.
Aren't you tired?
What Wolf?
I told you my name is Phantom Thief Mingwolf.
Phantom Thief Mingwolf.
I call you that because it's easier.
Stop running.
Why don't we take a break?
What do you mean easier?
You'd better...
Xuanyuan Mirror.
Thanks, miss.
Still running!
Zhao Wentao
Producer
Co-Producers
Weng Linjue, Ren Wei, Lu Gaofeng, Liu Chao, Shi Mingming, Chen Guanhua, Li Jiayi, Yao Mingxing
Executive Producer
Wen Wanliang
Chief Producers
Chen Bin, Liu Xiyang
Production Team
Writing Team
Directing Team
Art Department
Sound Department
Styling Team
Stills/Behind the Scenes
Set Team
Lighting Team
Action Team
Cast
Leading Actors
Special Guest Stars
Starring
Nian Chong
Jin Wu
Yu Jian
Extras
Zheng Mukun, Cai Zhenhua, Wang Kunzhun, Zhang Qingjie, Xie Zhunyu, Tong Guiyou, Hu Zhongyu
Guo Wei, Yang Mingjin, Hu Hesheng, Deng Qinzhun, Wang Junwei, He Yaxiang, Zhu Maoga
Wang Wenyang, Zhang Zhonghai, Deng Wenchao, Chen Yudi, He Zizhun, Jin Zongxin, Xu Yanfu
Li Suiming, Li Jie, Tan Xin, Guo Wei, Meng Chongzai, Tong Guiyou, Wang Junwei
He Qiuling, Zhao Yabo, Wei Zongyan, Wang Jingjing, Zhao Dongxue, Luo Qin, Chi Jiayi
Su Jianchang, Wang Wei, Wang Guoan, Wang Shengze, Ya Bo, Li Wenwen, He Jun
Luo Xiao, Zheng Kun, Li Yuqing, Bi Sifan, Zhen Shangxing, Chen Kou, Wang Qingrun
Zhang Xiaoting, Xu Yan, Yao Jieyi, Chen Mengyue, Leng Hui, Chen Xiaodi, Wang Junjie
Tian Dong, Han Haotian, He Yuke, Wu Shajin, Zhang Qilang, He Zijun
Acting Team
Management
Post-Production
Jiaming
Zuoshang
Mingshang Jiazuo (Beijing) Film and Television Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Hao Zhen
Zhang Dong
Guo Yan
Tong Zhi
Ultra HD Production Company
Beijing Youwei Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Jieshi Xiaoyao
Zhou Dian'ao
Chen Qiao
Wen Miaoqin
Li Ding
'Truth Breaker' (End Credits Song for 'Tang Detective: Youth in Prosperity')
Zhang Ruofan
Casting Company
Starlight Power Film and Television Culture Media (Beijing) Co., Ltd.
Yin Shitong
Assistant Director for Actors
Xi'an Film Media
Publicity Team
Beijing Weiye Shisui Film and Television Co., Ltd.
Production Companies
Xiangshan Xiangrong Film and Television Culture Co., Ltd.
Shaanxi Huashang Film Industry Co., Ltd.
Hangzhou Mingjue Cultural Creative Co., Ltd.
Zhejiang Randian Era Film and Television Media Co., Ltd.
Shanghai Suzihe Film and Television Media Co., Ltd.
Mingshang Jiazuo (Beijing) Film and Television Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Starlight Power Film and Television Culture Media (Beijing) Co., Ltd.
Beijing Youwei Culture Media Co., Ltd.