Li Chong, remnant of the former dynasty,
has been on the run until now.
Refusing to repent,
he robs households,
steals from gentry,
his crimes are heinous.
Sentenced to be executed at noon.
The time has come.
Proceed with execution.
Kneel down.
Kneel down now!
What's happening?
Is someone trying to rescue the prisoner?
Execute him immediately!
Why is the wind so strong?
Go
identify the body.
Yes, sir.
The coroner has confirmed the identity.
The prisoner is indeed dead.
Very good.
Come help here.
It's all my fault.
My fault.
This is not your fault.
Don't take it to heart.
Let's hurry up.
Don't delay the funeral arrangements.
What took you so long?
If you had come any later,
I would have suffocated to death.
How long has it been since you took a bath in prison, Wolf?
You stink.
Try being locked up in the imperial prison for a few days.
I am a bit smelly.
But it smelled quite nice in the coffin.
I thought it was my natural scent.
You're still laughing?
I was nearly scared to death.
Li Chong.
I'm sorry.
Why are you suddenly apologizing?
I'm fine, aren't I?
However,
it would have been better if you had given me a heads-up.
If we had given any warning,
your head
would have rolled.
The time has come.
Proceed with the execution.
Kneel down.
I said kneel!
What's going on?
Is someone trying to break up the execution?
Execute immediately!
Wuming
Miss Yu
You two saved my life.
Though I, Li Chong, am of noble birth,
I understand the principle that even a small favor
deserves great gratitude in return.
From now on,
I will stay by your side.
I'll face whatever enemies come,
and overcome any obstacle.
I'm willing to serve you both faithfully
with no regrets.
Wolf
When did you become so serious?
I'm not used to it yet.
What are you saying?
Haven't I always been serious?
It's about time to leave.
I don't want the authorities to know
that I'm hiding a dead fugitive in my home.
Mr. Xu,
thank you for your help.
Thanks to you today,
I was able to escape unharmed.
No need to thank me.
If Wuming hadn't blackmailed me
about killing my sister,
I wouldn't have helped.
What?
You killed your sister?
Mr. Xu,
you don't need to pretend anymore.
Actually, Miss Xu
is not dead.
You...
What nonsense are you talking about?
Didn't you replicate
all my methods of murder?
I...
I've already confessed to the murder.
Don't protect me
just because I helped you.
It's rare to see someone so eager to claim the title of murderer.
I'm asking for your help, Mr. Xu.
Actually, I wanted to verify my deduction.
What's wrong?
Is there a problem?
This smell...
I understand now.
Among the debris that hit Miss Xu's box
there was a strange odor.
It's the same as
what we smelled last time in the secret room
at the paper craft shop.
This corpse
looks somewhat familiar.
It's that demon.
How did he end up dead here?
I knew it.
How could anyone be impervious to weapons?
This has the same smell
as the corpse Mr. Xu used to replace Li Chong.
What do you mean?
The same smell?
How does that prove Miss Xu isn't dead?
These bodies
all have one characteristic:
they don't decompose for days.
If my deduction is correct,
this smell
must come from a preservative
unique to the Xu family,
which can slow down the decomposition of corpses.
There's really no smell of decay
but rather a faint scent of medicinal herbs.
So what if there is?
My Xu family, as a lineage of morticians,
naturally has our own embalming compounds.
That's right.
It would be fine if it was just elsewhere.
But why
is there the same smell on Miss Xu's
damaged trunk?
That can only mean one thing.
That trunk
already contained a preserved corpse
with its face deliberately destroyed.
You mean
the dead person
was a corpse hidden in the box beforehand
not Miss Xu?
That's right.
Miss Xu must have
used the moment when the box fell toward her
to hide among the funeral procession.
Nonsense!
This is merely your speculation.
Where's your proof?
What evidence do you have?
Brother Xu.
Is your finger bothering you?
Is it because something is missing?
Brother Xu.
This finger guard belongs to you, doesn't it?
No.
Executive Producer
Producers
Yu Runde, Ren Hailong, Xie Zhenggang, Jin Ruting
Co-Producers
Weng Linjue, Ren Wei, Lu Gaofeng, Liu Chao, Shi Mingming, Chen Guanhua, Li Jiayi, Yao Mingxing
Xu Zhongyan, Song Hongmei, Xiao Nan, Meng Yaoyue
Coordinator
Producer
Wen Wanliang
Executive Producers
Chen Bin, Liu Xiyang
Production Team
Writing Team
Photography Team
Sound Team
Styling Team
Stills/Behind the Scenes
Lighting Team
Action Team
Cast
Starring
Special Appearance
Main Cast
Extras
Zhang Weilong, Li Jie, Tian Yinghua, Wu Shajin, He Yuke, Li Shuang, An Xuechao
Zheng Mukun, Cai Zhenhua, Wang Kunzhun, Zhang Qingjie, Xie Zhunyu, Tong Guiyou, Hu Zhongyu
Guo Wei, Yang Mingjin, Hu Hesheng, Deng Qinzhun, Wang Junwei, He Yaxiang, Zhu Maoga
Yin Zhenzhen, Jing Xiyou, Zhou Xiaohui, Liu Wenfei, Zhu Fuhui, Pan Xuelian, Wu Shajin
Li Suiming, Li Jie, Tan Xin, Guo Wei, Meng Chongzai, Tong Guiyou, Wang Junwei
Su Jianchang, Wang Wei, Wang Guoan, Wang Shengze, Yabo, Li Wenwen, He Jun
Luo Xiao, Zheng Kun, Li Yuqing, Bi Sifan, Zhen Shangxing, Chen Kou, Wang Qingrun
Li Yang, Shi Yanmin, Yang Furong, Pang Youdan, Li Yilin, Li Jinqin, Qin
Tian Dong, Han Haotian, He Yuke, Wu Shajin, Zhang Qilang, He Zijun
Post-Production
Jiaming
Zuoshang
Mingshang Jiazuo (Beijing) Film and Television Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Zhang Dong
Ren Wen
Tong Zhi
Ultra HD Production Company
Beijing Youwei Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Jieshi Xiaoyao
Zhou Dian'ao
Zhang Yating
Chen Qiao
Hu Chunyu
Li Ding
Starlight Power Film and Television Culture Media (Beijing) Co., Ltd.
Cast Coordinator
Assistant Director for Cast
Guo Changzhi
Xi'an Film Media
Publicity Team
Beijing Weiye Shisui Film and Television Co., Ltd.
Production Company
Shaanxi Xi'an Film Digital Media Technology Co., Ltd.
Xiangshan Xiangrong Film and Television Culture Co., Ltd.
Shaanxi Huashang Film Industry Co., Ltd.
Co-producers
Shaanxi Baishang Industrial Co., Ltd.
Zhejiang Randian Era Film and Media Co., Ltd.
Shanghai Suzihe Film and Media Co., Ltd.
Baibaohuai (Xi'an) Technology Co., Ltd.
Starlight Power Film and Television Culture Media (Beijing) Co., Ltd.