So the mastermind behind all this
is you,
Fang Daming,
Governor Fang.
Congratulations.
You got it all right.
Don't you feel all the mysteries have been solved?
A sense of sudden enlightenment.
I don't understand.
Why did you do all this?
What's your purpose?
If you really want to know,
then submit to my command,
use your talents,
and help me achieve greatness.
Then,
you'll understand how great my cause truly is.
You call killing innocent people
a great cause?
Success is built on the bones of many.
Great achievements require sacrifices.
Even our Emperor
stands on the bones of countless soldiers,
and his own two brothers
died by his blade.
Only then
could he build such a prosperous empire.
So,
you want to use the Puppet Formation
to destroy our Tang Dynasty?
Not at all.
I want to revitalize our great Tang.
Nonsense!
Our Tang Dynasty's prosperity
cannot be achieved through such evil means.
What utter absurdity!
It seems that clever mind of yours
needs more time to come around.
No matter.
I'll wait patiently for you to change your mind.
The Chosen One.
I am the Chosen One.
How would you like to deal with him, sir?
Kill him.
We can't kill him yet.
I still have important use for him.
There are only a few days left
until the full moon ritual begins.
Starve him for these few days.
I don't believe
that after days without food or water,
he'll still be so stubborn when the time comes.
Come on.
How about it?
Want some?
Let us know when you change your mind.
Otherwise, once you're starving,
it'll be too late to regret.
Who cares?
In a few more days,
he'll die of thirst if not hunger.
Come, brother, have a drink.
Come, drink up.
Drink. Keep drinking.
Come.
Wuming
How are you feeling?
You haven't eaten for a long time,
you can only have plain porridge now.
Do you know
breaking someone out of prison is punishable by death?
I know.
Then why did you still do it?
Disrupting an execution
and replacing a condemned prisoner are also capital offenses.
If you can sacrifice so much for me,
why can't I do the same?
Besides,
I'm already a dead man.
Have you ever heard of a dead man fearing death?
Let me do it myself.
How did you know
I was imprisoned by the Imperial Guards?
You went to the Imperial Guards headquarters
to report the case and look for Miss Yu.
If I didn't go to the Imperial Guards to find you,
should I have gone to the Wannian County office instead?
Oh!
You've gotten smarter this time.
After being with you all for so long,
if I still didn't understand what 'water on the left,
flour on the right' means,
then my head would truly be filled with porridge.
I didn't know you were coming,
please forgive me for not greeting you properly.
Drinking while on duty?
You two must be tired of living.
We wouldn't dare.
The Commander ordered us
to eat and drink in front of that prisoner called Nameless
to break his spirit.
Yes, we weren't being lazy.
We were following the general's orders.
So that guy is indeed imprisoned here.
Very good.
The Commander
specifically sent me to reward you two.
Here.
So?
I'm impressive, right?
But anyway.
I've been at the Imperial Guard camp
but couldn't find any trace of Lady Yu.
I find this suspicious too.
Lady Yu's disappearance
must be connected to those evil people.
I just never expected
that the Imperial Guard Commander
would be working with them.
It seems we can't enter the Imperial City now.
Enough.
Stop being mysterious.
I know you already have a plan, don't you?
You really do know me well.
Could you please lower your voice?
This is a sacred Buddhist place.
Nonsense.
Try staying up all night without sleep.
Abbot,
this is Master Xu Yan from the paper craft shop,
and these two behind him are his assistants.
Thank you for your help, sir.
Please come in.
Abbot,
this is...
Last night, while the nuns were performing evening prayers,
something strange happened.
A person appeared walking to this spot
and turned into a pile of bones.
The temple is full of nuns,
and we dare not touch such impurity.
We only ask that you come to collect the remains.
Why not report it to the authorities?
To be honest with you, sir,
the nun in the meditation hall last night
was Master Mingyue,
who has a special status.
And these bones are dressed in imperial robes,
though they are just theatrical costumes.
If we report this to officials,
it might damage Master Mingyue's reputation.
I must trouble you, Mr. Xu,
to collect these remains as soon as possible.
Please keep this matter confidential.
You truly are prescient.
We have to rely on your skills as a phantom thief.
Executive Producer
Producers
Yu Runde, Ren Hailong, Xie Zhenggang, Jin Ruting
Co-Producers
Weng Linjue, Ren Wei, Lu Gaofeng, Liu Chao, Shi Mingming, Chen Guanhua, Li Jiayi, Yao Mingxing
Xu Zhongyan, Song Hongmei, Xiao Nan, Meng Yaoyue
Chief
Supervisor
Wen Wanliang
Executive Producers
Chen Bin, Liu Xiyang
Production Team
Writing Team
Photography Team
Sound Recording Team
Styling Team
Stills/Behind the Scenes
Set Team
Lighting Team
Action Team
Cast
Starring
Special Appearance
Main Cast
Crown Prince
Featured Actors
Jin Wu
Extras
Zhang Weilong, Li Jie, Tian Yinghua, Wu Shajin, He Yuke, Li Shuang, An Xuechao
Zheng Mukun, Cai Zhenhua, Wang Kunchu, Zhang Qingjie, Xie Chuyu, Tong Guiyou, Hu Zhongyu
Guo Wei, Yang Mingjin, Hu Hesheng, Deng Qinchu, Wang Junwei, He Yaxiang, Zhu Maoga
Yin Zhenzhen, Jing Xiyou, Zhou Xiaohui, Liu Wenfei, Zhu Fuhui, Pan Xuelian, Wu Shajin
Li Suiming, Li Jie, Tan Xin, Guo Wei, Meng Chongzai, Tong Guiyou, Wang Junwei
Liu Guangcheng, Wang Fugui, Xiao Jie, Tian Ye, Liu Xiaofei, Mei Zhuotao, Ren Yong
Su Jianchang, Wang Wei, Wang Guoan, Wang Shengze, Ya Bo, Li Wenwen, He Jun
Li Yang, Shi Yanmin, Yang Furong, Pang Youdan, Li Yilin, Li Jin, Qin Wu
Tian Dong, Han Haotian, He Yuke, Wu Shajin, Zhang Qilang, He Zijun
Post-Production
Jiaming
Zuoshang
Mingshang Jiazuo (Beijing) Film and Television Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Zhang Dong
Tong Zhi
Ultra HD Production Company
Beijing Youwei Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Jie Shi Xiaoyao
Zhou Dian'ao
Yu Deliang
Zhang Yating
Chen Qiao
Hu Chunyu
Li Ding
Vocal Producers: Ling Yuqian/Xu Zhewei
Starlight Power Film and Television Culture Media (Beijing) Co., Ltd.
Casting Coordinator
Assistant Director for Cast
Guo Changzhi
Xi'an Film Media
Zhang Ning
Publicity Team
Beijing Weiye Shisui Film and Television Co., Ltd.
Production Companies
Shaanxi Xi'an Film Digital Media Technology Co., Ltd.
Xiangshan Xiangrong Film and Television Culture Co., Ltd.
Shaanxi Huashang Film Industry Co., Ltd.
Co-Production Companies
Shaanxi Baishang Industrial Co., Ltd.
Zhejiang Ignition Era Film and Television Media Co., Ltd.
Shanghai Suzihe Film and Television Media Co., Ltd.
Baibahuai (Xi'an) Technology Co., Ltd.
Starlight Power Film and Television Culture Media (Beijing) Co., Ltd.