It got a lot of chase, the shifts and
You really go fishing with me.
A belter?
A belter.
So you'll catch me long.
Hey...
Time is over.
Welcome back.
Only Shiting's
only my skirt.
Milk
Mash
No Yi
She can beat No Yi, who is ranked third.
Is she really...
You lost. Give me back the glasses.
Play another round with me.
No Yi, you can lose if you play again.
Are you trying to play tricks?
Do you want it?
Come and take it.
You...
It doesn't matter.
You can play tricks when you get drunk.
I'm also an extension and...
I know everyone knows Zhang of the pro-cu round.
I had some strength to really beat her.
I'm sorry.
Luo Yixian
You lost to him
It seems
You can't leave him alive
I won't let you touch him. I haven't played enough
Leave him to me
I'll handle the charity poker contest
Okay
I'll go to the toilet
Jingjing
Let me do it
Jingjing, I was wrong last night
I did gamble in the Sun family's casino
But there is a reason
Brother Hao Ying, of course you have a reason
But don't tell me, I don't want to hear it
Jingjing, Miss Sun said
She can give us a gold card
Enough
Brother Hao Ying
Can you stop gambling for yourself?
And
About the gold card
Mr. Peng has already helped me do it
What?
You went to see Mr. Peng again?
Mr. Peng is not a good person. Don't be fooled by him
I don't know if Mr. Peng is a good person
But I know
You are definitely not a good person
You will become like my father one day
Once you bet on this thing
There is no turning back
Jingjing, I
Hello
I am Lawyer Jin Dazhuang
You should know me well
I won't introduce myself
I am here to be entrusted by someone
To deliver the copyright of the gold store
The copyright of the gold store?
So fast
This person doesn't look like a lawyer
Is it fake?
A career is not a matter of status
Who said a lawyer can't ride a bicycle?
This is called low carbon environmental protection
What are you doing?
It's really the gold store
What's up Jingjing?
Mr. Peng
Someone just sent the copyright of the gold store
Thank you Mr. Peng
What is this? Who am I?
An important partner of the Sun family
What's the point of a small store?
I promised you
I will definitely do it
I promise you
I earned the store
How did it become yours?
You earned the gold store?
Jingjing, don't believe her
She is a liar
Brother Haoyun
Now it's Mr. Peng who helped me get the gold store
You said he is a bad person
What do you mean by going gambling behind my back?
Jingjing, gambling
This is not good
Don't you know that Jingjing hates gambling the most?
This kind of person is not worth your attention
Remember
Leave it to me
Jingjing
Do you know what to do?
What are you doing?
Don't hit him
It's okay
I'm doing it for him
Do you understand?
You have to hit him once
Do you think he will gamble next time?
No
Let's see if our hearts are not good
Go
I
Wait for me to send the evidence to Jingjing
See what she says
See
This is the bargaining chip your little restaurant has been mortgaged on me
You owe me a lot
You can take it
Take it
Remember
If you want to play again, go to me
I won't make it difficult for you in our relationship
I'm sorry
Jingjing, I'm doing some thinking work
President Peng, I'll give you a ride
Good luck
You are hurt
It will be better if you get some ice
Thank you
Who is that Jingjing?
You actually do so much for her
Maybe we crossed the boat secretly
I was drowned on the beach
I was injured on my head and I can't remember anything
Jingjing didn't care about the money and insisted on taking me home
They gave me a good name according to the information on the boat ticket
Jingjing doesn't dislike me for stealing and playing black magic
She gave me food and shelter and paid me
I don't know how to repay her kindness
Then you should make up with her
Not what you think
Miss Sun, I always want to apologize to you
I'm sorry for making you angry last time
But I still want to know
You hate gambling so much
Why do you have to find someone to take part in the charity poker competition?
She is so sincere
Tell her my thoughts
Maybe she will help me
Only by winning the charity poker competition
I can take back the right to run the gambling factory
And cut the family's gambling business
The gambling is not just about money
But also their family and life
My parents are also...
Miss, the car is here. We can go
Give me a pen
Take it
This is my personal number
I don't care what you think
But I really hope you can help me
Miss, are you interested in this boy?
I'm afraid of the police
You know I hate gambling
I...
I'm just using him
Yes, you are so beautiful
How can you like him?
But you haven't seen anyone for so many years
Miss, since he doesn't want to help us
I will go to see Mokun
Ok
But I have a way to make him help me
But if Mokun can go out
We will have double insurance
Yes
Great
Congratulations
Thank you
Welcome to the gambling factory
Congratulations
Come on, brother
Mr. Peng Sai
Come on
Please
Stand here
Mr. Peng Sai
Dad, Mr. Peng Sai invited you here
You can stay here
But after the ceremony
You will go back to your restaurant
Don't see me again
We are family
It's not good
I won't forget what you did before
Jingjing
Why are you here?
Go back
I want Jingjing
You are a blind man
Why is she here?
Listen
Today is the day of Mr. Peng Sai and Jingjing's wedding
Don't be a third wheel
It will hurt their relationship
Jingjing
You should be careful
Mr. Peng Sai is not a good person
I have video evidence
No
And the store has nothing to do with him
He is lying to you
You
How can you talk like that?
Are you a monster?
Wait
Mr. Peng Sai
You are revenge for my dad
You have been persuading him to quit
Jingjing
You really believe what he said?
Why is there no sound?
Forget it
There was no sound
But it's me
Jingjing
I got the chips from the casino
I asked him to pay the money
To quit the gambling
Ask him if you don't believe
I have the money
Mr. Peng Sai has been helping me to quit gambling
Jingjing
It's not like that
They lied to you
You said that you didn't earn this store
Ok
Then tell us today
How did you earn it?
It's Sun Yiqian
I helped him
He promised me
Miss Sun who is famous in Laiwan
You helped her
If you don't know how to brag, don't brag
I'm a man who is honest in Laiwan
I have been with the Sun family for many years
You don't think I'm kidding
Kidding
You prove that you helped Jingjing to get this store
I don't have time to talk nonsense with you
This store is the store that I invested in
The boss
Jingjing and me
If you want to stay
Show your attitude
You will be nice
Or you kneel down and kowtow to me
I can't help thinking about keeping you
Bullshit
You are not a boss at all
Arrogant
Take it down
No, don't hit people
Don't hit him
You let him go
Let him go
Don't touch the kowtow
Hurry up
I have a strong desire for success
The world is just a devil
It's okay
Don't touch
Miss Sun
What's wrong with Miss Sun
She must know that I am opening today
I came to congratulate me
Miss Sun
You came today
The store is really a place to be proud
Miss Sun
Come on
You still have so many things
It's embarrassing, right?
Who are you
I
Miss Sun
Get out of the way
Don't go
I came today
To give her a gift
Miss Sun
I'm sorry