"PorschArm the Wedding"
(Episode 4)
[Anything special you want to do
before the wedding?]
I do have one.
I'll do what Arm hates the most!
[November 23rd, 2024
"48 Days Before the Wedding"]
These are horizontal and vertical cuts.
They are in different sizes.
Try this on. I think it's cute.
Aww, this is cute.
- Right?
- It fits perfectly.
Put the ring on.
- I'm going to the toilet.
- Hold on. Don't leave now.
Help me pick one.
Can I? There are a few diamonds on it.
This is what you call 'a few, ' right?
- Just a few, right?
- You're right.
- The whole ring is still a few?
- Not that many diamonds.
- Just one, maybe.
- Really?
I wanna try that.
Is there a ring with just one big diamond?
Oh!
- Whoa!
- Oh, my God!
It's gotta fit me!
I gotta get this!
I think a wedding band is...
a symbol of a couple.
Like, I got Arm here, and
Arm also got me there.
I'd touch it whenever I feel like it.
Personally, I feel like
the size of the diamond or the price
doesn’t define how much we love each other.
The diamond doesn't need to be so large.
Or if it's small,
it doesn't mean our love is little.
It’s about whether it’s proper.
I think a ring has to be with us everywhere,
in every day, hour, minute,
just like the love I have for him.
Honestly, that ring
with those diamonds
emphasizes his love so much!
This is the abundance of love we have shared.
Gotta have some diamonds, you know?
Diamonds are our best friends!
Oh... This one is incredible!
This is the best one so far!
Hi there.
Okay, alright.
Just like that, yeah.
Just like that.
[November 30th
"41 Days Before the Wedding"]
- Yay.
- Push it in!
Push it in.
Yes. 1, 2, 3!
Give it to me.
- Yeah.
- Put it in the envelope.
Just like this.
- Like this.
- Why? Why do we have to put it in?
Put it in,
so it's ready to be given
to your mom and dad.
I met my friend yesterday.
Umm!
I was asked if we both would change
our surname.
Ooh!
What did you answer them?
I was thinking about it.
But what would it be?
- Like...
- Huh?
Should it be 'Sappanyoo, ' 'Apiwatsayree, '
- or 'Apiwatpanatkool'?
- 'Apiwatpanatkool'?
Because both of us can
change our surnames freely, right?
Right!
The law was approved, right?
So we can change or switch
our surnames as we wish.
What about ours? Will we change them?
Or should we add the middle name instead?
Like...
Like, mine would be 'Sappanyoo...'
'Sappanyoo Panatkool Apiwatsayree.'
'Apiwat Panatkool Apiwatsayree, ' like this?
Or should it be 'Apiwat.
Apiwatpanatkool?'
Just create a new surname, is that it?
I don't know.
Do you want to have a child?
Huh?
Yes, I do.
I don't know if...
we are ready for a child.
Imagine having a kid running around like this.
Come here!
That's cute, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
- Yeah?
- But are we ready for that?
Come here, boy!
Give me a hug!
Come here. Come on.
- Oh.
- Why aren't you obedient?
Give me a hug!
A turtle is coming!
A turtle is on your way!
- Look at the dolphin.
- What?
Is that a dolphin?
- Yeah.
- Are you sure?
To have a child, we need to divide...
- not divide, we need to focus on them.
- You need to have a baby!
Huh?
- A baby?
- We need to, huh?
- Right?
- Yeah?
Really? Porsch and I have to have a baby?
Uncle Arm and I need to have a baby?
- Huh?
- Yes.
So, you'll have a friend to play with, right?
Yes, right?
- Yes.
- We gotta go to the post office.
- You just hit the bear?
- We can send out 100 invitations a day.
- At least.
- Yes, we gotta finish it.
I'm playing with Sunny first.
See? One will have to work
while the other focuses on the child.
Or both have to focus on raising the child.
And that will make us
less focus on each other?
No, that is not what it is.
- It's like we used to have 100% love.
- Don't overthink.
- And one day, our 100% is divided.
- Our love is still the same.
We have to give it all to our baby,
that's the right thing to do.
- Where are you going?
- So I want to know if we're ready.
Are you ready, Sunny?
- Do we want to have a child?
- We've discussed it a lot.
We wanted to have one,
but...
Yeah, we had talked it through.
I didn't want to have one.
We have to talk until it's clear.
We discussed the reasons on both sides.
It’s still up in the air.
I told him I didn't want one,
but I talked to my friend
the other day about it.
"Should I have a baby?"
So, we haven’t settled on anything yet.
But I just don't want any for now.
What we're facing is already tough
for both of us.
For the surname, it's not an LGBT thing,
it's universal.
- True.
- You can use his last name if you want to.
You can also keep your last name,
that's fine.
I think it's widely open now.
Even the name title, right?
- You can keep it or change it, for women.
- That's right!
Yeah, you're right.
For the children topic,
it may not be completely legal.
You can have one,
but surrogacy is still not legal.
This topic could be discussed
for an entire episode.
In my opinion, I appreciate all couples
who try hard for babies.
You should have one only when both are ready.
I agree with you. For the surname change,
it's something that needs to be questioned
to find the best solutions
that meet individual expectations.
When my wife and I met and got married,
we were happy in our own way.
That fulfilled our lives in a certain way.
Having a child has taught me
to love someone in an indescribable way.
I never had that kind of love
for someone else before.
I love her...
- Unconditionally.
- Yes, unconditionally.
Just looking at her,
I can keep smiling the whole night long.
Just by looking at her falling asleep.
It's...
I think it's the happiness
that is so special.
I can't describe it to you,
you gotta discover that yourself.
- Umm.
- That's true.
We believe that, in an imperfect world,
there's constant beauty in our children
that shines on us every day.
Plus, I think...
My partner and I used to discuss
how gay couples have babies.
I never got a friend in my circle
who had experienced that.
I just felt like...
Many men and women get married
and fail in their relationships.
Some families have only single moms
or single dads.
I grew up in a family
where my parent separated as well.
However, with love,
kids can be raised by anyone!
- It doesn't matter.
- Just ensure they're loved.
They will grow up being a happy,
content person.
I can tell you, I also have a kid.
We've never known what this feeling is like
until we experience it firsthand.
[Anything special you want to do
before the wedding?]
No, nothing special.
We've done everything already!
We've prepared everything.
No stress!
Fresh!
Oh, good job. Correct!
- Who's that?
- Huh?
Nothing.
- This.
- What is that?
What is this?
Yes.
Okay, confirm.
Right, as the time I reserved.
That's right.
About the details...
Ah.
Okay. That's great!
[December 1st, 2024
"40 Days Before the Wedding"]
Shall we go out for dinner?
I'm feeling tired.
Just order delivery.
I'm bored of it.
I can't think of any I want to have.
What do you want to eat?
Outside.
I know, I mean, what are we eating outside?
Just look it up later.
Jeez.
Just drive out
and look for a restaurant later?
Yeah.
Is that a joke?
No way, I'm too tired for that.
- Let's go out and have our dinner.
- No way, I'm tired!
Why not?
Let me ask you
what you want to eat if we're out?
- There are various options available.
- What are they?
Japanese, Mexican, Chinese, or Thai cuisine.
Umm!
Lots of options out there.
- For all these...
- And Italian cuisine, too.
We can order them home!
That's suspicious.
It felt like he was hiding something,
I don't know.
Suspicious!
Where are you taking me to?
- Are you excited for that?
- Huh?
Sure I am!
Why so?
You rarely drive for me!
Where are we going?
Isn't it great?
It's great...
- But...
- Isn't it great having me as a driver?
You’re acting suspicious.
What?
Seeing a newbie driver...
No, tell me where we're heading to.
I can drive it for you.
- Huh?
- What about that?
If I tell you, it's no longer a surprise.
Keep your eyes on the road, not me.
- Huh? Come again.
- Eyes on the road!
Where are we going?
This area...
Surprise!
This place?
Yeah.
Whoa!
Good evening, sir.
- Hello.
- Hi.
Whoa...
Thank you.
- Wow.
- Thank you.
Whoa!
- Were you surprised?
- What's with all this?
Were you?
I haven’t had dinner like this in ages.
- It's dinner before the wedding.
- What's this?
Aw!
What is that?
Here you are.
Thank you.
Hey...
- Is this even real?
- I know...
you don't like receiving flowers.
But I gotta give you this...
How many have you received
from dating me?
Remember?
This is the second.
- This is the second flower in 16 years, right?
- Yes.
- A flower before the wedding.
- I'm gonna cry.
Thank you, babe.
Thank you so much.
Thanks.
- Thank you.
- I love you.
I love you too, monkey-pie.
I'm so glad.
We're about to get married.
Let me sit and think about this.
Is it good?
Thank you.
- That's the Christmas tree.
- Oh, you're right.
Delicious, isn't it?
I'm extremely happy.
Thank you, babe.
What now?
- That's not it.
- What?
- The surprise is not done.
- What is that?
Huh?
Only a double surprise is a real surprise.
That's insane!
I don't want more of this.
What is that?
What?
Just kidding.
Come on.
What now?
No, no way!
Come on!
Please.
I know you're not into surprises.
We're getting married soon.
You need to agree with this.
- I'll put it on myself.
- Smile first!
I'll close my eyes myself.
Smile first.
Don't peek, okay?
Alright.
How many fingers am I holding up?
8.
What about these?
Huh?
- How many?
- 1.
What the heck is that?
What?
Our journey starts now!
- Where are we going?
- Don't peek. Promise me first.
Promise me.
Give me your hand, that hand!
This. Don't touch.
Don't touch, okay?
I'm stressed out!
Monkey-pie!
- Huh?
- Are we there?
Don't open the blindfold! Don't do it!
What the heck?
- Don't.
- No, I don't like this!
Don't peek.
- Don't open it. Don't.
- I don't like it now.
Don't do it, okay?
What the heck?!
- I don't like this.
- Hold my hand.
Why is your hand this cold?
Why is it so cold?
I just don't like this!
What is it?
I'm so excited, my heart is beating fast.
What is all this?
Huh?
I don't like doing this now.
Don't be upset. It's nothing!
Why are you crying?
Don't cry.
Why so? Don't cry!
Hello!
- Hello.
- Can I take this off?
- Hello!
What is that?
Don't you recall any voices?
He's about to cry.
- He is.
- Go comfort him.
Hold on.
- Don't you take that off!
- Don't!
- Don't you...
- What the heck is this?
Come on.
Is your stuff here?
- Is it?
- Is it??
- All you have is here, right?
- Right?
- Bye-bye!
- Thank you!
- Thanks!
Walk up. Keep walking!
- You know it's me?
- Keep walking.
You know?
I'm scared.
Nothing scary!
Everything's so scary, actually.
- Everything's mysterious and horrifying.
- I don't wanna do this.
I don't wanna do this.
Everything looks scary for real.
1, 2, 3!
Surprise!
I'm crying.
Give him a welcome drink.
Here are the welcome drinks!
How are you feeling now?
Pick one.
Don't use your hands!
What about this?
Look this way!
That's too low.
- Yay!
- Yas!
Bottoms up!
It's edible.
This is yummy!
- Hen Night.
- It's of course yummy!
Our bride is drop-dead gorgeous!
Hope we see him like this tonight!
Yay, like this!
Men... Oh!
Whoa!
Yay!
Porsch's side.
- He must be praying.
- Praying at home.
Praying?
I told you!
He actually did it!
- He sleeps at 8 P.M.
- Oh!
So lovely of him.
- Pity him.
- Did he set an alarm to pick up Arm?
- Aw!
- Wow!
- Whoa!
How was your night?
- What was all that?
- Tell me.
What was that? Hmm?
Did you have fun?
- What was that?
- Did you have fun?
It's like, what the heck, though!
I had planned it all ahead of time.
Was it fun?
It was!
But I told you I didn't like a surprise!
I was crying!
Thank you so much.
Don't thank me. Thank your friends.
I just...
What is it?
I was just a decoy.
Tell me what happened there.
It was extremely insane!
- It was totally insane.
- Tell me, I wanna know.
Your friends said there would be a dance...
A go-go dance, like wow, right?
- Yes.
- I want to see that.
There was a dance. I was sitting in a chair,
then they lifted me!
- Yeah.
- And you were like, this?
No, I was like, "What is this?!"
- I was so hilarious.
- What else?
Let me hug.
I love you, babe.
- I love you too, monkey-pie.
- Everyone loves you.
Did you cry?
Oh, I don't believe that.
- I cried so hard.
- Really?
- I cried a lot.
- I thought you were just teary.
I cried like...
I cried from the time I was in the car.
It's what a surprise is supposed to be.
Are you hungry?
- Wanna eat?
- Yes, I'm hungry.
What do we have?
- A fried egg?
- Sure, go ahead.
I'll do that for you.
Go take a shower first.
Come on!
I'm going.
I will take a shower!
A fried egg is served.
Hey.
A fried egg is served!
Come on.
Whoa!
Crispy edges, soft whites,
and a runny egg yolk!
Am I correct?
No one knows me like you do!
But the yolk is ruined.
It's all fine!
No worries, it's still delicious!
I want to keep frying your eggs.
I wanna keep eating it, too.
Your fried egg is the best in the world!
The fried egg eater is also the cutest!
I love you, monkey-pie.
I love you, too, babe.
(Next Episode)
Who do you love?
I love everything around me.
My family and myself.
Friends who have been through
thick and thin with me.
Long distance doesn't do anything.
Since I was 11 years old, let's say.
Sometimes, by looking in their eyes,
I knew what they were thinking.
Maybe, over 40 years.
Anything that makes me happy is called love.
Since I was a teenager.
In the future, we may be
in a nursing home together when we're 70-80.
Now, I have some love
for my family, my mom and dad.
It's been almost half a decade.
Love, for me, is for two people
that have feelings for each other.
I wanna say I love all my friends.
Whenever I want to improve
their surroundings
whether it's humans, animals, or objects,
it's a kind of love
that's worth living for as a human being.