♪Come closer♪
♪Be more intimate♪
♪Tell me if I am tempted♪
♪The moment you and I
looked at each other♪
♪We were both tempted♪
♪Remember how shy you were♪
♪That day♪
♪Sweet memories♪
♪Please be more♪
♪How lucky I am to have you♪
♪So sweet♪
=My Naughty Assistant=
=Episode 13=
I never thought
of getting you into trouble.
I didn't mean it.
(I'm willing to do anything for you.)
(Please don't leave me.)
(Don't leave me.)
(The lawyer is handling the case.)
(My Alipay and bank cards
are temporarily frozen.)
(I can't go out now.)
(You go to the supermarket
and buy me pasta with foie gras.)
What?
Did he forget
what he said to me yesterday?
(What is he doing?)
(I'm dying here,)
(and he only cares about his pasta!)
(I haven't signed
the termination contract yet.)
(I'm so late.)
Why are you here?
You're on your period.
Have a good rest now.
So messy.
I've brought you painkillers.
Take it and then you will be okay.
Open your mouth.
You will be all right.
Duoduo.
Thank you.
My birthday is coming,
the day after tomorrow.
Do you still remember?
Come to my birthday party, okay?
Okay.
(Xing Enchen, she's my girl.
Don't even think about it.)
♪How many times in my life♪
♪I am destined♪
♪To meet you and fall in love with you♪
♪In my finest age♪
♪It's a pity♪
♪That we are not together in this life♪
♪But still, thank you♪
♪For letting me♪
♪Walk into your world♪