. 。
Little rabbit.
What's wrong
with your left hand?
It seems that time is running out.
What time?
It's almost time.
What are you talking about?
Yuchuan,
I told you before,
I'm not from your world.
The key for me to leave this world,
is to find the Heart of Stallone,
The heart of Stallone is the heart of true love,
and when you find true love,
I'm about to leave here.
So you're afraid of affecting me?
What you said to Leng Feng,
you said it to me on purpose.
I'm afraid that after you know the truth,
you'll do something stupid,
I'm even more scared.
This fruitless love will make you regret for the rest of your life.
It doesn't matter.
What matters is that we're still together, aren't we?
We're still together.
That's right.
Why is it so dark?
Why didn't you turn on the light?
Ouyang,
Shengnan,
What's going on?
Ouyang, is that you?
What's wrong with you today?
Goddess,
who are you?
Let go of me!
Don't come over. I'll tell you.
Who am I?
I gave up my family for you and separated my wife.
I'll tell you who I am.
What does it
have to do with me?
If it weren't for you,
I would be like this.
I'll tell you who I am today.
-Don't come near me. -Listen to me, Yanyan.
What are
you doing?
Yanyan, listen to me.
Don't be afraid.
Let go of me!
Yanyan,
what are you doing?
Do you know how much I like you?
What does it have to do with me?
You know what?
Every one of your albums,
let go of me!
I'll buy all the products you endorse.
All the list ones in your live streaming room are me,
I don't need you to buy anything,
I lost everything for you.
I have nothing left.
Don't come near me. I'm telling you,
I'm telling you not to come over.
You're all I have left.
What are you doing?
Help!
Brother,
misunderstanding, misunderstanding,
Yanyan, wait for me.
I will definitely come back.
It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay.
It's okay now.
Are you okay?
Shengnan,
thank you so much today.
If it weren't for you,
I would have been ruined today.
As for what happened before,
I was always jealous of you and Yuchuan,
I even tried to harm you.
It's really my fault.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
It's all in the past.
What about you?
It's because I care too much about your brother Yuchuan.
Actually, I also know that he doesn't like me.
But I just don't know why I always want to
get close to him. That's because,
This is Yan Yan
who was set up.
I have one thing I hope you can promise me.
Shengnan, I'll promise you
whatever you say.
In this world,
Besides Manager Wang,
only you know your brother Yuchuan the best.
To understand his true nature.
I know how sincere he is to people.
I know how sincere he is to me.
so
I hope that one day, if I leave,
you can still take care of him like before.
Shengnan,
what are you talking about?
Why did you leave?
I won't hide it from you.
Actually,
I'm not from your world at all.
In a few days,
I'm going to be in this world,
It has completely disappeared.
Shengnan,
although I don't know why you left,
But I know you must have your reasons.
Well,
I really can't bear to leave you.
After spending so much time with you,
I really admire you.
Look at your courage to love and hate,
your independence and self-improvement,
I don't have any of these.
And I can tell,
Ouyang only has you in his heart,
Even if you leave,
he will never fall in love with anyone.
All right. Why did you bring him up?
He's a fool.
Even if all the women in the world
are set to like me.
But the only one I love
in my heart is Bunny.
Shut up!
Annoying.
So you're afraid of affecting me?
What you said to Leng Feng,
you said it to me on purpose.
I'm afraid that after you know the truth,
you'll do something stupid,
I'm even more scared.
This fruitless love will make you regret for the rest of your life.
It doesn't matter.
What matters is that we're still together, aren't we?
We're still together.
That's right.
It turns out I was the one
who was tricked.
Mr. Leng,
it seems that Miss Su
is already with Ouyang Yuchuan.
So our cooperation
is over, isn't it?
What I can't get,
Ouyang Yuchuan won't get it either.
One last thing for me.
Mr. Leng,
I won't do anything that involves human life.
You don't need to do it yourself.
You just need to take them to the place I arranged.
I'll do it myself.
When it's done,
I'll give you double.
Since Mr. Leng is so sincere,
it's not easy for me to refuse.
The last collaboration,