(Mr. Queen)
(This drama is fictional and
all characters, organizations, )
(and events are unrelated
to historical events.)
(Episode 5)
Everyone has a fatal weakness.
Even Superman becomes
nothing more than a pervert...
who wears underwear on the
outside when faced with kryptonite.
If Superman becomes like that,
imagine what would
happen to ordinary people.
I will tell you the truth.
Grand Queen Dowager,
I will obey your order!
She is not the one who should be beheaded!
Your Majesty.
Please.
Will you go against the King's order?
To an ordinary person,
this world is like a minefield of weakness.
We become one another's weakness...
and drag everyone to the underworld.
Even someone as perfect as me,
Jang Bong Hwan, had a weakness.
That is none other than...
I can't bear to see some other
guy looking cooler than me.
Those who tried to harm the Queen were...
Wait!
Especially when it's in front
of a woman I'm interested in.
I need to be the coolest person
in front of them to be satisfied.
You could say it's the only weakness...
of someone who is so perfect.
Since I am the alleged
victim of this incident,
allow me to shed light on the truth.
I...
was trying to take my own life.
I won't let you be the only cool one here.
Stay still, Cheoljong.
I should be the hero.
So please do not hurt
those who did nothing wrong.
Nice one.
What kind of a ludicrous statement is this?
Grand Queen Dowager.
I apologize,
but I was trying to end my own life.
("Desert your false self")
This is the suicide note that
I carry with me all the time.
I am going back tonight anyway.
I don't care if things get chaotic here.
Why on earth would you do that?
Furthermore,
why would you try to end your life...
on the night before you became queen?
The thing is...
What on earth is the reason?
The reason why I was so
depressed that I wanted to die was...
I'm sure I had a reason.
Your Highness!
Darn it!
So Yong.
Is he going to carry me right now?
Don't.
Don't come near me. Go away!
Grand Queen Dowager.
The Queen is saying false things...
in order to save the life of
someone lesser than her.
Please look fondly
upon the virtuous heart...
of forgiving someone who had
committed a great sin against her,
and show mercy.
Oh, my. Is that how he translated it?
What is so interesting that so
many people have gathered?
Your...
Your Highness.
What on earth has happened?
All right then.
Since the Queen is trying so hard,
I will show mercy after seeing her efforts.
(Episode 5,
A Heel That Can Easily Get Hurt)
It has been a while since we
had such an interesting spectacle.
I wonder what the Queen
was thinking when doing that.
Perhaps it is the heart of a woman.
Regardless, we can be sure that
it was not a plan from the Kim clan.
Yes.
Are you going to Seoneonjeon Hall?
I need something other than prayer today.
She is nothing but a
weak Royal Noble Consort,
but she is our only arrow.
So we must put some
poison on that arrowhead.
Goodness.
What do you mean she tried to end her life?
What do you mean by that?
I need to bide my time and
wake up at the right moment.
I am such a foolish
father to not realize that.
I have committed a great sin.
It is all my fault.
I should have taken better care of her.
This is all because I am lacking.
What on earth is the reason?
You should know since you
assist her in close proximity.
She would try to jump into the water
multiple times whenever she could,
and I thought it was because
of the shock from falling in.
"Multiple times"?
How much was she suffering?
Your Highness.
My gosh. Enough already.
If you keep crying, I can't wake up.
This is not the time for us to be crying.
If she sees us crying,
imagine how upset she would be.
That's right.
You are right.
At times like this,
we must stand by her side and be brave.
Should I get up now?
- So Yong. - My gosh.
When your mother gave birth to you,
she lost her life.
Is he starting again?
Your Highness.
Her Highness grew up...
without ever getting the
chance to see her mother's face.
I feel so bad for her.
I had no idea that she
was suffering so much,
and all I did was telling her
she could not do this or that.
I would chase after her...
and nag her all the time.
I might as well have been...
the person who pushed her into the lake.
Goodness, Your Highness.
Your Highness!
I give up.
This is not a situation I can handle.
(Gwanghwamun)
My Queen.
Please..
Take care of yourself.
Your pathetic father...
apologizes to you.
Byeong In.
I am entering the Palace today.
I am finally meeting
the King for the first time.
Are you that happy?
It is because I am curious.
One day, he appears as an ugly fool,
and on a different day,
he looks as though he was made from jade.
In my dreams.
Last night, he looked exactly like you.
I believed that I had to give
up on you to make you happy.
You were so happy before
you entered the Palace.
However, after entering the Palace,
you tried to end your own life.
Is it because of that?
She is crazy! She has lost her mind!
("Desert your false self")
She spent the past few nights
with the King. Are you sure that...
she was not the one who was
won over instead of the King?
Please calm down, Your Highness.
There is nothing to be
gained from being mad.
How can I not be mad?
We lost the perfect
opportunity like this so easily.
I cannot believe we
shot ourselves in the foot!
Furthermore,
did you see the King's behaviour just now?
That arrogant glare.
I saved him from living his days as
a countryman and made him king,
yet he dared to rebel against me like that?
We must discipline him if he rebels.
I will tighten the reigns,
so he knows his place.
What is the point of spending
time taking care of myself?
It all falls apart when I
worry over something once.
Call for Park, the doctor.
Yes, sir.
To be honest, the Queen came to see me...
on the night she fell into the lake.
Grand Queen Dowager. I...
will leave the Palace.
What are you talking about?
I cannot endure the position of Queen.
I do not want to live in such misery.
I had heard the rumours that
you have been acting atrocious,
but it was all on purpose...
so that you would not become Queen.
How cute.
I cannot believe you thought
you could get your way like that.
You were taking your lessons
diligently to become a queen.
I do not know what
suddenly changed your mind,
but I do not wish to know either.
Your fate was decided upon your birth.
You were to become
queen and serve your family.
That is your fate and the reason you exist.
Did you rise to your position on your own?
No, you did not.
That is why you cannot
step down on your own either.
If you want to die, die in the Palace.
I thought she said such things
because kids these days are...
too sheltered they make a
big deal out of small things.
That is why I did not give it much thought.
I never considered that she jumped
into the lake to commit suicide.
If she was willing to end her
life to avoid becoming queen,
her crazy behaviour today is also...
A way to step down from
her position as Queen.
If that is the case,
I will not let the Queen get away with it.
Wait for me! What if you fall?
I told you that you could take your time.
Who dares to block my way?
Grand Queen Dowager?
You will not be able to go home.
- What? - The Queen, Jang Bong Hwan,
has been ordered to stay here
forever until the day he rots,
and live in pain while being impotent.
No.
I don't want to.
I don't want to be impotent!
Your Highness!
What a terrible nightmare.
You tried to commit suicide in the lake...
and just now,
you fainted and I was so worried...
Calm down. I understand how you feel.
I am going to die with you!
That's enough already.
I've already reached the Max
amount of tears I can handle for a day.
It's not like it's contagious,
but how can you cry three times?
I ended up falling asleep
while waiting for you to stop.
Right. I am sure you do
not wish to see me cry.
You are pretty when you smile.
What about Court Lady Choi?
She insisted on bringing
your medicine herself.
Great Lord Yeongeun stayed by your side...
and returned home when the sun went down.
If you woke up a bit sooner,
you could have seen him.
Thank goodness I didn't see him.
Pardon?
If he finds out that a guy's soul...
is occupying his precious daughter's body,
he would be so upset.
Let's hurry before Court
Lady Choi comes back.
I'm sure the lake is filled now, right?
You want to go to the lake at this hour?
Today is finally the day.
- You are in a good mood now, right?
- Of course.
All I have left to do is to go back home...
and leave an afterglow of a handsome man.
Oh, right.
- Hong Yeon. - Yes, Your Highness.
I was able to endure this thanks to you.
I don't know about anyone else,
but I'll miss you.
Oh, that's right. I'll miss
Court Lady Choi too.
Hong Yeon. There's a will you
must leave for your descendants.
A will?
Buy land in Gangnam.
You have to tell them this.
If you leave it for about 200 years,
your future generations will live wealthy.
This is all I can give you.
Okay, let's go.
Your Highness. Please be careful.
Keep up your energy.
Hurry. You must hurry.
What is this?
Why did you go back to the old method...
when I created a perfect system for you?
The thing is...
The well has dried up.
That is why we have been
getting water from over there...
and bringing it over here, but...
Can you tell me that
again? I think I misheard you.
It sounds like you're telling me
you won't be able to fill it by today.
Please forgive us, Your Highness.
- Please forgive us, Your Highness.
A high-ranking government
official must keep his promises.
You said you would fill the lake by today.
The closest well from here...
is still far away.
It will take at least a week and a half...
Please kill me!
- Please kill me! - Please kill me!
Why do you guys always ask to be killed?
Is it because you don't
believe I'll actually kill you?
Do you want me to show you
what behavioural integrity is?
Do you want to face the consequences
of depositing a fake check?
Forget it. I'm sure it will
still work even if it's not filled.
No, Your Highness.
Why are you acting like this too?
I will not allow you
to end your life again.
It's not like that.
I'm not trying to die.
Then what are you trying to do?
Well...
I'm trying to live. This
is the only way I can live!
You can go after you kill me first!
Gosh. How come you're so strong?
Let go of me.
If that granny changes her mind...
and gets rid of the water in
the lake again, I'm doomed!
Everyone, stop Her Highness!
How dare we touch Her Highness?
Your Highness!
Please no!
I will stop nagging you from now on!
I will never say no to you!
You cannot do this, Your Highness!
You said you wouldn't.
You said you wouldn't say no to me!
Darn it.
You cannot do that.
Even if you tickle me...
I have lost my ability
to laugh a long time ago.
Darn it.
I won't do it. Forget it.
Gosh. Darn it.
So you don't want me to go in there, right?
Fine.
Raise your head.
Straighten your back.
Can you swim?
Is that it?
If I go farther, the water will be deeper.
Okay. Go ahead.
- Gosh. - Yes, that's it!
I slipped!
- Darn it. - Your Highness.
The Grand Queen Dowager asked
for your attendance immediately.
Darn it.
Lee Saeng Mang. That
name was my foreshadowing.
Darn it.
- My gosh. - Goodness. Nice.
Good.
What is wrong?
Do you get this kind of
feeling too from time to time?
You know, everyone is busy
doing something except for me.
You are the center of my world, my lord.
Well,
people who have great hunches like me...
sometimes get the wrong hunch like today.
I did not order Naengmyeon.
You give me the pleasure
of serving you every night.
It is from my heart.
Let me say something.
It might seem to you I am here to have fun,
but that is not true.
I am only here because I need
to find out the whereabouts...
of Lee Saeng Mang who had disappeared.
But why are you desperately
looking for that man?
I get the feeling that there is...
an important secret
behind his disappearance.
My sixth sense tells me...
that Lee Saeng Mang...
is at the center of the problem.
- What problem? - I do not know.
Pardon?
They are testing me right now.
- About today... - It is my fault.
For forcing you to marry
him when you did not want to.
Do you not want to be the Queen that badly?
Enough to throw away your own life?
Enough to be deposed as the Queen?
She tried to end her life because
she didn't want to be the Queen?
Fine.
As you desperately want it,
I will let you leave the palace.
I will depose you.
You will be stuck at your
house and never be able to...
set foot outside for the rest of your life.
No.
I can only go back through the lake here.
I do not remember it.
I have not regained my
memories since falling into the lake.
You have not regained your memories,
but you remember that
you wanted to kill yourself?
I still have painful feelings.
And I am sure that I was the one
who embroidered the suicide note.
But I do not know why
I wanted to kill myself.
If you have not regained your memories,
why did you interfere?
As you cannot give me a reason,
I take that you just
wanted to go against me.
No.
I do not have any intention to oppose you.
Today,
you have directly challenged my authority.
I must get out of this.
But I don't have a solution. Gosh,
I can't think of one.
And I cannot forgive you for it.
I deserve death, Your Highness.
You ought to end my life.
I am confused due to
the lack of my memories,
but I cannot turn my back on my family...
or my husband.
Please punish me...
with poison, so I can end this pain.
What they really want
isn't deposing the Queen.
Is it that easy for you
to give up on your life?
You jumped into the lake yourself.
And now, you want to drink the poison?
Why are you so weak?
They want to confirm that they
have power over the Queen.
My foolish decision to end my life...
caused this whole misunderstanding.
My action deserves death.
So I beg you to punish me with death,
Your Highness.
Your death will not fix anything.
The Queen Dowager will have...
an advantage over you
because of this incident.
But this goes beyond you.
This will be a disadvantage
against the entire Kim clan.
- I will try... - Please calm down.
I will ask this one last time,
Your Highness.
Do you truly want to leave the palace?
I want to...
live in the palace.
What do you think, Your Highness?
As I do not hold any old memories,
I have been born a new person.
I will become the perfect queen.
I do not believe promises
that come in words.
I will show you with my actions.
Please give her a chance, Your Highness.
Okay.
I am truly grateful for your kindness.
I will never worry you from now on.
I am not worried.
("Desert your false self")
Because we do not have any weaknesses.
If there is a problem,
we can carve it out.
He meant it.
It's a real warning.
It's so dark.
Should I bring more lanterns,
Your Highness?
No. I was talking about my future.
Prince Yeongpyeong
raided the place with his men.
"His men"?
Were they royal guards?
They were specially trained.
How many?
Not many.
- Seven. - They have been training...
only seven men in hiding?
You are out of medicine.
You would've become the best
warrior if it weren't for the disease.
I'm grateful...
that I am alive due to your help.
Thank you, my lord.
If you fail once again no
matter what the reason is,
you will not get this medicine anymore.
I will keep that in mind.
So far, we thought...
the Queen fell into the lake to
frame Royal Noble Consort Eui.
We also thought she lied she lost
memories with an ulterior motive.
I cannot believe that she
tried to end her own life.
She might have planned all
this to win over you, Your Majesty.
She planned this as she expected
me to stand up for Consort Eui?
If you did not come forward,
she could have framed Her Highness.
If you did step up,
she could have persuaded you.
Prince Yeongpyeong, you assume...
everything the Queen says
and does is out of hidden malice.
The Queen...
is the core of the Kim clan.
What kind of people are they?
They are the ones that
killed our whole family.
I cannot...
forget it even for a moment.
I cannot forget it either.
But look at what the Queen
has chosen to do today.
She revealed the truth
for me who tried to kill her...
and Royal Noble Consort Eui
she came up against so much.
Do you still think your
unchanged hostility towards her...
is right?
- Your Majesty.
- If it is really a suicide attempt,
I killed the Queen twice.
Why are you here?
I have something to say.
You made things complicated for nothing.
My fate is already in your family's hands.
Just ask me to hand
over the letter next time.
Do you not like me...
because I'm from the Andong Kim clan?
I did not say I do not like you.
Do you like me then?
If I were not Andong Kim,
do you think you would have
seen me in a different light?
No, I would have not.
You became the Queen
because you are from the Kim clan.
I always tried my best.
I am not going to be crowned as
queen just because of my name.
I dedicated my whole
life to this yet people say...
You will get what you
wanted so bad tomorrow.
It is late and we have an
important event tomorrow.
Please go to your bed chamber now.
You should love me.
Is that an order?
My coldness pushed her into the lake.
If she tried to end her own
life because of your coldness,
she would have fallen
into the lake by herself.
But she manipulated the letter
and fell in front of Her Highness.
I see an ulterior motive.
"Motive", you say.
I should go to see the Queen.
The bad ones come with a smile.
If she did that to change my mind,
I would be able to tell by her attitude.
Please take care of Royal
Noble Consort Eui here.
Pretending to be a
perfect queen for 15 days.
Would I be able to stand it?
If it goes wrong, I'll be trapped
in a suffocating woman's body...
and imprisoned as a dethroned
queen in the suffocating Joseon era.
I dug my own grave. Who can I blame?
Your Highness, the King has come.
Of course, it's Cheoljong.
That punk needs to be blamed.
I wouldn't have stepped up
for her if he didn't act cool.
Open it.
Before that, I wouldn't have
done it if he was not incompetent.
Even before that,
this woman wouldn't have...
tried to commit suicide
if he was nice to her.
- No, even way before that... - My Queen.
How are you feeling?
You're that worried about me
and still put a sword to my neck?
There's not even one day I felt
comfortable after coming here.
As soon as I opened my eyes,
they said tomorrow is the wedding day.
My husband who sleeps under the
same blanket with me tries to kill me.
And even the family that was on
my side threatens to dethrone me.
What do you mean dethrone?
Why? Are you tempted?
It's a perfect opportunity to put
Jo Hwa Jin in my place, right?
Why are you so worked
up like a fighting cock?
I did not come to fight with you.
I get angry just by looking at your face.
Don't you think I would?
You who tried to kill me,
and your lover you would die for.
I'm about to die as I'm
trying to save you two.
Before I kill myself, they will
make me kill myself first at this rate.
If I don't get angry in this situation,
am I a human? I'd be Buddha!
You must have so many reasons
to get angry at me. I understand.
No.
Don't try to understand me.
Don't even say...
that you understand after all that.
You should've understood me...
before putting a sword to my neck.
No. You should've understood
this woman when she tried to...
kill herself on the night
before the wedding.
It's late. Your understanding
means nothing now.
Hey, get out. I'm too tired to get angry.
I will come back after your
emotions are stabilized.
Don't come unless you're
going to kneel and beg me.
I will come back.
I said don't come!
Are they filling the lake with water again?
Her Highness requested Grand Queen Dowager.
Why?
I do not know the reason,
but I heard Her Highness
was at the lake today...
to supervise it by herself.
Your Majesty.
I am sorry for worrying you.
I was afraid that I might lose you.
Are you hurt?
Your wound is more painful to me...
than mine.
Today...
was very cruel to you, Hwa Jin.
I am sorry for dragging
you into this trouble.
Thinking how lonely and
painful you must have been...
because of the troubles in the palace...
I did not call you to share my tragedy.
So never do that again.
If you sacrifice yourself to save me,
how can I stay sane?
I will never do something
that makes you afraid.
Until the situation is settled,
Prince Yeongpyeong himself will guard you.
How about O Wol?
- Well... - Special Director Hong has come.
Come in.
How is Royal Noble
Consort Eui's maid doing?
She is getting treatment
at Royal Infirmary.
My brother did so much for this.
Thank you.
Did you meet with the Queen?
Yes.
- How was she? - She was angry.
- Pardon? - She blamed me...
for my lack of affection
which forced her to end her life.
And she showed hatred
as I tried to kill her.
She exploded with her emotions.
To think that she did this to win me over,
her action does not make sense.
On top of that,
the Kim clan tried to depose her.
Moreover,
Kim Byeong In has not figured out...
that the piece of robe
belongs to Your Majesty.
I knew it.
The Queen remained silent about it.
I do not know what her intention is,
but it does seem the
Queen is acting on her own.
I thought I would be able to...
figure out what kind of
person she is by her decisions.
But she puzzles me even more.
Father, this is Byeong In.
Yes. Come in.
I thought you quit smoking.
I did.
I am sorry about today's incident.
Why would you apologize for it?
What do you plan to do?
I will try to talk some sense into her.
And if she fails to understand,
she will be gone.
Who are you referring to?
It could be anyone.
There is no such thing as an eternal ally.
I am afraid this is not the
right time to bring this up,
but I must tell you something.
Okay. Go ahead.
I have decided on the
magnitude of my dream.
I am happy to hear that.
Which position is it?
I will be the head of the
Department of Justice.
The head of the Department of Justice?
Is being a warrior all
you want for your dream?
I will start from a position
where I can handle...
and make my own path.
Is that so?
You are saying,
you want to make your own path?
The Royal Noble Consort Eui is here.
Do not move.
Your Highness.
I am sorry.
I should have resisted to the end.
Your busted knees are the proof.
I know.
They are nothing.
With the medicinal herbs for a few days,
I will be able to run in no time.
Yes. I am sure you will recover.
Who would hurt you so brutally like this?
I could not see anything
as he was wearing a mask.
But I do remember his voice.
Your Highness.
Please excuse me for saying this.
When people who are not
from the royal family get hurt,
they cannot stay in the palace.
But how could she leave
the palace in this state?
That is the custom of the palace.
Everything from here shows no compassion.
If anyone tries...
to harm you on your way out,
use this as a bribe.
Once you get out of the palace,
use this to keep you comfortable.
No. This is too much.
I will send a letter to my family.
Do not worry.
Thank you for your service.
I am too ashamed to face Lord Jo.
I cannot go.
O Wol, you and I have grown up together.
You are my family.
You must hang in there,
for me to do the same.
Be more courageous for me.
You must live.
Do this for me.
- What happened? - It was crazy yesterday.
The Queen...
My lord.
Did you hear?
High Majesty threw daggers with
his eyes at Grand Queen Dowager.
His eyes got so big.
Hey. You.
His Majesty lifted her in
front of the Queen and...
Royal Chef, did you hear?
His Majesty held the sword
and the Grand Queen Dowager...
Did you hear what happened
at Donggungjeon Hall?
I heard they do that all the time.
The head of the Department of
Justice will be appointed today.
"Will be"?
We have a request of an appointment.
Who has been recommended...
to be the head of the
Department of Justice?
It is Byeong In of the Andong Kim clan.
That is quite a surprise.
I am sure there are many candidates
in the Department of Justice.
If I appoint someone who has
passed the civil service exam...
as the head of the Department of Justice,
there will be complaints.
Do you not think so?
We unanimously agreed
on this recommendation.
"Unanimously"?
I did not expect such
harmony among my people.
As I have heard,
he must be an excellent individual.
The royal notice of appointment
has already been prepared?
To catch up with your swift
decisions as I am a slow king,
perhaps, I should cut down on my sleep.
Please do not say so.
You must take care of your
health and produce an heir.
He is no king. He is a breeding horse.
You are always humble.
Please do not lose your humility.
Yes, Your Highness.
The Pungyang Jo clan...
has brought this disaster upon ourselves.
Because of Royal Noble
Consort Eui's false confession,
we have suffered such a humiliation.
The failure is the cause, not the result.
Pardon?
That is what the Queen Dowager said.
We agreed on the
appointment of Kim Byeong In...
and helped them
reinforce their tradition...
because we lost.
More defeats will decrease
our chance of winning.
She said...
we must make the move first.
Do you think O Wol
was able to recover a bit?
I will look into how she is doing.
She is a lively girl,
so she is always running around.
She will never be able to run around again.
If she had not come
to the palace with me...
Do not think too much about it.
Sometimes, thinking can put you in a swamp.
The more struggle, the deeper
you fall. It will be more painful.
What do you do...
to clear your head when
you have a lot on your mind?
I...
go to Special Director Hong.
He can comfort you.
He is so silly.
When I am with him, he makes me angry.
And when I vent my anger on him,
I am out of the swamp before I notice it.
Then can you make me angry?
- That is... - Or...
You must not move.
I have finished.
What is wrong?
It is nothing.
Did you get hurt?
You must not touch me.
I have a cramp.
Has it been that long?
Thank goodness.
You focused so hard
that you forgot the time.
If you wanted to sew,
you should do it in Daejojeon Hall.
Why are you doing it in the royal kitchen?
But are you really sewing something?
I promised to be reborn
as the perfect queen.
Did you say perfect?
You must be free. Do you
want me to give you some work?
Oh, my back.
When will I finish all of this?
What happened?
- Come in. - Wait.
Is that from Tongmyeongjeon Hall?
- Yes, Your Highness. - Let me see.
Since she has tasted
a new dish that I made,
I'm sure she's tired of the same
old meals she used to have.
Okay. Bring this to the saboksi.
If they cover the food palanquin
with a cloth about this size,
it will prevent the food from getting cold.
Tell them to make it nicely.
All right.
Are you going to the
lake after sending me off?
Have you seen anyone who...
work so hard like this
when they want to die?
Also, you must've forgotten
because it's become so natural,
but I'm being watched by a CCTV.
What are you worried about?
Now, shall I try to work my magic?
Your Highness!
Yes!
Hey, you. Is the ground meat ready?
Yes.
Hurry up and bring it over.
Bring me some salt.
The Queen wants me
to bring this to her first.
My goodness.
Fine. Do whatever you want.
Let me see how well things work out.
What if we asked the
Queen to prepare a meal...
Grand Queen Dowager,
this is the Head Inspector.
The Queen has prepared lunch for you.
Should I tell him not to bring it in?
Goodness.
What is it?
She is so tactless.
Your Highness.
Your lunch has arrived, but...
(Tongmyeongjeon Hall)
Be careful.
That is...
The Queen has told me that...
the theme of today's lunch is COSI.
"COSI"?
I have never heard this before.
Is it from Mencius?
No, it is not. Is it from "The
Analects of Confucius"?
It means that...
the food is crunchy on the outside...
and soft in the inside.
Oh, really?
The food palanquin is here!
Here. Take the dishes.
Be careful.
Your Highness.
She was very satisfied,
and she complimented you.
In particular,
she saw the food palanquin...
and asked how you came
up with such a brilliant idea.
Of course. That's an obvious result.
It's an item that was successful
in the competitive nation of Korea.
Josean's deliveryman.
I'm so proud of myself.
Generally speaking,
a woman of the royal family...
must always be humble...
Are you...
going to nag me right now?
Must they be humble? It was a question.
No. Life is hard even if
you live off your own pride.
I do not know what she is saying,
but it is still annoying.
It is a stroke of good luck
in the midst of misfortune...
that O Wol was able to survive.
I am sure this experience
has made you more aware...
of what kind of people the Kim clan are.
I had no idea they would go this far.
I am sure you are scared and in shock.
However, this is just the beginning.
They never give up the game they missed.
They said the late king did
not die because of his disease.
Then...
He thought the Kim clan is ruining Joseon.
Do you know your sin?
He dragged down Kim Hong Geun in power...
and exiled him.
He revised the law on bribery.
He stood up...
against the Kim clan like that.
But they are not the kind of people
who would sit back and watch.
Fortunately,
he avoided a misfortune...
and was finding evidence
to reveal the people behind it.
After the late King had passed away,
his food taster disappeared.
He must have been poisoned.
If we had moved more quickly,
he would have been alive.
I told you. It is not late for you yet.
But if you miss this moment,
it is too late.
It was a court maid called O Wol this time.
But it will be you next time.
I will make appeals.
To request to dethrone the Queen.
You do not have to do anything.
The King will like it that way.
All you need to do is to approve it.
Queen Dowager, please forgive me.
But I need your help.
All you need to care
about is the King's heart.
The King will see the Queen
in a different light after this.
Without knowing her ill intention.
The weather is gloomy today. It might rain.
Court Lady Han.
The room is dark. Light the candles.
Yes, Your Highness.
You will not see His Majesty tonight.
Why are you...
Will you be satisfied only
after taking everything I have?
Did you change the content of the letter?
You changed something
that is even more important.
Why can I not change such a thing?
I am not sure what you are talking about.
I know your lies.
If His Majesty knows the truth I know,
you will understand me.
The feeling when your loved
one is looking at you with despise.
How cruel it is...
to see those eyes...
for the rest of your life.
If you want to keep the lie,
leave the palace.
You found my weakness.
Reveal the truth to the King.
But you will have to
reveal another truth as well.
That you...
tried to kill His Majesty.
You know everything.
You...
can not do anything.
I swear...
you will also lose someone dear to you.
What is the matter?
You know it as well.
His Majesty...
is weak when he feels guilty.
It is what you have to pay for surviving.
It is what guilt is.
Did you go this far just
to win the King's heart?
Hurry and take them in before they get wet.
Hurry and take them in.
The cloud looked unusual
for the last few days.
It is finally raining.
My rank in this life is higher
than my rank in the real life.
But why is my life more miserable?
Your Highness.
Do you think I have this
life and the next life too?
According to the parallel universe theory,
it's possible.
Here.
This is our current life.
This is another life, Okay?
It is freaking difficult.
The way she speaks...
became weird hanging out with the Queen.
Do you think this puppy was
also a human in the past life?
It's possible.
That Mr. Fool over there too?
Sure. He would've done
anything I asked him to do.
How about me?
You will always be Court Lady Choi.
Hong Yeon, you...
Do you think my parents...
will have a comfortable
life in their other life?
What?
My mother has four fingernails only.
She lost her fingernails while
picking out stones in cold winter.
In her other life,
she would have ten fingernails, right?
Yes, right.
My father's eye would be perfectly fine,
too.
What happened to your father?
- He was whipped with a pitchfork. - What?
He must have borrowed
rice to fulfill the military duty...
and have not paid the interest.
They need to threaten people
to make them pay it back.
One out of every two households
has someone that is disabled like that.
Don't worry.
In their other life, all your
mother's fingernails are so shiny...
that she doesn't need
to get her nails done.
Your father's eyes...
are sparkling as if he's
wearing coloured contacts.
I want to see my mother
with ten pretty fingernails.
(Pouty)
Me too.
I want to see my mom.
You do not even know your mother's face.
Oh, no.
Why did you bring up her mom?
I mean, it's another mom.
I was talking about Lady Lee
Soon Shin who is alive and healthy.
She's even doing Zumba for fun these days.
Why are you making me feel like an orphan?
Gathering at the royal kitchen
where women are forbidden...
and whining like that.
I cannot understand women.
Mother?
Mom.
It's raining and sentimental.
Hey. Bring me some pajeon and makgeoli.
You should go to Daejojeon Hall quickly.
The rain is not going to stop for a while.
How do you know?
Are you a supercomputer from
the Meteorological Administration?
I do not understand
what you are talking about,
but given my wrist hurts like this again,
it will rain heavily overnight.
How heavy will it be?
I am not sure.
If it hurts this much,
it will pour buckets...
for a good several hours at least.
Pouring buckets?
Then the lakes and wells
will be filled with water?
Head Eunuch.
Yes, Your Majesty.
("Changes of Zhou")
To focus on the consecutive bed-sharing,
I want to go to my bed
chamber after reading more.
It is late. You may leave first.
Yes, Your Majesty.
("Wubei Zhi")
I will come back after your
emotions are stabilized.
Don't come unless you're
going to kneel and beg me.
I said don't come!
I knee every day,
but I did not kneel
before the person I should.
Your Highness!
You are going to catch a cold!
Catching a cold is nothing!
When the sky is helping me like this!
Oh, my, Your Highness. You cannot do this!
Please come to your senses.
Your Highness.
Your Highness?
Once again.
What are you saying, Your Highness?
Okay! Yes! This is great!
Your Highness.
What is that, Your Highness?
What kind of woman is she?
She is so unpredictable.
Oh, yes! Okay!
What is the matter, Your Highness?
Why are you alone unlike usual?
Did you come out to get rained on too?
I came to apologize to you.
Never mind. I don't care anymore.
No.
I cannot turn a blind eye like this.
I said never mind. Why are you so clingy?
"Clingy"?
I'm a simple person.
I curse when I'm glad to see someone,
and I pick a fight when I'm thankful.
I hate sweet talkers so,
get lost.
"Get lost"?
I gathered my courage to apologize,
and that is the only thing you can say?
Hey. If it's up to a person
who apologizes and...
not a person who is apologized to,
is it an apology?
But there are rules for the royal family.
Until when are you going to
speak in a weird way like that?
Until today. Just until today.
Everything will be back
to its place tomorrow!
Yes! Ah, yes!
Your Highness.
- Ah, yes! - Your Highness!
Yes!
Your Highness! Please come to your senses.
I cannot share a bed with you today
because you have hurt my feelings.
Sleep by yourself tonight.
Oh, yes! I'm so happy to hear that!
That was a smooth move.
Did you come out without an umbrella?
It feels great to get rained
on like this sometimes.
It feels like it washes
all the worries away.
Don't feel sad.
Your Highness, will you go inside?
Oh, my goodness. Your Highness!
Please!
What is it? Why is it
thundering at this very moment?
The sky is enraged!
Be enraged!
Be enraged by my pelvic
movements and pour it more!
Your Highness! You cannot do that!
Oh, yes!
Please!
Your Highness!
The Queen's mental illness
is getting worse every day.
She tries to end her
own life at every chance.
The core of the Internal Court is shaking.
Would it not be right...
to petition for dethroning the Queen?
- You are right. - Yes.
It is time for the Pungyang Jo clan...
to gather strength.
They have shown their
vulnerable neck in front of you.
You must bite it off.
The core of the Internal
Court is in danger.
Dethroning the Queen
is the right thing to do.
There was an immortal
being called Achilles.
But the heel was his only vulnerable spot.
They say he died from
an arrow in that heel.
That's the origin of the expression,
"Achilles' heel".
The actual reason behind his death...
is that there was no artisan
to make armour boots for him.
They say...
We might've not needed each
other if we didn't have a weakness.
Avoiding danger...
We're each other's weaknesses,
dragging each other to our misery.
But we also make up for each
other's weakness and save each other.
Hong Yeon.
You must keep my will
to buy land in Gangnam.
Yes, Your Highness.
Court Lady Choi.
You went through a lot because of me.
Finally.
(Choondangji Lake)
(I came here for nothing. Jang Bong Hwan)
I should write something to celebrate.
Now, everything will go
back to where it should be.
(Mr. Queen)
(This drama is fictional
and all characters, families, )
(dynasties, and events are
unrelated to historical events.)
The Queen is the most
eccentric and strange person...
I have met in my entire life.
As if she has come from a different world.
Whose soul are you trying to call upon?
Then I'm sure this woman
has completely lost her mind.
The internal crisis is more dangerous...
than the crisis from outside,
do you not agree?
You are saying,
there is an internal crisis...
that was not there before.
That means...
The interest that His Majesty
has towards the Queen...
will end up becoming our weakness.
Then today will be our first day together.
What?
>>>>oakislandtk
www.opensubtitles.org