(This drama is purely fictional. The characters, groups, events, etc.
None of which is relevant to history)
It's you
You are that guy.
I absolutely can't forgive
I must take your life
(Episode 12: Sword Dance)
(Episode 12)
Do you understand now?
Who is the owner of this palace?
I thought you were my prey and almost shot you.
Aren't you regretting that you didn't hit the target?
You misunderstood
You better remember where you are now
I'm going to change my clothes.
It's your highness
I need you to do something in Yijinfu
Do you have to be so cruel to Hongyue?
What's wrong with me
Do you have to kill her?
After killing her, why do we have to throw her into the well miserably?
To threaten me
Are you going to do this to an innocent child?
I killed her
How could you have such a big misunderstanding?
If it weren't for cooking
I won't endanger any life.
The body found in the well was just a coincidence
Or someone is alienating us.
Keep denying it.
I'll only get angrier
It's really driving me crazy
It's really not me
Why do you always think so bad of me?
Because you've always been like this
What I Know About Kim So-yong
Fully capable of doing this
I don't even know myself, do you know me so well?
Who liars most often deceive
It's yourself
You always deceive yourself
Can you understand yourself?
You and I have now truly crossed the river of no return
I won't care anymore no matter what misunderstandings you have about me
It's up to you.
Who shot it?
We have been chasing for so long, who dares to...
The winner is decided
Let's go back
It's the queen
Blood
I go
Are you crazy?
It hurts so much
Forgive my fear
My hand slipped
I go
Are you okay, sis?
It's painful even if it's cotton.
Yipin, what are you doing...
Let me give an eye for an eye and a tooth for a tooth
You are dead
Huh
I will bear with it today for the sake of the three concubines.
After all, he is in a high position
That's right
I'm going to Heejeongjeon
But
I have to accompany you to change clothes...
Things are not good recently
I can act alone.
Those who are gathered here today
You should think that the Lord is a powerful person.
Always following the Lord
The title of Jiang Hua Shao Ye
Will become just gossip
The reason why the Lord insisted on holding a banquet
In order to change his position in the court
When he was preparing these things
Brother, what on earth did you do?
I am afraid
only
I have also prepared a gift for my lord.
Please wait and see.
Then your gift better not disappoint me
One point for Concubine Hong
Two points for Concubine Yi
Concubine Min Shu
Concubine Yin Shu also scored four points
Empress of the Middle Temple
very
So the winner
The Queen Mother
Please ask the Queen Mother to present the award
Just enjoy the process.
Did you practice secretly?
It's just that I'm better at performing on the spot.
So the actual combat is stronger
Congratulations, Madam
Cunning Woman
Now we are going to the main hall to attend the banquet.
There's still some time before the banquet starts.
Take a break before going again
Hunting must be tiring.
It's the Queen Consort
It hurts, right?
This one?
I finally understand why Eunuch Jin was so scared.
Niangniang
Go to the Dazaodian and change your clothes.
Just go back and take a rest
yes
It still hurts a bit now.
The banquet is about to begin
Why did Yipin do that?
Someone must be trying to drive a wedge between us.
Who is it?
Those who know the evil fate of the well
There are three types of history since ancient times
The most vicious rumor in the palace
The secret fight between women
Power struggles in the imperial court
Finally,
Poison
Is that why Choi Sang-Gong keeps mentioning poison?
I have lived in the palace for decades.
I've seen all kinds of poisons.
Taking away lives
A drop of deadly poison
Slowly let the poison disguise as a hidden poison that causes death
There are many cases where the cause of death has not been determined.
But he was definitely poisoned to death.
Yes, the palace is too dangerous.
Now it seems that the person who just looked like Han Shizhang
Yes, that guy.
Didn't see
I ran away immediately
Are you sure?
yes
Let me catch you.
Choi Sang-Gong
Who was that guy who just whispered to him?
Go and ask around.
I guess that guy's last name is Han
I can bet two dragon balls that I don't have
The party is about to begin
Won't start
As long as that guy is still rampant
What
Then wait for the experienced
Damn
How did this development relate to my experience at the time?
Exactly the same
That guy Cheoljong knows nothing.
It turns out that people still have to live their own lives so that they won’t regret it.
I'm going to be myself and ignore it
But that guy clearly added something to the water just now.
Could it be poison?
Really not.
No matter how dangerous the palace is
It couldn't be a group poisoning.
No
You see, anxiety and fear are contagious.
I go
where are you going
I go to crime scenes to secure evidence
That's the Dazao Temple.
My heart was swaying back and forth, causing my feet to go astray
Let's go together, my lady.
Why does it smell a bit like grass?
What did he add?
No, my lady.
Right?
How to do this
Your Highness
I've tried my best to prepare
But the party is about to begin
The materials have not arrived yet
The materials will come even if it is a little late.
Trust me, don't give up.
Then I'll think of a way.
Just give up
You'll be much freer if you give up, you fool
nave
You know this won't work.
Instead of struggling like this
It will only make you and the people around you suffer.
You mean
Do you want to be bullied like a corpse all the time?
I can't do this
I will try my best
If I am causing pain to the nave
Then forget it.
That's right
We have a no touch relationship
Ok I understand
Niangniang
Why do you say such insincere words?
What is insincere?
Even if I say nonsense, I say it from the heart.
I never say anything that I don't mean.
You are worried
Seeing His Highness trying so hard, I'm afraid he'll get hurt.
Oh, what do you know?
The most useless thing in the world is to worry about celebrities
And Wang
Every time you want to hide your true feelings
I'll say something weird like this
The water is poisonous.
Hello
Waiting for an experienced person
Just here.
not good
Did you escape?
Always pretending to be so professional
Just live for yourself
So what should we do at today's banquet?
Your Highness works so hard.
Without ingredients, the chef ran away again
Already finished playing
You mean
Do you want to be bullied like a corpse all the time?
I can't do this
I will try my best
Oh, really.
Hong Yan, thank you for your hard work
Oh, thank you for your hard work.
Hard
What's the name of the person who just left?
Why do you ask this?
Because I have to ask
I can't just tell you
oops
Leaving a scoundrel-like lady
Alone in the palace
I don't know what trouble will happen.
Oh, long time no see.
Because I have a cold
Borrow it, thanks.
Mimi is rice
Come soon
Hey, my old customers.
A lot of good stuff just came in.
Now is not the time
You got the wrong person.
oops
yes
Damn
Why are there so many temptations today?
But I, Choi Sang-Gong, will never waver.
Shang Gong
What can I do for you?
He actually hid such great strength.
Always pretending to be unknown
Your body must feel very uncomfortable.
How did you endure it?
I'm used to it so it doesn't feel strange.
I see
Is this all I can give you?
The man in the magic mirror
Is it really not you?
Really, I said it wasn't me
to be honest
Although this person who carved with a knife
Really like me
But unfortunately, this is not me
It's great to be able to sign the name of someone who looks so similar
I feel honored
Where is it
I said
This man is among the maids
Is it that popular?
It's more like a craze than a popularity.
I didn't know I was so popular
oops
What is the name of such a distinguished person?
Last name: Han
The name is Shen Yan
So you are
Han Shimeng
Don't forget
When the atmosphere of the banquet reached its climax
When the Lord rises
At that time
When you take out the account book
Hey little girl
I have something to trouble you.
Can you give this to that person?
Who is it?
That's her
Oh, okay.
grown ups
The young master asked me to give this to you.
I have something to say in the name of my family.
I'll wait for you at the pavilion.
No
Did you find anything?
You are here
I have something to tell you
So I took the liberty of asking you to come here
For me, family
As important as my life
but
After countless troubled nights
I have decided
Choose something more important than family
If my family disagrees
I'm giving up my family
From now on I
I just want to be your flower boy
You now
Are you kidding me, Busy Man?
You are...
There was such a transportation accident.
What did I do again?
Oh my stomach
Stick out your tongue
Stretch out a little more
My belly
It seems that he ate poisonous herbs.
Probably
Grind the marijuana leaves into powder and pour it in
I said everyone
no
Will the imperial physician come in person?
The Queen Mother asked me to come.
My aunt asked me to look at the drinking water.
I found out someone put some poisonous weeds in there.
This drinking water...
It's a drinking water problem.
How can it be so normal to wait for an experienced person?
As I look like a very sensitive type
If you are nervous, you can't even drink a sip of water.
Obviously looks like
Can fall asleep even when there is gunfire all over the sky
How can a royal doctor be so incapable of judging people?
I am an imperial physician, not a fortune teller.
But
I am a famous doctor.
It's hard to recover today.
Even if the ingredients come
These experienced people look like this
Which guy is it?
Guy I haven't seen before
Did you poison him?
I'm here for this party.
A specially invited expert sent by the master
His name is Li Shengli
Come save this hellish kitchen
for you
Anyone who sees it knows it's the queen
Isn't it?
How can you tell it's the empress? Looking at that man
I really don't have the eyes to look at people.
Now I am watching the dancing lady carefully. Why is she looking for her here?
The official lady
In the amusement park.
Isn't it?
tomato
What nonsense are you talking about?
This is a persimmon. You are a persimmon because it only grows for one year.
Where did the country people come from?
A person who is called an experienced person may not even know the age of a persimmon.
hateful
How dare you call a guy
Is it not okay for experienced people to call each other guys?
Isn't it?
Yeah, you guy.
That's not right.
What kind of skilled worker is this guy who left the kitchen and ran away?
What are you saying?
I don't have a stomachache
I thought that no matter what kind of ingredients I had, I would go to the inner farm.
Inner farm?
The King's Vegetable Garden
I don't know anything
See what's there
The beginning of cooking
Start by finding good ingredients
Next to the King's Garden
Is there no king's chicken coop?
If you have eggs, you can cook anything.
I'm starting to growl with hunger so soon
It seems to be for the banquet food
I've been hungry since yesterday.
I know I'm hungry
This means that the Minister of Personnel is also like this.
In a little while
The banquet that the master is so persistent about is about to begin
Looking forward to it
The banquets at Cheong Wa Dae always have a theme.
Because it's not just a dinner party, it's a political occasion
What is better?
What is the purpose of today's banquet?
What's this
There are also food recipes made by His Highness himself.
List of people attending the banquet today
This is the food recipe I have only heard of.
Will match the ingredients
Making new food recipes
how's it going
I'm too embarrassed to see you.
Encountered a thief
Food is not the goal
It's finally started
Didn't you say we're going to have a banquet?
Just presenting a few?
Is this a dining table bed?
(The food served to the king at a national banquet)
Could it be
Is this all?
(The food served to the king at a national banquet)
There must be others.
Your Highness
What's going on
Every year, the people cannot get enough food.
Most died of hunger.
In order not to forget such hardships
today
Prepared a simple
The meals people eat
Although the idea is good
But this is not the level of simplicity
Even if it is right to teach the ministers
For those who have come from afar
The adults of the three families
It's a bit unreasonable to give such a hospitality
That's right
You have to treat guests like this.
It's a punishment.
Although food is insufficient
My thoughts are profound
I hope you understand
(30 minutes ago)
Like this through
What is this graffiti?
Give me the potatoes
Let me show you
The big needle has only now found its original position
What
Now
Light the fire and pour the oil
Oil
Dare
My precious needle exploded.
I'll clean it for you.
What a big needle that is!
This is a 50-year-old acupuncture technique passed down to me by my master.
Come come come
If it's 50 years, then all that should be used has been used up.
No, I can't use it again.
I will pass it on to my apprentice.
Don't push me
alright
It looks good with a piercing in the middle
In the middle of the potato
Evenly fried in a short time
How did you come up with this novel cooking method?
Street food is a battle against time
An emergency like today is just right.
Street?
There is this thing
It can be said to be a battlefield of taste
It's food for surviving in very intense places.
Come
for you
Skin it
Me?
So who's coming?
It says it needs a mat
I'm here to see how the banquet is being prepared.
Cut it cleanly
Cut as thinly as possible
The end should be pointed
Because it is convenient to string the potatoes in.
Take some out. The fire is too big.
yes
The fire here is a little stronger.
Come Come
Everyone pays attention
Today we made
More than just food
It's the president's face.
What I mean is
This is the Lord's face.
Is this level okay?
Niangniang
Not a chef
Let me see
well done
They need to understand my purpose.
This is
Plain
Food for the people?
Your Majesty, don't you know what the people are eating these days?
(Dragon Beard Potato)
No matter how well-intentioned
Welcoming such precious guests
You can't treat it with negligence.
so
Although the material is simple
But the meal was prepared in a very fresh style
The first course of the banquet
Made from potatoes
This is
Potatoes?
Not your average potato
This name is
Spray dragon beard
Dragon Beard Potato
Because it looks like a dragon's beard
So it is called dragon beard potato
Eaten on special days
Special food
It's just potatoes.
What dragon are you talking about?
Too exaggerated
If there is no potato
More people lose their lives every year
Rough-grown potatoes
It can grow well even in bad soil.
Easy to store
That’s why it became the staple food of hungry people.
This fresh product saves people's lives
You can't say it's just potatoes.
Try it.
This is so delicious
This is the first time I've experienced this taste.
It seems our council is very hungry.
Is this a potato?
The three seasonings served together
Green powder is used
The Nanyang Hong family is located here
Venus leaf of Hwaseong Palace
Made with Chili Salt
Kosher salt
The red powder is
Using Barley Flower Sugar
What are you talking about barley flower candy?
If the barley flower is so luxurious
There's no need to worry about any danger.
It is the food that people usually eat.
Staple food ground into powder
Mixed with wild grapes grown at the gate of the Yin family in Popyeong
Producing beautiful colors and aromas
The yellow liquid is peach juice
This is where the Yongxing Min family is located.
Made from the finest peaches
The theme of today's banquet is
and
Although politics divides people
But good food brings people together
Let this place shine
The fusion of the three excellent families
I hope you all enjoy this delicious
Sweet Potato Zucchini Eggplant
After all the cutting and frying
Boil with broth and eggs and add tomato puree
A fresh experience of eating with a bowl
It should be surprising
Is it still far away?
Still a long way off
Meat powder plus soybean powder
Mix almost all the powders in the world together
Now waiting for the skilled hands to make
It is the centerpiece of today's banquet.
knew
What are you doing?
You have to use as much strength as I do.
This is the joint for the shoulder and wrist
Very bad action
Let you come with force, force
Use your shoulders and wrists to mix the powder.
master
All ready
Yeah
OK
It would be a shame if there was no meat at the banquet.
Plus the unconventional hamburger meat
Staple food completed
This is a comprehensive food
Starving for a year
The red color of this product, called the sweet of the year
It is also what the Japanese soldiers are pursuing.
How can it be so soft?
Steak?
How is it possible?
The meat is clearly out of reach.
I mean, people won't have meat during their hunger period.
In the words of the Qing Dynasty
There is a saying that dragon meat is in the sky and donkey meat is on the ground
Here is one more reason.
barley
bean
Soft Shell Meat
Belly
Put together,
Wheat Bean Soft Belly
McDonald's
Just like real meat
The taste is also very good and very filling
Can you still say that?
It's done
Pre-made pigments plus decoration
A treat for the eyes
The point of dessert is
Enjoy it with your eyes and mouth
This color
If you add a little surprise on top of that
The perfect party ending
(Baochun Yokan)
Although it is beautiful
But it's just the yokan that you can eat very often.
It seems that this magical scene has to be seen to the end.
This is not just convenient to eat
It is also a fortune-telling item with fortune written on it.
Because I embrace spring
So it is called Spring Yokan
The beautiful wish that your future will be spring
As the party ends
Check your fortune.
What fortune is this inauspicious in a sacred job?
(One more)
One more
Another one?
Next opportunity
(Next chance)
(null)
My waist My waist
I'm going to die.
Seriously, alternative materials
Put my soul in it
Oh, I'm dying.
Did it. Did it.
Do you know what I'm thinking now?
I know I feel the same way.
Fish cakes. I'm thinking of fish cakes now.
The Imperial Chef Who Was Almost Killed by Qin Shi Huang
Invented fish cakes the night before
I thought it was just luck but it wasn't
It must have come to mind after the last struggle
Inspiration for those who give up
It's not something that comes easily.
MILF
I'm going to be angry.
Drink this to moisten your throat
Her surname is Han
Your last name is Han, right?
Yes
The name is Shimeng Han Shimeng
Why is Shi Meng's name so exotic?
Han Shenmeng
Yes
But what is this
Nothing is a queen
I happened to leave the palace and go to Han's house
I looked through his family tree.
It is indeed a fake family tree bought with money.
Very much like Han Shizhang's ancestors
Because it's a fake yangban class, I won't bring them with me.
They use this dirty trick to pull the strings
My lady, now is not the time.
If you're away for too long, something bad will happen.
Yes, yes, Choi Sang-Gong has worked hard.
Let's go.
Madam, slow down.
Go fast
Niangniang
MILF
What happened?
Now there's something going on in my stomach
Folk art farm music performance
What happened?
So the water hasn't been thrown away yet?
What is that water?
That's water mixed with poisonous weeds.
Poison
Choi Sang-Gong
Here it comes
Yes, of course I'll come.
This is a banquet to celebrate the recovery of the nave.
Watch carefully from now on
What consequences will your actions have?
Cooking is not an ordinary thing.
There is no place that doesn't hurt
Plus, the head chef is good at suppressing me.
This is damn
Come on, come on
Any more potatoes to shave?
Choi Sang-Gong, please save Choi Sang-Gong.
Thanks for your hard work
sorry
Wearing a ghost mask with an old scar on the jaw
Excuse me
Wait a moment
sorry
It's not that you look so uncomfortable
Give me acupuncture and moxibustion
Prescribe the antidote again.
Don't interfere.
I'm the leader here.
Okay, okay.
This is a stinky hand in the royal kitchen
In the hospital, it's the golden hand.
There is a place for everything, for people.
But the big needle is more suitable for the royal kitchen.
Said it wasn't
There is nothing better than a big needle to prick potatoes
I'll use this.
What can't you touch?
Scraped potatoes are better.
I'll use these.
No, no, no
hot
Niangniang
The music in my stomach has stopped now.
Now is not the time
Niangniang
Choi Sang-Gung
It's not impossible to recover so quickly.
Strong Woman
Damn
Oily smell
Why did you take so long?
that
sorry
It was my hand that slipped and shot the arrow towards the nave.
No injuries anywhere?
Yes no
Hunting is just tiring.
Fell asleep while changing clothes
Really
apron
When did the Queen Mother prepare?
Wait
Your Highness has worked so hard to prepare this banquet.
Now is the time to highlight His Highness
I would like to take this opportunity to
Because I understand that people are hungry and don't want to be full
Those who set an example for scholars say
We will implement a reduced meal plan starting from today's banquet
(Reduce the amount of food on the imperial table and set an example for the people)
Reduced Meal
What does this mean?
(Reduce the amount of food on the imperial table and set an example for the people)
The king has always been in times of difficulty for the country.
Reducing food on the royal table
Share the suffering with the people
The purpose of reducing food intake is to share the difficulties faced by the country
Things to solve together
Like now
Food that can save dozens of people
It is a sin to become a piece of meat to please the tongue
So no matter who is in the palace
Bringing meat to the table will be punished
Not only meat, but also a sumptuous table is prohibited
Ministers are no longer allowed to enjoy drinking, singing and dancing
Stop the partisanship
If you disobey, it will be understood as a willingness to be punished.
Your Highness
Minister Jin Zuogen is terrified
Will report the sad news
They all hide their identities.
Criminals hiding in the Guards
To be by your side and protect you
So I created a fake identity.
When I got there, I twisted off the head and hid it.
It's time for pheasant neck
I should think that they are the backbone of strength that I have cultivated.
To uproot them and tear them into pieces
So that they can no longer get up
In such a good occasion
What are you doing?
Do you know what their true identity is?
A family with a rebellious background
A thief who robbed the literati
A person wanted for using critical writings in the public
They are all people who are dissatisfied with the court.
Hiding his identity
I will guard you by your side.
This was created for the purpose of rebellion.
Because this matter is very serious and urgent
I'm in such a hurry
impossible
This is someone's murder.
My warrior guard creates a flaw
A trick to threaten me
Someone's words
Who exactly are you referring to?
For example, General Kim Jakeun
Murphy
Do you believe in the backers of those three families?
Just a few words
Do you really think they'll stand behind you?
How stupid!
Please wake up from the illusion
Bold
How dare a mere official insult me?
This is beyond disloyalty and is treason
You are very unlike His Highness now.
Please calm down
How dare you order me, the king,
Your Highness, it seems like you have someone else you trust.
But if the limbs are cut off
That thing is useless.
Please forgive me for not being able to defeat the hot-blooded
And pay the price
The criminals were beheaded
Your Highness
I will use military law to control
Those who are plotting rebellion are no longer under the jurisdiction of the Imperial Guard.
So it has to be handled by the Yijinfu
Your Highness
Should the Guard Battalion handle this?
No, Your Highness
The Royal Guards General
Now you know the identities of these people, right?
It's possible that all the guards are rebels.
Violations of the Guards Camp will be dealt with in the Guards Camp
This is inappropriate.
Please think twice, Your Highness.
Disband the Guards
It is possible that the Royal Guards General will also be implicated.
but
If you will deal with sinners
If you give me carte blanche
From now on, Your Highness, you must abide by your promise not to do anything
I'll stop here.
It turns out everything
It's useless.
What are you going to do, Your Highness?
knew
I've given full authority to the training general.
Pray to the four gods who rule the land
and the god of millet, who is in charge of the five grains
The Grace of Siam Vientiane
The seeds planted in the ground grew luxuriantly.
Willing to serve the people
Live without hunger thanks to the mercy of God
Please
Your Highness
(Preview of the next episode)
Hearing loss due to the explosion
cut
There must be no problem.
Of course
No one else
I chose the way to live
So you don't die either.
Dust off quickly.
Let me hit you on the back of the head
What's even more frightening is
The Enemy Within
Niangniang
His Highness
His Highness, that's him, right?
I request to withdraw my power from behind the scenes
Lord
It was this entire palace that killed Kim So-yong