(This drama is purely fictional. The characters, groups, events, etc.
None of which is relevant to history)
(Grand Finale)
Stop
Search
yes
No abnormality
arrive
All the carriages carrying tribute must be carefully checked.
yes
Niangniang
Duxelles
Your Highness
Finally caught you
This mouse
What time does the ceremony start?
Noon
That's still early.
You can't relax either.
Let's go
Wait a moment
What are you doing?
I don't know either
There is still some time.
I really have to go now
(Episode 20 I'm missing my own life)
Your Highness
Wait a minute, I haven't sorted it out yet.
Oh my god
Your Highness
How unwilling are you?
Still wandering in the nine springs
Your Highness
Shangshan
Come with me
Together
Get out of here!
Your Highness
You go with peace of mind
Come with me
Niangniang
Your Highness
Are you still alive?
Shhh
Your Highness
what is going on
This dragon robe suits you very well.
It's me indeed.
Over there
hateful
Oh Yes
How do you throw so accurately?
Um
A trick that has been practiced for a long time
What has been
I'm a knife wielder.
oh
Don't do useless work
How many soldiers are there in the palace now?
Too late
That's the sound of the ceremony starting.
How dare you speak plainly to me?
So early
Kneel
Four prostrations
rise
They actually held the ceremony in advance
Let me tell you
Um
I prepared in advance just in case
What are you doing? Hurry up and get on with it.
How come?
The seal is missing
There is no jade seal inside
I'm crazy
Because of that sentence
My heart is warming up again
Lift your head
Greetings to you for the first time
The Queen
mother
Li Shengli
Aren't you Li Shengli?
You're crazy
still
Or am I crazy?
Steal the Imperial Seal
Haven't I always been crazy?
Then we still have a chance
Let's go
Um
It went smoothly last time.
Please open it quickly.
Shut up, it's so noisy
You really are
grown ups
Is it you again?
I told you not to come here.
Really
No one to ask
I was entrusted by the Queen Mother
I stole something.
This dazzling and noble thing
It doesn't feel auspicious.
What is that?
Imperial Seal
You now
Where did you go after stealing the imperial seal?
That's the Yijinfu.
I am here now
Have you fallen into a trap?
What to do for me
What You Do Here
I came to see my friends
Can't
Please get out immediately
Stop
How dare you touch my loved ones without permission?
You are crazy
How can I take out the imperial seal?
Imperial Seal
Do you want to see it?
There is a bomb
Run away
Thanks for your hard work
Breaking through Hanyang
Are the gates of the capital about to be breached?
yes
Please order the troops to go out
first
The top priority is to successfully complete the inauguration ceremony.
You guys wait for orders first
Soldiers are mobilized to guard the gates of each city
Go
Just wait until the ceremony is over
I will catch you all
How can we hold the ceremony without the imperial seal?
Oh
How could this happen?
Brother, what on earth did you do?
You are of no use at all
What is it?
so what
Now because of that
The blinding smoke of unknown origin
It's not convenient for us to attack
In order to carry out the ceremony smoothly
I will send soldiers to guard the gates of the capital.
Making a feint to the east and attacking in the west
(Feint to the east and attack in the west:
Make a noise in the east, and then attack the west to disrupt the operation)
Making a feint to the east and attacking in the west
(Feint to the east and attack in the west:
Make a noise in the east, and then attack the west to disrupt the operation)
What's wrong
(Feint to the east and attack in the west:
Make a noise in the east, and then attack the west to disrupt the operation)
nothing
I will go find the seal myself.
Go and call the soldiers back to the palace immediately.
What
Didn't you hear?
yes
How can it be so empty?
It seems that the outside diversion was very successful.
Finally got here
Are you nervous?
Nervous and
Excited
good
This is just before the game ends.
The feeling of facing the big boss
That's right, Big Boss
If you can't beat the big boss, you will die.
Who doesn't swear?
Play from the beginning
We only have one chance
Nervous?
let's go
Caught
nave
I'm fine
I was just frightened by the sound.
I don't feel any pain at all
nave
Don't move, Central Hall
Are you going to stop the coronation ceremony?
The nave is more important
Stop the bleeding first
Lord
Are you going back?
No reason why it's now
Please
Let me see him alive
Just take a look
My Body
Is it back?
Where is Cheoljong?
You can't save him.
But how could I save him? That was two hundred years ago.
(VIP Ward)
Hey Jang Bong-hwan
Zhang Fenghuan
Patient Zhang Fenghuan
stop
You can't run like that, Jang Bong-hwan
Zhang Fenghuan
Over there
Jang Bong-hwan stops
Catch Him
How can you run so fast, you bastard?
Really
Hello
It’s great to be young
Has he really been a vegetable these past few months?
(Daehan Bookstore)
Annals of the Joseon Dynasty
(Annals of the Joseon Dynasty)
Don't die
You can't just die like that.
(The 25th King Cheoljong's Annals)
No more
He disappeared
Your Highness
You can't just leave like this. Wake up, Your Highness.
nave
Are you okay?
I'm fine
Your Highness, you shed a lot of blood.
I feel like I'm dying of pain.
It seems that he will not die
This bulletproof vest saved both of us.
Thanks
What are you doing?
A king is actually in cahoots with the Eastern Bandits
I seem
Still a king
Why don't you just stay still?
If you are content with your position
Stay still
This is good for all of us.
I
The families of the people you killed.
You are the king of the people you once trampled on.
We must not stand aside
You seem to be out of breath.
You can't avoid my knife.
temple
My child, please, please
Please
Kill me
Live
Let you live in a world like hell
It's the punishment given to you.
If you dare to kill yourself
I will save you no matter what.
Even if your body is destroyed
I'll keep you company too.
Only the body is alive
What is it like?
It will be unforgettable
what to do
Hiding in the crowd is what you do best
A no-travel order has been issued
So there is not even an ant in the street
you
Nowhere to hide
nave
Your Highness, please end this battle.
Can't
There is nothing more important than the nave.
Don't worry, I'll overcome it too.
Your Highness
hurry up
I will take good care of my wife.
You are going to
If I were a step later
I don't know how things will turn out.
Go now
I'll be back soon
OK
Niangniang
Are you okay?
We have to find a way
Why are you so useless?
Please show us one
The majesty that a master should have
I'm so scared of the Queen Mother
Hold your position
Come down
The King and the Concubine
Greetings
Niangniang
His Majesty has arrived
nave
She is unconscious.
how's it going
Signs of a miscarriage
(Partial abortion)
Because the bleeding doesn't stop
(Symptoms of continuous bleeding and uterine bleeding)
If this continues
The empress and the fetus in her belly
It will be dangerous
But why did you withdraw the needle?
Now
It is a state where even acupuncture treatment is unacceptable
We can only wait for the two of them to get through this difficult time.
Tonight
It's a critical moment
Niangniang
MILF
Your Highness
Although I'm sorry
Because you need to continue treatment
Please temporarily avoid
Your Highness
Please go out for a while.
Niangniang
What I can do
There is nothing
nave
Both
Safe and sound
Your Highness
Now, for my world,
All is well now.
Your Highness
it's all over
I didn't expect that the guy on the Lord
He is really a capable person.
Niangniang
How dare you yell?
That's because
The decree that the Queen Mother move to the West Palace
What
Do you mean you dared to send me to the West Palace?
What do you think of my family?
What are you doing? Open it now.
The door cannot be opened, Queen Dowager
Why don't you open this door right now?
The Queen Mother Arrives
Open it
I heard that he was very healthy after being in critical condition all night.
It's all thanks to the Queen Mother.
Where do you want to go?
Can I report this to you one by one?
It has been decided to move the Queen's residence to the West Palace
Until then, you can only live in Tongming Palace.
No going out
Does that mean the Central Palace dared to imprison me?
That's ridiculous.
Get out of the way
Can't
Get out of the way immediately
The King and the Concubine
Even if I die
Please die here too.
What is the Queen doing?
It's the queen
How dare you
The era of the empress is over
Now the master of the inner lady
It's a concubine
Aijia is the master
Aijia persists until now
It's Ai's.
Everything will change in the future
Especially the one the Queen Dowager wants to make
Rules and Etiquette
This is accumulated over hundreds and thousands of years.
Do you think it will collapse in an instant?
It's already collapsing
Such a scary change
It has already started
Damn, super refreshing
Oh my god
Choi Sang-Gong
What did I just say?
Damn, super refreshing
You said so
Maybe my inner nature has been awakened?
The refreshing feeling in my heart
It can't end, damn it.
Neuropathy
Good mood
hateful
Dog-like
What's up
Sinner Zhao
Spreading rumors to frame the High Temple
Makes people doubt the bloodline of the prince
Tarnished the reputation of the royal family
The crime of throwing the country into chaos
Ordered to be exiled to the West Palace
Another false accusation
I definitely didn't do it.
Is that true?
I swear on the honor of my late king.
I definitely didn't do it.
Come in
The sinner below
Confiscating property and fighting a hundred battles
Imprisoned in Jeju Prison
His wife and children are not held responsible
Former Prime Minister Kim Byung-hak
Former Right State Councillor Cho Man-hong
Former Left State Councillor Kim Seok-geun
Former Military Minister Kim Chang-hyup
Kim Soo-hoon
Zhao Dewen, former Minister of Personnel
In addition, the criminals recorded in the text
Exemption from the death penalty and confiscation of property
Three years in prison
Wrongly accused His Highness Wrongly accused His Highness
We are just threatened by the traitor Kim Byung-in.
I absolutely do not have
Thoughts of rebellion
Please look carefully at your highness.
That's right, Your Highness.
We're just stupid
Took the lie that His Highness was killed by the Eastern Bandits seriously
Yeah
Then let me tell you about your other sins.
People who are now full in North Korea
The most sinful person
Is there anyone hungry here?
You use the blood and tears of the people
Fill your stomach
Forgot to govern the country
We should guide the people to take care of the people
Just trample the people underfoot
Pushed them in
A rocky mountain where even a hoe can't get in
And in return, they collected more taxes.
You are in a warm room
When I leaned back and rubbed my swollen belly
The people were lying on the cold ground
Can't sleep because of worrying about tomorrow's meal
How can I not be hungry?
How can I get taller?
How can I become bigger?
When you are comfortable
Even breathing is painful for the people
Don't think about the future.
Even now it feels like living in hell
That
Cherish your life and despise the lives of the people
The first sin
Let them live in hell every day
The second sin is not being able to think about the future
Let the father who cannot protect the family and
The father feels desperate because he cannot protect his country
The third crime
If there are people who have nothing to do with these crimes
Come to the front
Keep these sins in your bones
Repent
You are just shameless robbers.
That prince
He deserves to die. He is the worst.
He's the worst and most damnable.
He is the one who deserves to die.
He is the public enemy
Put that down and go.
Used every day
Although I can't go out and see people in the palace
That too
I always keep Jeon Sang-Gong by my side
Because you're honest.
You can't become a great man with different intentions
Too
People live in different ways
Madam, you are not angry as usual.
The Queen didn't know how to read the eyes until the end
I endured it all
What is the purpose of the crying Queen?
Niangniang
I will definitely live
Being alive is winning
Hold my hand
Until you escape safely
What trick do you have?
If there is memory
There is still Zhao Rong in your body
My brother found me again.
I will hide myself tightly
Really
real
hurry up
Sorry, Madam.
Your laughter is beautiful.
A lot of girls have changed
Haven't been myself for a while, have I?
At once
It's too big to treat it as the middle hall.
It's different from before the marriage, my lady.
At that time, I thought I could decide
Only Death
(Bad Comes Jang Bong-hwan)
Did you get back safely?
Niangniang
Father
Can't
Don't come over here if you're in this condition.
I went
How are you? How are you?
Father, you speak first.
No, empress first
Very healthy very healthy
Nothing's wrong?
Of course, of course
Thank goodness you survived
The coronation ceremony was not because
Did the army that reached Hanyang tremble in fear?
At that time, the villagers came forward to protect our family.
Open warehouse
Help their virtuous families
I just
Just listen to what the queen says
I feel so ashamed.
Just show your virtue from now on.
Of course, of course
Even for our little baby
I also want to be a grandfather with a clear conscience.
Oh my god, fetal movement
The fetus moved so quickly.
Is my grandson a genius?
Onion flavor
What are you working on so seriously?
Before I imitated
The secret recipe of Sanxiang Ramen made by the Empress
So
Let me have some ramen before I leave.
Cooked in no time
I thought we were in a peaceful and prosperous era.
I can relax now.
How can it get busier?
No one
Hongbiejian
I am busy
You can complain later.
I've stopped complaining.
You?
Because I have made great contributions this time
His Highness wants to give me a high position
That is to say
I am still Hongbyeol
Did you ask His Highness for the position of Prime Minister?
What is that ugly object?
What should I do if I have no vision?
This time I
I applied to join the diplomatic mission at the Institute of Translation
For a talent like me
North Korea is really too small
congratulations
Stop complaining
Then it became the business of the diplomatic corps.
Things to run around for
What is there to congratulate?
But I still can't believe it
Li Shengli is the queen
You who I haven't discovered yet
It's unbelievable to me
Is Douyi not finished yet?
You are here too.
Long time no see Zongzhe
ah
If Li Shengrui is the queen
That Zongzhe you
She's a woman too.
As expected, Jin Huan, you have a good intuition.
I heard you got an official position this time.
Your Highness gave it to me.
Oh my god
April
You go back first
yes
How come you are here?
The weather is so cold. Have you been waiting for a long time?
No
I just
What's wrong with you?
I have some cramps.
Are you alright?
Um
Your Highness is doing well.
no
I'm asking you, Yongping-kun.
I
Now the Three Political Rectification Office
Also stabilized the position
Thanks to you, I have so much work to do.
So what to do next
I want to use my strength
Distribute to the people one by one
Become a force that can surpass the power of the few
Let those corrupt people
No longer able to dominate
I think that's the hard battle.
And the end of an amazing journey
It sounds like I'm going to be busier.
You'd better get off work quickly.
Really
Better leave quickly.
Anyway, I have to watch it again tomorrow morning.
It really doesn't match me.
Even so, you have to organize
Take a break
OK
Fighting One
You also sorted it out
Dou Yi is really
(Nave Dictionary)
Did I lose something?
This feeling hurts my heart
Success
He finally succeeded
(Veritable Records of the 25th King Cheoljong)
(Chekjong Veritable Records)
nave
Isn't it funny?
(Cheoljong Goshin)
Zhang Fenghuan
hateful
Don't come over
We need to find Director Han first.
wrong
Is it the fastest to spread it to the public?
Why on earth are you running away?
Obviously did a good thing
Good things
But why surveillance?
Someone who did good things
Not surveillance
It is to provide personal protection for public interest whistleblowers
Public welfare?
Isn't there a surveillance camera in the food warehouse?
The one you secretly repaired
Me?
Wait a moment
Are you in charge of the surveillance video?
It's strange that there are always glitches.
To catch the thief
Why do useless things?
You are nothing like Jang Bong-hwan
Here we come
Why don't you come and tell me soon?
I've gotten into trouble
What
The surveillance video was given to the media free of charge
Very unlike my style
He must be lying.
Definitely
The Zhang Fenghuan I know
Not the justice type
Before giving it to the media
The guy who made the first deal with me
Isn't it?
Yeah, I'm that kind of guy.
but
I have changed
Really? Why?
have no idea
I just want to do that.
You stinky guy
Push him
Push him quickly
Really
Cheoljong successfully changed his destiny
I've changed too
But why is Director Han still the same?
(Cheoljong)
Hasn't the world changed?
Are Cheoljong and I the only ones who have changed?
(Zhezong's gentle courage shocked Joseon)
(Zhezong, who led the reforms by standing on the side of the people,
Queen Cheorin's non-status responsibility system)
(A role model for reforming monarchs, the achievements of King Cheoljong and Queen Cheorin)
(Cheoljong, laid the foundation for democracy in the Republic of Korea)
Please say something. Look here.
Even if history has changed
But the corrupt
No matter what method you use, you will survive
But in a beautiful world
Will not rot due to corruption
But a world where the rotten parts can be removed
Try to change your life
The world will change without you noticing
Just like me and Cheoljong
Your Highness
Um
Uh-huh
Your Highness
Can't concentrate?
The face of the nave always appears before me
It makes me unable to concentrate.
No more
I want to take a look at the rear of the palace
Come back and focus again
Next Steps
Allowing women over 18 years old to marry
Then
It is forbidden to take palace maids under the age of 10
Bring it to the inner lady
Then
What's next, sis?
Niangniang
Sorry Choi Sang-Gong
I couldn't concentrate from the beginning.
How long has it been since I last saw His Majesty?
Not me
It's our children
For prenatal education
How about going to see the Emperor?
That is to say
Your Highness
Um
The Queen Mother of the Central Palace went to Xuanzheng Hall
Oops, I took the wrong road.
Has Your Highness gone to build a grand palace?
Yes
Let's go together, my lady.
Are you so happy?
Oops, I took the wrong road again.
It's not hide and seek
No more
At this time
I finally see you
I really missed too much.
That short
It feels like a long time has passed.
but
Why do you always use honorifics with me recently?
Are you trying to scare me again?
(This drama is purely fictional. The characters, groups, events, etc.
None of which is relevant to history)
(Thanks to Choi Jin Hyuk for his special appearance)