=Secret Files Of XSA=
Secret filming at Azure One Base risks leaks.
I tell you to open the door!
If we don't agree,
they will end our cooperation at any time.
I'll kick you all out.
What exactly happened?
=Episode 13=
(Xizhao Provincial People's Hospital)
If I were you,
I'd go and talk in person.
Share your thoughts clearly with Uncle.
I believe you can do it.
Do you really trust me this much?
Whenever you need me,
I'll stand where you can see me.
To accompany you.
Hello, are you Lin Shoulong's family?
You can visit now.
Yes.
This way.
Yasheng, you're here.
Let's go in.
Sorry,
only immediate family member can enter.
You go inside.
Wait for me a moment.
What did the doctor say?
When can I be discharged?
Don't you see how serious this is?
Still wanting to be discharged,
don't you care about your life?
Azure One
is more important than my life.
The negotiation can't be delayed.
It must be done as soon as possible.
Alright, calm down.
We can't delay.
Stay calm, just stay calm.
I just don't get it.
What's so great about Shoulong?
If Shoulong Group's Azure One
is finished,
it will benefit everyone.
But in these past few years,
I've let you down.
Dad,
last time we had a good talk like this
should have been when I was in middle school.
I'm grown up now.
It's time for me to step up
and charge into battle for you.
Let me try handling the negotiation.
Weren't you not interested?
I'm really not,
even a bit annoyed.
But I can't just watch you
and Shoulong fall apart like this.
The difficulties Shoulong Group
is facing are indeed many.
Dad,
but they're not unsolvable.
Go ahead, tell me.
Lie down.
Close your eyes.
I'll talk properly.
Go on.
About the challenges Shoulong Group faces,
I've summarized three points.
First,
let them know Shoulong Group's strength.
Come in.
Dr. Fan, someone is here for you.
Dr. Fan?
Hello.
Hi.
I'm from the National Security.
Hello, please have a seat.
(National Security)
Here's my ID.
Please sit.
Thank you.
Here's the situation.
I'm here to ask you about something.
You performed Lin Shoulong's surgery, right?
Yes, I did it.
Was there anything unusual?
Unusual?
I mean
is it possible that Lin Shoulong's illness
was caused by medication
or human intervention?
Probably not.
I'm quite familiar with
President Lin's condition.
His past medical history includes
cardiovascular issues.
Recently, he's experienced
some mental stress
and emotional fluctuations,
triggering this acute heart attack.
Here are his
reports and some test results.
You can take a look.
From this,
we can see that there's nothing unusual.
I need to take a photo for records.
Sure, no problem.
Thank you.
(Laboratory Test Report)
How is he?
My dad woke up.
He wants you to come in.
Is everything set?
Alright.
This way.
No issues at all.
Temperature's normal, take care.
Okay.
You all come.
President Lin, take care of yourself.
How are you feeling, better?
Much better, don't worry.
About this negotiation with Gapung,
Yasheng has done a lot of work.
He talked to me about it.
I think it makes a lot of sense.
Yasheng used to be a backup role
at the company.
But outsiders see clearly.
He understands the company's state
very well right now.
So, I think
he should lead this negotiation.
Sometimes a bold move
might turn out surprisingly well.
President Lin, here's the thing.
This negotiation is quite technical.
I'm worried that Yasheng...
Yasheng.
From now on, if anything comes up,
discuss it more with President Jin.
President Jin,
please cooperate well with him.
President Lin,
maybe wait until you feel better.
Our negotiation can be postponed.
President Jin,
I'll seek your advice later.
And I'll report to you
my strategies and ideas
about negotiating with Gapung.
What do you think?
Absolutely, I support it.
Alright, alright.
Works can be discussed later.
Just focus on recovery,
and take good care of yourself.
Thanks a lot.
Experts reviewed Lin Shoulong's case,
and found no issues.
I honestly didn't expect
Lin Yasheng would voluntarily take on
the negotiation in the end.
The relationship between Lin Yasheng
and his dad.
How should I put it.
It should be called
both helpless yet unbreakable.
He acts indifferently on the surface,
but actually he cares a lot about his dad.
Most people are like that, aren't they?
Since his childhood, all approached him
with their own motives.
Even if their bond isn't about
teaming up to fight enemies,
it should be mutual reliance to survive.
Don't you think
since Bai Keqing appeared,
Lin Yasheng has changed a lot?
Didn't you guys investigate her before?
Any findings?
The information shows Bai Keqing
(Bai Keqing, Gapung student)
is an orphan.
(Senior PR Planner)
Gifted since childhood.
(Gapung University)
Adopted by Gapung couple.
Graduated college
with continuous scholarships.
After her returning this time,
she planned to work with
an international hotel.
But because of Lin Yasheng,
she switched to Shoulong.
And made a name in Xizhao.
But there seems to be no issue.
Bai Keqing doesn't seem aggressive
and can easily break
the distance with people.
Fairly honest.
But,
her questions are always crucial.
Makes you feel like
she's not that simple.
A woman in love can solve cases.
Huh?
Who are you saying is in love?
Not me, Lin Yasheng said it.
But I think
even if she's a master of disguise,
we're sharp enough to notice, right?
While she is approaching us,
we're also approaching her.
Where are they? Not here yet?
Please.
Can you stop focusing on eating?
We're here to work.
I'm not spending public funds.
Besides, we're in a restaurant.
Everyone's eating,
just two of us staring at each other?
Isn't that odd?
Right?
How's the food?
I seriously checked this restaurant.
Its rank is really high.
The flavors are...
Let me give it a try.
You can eat,
but pay for yourself.
That's so lame.
Don't get stuck in negotiations.
Focus on Azure One's R&D Base.
Now it's your turn.
These are all yours.
Young Mr. Lin and President Lin
are different.
We're having such a formal negotiation,
yet meeting in a place like this.
Chinese Compressor Factory's data.
You've seen it, right?
Products from these OEM factory
are technically second-tier.
No comparison with our compressors.
We're not the top tier,
but we can get the things done.
As far as I know,
your group's project
is a national key project
with strict commitments.
If you use Chinese compressors,
I'm afraid the product performance
will have significant flaws.
Let me tell you,
I'm different from President Lin.
He's a perfectionist.
Can't accept imperfections.
But I can.
I think we can launch first.
Then continuously optimize
based on the market feedback.
Maybe we can even create
something better suited for the local market.
As for the timeline,
a day early or late,
I'm not in a hurry.
President Lin, give me ten minutes to think.
Twenty minutes.
Alright.
Buddy, let's go.
Yasheng, how's the negotiation going?
Feels great.
It'd be perfect if President Lin was here.
He'd be proud of you.
President Lin,
after discussing with my team,
we agree to make concessions.
No longer insisting on tech exchange,
but hoping for tech equity investment.
What do you think?
You should've said it earlier.
That's great.
Looking forward to your guidance
and support moving forward.
Thanks.
President Lin,
since we've decided to collaborate,
I have one more small request.
Go ahead.
I've heard Zhongjing Chip's tech
is suspected of
defrauding national subsidies.
To be cautious, we'd like a tour
of the Azure One R&D Base.
Seeing is believing.
It's just a temporary visit.
It should be possible.
After all, seeing is believing,
rumors will naturally fade away.
Young Mr. Lin,
I think this matter
should be consulted with President Lin.
You know my dad's health condition.
Let's not stress him out.
Just a quick visit.
- Just looking around.
- Right.
Not enter the core area, don't worry.
President Jin,
please don't destroy
our hard-earned agreement.
What's wrong? Is it tough?
Or is the Zhongjing Chip not ready?
No,
I'll arrange it now.
President Lin, looking forward to guidance
and support moving forward.
I'll arrange the car.
(Gapung heading to Azure One Base.)
(With covert cams and jammers.)
Feijiang,
Lin Yasheng is taking Gapung
to visit the Azure One R&D base.
Thunderbolt has found
Gapung probably had
covert cameras and jammers.
Secret filming at Azure One Base risks leaks.
Using jammers,
they might launch a remote attack.
Orders are to prevent them
from approaching the base.
Xiaolong, send the address to Feijiang.
Got it.
(Shoulong Technology Industrial Park)
Seatbelt.
President Lin, welcome to visit Gapung
whenever you can.
He's tired.
Nurse, I feel much better now.
I can be discharged.
Don't rush to leave.
Once you are here,
the doctor decides your discharge.
President Lin needs rest.
Step aside.
- President Jin.
- I have something to...
President Lin, something happened.
What happened?
Keep your voice down.
Get out.
Patient needs quiet.
Get out!
President Lin,
Gapung's representative suddenly
supposed to visit ZJ Base.
Young Mr. Lin has already taken them there.
Visiting the base?
The negotiation were going smoothly.
But the Gapung rep
suddenly requested to visit ZJ Base.
Judging by the situation, if we don't agree,
they will end our cooperation at any time.
Yasheng is worried about your health,
so they didn't inform you earlier.
But I'm really concerned.
No way.
I'd rather halt the negotiation
than let anyone from Gapung enter the base.
Call him right now.
(Jin Chuan)
He doesn't answer the phone.
What are you doing here?
Who let you in?
Don't worry, President Lin.
I'll definitely protect Azure One.
Get out.
Leave now.
Health is important, President Lin.
Rest more.
Lu,
Lin Yasheng is just one intersection.
How much longer?
One minute.
Sit tight.
(Emergency Exit)
Open the door.
Vice President Lin will tour
Gapung guests.
Tour?
Got a pass?
No, don't you understand?
The group's eldest son.
Lin Yasheng, Young Mr. Lin.
Hurry up.
Here's the thing,
we have rules here.
Without President Lin's special pass,
no one can visit freely.
Don't you want to work here?
- Hold on.
- Sir.
Sir.
Who's in charge here?
Me.
Open the door.
I can't open it.
Don't you know who I am?
You don't recognize him?
No wonder you got
President Lin hospitalized.
Unbelievable!
Go tell your leaser.
Vice President Jin has arranged it all.
Sorry.
Even if our leader comes today,
without President Lin's special pass
he also can't get in.
Open the door.
I tell you to open the door!
Hurry.
Can't open it.
Don't fight, don't fight.
Stop it.
President Lin, what's going on?
Nothing.
Just ran into a fool.
It'll be handled soon.
Young Mr. Lin.
Yasheng, I just came from President Lin's.
He said no one can enter the R&D base.
You find my dad again.
Haven't I told you?
Don't go to him for anything.
President Lin got kinda upset
when he heard this.
I'm telling you,
if anything happens to my dad,
I'll kick you all out.
Mr. Jiang, my apologies.
There's a small issue.
It will be resolved soon.
Don't worry, don't worry.
With Young Mr. Lin here,
everything's under control.
Since Shoulong Group's attitude is like this,
what are we waiting for?
The terms of today's negotiation.
Let's discuss it another day.
Goodbye.
Wait, Jiang.
Can you handle this or not?
Didn't you see my signal?
Still hit too hard.
I thought you wanted me to
act more realistically with you.
Hello.
We've got it under control here.
Lin Yasheng went to find Lin Shoulong.
Don't know what's going on with Lin Shoulong.
Alright, got it.
Hold on, Matt's calling.
Gotta go.
(VIPER)
Hello, boss.
Half an hour? That urgent?
Alright, I'm on my way.
We'll settle this later.
(Jinkai International Apartments)
Bro, what does boss want from me?
Wear it.
Still need to wear a mask?
What are we doing?
Just wear it, no more nonsense.
It's not that, it's just...
About the money, you know?
Get lost.
Boss wants us to investigate someone.
To check if she's from Shura.
Go.
Who are we investigating, bro?
Bro, bro!
Just using force?
What else? Isn't that obvious?
Aren't you wearing a mask? Why worry?
Bro, bro!
No need, no need.
Let me do this, let me.
You've done this before, huh?
- Where you learned it?
- Forced by life.
Let me use it for a moment.
Know who to check now?
Copy everything.
Let's go.
(Xizhao Provincial People's Hospital)
Seems if Lin Shoulong is still alive,
all our plans will be on hold.
So...
Keqing.
Yasheng.
How's Uncle going?
My dad's fine.
Are these flowers for him?
I'm worried he might not like them.
You'd better go take care of uncle first.
He'll like them.
Alright, alright.
No need to say more, I get it.
Don't worry.
My dad's fine.
Yasheng,
speak properly once inside.
You've done really well.
Did the Gapung People enter?
You're keeping an eye here.
How could I let them in?
That's good.
Ready?
Report, we're ready.
This is the heart disruptor.
Just set it to one.
His heart will fail immediately.
No one will know.
If you want him to die faster.
The higher the value, the faster he dies.
You do it.
Take it.
I can't.
Father.
Useless!
We were set to sign today.
`But...
That's not important.
We can't let Azure One
have any risks now.
Shoulong,
Azure One.
Are they really that crucial?
Son,
your dad just wants to
build a national enterprise
that takes social responsibility.
Look at our Shoulong Group,
it's growing bigger.
Once Azure One succeeds,
it'll benefit so many people.
I just didn't expect
time flies so fast.
In a blink, you've grown up.
Dad,
please get better soon.
Azure One needs you.
Alright, I promise you.
Get well soon.
So I can support you
in doing what you want to do.
Alright, it's a deal.
From now on, I'll follow your lead at work.
But you must follow mine in life.
Alright, I will.
Listen to me?
Seriously?
Yes, I will.
Hurry up.
Come on, pinky swear.
Alright.
Dad.
Dad!
Doctor!
Dad.
Doctor! someone help!
Useless!
Dad!
Someone, come! Dad.
Take the family member out.
Dad!
Doctor, save him quickly!
Dad.
Dad!
Prep cardiotonic injection!
Dad.
Dad!
What's wrong, Young Mr. Lin? What's going on?
Go save my dad!
President Lin!
Keqing.
Keqing!
My dad is not going to make it.
He's not going to make it.
How did this happen?
What exactly happened?
(Lin Shoulong's death seems weird,
investigate quickly.)
(Security Department)
- Captain Sha, right?
- Yes.
Hello.
I'm from National Security.
Here are my investigation documents and ID.
Retrieve all surveillance
for this period from hospital
entrances and exits as well as
this ward's interior and exterior.
May I ask what caused Lin Shoulong's death?
Due to the patient's extreme emotion
overworking the heart,
leading to broken blood vessels.
Send us Lin Shoulong's related information.
We need to conduct
medical and toxicology tests.
Hold on a moment.
One minute and 42 seconds.
Only Lin Yasheng and his son were there.
Bai Keqing and Lin Shoulong
didn't have direct contact.
Lin Shoulong wasn't agitated then.
In such a short time,
how did this happen?
Where was Bai Keqing
before coming to hospital?
At home.
Distance from home to hospital
is basically consistent with the time taken.
That's strange.
Why is SAD investigating her?
Did she approach Lin Yasheng with a motive?
The videos are all intact.
No one else came in.
Could it be
really an accident?
In our field, nothing's accidental.
If there is,
it's just pre-planned
to make people believe it.
Expand scope of video surveillance,
keep looking.
Hold on a second.
Lu, you keep investigating.
Need emergency leave!
What's wrong with her?
Did she discover anything?
I don't know.
Xiaolong, rewind and play it again.
Okay.
Come on.
Watch closely, everyone.
(Oncology Center)
(Inpatient Medical Record)
Breast cancer.
When did this happen?
Why didn't you tell me?
Didn't someone also fail to
tell me what she does for living?
Looks like we both have secrets.
We all have things we need to bear.
Alright.
What did the doctor say?
I'm doing pre-surgery tests now.
If surgery is needed,
I'll let you know to sign for me.
I'm sorry.
It's my fault.
It's fine, don't worry.
After surgery finished, it'll be okay.
I've raised you well already.
I'm the one who should cry.
Why?
Is it because it hurts a lot?
Silly child.
My own sweetheart
is doing a dangerous job,
yet hiding it from mom.
Shouldn't mom
cry out because of fear?
(Azure One Base structure diagram,
please receive.)
(Lin Shoulong is dead. If Lin Yasheng rises,)
(negotiation with Gapung will speed up.)
Class is over.
Goodbye.
Boss,
how's the Operation Annihilation prep?
Missing two electronic components.
What about yours?
Hurrying with installation.
Tomorrow's shipment,
let Huo Min pick it up.
Huo Min?
Can he be trusted?
I've verified the map he gave me.
No issues.
How's the investigation on Bai Keqing?
Huo Min and I have checked her place.
Is it related to Shura?
Probably not.
By the way,
this is what we found at her home.
Busy yourself.
Yes.
Lin Shoulong's death probe is reassigned.
Now we must assist Huo Min
to get the components.
Control involved people.
Whose case is this?
It's mine.
Come over here.
Please open it.
What's inside?
It's just a product sample.
I don't know
about the details.
My friend asked me to bring it
for a domestic client.
I have customs documents. Check them.
Where are the documents?
Here they are.
(Customs Ex & Im Declaration Form
of the People's Republic of China)
Alright, you can go.
Where is you?
On your right.
- Got the money?
- Where is the stuff?
Be careful, someone's watching.
Abort the mission! Abort!
Hey, cancel the order.
I've arrived and you want to cancel it?
Okay, fine.
Boss, we're being tailed.
You guys retreat. Leave the rest to me.
Got it.
♪Clouds witness storms in silent chase♪
♪Seas heed tides' roar in hidden space♪
♪Movements in your sight♪
♪All lies in your heart♪
♪No regret in the fight♪
♪Your resolve stands like mountains♪
♪Risk runs through your veins♪
♪Your shine is as hot as the fire♪
♪Years pass unseen♪
♪Fame fades to mist♪
♪Lotus blooms with its own gentle scent♪
♪Even in murky and filthy mud♪
♪Guard this land we prize♪
♪Nothing we won't sacrifice♪
♪Victory bears my name♪
♪The nameless one melds into the crowd♪
♪Love this land we prize♪
♪Nothing we won't sacrifice♪
♪Victory bears my name♪
♪You're the mute one hums in the crowd♪
♪When tempests scream loud♪
♪You always stand by my side♪
♪Though buried in clay♪
♪You yearn for the spring scenery♪
♪Guard this land we prize♪
♪Nothing we won't sacrifice♪
♪Victory bears my name♪
♪You're the mute one hums in the crowd♪
♪Love this land we prize♪
♪Nothing we won't sacrifice♪
♪Victory bears my name♪
♪You're the mute one hums in the crowd♪
♪For love that knows no bounds♪
♪Our nation's heartbeat sounds♪