♪From an unreal world♪
♪You suddenly come into my life♪
♪Our destiny is written♪
♪It's unbelievable, baby♪
♪That out of everyone, I find you♪
♪It gives me a sense of love's warning♪
♪Challenges fall from the sky♪
♪Yet they lead me straight to you♪
♪Yeah♪
♪Every day brings a new chapter♪
♪I'm starting to embrace this bond♪
♪The most inexplicable thing♪
♪Love is destiny♪
♪I don't ask for too much♪
♪As long as you're my one and only♪
♪My answer is just you and me♪
♪Meeting you at the right time♪
♪No matter how many dangers arise♪
♪Let our hearts overlap♪
♪Move toward our future promise♪
♪Meeting you at the right time♪
♪Holding onto courage and faith♪
♪After the rain, I only love you♪
♪Forever love♪
♪Forever heart♪
=Love is Always Online=
=Episode 29=
Thank you for coming.
What would you like?
Uh...
I'm just looking around.
Oh.
It's my first time here.
I want to buy something
for my grandson.
Hey,
do you have any recommendations?
Just look around, it's all there.
Then,
I'll take this.
Chocolate ice cream.
Fifteen.
Alright.
I'll pay.
Sorry about that.
Hurry up, will you?
There's a line behind you.
Okay, sorry about that.
I'll wait.
It's fine.
But your attitude…
I think you should at least be polite.
He is an elder, after all.
Respect for the elderly.
You should know, right?
Besides, it's your job to serve.
What attitude do I have?
What's it to you?
It's not your place to lecture me.
So this is how you train your employees?
What's wrong with you?
How can you talk like that?
Manager Lin.
Chairman.
As a big mall,
we need to address staff attitudes,
or it will affect the overall image.
Understood.
I'll handle it right away.
Dear,
you're so amazing.
If I were there, I'd fully support you.
Of course.
I hate it when people pick on the elderly.
Dad would really appreciate
your sense of justice.
This visit to my family will earn you points.
Anything I should pay attention to?
Well,
I'll have to give you
our family genealogy and rules.
You might need to memorize them.
Okay.
Just kidding.
Just be yourself.
That's how I've always been.
So you were kicked out?
I chose to move out myself.
But,
after we're married,
my parents might want us to move back.
Do I need to
serve tea
and pay respects?
No need.
In our family,
apart from family reunions,
we keep to ourselves.
Not that many formalities.
But going there empty-handed
doesn't seem right.
I should buy something.
What does your dad like?
And your mom?
Your grandparents?
Honey,
you just need to dress up beautifully
and show up holding my hand.
Really?
Really.
If the sky falls, won't you hold it…
I mean, I'll hold it up for you.
Okay, I'll help you hold it.
Deal.
Wenqian,
watch what you say later.
Don't make things awkward.
Or you'll upset Anlan.
No matter what, I'm his aunt.
Do I have to watch my words around him?
This time,
Wenhua rarely wants to meet Yao Yuan.
Take this opportunity
to get to know her.
Mm.
- Dad.
- Mom.
- Hey.
Look,
Anlan said he'd bring his girlfriend home.
Why haven't they arrived yet?
Dad, don't worry.
It's not time yet.
How can we not?
This is a big deal for our family.
Any girl Anlan brings home
- has to be the right one.
- Exactly.
Grandpa, Grandma.
Oh, here they are.
- This is Yao Yuan.
- Hey.
Grandpa, Grandma.
Hello.
I brought some gifts for you.
Oh.
Thank you.
She's really charming.
When I was young,
I also learned painting.
After retiring, I painted some ink paintings.
How about this?
After dinner,
we can exchange ideas,
and you can instruct me.
No one gets your dark paintings.
Of course, you wouldn't get it.
Yuan can understand them.
Grandpa, I'm no expert.
Let's take a look later,
then we can exchange some ideas.
Yeah, that sounds good.
Mom, Dad,
there'll be plenty of time to talk later.
Miss Yao isn't going anywhere.
Right, go ahead and sit.
Dad.
Hello, Mr. Jiang.
Yao Yuan.
We meet again.
This is my uncle.
He works in our company too.
- Hello, sir.
- Hi.
Hello, Ancheng.
Alright, don't just stand there.
Let's eat.
Here, try this.
My mom's signature soup.
I raised you this big,
and you've never served me soup.
Mrs. Jiang,
didn't you know?
Once a son has a girlfriend,
his focus completely shifts.
Mom, don't worry.
Yao Yuan will serve you soup every day.
So quick to push the responsibility?
Brother.
Miss Yao,
I heard your parents passed away.
Just take Anlan's parents
as your own.
I will.
Thank you.
From now on,
please take care of Yao Yuan.
Since you've asked,
how could we say no?
Wenqian.
Alright.
I mean,
Anlan already spoke up.
Of course, we'll treat Yao Yuan like family.
Anlan,
when do you plan to get married?
Dad,
my brother hasn't agreed yet.
Why not?
I'm waiting to hold my great-grandchild.
Grandma.
Look.
Anlan is blushing.
He is. Let me take a photo.
Let me take a picture.
Come on.
One, two, three.
Perfect.
Alright, Uncle.
Yao Yuan,
I heard
you've been helping out at Anlan's company.
Yes, that's right.
That must be hard for you.
Anlan
has some bad habits.
You know that, right?
Probably.
- Dad.
- Be quiet.
About Anlan,
let me sum this up for you.
Stubborn.
Bad temper.
Loves to talk back.
And there's more.
Yuan, I'm telling you,
Anlan doesn't like
to lock the bathroom door
when he's on the toilet.
Also, when he showers,
he likes to play loud music.
Whenever that music starts,
everyone in the house
knows he's in the shower.
He likes to raid the fridge
in the middle of the night.
One time I came home from work,
I thought someone broke in.
You all enjoy watching me
embarrassed in front of her.
Is that so?
Jiang Anlan,
didn't see this coming, did you?
Brother,
when you bring a wife home,
I'll make you twice as embarrassed.
You don't lock the door?
Alright, enough talk.
Dig in.
That's my brother.
Grandma must be mistaken.
Come on, eat up.
Yao Yuan.
Eat more.
Thank you.
Here.
Huang.
It's been ages since we last met.
Yeah, it's been a while.
By the way, what are you up to now?
You look pretty well.
Have you settled
all your debts?
Not so fast.
Right now,
I'm taking it step by step.
Working hard
to pay off the debt as quickly as I can.
Being steady and practical
is pretty good.
Come on, try some.
Yeah.
Let me try the braised pork.
- How is it?
- Mmm.
Your braised pork is amazing.
Rich but not greasy,
melts right in your mouth.
That chain restaurant you opened before
still calls it their signature dish.
But anyone who's eaten there
can taste the difference.
Wasn't that place taken over?
It wasn't.
Look.
I just went there a few days ago.
They still serve
your signature dishes.
And the owner is
still your old business partner.
Hey, Zhengyi.
Zhengyi.
(Diner of Delicacies)
Xu.
Stop right there.
Tell me what's going on.
What's really happening?
What do you mean?
What's wrong with you?
Didn't you say the place was taken over?
Want me to take the loss?
Now what's all this?
Huh?
Reaping the profits alone?
Don't accuse me.
That's just how things were at first.
Later, Jiulong proposed a takeover.
They even offered me a manager position.
How could I refuse such a good deal?
Right?
But you should've told me about it.
That restaurant was my life's work.
For this place,
I put all my savings into it.
Even went into debt.
Now I'm stuck cooking in a tiny diner.
How will you fix this?
How do I fix it?
We already have a chef.
You don't know business., do you?
Cut it out.
- You…
- Listen up.
You can't steal my life's work.
You can't take my restaurant!
You can't…
Hey, are you alright?
Shi Zhengyi.
What's up, Boss?
Ancheng,
don't you think
Yao Yuan looks familiar?
Have you met her?
No, I haven't.
But that name,
I feel like I've heard it somewhere.
When I was little,
I loved playing
hide and seek here with my brother.
We'd play all afternoon.
Look over there.
Those are fruit trees.
In autumn,
we can come pick the fruit.
Hello?
Okay.
I'll be right there.
What's up?
My uncle's in the hospital
for a heart attack.
I need to go now.
I'll go with you.
Uncle,
what happened?
I'm fine.
I put in so much effort
in the restaurant.
I just got too upset.
What do you mean?
That restaurant
didn't go under.
The new owner is from Jiulong Group.
Xu told me
the debt was converted to operations.
Only I was kept in the dark.
I didn't know about this.
I'll find out.
Uncle, try to calm down.
Maybe there's a misunderstanding.
Misunderstanding?
A small fry like me,
no matter how hard I work,
I can't fight big companies.
Back then, I didn't want
to stay in the tea fields for life,
so I came to the city to make a life.
Finally,
I became a cook
and opened a small eatery.
Thanks to loyal customers' support,
I made my dream restaurant happen.
You've all tried the dishes.
Decent, right?
You've been a great cook.
That restaurant—
from dishes,
to décor,
to staff—
I poured my heart into it.
Now there's a new owner,
but even the name hasn't changed.
The menu shows
all my signature dishes.
Do you know?
Those dishes
were created
after countless burns
and countless failures.
It's okay.
I'm so useless.
No skills, no talent. Just useless.
Hard work doesn't pay off.
No one cares how much effort you put in.
Mrs. Jiang already knows.
She asked me to bring Shi some supplements.
Boss,
tell me,
ever since Ancheng lent money to Shi,
has this been planned all along?
I think he initially just wanted to help.
As for who planned what happened later,
and whether he knew,
I'm not sure.
Objectively speaking,
Ancheng's team came up with this.
We can't put all the blame on him.
Even so,
my brother didn't stop it.
Uncle,
have some fruit.
It'll help you recover.
Yuan,
Anlan was just here,
and I didn't get to ask.
How is he with his brother?
From what I know, pretty good.
His brother is a very upright person.
I don't think he is to blame
for the restaurant.
Maybe so.
He's helped me a lot,
and I'm grateful.
But if it's not what we think,
you should cut Anlan some slack.
After all, they're brothers.
Don't worry.
Anlan will handle it well.
Ancheng,
I've invited Chairman Zhang.
He's here.
Hi.
Mr. Zhao.
Mr. Ma.
- Mr. Zhang.
- Okay.
Please have a seat.
Please.
Have a seat.
Thanks for coming today.
Some of my recent projects hit a few snags.
My father's been critical of me.
So I want to take this chance to explain
my plans for the Group's future development.
You want to hear what we think, right?
I want to show my drive and determination
and earn your support.
Then we'll be honest.
Frankly, we don't like
some of your ways.
Take Liu from my department last year.
He was dealing with a divorce,
inevitably slipped up a bit.
You kicked him off the project
like his effort meant nothing.
And recently,
you took on that restaurant project.
Finance said
you knew what was going on.
How could you let them bleed money like that?
I think
you misunderstood me.
Manager Liu was reassigned
because he was moonlighting.
As for the restaurant,
Mr. Jiang
didn't get involved.
Funny.
Isn't that the very project
you used to fill your performance gap?
I know you're serious.
But regarding performance,
you show no mercy.
What if someone disagrees with you?
What happens then?
Which is why I hope
we understand each other better.
With your support,
I'll have the space
to bring our shared vision to life.
Don't you agree?
Here's to you all.
Come on.
Cheers.
Let's drink.
Alright.
Cheers.
Zhang,
finish yours.
Last time at your place,
I drank way too much.
Yeah.
- Bottoms up.
- Cheers.
Come on.
Here, one more round.
Ma, drink more.
Come on.
- Drink up.
- Cheers.
Picked a wedding gift for Jiang yet?
I've been thinking about it.
But...
They finally made it official.
Anything will do.
Jiang is here.
Let's raise a glass to Jiang.
To celebrate his engagement.
Thanks, guys.
Jiang,
let's have a drink.
Congratulations.
You finally beat me
and won Yao Yuan's heart.
There's no winning or losing here.
I never saw you as a real rival.
Anlan, you're way too confident.
When it comes to flirting,
you might not beat Su Wen.
Here's your chance. Buy me a drink.
Isn't there some alcohol
in your glass?
You can buy a second, even a third.
So we can…
Sorry.
You actually turned her down?
I think Su Wen must be ill.
Didn't I tell you
that I've changed?
Better to stay single than settle,
that's my new rule for love.
A leopard can't change its spots.
How could you suddenly change?
No point forcing it
with someone you don't love.
I won't settle out of loneliness.
Or be alone because I made a mistake.
Is this really the Su Wen I know?
Love isn't supposed to be a shelter.
The more you treat it like one,
the easier you get pushed out.
So I've decided I'll stay single
until I find true love.
If I'd understood this sooner,
I would've avoided the wrong turns.
Let's raise a glass to Su Wen.
To Anlan's engagement
and Su Wen's fresh start.
Here's to that.
Jiang,
shouldn't you let Yao Yuan know
you'll be home late?
It's nothing.
You're not being henpecked,
are you?
It's just pre-wedding jitters.
Stop talking nonsense.
Like anything could stump the boss.
You're back.
How's uncle doing?
His condition is stable for now.
But he needs some rest.
Don't worry. Uncle will be fine.
Be focus on the wedding now.
That'll make him feel at ease.
By the way,
I've packed your clothes, bags, and shoes.
All sorted by season and color
and packed.
Xinran, thank you.
You've always taken care of me.
Well, you are my cousin.
I can't believe I'm really leaving.
After all these years living with you,
I'm moving out.
You'll live all by yourself.
Silly girl.
We'll both get married sooner or later.
We'll eventually separate.
But now, Anlan is here to take care of you.
That puts my mind at ease.
Hello.
Cheers.
Oh,
you're about to become Mrs. Jiang soon.
From now on,
will we still hang out?
Of course we will.
We'll still be friends after marriage.
We'll definitely hang out.
But the topics will be different.
Mostly about husbands.
You both have your futures set.
But
I'm still lagging behind.
How are things going with Ancheng?
I like him.
But I feel like he's so mysterious.
Hey, Yao Yuan.
Besides Fang Jianing,
has the Ace mentioned
if his brother has a girlfriend?
We never talk about that.
You've gone on dates,
haven't you figured it out?
He said Fang Jianing is like his sister.
But,
before marriage,
everyone has a chance, right?
Forget about it.
Today's star is my cousin.
I've made up my mind.
Since I like Ancheng,
I'll spend more time getting to know him.
How else will we know if we fit?
Right?
I must be out of my mind.
Coming here with you,
and bringing Wen Cheng.
I'm here to stop a mistake.
What exactly are we doing here?
Isn't that Fang Jianing?
I don't think they are in the same company.
It's noon. They're probably going to eat.
So they're going on a date.
Is a meal between colleagues a date?
Yeah, it's just having a meal.
Coming this way.
Let's follow them.
Huh?
What a terrible idea.
I'm curious.
Let's go.
Ancheng,
are they all on board
with our no-plastic initiative?
Yes.
That's why we need to confirm some details.
Come on, what are we doing?
Mr. Jiang,
I've banned the use of plastic bags
as you instructed.
We even switched the takeout utensils
to eco-friendly materials.
Isn't that Yao Yuan's uncle's restaurant?
I plan to turn this place
into a low-carbon, eco-friendly showcase.
Ancheng,
after the merger,
Xu and I have been dedicated
and managing according to the strategy.
Thanks to Mr. Jiang and Chen
taking over,
I've been able to keep the business going.
Now it's getting better and better.
Back when we first partnered with Shi,
he was managing blindly.
But now he had a heart attack
after it was taken over.
I shouldn't say more.
Right?
How could you do this?
Shi got sick because of this, didn't he?
You set him up.
Then,
isn't this called hostile takeover?
Don't use every negative
business term you've heard.
Things might not be what you think.
You can tell by how guilty this person looks.
Did you take advantage of Yao Yuan's uncle?
Misunderstandings or what,
Ancheng is not that kind of person.
You. Explain.
What's really going on?
How come people are
talking about Ancheng like this?
You have no respect at all.
This is our company's business.
Mr. Jiang isn't someone you can question.
Don't waste time.
Let's go.
Jianing.
How could you do that?
Other people's hard work
means nothing to you, does it?
It's just normal business operation.
It's also the company's strategy.
I know I don't have your experience.
But he's Yao's uncle.
If Anlan finds out, he'll be furious.
He doesn't know...
Why is it always about Anlan?
I thought you understood me.
Is that what you think of me?
I'm sorry.
So my uncle's restaurant
was sold to Jiulong Group
by his partner?
I'm sure of it.
When I mentioned Shi Zhengyi,
Jiang Ancheng looked really off.
We checked the menu online.
All three chain restaurants still have
your uncle's signature dishes.
Why would Ancheng do this?
Before, my uncle and I thought
it was Jiulong Group's strategy.
Unexpected.
Jiulong is Anlan's family business.
How can it be like this?
No matter whose company it is,
malicious intent can't be forgiven.
But this kind of practice
is usually done within legal bounds.
Anlan said,
talent is the greatest asset.
I believe he won't approve of this.
He won't ignore it.
Are you here for Shi Zhengyi?
You took over his business?
Yes.
He couldn't pay back his debt.
After evaluation,
we found he was not business-savvy,
but his choice of locations was good.
So I decided to take over.
Just because it's more profitable?
So you just watched
as his business failed?
My earlier loan was purely personal.
I don't decide on the investment.
Didn't you also say
that those meant to fail
are destined to do so?
Business isn't as simple as he thinks.
He's completely an amateur.
So you're the expert?
When you lent him money,
you knew he'd fail, right?
Are you blaming me for helping him?
Or are you saying
I abandoned him
for my own gain?
Is that part of your reported achievements?
You know I left the company
because I couldn't stand this approach.
I don't need your approval.
But you can't mess with Yao Yuan's family.
Dad was right.
You'd question family
for Yao Yuan without hesitation.
Don't mix things up.
You shouldn't, either.
You repay his debts your way,
and I do business my way.
No interference.
You know about her uncle
falling sick, right?
You need to make amends.
If I hadn't stepped in,
Shi's restaurant would've shut down long ago.
Everyone would have been fired.
Do you think you're helping him?
You're no different than a corporate vulture.
Don't lecture me with your theory.
It doesn't apply to me.
Ancheng.
What's up?
It's because of Anlan.
He scolded me for some outsider.
Outsider?
Who?
That chain restaurant acquisition you led.
Oh, that one.
You two argued
because of Yao Yuan's relative?
He even called me a corporate vulture.
He really said that?
Isn't he basically
calling Jiulong a vulture company?
Oh, man.
What's going on?
Uncle.
It's all because of Yao Yuan.
Last time,
we took over your uncle's restaurant.
Now, Anlan
confronted Ancheng about it.
I came because of her, too.
Don't you think
she looks familiar?
Do you remember
Mr. and Mrs. Yao back then?
Dad, when will you finish talking?
Soon.
Wait here for a moment.
We'll go in first.
Sit for a bit.
Alright.
See you.
You can't pull out now.
I'm sorry.
This is the company's decision.
This is the toughest time for us.
Can you give us a little more time?
Look,
we've proposed a plan to improve operations.
And by the way,
we've always
placed great importance
on employee welfare.
Facing this difficulty,
we had no choice but
to cancel all company benefits.
We've also implemented pay cuts.
If you'd done this from the start
when there were losses,
wouldn't it be solved?
It's not that simple.
Employees are our most valuable asset.
They deserve
the best benefits.
That mindset is exactly
why the crisis is this severe.
Your operational plan seems useless.
That's not true.
Everyone knows the situation.
No one has quit.
In fact, they vowed
to fight alongside us to the end.
The data says
recovery will
take a year.
Can you guarantee
they'll work just as hard
with pay cuts or even working without pay?
Of course.
This improvement plan
is based on precise calculations.
It's solid.
Please trust us.
Mr. Yao,
Mrs. Yao,
we've given you a chance.
Your operations haven't been good.
We only decided to withdraw investment
after observing for a year.
This is just a transition.
It's inevitable.
We will get through it.
Our hard work will pay off.
I'm sorry.
Please go back.
Dad.
Yuan.
Let's go, sweetheart.
We're having a feast.
Really?
What's the occasion?
Do you think
their plan is viable?
The risk is too high.
I agree with Wu Wei.
Paperwork claims
they'll break even in six months
and recover in a year.
They attached enough confirmed actual orders.
But
clients are fickle.
Until orders are signed,
they mean nothing.
I feel bad for them.
Nothing we can do.
Data rules all.
The Jiang family motto is simple:
Maximize profit, minimize risk.
If a company can't turn a profit
or feed its staff,
it should close down.
Ancheng,
do you understand?
I understand.
If you consider
every individual's plight,
that misplaced mercy
will cloud your risk assessment.
So it was her.
I heard
they had a car accident,
and only the daughter survived.
We even went to see her, right?
This is it.
Wait.
Give this to her.
I'm not going.
You handle it.
I'll wait here.
Hello.
This is a small token from our company.
Please accept it.
Here.
Take it.
Just take it.
Young lady,
it's enough
to support you for a while.
Why won't you accept it?
Come on, take it.
Take it, please.
Please, take it.
I never expected
to see her again.
How did she end up
as Anlan's girlfriend?
No, his fiancée?
Looks like
Yao Yuan doesn't know about this.
No,
Anlan knows about it.
Right,
he found out during his internship
at the company.
He even punched me.
Did he love her
even then?
Seems like this is
more complicated than we thought.
Anlan must've
been watching Yao Yuan for a while.
I wonder how she'll react
when she finds out.
Mr. Jiang.
Why were you
stalking me?
I'm really sorry.
We didn't mean to follow you.
It's all my fault.
I just wanted to know
if you had a girlfriend.
So I took Yao Xinran
and Wen Cheng along to...
We aren't close enough for that.
It's my mistake.
I overstepped.
I'm sorry.
Save your explanations.
You disrespected me
and caused trouble.
Don't contact me again.
We shouldn't meet anymore.
Ancheng.
Please.
I know I was wrong in this.
I apologize.
You just said that
because you're upset right now.
You have to trust me.
I really didn't mean any harm.
Please forgive me, okay?
You should go.
Well,
can we still be friends?
Wait a minute.
Don't tell Yao Yuan
that you came here today.
Hey, how did it go?
To be honest,
if I were Ancheng,
I'd be really upset too.
No one likes being stalked.
But you don't have to feel bad.
Someone who does this kind of thing
is too calculating
for you to handle.
Don't make him sound so cunning.
He used to be nice to me.
You're still defending him?
You did mess up.
But you admitted it and want to change.
Besides, you didn't mean to cause trouble.
But to be fair,
we did cause them some trouble.
You silly girl,
do you think Ancheng likes you?
He stopped me as I left.
Not to ask me to stay,
he wanted me
but to warn me not to tell Yao Yuan I came.
Why?
I don't really understand what he meant.
Why keep it from Yuan?
What does Yuan have to do with it?
Jiulong Group.
(Jiulong Group)
Jiulong Group is Jiang Enterprises.
Huh?
The Jiang family is the reason
Yuan's family went bankrupt.
♪I want to take you to the tropics♪
♪To a blue sea of love♪
♪The aurora spills down♪
♪Still not enough to express my heart♪
♪I can show you all the colors of the world♪
♪Or wait for you alone♪
♪Every moment, I give you♪
♪The most romantic arrangement♪
♪The stars, the moon♪
♪I'll pluck them all for you♪
♪On different canvases♪
♪Blending different hues♪
♪To make our tomorrow♪
♪The most beautiful hope♪
♪I want to give you♪
♪All the best this world has to offer♪
♪Only to find♪
♪The best in the world is you♪
♪Even the air is filled with love♪
♪Because we have each other♪
♪Two people together♪
♪Relying on one another♪
♪I want to give you♪
♪All the best this world has to offer♪
♪Only to find♪
♪The best in the world is you♪
♪Even if small troubles come our way♪
♪I won't let them stay♪
♪One love, one heart♪
♪Wholeheartedly yours♪
♪Never to be apart♪
♪I want to take you to the tropics♪
♪To a blue sea of love♪
♪The aurora spills down♪
♪Still not enough to express my heart♪
♪I can show you all the colors of the world♪
♪Or wait for you alone♪
♪Every moment, I give you♪
♪The most romantic arrangement♪
♪The stars, the moon♪
♪I'll pluck them all for you♪
♪On different canvases♪
♪Blending different hues♪
♪To make our tomorrow♪
♪The most beautiful hope♪
♪I want to give you♪
♪All the best this world has to offer♪
♪Only to find♪
♪The best in the world is you♪
♪Even the air is filled with love♪
♪Because we have each other♪
♪Two people together♪
♪Admiring one another♪
♪I want to give you♪
♪All the best this world has to offer♪
♪Only to find♪
♪The best in the world is you♪
♪Even if small troubles come our way♪
♪I won't let them stay♪
♪One love, one heart♪
♪Wholeheartedly yours♪
♪Never to be apart♪