(Floss)
Excuse me.
Hey! What are you doing?
Any plans later?
Netflix and chill at my place?
Let me see. I’m rather tired.
Li Ting!
Hey!
Ah, where were we?
You wanna tell me
what’s happening in the movie?
It’s late.
Maybe some other time.
Actually…
You are welcome to stay over.
Nah. Diandian’s gonna miss me.
See you next time.
Oh yeah, right!
Sorry for the wait.
Diandian, look what I got for you.
Not again!
You’re spoiling him.
Where’s my floss?
Theses should be enough.
I want floss in dispensers, not the picks.
They're the same. I think picks are better.
You never kiss me, Why?
I just did!
No. I meant the French kissing.
Does my breath smell?
Seems like it.
What did I eat tonight?
What about now?
What’s wrong?
I’m rather tired.
Spit out.
That’s a lot of spit.
Your lower teeth are OK,
but upper ones could be adjusted.
How’s it going with Mark?
It’s OK.
You slut!
That was a very horny sound you made.
You got me hard down there.
Happy birthday!
Wow, this is so expensive!
I can’t. Just had my teeth cleaned.
Cheers!
Sorry! Sorry! Sorry!