♪Tear up all the memories of the past♪
♪Let go of all regrets♪
♪I exchange my whole life for a change♪
♪If I decide to let my guard down♪
♪Will I fall for the wrong one♪
♪I dare to give
without fear of destruction♪
♪Love refuses to fall asleep♪
♪I dare to shake heaven and earth♪
♪Even with different paths and goals♪
♪I have no regrets♪
♪Because you're
an unsolvable riddle by fate♪
♪I pray for a miracle♪
♪Over the time♪
♪Even if I'm burned out♪
♪I'm willing to search for the miracle♪
♪Of being with you forever♪
♪I will travel with you all the way♪
♪Love is the most beautiful in life♪
=Sword and Fairy=
=Episode 18=
I bet you've upset Her Lordship again.
Go apologize to her.
Shuo Xuan, ever since I met you
in the Jincui Oasis,
you've been treating me badly.
Do I owe you money
or have I done something to you?
You took away my mother.
You are Zhu Yu's daughter too?
My mother was Ling Ye,
the former queen of our clan.
The body that Zhu Yu is using now
is my mother's.
Hundreds of years ago, the Yu Clan
resided at the bottom of the North Sea.
Our Queen Ling Ye,
my mother,
found a nice and warm habitat
at the North Sea
and migrated the entire clan there.
Hundreds of years later,
the Sea of Clear Skies prospered
and became the Pearl of the North Sea.
And then? How did Ling Ye pass away?
How did Zhu Yu become
the Lord of the Yu Clan?
Nobody knew
the Sea of Clear Skies
was built on the back of Kun.
Kun was born from the sea.
It sleeps for hundreds of centuries
to gather strength,
waiting to jump out
of the sea and ascend.
You're right.
On the day of its ascension,
the Sea of Clear Skies on its back
almost collapsed into ruins.
My mother Ling Ye drained her power
to reach Kun's awareness
via the Meditation Spell
and stopped the ascension.
So Kun was Zhu Yu?
Her Lordship stopped ascending.
She took over Ling Ye's body
and started saving the Yu Clan.
She housed all the survivors here
and treated them with her life power.
Years later, those who were
less injured or had greater energy
could finally move around.
All the survivors of the Yu Clan you see
are cured by Her Lordship
with her life power.
She was drained and about to die.
But thanks to Qiyuan...
Since you're back to Her Lordship now
and become the young lord,
you should appreciate
her sacrifice for the clan.
She ended up like this
because of us.
Zhu Yu.
I thought you were gone.
Zhu Yu, Shuo Xuan told me
what happened back then.
I didn't know you had suffered.
So will you stay
at the Sea of Clear Skies?
I'm willing to offer you anything
as long as you stay.
You're still mad at me as I lied to you?
No, it doesn't matter anymore.
Zhu Yu, Shuo Xuan would make
a better young lord than me.
There's nothing I can do here right now.
I don't feel the responsibilities
she mentioned.
I want to go out there
and gain strength.
Only then can I be helpful
to you one day.
My daughter is a big girl now.
I often recall the days
when I was carrying you.
I was amazed.
You were such a tiny creature.
Yet your heart pounded louder
than anything in the world.
I said you were free
to stay or leave.
The Sea of Clear Skies moves.
Take it with you
and you'll sense my location.
Next time I come back,
I'll bring you
my favorite Ji's pastries.
Go.
Mr. Gu.
You're finally here.
It looks like someone has told you
I'd come by today.
Miss Ming wouldn't eat or come out.
Is she fine in there?
There is a reason. Xiu hates to
meet people on her birthday.
I apologize on her behalf.
Please don't say that.
Mr. Ju, do you own this property?
Well... I guess.
Senior, what...
He lost it without any sign.
Like "master", like "disciple".
Master.
I rarely come to Jing'an.
I heard that the river view
in the city is amazing,
especially at night.
Xiu, come with me for a walk.
Join us at the port for fine wine.
I'll go get Jinzhao.
Here. Come on.
Welcome. Pick whatever you like.
Look, the lanterns are also
local specialty.
Look around. Pick anything you like.
This one? Alright.
It's a pretty lantern.
Thank you, Shifang.
Don't mention it.
And for Mr. Gu. Here.
Get him the same one as yours.
What do you say?
Thank you. Such a delicate lantern
brings out the deepest nostalgia.
Jinzhao, check this out.
If Little Yue was here,
- See you at the port.
- she'd love it.
Look. So lively.
Yeah.
Over there.
Xiu is here.
Please get to the shore.
Alright.
How many are there left?
- Five.
- Qi.
You are...?
I'm sorry.
Zhaoyan, why is your lantern
different from Xiu's?
It was a random pick.
You picked a wolf?
A wolf? It's obviously a dog.
The meat smells great.
It looks like a wolf to me.
♪Looking back♪
♪I try to bring back memories♪
♪We're connected♪
♪It's meant to be♪
Qi.
♪Years leave no trace behind♪
♪On a moonlight night♪
♪I lapsed into my memories♪
♪About you♪
♪All laughter and joy are about you♪
♪It's unforgettable. It's all about you♪
♪The past glided before my mind♪
♪I smiled and cried♪
♪For happiness♪
♪I went about the world looking for you♪
♪All I have was the echo in the valley♪
♪In this tranquil world♪
♪I've finally found you♪
♪I'll spend the rest
of my life with you♪
♪I've been looking for you♪
Jinzhao, our feelings are not fake.
There's no such thing as Husheng Spell.
I know.
♪Believe me, you're the only one♪
Ming Xiu, happy birthday!
Thank you. Welcome back.
Everyone's here. Xiu will have
a perfect birthday.
Yeah. Time is pressing.
I made a gadget for Miss Ming.
It transfers small items. Here.
Miss Ming, do you like it?
Thank you, Shifang.
Miss Ming, I saw this
at the accessory shop.
I hope you like it.
Thank you, Zhaoyan.
How do you know it wasn't Hanjiang?
It was me, though.
Only you would make a fuss about it.
It's not an important day.
I find it important.
Ming Xiu, birthday matters.
But I didn't...
Didn't what?
- Here. It's from both of us.
- Thank you.
- When did you get it?
How do you know I'd be back?
I just do.
Miss Ming, I heard
in the Western Regions,
if someone makes a birthday wish,
Heaven will make it come true.
Really? Miss Ming, come on. Make a wish.
My master knows my wishes.
I've aged.
I only hope that someone can
fulfill your wish soon.
Some wishes
can't be fulfilled by random people.
Little Yue, what do you wish for?
Endless delicacies, I guess.
I wish I could live happily
and peacefully with Jinzhao forever.
So I matter more than food.
Of course. You'll get me delicacies
when we're together, anyway.
It's killing two birds with one stone.
Thank you.
We know what Jinzhao wants.
And you, Luo?
It's still the same.
I want the people
to remember the Luo family
and me.
Master Luo is truly ambitious.
Xian Qing, what do you wish for?
I have no obsession, hence, no wishes.
Xian Qing, don't be so resolute.
Hanjiang, let go of your obsession.
What about you, Shifang?
M-My wish is to
become a great gadget technician
like my mother
and to gather for birthdays
like we're doing right now.
We will.
So we can make two wishes.
I lost my chance.
Come on, cheers.
- Cheers.
Ming Xiu, happy birthday!
- Happy birthday!
- Thank you.
Jinzhao, look. River lanterns.
Come with me.
Alright.
Flow far far away, my little lantern.
Qi.
Let's stay together forever, okay?
♪That determined look on your face♪
Deal. Pinky promise.
♪Light and shadow freeze at the moment♪
♪I look for you here and there♪
♪Following the strong heartbeat♪
♪Holding your hands, I breathe rapidly♪
Do you remember
what I asked you in the mine?
♪One hug is enough for an answer♪
Qi, who am I
to you?
♪Why do I only want you♪
What is your answer?
♪It's all worth it
as long as you're around♪
Not an older brother, anyway.
♪I'm sure I only want you♪
♪A smile of yours melts all my sorrow♪
♪It's all worth it
as long as you're around♪
♪I won't listen to any rumor♪
♪I'm sure I only want you♪
Shuo Xuan, I don't eat fish anymore.
Mr. Ju can't drink at all.
Master, your eyes...
It's fine. Maybe I drank too much.
I just remembered.
You used to imitate Xian Qing and me
drinking when you were a kid.
But you fell asleep after a few sips,
and I had to carry you to your room.
Time flies and you're a big girl now.
Master, has it ever
crossed your mind that I was only...
You drank a lot. Take a nap.
Will you run away when I'm asleep?
Run away?
I'm not leaving.
Xiu, I am really worried about you.
Mother, is it true
that I'm not gifted as a technician?
I want to be like you
and make fabulous gadgets like Dou Bao.
Also, I swear I will protect Dou Bao.
That's the only thing you left me.
The view is truly breathtaking.
You're heading to the Zhengwu Alliance.
I won't go with you.
Take care.
Be very careful when you try
to take their headquarters.
Alright.
Xian Qing.
Where are you going?
Why? Are you reluctant to leave me?
Next time we meet, we'll enjoy
the river view during the day.
What do you say?
I'd love to.
It's a deal.
Deal.
(Zhengwu Alliance)
Guanren, the trigrams show
the alliance will be in grave danger.
I'm worried that it's about
your attack on the Qiyuan Sect.
I finally found out
where their headquarters is.
It's a rare chance.
It will be hard to take them down
if we miss this chance.
Hanjiang, you're a great man,
wise and brave.
But you are slightly obsessed
with fortune-telling.
Fine. But I'll come with you.
That would be great.
Mr. Zuo, Mr. Gu.
Here's the map Meng Cheng provided.
It shows the headquarters
of the Qiyuan Sect.
They have a front and a rear gate.
Judging from the terrace,
we will break in from the front.
As for the rear gate...
We got this.
Alright, you are highly skilled.
They won't be able
to handle our attack on both fronts.
It would be great if we could
wipe them out at once.
Time is pressing. I'll inform everyone.
Alright.
Master.
Master, why didn't you come back
with Xian Qing yesterday?
And what happened to your eyes?
You have so many questions.
Which one should I answer first?
I had a glimpse of the future
at Pureness some days ago.
I took a few glances and hurt my eyes.
Are you joining them on the attack
because of what you saw?
Xiu, I will go with Mr. Zuo.
You will go with Mr. Yue.
Be careful.
Aren't you going to protect me?
You're a big girl now.
You don't need my protection.
Master, I've never let you down.
But you don't mind letting me down.
(I saw a huge casualty
of the Zhengwu Alliance at Pureness.)
(But I don't know whether)
(it will happen during this attack.)
(It's less worrying to have Xian Qing
protect Xiu in the dark.)
(Other than that, I have to)
(change what I've seen
even if it costs me my life.)
Over the past two decades, our alliance
has annihilated
countless evil creatures
to guard our nation.
(Ningzheng Hall)
Right now, the nation is at risk.
People are tormented by the Qiyuan Sect.
We must bring justice to the world.
- Bring justice to the world.
Yue Jinzhao.
(Ningzheng Hall)
Mr. Zuo.
This blade is the Silver Shadow,
a collection of the Sword Sage
on Shushan Mount.
It was passed on
to the Demon Lord's son.
I will give this blade to you today.
♪The world is everchanging♪
All the divine and demonic
weapons were known
because of
what the weapon owners had done.
♪The vicissitudes of life♪
♪The world is in turbulence. So what♪
♪You're fighting the world alongside me♪
Mr. Zuo, thank you
for giving me this blade.
I shall carry on
its spirit of righteousness
and make it known in jianghu
as my weapon one day.
Good. Men shouldn't seek fame
from the weapons they hold.
Our weapons should be known
because of us.
Mr. Yue, try it.
♪Nostalgic about your gentle look♪
♪Wander the world with a sword in hand
while all love and hatred♪
♪Fade away through time♪
(Materialize your dream)
(Headquarters of the Qiyuan Sect)
Our great Lord Ming.
All mighty Lord Ming.
I, Gao Xiao, pledge to you
as the sect leader of Qiyuan.
We shall serve you
with the greatest loyalty
and make your glorious glow
shine upon the world.
May Lord Ming bless us.
- May Lord Ming bless us.
The map says it's the rear passage
to the headquarters.
Jinzhao, we must destroy the Qiyuan Sect
ruthlessly.
Jinzhao, how come you're always so calm
like you can see the future?
To the left.
Jinzhao, are you alright?
Don't worry. It's always like that.
I can see the future indeed.
So pull yourself together.
I'm here so we won't lose.
Mr. Yue, Mr. Ju, let's enter.
My master came along this time
and I have the feeling
that he's hiding something.
Don't worry, Miss Ming.
There are so many alliance disciples.
And Mr. Gu is a great fighter.
Nobody will be in danger.
Let's go.
Why so hesitant? Hurry up.
Qianjun, no rush.
The ground seems dug
on both sides. It's fishy.
Let's talk first.
Mr. Yue, what do you say?
To the left.
Do as he says. To the left.
Xu. Can we count on him?
Of course. Remember
what he did at the Langyin Pavilion...
Step aside.
♪Looking back♪
♪I try to bring back memories♪
♪We're connected♪
♪It's meant to be♪
♪I've fallen in love silently♪
♪Years leave no trace behind♪
♪On a moonlight night♪
♪I lapsed into my memories♪
♪About you♪
♪All laughter and joy are about you♪
♪It's unforgettable. It's all about you♪
♪The past glided before my mind♪
♪I smiled and cried♪
♪For happiness♪
♪I went about the world looking for you♪
♪All I have was the echo in the valley♪
♪In this tranquil world♪
♪I've finally found you♪
♪I'll spend the rest
of my life with you♪
♪I've been looking for you♪
♪I wish to share joy
and sorrow with you♪
♪Among the vast sea of people♪
♪I engrave your name♪
♪Believe me, you're the only one♪
♪Wind rises and rain ceases♪
♪During the long-lost quiet time♪
♪Both of us get closer♪
♪And watch the stars♪
♪I've fallen in love silently♪
♪Stories leave no trace behind♪
♪On a moonlight night♪
♪I lapsed into my memories♪
♪About you♪
♪All laughter and joy are about you♪
♪It's unforgettable♪
♪It's all about you♪
♪The past glided before my mind♪
♪I smiled and cried♪
♪For happiness♪
♪I went about the world looking for you♪
♪All I have was the echo in the valley♪
♪In this tranquil world♪
♪I've finally found you♪
♪I'll spend the rest
of my life with you♪
♪I've been looking for you♪
♪I wish to share joy
and sorrow with you♪
♪Among the vast sea of people♪
♪I engrave your name♪
♪Believe me, you're the only one♪