Those three young men were having a meal.
Your mom happened to pass by.
She saw the bottles on the table
and reached out to take them.
The guys didn't refuse,
but they wanted to finish eating and drinking first.
Then, they would have given her the bottles.
But your mom wouldn't let it go
and insisted on taking them right away.
Does your mom have some mental issues?
She's just getting old,
her mind's not as clear anymore.
She moves pretty fast, though.
Has she trained for this?
Look,
she beat up all three of them.
Over a few bottles?
Was that necessary?
Sorry.
Alright, you guys figure it out
among yourselves later.
Here, your mom's over there.
You're here.
What trouble did you get into this time?
You really don't see yourself as an outsider, huh?
Get up.
Your daughter's here to take you home.
Why are you taking off your seatbelt?
Buckle up, we're still on the road.
Okay.
What are you doing?
I really can't with you.
You've got skills, huh?
Taking on three guys at once,
and they were all young.
That brat tried to steal my phone.
He even touched my bag!
The police checked the security footage.
They didn't touch you at all.
Want some water?
No.
Call Zhou Kai.
I'll take you home.
Stop touching things, okay?
Hey! Stop that!
Where do you live?
What's wrong?
My... my tooth hurts.
Come on, brush your teeth and wash your face.
What are you doing?
Come on, brush your teeth and wash up.
Did you not hear me?
I've been calling you, and you didn't respond at all.
Didn't I tell you to change?
This one's comfortable.
I wanna give it my daughter.
Just change into it.
I've prepared two more sets for you.
This pink one is so pretty!
Come on.
Go brush your teeth.
You don't need to take that to brush your teeth.
That's mine.
Here.
Come.
Brush your teeth first.
Come on.
What's wrong?
My tooth...
It's swollen.
I'll take you to the doctor tomorrow.
It's fine.
Aren't you going back to school soon?
You focus on your stuff.
I've been working for years already.
Didn't you come to visit me at the hospital before?
Right.
Your brother Zhou Kai,
he's such a troublemaker.
He went to hang out at the internet café again.
Then the teacher called me.
Asked me to go to the office.
I got so angry, look,
my tooth's swollen now.
It's driving me crazy.
Has anything happened to you in the past years?
Did you hit your head or get sick?
No.
I'm perfectly fine.
How's your mom doing now?
Is she alright?
She just fell asleep.
I'll take her to the hospital tomorrow.
Let me go with you.
It's fine. I can go by myself.
I'll pick you up tomorrow morning.
No, no need to go out of your way.
Good night.
Yun.
What seems to be the problem today?
Her face is swollen here.
Could you take a look?
Her left cheek is swollen.
Alright, I'll take a look.
Thank you.
Okay, please rest your head back.
Don't worry. Relax.
Alright, keep your head straight and lie down.
Relax.
Listen to the doctor.
Okay, please open your mouth.
Open.
Open your mouth wide.
Good, very good.
Relax, don't be afraid.
It's fine.
Lie still and don't move.
Just check your tooth.
It won't hurt.
Just cooperate and open your mouth.
We just need to take a quick look.
Let's try again.
Open your mouth wide.
Turn your head.
Very good.
Open your mouth wide.
Good, very good.
Are you thirsty?
Do you want some water?
It's fine.
Don't pull me.
Who are you?
Stop fooling around.
This is a hospital, keep quiet.
Sorry.
Let's go.
Where's my wallet? Where's my son?
I'm your son.
You didn't bring your wallet when you left the house.
My wallet...
You took my wallet, give it to me.
Getting more forgetful with age.
Here's the wallet, Dad.
He doesn't even recognize his own son.
Where's my son?
Come, I'll go find my son.
My son...
Sir,
your son is inside here.
Yes, your son is inside.
He's here.
Are you dating her?
Are you seeing her?
I'm pursuing her.
But I haven't caught up yet.
Pursue her.
Regarding your mom's condition,
it can be basically diagnosed
as Alzheimer's disease.
There's no cure for this illness at the moment.
The most important thing is companionship.
Try not to let her be alone.
Stay with her more.
You're here.
Let's see.
Did you see the water he threw?
Stop teasing the kid.
It's a silk doll made by Hua's mom.
Silk doll?
Yes, try it.
Silk doll.
Her mom wants your number.
She said when Hua grows up, she'll visit you.
It's so spicy!
It's okay.
Elderberry.
Shredded potatoes.
Can't you taste it?
Elderberry. Do you like it?
It's a bit spicy.
You'll get used to it the more you eat.
This place is really beautiful.
The last time I saw such a view
was over ten years ago.
It was when my dad took me back to our hometown.
Yesterday, Dadan was planning to play chess with your dad.
Call him.
Save it.
My phone's out of battery.
Can I borrow your phone?
Mine's out of battery too.
Thinking about leaving soon,
why do I suddenly feel a little anxious?
What's there to be anxious about? I'm here.
Let's go.
No. Don't go.
I wanna stay here.
Wait until it gets dark to watch the stars.
No need to wait until night.
I'll show you a gorilla right now.
Are you stupid?
Acting like a gorilla.
Your gorilla expression is all wrong.
Look at you.
What expression?
Dr. Lu.
Do you like elderberry?
I dislike you.
You're so ugly.
Well, I happen to look even more like it than you.
Interested in medical aesthetics training?
One flyer per person, don't be stingy.
Here.
Study it.
Interested in medical aesthetics training?
Discounts available!
Let's go.
There are promotions and discounts!
No prior experience needed.
Tuition is only 28,800 yuan.
Partnered with multiple medical aesthetics institutions.
Thread-lifting enhancement.
Industry certification and direct job placement.
Limited spots available, first come, first served!
These shady medical aesthetic services...
Wasn't there a crackdown on them recently?
Didn't take long for them to pop up again.
The cost is low, but the profit is high.
Fortune favors the bold.
Look, they've gotten smarter now.
No phone numbers or addresses,
just a QR code.
Hurry, make some noodles.
- Customers are here. - Mom?
Quickly!
Where did you go?
Zhou Kai, Mom's back.
Mom,
where did you go?
Go inside.
Alright, let's go home.
Go home first.
Then...
Alright, I got it.
You go ahead.
And you two are...?
First time meeting, Jingwen.
Thank you.
And this is...?
My brother-in-law?
How long has this restaurant been open?
We've been open for almost two years now.
I always said that since we were here,
we should go find you.
But Zhou Kai is so stubborn.
He wouldn't let me tell you.
What are you guys talking about?
There's a whole pile of dishes that haven't been washed.
Wash the dishes.
Eat while it's still hot.
Speak properly.
Thirty-six yuan.
I'll pay.
She's been diagnosed with Alzheimer's.
Don't let her wander around alone.
Take good care of her.
What does that have to do with you?
How does it not concern me?
The police even called me.
You said yourself, even if the whole family died,
it had nothing to do with you.
Give it back.
Give it back to me.
Stealing money from the house.
Zhou Jingwen!
Have you no conscience?
This is my own bonus from my exams.
It's my money!
Give it back!
Your money?
Other daughters bring money home.
You took the money.
What about my wedding in the future?
What if Mom gets sick?
All you ever think about is yourself.
If you have the guts to leave, don't come back.
I never planned on coming back.
Even if the whole family dies, it has nothing to do with me.
That was when you were kids.
It was just angry words.
I wasn't just speaking out of anger.
I really never planned on coming back.
I just never expected
that after all these years, she would turn out like this.
I still haven't forgiven her.
Who are you?
Jingwen!
No need, I'll drive myself home.
Charge!
This is really comfortable.
I wanna give it to daughter.
Your mother's condition
can basically be confirmed
as Alzheimer's.
There is no cure for this disease at the moment.
The most important thing is to be there for her.
Try not to leave her alone.
Spend more time with her.
Found it.
You took my little cutie.
Then will you come to see me?
Good boy.
Did you get the new medicine?
Yes, I brought it.
Once a day.
The stitches come out next Wednesday.
Okay.
In the meantime, make sure the wound doesn't get wet.
Got it.
Also, keep the diet light
and pay close attention.
If the wound gets red or swollen,
make sure to come to the hospital right away.
Qi Dacheng!
Don't run!
Don't run, Qi Dacheng!
Qi Dacheng!
Stop running!
Qi Dacheng, you can't run!
Qi Dacheng!
Don't run!
- Dad! - Qi Dacheng!
- Dad! - Are you okay?
Dad!
Dr. Qiao,
Long...
He went for a checkup.
Go ahead, run.
Keep running.
Qi Dacheng, were you a long-distance runner before?
Are you especially good at running?
Back then, when you ran out of our hospital,
you told me your child was in trouble.
Did I stop you?
Then why did you change your phone number?
Why did you make it so we couldn't contact you?
Do you know that your condition
requires regular medication to prevent rejection?
If you get an infection,
you could lose your life.
Dr. Qiao, listen to me.
Listen to me.
Five years.
We waited five years for this donor.
Qi Dacheng,
so many people put in so much effort
to get you this surgery.
And you just ran away?
Do you know how worried we all were?
Do you know that by doing this,
you've broken the hearts of so many doctors?
Dad!
Are you feeling any better?
I'm fine now.
Did you finish your checkup?
This doctor took me through it all.
We can go home now.
No, you can't go home.
He's in a dangerous condition, he can't leave.
Dr. Qiao,
are you done scolding me?
No.
Listen to me.
Listen to what?
Look.
Wherever I go, my medicine goes with me.
I was afraid I'd forget one day,
so I even wrote it down in a notebook.
See?
I haven't missed a single day.
Then why did you run when you saw me?
Don't you know you have an exercise-induced allergy?
I got nervous when I saw you and forgot.
I usually don't run at all.
I know how I looked when I left back then.
You must have been really worried.
But every word you told me,
I remember them all clearly.
You saved my life.
I regret performing your surgery.
Dad,
didn't you say Dr. Qiao is really gentle?
Why is she so fierce?
What are you laughing at?
The kid didn't lie,
did he?
Dr. Qiao is just looking out for me.
I made all of these myself.
Pick whichever one you like and take it.
Alright.
If the weather gets colder,
I'll make you a down jacket.
Sounds good.
You're really skilled.
So, is this house yours?
No.
We're renting it.
Long needs to go to school,
and this place is closer to the school.
You know about Dacheng's condition.
He can't go out.
The rent here is cheap,
and business is good.
We can cover our food,
plus both of their
medical expenses.
That's great.
Really great.
Go cook the pork.
You still don't know how to cook it?
Yours tastes better.
Alright, I'll go.
Okay.
Dr. Qiao,
there's an old street up ahead.
You guys can take a walk.
The food will take a while.
I'll call you when it's ready.
Alright.
Stop running.
Walk slower!
Don't worry, I'm fine.
- Don't faint again. - Lion.
Lions run the fastest!
Who's the second fastest?
Tigers.
And the third?
Cats.
And last is the little chick.
- Right? - Right!
Wow,
Dr. Lu, you can even tutor math!
What do you mean?
You do it?
My P.E. teacher taught me math.
I'm no good.
Just a few days here,
and it feels more exhausting than working a month in the hospital.
Not easy, huh?
So now you know what exhaustion feels like?
But you look pretty happy.
I saw you smiling all day.
If I still couldn't smile,
wouldn't that let you down?
You went to such lengths to bring me here,
just so
I could feel the beauty of life,
and not sink into despair
over one accident.
Right?
What accident?
Did you lose a patient?
Almost.
Were you scared?
As doctors,
is death the thing you fear the most?
I'm not afraid of my own death,
but I am afraid of others dying.
Focus on your homework.
Why are kids so nosy?
Do this question on your own.
Come on, let's go for a walk.
I used to roll my eyes at those stories,
people getting hurt
and then running off to Tibet
for some kind of spiritual healing.
Never thought I'd
become the main character of one myself.
You know,
this vulnerable side of you
is kind of charming.
Can I ask you a question?
Go ahead.
What happened to your breast?
It's okay,
you don't have to answer if you don't want to.
I'm just curious.
Why did you wait until now to ask?
That first time we went to a hotel,
you saw it but didn't react at all.
I was pretty surprised.
That's just basic professionalism
for a surgeon.
Dr. Lu is quite the gentleman.
When I had just divorced Ji Xuefeng,
I was diagnosed with breast cancer.
Being a doctor,
after the initial shock,
I calmed down pretty quickly.
It wasn't as scary as I thought.
If you're sick, you just get treated.
I decided to have a mastectomy without hesitation.
It was the best option anyway.
I was lucky,
the surgery was a success,
and I haven't had a recurrence since.
That's great.
After all, in life, besides life and death,
nothing else really matters.
From a scientific perspective,
the true function of breasts in women
is for breastfeeding.
Since I never planned to have kids,
that function was meaningless to me.
And think about it,
who decided the beauty standards
for women's breasts?
Breast augmentation is painful.
Do you remember my patient, Ding Manheng?
That young, vibrant girl
who was diagnosed with breast cancer.
But she never felt like
losing a breast
made her life incomplete.
I share her perspective,
so I understand her completely.
Do you wanna hear how I really felt at that moment?
At the time, I thought...
this woman
is so cool.
Praises that don't touch on real emotions
are just empty words.
But I truly felt it.
When we looked at each other,
I finally understood
what true perfection is.
I know you don't want emotions
to take up too much of your energy.
You don't wanna define our relationship.
I respect your choice.
I've thought about it too.
My hope for our future
is that you'll be my girlfriend.
That we can have a future together.
Didn't you say before
that you don't care about the outcome?
Don't break your own character!
All I know is, every day I'm with you,
my heart is filled with endless exclamation marks.
And I want every future day to feel the same.
Oh, there's a market today!
Let's go buy some groceries.
You should show off your cooking skills for lunch!
Be my girlfriend.
Did you hear me? Be my girlfriend!
- Where are you going? - Look, they have radishes here!
Hurry over!
Is there anything else to fill out?
No.
Let's wait for a moment.
Please have a seat.
Take a seat.
What are you looking at?
Hey,
look at the one wearing the hat.
Isn't that the person who was on the news before?
No way.
Quick, check it.
Okay.
Hello.
You must be Ms. Zhou.
I'm Duan Mengmeng.
How many times have you had your nose done?
Three or four times, I think.
My nose is like a seesaw,
press the middle,
and both sides lift up.
That sounds tricky.
What material was used previously?
Was it Gore-Tex or rib cartilage?
The nose isn't important.
Look at my eyes instead.
Open your eyes wider.
Wider.
This is ptosis.
No,
don't you think my eyes
are different sizes?
That's completely normal.
No one in the world
has perfectly symmetrical eyes.
But it bothers me.
I want to open up the inner corner of my right eye
to make them symmetrical.
Let me take a look.
Ms. Zhou.
What's going on?
Didn't you see there's a patient here?
There's an urgent matter that requires your signature.
Sorry about this.
That online activist Duan Ling,
she's now changed her name to Duan Mengmeng.
This woman
has had dozens of cosmetic surgeries.
But she's also sued hospitals dozens of times.
Every time, it's because she was dissatisfied with the results
and wanted to defend her rights.
She's already been blacklisted
by countless hospitals.
Now, in Rongchuan,
there's practically no hospital left
that dares to take her in.
Last month, she sued another hospital,
the one at Exit C of the subway station.
Ms. Zhou, tell me,
she's had so many procedures,
not a single one satisfied her.
Why do you think that is?
Everyone, take a look.
This is her current face.
It's a complete mess.
Look at her eyes, nose,
mouth, chin, even the jawline,
shes had work done on everything.
But all of them turned out badly.
Her mouth is infected,
her nose has perforations,
and her cheekbones are uneven.
So I plan to do a full reconstruction for her.
That's too risky, isn't it?
We understand the sentiment.
Seeing a patient like this,
which one of us here wouldn't want to help her?
We all do.
In the past, for cases like this,
we've had plenty of arguments with consultants,
haven't we?
Yes.
But this patient,
her case is really quite special.
We need to be extra cautious.
Mr. Chu,
you have the most experience.
What's your take?
Looking at the scans,
see this lower part?
The bone here
is almost entirely shaved down.
There's nothing left to work with.
And looking at her in person,
her skin has already
been stretched to the limit.
There's hardly any room left for adjustments,
right?
Now, can this reconstruction
be done?
Technically, yes.
But I worry about causing her further harm.
It could do more harm than good.
That's exactly my point.
Exactly.
That's right.
Look.
With so much prior history,
if anything goes wrong again,
who takes responsibility?
Right?
I had no idea you used to run this kind of institution.
You never mentioned it before.
The industry developed too fast,
and there was a huge talent gap.
Some friends pulled me in,
so I helped them set things up.
For those of us with experience,
we have a responsibility to contribute to the field.
Eat up.
Alright.
So, in our hospital,
do we have people who came from these kinds of institutions?
We mainly collaborate with downstream institutions.
As for you,
just focus on teaching for a while.
Teach the subject well.
You don't need to worry about anything else.
But...
teaching completely inexperienced people
and in just one week,
getting them to learn thread lifting?
I have no teaching experience.
I don't even know how to teach.
Ms. Li.,
I don't think I can help you with this.
My dear,
we've known each other for so many years.
You have talent, vision,
and you dream of being a great doctor.
I've seen it all.
To be honest,
among the new generation of doctors at Gemu,
you're the most outstanding.
But talent alone isn't enough.
Besides skill,
the most important thing in life
is making the right choices.
If you make the right choice,
if you're heading in the right direction,
your abilities will take you even further.
But if you choose wrong,
the harder you work,
the further you'll be from your goal.
I've suffered too much from this myself.
It's only in the past two years that I've started to wake up.
Cheng Xiaoli
was in the same year as you, right?
Yes.
She wasn't nearly as talented as you.
But look at her now,
she teaches effortlessly,
earns a ton of money from lectures.
Look at your bag, how many years have you carried it?
Every time I see you, you have that same bag.
Do you know what kind of bag
Cheng Xiaoli carries now?
Ms. Li,
you're absolutely right.
Choice is crucial.
That's why I chose Jiao Ai.
Now, my career is on track.
I have plenty of clients.
Right now, I just wanna
focus on doing my job well,
to live up to the opportunity
you gave me.
Speaking of opportunities,
let me share a little story of my own.
I entered the workforce early.
A poor kid learns to take charge early.
In 2004,
I was working as a technician at a beauty salon.
At that time, there was a supplier named Chong.
He was...
always getting handsy with the girls.
He was truly disgusting.
Everyone avoided him.
Even the boss's wife kept her distance.
Except for me.
I took the initiative to work with him.
The more we interacted, the more familiar we became.
In the end, I was able to open my own shop,
all thanks to
the clients he introduced to me.
I understand what you're saying.
Opportunities have to be fought for and created by oneself.
I'm just...
worried...
Worried about safety?
When cars were first invented,
people were worried about safety too.
And now?
The same situation,
some people see risk,
some see opportunity.
I never give up
on any possibility.
Who knows what tomorrow will bring?
It's okay.
Take your time, no rush.
Waiter.
I see you're not a fan of eating greens.
We should eat meat,
not suffer through grass.
No.
It's fine, really.
Excuse me,
can we have a filet mignon?
Sure, no problem.
No need, Ms. Li.
It's fine.
We haven't even eaten much yet.
I'll cover the bill, take your time eating.
I've got things to do.
This way please.
Take your time.
Alright.
Take care, Ms. Li.
Wait.
Jingwen.
- Come. - Mr. Chu.
I suggest that for patients like Duan Mengmeng,
it's best to start with psychological counseling first.
Are you kidding me?
I came to you for service,
not to hear you criticize me.
What do you mean by "comprehensive repair"?
I think you're just desperate to make money.
Calm down, let's talk it through.
Have some water first.
I've seen plenty of people like you.
Tricks won't work on me.
Duan Mengmeng.
No,
I should call you Duan Ling, right?
Then just say it straight.
Can you fix my eyes or not?
In the early days, at the unlicensed black clinic,
which you referred to
as the so-called"famous doctor's" place,
you suffered a lot of losses.
This led to severe damage to your jaw and facial bones.
If I keep working on your face,
your entire face could collapse.
I know.
Looks like you have a lot of experience.
You should've done a repair two or three years ago.
Instead, you went ahead with so many procedures.
Why?
Are you trying to say that I've lost my mind?
I suspect you have Body Dysmorphic Disorder (BDD).
It's also known as body image disorder.
I wish
I did have BDD.
At least I wouldn't look ugly.
Look at my face,
who wouldn't be shocked when they see it?
No, BDD has nothing to do with appearance.
It's because you care too much about your looks
and exaggerate and imagine
flaws in yourself.
Then you become addicted to plastic surgery.
Addiction to plastic surgery
is also a form of BDD.
But you never reject any patients, right?
You did the procedure for that person
who was looking for her child.
So why are you refusing me?
No problem.
I'm more than willing to do the repair surgery for you.
But beyond that,
I won't do any other procedures for you.
I have a friend
who is very experienced with BDD.
I'll share her WeChat with you,
you can talk to her.
I thought you were someone of importance.
That's why I came to find you.
Don't pretend to be some benevolent doctor.
Zhou Jingwen,
the dirty things you did in the past,
do you really think no one knows?
You caused someone's death and ran off with the money.
Was that you?
Do you know plastic surgery is addictive?
Just help me one more time.
Zhong Shunhua's daughter told me
that you're actually a good person,
but unfortunately, your skills aren't up to par.
That remark didn't hurt much,
but it was deeply insulting.
In fact, that statement didn't mean much.
But when her mother woke up
and said "thank you" to me,
it made me feel incredibly ashamed.
From that day on,
that "thank you"
became a gun hanging over my head,
ready to fire at any moment.
That's why I ask you,
even if there's no legal responsibility,
can you really be at peace inside?
So, do you have an answer in your heart now?
When I was in Guizhou, during a surgery,
halfway through, the power suddenly went out.
Later, I had to finish the surgery using the light from my phone's flashlight.
When I walked out of the operating room,
everything outside was pitch black.
Someone lit a candle,
and we walked forward in the candlelight.
Beyond the candlelight,
we couldn't see anything ahead.
I wanted to review the surgery from that day,
but I realized I couldn't remember anything.
At that moment, I suddenly realized
that the doctors who stay there,
they go on like this every day, walking in the dark.
Every day, they save one person,
and then save the next.
If they can save one, they will.
They don't think about
whether they feel at peace or not.
It's rare for you to have
such feelings.
Sometimes,
being too fixated on your own feelings
can actually be a form of narcissism.
How you face failure is not important.
What matters is performing surgery,
doing surgery continuously,
doing it until you're old,
doing it until you die.
Here we go.
Meatballs.
What's been bothering you recently?
Suddenly you've started gardening.
Qi bought it.
Such a hassle.
She keeps urging me to water it.
You'd think
missing one watering wouldn't kill it.
Seriously.
Here.
Let's eat.
When will they be back?
Next week.
What's the difference between the cherry blossoms
and the peach blossoms in the yard?
Why do they have to go all the way to Wuhan to see them?
The one in the yard is a begonia,
and it's been growing there for decades.
Really?
I thought they were all the same.
You probably never really looked at them.
This meatball
is about 70-80% like the ones my mom used to make.
How come I can't get the taste just right?
I followed your mom's
recipe exactly.
I followed her recipe too.
It's your cooking pot that's not good.
When I leave later, give me your pot.
That won't do.
You only cook a few times a month.
Look how frugal you are.
From now on, I'll come here to eat every day.
Sounds good.
But you'll need to pay for the meals.
Fine, I'll pay.
Just don't back out later.
Before I went to Guizhou, I went to visit my mom.
You should visit her when you have time.
My meniscus
is getting worse.
Climbing mountains is difficult now.
Do you know my mom's eyebrow
is missing a section?
On the left side,
below the arch of the brow.
You had the same thing when you were little.
Really?
I don't know when,
but it grew back later.
Your mom even mentioned this before.
I never really noticed before
what my mom's eyebrows looked like.
Until the day I went to the funeral home to see her,
I stared at her for a long time.
I suddenly realized,
so this is how my mom's eyebrows looked.
At that moment, she almost seemed unfamiliar to me.
Why bring this up suddenly?
Actually,
I'm not as loving toward my mom as I thought.
I just couldn't bear to see her go.
Your mom was a person
who could really endure.
If it were someone else in that much pain,
they'd have seen a doctor.
You know,
we have an orthopedic doctor in the family,
but we didn't realize it was osteosarcoma.
We just kept thinking it was arthritis.
Arthritis.
She just kept applying the patches herself.
If we had found it two months earlier,
maybe there would've been a chance for treatment.
But in her case, not even a god could have saved her.
It's not your fault.
Don't blame yourself anymore.
That day, you said,
you didn't know whether your mom was happy.
But I remember she said
having a daughter like you
was the happiest thing for her.
She was very content.
What's wrong?
Did you pour the whole
bottle of vinegar in?
Why is it so sour?
No way.
Did you follow my mom's recipe?
No, this is my own.
You still can't get it right.
I won't pay for the meal.
You eat it yourself.
I just didn't add enough sugar.
Have more meatballs.