What are you doing here?
The 5G project doesn't proceed well.
Why are you dressed like you're going to a red carpet event?
Have you won an award for acting?
It seems you have watched my live stream.
Back to how it was fifteen years ago.
How can you say such nonsense.
Whether it's five years younger or fifteen years younger,
Isn't it all a matter of perspective?
Relying on makeup or today's technology.
Getting twenty years younger is not
a problem either.
Her son is the only thing matters to her.
Oh, that's what parents do.
Plastic surgery cannot solve her life issues.
It can't fix a broken relationship.
Zhang Zhe left home as an adult.
Who can stop him if he wants to go home?
He must have a reason for still drifting outside.
There is nothing to do with
how many wrinkles Liu Xinfang has
on her face.
Why deceive yourself?
As a doctor,
we have no way to
change the fate of patients.
But choices can be made.
Studying medicine is one choice.
Getting married and having children is also a choice,
and plastic surgery is her choice.
How do you know weather this choice
will change her or not?
I actually think
the changes you made
have really made you look like a celebrity.
Thank you.
Goodbye.
That's right.
Yes, yes, yes.
Drink more tonight.
Has she arrived?
Ms. Zhou is here.
Mr. Du,.
Congratulations.
You are so remarkable even working in Jiao Ai.
Ms. Zhou, let me tell you.
Starting a business
is so damn hard.
Right?
I only understand now.
How difficult it was for you back then.
We must toast.
Yes, yes, yes.
Let's toast. For all these years staying at Gemu,
I've learned quite a lot.
I really feel grateful.
Alright, alright, alright
Come here.
Is that how you show gratitude with that little wine?
Come on.
Fill it up.
That's enough.
Since I have learned so much from Gemu,
no more copyright fees.
Let's do it.
Come on.
Sure.
That will be it.
Mr. Qin is here.
Ms. Zhou has to perform a surgery tomorrow.
So she can't drink too much.
That's right. She can't.
Let's drink.
Excuse me
Sure.
Take your time.
Let's drink another day.
It's almost time.
Can we go back now?
I didn't plan to go back.
If you want to go back, go by yourself.
I'm drinking happily.
On the way here,
I came across a public account article on my phone,
titled 'Family Emotional Abuse'.
Both spouses are victims.
So,
in order to prevent further harm to both parties,
shouldn't we have a chat?
Do you think it is suitable to talk about couple matters
on such occasions?
Drink more.
This is too much.
Excuse me, may I interrupt you two?
Ms. Li asked me to help you both take a photo together.
Will that do?
Come on, fill it up.
Fine.
Ok.
Then please come this way.
Sure.
Come, let me help you with that.
Your tie is misplaced.
Okay.
Handsome.
You wanna talk, right?
Let's talk right here.
Honey, I don't know why
our communication has become so difficult now.
I don't understand why you're angry.
I just suggested a
solution to the problem.
Yeah.
You're always solving problems.
Shouldn't I?
Is it okay not to solve problems?
What exactly is the problem?
You don't want me to be the dean.
And that's the biggest problem.
Jingwen,
I know the biggest problem we have now
is not that you want to be the director,
but your lack of sense of security.
If you don't trust them,
I hope you can trust me.
Trust your husband.
Now Mr. Chu and Qiao Yang have both joined us.
Plastic surgery department is all right now.
Even if Li Qi
has different views on business philosophy,
she can't stir up much of a storm.
You don't need to be so defensive.
Right?
Who is being so defensive anyway?
You're not happy when I work overtime.
You're also not happy when I go on a business trip.
I want to be the director now.
Will you support me?
If I were the kind of person
who doesn't support my wife in her career,
I wouldn't have built this hospital in the first place.
It's not you who built this hospital.
This hospital
was our shared ideal from the beginning.
Have you forgotten?
Your biggest ideal right now
is for me to go back with you and have children.
Jingwen, have you ever thought about that
actually,
I also need a sense of security.
Auntie, what about me now?
I have prepared three pillboxes for you..
Remember to take your medicine in the morning, at noon, and in the evening.
If it hurts too much, just add one of these.
Ms. Li.
I asked the nurse to help you with that.
Thank you!
Take a picture over there in a while.
It's ready over there.
You must take the medicine on time.
If you do so,
you will recover soon.
Don't forget it.
I am Zhang Zhe.
Zhang Zhe.
It's me, Mom
Son.
Mom.
My son.
Mom finally sees you.
Mom.
You finally came back.
Where have you been all these years?
Mom misses you so much.
I miss you too.
Why did you come back now?
Mom misses you so much.
Mom.
My son.
You finally came back.
Mom.
Where have you been for so long?
Wow, a lost child is easy to find, right?
What a coincidence.
Even TV dramas wouldn't dare to write this.
Well, our operation of this surgery has gone viral.
The power of the internet is very strong.
Liu Xinfang has already acknowledged it.
How could she not recognize her own child?
Given the current situation,
the dean must be Ms. Zhou.
Dr. Chen.
Stay low-key.
It's not settled yet.
Ms. Qiao once rejected
a batch of lower blepharoplasty patients.
Later, those patients came.
On the contrary, they wanted Ms. Qiao to perform the surgery.
Really?
And Qi Dacheng's face transplant surgery
has boosted her reputation more.
What do patients care about?
What?
The doctors.
That's right.
So you mean that
Dr. Qiao stands a greater chance.
I don't know.
The 5G remote robot project
that you are working on
is still hanging in the air.
If in any chance,
it fails.
It will backfire.
See?
She got nothing to refute me.
Why is Dr. Wei angry again?
Dr. Chen has got used to it.
Honestly
whether it's Dr. Zhou or Dr. Qiao,
neither stands a chance.
Our department's performance can't win.
Performance talks.
What's with the pout?
If you won't join,
there is no need for sarcasm.
I'm just being realistic.
That project is too risky.
If you pull it off,
I will celebrate it for you first.
Sure, Mr. Rational.
You can even eject the 5G robot.
Now you call yourself a geek?
I guess that
you don't want the drone for your birthday.
You remembered?
Buy it yourself.
What are you staring at?
Chen Mingjie, get back here!
Wang Qian, that ingrate,
stopped reporting to me recently.
He must be charmed by Qiao Yang.
“Charmed”?
I asked Wang Qian to assist Dr. Qiao
since she is new here,
and her help as much as he can.
So you don't even
keep up with this 5G robot project, right?
I'm not a doctor.
How would I understand?
What nonsense!
Young people these days
have no curiosity
about the world.
I remember that You have a college degree.
I have never got one myself.
Yet here I am, lecturing you as my subordinate. Do you know why?
Because from the first day I was out there working,
whatever job I am doing,
I never let anything I encounter
stays a mystery.
Ever heard the saying that,
“Enter a treasure mountain and leave empty-handed”?
Ask! Learn!
Steal knowledge if needed!
Or use the internet!
Or you'll be the first to get axed.
You are just lazing around
and wasting your time.
Is Ms. Gao here?
She is in the next room.
We're ready to start.
Hurry.
Get more close-ups!
You look good.
Have you taken your meds today?
It'll help recovery.
Sitting like this also
reduces swelling.
Like I said,
everything will get better.
Relax.
Thank you, Dr. Zhou.
Another surprise.
You told me before that you love to sing, right?
Guess who's here?
This way.
Dr. Chen.
No, it's not me.
Hello.
Oh my god.
Ms. Gao.
No need to get up!
Is it really you?
Yeah.
After hearing your story,
I had to come.
You're so brave.
"A mother's love makes her strong".
You have embodied that.
This must be Zhang Zhe?
Hello, Ms Gao.
Young man.
You should take good care of your mom.
I will. Thank you.
I can't believe that
they got you here.
I'm Dr. Zhou's patient.
Years ago, a car accident
broke my nose.
The initial treatment didn't go well.
Thanks to Dr. Zhou, I can.
What is happening? Wang Yibo is here?
Gao Yalan—Ms. Gao is inside.
See how well I've recovered?
Can't tell, right?
Yes.
I have just watched your show on TV
last month.
Really?
Zhang Zhe.
You like singing, too. Right?
A pro is here.
Don't flatter me.
Ms. Gao.
I've studied vocal music before.
I can play guitar well.
And I have also published several songs.
Please get in.
You've got potential. Relax.
You can just leave medical issues to Dr. Zhou.
As for your music career,
you can come to me.
Don't be shy.
Thank you!
Thank you, Ms. Gao.
Never mind.
Thank you!
Changing the fish tank water
must be a hassle.
I got no time for that.
Qing is caring them all the time.
They are lucky fish.
I often get new ones
from the market.
There is always something new in the market.
Look at this.
that black one with red edges.
It's always alone
and doesn't vie for food.
I just thought that
it can't make it to this month.
But it proves that I am wrong.
Less eating guarantees longevity.
Maybe it will live longer than others.
Fish keeping is like parenting.
It doesn't matter how you cure them,
but how you prevent them from falling ill.
This tank is pricey.
It can't accommodate too many fish at a time.
It can't contain too many big ones.
The water temperature. flow and quality
should all be well managed.
You just said you are not interested in raising fish.
But you know everything.
I am indeed not interested,
but that doesn't mean I have to stop getting to know them.
Come.
Let's have some tea.
I'm planning to talk to you anyway.
That robot is too large.
You can't just
always push it around the hospital.
That's crazy.
It looks like a Transformer set.
Mr. Qin
shouldn't just let you handle it alone.
The 5G tele-operation is a big project.
Everyone should do their part for it.
Mr. Qin has already funded us.
He shall not be bothered by these trivial things.
Come on.
We can just talk about it in the meeting.
Black tea or Longjing tea?
Whatever you get me.
I' m both fine.
Is the date scheduled?
Please keep me informed.
So I can send those young people
to learn something.
They are fooling around.
They don't even know
the current situation of the project.
You are quite interested.
I have to.
The era we are living in
is so horrible.
New things keep coming.
I'm so happy that you can be here.
You have brought us a lot fresh ideas.
Not flattery.
I do think that
the medicine aesthetics industry really needs people
as visionary and ambitious as you.
I do have a vision of
how good your tea will be.
Right?
Ms. Li from Li Ge gave it to me.
She told me that
an entire tea hill can only
produce a small bag of it.
Take it if you like.
I will ask her to get me more later.
I appreciate it. But no.
That's too good for me.
Grape is enough for me.
My biggest flaw I think
is my crazy pursuit of talents.
Since you have joined us,
we have never talked.
Today,
I have to win you over.
Training a doctor’s tough.
You have to go through medical school, PhD,
training, residency and a lot
which will take at least 15 years.
Not to mention talents like you,
who have got this far
by performing operations to gain reputation.
That's really amazing.
My duty
is to make sure that
every doctor here can fully exert their talent.
Good to hear that.
Then I shall tell you directly.
I have met many obstacles
in promoting the 5G tele-operation
in our hospital.
I don't have any other interests
but a perfect operation.
But recently I notice that
there is something troublesome
unrelated to surgery
bothering me a lot.
That's quite annoying.
So I come to you today,
hoping that you can support me.
I understand.
Then you shall get my support.
That's great!
But there is a string attached.
You have to answer me a question.
What's that?
You had a stable job at the Third Hospital,
and you are so excellent.
Why did you choose us?
Maybe it's because the salary,
cute guys here,
and the 5G tele-operation.
So I am here.
All right, it's the time.
Time for surgery.
Keep pushing for the project!
Professor Chu.
Dr. Zhou says you're her mentor,
a legend in this field.
I'm honored
that you're treating me.
Thank you.
Don't believe them.
This is just my job.
I'm also a fan of yours.
When HongKong was recovered in 1997,
you performed at our military compound.
We have taken a photo together.
Really?
You wouldn't remember.
It was a long time ago.
Times change.
Relax.
When I was young,
I have won every award.
But now,
I was eliminated in two rounds on The Voice.
I know it myself that
I am just a stepping stone for kids.
But I still can't accept it.
All right, relax now.
People nowadays have taste for art.
They only care about appearance.
"Countenance matters" as it's used
in the catchy words today.
People always say that,
singer may get older,
but the fans will always remain young.
That's right.
The same is true of my job.
People aesthetics are evolving every year.
If I were young ladies,
I will also choose Zhou to perform operation on me.
You really have a light heart.
You have taught me a lesson.
We should never
take ourselves too seriously.
When I just retired,
I felt low as well.
No matter how great you are,
you are an ordinary person after all.
The higher people place you,
the more arrogant you will be.
And when that happens, all you hear will be lies.
You won't have any real friends.
You will just live your life alone,
like a statue.
That kind of life is meaningless.
Look at me now.
Doing something
within my capacity
not only pleases you
but also makes me happy.
I really need to think about
what you just said.
Yeah, you can think about it now,
but don't frown.
Can I check it now?
Here, the mirror.
Well, let me see.
Isn't that better now?
Well. it really is.
The hyaluronic acid
is injected into the bone layer.
You might feel odd
at first,
but that feeling will disappear
in weeks.
Well.
A face lift would hurt more, right?
Liu Xinfang is so amazing.
She can even stand that pain.
That's understandable.
That's all for her son.
Her son of my ass.
That's not her son.
It's just a show.
They may fool you.
But not me.
I've been in this field too long. That's easy to identify.
(Zhang Zhe.)
(If you are watching this,)
(please come home.)
(I miss you a lot.)
(Auntie, don't be sad.)
(You will find your son someday.)
(We will try our best to help you.)
(Can you express your desire again?)
(Regret now?)
(That's too late.)
(I'm wondering)
(were they amicable like this)
(when Zhang Zhe was still at home?)
(That's right.)
(The miserable deserve their misery.)
(No parents are perfect.)
(They are not saints. They will make mistakes.)
(Even if they had disputes before,)
(but they still love their kids.)
(Don't be too hard on parents.)
(You are family.)
(Let's see.)
(Will any normal person)
(abandon their parents?)
(From this day on,)
(no more guitar.)
(What did I do to deserve you,)
(a good-for-nothing kid.)
(You are meant to get nowhere.)
(Do you have any idea that)
(if you are to be admitted to a college.)
(I will support you to play anything you want)
(not to mention the guitar.)
(You wanna leave this family, right?)
(Then go.)
(If you dare to go, you shall never come back.)
(What if they still)
(refuse to acknowledge their fault,)
(and try to find the son in such a way,)
(it only proves that they only love themselves.)
(Zhang Zhe has already forgiven his parents.)
(What are you doing here?)
(You should)
(tell your own parents this crap.)
Is that really her son?
Are you talking to me?
Come on.
Everyone in the hospital knows
that kid is a fake one.
You know that, don't you?
He needs a home.
Liu Xinfang needs a son.
And I need a touching story.
A story associated with the surgery.
That's it.
Own up to your lies.
Why wouldn't I?
Happy mother and son.
That's a perfect ending.
Perfect?
Her husband didn't look thrilled
when he saw his "son".
Again.
You're a doctor, not God.
You can't fix ger life.
Dr. Qiao, a word?
Wait a minute.
What now?
Well.
The company called
they want to accelerate the surgery date.
So can you just
perform this operation earlier?
What do you think the operation is?
A game?
Ms. Qiao.
I'm under great pressure now.
If we can't make any progress,
they will call it off.
Here, eat a chicken leg.
So you can keep working.
I want that, too.
Go get it yourself.
I wanna get it from you.
Well then you have to be as good as Xi.
I know you are pursuing perfection.
You've finished
more than 300 operations on double eyelids.
I believe you can do it with your eyes closed.
Well, that's too much.
Can you show us how to do it?
Surgery starting.
What are you doing?
Having a stroke?
Careful. I'll practice on you.
Why the long face?
You just did well.
Just enjoy your meal.
No more comforting words.
I have seen you guys chatting there.
They wanna replace me, right?
No.
I have practiced it many times.
I can do it.
But I'm kind of nervous
when there are too many people watching.
You must be very nervous.
I swear
that will never happen again.
No, you have to do.
If not, how can you conduct a perfect surgery?
Nervousness is not your enemy.
We tend to classify
nervousness, fear and frustration
as negative emotions.
But they can be transformed into
our weapon.
You see.
Our ancestors survived predators
when they were in jungles,
thanks to nervousness.
When disaster comes,
human will instinctively
perform the action of avoidance.
When the critical moments draw closer,
nervousness will make our brain thrilled,
so that we are highly focused
and become more innovative.
So.
Nervousness is the key factor that
stimulates people's potential.
What if I'm too nervous,
and I have that nervousness affecting my operation.
That's because
you consider nervousness as your enemy in your heart.
So you become absent-minded.
How can you focus on the operation then.
That's right.
I do notice that sometimes the more nervous you are,
the worse you may perform even if you are good at it.
As your tutor. Here is a trick.
Next time you're stressed,
take a breath
and say:
Great, I'm nervous!
With that baby,
I can surely finish the surgery.
What did you say?
God you didn't hear it.
All right. I have wasted my breath.
You just said you are my tutor.
Did I?
You did.
You said as your tutor.
Well, like you said.
I'm gonna do more practice now since I'm still nervous.
Here, the chicken leg.
Oh you foodie.
Go practice with her.
I'm not nervous.
Well you should be.
Is that trick really useful?
If so, I wanna give a try next time.
How the hell I know. I just made it up.
I'm nervous anyway.
What?
But all that talking.
The theory things, so you just made it up?
Well,
that's what I have learned from the book.
You are a terrible tutor.
An unreliable one.
Then let me give a real trick.
You will get nervous when you're afraid of loss.
And you will be relaxed if you wanna win.
What?
Ms. Qiao.
The chicken leg
has really done it part.
Oh, you freak me out.
Mr. Chen.
Tomorrow is the last animal trial.
Please make arrangements.
All right, I'm on it.
God.
It totally freaks me out.
Are you still nervous now?
No.
But I was nervous at first.
But Ms. Qiao.
I have used your trick.
I was thinking that
with this trick
I can definitely perform well.
I'm not nervous at all.
Well. Keep going.
Don't be too proud.
Sure.
Auntie.
Where is your son?
You know, weekends.
They are always busy.
Yeah.
Did you have a good sleep?
You should have because your stitches will be removed later.
How is Zhang Zhe still not here?
He should be here now.
Come, let's talk inside.
Auntie.
After being with him for several days,
have you noticed any differences?
Is he in the middle of something now?
Can you call him?
Calm down.
He asked me to tell you something.
He told me that he had a great time with you these days.
He was so happy.
But he also felt guilty
because he is not Zhang Zhe.
He is just a kid with similar experience of Zhang Zhe.
What do you mean?
I don't understand.
He
left his mom after a quarrel when he was young.
Then his mom passed away.
He never got to see her again.
He was so regretful.
When he watched our live streaming,
he said he shared same feeling with you,
so he came here to see you.
Auntie.
He says sorry.
He shouldn't lie to you.
Don't worry.
We still got time.
We will find your son eventually.
No need for that now.
I have found my son.
Stop that nonsense.
Zhang Zhe will be sad when he arrives.
Auntie.
Remember to take your medicine.
What medicine?
You ask me to take medicine everyday.
But I am not sick.
You're a liar!
You promised me to find my son.
Now he is here.
I think he is my real son.
Who dare you doubt me?
Auntie.
What right do you have to send him away?
Calm down.
Your wound is not healed yet.
He is my son.
He is Zhang Zhe.
Go get my son back.
I…
Go.
Zhang Zhe.
You won't be so unfeeling.
I have never let you suffer
since you were born.
What did I do wrong?
I just wanna see you,
hear your voice again.
After all these waiting,
we reunited.
But you left me again.
Are you punishing me?
Then what's the meaning of
doing all of these?
Don't tear it off, auntie.
Don't bite me.
Loose.
Let go of me.
Give my son back.
What to do now?
Many people are waiting for the updates now.
We have already started it.
We have to finish it.
Fine.
Anything you want.
Just let me know.
I have noticed
a weird comment before.
This one
named drifting guitar.
Can parents abuse and beat children willfully
in the name of love?
That's ironic though.
The plastic surgeon
can help people change their faces.
But faces
that are etched in people's heart
are hard to be changed.
Well. I will handle the life streaming.
You should take care of the patient.
Drifting guitar.
Let's see.
Don't speak now.
Your face is still swollen.
Once muscle tension eases,
you can move you tongue freely.
You can not only say thanks but also sing.
All right. Calm down.
Calm down.
Dacheng.
Can you close your mouth now?
Have a try.
Come. Let me help you.
Try harder.
Ok. Open the mouth.
One.
That's not enough.
His face is still stiff now.
You see. He is drooling.
Right.
Where is his family?
I can't leave now.
He has to stay in the hospital.
Family member of Qi Dacheng.
Come on.
The doctor is calling you.
I will call you back later.
Come on.
Come here.
His face is still stiff now.
You have to help him
do some exercise to activate his facial muscle.
In about 2 months,
when the facial nerves heal,
he will be able to make expressions.
I know.
Doc.
When can he be discharged?
His condition is not stable.
He has to stay here a little longer.
Even if he is discharged later,
you have to make him
take anti-rejection meds daily.
I know.
Don't worry.
It will be fine.
Why are you sitting here?
I'm fine.
Just wanna sit here and have a rest.
Hurt anywhere?
Does it hurt?
Shall we go to the hospital?
No.
I'm a doctor myself.
I have already handled it well.
I'm fine.
You can't drive now.
I will send you home.
Oh you.
When such things happen next time,
you have to protect yourself first.
I heard that
you didn't even dodge.
If she really hurt your hands badly,
how can you perform operations again?
Liu Xinfang is also a poor woman.
With all these efforts, she only got a fake son.
No wonder she is devastated.
But
she shouldn't never attack you.
And Zhang Zhe.
Where the hell is he?
Just some disputes among families.
How could elusion solve the problem?
When one is determined to leave the home,
leave the parents,
he must had hardened his heart.
I think
Zhang Zhe was not doing things impulsively.
I agree with that.
I just thought that
it's a pity to see a family scattered.
I mean they are families.
Even if they have different views,
they do can seek common ground while shelving differences.
Forget it.
I'm hungry. Let's find some food.
Sure.
Waiter.
Please refill my cup.
Ok.
The fake Zhang Zhe was my idea.
During her consult,
I noticed that Liu Xinfang
has some mental issues.
There is something wrong with her.
She is mentally healthy, right?
She is too stubborn.
She has to make herself look like
a 30-year-old lady.
That's crazy.
The water overflowed.
I'm sorry.
It's fine.
I will clean it for you.
Don't worry. I will do it.
It's okay.
Sorry.
Why didn't you refuse?
I did.
But her husband came to me later,
and showed me her diagnosis report.
Her mental illness is confirmed.
But she doesn't believe it, and refuses to take medicine.
She insists that she is not ill.
During these years,
her mental state is getting worse.
She was hot-tempered when she was young.
But that was all for the goodness of the child.
We wanted him to attend a good university
so that he can get a good job in the future.
I do understand.
But that is different.
Plastic surgery has nothing to do with finding your son.
Even if I have performed the surgery
to make her look younger again,
we can't ensure that
you can find Zhang Zhe.
I know.
I have to try
even if he won't show up.
Or we can get her a fake one,
so that she can receive treatment.
Or at least she is willing to take medicine.
If it continues to go like this,
the whole family will be screwed,
let alone finding our son.
Move your wrist.
All right. Be careful.
Slow down.
Hold it.
Sure.
Hello?
Qi Dacheng is gone.
What do you mean he is gone?
I just found out when I was on ward rounds.
He left in advance.
He won't answer the phone.
His stats are bad these days.
His condition is very unstable.
I have already asked Mr. Chu.
He knows nothing as well.
Has he ever called you?
No.
Zhang Zhe will never come back home.
I'm such a failure.
After all these years of suffering,
I end up raising an ingrate.
He had meningitis as a kid.
We tried our best to save him.
If I know he is such an ingrate,
I would never save him.