Opening OST: Jun Jiu Ling - Deng Yujun
♫ Sighing at how fleeting life is, the swords tell of the scars ♫
♫ After our meeting, I'm unwilling to separate ♫
♫ Journeying alone and cold,
the past is a secret guarded closely ♫
♫ Hide the love and hate of tonight, stow away the naivety ♫
♫ Meeting an old friend,
we look at each other as the memories emerge ♫
♫ Only daring to show a bit of gentleness in dreams ♫
♫ This kiss caused the emotional entanglement
with you to surge ♫
♫ The warmth in the rough birch disturbs the stars  ♫
♫ The art of healing become edges used
to guard the mountains and rivers ♫
♫ Hurt and hatred have not taken over ♫
♫ Unwilling to let so much hatred be in this chaotic world,
a heart of sincerity in exchange for eternity ♫
♫ Journeying together, waiting for some prosperity ♫
♫ Rewrite this life because looking back, the heart aches ♫
♫ For the rest of this life, running in the field with you
without any regards, waiting for dawn ♫
♫ Dawn... ♫
[Jun Jiu Ling]
[Episode 24]
[Jiuling Hall]
- What do you come here for?
- Summon Physician Jun.
Why do you summon Physician Jun?
Prince Huai developed a high fever last night.
It hasn't come down since.
I'll wait for you outside.
This...
Liu'er, get the medicinal box.
Miss, do you still want to go at a time like this?
This is my patient, so I need to go at any time.
But this is really not a good time.
- Let Physician Feng go.
- That's right.
At this time, Lu Yunqi is surely waiting at the residence for you to walk into the trap yourself. You must not go.
I was conferred as the County Princess of Shanyang by His Majesty.
He cannot do anything to me.
Do you think you can reason with those lunatics?
Enough. Rest assured and wait for my return.
Chen Qi, prepare the carriage.
All right.
My Lord.
You're here.
Where is Prince Huai?
Physician Jun is smart.
You must have been able to guess that I tricked you here
with an excuse.
Lord Lu,
I have come to Prince Huai's residence as a physician's duty.
Is it your duty to humiliate me like this?
Physician's duty? You changed your name,
made a lot of inquiries about various noble and imperial families,
and even went against the Imperial Physicians Hall.
Isn't it in order to arrive here?
Lord Lu, you most likely have become too detail-oriented after working at the Martial Moral Ministry for so long.
I'm quite simple.
Since you want to come, I'll let you.
Moreover, I'll keep you here forever.
What do you mean?
Very soon you'll know what I mean.
Prince Huai is fishing in the back courtyard.
Your Highness, Physician Jun is here.
Greetings, Your Highness Prince Huai.
Your Highness, do you like fishing?
Let me see how many fish Your Highness has caught.
Go away! You scared my fish away!
You seem to hate me very much.
So what? I do hate you! Go away!
You seduce my brother-in-law and bully my sister. Go away!
Go away! Go away! Go away!
Go away! Get lost!
Get lost!
Who are you?
Rong'er.
Rong'er!
Second Elder Sister!
- I missed you so much.
- I did too.
A few days ago, I dreamed that you bought me a lot of delicious food,
and even told me lots of stories.
- Really?
- Really.
It just so happens that I brought you some tasty food.
- Come.
- Really?
Second Elder Sister treats me the best.
- Have some.
- Thank you, Second Elder Sister.
Second Elder Sister, you have some first.
I especially bought this for you.
Rong'er, you've grown taller.
Let me see if you have done your work correctly.
Show me.
Second Elder Sister.
Written quite well.
Are you my Second Elder Sister?
I'm not your Second Elder Sister.
However, I'm a very good friend of hers.
Your sister told me to take good care of you.
I don't want it.
My eldest sister has gotten married and my second elder sister is dead.
You bullied my sister.
You all have been bullying my sister this whole time.
Your Highness Prince Huai...
In this lifetime, I would never bully you or your sister.
I would never.
I wonder who spread the rumor
that Miss Jun returned safely from Prince Huai Residence
because Lord Lu didn't make things difficult for her.
They even said that Lord Lu... has genuine and sincere feelings for Miss Jun.
Do we even need to think about who it is?
Besides the people from the Martial Moral Ministry and the Imperial Physicians Hall,
who else could it be?
How disgusting. Those low lives!
They can't win righteously so they play tricks using the affairs between men and women.
If this continues, I'm afraid it won't be good for Miss's reputation.
Who cares? Our Miss doesn't rely on her reputation to cure diseases or save lives.
That's true. When she was first in Zezhou,
her reputation wasn't all that great either.
Miss! Miss!
Duke Cheng's heir apparent is fighting with the Martial Moral Ministry's people.
- What? What happened?
- Lord Lu sent people to deliver betrothal gifts again.
The heir apparent stopped it, so he was dragged back to the Martial Moral Ministry.
Miss!
- You both stay here. You both stay here!
- Miss!
Young Lady!
- Hurry.
- Wait for me.
- Miss.
- Miss, over there.
[Duan's Fabric Store]
[Martial Moral Ministry]
A bunch of useless scraps of metal.
My stall!
- Move aside!
- Get out of the way!
Stop!
Ridiculous! You all are in such close proximity to the imperial city.
Did you think His Majesty wouldn't know about this?
My Young Lord the Heir Apparent,
since your arrival to the capital, you haven't stopped with your activities.
What's going on today?
Why did you fight in front of the Martial Moral Ministry?
Because he's shameless.
- What did the ministry do that is shameful?
- Whatever he does is shameful.
Fine.
Then, you must clear things up today.
Since you can fight in front of a crowd,
then, naturally, you can speak in front of a crowd.
Young Master, the celebration for the scholars who passed is in a few days.
At that time, when you ride a tall horse,
many civilians will surely come to watch.
Excuse me! What's going on up ahead?
Duke Cheng's heir apparent and Commander Lu started fighting at the entrance of the Martial Moral Ministry.
Hold on. Why?
- I heard that it was because of Young Lady Jun from Jiuling Hall. I'll go now.
- Jun...
I'll go and take a look.
Lu Xiaozao, aren't you aware
of what you've done?
I don't understand why you broke the doors of my Martial Moral Ministry and you even used
my betrothal gifts to do it.
I like Miss Jun and sincerely want to marry her. What does it have to do with you?
Can you marry a woman just because you say you like her?
If you like the princess of Northern Qi and send your betrothal gifts to Northern Qi,
does that mean the princess of Northern Qi should marry you happily?
- That's right.
- Exactly.
Everyone, don't laugh yet.
You all have wives and daughters at home.
If one day Lord Lu takes a liking to your wife or daughter,
and sends betrothal gifts directly to your home
without asking or seeing how you feel, will you agree to it?
- I won't agree!
Do you hear that? Miss Jun doesn't agree to it.
That's why I threw the betrothal gifts at your door.
Do you still not know what the meaning of this is?
You keep sending betrothal gifts again and again shamelessly.
What is this considered? Forcing a marriage.
Even if she is unwilling to accept,
this matter is between her and me.
As for you, what right do you have to interfere?
Commander Lu dares to say such words. However, the heir apparent of Duke Cheng dares not.
As heir apparent, he will take over the duke's position.
How could he decide his marriage on his own? If he says such things
and his parents don't agree to it,
then Miss Jun will become a laughingstock.
If he doesn't confess,
how will he explain his actions now?
It's like fighting for a courtesan in a brothel.
- Because I am—
- Because Miss Jun
is my fiancée.
- What?
- Is he crazy?
Miss Jun and I have had a marriage arrangement since childhood.
We decided to discuss it after the imperial court examination.
Unexpectedly, Lord Lu has misunderstood.
The young lord knows of this matter
so he helped me. I hope Lord Lu won't blame him for interfering.
Thank you, Young Lord, for helping me. I really appreciate it.
Everyone,
I swear in front of all of you as the newest first-ranked scholar,
that my marriage arrangement with Miss Jun is still valid
and we'll get married soon.
A marriage arrangement?
What a surprise.
I really did not expect our newest first-ranked scholar to be an affectionate person.
Yes, but this matter is actually beneficial to Your Majesty.
Think about it. Jun Jiuling is a woman after all.
Three men fought on the street over her. Her reputation is considered ruined.
What's the point of her making huge contributions? Civilians are more interested
in those private affairs between men and women.
Such a mess.
The Fang family, the Zhu family, and now the Ning family.
Later on, tell Lu Yunqi
not to do anything that disappoints me again.
Yes.
Do you have something on your mind? You've drunk a lot.
The last time I saw you drink like this, it was because of Princess Jiuling–
I...
It's because of Miss Jun, isn't it?
Of course not.
What does this have to do with her?
He's crying.
Okay. Okay. That's not it, it's not.
Then, why did you throw things at the Martial Moral Ministry's doors today?
I... can't stand Lu Yunqi.
I just happened to help her as well.
I see.
Go ahead and cry. Cry for a bit.
Second Brother,
if it isn't because of Miss Jun,
then there's nothing troubling you.
So then let's not cry like this. Okay, Second Brother?
Frankly,
I want to go back to the North.
I want to ride horses,
practice martial arts,
and go fight men from Northern Qi.
I'm going to be bored to death in the capital.
You should know why that person
is trapping you here in the capital. Try to let it go.
Second Brother has been suffocating for a while now.
Let him vent.
He's obviously troubled by love, Eldest Brother.
Do you think
it's because Young Master Ning claimed to be Miss Jun's fiancé
that he's gotten so depressed?
I want to know
what he would've said
if Young Master Ning hadn't shown up.
I guess...
- Second Brother.
- Forget it. Forget it.
Forget it. Let him drink.
- How about another—
- If you don't let me drink, I'll beat you up.
All right. Beat me up. If you're truly upset, why don't you beat me up then?
Here.
I'm afraid what happened today is the talk of the town and everyone knows it. What do you plan to do?
One is the newest first-ranked scholar, one is the Commander of the Martial Moral Ministry,
and one is Duke Cheng's heir apparent.
Three men like that fighting on the street over our miss,
I wonder how many women are jealous.
Are you a fool?
Do you think this is some kind of blessing?
This proves that our miss is likable.
Isn't being liked a blessing?
Being liked is a blessing indeed, but
one shouldn't "overfill a cup with water."
- What does that mean?
- You won't understand even if I explain it.
Young Master Ning.
Miss Jun.
Are you here because of what happened during the day?
Yes. I would like to discuss it with you.
Thank you for helping me today.
I said such a thing without discussing it with you in advance,
I hope you don't blame me.
Of course not.
- Let's go. Let's go.
- Why?
Young Master Ning, take a seat.
Under those circumstances, I didn't have any choice except to use the previous marriage contract to stop him.
I have no intention to ask you to fulfill the marriage contract.
Of course, I understand.
After coming to the capital for so long, you haven't returned to Zezhou, have you?
Young Master Ning, do you wish I go to Zezhou to lie low until this blows over?
Miss Jun, you are indeed smart. Those rumors and slander...
From Zezhou to the capital, it seems that rumors about me have never stopped.
I'm used to it now.
However, I have wronged you. You are now the newly appointed first-rank scholar by His Majesty and in the limelight,
yet I have implicated you.
Fame is just a superficial thing.
Miss Jun, you don't even care, so why should I be afraid?
As for the marriage arrangement, only we know it's fake.
If it's inconvenient for you, I can clarify at any time.
It's not inconvenient for me. I'm concerned that it is inconvenient for you.
How would it be inconvenient for me?
This is what the Ning Family owed you from the beginning.
It should be returned.
You have never owed me anything.
Zhu Zan?
How much did you drink?
Why did you come here so late?
Enough, enough. Sit.
Hurry and sit.
How many... husbands do you actually have?
What?
How many husbands do you have?
Chengyu is the first one. You've met him.
Confess... the second one.
I also know him.
- You've also met the third one.
- Is it me?
That's right.
Don't flatter yourself.
Also, don't make casual jokes. I have someone in my heart already.
I'm not joking.
Today, if Young Master Ning hadn't said it, then wouldn't you have?
You're still flattering yourself.
Let me list it out for you. The first one...
is the rich young kid.
Another is the talented first-rank scholar.
How dare you even imagine me,
a young and handsome hero being another?
Hero, quickly drink this tea to clear your drunkenness.
W-What are you looking at?
I'm thinking...
What caused that Lu Yunqi, that lunatic, to be so deranged?
Merely because of a name?
That is not enough to cause that crazy man to be so deranged.
Why is he so stubborn
and insists on marrying you?
H-Have another cup.
Then clear your head and go home. It's very late now.
That's the wrong one. Zhu Zan!
You're not allowed to drink anymore.
It's too late. You better hurry back.
You're not going to tell me, are you?
Don't lie down!
If you don't say, I won't leave.
You can't stay here.
Don't mess around. Don't mess around.
Zhu Zan, hurry put your clothes back on!
Zhu Zan, can you please put your clothes back on?
Zhu Zan?
You even know that Lu Yunqi is the third husband.
Are you awake?
Why are you in my room?
Take another look.
You came here in the middle of the night uninvited,
asking me how many husbands I have.
So... did you answer?
I did, I said I have had two.
Impossible. I was drinking with Zhang Baotang last night.
He must've said it.
You also said that you already have someone in your heart
and told me to not flatter myself by liking you.
Miss Jun, you are too improper.
You were able to say such an answer out loud?
Since you dared to ask, then why should I be ashamed to answer?
This bed is quite large.
There was only one bed last night.
Did you and I... I...
You're not asking me to take responsibility for you, are you?
Yesterday, thank you for helping me out.
No need to thank me.
You should thank your first-ranked scholar husband. He was the one who helped you.
I did thank him.
It happened at 1:00 p.m. yesterday,
yet you already saw him afterward?
Didn't I also see you after?
Second Brother's alcohol tolerance now is quite surprising.
He even slept in someone else's bedroom.
Do you want to drink some more, Second Brother?
Second Brother, don't be angry.
Did you both have nothing better to do than come here to laugh at me in the morning?
Stop messing around. Speak of serious matters.
How's my father? Has he replied to my letter?
Duke Cheng hasn't replied to your letter.
But calculating the time, it should arrive in the next few days.
There's also news about Yunxiao Pavilion. The orphan of the Wan family, Wan Qing,
appeared in Nanyuan Town once but there have been no traces of her after that.
Nanyuan Town is over twenty miles away from the capital.
Two possibilities.
One, she got captured by those from the Martial Moral Ministry.
Two, she took a risk and entered the capital to try to avenge the Wan family.
If that's the case, I'll ask around at the imperial prison.
However, knowing Lu Yunqi's personality,
I'm afraid even if she was captured, she would be locked up somewhere else,
or... was executed on the spot.
Baotang,
ask around. You must do it secretly.
Have someone from Yunxiao Pavilion make inquiries in the capital. If she truly came to the capital for revenge,
she will definitely make an appearance near Huang Cheng and his son.
You must stop her before she gets there;
otherwise, she'll only sacrifice her life for nothing since she is alone.
- Baotang, you'll take care of the imperial prison.
- Sure.
Sanbing, you'll be responsible for looking for her in the capital.
Okay.
Young Master, I don't think what you're doing is appropriate.
You don't understand. My way of doing things
can't be determined good or bad by the judgment those standing on the sidelines make.
Then, how do we determine whether it is good or bad?
By whether you follow your heart.
As long as it's what you want to do, you'll do it despite facing tens of thousands of people.
Even if there are many disadvantages,
it's the best, as long as you want to do it.
Young Master, maybe it's good for you,
but it's not good for Miss Jun.
Why not?
Doing this will cause Miss Jun and Madam to not get along.
This future relationship between the mother-in-law and daughter-in-law will not be harmonious.
Look! Matters between women are very troublesome.
Madam doesn't like Miss Jun. Right?
But you suddenly said your marriage arrangement with Miss Jun is still valid.
If Madam knows about this in Zezhou,
she'll certainly be furious.
Then Mother will be angry at me since it is my doing.
Why do you still not get it?
Madam won't get angry at you.
She'll surely hate Miss Jun.
Even if Miss Jun does nothing,
it is not all right either. In Madam's eyes,
everything is her fault and she does everything wrong.
That... That is a bit unreasonable.
Exactly.
Things between a mother-in-law and a daughter-in-law are unreasonable just like that.
If you first make Madam happy
and have her approval,
then go to Miss Jun to make the marriage proposal,
I believe it'll be easier to accomplish.
Yunzhao isn't the kind of child who causes trouble for his family. Why did he do that?
That's because he doesn't know he's causing trouble.
If he hadn't said anything back then, would it have been as serious as he says?
It doesn't matter anymore.
The most important thing now is we cannot deny it
or the consequence will be more serious.
Do we just acknowledge it then?
Acknowledge it. Furthermore, we acknowledge it seriously.
Even within the family, we must keep it a secret.
Sister-in-Law was waiting
to be a matchmaker after Yunzhao passed the imperial court examination.
Maybe we'd have grandchildren next year.
Now, this is great. Can we hide it even though it's fake?
We can make it come true.
My Lord!
Madam, Miss Jun is not bad.
Back then, you all said she did ridiculous things. Maybe she was young.
What about now?
Even now, she won't do.
Do you men only know to weigh the benefits and drawbacks
without taking relationships into consideration?
Even if Miss Jun is wonderful now, Sister-in-Law won't agree.
First, pass on the news that he's become the first-ranked scholar for now.
We can't put it off.
Do you mean we hide it from Sister-in-Law and the others for now?
How could we hide such an important matter?
We cannot speak of this matter in the letter.
You should know the dirty tricks
the Martial Moral Ministry use. It's better to be careful.
We'll hide it for as long as we can.
Grandmother, Jiuling's problem has finally been resolved.
That is great news.
Now you won't have to go to the capital and play the victim.
What do you mean?
Were you planning on going to the capital if Young Master Ning hadn't helped her?
I was thinking if we were truly left with no choice,
I would go to the capital, share my pitiful story,
and complain that Lord Lu is stealing another man's wife.
You, child, are possessed.
What does the Ning family want to do?
Grandmother, what you said would hurt Young Master Ning.
He had no other intentions, he simply wanted to help Jiuling.
Based on his status and the fact that he and Jiuling are friends, he's the perfect person for it.
Not only does it avoid doubts,
but it also solves the problem. It makes sense.
I know all that.
I just don't understand why he did that.
Exactly. Why did he do that?
To help Jiuling of course.
Grandmother. Mother.
Since Young Master Ning was willing to help, he's must be sincere.
How could it be sincere?
Breaking off their marriage arrangement made Madam Ning furious.
On the streets, they joke that he's worth 5,000 taels,
the same price as a famous courtesan.
There's also what happened at Jinyun Restaurant.
How could they forget
all those things in the past?
This Young Master Ning has just become a first-ranked scholar.
Frankly, it doesn't make sense.
Grandmother. Mother.
You may not trust Young Master Ning, but do you not trust Jiuling as well?
She said he helped, so surely he must have helped.
Jiuling is so intelligent. How could she let herself be at a disadvantage?
That's why I think
Jiuling and Young Master Ning had discussed it in advance.
Maybe it was Jiuling's idea.
This child. One thing happens after another.
I can't be bothered with them all.
By the way, Grandmother, I need to go to De Shengchang with Second Sister later.
We're leaving now.
All right. Learn more from your second sister.
Yes, Grandmother. Mother.
Ending OST: Sounds of Rain - Jiang Long & Yin Luxi
♫ The outline of my dream is carved on your face ♫
♫ Times interlace in the watery eyes ♫
♫ Allow me to weigh every word for indescribable
cause and effect ♫
♫ Life is full of ups and downs and hard to be free ♫
♫ With many tomorrows to come,
I’m willing to entrust my whole life to you ♫
♫ And see the starry night, mountains and rivers together ♫
♫ In the long silence, we are separated by a huge crowd ♫
♫ I can only sigh deeply. The rest of my life is bumpy ♫
♫ The vast sky is you and the wind is me ♫
♫ I’ll eventually be passed by ♫
♫ The wind is in hot pursuit and locked in deadlock with the sky ♫
♫ If memories could speak ♫
♫ I wouldn’t stop shedding tears like the rain ♫
♫ It’s hard to see you again. I’m wailing in deep sorrow ♫
♫ With many tomorrows to come,
I’m willing to entrust my whole life to you ♫
♫ And see the starry night, mountains and rivers together ♫
♫ In the long silence, we are separated by a huge crowd ♫
♫ I can only sigh deeply. The rest of my life is bumpy ♫
♫ The vast sky is you and the wind is me ♫
♫ I’m destined to be passed by ♫
♫ The wind is in hot pursuit and locked
in a deadlock with the sky ♫
♫ If memories could speak ♫
♫ I wouldn’t stop shedding tears like the rain ♫
♫ It’s hard to see you again. I’m wailing in deep sorrow ♫
♫ The vast sky is you and the wind is me ♫
♫ Going through the bottom of my heart ♫
♫ Has God ever asked for clues about the wind? ♫
♫ If I could write down how much I miss you ♫
♫ It would drift like the rain  ♫
♫ Seeing you again as if we’re strangers,
I’m wailing in deep sorrow ♫