Jun Jiu Ling - Deng Yujun
♫ Sighing at how fleeting life is, the swords tell of the scars ♫
♫ After our meeting, I'm unwilling to separate ♫
♫ Journeying alone and cold,
the past is a secret guarded closely ♫
♫ Hide the love and hate of tonight, stow away the naivety ♫
♫ Meeting an old friend,
we look at each other as the memories emerge ♫
♫ Only daring to show a bit of gentleness in dreams ♫
♫ This kiss caused the emotional entanglement
with you to surge ♫
♫ The warmth in the rough birch disturbs the stars  ♫
♫ The art of healing become edges used
to guard the mountains and rivers ♫
♫ Hurt and hatred have not taken over ♫
♫ Unwilling to let so much hatred be in this chaotic world,
a heart of sincerity in exchange for eternity ♫
♫ Journeying together, waiting for some prosperity ♫
♫ Rewrite this life because looking back, the heart aches ♫
♫ For the rest of this life, running in the field with you
without any regards, waiting for dawn ♫
♫ Dawn... ♫
[Jun Jiu Ling]
[Episode 34]
Chu Rang doesn't know my identity. It's good too.
However, Duke Cheng has always
been old friends with the previous emperor. I fear he will be implicated.
So what if he knows?
He has already given up his military power. What else does he still want?
Sometimes, one fears the hearts of the people more than military power.
Do you have a solution?
There's one for a county princess.
As for a royal princess, it's still far away.
It's not that far.
Chengyu is arriving today. I'm receiving him later.
All right. I will go with you.
- Jiuling.
- Chengyu,
it must have been a tiring journey for you.
I'm fine.
Heir Apparent.
Perhaps, I should call you "Brother-in-law."
Haven't seen you for a few days
and you are so sensible. It's so gratifying.
Well done.
You should still call him "Heir Apparent."
I think so, too. Your letter states that
this marriage contract is similar to the one in the past.
It doesn't count either. Hence, I should still call him "Heir Apparent."
It will reduce gossip later.
Baotang already calls you "Sister-in-law." Why can't he call me "Brother-in-law"?
I already told my family that our marriage arrangement was just a stop-gap measure.
It's the same as a form of address.
We hadn't recognized each other then.
Wife's younger brother, are you thirsty?
No. I merely think that,
before we are a family, we don't need to be that close.
Moreover, just like Jiuling, you should call me "Chengyu."
Fine, wife's younger brother.
You just arrived. Have a nice time catching up with your older sister.
As your brother-in-law, I'm leaving.
Take care, Older Brother.
Wife's younger brother, I'm leaving.
Older Brother, take care.
[Bright Gate]
Let's go back.
- Let's go.
Miss.
- Liu'er. Chen Qi.
- Young Master.
Young Master.
Shopkeeper Liu.
Where's Heir Apparent?
He went back to his mansion.
Where's Eldest Sister?
Jinxiu was busy this morning tidying up your room
and went to deliver medicines after that.
Young Master, you are not aware.
When she knew you were coming, she prepared four layers of padding for you.
She has always treated me very well. I know.
Not only that. When Jiuling Hall started business,
the expensive tea set that was gifted by others, she even placed it in your room.
She usually doesn't touch it and banned us from touching it, too. She even specially prepared...
Eldest Sister took a lot of trouble.
I'm not done talking, Youg Master.
- Jinxiu also...
- Shopkeeper Qi,
you keep talking about Miss Jinxiu.
Chengyu,
the conditions here are incomparable to home; however,
Jinxiu has provided you with the best.
It's already great.
- Miss, I'm going to unpack for Young Master.
- All right.
Santao, let's go. This way.
Chengyu, sit.
I want to chat with you regarding meeting His Majesty in two days.
His Majesty summoned you. It seems like a commendation and reward, but, in fact, a dangerous crisis lurks in four corners.
Since he doesn't want us to take his superior's written instructions,
why don't we use this opportunity to take the initiative and hand them over to him?
Seems like we both think this is a good idea.
Jiuling, if you hadn't brought this up, I would still have done as you said.
Jiuling, we are really soulmates.
I am rather nervous to enter the palace.
Don't worry. I'm here.
Heir Apparent, can you tell me again what else I should take note of when I meet His Majesty?
Didn't the staff from the Ministry of Rites teach you all that?
I'm nervous and afraid that I will forget.
In fact, there's no need to be nervous.
Jiuling's going to the palace with you. She will teach you.
Jiuling is a woman. She's still different from a man.
Moreover, you always enter the palace and are familiar with His Majesty.
I should listen more to you.
Forget it, Young Master. You must not learn Heir Apparent's methods.
Be careful or you will be taken to prison for interrogation.
You are being more extreme and even dare to make fun of me.
I was wrong, Heir Apparent.
Chengyu, don't worry. I'm here.
It's almost time. We are setting out.
- Greetings, Your Majesty.
Rise.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
- Thank you, Your Majesty.
You are indeed young and outstanding.
Courageous and knowledgeable. De Shengchang did such virtuous merits.
I will reward you generously.
It's my blessing to share Your Majesty's worries. I dare not take credit.
De Shengchang is willing to serve Your Majesty.
I know the distinction between rewards and punishments.
Speak. What rewards do you want?
Since this is the case, I will be bold to request a scroll of your beautiful calligraphy.
Your Majesty's calligraphy is
powerful and vigorous. Being able to obtain your calligraphy
is the greatest gift to De Shengchang.
The late emperor placed this under the care of the Fang family.
When De Shengchang was the Imperial Merchant, this was bestowed by His Majesty.
As of today, De Shengchang is no longer in-charge of imperial trading.
It's inappropriate to retain this.
Your Majesty, please take this back and gift us with beautiful calligraphy instead.
Since this is the case, fine.
I will take back the written instruction of the late emperor.
Speak. What words do you want?
"A kind and charitable family." Is that good?
I would like to request the "Fu" character from Your Majesty.
(T/N : Fu means good fortune)
Your Majesty's virtue carries great blessings. People’s fortune and longevity are destined by Heaven.
It's my honor to obtain your blessing.
I will allow this.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
[Good Fortune]
Jiuling, I thank you on behalf of Grandmother.
Thank me for what?
For handing over the written instruction to me yesterday, in exchange for saving the Fang family again.
Of course, I must thank you on behalf of Grandmother.
No need to thank me, because our Chengyu has grown up
and is able to undertake tasks alone for the Fang family.
This written instruction was the royal decree.
His Majesty intended to bestow this. Hence, there's this fate.
If His Majesty is set on recalling this, it will lose its meaning.
It's not a blessing to retain something which is meaningless. It's a calamity instead.
You are right.
Hence, exchanging this written instruction for this scroll of calligraphy is worth it.
Of course, it's worth it.
Is this Huang Cheng?
What does this crazy person want to do?
Jiuling. Younger Brother. Come here.
Xiaozao, what are you looking at?
This is my wife.
Perhaps soon she will not be.
Even if she's not, you will not get your turn either.
Right, Younger Brother?
Yes.
Do you still remember what today is?
[Red Phoenix Gate]
Today is the first anniversary of Jiuling Hall's opening.
That's it?
Or the first anniversary of the big marriage between Lord Lu and Princess Jiuli.
Do you invite us to the celebration?
Today is her birthday,
and also the second anniversary of the day we got married.
Did you forget, Heir Apparent?
How could I forget?
I thought...
you only remembered the new guy who was smiling and had forgotten the old guy who was crying.
Let's go, Younger Brother.
Happy birthday.
Congratulations, Your Majesty, for getting what you wanted.
With this manuscript in my hand, only the dead cannot talk.
I will go and arrange now.
Go.
Yes.
Previously I was wrong; too childish.
Today in the palace, many thanks to Heir Apparent for protecting Jiuling.
No need to thank me.
Why not let me listen to you call me "Brother-in-law"?
I can call you brother-in-law, but you must promise me some things.
Tell me. I'm listening.
Our Fang family is grateful for Jiuling.
If you treat her badly, the Fang family will give it all
to go against you, this is the first.
Yes. What's the second one?
Jiuling has quite a lot of enemies.
You must be in front of everything to protect her fully.
- This is the second.
- That comes naturally.
Even though the Fang family is Jiuling's maternal side, Jiuling's family
has no one else. She might feel desolate.
You have to make her happy throughout her life.
I will definitely do it.
Brother-in-law.
Come, come! Drink tea, drink tea.
What are you chatting about?
Oh, nothing much.
So secretive.
Chengyu,
I'm thinking now that the imperial edict has been returned to His Majesty,
shouldn't you go back earlier?
I finally came to the capital, I want to accompany you for a few more days.
It's still not the time to be lax.
I'm afraid...
Jiuling, the manuscript was already been returned,
what are you worried about?
This secret is connected to His Majesty?
Yes.
All these years, the person who framed our Fang family behind the scenes,
don't tell me it's His Majesty?
So you are worried that as His Majesty has taken back the manuscript,
and has no leverage and worries, his target will be Grandmother?
Exactly.
So do you have enough manpower in the family?
Manpower in the family...
Before I left, I especially increased people to protect the courtyard, and asked Master Lei to help.
But if His Majesty starts his attack, I'm afraid it'll be hard to defend.
How about this? I'll go back with you.
No way, you cannot leave the capital.
Not to mention once you leave, it'll cause His Majesty to suspect.
You two don't have to worry.
I will arrange manpower.
One more thing.
I want to discuss this with you two.
What is it?
My Lord, if I may be so bold, today is the first anniversary of your marriage to Her Highness.
The kitchen has prepared wine and food. Do you want to stay and have a meal together with Madam?
She knows where I'm going.
Almost done.
- Let me try.
- Put it down.
- Put it here.
- Put it down, put it down.
Food is here.
Come.
We are back.
- You are back.
- Miss.
Mei Xin wine?
Yes.
Jiuling said you told her
only this wine accompanying your meats will make them delicious,
so she especially pulled me to Three Yuan Building to buy it.
What are you all doing?
Its almost done, wait a while.
- Scalded, right? Let me do it.
- It's okay, let me do it.
- Let me do it.
- It's okay.
Why are you so careless?
It's full.
Sister.
I'm leaving tomorrow. Let's chat.
The kitchen has two more dishes. I'll go and bring them.
Leave it to me, you don't need to take care of it.
Heir Master, your meat is left.
All right.
Yes, yes! Let me and Liu handle the things in the kitchen.
You go to the front and take a look if the door is locked. We are closed.
Okay? Go, go.
Miss, I'll go and prepare two more dishes.
I'll go and help too.
It's okay, it's okay.
Can you be more careful?
Why are you making noise? A toothache?
Painful, sour,
so sour that I have a toothache.
Sweet toothache.
That's good. I don't have anything here, but I have medicine.
When you have a toothache don't eat meat, eat medicine.
Then I will continue to have a toothache.
Is it hot?
It's okay.
I suddenly feel like I have a stomachache.
I'm going to the toilet.
What about you?
Eldest Brother, don't you have a stomachache?
Third Brother,
I cannot control it anymore.
- I will go first.
- Yes.
- Everyone is leaving, why?
Why are you all leaving?
Why did they leave? Really!
Looks like today's scene has some deeper meaning.
Yes, there's a deeper meaning.
Jiuling.
Happy birthday.
In the past years, your birthday used to have a lot of people.
But this time, the situation doesn't allow it, so we cannot make it big.
I can only take this opportunity to wish you a happy birthday.
I've prepared a present, you take a look.
Must be serious.
Jiuling, I know every year on your birthday,
you would go to the imperial dining room to eat longevity cake.
So I asked someone for the recipe.
I made it myself. You taste it.
If it does not taste good, don't dislike it.
Just make do with it and eat.
You can try it.
Previously on my birthday every year,
Imperial Father would ask the imperial kitchen to make this.
Last year, I didn't get to eat it, I thought this year...
Zhu Zan, thank you.
In the past, it was your Imperial Father who protected you.
In the future,
I will protect you.
You taste it.
What do you think?
Is it delicious?
- Very sweet.
- Very sweet?
I didn't put sugar in it.
I mean, your love is very sweet.
Jiuling,
when did you learn to say things like this?
Sister.
Chengyu.
How is it? Are you used to living here?
Pretty good.
I didn't get to ask you. Is everything okay back home?
Everything's fine. Grandmother is still healthy.
Look at you. You've really grown up.
Yes, I'm different from what I used to be.
Now that I've recovered, I'm no longer the Chengyu who needs to be taken care of at all times.
I can ride a horse, shoot arrows, and even come all the way here to visit you now.
Chengyu,
I'm sorry.
You're saying something silly again.
Didn't we agree on it at home?
We have all gotten over this matter.
You're always free and easy. Can't you get over it?
I... I got over it a long time ago.
Thank you, Chengyu.
I used to not understand why you started your business on June 18th,
but now I do.
I used to not understand
why Lu Yunqi chose June 18th as his wedding day either,
but now I do too.
Did you know his feelings for you?
I agreed to the marriage arranged by the emperor for revenge.
To me, there's no difference between him and others.
I'm very satisfied with this answer.
What am I to you then?
Not as good as others.
That was a punishment for your lie.
Someone's here.
Nobody's here.
Another chance for you. Give me a good answer.
You...
You're so beautiful.
They're kissing.
Young Lady, our dishes...
are ready.
Everyone, come and eat. The food is ready.
Let's eat.
- All right.
- Take a seat.
- Here. Sit down.
Jiuling, why don't you say something?
- Say something.
- Say a little.
Yes, say something.
Today marks the first anniversary of the opening of Jiuling Hall.
Over the past year, everyone has gone through a lot of things.
I'd say Jiuling Hall wouldn't be here without you all.
Here. Let me thank all of you.
- Here.
- Cheers!
Jiuling, happy birthday.
[Wife Princess Jiuling's Memorial Tablet]
I've met another girl.
She... is very much like you.
Every time I see her,
I think of you.
Next time, I'll bring her here to see you. Okay?
Ling Jiu,
I feel really happy now
with you by my side.
Same here.
I never thought
I would still be able to see you again, eat, drink wine and stargaze with you.
Why do you look shocked?
When did you start having a crush on me? Why didn't you tell me?
I liked you a little when I was a kid.
Only a little?
It was a little when I was a kid, but I liked you more as I grew up.
I wanted to tell you at the right time,
but I never knew I'd spend eight years in the North.
When I came back, everything had changed.
Can you promise me one thing?
From now on, no matter what happens,
no matter who it is,
don't get separated from me.
♫ The past is like smoke, and youth is like a dream ♫
Let's make a pinky promise that can't change for 100 years.
We've agreed.
We've made a promise. You're not allowed to break it.
♫ Don't forget what I used to look like ♫
I'm no longer alone.
When you weren't with me,
I had to pretend to be strong in front of everyone,
because I needed to help them,
so that everyone could rely on me.
♫ Don't forget what I used to look like ♫
But I actually wanted a shoulder to lean on.
Then there you were.
When I'm with you, I can be what I like to be most,
what I used to be,
and be as relaxed as possible.
You're annoying.
Because even if I have tough armor, you're my weakness.
♫ The past is like smoke, and youth is like a dream ♫
From now on, you won't have any weaknesses anymore
because I'm your toughest armor.
♫ Don't forget what I used to look like ♫
How beautiful.
I'll add two more herbs to your prescription.
Stick your tongue out for me.
Take her over there for the medicine.
Sure.
- Come with me.
- Thank you, Physician.
This is your favorite. You eat it first.
You can eat it.
Sister, come here and visit me often.
Is it delicious?
Uncle, please take a look.
Chengyu can finally retreat on this trip.
The imperial decree is gone, but our people are the most important.
Yes, it's good as long as Chengyu is safe.
The imperial decree turned into a blessing,
and it helped the government settle the refugees in the North.
We suffered financial loss but avoided misfortune.
- That's right.
- His Majesty let our Fang family help settle refugees, which is our Fang family's honor.
Don't say things like that outside.
Yes, Mother.
Madam... Madam...
Madam... Young Master...
What's wrong with Young Master? Tell us now.
The inn Young Master stayed at caught fire. He is gone.
Madam.
His Majesty summoned me to go to the capital. I'm the only man in the family.
It's a long trip as well.
Grandmother, you're already old. I can't let you risk it again.
Chengyu, this time you're summoned for rewards. We have to be careful.
This is the exact reason why only I can go, not you.
Impossible. Impossible.
Chengyu, Young Master Ning helped Jiuling.
Are you happy?
The fish delivered to the capital tastes even better.
Chengyu.
God is unfair.
God is unfair
to our Fang family!
Chengyu!
The inn Young Master of the Fang family stayed at
had a fire by accident. He died in the fire.
- Any mistakes?
- According to the Fang family,
Young Master Fang brought a jade pendant with him.
It was passed down from his ancestors. He never left it behind.
The Fang family found this jade pendant on the dead body.
Despite being damaged, it was recognizable.
Send someone there to take another look.
Yes.
When Young Master left,
he was still...
God is so unfair!
I think the family has received the letter now.
I wonder if Old Madam
can deal with this blow.
Since something awful happened, I have to go back and visit my grandmother.
- I'll go back, too.
- I'll go with you both.
When are you leaving? I'll have the carriage ready.
Tomorrow morning.
I'll have the carriage ready.
You're smart and skillful.
You're my very good sister.
You're my sister forever.
Look at you. You've grown up.
Yes, I'm different from what I used to be.
Now that I've recovered, I'm no longer the Chengyu who needed to be taken care of at all times.
Did Chengyu die in an accident...
or in someone's trap?
Are you doubting if someone set it on fire?
Chengyu went to the capital this time, which was dangerous already.
He finally handed over the imperial decree and did all kinds of work.
He sort of prevented His Majesty from fearing De Shengchang.
Look! What a coincidence.
On his way back to Zezhou,
he got into trouble.
Chengyu!
[Jiuling Hall]
In this world, no preparation is completely safe, and no promise is always the same.
Are you still deceiving yourself?
You're well aware that His Majesty sent him here
not only to keep an eye on the Fang family, but also to get rid of the Fang family.
Sounds of Rain - Jiang Long & Yin Luxi
♫ The outline of my dream is carved on your face ♫
♫ Times interlace in the watery eyes ♫
♫ Allow me to weigh every word for indescribable
cause and effect ♫
♫ Life is full of ups and downs and hard to be free ♫
♫ With many tomorrows to come,
I’m willing to entrust my whole life to you ♫
♫ And see the starry night, mountains and rivers together ♫
♫ In the long silence, we are separated by a huge crowd ♫
♫ I can only sigh deeply. The rest of my life is bumpy ♫
♫ The vast sky is you and the wind is me ♫
♫ I’ll eventually be passed by ♫
♫ The wind is in hot pursuit and locked in deadlock with the sky ♫
♫ If memories could speak ♫
♫ I wouldn’t stop shedding tears like the rain ♫
♫ It’s hard to see you again. I’m wailing in deep sorrow ♫
♫ With many tomorrows to come,
I’m willing to entrust my whole life to you ♫
♫ And see the starry night, mountains and rivers together ♫
♫ In the long silence, we are separated by a huge crowd ♫
♫ I can only sigh deeply. The rest of my life is bumpy ♫
♫ The vast sky is you and the wind is me ♫
♫ I’m destined to be passed by ♫
♫ The wind is in hot pursuit and locked in
a deadlock with the sky ♫
♫ If memories could speak ♫
♫ I wouldn’t stop shedding tears like the rain ♫
♫ It’s hard to see you again. I’m wailing in deep sorrow ♫
♫ The vast sky is you and the wind is me ♫
♫ Going through the bottom of my heart ♫
♫ Has God ever asked for clues about the wind? ♫
♫ If I could write down how much I miss you ♫
♫ It would drift like the rain  ♫
♫ Seeing you again as if we’re strangers,
I’m wailing in deep sorrow ♫