Opening OST: Jun Jiu Ling - Deng Yujun
♫ Sighing at how fleeting life is, the swords tell of the scars ♫
♫ After our meeting, I'm unwilling to separate ♫
♫ Journeying alone and cold,
the past is a secret guarded closely ♫
♫ Hide the love and hate of tonight, stow away the naivety ♫
♫ Meeting an old friend,
we look at each other as the memories emerge ♫
♫ Only daring to show a bit of gentleness in dreams ♫
♫ This kiss caused the emotional entanglement
with you to surge ♫
♫ The warmth in the rough birch disturbs the stars  ♫
♫ The art of healing become edges used
to guard the mountains and rivers ♫
♫ Hurt and hatred have not taken over ♫
♫ Unwilling to let so much hatred be in this chaotic world,
a heart of sincerity in exchange for eternity ♫
♫ Journeying together, waiting for some prosperity ♫
♫ Rewrite this life because looking back, the heart aches ♫
♫ For the rest of this life, running in the field with you
without any regards, waiting for dawn ♫
♫ Dawn... ♫
[Jun Jiu Ling]
[Episode 22]
You are all helping Zhu Zan, thus disobeying the imperial decree.
You all must die.
Hold on.
Lord Lu, since you are here asking for his whereabouts,
you must already know that he's not here at Qingshan Court.
However, you are under an imperial decree to guard this place.
Now that someone is missing, it will be difficult for you to escape blame. Right?
Physician Jun, should I praise you for being a smooth talker
or should I convict you of the crime of inefficient treatments for patients?
Physician Jun has worked tirelessly and made lots of contributions. What crime has she committed?
Young Lord.
Xiao Zao, do you recognize these people?
- You actually brought them out.
- Since I am able to bring them out of the prison meant for those on death row,
then it shows I am acting on His Majesty's orders.
Xiao Zao, I have two imperial decrees with me now.
What can you do to me?
Come.
Young Lord, this is...
They are children you can try the inoculation on.
What? Try the inoculation on these two children?
They are the descendants of Grand Guardian Zhou.
- But...
- If we send them back,
they will be beheaded. I requested an imperial decree.
His Majesty said that as long as they survive the inoculation,
they can escape death.
Come. Tell them. What are your names?
I am Zhou Jing from Zhending.
My grandfather is Zhou Bentang.
Z-Zhou Bentang?
Is it that traitor Zhou Bentang who colluded with the enemy?
Colluding with the enemy is a capital offense.
However, children are innocent after all.
My grandfather didn't collude with the enemy or commit treason.
No. Of course not.
He was set up.
All I am capable of...
is saving the two siblings.
Little ones,
inoculation is very dangerous. You...
Older Sister, just give us the inoculation.
Mao Mao, say something.
Older Sister, I want to try the inoculation.
Physician Jun, these children are so mature.
You must help them live.
That's right.
Thank you for having faith in me.
I promise you...
that I and the rest of the physicians here will do our best to protect your lives.
Also, to not waste this older brother's efforts in
saving you from that prison by risking his life.
Physicians, I believe in all of your capabilities.
Please do your best.
That's our job.
Lord, do we really let them be?
They are descendants of Zhou Bentang.
I spoke out of line.
My Lord, will we still use the inflammable materials?
No.
Why are you here?
You haven't slept for a few days. I'm worried you're too tired.
You care that much about me?
That night when I was in excruciating pain,
you kept me company the entire night. Chen Qi also said
that you hadn't slept for days now.
Try it. I made it.
Even you risked your life to try the inoculation.
How could I fall asleep?
This battle is finally over.
We can have some rest. It's exhausting, isn't it?
Hurry and try it.
How is it?
This bowl of ginseng soup...
is the worst I've ever had.
Don't drink it then.
That's fine. There will be plenty,
plenty of opportunities.
Zhu Zan,
thank you.
Miss Jun,
don't develop inappropriate thoughts for me.
Physician Jun, thank you for saving my daughter and me.
I can't accept it. Please get up.
Physician Jun and other physicians
are benevolent, curing all diseases.
They're all miraculous physicians.
- Yes.
- Miraculous physicians.
Thank you, Older SisterJun.
Guo'er, Heaven was touched by your filial piety.
That's why you and your mother could recover so quickly.
From now on, Guo'er, you shall be the strongest kid.
Okay?
Physician Jun came up with a way to treat the pox.
The young lord personally tested the inoculation.
All the physicians spared no effort. Your kindness is beyond description.
We should kowtow to them for their help.
- Thank you, Physician Jun.
- Please get up.
- Everyone, get up.
Please get up.
Thank you, Young Lord, for saving me.
What I did for you was trivial.
The physicians behind me
are the true saviors.
You must learn from them.
Do you understand?
Everyone, you being well
is the greatest reward for us. I've promised before
to make sure you all go home safely.
So, ridding you of the suffering of the pox
is the greatest consolation to us.
Physician Jun, if it weren't for you all,
I would never have had a chance to see my family again.
I can't repay you enough for your kindness and what you have done.
- Exactly.
There's no need for thanks. If you want to thank someone, you should thank yourselves.
It was your trust and perseverance
that lead to such positive results.
You all are the greatest contributors.
Yes. The young lord sacrificed himself for the sake of others.
Duke Cheng's generations of loyalty
is admirable indeed.
Now that everyone has recovered,
your family is waiting for you. Go home.
Thank you, Brother. Thank you, physicians.
Thank you, physicians.
- Hurry and go home.
- Let's go home.
Let's go home now. Go home.
- Thank you, physicians.
- Goodbye.
- Take care, physicians.
Let's go, too.
We're going home now.
Miss Jun.
Thank you.
You worked hard.
Many people have already entered the city.
The people Young Master arranged for, have arrived.
They said they would come back today, but why isn't Miss back yet?
Where is she?
I don't know where Chen Qi is either.
He's dead when I see him!
I kept watching from the top of the city gate.
I didn't see Miss even with my eyes wide open.
Those physicians had a glorious welcome.
What about our number one heroine?
Where is Miss?
What should we do?
What are you talking about?
- You're back.
- Miss!
- Jiuling!
Miss.
Miss, when did you come back? Why didn't you come back with the others?
Why didn't you tell us in advance, so we could pick you up?
You're asking me so many questions at once. Which one should I answer first?
That's because I was worried about you and missed you very much.
Rest assured. Don't worry. I'm back, aren't I?
- Shopkeeper Liu.
- Young Lady Jun.
What did the Eldest Young Lady Fang say will happen to Chen Qi when she sees him?
He's dead!
It's my fault. I... won't worry you again.
Why didn't you let us know you were back? We were so worried.
Young Lady knew that Young Master was going to have a celebration to recognize her achievements.
We anticipated that when we entered the city, there would definitely be many citizens to welcome us.
She doesn't like such scenes, so we decided to return to the city on our own.
I'm just afraid that Chengyu's kind act will go to waste.
It won't. Whatever you do is right. Young Master won't blame you.
There's actually no need for a celebration in recognization of her achievements. Now that the pox is treated,
our Jiuling Hall will surely be well known.
That's absurd. Jiuling Hall stole the show.
Surprisingly, they succeeded only one day before His Majesty's deadline.
How great is it now? Even people from Ru'nan and Zezhou
have come all the way here with their kids to get inoculations from Jiuling Hall.
Inoculation is a serious matter,
which involves all the people.
How could such a small medicinal hall be in charge of it?
We should ask His Majesty to let Imperial Physicians Hall take over this matter.
That's right. After some time,
they'll think it's the Imperial Physicians Hall that is responsible for their inoculation.
However, that Jun Jiuling is not easy to deal with.
Will she be willing to tell us about the method of inoculation?
His Majesty will summon her in a few days to ask about the inoculation.
She's just an ordinary woman.
When facing His Majesty, she'll surely feel terrified and uneasy.
At that time, I will propose this matter in court.
I don't think she'll dare to say no in front of His Majesty.
That's right.
Miss, you must've been so tired, you've lost some weight.
Your favorite snacks. Eat some.
I'm fine. It's just that Chen Qi has suffered lately.
Without his help, I wouldn't have been able to handle it.
I did not help that much.
Thinking about it, our young master is so smart.
He held celebrations in recognition of your achievements in Ru'nan and Zezhou in advance.
He did it because he trusts you. He trusts you very much.
Ever since I left the Fang family, I've still caused my grandmother and aunt trouble.
I understand what it means. Other people with ulterior motives
can understand it, too.
What he did is too risky. If someone took advantage of him
and criticized the Fang family for this
by saying the Fang family is manipulating the people, it would be a serious crime.
You're right.
I have to write him a letter.
Young Lady Jun, if there's nothing I can help with, I'll go back now
to get ready for tomorrow's trip to the palace.
Thank you, Shopkeeper Liu.
All right.
Miss, don't worry. It'll be fine. We're going to the palace tomorrow.
Going to the palace this time, I can finally see Chu Rang again.
Horseback riding in the moonlight is supposed to be delightful, so why do you look so worried?
Are you still concerned about entering the palace?
Miss Jun,
what's your purpose in entering the palace?
Sometimes I feel like I've known you for a long time. It feels quite familiar.
But when I see you clearly, you're hidden among many secrets
as if you're wrapped up in the fog.
It's blurry.
I came back to the capital for revenge,
for Princess Jiuling
and for my father.
You've finally opened up to me.
I know that you have many secrets.
That's fine.
From now on, if you don't say it, I won't ask you.
But whatever you want to do,
I'll be with you.
♫ The outline of my dream is carved on your face ♫
♫ Times interlace in the watery eyes ♫
♫ Allow me to weigh every word
forindescribable cause and effect ♫
for indescribable cause and effect ♫
♫ Life is full of ups and downs and hard to be free ♫
♫ With many tomorrows to come,
I’m willing to entrust my whole life to you ♫
Fireflies.
"Rain cannot smother the fire.
(T/N: The poem "Singing Firefly" by Li Bai, a famous poet.)
As the wind blows, it becomes brighter.
If it flies high into the sky,
(T/N: The poem "Singing Firefly" by Li Bai, a famous poet.)
it'll surely become a star by the moon's side."
Fireflies are truly a great medicinal ingredient.
♫ I’ll eventually be passed by ♫
With a beautiful view in front of you, you can only think of medicine?
That's right. Fireflies can cleanse your liver and improve your vision. A great medicinal ingredient it is indeed.
You're truly not an ordinary woman.
Then, what is an ordinary woman like?
"Wow, such beautiful fireflies!"
Forget it. So disgusting. I can't take it.
Young Lady Jun, when it comes to the inoculation, nobody can compare with you.
Why do you want me to enter the palace with you?
Because there are things that even I can't do.
Physician Feng, rest assured. There's no need to be anxious.
Physician Jun, entering the palace is a serious matter.
Why are you not nervous at all, as if you're returning to your home?
Physician Jun, please.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
I, Jun Jiuling, greet Your Majesty.
Please rise.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Your success in treating the pox at Qingshan Court
is just like a victory in war, a great honor of our nation.
Having made such a great contribution, I should reward you heavily.
I dare not take credit.
Treating pox successfully is due to the right time, the right place, and the right people.
First, Your Majesty showed grace by delivering materials. Heaven being touched, gave us this opportune time.
Qingshan Court is spacious, making it easy to separate and treat patients. That was the right place.
Meanwhile, many physicians
and the young lord, who willingly tried the inoculation, helped. Those were the right people.
How humble you are.
You came up with the inoculation,
so you should take the credit.
Your Majesty, there is something
I would like to ask Physician Jun to enlighten me about.
These useless things come forward when there is a reward.
Forget it. I'll see how she handles it.
- Go ahead.
- Your Majesty,
the method of treating pox is a fortune for our nation.
However, not many know how to perform the inoculation,
and most of them are here in the capital.
How to promote it in every region
needs to be discussed.
What suggestions do you have?
I believe the Imperial Physicians Hall can be responsible for this matter.
Every medicinal hall can send someone to the capital to learn the method of inoculation,
under Physician Jun's supervision.
Those who pass shall return home and promote it so that our people
can avoid suffering from smallpox.
Your Majesty, I agree with what Imperial Physician Jiang has said.
What does Physician Jun think?
Your Majesty,
I disagree.
Miss Jun is most likely meeting His Majesty in the palace now.
After treating the pox this time,
I'm curious to see how those people from Imperial Physicians Hall will give her a hard time.
It's hard to give her a hard time.
She knows what to say in front of different people.
During Miss Jun's meeting with His Majesty, I'm afraid those from Imperial Physicians Hall
will steal her method of inoculation.
If that's the case,
do you think Miss Jun will give the method away or not?
- Yes.
- No.
Jiuling Hall is just an ordinary medicinal hall.
Imperial Physicians Hall is set up by the Imperial Court.
Whom the smallpox treatment belongs to
and what His Majesty thinks are easy to guess.
Miss Jun is powerless, so it will be very difficult for her to refuse.
But if she gives it away,
then she won't be who she is.
Physician Jun, are you unwilling to make your methods public?
Imperial Physician Jiang, physicians find honor in treating the people.
Of course, I'm willing to make my methods public.
Even more so, I'm willing to have all physicians come here to learn.
But...
Not through the Imperial Physicians Hall, but through the physicians who've been to Qingshan Court.
Are you saying you don't trust Imperial Physicians Hall?
Imperial Physician Jiang, you have misunderstood.
Inoculation requires practical learning.
It cannot be taught orally.
However, the epidemic in the capital is now over.
Unless there's another epidemic and the physicians from Imperial Physicians Hall learn from that, then they can promote it.
- How could that be acceptable?
- How absurd!
She does not know what's good for her!
Your Majesty, that's why
I cannot agree with what Imperial Physician Jiang said.
She isn't nervous at all here at the great hall. I can't underestimate her.
What do you think we should do then?
Your Majesty, Physician Feng
is a famous physician who has run a medicinal hall in the capital for years. He's very reputable.
Also, Physician Feng has made irrefutable contributions to the treatment of pox this time.
I recommend Physician Feng take charge in the evaluation and promotion of the smallpox treatment.
The regional government offices can send physicians here to learn.
Let Physician Feng lead physicians who know how to treat the pox to teach classes.
You created this smallpox treatment.
It would be better for you to be in charge.
Your Majesty, I am young.
This is an important task, and it would be difficult for me to convince others.
Besides, Physician Feng has more experience in inoculation than I.
At such a young age, she understands the concept of avoiding danger and being modest?
Approved.
However, you must take the post of supervisor.
I shall obey.
Thank you, Your Majesty, for your grace.
Please rise.
This is not my reward for you.
If you want to thank someone, thank her.
Physician Jun, how outstanding you are.
You're young, but you don't take credit or get arrogant.
You are not simple.
Chu Rang is skeptical in nature.
If I don't request anything, I'll certainly make him suspicious of me.
Your Majesty, I'm flattered.
Actually,
I do have a small request.
I hope Your Majesty can make it happen.
Tell me about your request.
I shall make sure you are content.
I don't care about money.
But if Your Majesty could bestow me a title,
I would do my ancestors proud who practiced medicine for generations.
How dare you!
You're just a small female physician. How dare you ask for a title?!
His Majesty is benevolent. Do you think you can be outrageous
and ask for anything just for treating the pox?
I was being absurd.
Your Majesty, please punish me.
Lord Huang, no need to be so angry. I think
Physician Jun's request is reasonable.
I'll confer you as County Princess (Princess of the Fourth Rank ).
Your title shall be... Shanyang.
I, commoner Jun Jiuling, thank Your Majesty.
Physician Jun, you're no longer a commoner.
I, County Princess Shanyang,
thank Your Majesty for your grace.
Your Majesty,
the princes and princesses are waiting for Physician Jun to give them the inoculation.
Go ahead.
[Red Phoenix Gate]
Physician Jun, they're here.
Miss Jun.
Physician Feng, I shall go see you tomorrow about the matter of inoculation.
All right. I'll take my leave now.
Thank you.
Older Sister, I missed you so much!
I missed you very much, too.
What is it? Why do you want to see me today?
Get up.
What is it?
Older Sister, we're leaving.
Don't worry. Everything has been arranged and settled.
Zhou Jing. Mao Mao.
Remember that when I'm not by your side,
you need to learn how to take care of yourselves.
Do you understand?
- Yes.
I'll always remember your courage and kindness
when you were at Qingshan Court. Remain that way in the future.
Miss Jun, if you are so reluctant to let them leave,
why don't you take them as your godsons?
Can I call you godmother?
Then you're my godfather.
Then you're my godmother.
- Godfather.
- Godmother.
Nonsense.
It's getting late, they have to get on the road.
Come on.
Say goodbye to your godfather and godmother.
- Godfather. Godmother. Take care.
- Let's go.
- Take care.
Say, am I that old? He called me Godfather.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Suddenly, I just...
I just suddenly want to cry.
Is there something you want to tell me?
No.
This Jun Jiuling is a bit different from what people say.
Based on you're understanding of her,
was she acting or being her true self at the imperial court?
I think it's fake.
Although I did not have many
encounters with her at Qingshan Court,
from what I know,
she is normally even more rude and daring.
Her words and actions today clearly show her longing for power and influence.
What's your opinion on that?
She dares to have such a request in the great hall.
I think that's what she truly wants.
Have all the princes been inoculated?
Your Majesty, besides the third prince,
the rest of the princes and princesses have been inoculated.
The Third Prince has had a cough lately.
Physician Jun said you have to be healthy before being inoculated.
Therefore, we must wait until the Third Prince recovers from his cough before he can get inoculated.
All the physicians have learned almost everything except for Physician Liu.
There are two more who are not as well-versed in inoculations.
After a few more days of practicing, they can return home as well.
It looks like everything is going well.
Yes.
What are they looking at up ahead? It's so lively there.
Today is the 18th of the third month.
(T/N: lunar calendar)
The imperial court examination results have been published.
- Is the Ministry of Rites' grand exam over?
- Yes.
Wonder how Young Master Ning has done. Miss, let's go and take a look.
Then, I'll go check on Physician Liu.
- Thank you, Physician Feng.
- No problem.
Let's go.
- Excuse us, excuse us.
- Look! Look, my name is there!
I passed!
He got in!
[Third place : Ning Yunzhao ]
Young Master Ning passed!
[Ning Residence]
Even though you didn't get the first place,
until the palace exam, nothing is set.
Yes.
I won't criticize these writings.
Revise it and wait for my return to discuss it in detail.
Yes, Uncle.
Xiao Ding, how's Qingshan Court?
Young Master, you were busy with the exam a couple of days ago. Master Ning wouldn't let me tell you.
Miss Jun successfully treated the pox and has come down from the mountain with everyone.
She always has had the ability to escape danger.
Is Miss Jun back at Jiuling Hall?
Yes.
Not only that, but His Majesty also summoned her.
His Majesty bestowed her the title of County Princess Shanyang.
Lord Ning was there, too.
He... didn't tell you?
Uncle doesn't like me to have anything to do with her, so of course, he won't mention it.
Then once Madam finds out,
she will cut my skin off.
Don't worry, I won't tell Mother.
Thank you, Young Master.
Young Master, there is a congratulatory gift for you.
Leave it.
Young Master, this is from Miss Jun.
[From Jun Jiuling]
Frank, open, and genuine, she is better than I.
All you students studied hard for dozens of years.
Here at the palace exam, you all are pillars of society.
Ning Yunzhao is the best among the scholars.
He has brilliant literary talent and is thus, awarded as the top scholar.
The rest of you keep working hard.
Make the country prosperous and stable.
Look, there!
[Jiuling Hall]
Jinxiu, can I go out to get some air?
Go! Why did you ask me?
From what I see, Chen Qi
is completely in the palm of Miss Jinxiu's hand.
Who wants to control him? It's because he is not very reliable.
When Chen Qi was at Qingshan Court,
he took care of everything very well.
Miss Jinxiu seems to know that.
That's right.
I didn't know. We are not that close.
I have no idea.
Oh, not very close.
Miss! Miss!
Lord Lu is here.
Why is he here again?
Ending OST: Sounds of Rain - Jiang Long & Yin Luxi
♫ The outline of my dream is carved on your face ♫
♫ Times interlace in the watery eyes ♫
♫ Allow me to weigh every word for indescribable
cause and effect ♫
♫ Life is full of ups and downs and hard to be free ♫
♫ With many tomorrows to come,
I’m willing to entrust my whole life to you ♫
♫ And see the starry night, mountains and rivers together ♫
♫ In the long silence, we are separated by a huge crowd ♫
♫ I can only sigh deeply. The rest of my life is bumpy ♫
♫ The vast sky is you and the wind is me ♫
♫ I’ll eventually be passed by ♫
♫ The wind is in hot pursuit and locked in deadlock with the sky ♫
♫ If memories could speak ♫
♫ I wouldn’t stop shedding tears like the rain ♫
♫ It’s hard to see you again. I’m wailing in deep sorrow ♫
♫ With many tomorrows to come,
I’m willing to entrust my whole life to you ♫
♫ And see the starry night, mountains and rivers together ♫
♫ In the long silence, we are separated by a huge crowd ♫
♫ I can only sigh deeply. The rest of my life is bumpy ♫
♫ The vast sky is you and the wind is me ♫
♫ I’m destined to be passed by ♫
♫ The wind is in hot pursuit and locked
in a deadlock with the sky ♫
♫ If memories could speak ♫
♫ I wouldn’t stop shedding tears like the rain ♫
♫ It’s hard to see you again. I’m wailing in deep sorrow ♫
♫ The vast sky is you and the wind is me ♫
♫ Going through the bottom of my heart ♫
♫ Has God ever asked for clues about the wind? ♫
♫ If I could write down how much I miss you ♫
♫ It would drift like the rain  ♫
♫ Seeing you again as if we’re strangers,
I’m wailing in deep sorrow ♫