Opening OST: Jun Jiu Ling - Deng Yujun
♫ Sighing at how fleeting life is, the swords tell of the scars ♫
♫ After our meeting, I'm unwilling to separate ♫
♫ Journeying alone and cold,
the past is a secret guarded closely ♫
♫ Hide the love and hate of tonight, stow away the naivety ♫
♫ Meeting an old friend,
we look at each other as the memories emerge ♫
♫ Only daring to show a bit of gentleness in dreams ♫
♫ This kiss caused the emotional entanglement
with you to surge ♫
♫ The warmth in the rough birch disturbs the stars  ♫
♫ The art of healing become edges used
to guard the mountains and rivers ♫
♫ Hurt and hatred have not taken over ♫
♫ Unwilling to let so much hatred be in this chaotic world,
a heart of sincerity in exchange for eternity ♫
♫ Journeying together, waiting for some prosperity ♫
♫ Rewrite this life because looking back, the heart aches ♫
♫ For the rest of this life, running in the field with you
without any regards, waiting for dawn ♫
♫ Dawn... ♫
[Jun Jiu Ling]
[Episode 11]
Who on earth did all this?
It looks like we're about to find out.
Li Changhong became an advanced scholar at the age of 20.
Successively, he became the registrar of Luting,
martial officer of Taizhou, local Magistrate of Qingyang, local Magistrate of Anyang,
vice magistrate of Weihui and, now, local Magistrate of Zezhou.
Every post he held is near Zezhou.
If that is the case, he may have had his eyes set on our family 20 years ago.
I do not understand. Our family just does business.
What is worth him plotting for so long?
It was all about money. He coveted the Fang family's wealth.
Did he plot for twenty years just for our money?
Besides, our family had not built up a family fortune 20 years ago.
Zhenzhen, why did you change your name to Jiuling?
I remember now.
Jiuling is the name of the princess of the late emperor.
She was the late wife of Martial Moral Envoy Lu.
No wonder this name sounds familiar.
Zhenzhen knew Princess Jiuling. I believe she did it in memory of her.
Both of Zhenzhen and Princess Jiuling's parents passed away.
Princess Jiuling got married but didn't live long.
Zhenzhen got engaged but was rejected.
They're different, Grandmother.
Even though Zhenzhen isn't a princess,
I think she is living much better than a princess.
At least she's still alive.
Grandmother, you two may go home first.
I need to go out to do something.
We're almost home.
Go after the welcoming banquet.
I'll definitely come back before the welcoming banquet.
Yuan Bao?
Isn't that Miss Jun?
Keep quiet.
- What are we doing?
- Stay put. Don't move.
Grandmother, Chengyu has come home safely .
It also seems that Elder Sister knows of nothing.
She has nothing to do with what Madam Su did.
Keeping her locked up like this, with her personality,
I'm afraid that she won't be able to take it any longer.
Grandmother. Mother.
Considering she's a descendant of the Fang family,
please show some mercy.
Grandmother, I think Second Sister is right.
Let bygones be bygones.
Eldest Sister is not at fault. She should not be implicated.
Furthermore, I am standing here, perfectly well.
Jinxiu is bad-tempered and arrogant.
Actually, I had locked her up for her sake.
It's to prevent her from hearing rumors
and torturing herself every day.
Grandmother, I have an idea.
Maybe it'll work.
Elder Sister. Elder Sister.
It's me.
Chengyu?
- Chengyu?
- It's me.
- Can you really walk now?
- Yes, I've recovered.
- Does it hurt?
- It doesn't hurt anymore.
This is great!
By the way, on my way back,
I bought you a lot of toys.
Look. This little doll.
Look. Do you remember this?
Turns out you have gifts for me, too.
Of course, I have gifts for you.
What's wrong? What's wrong?
I don't think I'm qualified to call you my young brother now.
Nonsense. We all believe you.
I know you're innocent.
It's not about who believes me.
It's that I'm born with sins.
My birth...
was just her reason to stay in the Fang family.
Other than that,
I have no other use.
Believe me. None of us blames it on you or complains about you.
It is just that everything happened so suddenly.
We did not know how to deal with it all.
Yes, she gave birth to you.
But you have nothing to do with her now. You are you.
Also, since you were born,
you've been an independent individual.
Even if others murder people, ignite fires, and commit crimes,
as long as you didn't do any of those things, it has nothing to do with you.
Really?
Also, I have such a great sister
who knows how to read books, write characters,
look at accounting records, count rods,
and even deal with merchants.
You're smart and skillful.
You're my great sister, and you're forever my sister.
There are many things you may find difficult at the moment,
but they'll get better over time.
Look at me. Look.
I've recovered, haven't I?
Younger Brother.
- I want to leave the Fang family.
- Leave?
I'll no longer be the Eldest Young Miss of the Fang family, but Fang Jinxiu.
I'll start a new life as Fang Jinxiu.
Everything is fine now.
It has all passed now.
Enough.
[Fang Residence]
Eldest Sister, take good care of yourself after you leave here.
Rest assured. It is I, why would you worry?
It's just that from now on,
you need to take on more responsibilities for the family.
It's my duty.
I am leaving now.
Grandmother. Mother. Rest assured.
Elder Sister is very capable.
Let her do as she wishes
so she'll feel more at ease.
It'll be good for her to gain more experience and learn endurance.
We'll see when she is willing to come back.
Old Madam!
Old Madam, Miss is gone.
I looked for her everywhere but couldn't find her.
Don't cry. Hurry and tell us.
Did Li Changhong die?
It was done neatly. Nobody will find anything suspicious.
Are the men ready?
They should be here soon.
I have followed your orders and called them here from afar.
Everything was done very covertly.
Good.
This time, the people of the Fang family
shall be uprooted and eliminated.
Where's my hot water? So slow!
I apologize for the delay in the hot water.
You. What are you looking at?
I asked for this hot water first.
Is there more hot water?
Yes, yes. I'll deliver it to you later.
Deliver it in to the room for me.
Yes.
My Lord, she must have just been passing by
to deliver hot water to the other room.
This strange place.
Why do I keep feeling like something is not right?
Go. Ask the people working at this post house
- and confirm things.
- Yes.
Officer, all the hired hands of the kitchen are here.
Does a young lady work here at the post house?
Except for her, all the servants here are male.
Not good.
My Lord, they escaped.
- After them!
- Yes.
How do you know Yuan Bao, and why were you following him?
I don't have time to explain now. I will tell you later.
If it were an ordinary person, then he would have been deceived and this would be over with.
However, Yuan Bao is different. Firstly, he is skilled in martial arts;
and secondly, he has an imperial edict with him at all times. Guards from the Martial Moral Ministry are bound to be protecting him.
Then, what should we do?
Create chaos and scatter the troops.
- You return to Zezhou as quickly as possible.
- What about you?
I have my own way.
Miss Jun, remember this. You owe me an explanation.
Zhu Zan!
What do we do?
It's been a whole night and we still have not found her.
Old Madam, what should we do?
Any news after reporting it to the local court?
The officials are helping to find her but they say she may have lost her way.
This is not a very serious matter and said...
- What did they say?
- They said that we are mobilizing so many people,
as if bandits are causing chaos
and wanting to upheave the city.
Old Madam, please think of a way to
find my lady.
I beg you.
For Jiuling, even if we upheave this city,
it's fine by me.
Bring me my cane.
Lord Magistrate, we have already informed you of all the clues we have gathered.
My Lord, please send men to search for her immediately.
The Fang family will certainly engrave your benevolence and favor in our hearts.
Say, Young Master Fang, there is no need for you to be so worried.
Young Mistress has only been away from home for a short period of time.
Rest assured. She will surely return home safely.
Should anything happen to Jiuling,
I, as her grandmother, will not be able to escape censure.
I must find her even if I have to turn this city upside down.
Lord Liu, please send men to look for her immediately.
Old Madam Fang, how serious can this be?
She hasn't been home for only a day.
Is it truly necessary to overturn the heavens?
(T/N: Idiom – to cause a huge fuss)
My granddaughter-in-law is our family's "Heaven".
Should anything happen to her, then the Fang family's "Heaven" will collapse.
Old Madam Fang, I'm begging you. I'm begging all of you from the Fang family.
Can you not make such a fuss?
"Setting your eyes on this written order is akin to seeing the prince in person. I exhort you to do your duty".
Old Madam Fang, may I see it?
"Setting your eyes on this written order is akin to seeing the prince in person. I exhort you to do your duty. – Chu Rang"
This humble subject apologizes for the offense!
This written order was given to my Fang Family when His Majesty was still a prince.
Now, he has succeeded to the throne and become the emperor.
Lord Liu, dare I ask if this written order is valid in your eyes?
It is valid, it is certainly valid!
"Setting your eyes on this written order is akin to seeing the prince in person. I exhort you to do your duty. – Chu Rang"
Lord Liu, please assist our family
in searching for our Young Mistress, Jun Jiuling.
This subject will obey the order!
I will take my leave now.
All of you, don't just stand here! Go and look for her!
Yes!
Grandmother, this written order...
I have already done all I can.
[Local Magistrate's Office of Zezhou]
You men head west of the city.
- You men...
- Grandmother.
...head east of the city.
-- Yes!
Set off!
Miss! You've returned!
Are you all right? The Old Madam sent us to look for you all night long.
- Grandmother.
- Where have you been all night?
I went to pick some medicinal herbs.
You...
You are so senseless.
Grandmother, it's great that Jiuling has returned safely.
She went to pick those medicinal herbs for my sake.
Look at yourself. You're no longer a child,
so why are you still so rash and careless?
You stayed out all night picking medicinal herbs.
Shouldn't you have informed your family members beforehand?
I was careless.
I did not keep the time in mind and caused you to worry, Grandmother.
Miss Jun isn't a physician,
- so why did she go to the mountains to pick medicinal herbs?
- Exactly.
Jiuling is a physician.
My legs were cured by her.
The Jun family is a family of physicians and she has inherited the responsibilities of her family.
It looks like His Majesty's written order
was presented at such an opportune moment.
What written order?
Grandmother, everything is fine now that she has returned safely.
Let's go home.
Jun Jiuling, your actions this time are very inappropriate.
- Grandmother, Jiuling–
- Chengyu,
don't talk back to your grandmother.
I did not think things through and have caused you to worry, Grandmother.
Grandmother, I have something...
All of you may go.
Yes.
Jiuling, stay behind.
The written order...
As for the written order, all you need to know is that it is real.
However, I have sworn not to tell anyone
the origins of the written order.
What I don't understand is why you would bring out the written order at this time.
When Father was in trouble, you did not bring out the written order.
When My Lord was in trouble, you did not bring out the written order either.
At the time, I did not know they were harmed by evildoers.
Grandmother was afraid I would be harmed by evildoers.
Then, why did you bring it out now?
Very simple. She can cure Chengyu's illness.
Our family is in debt to her.
Thank you, Grandmother.
Grandmother, I want to
ask you something.
I will leave now.
- Mother.
- Mother, how is Grandmother?
Don't worry. She is no longer upset.
It's good that she isn't angry anymore.
I know that she can make everyone like her.
Of course.
Mother, since we didn't have the welcoming banquet yesterday, why don't we have a grander lunch today?
We'll celebrate today.
- Shaoyao, let everyone know.
- Yes.
Hold on. Warm up a pot of wine as well
since Jiuling is back safely.
Mother, I'll go get ready now.
Go ahead.
It's true that a man forgets about his mother after marrying a woman.
I didn't expect this day would come for me.
Mother, I'm not that kind of person.
Mother, before, you had suffered because of me.
Grandmother, I was delayed in my return to the city
because yesterday
I saw someone I shouldn't have seen on the streets.
- Who?
- A eunuch.
- Eunuch?
- Yes.
Eunuchs can't exit the palace casually.
Maybe you were mistaken.
I saw him before when I went to the palace with my father. There is no way I was mistaken.
Eunuchs cannot exit the palace on their own accord.
But what if they are under orders?
Even if it's true, it's nothing serious.
Our Fang family has His Majesty's written order.
It makes perfect sense for His Majesty to send his attendant here.
Grandmother,
one should not have intentions to harm others
but should have intentions to protect oneself.
In regards to all the things of this world, one cannot possibly be fully prepared
and there are no promises that cannot be changed.
That is the delight of living,
competing against Heaven and Earth.
Will you continue to deceive yourself even now?
You're well aware that His Majesty sent him here
not only to keep an eye on the Fang family,
but also to get rid of the Fang family.
I personally heard from the eunuch that His Majesty is acting against the Fang family.
To be frank, I've seen the seal in your casket.
It is related to the silver transported during the third year of Taiyan, right?
- How do you know that?
- If my guess is correct,
that batch of official silver
was never handed over to Northern Qi.
Back then, Chu Rang was still a vassal prince and Zezhou was his territory.
That batch of official silver passed through here on its way to Northern Qi.
However, Chu Rang did something in the midst of the transport.
Chu Rang delivered that batch of official silver to the Fang family
and it was the capital used to start the family business.
Later on, the Fang family recruited people for Chu Rang's army and made money for him.
However, as for his father and brothers kidnapped by Northern Qi,
he did not care about their lives at all.
The fewer people in his way, the better.
No, no.
Back then, our Fang family was confused and made a huge mistake.
We also got the punishment we deserved.
Chengyu's father and grandfather
died because of this.
Why? Why won't they let us go?
Why?
Grandmother,
have you never thought
that he's the one who has been harming the Fang family all these years?
I've suspected that,
but I had no evidence.
Chu Rang knows our Fang family still has the written order.
He won't harm us.
He won't harm our Fang family. He won't. He won't.
He won't harm our Fang family!
He won't. He won't.
Grandmother, to the Fang family,
the written order is no longer an assurance.
Our priority now should actually be resolving the problems that the written order brings with it.
We can no longer hide the Fang family's identity as an imperial merchant.
Firstly, everyone in Zezhou knows that you have brought out the written order,
which will surely fuel speculation.
Secondly, Chu Rang will definitely become suspicious after learning about that.
Who knows what he'll do next?
What should we do then?
In regards to hiding the official silver during the third year of Tiayan
and the identity of our family as an imperial merchant, let the public know.
Don't worry. I'll have someone arrange everything.
The farther it spreads, the better.
That way, Chu Rang surely will not dare make any rash moves.
Perhaps the Fang family can avoid being eliminated.
All right.
This is our Fang family's last resort
to get out of danger.
We'll listen to you.
I know how serious this matter is.
Nobody in the Fang family will know about it except you and me.
Rest assured.
Jiuling, our Fang family
has hope now.
She should be done talking to Grandmother now, right?
I'll go see her. She hasn't eaten all night.
She must be hungry.
Chengyu,
I need to tell you something.
What is it?
The marriage between you and Jiuling is fake.
Mother, don't say such lies.
It's true, Chengyu. In order to cure your illness without others noticing,
we let you two get married in the name of bringing good fortune.
Then why...
did she never tell me that?
She had to go through with it.
It would be unfair for her to be one to tell you, too.
So, because my legs are cured and she wants to leave,
you are allowed to tell me all this. Right?
No, Chengyu. It is not what you think.
I thought that since my legs are cured
and I can stand now, then I can be with her.
Turns out everything is fake.
Of course not. Your legs are cured and you can walk now.
All that is real.
I'd rather I not be cured.
Don't say such things out of anger, Chengyu.
Jiuling doesn't want to see you like this either.
You are an intelligent child.
Jiuling doesn't have romantic feelings for you.
You should know that in your heart.
You are a man.
You should be able to let go of things.
If something should be broken, then let it break. If something should be let go of, then let it go.
Mother, in regards to this matter,
we owe Jiuling an explanation.
We got married, bowed to Heaven and Earth, and offered sacrifices to the gods.
We even held a wedding banquet and invited everyone from the city to attend.
This matter cannot be fake just because we say so.
That is unfair to Jiuling.
Then, what you mean is to give her a divorce letter?
Not only that,
but I want everyone in the city
as well as Heaven, Earth, and the gods to know about it.
Only in this way will we be fair to Jiuling.
Because of me, she lied to Heaven and Earth, lied to the gods, and lied to everyone in the city.
Then I should tell Heaven, Earth, the gods, and everyone in the city
what a good person Jun Jiuling is
and what meritorious deeds she has done.
My Chengyu has grown up.
Miss.
- Are you all right?
- Yes.
Are you done packing?
You can finally go to the capital to fulfill your wish.
Yes. I have wanted to go this whole time, and now, I can finally go.
However, I am still quite reluctant to leave.
Could it be that you'll miss Young Master?
What are you thinking of? I have always treated Chengyu as my younger cousin.
So, that's how it is.
Besides, the Fang family has always treated us well. Right?
Cousin.
- Chengyu.
- Young Master.
Miss, this is the first time I heard Young Master call you "cousin".
What is your reason for coming today?
There is something I want to talk to you about.
Go ahead.
I believe you will need this.
[Divorce Letter]
A divorce letter.
Thank you, Cousin, for protecting our Fang family.
There's no need for you to be so polite.
We are a family and don't need to be so polite with each other.
Cousin, are you leaving tomorrow?
Yes. Let's go outside for a stroll.
All right.
It is a long journey. You must be careful and take care of yourself.
I am not alone. I am taking Liu'er with me.
Then you have to look after Liu'er, too. Even more of a reason for you to take care of yourself.
Cousin, if you encounter any problems, just go to our store directly.
De Shengchang has branches located within the capital.
I'll coordinate things with them.
All right.
You came to see me today
because you're afraid I'll leave without saying goodbye. Right?
I was planning to go see you after packing everything up.
I didn't expect you to come to me first.
Then, can I ask you a question?
Go on.
Will you come back?
Why wouldn't I come back?
This is my home.
I will return after settling my matters.
"The swordsmen have been around for some time."
(T/N: a Chinese legend about swordsmen)
"Wei Niang is discussed as unique."
Everyone knows that those who do good are blessed.
She is not considered an outstanding lady.
All of you are familiar with the unique lady I am talking about.
Well-known in Zezhou, she is Miss Jun.
If I'm going to talk about why and how Miss Jun is unusual,
then I'll have to start from the very beginning, far back in time.
No need to discuss her breaking the engagement with Young Master Ning,
being in the limelight at Jinyun Restaurant,
nor finally marrying Young Master Fang.
This was all arranged by Miss Jun right from the beginning.
Everyone, be patient.
Let me tell the story slowly.
All this starts from Miss Jun's origins.
You only know that Miss Jun is the Fang family's granddaughter.
However, do you know that her Jun family is a family of physicians
who have passed down their skills for over 100 years?
Her father, Jun Yingwen, was a famous physician in Ru'nan.
Even if she hid away in her bedroom, she was already too entrenched in her family's medical teachings.
She is the successor of her family legacy as Ru'nan miraculous physician,
Jun Jiuling!
"Sound of Rain" - Composers: He Huihui/Wang Zitong - Lyricists: Liao Yu/He Huihui
♫ The outline of my dream is carved on your face ♫
♫ Times interlace in the watery eyes ♫
♫ Allow me to weigh every word for indescribable
cause and effect ♫
♫ Life is full of ups and downs and hard to be free ♫
♫ With many tomorrows to come,
I’m willing to entrust my whole life to you ♫
♫ And see the starry night, mountains and rivers together ♫
♫ In the long silence, we are separated by a huge crowd ♫
♫ I can only sigh deeply. The rest of my life is bumpy ♫
♫ The vast sky is you and the wind is me ♫
♫ I’ll eventually be passed by ♫
♫ The wind is in hot pursuit and locked in deadlock with the sky ♫
♫ If memories could speak ♫
♫ I wouldn’t stop shedding tears like the rain ♫
♫ It’s hard to see you again. I’m wailing in deep sorrow ♫
♫ With many tomorrows to come,
I’m willing to entrust my whole life to you ♫
♫ And see the starry night, mountains and rivers together ♫
♫ In the long silence, we are separated by a huge crowd ♫
♫ I can only sigh deeply. The rest of my life is bumpy ♫
♫ The vast sky is you and the wind is me ♫
♫ I’m destined to be passed by ♫
♫ The wind is in hot pursuit and locked
in a deadlock with the sky ♫
♫ If memories could speak ♫
♫ I wouldn’t stop shedding tears like the rain ♫
♫ It’s hard to see you again. I’m wailing in deep sorrow ♫
♫ The vast sky is you and the wind is me ♫
♫ Going through the bottom of my heart ♫
♫ Has God ever asked for clues about the wind? ♫
♫ If I could write down how much I miss you ♫
♫ It would drift like the rain  ♫
♫ Seeing you again as if we’re strangers,
I’m wailing in deep sorrow ♫