Jun Jiu Ling - Deng Yujun
♫ Sighing at how fleeting life is, the swords tell of the scars ♫
♫ After our meeting, I'm unwilling to separate ♫
♫ Journeying alone and cold,
the past is a secret guarded closely ♫
♫ Hide the love and hate of tonight, stow away the naivety ♫
♫ Meeting an old friend,
we look at each other as the memories emerge ♫
♫ Only daring to show a bit of gentleness in dreams ♫
♫ This kiss caused the emotional entanglement
with you to surge ♫
♫ The warmth in the rough birch disturbs the stars  ♫
♫ The art of healing become edges used
to guard the mountains and rivers ♫
♫ Hurt and hatred have not taken over ♫
♫ Unwilling to let so much hatred be in this chaotic world,
a heart of sincerity in exchange for eternity ♫
♫ Journeying together, waiting for some prosperity ♫
♫ Rewrite this life because looking back, the heart aches ♫
♫ For the rest of this life, running in the field with you
without any regard, waiting for dawn ♫
♫ Dawn... ♫
[Jun Jiu Ling]
[Episode 37]
What's the status of the task I handed over to you?
Due to the division of De Shengchang, Jun Jiuling has returned to Zezhou.
I have ordered Jin Shiba to go there.
The Fang family has failed and the Zhu family has collapsed.
This is a good opportunity.
We can't miss out on it anymore.
Yes.
Absolutely right.
The other places need to be monitored tightly.
Understood!
Greetings, Marquis Qinghe.
Since General Wei is here, tell him to go to the Yongjing Army.
- Lead your subordinates to Jiaohe.
- Understood.
My Lord, we have been deploying our soldiers frequently.
I think if we place our troops on defense on such a large scale,
we may provide Northern Qi with an opportunity.
General Wei, are you implying that Marquis Qinghe's defense is not comparable to Duke Cheng's arrangement?
This is not what I meant.
Are you implying...
you are reluctant to be deployed?
My Lord, it's not that I'm reluctant to be deployed.
It's just that your deployment doesn't seem to be for defense. It's more for...
disarming and dividing the power of the army.
This...
My Lord, this is a taboo for the direct line of descendants of Duke Cheng.
I can understand that you are suppressing me,
but the people in Northern Qi are eyeing us covetously. We must not panic.
Arrest him.
Sir!
General Wei, do you know...
why Duke Cheng escaped from the capital?
Because he knows that the North is his kingdom.
Just because you are here,
he's convinced that he can definitely seek shelter here.
No. We are officials and soldiers of Tianyou.
If Duke Cheng is guilty, we will never protect each other.
Many officials and soldiers in the North were once under Duke Cheng.
- Enough!
- Let's go!
- My Lord.
- Let's go now.
- Let's go.
- My Lord!
Looks like as long as Zhu Shan doesn't fall into our net,
there won't be any peace in the North.
Who else doesn't want to obey military orders?
His Majesty has declared to the kingdom that
we have been convicted of treason.
Whoever sees us, can behead us in public.
In the future, every province
and city will be difficult for us to pass through.
No matter how difficult it was, we were fearless.
As long as the family was together, we could cross any hurdles.
However, this time, we have implicated Miss Jun.
That's right.
We should have resolved their marriage agreement earlier.
We dragged her into this.
Father. Mother. Don't blame yourselves.
Who can foresee the future?
Besides, she's a country princess
and a miracle physician. She will avert disaster, right?
I hope so.
Your Majesty, Marquis Qinghe replaced his defense without authority.
Crown Prince Yu Chihai of Northern Qi led his army to conduct a sudden assault and seized the opportunity.
Marquis Qinghe has fallen under the siege of Northern Qi's army. We lost news about him.
Half of the previously arranged reinforcements
can't be accounted for.
What's happening?
How can this happen?
I don't want to know why they went back against their words.
I also don't want to know who committed the mistake.
I only want to know if they can be stopped.
The Northern Army has been divided among three routes to intercept the Northern Qi troops.
In addition, the commanders of Shandong and Shanxi rushed to help.
The two armies are in Hebei. We must totally wipe them out.
That's to say, we still didn't stop them.
A bunch of useless creatures!
Your Majesty, don't be angry!
My Lord, go in and take a break.
- How long has it been?
- Six days.
Based on the pre-deployment, the reinforcements should have been here earlier.
What do you mean? Speak now.
My Lord, we just received news that
our troops along the three routes absconded.
What?
These bunch of scoundrels. How many absconded?
Ten thousand from the east route, twenty thousand from the west route,
the south route... twenty thousand from the south route, too.
- A total of 100,000 reinforcements from those three routes and we are down by half. How can we fight?
- That's right.
When did those officials and soldiers in the North turn into such cowards?
They are not cowards.
Even if they wanted to abscond, it can't be that many at once.
I fear they followed another military order.
- Duke Cheng?
- That's right.
The only one who can make them so bold is Duke Cheng.
Yes, it's Duke Cheng.
Zhu Shan,
are you trying to kill us?
Duke Cheng, excluding the 30,000 soldiers and horses who are rushing to the capital,
there are still 20,000 waiting for your instructions
to rob the rations of the Northern Qi's army. We will meet up tonight.
Excellent. After we have assembled,
rescue Marquis Qinghe immediately
Understood.
It hasn't been easy for him to stand firm and defend for so long.
Will he convict you of privately deploying the troops?
So be it. I did the same, too.
Duke Cheng, you did this
because Marquis Qinghe deployed his troops without authorization to create disaster.
Without your deployment, we would have lost the state war earlier.
But is he willing to learn from this lesson?
Father, we can give them a taste of their own medicine.
Zan'er, explain.
Northern Qi is doing its best to raise the power of their country.
They will definitely want to smash our line of defense.
There must be some internal void in their defense troops that is not that tight.
I want to penetrate into the enemy's territory to assassinate the emperor of Northern Qi,
to solve our situation.
No. It's too risky for you to go alone.
Father, we can't hesitate anymore.
This is our only strategy now.
Duke Cheng, I'm willing to go with Heir Apparent.
Duke Cheng. Madam. We will protect Second Brother and bring him home safely.
We escaped death under the hands of His Majesty. Would we still fear that we won't succeed with the emperor of Northern Qi?
Father, I have been with you in the army since childhood.
I know what I should do and shouldn't do. I won't be reckless.
Zan'er.
All right, but you must come back safe and sound.
Zan'er,
promise me. Regardless if you succeed or not,
you must come home safe and sound.
All right. Don't worry.
Father. Mother. I'm not filial for going ahead first.
Father. Mother. Take care.
Son.
Father, I'm leaving.
You must come back safe and sound.
Don't worry.
Zan'er has fought with me since childhood. I believe he will come back safe and sound.
If he succeeds in the assassination,
I will rush back to the capital and you will remain in the North.
If it's the will of Heaven,
we will meet again in the North.
For decades, we have
supported each other and have been united as one.
If you are really afraid that I will worry,
you and Zan'er must survive.
I promise you.
Zhu Zan, are you doing well in the North?
Jiuling, are you doing well in the capital?
I know it's extremely dangerous for me to go and I may not be able to return. But with you here,
I will hang in there and come back to see you.
Wait for me, Jiuling. Wait for me.
My Lord, from my observation, the encirclement in the West is weak. Why don't I wait
to escort you out from the siege? Where there is life, there's hope.
I'm willing to remain here to resist the enemy, fight through the siege for you and take revenge.
Absurd. When have I ever escaped when the enemy was in front of me?
My Lord, you are not fleeing from the battle. It's not worth it for you to die this way.
That's right, My Lord. It's not worth it.
My Lord, think carefully again before taking action.
- My Lord, leave now...
- Enough!
It's important to fight a defensive battle without a break.
If we break through the siege and this leaks out,
my army will immediately be defeated and scattered. Everyone will abscond.
When that time comes,
the army of Northern Qi will advance here without stopping and head straight to the capital.
Have you thought of this aftermath?
The enemy is powerful.
I only need to stay calm and hold on to the camp. Compared to escaping to the wilderness,
there are more hopes for survival.
When the reinforcements are here, we can do a flank attack
and fight our way out.
- Yes!
Report!
My Lord, the reinforcements... the reinforcements are here.
Great.
My Lord, the reinforcements are late and caused you to be stranded by the siege.
Zhu Shan, do you think you can earn merits to redeem your crime by doing this?
You privately deployed officials and soldiers and placed me in danger.
You detachedly watched our battle with the Northern Qi's army.
You waited till both parties were exhausted and suddenly fell from the sky.
Is this how you earned your heroic and reputable name?
My Lord, it's not like this.
Duke Cheng deployed us because he guessed the plot of Northern Qi.
That's why we led soldiers to Mount Song to rob the rations of the Northern Qi's army.
Duke Cheng intercepted the reinforcements in the north wing.
Duke Cheng instructed us to attack Northern Qi in the right wing.
My Lord, we were blocked and attacked by Northern Qi and couldn't advance or retreat. Duke Cheng rescued us.
Get up.
So, you already guessed the plot of the Northern Qi's army in advance.
So, to say, you guessed that I would be ambushed by the Northern Qi's army?
Yes, I did.
- Why didn't you mention this to me...
- Sir,
now's not the time to argue about this. The top priority now is to rush to rescue the capital.
Rush to rescue the capital?
How can this be?
Is Northern Qi attacking the capital?
The 60,000 cavalries of Northern Qi have already arrived at the east of the capital.
What?
We are doomed. So, the goal of Northern Qi
was not the northern territory but the capital instead.
60,000 cavalries? The capital is doomed.
It will not be the end of the capital.
When you were stranded by the siege,
I already instructed the soldiers and horses at Suning Pass to head to the capital.
I'm worried there's insufficient time.
The only hope now is that
they can hold on till our reinforcement arrives.
What has the military defense been doing?
Why did they allow the commander of Northern Qi's army to ride to the South?
Your Majesty, after we lost communication with Marquis Qinghe,
it has been difficult to grasp news from the frontline.
Your Majesty, please order the troops from the eastern route to resist the enemy and defend themselves till death.
Permission given. Include the troops from the western route to form an overall defense.
Understood.
Is there any reply from the Northern Qi's envoy?
We sent them letters but there were no replies.
Your Majesty, I'm willing to go to Northern Qi to negotiate with them.
I will wait for your good news.
I will do my best.
Your Majesty, the North can't be without a general for a day. Please give Duke Cheng a chance.
Are you telling me to hand over the army in the North to a criminal who's convicted of treason?
And then, wait for him to head south with the iron cavalry of Northern Qi
to engulf the capital?
Your Majesty, Duke Cheng is not this kind of person.
I believe there's a misunderstanding.
This means I'm wrong.
Of course, Your Majesty is not wrong.
The one who's wrong is Duke Cheng who committed treason
and Lord Ning who made a verbal mistake.
Uncle.
Move aside.
What happened?
Lord, the army from Northern Qi is here.
We couldn't resist the enemy along the eastern and western routes to the capital. We were ambushed.
Lord Lu,
the army from Northern Qi is here.
Leave now.
What are you doing?
Come with me! They are about to invade the capital.
Northern Qi fought their way in?
It's said that the spy bribed the officials and soldiers
to open the gate of Baimang City. In order to cover up his crime, Marquis Qinghe
intends to frame Duke Cheng.
Come! If we don't go now, it'll be too late.
Wait, wait! I can't go.
You don't know how critical the situation is now?
Northern Qi planned and deployed all their garrisons.
The eastern route to the capital is now empty and defenseless. Lord Han has sent the troops there.
However, breaking into the city is only a matter of time.
The capital's defense is still stable.
Besides, it's guarded by the Forbidden Army. We won't have any problems.
We cannot wait!
Your Majesty is leaving!
Chu Rang is leaving?
Once the emperor is gone, the people will naturally be demoralized.
The city cannot be defended anymore.
That is why I want you to leave now!
Only when you are at my side, will you be safe.
What are you hesitating for? Leave!
Today you have to leave whether you want to or not!
Lu Yunqi!
I want to defend Imperial Father's country.
At that time, Imperial Father swore in Qingshan that
he would protect the country's prosperity and the well-being of the people.
Royal Father has passed away but I can't forget his oath.
Jiuling...
you finally admitted it. At that time in prison, I already wanted to leave with you.
But I missed it.
This time, I won't miss it.
So you leave with me, please?
Like protecting Jiuli and Jiurong
I bore the infamy of everyone
to marry Princess Jiuli so that I could be beside them to guard them,
in order to protect them fully. I'm sitting in a high position in the civil service system.
Only this way can I then guard the important people.
I know, everyone is scolding me, saying that I'm evil.
I don't mind it. I don't care when people say I'm a lackey.
What I, Lu Yunqi, care about
is what everything you, Chu Jiuling, care about.
Leave, please?
There's no time left. Leave.
Lu Yunqi,
humans throughout their lives not only need to live with life and death,
but also need to understand right from wrong.
What I need is never to peacefully survive.
Follow Imperial Father's ambition, follow Imperial Father's boldness,
protect the safety of the common people. Even if I sacrifice my life, I will not hesitate.
This is my choice, and also the life that I want.
Tianyou is unstable and in a dangerous situation now. How can I be righteous without caring for others?
Guarding the well-being of the common people is my responsibility, I cannot retreat for even half a step.
If you really want to help me, then please let me fulfill it.
I may be wrong.
Initially I thought only when I was by your side,
you would be very safe.
Jiuling,
you must promise me, to live your life well.
I will help you take good care of Jiuli and Jiurong.
The mistakes that I, Lu Yunqi, made originally,
I admit. But I will never make the same mistakes again.
I know what to do in the future.
Your Excellency, there's really no more time.
Second Brother, I personally feel that maybe—
- Is there news?
- Yes, I verified it. The Emperor of Northern Qi will go to the border tomorrow to reward the army.
We have a chance.
However, it's heavily guarded and it's in broad daylight. It won't be easy for us to take action.
So we can't have too many people; otherwise, it will be easy to be exposed. Is there news from the capital?
The capital's east and west roads cannot hold on anymore, soldiers from Northern Qi are nearing the capital.
Tomorrow, we must be successful. Go and find a path.
Jiuling, wait for me.
Such a big thing like a siege from Northern Qi,
the imperial court is still hiding it from everyone.
Incapable ruler. Only cared about escaping swiftly himself,
he didn't even give a chance for the common people to guard the city and escape.
Northern Qi is invading soon, do you know?
Are you crazy?
Northern Qi is invading soon, do you know!
What nonsense are you talking about?
Quick, quick!
Dimwit!
You don't want your life?
I deserve to die! I deserve to die!
Eunuch Yuan.
Your Majesty asked you to go over.
Yes.
Eunuch Yuan, rest assured, I will take care of things for you here.
Many thanks, Lord Ning.
Be more efficient. Pick up and take things securely.
Lord Ning.
Lord Lu.
It's time to set off.
Yes.
Take these also.
Is everything ready?
Your Majesty, we can leave anytime.
- Was the news ever leaked?
- No.
Your Majesty, but the capital has so many people.
Can't look after it anymore. Quickly leave.
The amount of population left in this capital.
In your eyes, is it an empty city?
Jinxiu! Jinxiu!
- Jiuling! Jiuling! You're finally back!
- Where is everyone else?
Jiuling is back! Jiuling is back!
Miss is back!
Miss, you're finally back!
You're finally back. Where did you go?
I have no time to explain. The Northern Qi army is going to break in.
This... How did this happen?
The east and west paths of the capital have already been breached.
The latest would be tomorrow. Tomorrow, the Northern Qi army will reach the capital's borders
and attack the capital city.
But there hasn't been any activity in the capital. It does not seem like we are preparing for battle!
This is because Chu Rang has run off. He took his trusted men and secretly left the capital.
He is basically giving the capital away. He doesn't want the city or the people.
How could he be like that?
How is he fit to sit on the throne?
What a useless king!
Now all the citizens are unaware of this. What should we do?
Who in the capital now is capable of taking charge?
Such a useless king, a coward!
Should we go and inform everyone first?
What should we do, Miss?
I'll look for Prince Xian.
Jinxiu. Shopkeeper Liu. Go and get all of De Shengchang's excess cash.
- Think of a way to purchase all the weapons in the city.
- Yes!
Chen Qi, you will be in charge of distributing the weapons.
Also, go and get other materials that can be used to make weapons, too.
- Leave it to me.
- Miss, what about me?
Liu'er, use the name of Jiuling Hall and buy rations from all the city businesses. You have to be done before tonight.
In case a war really breaks out, the prices of all these resources will rise and the citizens will be left with nothing.
I understand, Miss.
Now that the capital is in danger, I can only rely on all of you.
We will live and die together. Show no fear and no retreat!
Show no fear and no retreat!
- Hurry and go!
- Yes!
Let's go, hurry!
Is this true?
The news cannot be hidden for too long. At most by tomorrow morning,
everyone in the capital will definitely know that His Majesty has already abandoned the city.
So, in other words, we only have tonight to prepare?
- Yes.
- In the city, the number of guards and horses
only number by the thousands. While outside there will be an army with tens of thousands.
How will we be able to block this?
Your Highness, don't forget that there are still tens of thousands of citizens in the city.
They share the same fate of life and death. Everyone can fight together.
Furthermore...
Furthermore, once the Northern army arrives we could have a chance of survival.
But the problem is, without His Majesty's command token,
the soldiers from the five counties may not listen to us.
Right now, whether they want to or not, they will have to obey. You need to display your strongest attitude to face them.
Your Highness, right now in the city only you are able to take charge.
The lives of over ten thousand citizens rest in your hands.
I believe as long as you are willing to lead, things will be as you said before.
Once the Northern Qi army is beaten, the lives of our citizens will be saved.
How would you know what I have said before?
Imperial Uncle, this is because I am Jiuling.
Chu Jiuling.
You are Jiuling?
- You didn't die?
- Yes.
I didn't die in the fire. I'm still alive.
But your appearance–
Imperial Uncle, I will definitely explain it to you in the future.
Right now, you need to get a handle on things!
Royal Uncle!
Do you remember the osmanthus cakes from Yushan Restaurant?
In the past, on my birthday every year,
you and Imperial Father would make it for me.
You are really Jiuling.
Jiuling, you must know that the most important things in leading an army to battle are
firstly, weapons. Secondly, rations.
I know. Rest assured on these two fronts.
I have already asked Jiuling Hall and De Shengchang to settle this.
If you were a boy,
you would definitely be a hero who can protect the country.
Let's do this, Jiuling.
I will go and mobilize the soldiers from the five counties.
If they insist on not obeying, I will mobilize my personal guards.
They will go to each city gate. I shall see who dares to open the city gates!
All right. Imperial Uncle, we shall meet at the eastern city gate at the hour of Mao.
(T/N : 5:00 a.m. - 7.00 a.m.)
- Then I will go and prepare.
- All right.
Royal Uncle, do you have news about Heir Apparent?
Ever since he and Duke Cheng escaped the capital,
I have not heard any news from them.
All right, I understand.
Then I shall take my leave.
Floral umbrellas!
Take a look at these floral umbrellas!
This one has a good meaning. Let's take this one.
If you asked me what were the best days of my life,
I would say that they were the days with you.
Me?
When did I become such an important person?
No news... That still counts as good news.
You are so smart. You would definitely not be caught.
Right now, do you know about the Northern Qi army coming to attack the capital?
If you were the one in charge of leading the people here, what would you do?
Zhu Zan...
Why hasn't His Majesty appeared in court?
Bad news! His Majesty is gone!
- His Majesty is gone!
- What?
I searched the entire royal palace, I just cannot find him!
- You checked everywhere?
- I checked everywhere!
Even Third Prince is missing!
We are finished!
Wouldn't that mean the Northern Qi army is going to break in?
Don't be scared. I am under Duke Cheng's orders.
Heir Apparent is injured. Where is Young Master Fang?
Young Master Fang!
Brother-in-law! Brother-in-law!
How did this happen?
Once he learned that our army was in danger, he got injured while trying to assassinate the Northern Qi emperor.
But the wanted order on him wasn't removed so we dared not wander around to find a physician.
Without any other methods, we can only come to Young Master Fang for help.
Santao, bring them in first. I will find a way to get a physician.
Young Master Fang, the physician must be someone reliable. If not, things will be worse.
I understand.
Then you come with me.
Master, what should we do now?
Stop crying and making a fuss.
Prince Xian has already stood out to lead the situation. The capital will not fall into chaos.
You also should not blame Yunzhao for bringing the news late.
It was already difficult for him to save himself.
I watched Yunzhao grow up; of course, I understand his personality.
- But Master, can you not go?
- I have to go.
I didn't go in the past. I received the blessings of others.
I appealed and His Majesty did not listen. I can only persevere till the end!
But even His Majesty has fled!
It is because he has fled!
That I have to go out even more!
For the sake of the right path and the sake of all the lives.
You are one of the common people.
Go and hide well at home with the kids. Don't run around outside.
These few days, the capital cannot fall into chaos.
We are willing to follow Lord to protect the city!
To protect the country is to protect our home!
To protect our home, we all have a duty!
In battle defense, it's most important to defend well. The greatest taboo is to be flustered and make mistakes.
We need to divide tasks immediately and ensure we make the best use of those who have been deployed.
- You know best about the defense layout. I will leave this to you.
- Sure.
- I'll take care of this.
- Select more strong people from the city
to supplement the four gates of the city and the manpower for the walls.
Especially the north gate where the wall is lower.
Northern Qi is most likely to attack the city there.
When that time comes, use the drum as the order for concentrated defense. The drumming and fighting must not stop.
Understood.
Chen Qi, lead the chosen people to De Shengchang to receive the weapons.
Jinxiu. Liu'er. Take charge of organizing the people who are willing to help to ensure the supplies.
- Go now.
- All right.
Prince Xian.
Lord Ning.
I'm ashamed that I was late.
It's not late as long as you are here.
Sounds of Rain - Jiang Long & Yin Luxi
♫ The outline of my dream is carved on your face ♫
♫ Times interlace in the watery eyes ♫
♫ Allow me to weigh every word for indescribable
cause and effect ♫
♫ Life is full of ups and downs and hard to be free ♫
♫ With many tomorrows to come,
I’m willing to entrust my whole life to you ♫
♫ And see the starry night, mountains and rivers together ♫
♫ In the long silence, we are separated by a huge crowd ♫
♫ I can only sigh deeply. The rest of my life is bumpy ♫
♫ The vast sky is you and the wind is me ♫
♫ I’ll eventually be passed by ♫
♫ The wind is in hot pursuit and locked in deadlock with the sky ♫
♫ If memories could speak ♫
♫ I wouldn’t stop shedding tears like the rain ♫
♫ It’s hard to see you again. I’m wailing in deep sorrow ♫
♫ With many tomorrows to come,
I’m willing to entrust my whole life to you ♫
♫ And see the starry night, mountains and rivers together ♫
♫ In the long silence, we are separated by a huge crowd ♫
♫ I can only sigh deeply. The rest of my life is bumpy ♫
♫ The vast sky is you and the wind is me ♫
♫ I’m destined to be passed by ♫
♫ The wind is in hot pursuit and locked in
a deadlock with the sky ♫
♫ If memories could speak ♫
♫ I wouldn’t stop shedding tears like the rain ♫
♫ It’s hard to see you again. I’m wailing in deep sorrow ♫
♫ The vast sky is you and the wind is me ♫
♫ Going through the bottom of my heart ♫
♫ Has God ever asked for clues about the wind? ♫
♫ If I could write down how much I miss you ♫
♫ It would drift like the rain  ♫
♫ Seeing you again as if we’re strangers,
I’m wailing in deep sorrow ♫