Opening OST: Jun Jiu Ling - Deng Yujun
♫ Sighing at how fleeting life is, the swords tell of the scars ♫
♫ After our meeting, I'm unwilling to separate ♫
♫ Journeying alone and cold,
the past is a secret guarded closely ♫
♫ Hide the love and hate of tonight, stow away the naivety ♫
♫ Meeting an old friend,
we look at each other as the memories emerge ♫
♫ Only daring to show a bit of gentleness in dreams ♫
♫ This kiss caused the emotional entanglement
with you to surge ♫
♫ The warmth in the rough birch disturbs the stars  ♫
♫ The art of healing become edges used
to guard the mountains and rivers ♫
♫ Hurt and hatred have not taken over ♫
♫ Unwilling to let so much hatred be in this chaotic world,
a heart of sincerity in exchange for eternity ♫
♫ Journeying together, waiting for some prosperity ♫
♫ Rewrite this life because looking back, the heart aches ♫
♫ For the rest of this life, running in the field with you
without any regards, waiting for dawn ♫
♫ Dawn... ♫
[Jun Jiu Ling]
[Episode 30]
Miss.
- There's a letter from the young lord.
- Where is he?
He's heading north. From the look of it, he's moving towards Duke Cheng.
Also, Hejian Prefecture delivered news that the peace treaty has been signed.
The soldiers and horses from Northern Qi will enter the three provinces soon.
All garrisons in the North are to be withdrawn immediately. Any violations of the decree...
will be punished as treason.
Treason?
Isn't this targeting Duke Cheng?
Miss, by the looks of it now,
many people may not be able to evacuate.
So that's what Duke Cheng is doing.
Old Lei and General Li, let's continue north.
But, Miss, based on the map, once we pass three more towns,
we will be able to meet up with the wife of Duke Cheng.
Let's continue north and change our route. Furthermore, secretly inquire the whereabouts of Duke Cheng and his heir apparent along the way.
You're thinking...
I'm thinking we must not disappoint Duke Cheng.
He trapped himself in the North just to buy time to evacuate the people.
But with our limited soldiers and horses, we won't be able to help evacuate the people at all.
- Ensure you have an accurate count of the people. Go on.
- Yes, Sir!
[Benevolent Winds, Auspicious Clouds]
Lord Tian.
Madam Yu.
Most of the people of Bazhou have been brought back.
As of yesterday, 190,000 people have entered Hejian Prefecture.
We are still counting the people you have brought back today.
It has been tough for you. With the influx of so many people, it's a big burden to you.
Our burden is nothing.
Besides, Miss Jun and you have ordered
that we guide and disperse the people in advance so many of them have already gone south.
We can still manage here.
That's good.
Where's Miss Jun now?
Based on the schedule, she should be back.
Yizhou is in the North.
It's most likely that the child went to Yizhou.
Yizhou?
Isn't that the place Duke Cheng is currently trapped at from his surprise attack on the Northern Qi troops?
Yes.
The Northern Qi's great army hasn't crossed the border yet,
so Duke Cheng's power is still at work.
That means he and his troops are still there.
This child must have gone there alone to rescue them.
Madam, don't worry. I'll request the Imperial Court
send troops and reinforcement of Daming Prefecture to the North.
Thank you for your trouble, Lord Tian.
Madam, take a break. I shall go and count the people.
- You go on then.
- It has been tough for you.
Madam.
It's impossible that the Imperial Court will agree to Lord Tian's request.
We already signed the peace treaty with Northern Qi. Yizhou is their territory now.
How could His Majesty possibly expand the war? What's more,
Daming Prefecture is under the control of the Earl of Qinghe.
He won't possibly agree to send out the troops, especially if it's for our Duke Cheng.
- Madam Yu.
- Madam.
Where is our young lady? Didn't she come back with you?
Did she not meet up with you?
She's worried about the refugees at the border and went to rescue them.
Don't worry too much.
Thank you, Madam Yu.
[Tianyou - Baozhou Border]
Second Brother,
thanks to Duke Cheng for taking the risk to gain more time,
we were able to evacuate the people safely.
Where are we going next?
Yizhou.
Yizhou is Northern Qi's territory now. There are tens of thousands of troops surrounding it.
It's impossible for the few of us to help Duke Cheng.
Why don't we go back to ask for reinforcements?
We escorted tens of thousands of people. The Imperial Court should pardon our crimes because of our good deeds.
They most likely will send reinforcements.
If there's a reinforcement troop, would today's situation exist?
Let's go. We must not delay reaching my father.
What were the casualities from last night's battle?
Duke Cheng,
there are 120 survivors in our right-wing troops.
This group of soldiers must be recorded in detail. We must remember them.
They used their lives to exchange for the hundreds of thousands of lives in the three counties.
How much longer can our provisions last?
Duke Cheng, it can last at most three days.
Let's rest for a day and think of a way to break through the siege.
Duke Cheng, we will absolutely follow your commands.
You all have followed me for decades.
For the people of Tianyou, you all must again—
Duke Cheng, for the people of Tianyou, what's there to fear about death?
What's there to fear about death?
Yesterday, Duke Cheng had a battle with Northern Qi and suffered heavy losses.
Yizhou is now besieged and in jeopardy.
There must be at least 10,000 Northern Qi soldiers to put Duke Cheng in such a dangerous situation.
Your judgment is right.
Miss, why don't we do this?
You wait on the outskirts, and I will lead our men to kill our way through.
There's no other way at this time.
That's right. Worse comes to worst, we'll die. Miss,
we can't watch Duke Cheng and his army be annihilated.
What if the Northern Qi's military camp have a false impression of a smallpox outbreak?
Miss, what do you mean?
The plan now
is to make a dangerous move to disrupt the morale of the army.
Old Lei, find a few men who can be trusted. I will prescribe a dose of medicine.
After they consume it, they will have the same symptoms as the pox.
Then take them to Northern Qi's military camp and exchange them with their soldiers.
Let their military camp think they have a smallpox outbreak.
- What is going on? This...
- What's going on?
- Over here too!
- What do we do?
Duke Cheng, there's a sudden smallpox outbreak in Northern Qi's military camp. It's chaos over there now.
Smallpox?
- Is the news reliable?
- It is.
Duke Cheng, Heaven would never seal off all the exits.
(T/N:There is always a way out.)
- Should we break out of the siege now?
- He's right, Duke Cheng.
Relay my orders. Gather our troops immediately and break out of the siege!
Yes, Sir!
I've already applied medicine to your wound. You mustn't let it come in contact with water for the next two days.
Miss Jun! Miss Jun! Duke Cheng has successfully broken out of the siege,
but he's been injured.
Where is he now? How serious are his injuries?
He suffered external wounds and is in his room resting now.
His Majesty repeatedly ordered to retreat.
Only Duke Cheng did not retreat.
Why is that?
- Why is that?
- This... This...
- Because Duke Cheng is concerned for the North.
- Nonsense!
He did it for his own sake.
Once he retreats and there's peace,
how is Duke Cheng going to continue making a show of his authority in the North?
Everyone, let me tell you. The person who loves being in war most
is he, Duke Cheng!
- How can he say that?
- It can't be true.
It's already the third month, the height of springtime.
But why does one's heart still feel chilled to the core?
That is why Duke Cheng must have
purposefully gone to Yizhou
with the goal of disturbing the peace!
- He's deliberately insulting Duke Cheng.
- Precisely!
- Who did that?!
- Exactly.
What are you doing?
- Why are you slandering Duke Cheng?
- Duke Cheng put the nation in peril and caused the people to suffer!
You are not allowed to disrespect Duke Cheng!
We would not have been able to stay alive and come to the capital if not for Duke Cheng,
yet you claim Duke Cheng put the nation in peril and caused the people to suffer.
You're spouting nonsense. Spouting nonsense!
You're spouting nonsense. Spouting nonse!
Duke Cheng clearly went to Yizhou to fight against Northern Qi.
He did not hesitate to put his life in danger for us.
The wife of Duke Cheng and their Heir Apparent's wife distributed porridge during the entire journey
and even told people not to shut their doors on us.
You've all been living well and comfortably!
You don't know the hardships of those who live in the North.
Yet you're slandering people like this!
- He's really gone overboard.
- That's right!
Urgent report! Urgent report!
Duke Cheng has escaped danger in Yizhou and has obtained great victory!
- Wonderful!
- Outstanding!
Get down from there, you!
Spring is coming after all.
- The weather won't be cold much longer.
- The people in the capital have not seen
what Duke Cheng has done,
but all the Northerners have all certainly witnessed it.
It is as Miss Jun said, justice does exist in Heaven and on Earth.
She's finally going to return.
[Baimang City Local Government]
Stop right there! Who are you?
- How dare you barge into the government building!
- He is Duke Cheng's Heir Apparent.
You're the Heir Apparent? I have eye sockets yet no eyeballs.
(T/N: I was blind.)
- My apologies for not recognising you, Young Lord.
- Where is my father?
Duke Cheng was injured and is recuperating now. He's prohibited from seeing anyone unless his physician permits.
Duke Cheng's Madam is currently distributing porridge at the temple of the City God.
Your wife is available though. I will notify her immediately.
Where is she? I'll go and look for her myself.
She's in the second chamber on the left side of the rear courtyard.
- I sense an impending foul wind and a rain of blood.
- What do you mean?
It doesn't matter who she is. This "Heir Apparent's wife" is in a lot of trouble.
You have a point.
My wife, I have returned!
I wonder if you've seen my letter.
I won't ask how you became the Heir Apparent's wife,
for the time being.
I just want to say that I admire what you've done very much.
However, I am unable to comply with this marriage much to my embarrassment.
I will notify my parents and let them explain everything.
Also, to prevent your innocent reputation from being ruined.
♫ The outline of my dream is carved on your face ♫
♫ Times interlace in the watery eyes ♫
Why is it you?
So, were you hoping it would be me?
Yes! Yes, I was.
How is my father's injury?
Don't worry, Duke Cheng is all right now. He will be fine after resting for a few days.
♫ And see the starry night, mountains and rivers together ♫
♫ In the long silence, we are separated by a huge crowd ♫
No matter what,
I must thank you on behalf of my father and the people of the three counties.
♫ The wind is in hot pursuit and locked in a deadlock with the sky ♫
♫ If memories could speak... ♫
You.
Why did you run all the way to the North after resolving the issue with the inoculations?
So dangerous.
It wasn't dangerous at all.
Didn't I have Master Lei and the others protecting me?
Nothing happened to me at all.
Then... the Martial Moral Ministry was watching you closely,
and I didn't receive any news about you.
How was I supposed to know if you were in trouble or not?
♫ With many tomorrows to come,
I’m willing to entrust my whole life to you ♫
♫ And see the starry night, mountains and rivers together ♫
So, what's this about you being the Heir Apparent's wife?
Do my parents not know who you are?
It was never mentioned in the letters.
How could they not know who I am?
It's just... I don't know why
they didn't tell you either.
So are you delighted to see me?
♫ I wouldn’t stop shedding tears like the rain ♫
I am very delighted.
I'm not used to seeing you so serious.
I've always been this serious, didn't you know?
All right.
Enough. Duke Cheng is just next door, so you'd better go and visit him.
I won't intrude on the both of you.
- All right.
- Go.
Father!
Your injury...
Zan'er.
You've returned.
My injury is not serious. It's only a small wound.
Miss Jun has taken very good care of me.
Here.
Father, you've... aged so much.
I'm glad you've returned.
Go get some wine!
Today, you and I shall drink well.
Sure.
Father.
I haven't had a good drink in a long time.
Today, we father and son will drink to our hearts' content.
Here.
Zan'er?
Father, this cup is for those soldiers who have passed away.
They should be venerated.
They were willing to sacrifice themselves for their nation.
They should be remembered.
They should be admired by all of our people.
Father, I was a bad son in the past...
and caused you to worry.
Zan'er,
in my heart,
you have always been the pride and joy of your mother and me.
You entered the capital by yourself and resolutely showed up on the battlefield.
Your mother and I are both aware.
You did extremely well. You're indeed my son.
Father, I have neglected my obligations
by failing to go into battle with you. I have returned now.
I won't let you become injured again,
or let Mother have any reason to be worried and afraid.
Father, thank you.
Thank you for everything you've done for me.
Zan'er,
you have grown up.
As I said,
we shall rest and get drunk today.
- All right.
- Here.
Another one.
Here.
Your Majesty, the return of the people to the three counties displayed your saintly prestige.
In addition, Northern Qi's army has been seriously wounded,
so they should be more passive now.
Duke Cheng will enter the capital soon
to receive his rewards.
Huang Cheng said we can use this opportunity
to let Earl of Qinghe temporarily
act as the guardian of the North. What do you think?
I think this is a good strategy.
What happened with Zhu Zan?
Your Majesty, Zhu Zan is not alone.
With him is a group of highly skilled martial art experts.
Also, after he returned to the North,
he encouraged the governor of Baozhou to lead the army to save the people.
There were many people around, so I...
found it hard to take action.
Regarding them, father and son, returning to the capital,
let Huang Cheng take care of it.
Yes.
Jun!
Why are you so drunk?
Let's go...
over there first. Let's first sit there.
How come you've fallen into the water?
I'm here to save you!
You are so drunk.
Quickly, quickly! Sit over here.
Get up. Hurry and sit there.
Why are you sinking?
Sit down right now.
Quick.
- Wine.
Pour the wine. The wine.
I'm pouring the wine. I'm pouring the wine.
Here.
Am I handsome?
Too handsome.
You have good taste.
Let's drink another cup. All right.
Here, drink another cup.
W-What's wrong?
Why do you...
look so much like her?
Hury and drink the wine.
I will pour some more for you.
I'm going to sleep now.
You are not sleeping here.
Zhu Zan, you...
You're over there. Wait.
You're over there. You—
Bed.
Zhu Zan, g-get up.
What that Jiuling...
owes you....
will be repaid by that Jiuling.
What that Jiuling doesn't owe you,
I will compensate instead.
You are drunk.
Come.
Hurry and get up.
Jiuling.
- Jiuling.
- Madam.
Zhu Zan, hurry and get up.
Madam, it's not what you think! Madam!
Jiuling, I didn't see anything.
- Ma—
I left the snacks on the table. Remember to eat them.
Zhu Zan.
Zhu—
Jiuling.
You're awake?
Jun...
W-What am I doing in your room again?
You have to ask yourself that.
You didn't take advantage of me, right?
It's not entirely sure who took advantage of whom.
So that's what happened.
While I was drunk, you took the chance
"to cook the rice."
(T/N: to do something which can't be undone)
Then, your fake identity as the Heir Apparent's wife
becomes real.
Dream on.
Here.
Earlier I decocted some hangover soup for you.
Hurry and drink it. Quickly.
By the way,
Duke Cheng Madam may have seen.
What?
What else did she see?
She saw everything.
The young madam who escorted the people of the three counties back
turns out to be Physician Jun.
Thinking about it, that is not strange at all.
Physician Jun would never just watch the people suffer.
Or else, would she be able to do things like creating inoculations
to save the world and its people?
Save the world and its people? That's an exaggeration, right?
Everyone has his own selfish goals.
Even if she has other thoughts,
what she has done has benefited everyone.
Then it is good work.
Physician Jun and the Duke's Heir Apparent are indeed well matched.
Execellent.
Mere excuses under dire circumstances.
Regardless if it's true or false,
her identity now is the Heir Apparent's wife.
Looks like you do not really understand me, Princess.
What is it to me whether it is true or false?
Lu Yunqi, is there any meaning in deluding yourself like this?
Then, what is the meaning of your existence?
My entire life is as is.
Being able to see the people around me be happy is the meaning of my existence.
Well, that's not me.
The meaning of my existence is to control everything I deem beautiful.
My Lord.
News from the North says Miss Jun is at Baimang City.
Do you want our men there to make a move?
No need.
Didn't she do so much in order to come back?
Your Majesty is summoning you back to the capital?
Having such serious events happen,
it's only natural that your father needs to report back.
If it's just a simple report,
then why is Earl of Qinghe taking the place of the Grand Marshal in leading the troops?
Since it's a royal decree, then we shall follow.
Father, you can't go back.
Only with an army, do you have power. Without an army, you have no power.
Isn't it like a tiger without teeth?
But what else can we do if we don't return?
This must be the work of that Huang Cheng.
Maybe this is not bad news.
What do you mean?
After His Majesty found out that Duke Cheng survived the calamity,
he cried tears of joy right there in court.
He said Duke Cheng was brave and that the nation having a great general such as you,
was the fortune of the nation and people. Thus, you must be properly rewarded.
From the looks of it, Your Majesty will not slap his own face.
(T/N: slap face mean go back on one's words)
On the contrary, it proves that Duke Cheng is safe for now.
His Majesty is still like this after so many years.
He still lies to the people like this, but who knows what he's done behind—
Zan'er.
It's been so many years now.
I also want go back and take a look.
See His Majesty, see the capital.
Fine. It's unavoidable.
Since we can't avoid returning to the capital,
let's devise a good plan.
Duke Cheng has been in the North for many years, and he is open and honest.
However, that Huang Cheng has been laying in ambush in the capital for a very long time,
so he has advantages in all areas.
Therefore Duke Cheng, if the young lord and I return first to the capital to make arrangements,
and you and the Madam can follow with the army, what do you think?
This plan will work.
If Huang Cheng takes any devious actions, we can find out in advance in order to foil his plans.
It's better than to receive blows in the back.
In addition, there's another matter that I made, a decision for myself.
I hope Duke Cheng and Madam will forgive me.
What is it?
Various branches of De Shengchang reported that
there are still many refugees wandering the three counties.
Therefore, I have privately arranged for
the refugees to accompany Duke Cheng to the capital.
I think we should let the imperial court see as well as the citizens of the capital see
these are also the people of Tianyou. Why must they suffer homelessness?
These are the people that the Northern soldiers risked their lives to save.
Without the lands of the three counties, where would the people come from?
Without the people, how is there Tianyou?
Well said.
Then we shall trouble you, Miss Jun.
- Mother.
- Zan'er.
Come, sit.
All right.
Our son has really grown up.
Then... you didn't call me over just to praise me, right?
I want to say that the events in the capital involving you and Miss Jun,
I've heard about some of them.
Mother, what is heard may not be the facts.
It's hard to explain all those matters.
I was thinking that this time when we go into the capital,
I am worried that you might have some regrets.
I know the matter that you have kept hidden in your heart all these years.
But you didn't have a marriage arrangement with Princess Jiuling.
Now that the two of you are separated by Heaven and Earth,
it's truly a twist of fate.
If in Heaven, she knows of the feelings you have for her,
she will surely be comforted.
But feelings cannot become shackles.
We need to look forward in life.
- Mother...
- Listen to everything I have to say.
In regards to your feelings for Miss Jun,
I can see them.
Miss Jun is adept in both pen and sword. Even I am in great admiration.
Zan'er, being able to meet is fate.
You must understand how to appreciate the people in front of you.
Mother, I have another matter to discuss.
The matter regarding my wife, by chance,
has become widespread.
It now affects her innocent reputation.
Mother, I also want to be an upstanding man.
Therefore, in front of everyone, I want
to clarify this misunderstanding in order to return to her an innocent reputation.
Ending OST: Sounds of Rain - Jiang Long & Yin Luxi
♫ The outline of my dream is carved on your face ♫
♫ Times interlace in the watery eyes ♫
♫ Allow me to weigh every word for indescribable
cause and effect ♫
♫ Life is full of ups and downs and hard to be free ♫
♫ With many tomorrows to come,
I’m willing to entrust my whole life to you ♫
♫ And see the starry night, mountains and rivers together ♫
♫ In the long silence, we are separated by a huge crowd ♫
♫ I can only sigh deeply. The rest of my life is bumpy ♫
♫ The vast sky is you and the wind is me ♫
♫ I’ll eventually be passed by ♫
♫ The wind is in hot pursuit and locked in deadlock with the sky ♫
♫ If memories could speak ♫
♫ I wouldn’t stop shedding tears like the rain ♫
♫ It’s hard to see you again. I’m wailing in deep sorrow ♫
♫ With many tomorrows to come,
I’m willing to entrust my whole life to you ♫
♫ And see the starry night, mountains and rivers together ♫
♫ In the long silence, we are separated by a huge crowd ♫
♫ I can only sigh deeply. The rest of my life is bumpy ♫
♫ The vast sky is you and the wind is me ♫
♫ I’m destined to be passed by ♫
♫ The wind is in hot pursuit and locked
in a deadlock with the sky ♫
♫ If memories could speak ♫
♫ I wouldn’t stop shedding tears like the rain ♫
♫ It’s hard to see you again. I’m wailing in deep sorrow ♫
♫ The vast sky is you and the wind is me ♫
♫ Going through the bottom of my heart ♫
♫ Has God ever asked for clues about the wind? ♫
♫ If I could write down how much I miss you ♫
♫ It would drift like the rain  ♫
♫ Seeing you again as if we’re strangers,
I’m wailing in deep sorrow ♫