[Reset]
Let me get you two some more water.
- This tea has no color. I'll go get you some new tea.
- No need.
Reporter, I'm so sorry about this.
Driver Wang is usually never late.
I don't know what's going on with him today.
How about I give him a call to see where he is?
Hello, where are you? What's going on?
The reporter has been waiting for you for almost an hour.
She's getting tired of waiting.
Old Wang, what is it that you're so busy with right now?
Besides, I had someone notify you of the interview yesterday, didn't I?
Old Wang, I'm telling you. This is a big deal for both you and the whole company. You...
Hello?
Reporter, why don't we do this?
Let's set up the camera and interview me first.
We've kept the two of you waiting for so long.
It wouldn't look good for you to go back empty-handed. I can do the interview instead of him.
Okay. Sure.
Thank you, thank you.
I won't sit in this chair. I'll stand instead.
Sure.
[Pick up gold and return it to its owner; embody noble virtues]
Speaking of "pick up gold and return it to its owner",
I recall that this isn't the first time Driver Wang has returned something valuable to its owner.
This time, he discovered a wallet that had been left by a passenger on the bus.
He didn't even think twice about picking up the wallet to keep it safe.
When the owner came looking for it,
none of us had imagined that there would be ¥30,000 inside. ($4,711 USD)
He has always worked very hard, and he never complains no matter how difficult the work is.
You could say that he has fully devoted himself to doing his job well.
President Yang, let's take a picture.
That's it?
Please move this banner to the side. Later, I'll edit Driver Wang into the picture.
Sure. That's a good idea.
Okay. Look this way.
[Reset]
[Episode 11]
The vehicle is in motion, please be seated.
We have arrived at Yanjiang East Road.
I'm sorry. I just...
Xiao Heyun.
Xiao Heyun?
Are you okay?
You...
- How come these last few times, your condition has...
- What did you say?
What did you want to ask me before?
We've proven that they're working together.
I'm sorry. I-I acted rashly earlier.
I just... I just really didn't know what else to do.
Why did you react so strongly when you found out?
It was a feeling of
when someone you deeply trust suddenly betrays you.
I moved to Jialin by myself for school.
Every time I take this bus,
when I see him I always feel like he's familiar and approachable.
Didn't I tell you before,
every time I take Bus 45, I always see him?
I've known him for about two years.
Two years.
That just means that he's been planning this for a long time.
But he really doesn't seem like a bad person.
- He even helped me before.
- Just because someone does one nice thing
doesn't prove that they're a good person.
But that's why I trusted you in the beginning.
Think about it. He has been driving this route for so many years.
This means that one person was responsible for planning out the route and calculating the times
while the other person was responsible for making the bomb.
It's terrifying just to think about.
I know that you're sad. I can understand.
How about this? Let's get off at the next stop without arousing suspicion, that way we'll have more time to plan.
Actually, now that I think about it, there were several times before when our plan failed because of the driver.
It's just that we didn't suspect him at the time.
It's all my fault.
Why is it your fault? You didn't know what kind of person he was.
But do you remember
that time, in the end, that strange woman kept yelling at him.
She was saying that he went back on his word and
she suspected him of calling the police.
Do you think it's possible
that the driver was forced into being an accomplice?
Also, think about it. If he really wanted everyone on the bus to die with them,
then he would never have let us get off the bus,
but we were able to get off the bus in between stops twice.
The driver is the one who chooses
to open or close the bus doors.
Before getting the job,
bus drivers must go through different types of emergency training.
Encountering emergencies like having a pervert on the bus,
they usually call the police,
secure the doors, and settle the situation at the next stop.
How could he stop the bus and let you off?
In that situation, it doesn't make sense for the driver to let me get off there,
but he opened the doors.
This means that he wanted to let me get off the bus.
He must have wanted to save me.
If he really had good intentions and wanted to save lives,
then he shouldn't have let that lady on the bus.
Yes, maybe he felt bad for you and let you get off the bus twice,
but in the end the explosion still happened.
I just feel like...
No matter what difficulties put him in this situation,
this isn't the way to solve the problem.
Yes, maybe from your perspective he's a good person,
but what about all the other passengers?
If you were one of their loved ones, friends, what would you think?
Would you care about why he was forced to do this?
Shiqing, what we need to do is to prevent the explosion,
not find excuses to protect him.
It seems like I was right.
This was our first time seeing what would happen if we got off the bus and didn't try to intervene.
At 1:45 p.m., the bus explodes on the bridge.
This was their original goal.
[Communist Frontline Position]
Which school did you guys say you were from?
Jialin College.
I have my student ID.
Why is the school's television network reporting on things happening outside of the school?
We want to be more integrated with society,
so anything that is related to the students' lives is relevant news for us to report on.
You probably know this as well. From our school, the fastest way to get into the city is to take Bus 45,
so all the students at school are familiar with this bus route.
They also say that many heartwarming things have happened on that bus.
Of course, anything can happen on a bus,
but we just work in the office. We don't know anything about that.
Here's the thing. Last time, we did a survey at school
and we discovered that one of your drivers, Wang Xingde, has done many good deeds.
He's the perfect example to showcase on our next broadcast
so we wanted to find out more about him by asking the people around him.
This is also good publicity for your company.
If you guys just suddenly show up here, it's difficult for me to help you.
Even though you're students, you should still have notified us beforehand
or given us a letter of introduction.
Without understanding the driver's general background,
we can't write a letter of introduction.
How about this?
I'll just ask you some general questions for now,
and then, later on, I'll ask the school to write an official letter of introduction.
Then I'll schedule another time with you for an official interview.
Will that be okay?
Uncle, please help us out.
No, no, don't call me Uncle. I'm not that old yet.
Brother. Please.
I don't want to make it hard for you either.
We have several drivers here. If you want to get to know just one of them,
we wouldn't know too much about them either.
Bus 45, Wang Xingde.
- Bus 45.
- Brother, something happened.
What's wrong?
Please wait.
What is it?
One of our buses had an explosion on the bridge.
- The bus is destroyed and no passengers survived.
- When did this happen?
It just happened not too long ago. The police will be here any minute.
We have to go to the entrance right now and assist the police with their investigation.
They need to see the driver's schedule.
Let's go.
- Do they know the cause of the explosion yet?
- They're not sure. It might be a bomb that was placed on the bus.
Tell the mechanics who worked on the bus before it was released for use to come here immediately to assist with the investigation.
Tell them to bring the list of repairs and inspections the bus went through. Also, get ahold of any surveillance footage that captured that bus.
Wait a minute. Which route?
Bus 45.
- Who's the driver?
- That's why we're going to get the schedule!
Bus 45, Wang Xingde.
- You guys go ahead first.
- Where are you going?
You guys go ahead first.
[Driver Personal Information]
[Wang Xingde]
So Wang Xingde isn't native here.
He originally didn't drive a bus, he drove a truck.
Before the loop, he did say it.
He didn't lie.
Why did he leave his hometown and quit his job?
Did he come to Jialin and drive a bus for four years
just to plan this attack?
Look at this. It says the reason he quit his job
was because his spouse was relocated for work.
Do you think the lady carrying the bomb is his wife?
It's not impossible, but if he has a spouse,
then why would he live in the company dorm?
It wasn't easy to get this,
but the information on here is too limited.
With only this information, we're not able to draw any conclusions.
There's probably more evidence at his dorm.
Maybe there's a photo of them together or something.
Let's go take a look.
I'll look it up.
Auntie, the bus company dorm is...
- This is it.
- Is it upstairs?
Thank you.
[Employee Dormitory]
Is there any noise?
Then what should we do?
If this doesn't work, then we'll just have to call the locksmith company.
Locksmith company?
Are we really going to do this in broad daylight?
If it comes to it, we can just show our IDs.
Hello.
I lost my key. Could you come to help me break this lock?
Yes, it's the third floor of the Jialin bus company employee dorm.
That's right. 303.
My ID? I...
I'm sorry, I don't need it anymore.
Do you live here?
You must be my uncle's roommate then.
- Who is your Uncle?
- Wang Xingde.
He wanted me to get something
- but I lost the key.
- That's right.
Come in.
If you lost the key, shouldn't you let him know?
I tried calling him but he's not picking up.
We even tried calling a locksmith. Thank goodness you came back.
He didn't pick up?
He's working today.
Okay. Come in then.
Come inside.
What did he tell you to pick up?
His household registration booklet.
Yes, for a family matter.
- His room is over there.
- Over here?
That's right.
[Fortune]
Sit down.
- Have a seat.
- Thank you.
Are you his girlfriend?
That's nice. You two look good together.
How long have you been living with Uncle Wang?
About two years.
I've lived with him since I started working here.
We've known each other for a long time now.
- Uncle.
- You don't need to call me Uncle.
You can just call me brother. Old Wang is much older than me.
Brother.
I want to ask you about something.
Tell me.
Come over here.
Speak.
It's like this.
My boyfriend is planning to introduce me to his family soon.
Uncle Wang is his only relative in Jialin. I'm a little nervous,
so I wanted to ask you what Uncle Wang is like. Is he easy to get along with?
No need to be nervous, young lady.
Uncle Wang is a great guy.
He's honest and trustworthy, and he's pretty quiet.
He's not like an intimidating parent at all.
In the future, if the two of you stay in Jialin,
it'll be good to have a relative like his uncle around.
You can both take care of each other.
Have you met his wife before? How is she?
I know why you guys came to get his household registration now.
Is it because of that incident? Sit down.
They're getting a divorce, aren't they?
Little girl,
I don't like to interfere in other people's family matters,
but let me give you some advice.
Old Wang's wife,
she's definitely someone to worry about.
I think she's mentally unstable.
You need to be careful when you meet her in the future.
What mental health problems does she have?
Is that why they're getting a divorce?
Most likely.
That woman is quite good at tormenting others.
She causes trouble every few days.
No matter how good of a man he is, how could he continue to put up with it?
If their home life was so peaceful,
why would your Uncle Wang live here?
Could it be because their home is too far,
so it's more convenient for him to live here?
How could it be too far?
His house is in Gangwu New Village, right over there.
It's very convenient to commute from there.
Anyone could see what's happening.
Uncle Wang never wants to deal with her.
Since their marriage is already like this,
why not just get a divorce?
But that woman keeps calling here to harass him,
how could anyone put up with it?
- That's true.
- I know.
They have to get a divorce sooner or later.
But I heard from my boyfriend
that his aunt is very kind and easy to get along with.
He also said that their marriage is very happy.
Kind?
Kind, my foot.
Don't let him fool you.
Last month,
I saw it for myself.
In the middle of the night, Old Wang's wife called him and told him to come home.
It was because their house had a fire, so she asked him to come to help put it out.
There was a fire?
Also.
You found it?
- Then we'll...
- All right.
- Thank you for your help.
- No problem, no problem.
- I'll be leaving.
- Okay.
Young lady.
You should tell your boyfriend this.
If he ever interferes in his uncle's family matters,
make sure he doesn't bring you with him.
Okay. Thank you.
No problem.
Thank you.
Here, let's regain some energy.
Let's go over what we know.
Now we know the bus driver's personal background
and we know he lives in Gangwu New Village.
Combined with what we saw on the bus,
that lady must be his wife.
But we still don't know anything about their motive for doing this.
Think about it carefully. You didn't see anything else when you were looking in his room just now?
I only saw what I mentioned earlier, his health report showing that he's in good health.
There was also a savings account book, he doesn't have much savings.
Anything else...
Oh right, there was an old cell phone. It looked like a really old model.
Did you find anything on the cell phone?
The phone won't turn on.
Knowing about his job and his family
is far from enough.
[Convenience Store | Food | Polar Park]
Oh right. You didn't finish what you were saying when we got off the bus.
How did you come to the conclusion of 1:45 p.m.?
There are three points supporting this.
The first one was when we got off the bus at the stop.
We got into a conflict and you went to the police station. I was outside
and I saw that the police said on the news
that the explosion happened at 1:45 p.m.
The second time was when we tried to open the window and throw the bomb out.
That time, when I heard the cellphone ringtone, I looked at the time and it was 1:45 p.m.
The third time is this time, so we can be pretty sure of it now.
Now that you say that,
at that time, the driver
kept saying that it was time.
But why is it at 1:45 p.m?
Could it be that someone was giving them orders?
Like a terrorist?
But even if it was a terrorist attack, there would need to be a reason for it.
If that's the case, we also need to investigate who they're in contact with.
We're not the police, we won't be able to investigate it.
That's right. We won't be able to investigate it, but the police can.
Let me think about it.
No one intervened on the bus.
The bus exploded on the bridge.
If the police have to rule out all the possibilities will take a long time.
They won't make it.
If we go to the police station
and secure the target on those two,
- it will shorten the investigation time tremendously.
- Correct.
- I'm going to call right now.
- Wait a minute.
Let's talk about how we're handling the conversation with the police?
What do we tell them? We can't be coming out empty-handed again.
[Punish Criminal Forces | Maintain Jialin City's Safety]
[Police]
Master.
All the passengers on the bus are dead.
Have you determined their identifications?
The Forensic Team is examining them right now.
Xiao Jiang.
When we encounter this kind of situation, we must stay calm.
This is my first time working on a case with this scale.
I understand.
First, we need to stay focused and calm.
- Hello.
- You must be Xiao Heyun.
- Yes.
Hello. You made the call, your name is?
I am Li Shiqing.
I was waiting for you. I’m the captain of the city detective unit. My name is Zhang Cheng.
This is my colleague, Xiao Jiang.
- Hello.
Let's go in. This way.
Chief Du. They are here.
Thank you for your cooperation. Have a seat.
- Pour two glasses of water.
- Okay.
Sit over here.
[Loyal to the party, serve the public, uphold the law, follow the rules]
Thank you.
Thank you so much for coming to the police station and helping us to investigate the bus explosion case.
I hope you two can think carefully
and tell us what you heard and saw on the bus.
More detail the better.
Thank you.
We were planning to take the bus downtown,
but because of some reasons, we decided to get off the bus sooner.
Then we saw the news about the explosion and realized that it was the bus we were on.
We thought it is necessary for us to reach out to you.
Why?
Why did you decide to get off sooner?
When we were at the Gangwu New Village stop,
a woman with mental issues got on the bus.
We were pretty scared.
How do you consider her has mental issues?
Once she sat down, she took out a knife.
Then she was mumbling something.
She was muttering something under her breath.
I was scared, so I asked her to get off the bus.
She took out a knife? What kind of knife?
It's about this long.
It's like a dagger.
The words she said were pretty alarming.
She said that
everyone will blow up, no one can stay behind.
At 1:45 p.m, everybody will be dead.
No. This definitely is not going to work. It's too detailed.
They will question our intention. We should be more vague.
We can't.
If we want to shorten police's investigation time,
then we need to provide direct clues.
We know how alert they are.
If they suspect us, we will become passive.
It's better to listen to me.
She talked to herself with specific information,
and only you two heard it?
What I'm trying to say is,
you two heard her say it clearly, I bet other passengers
must have heard it too.
What was their reaction?
I don't know if they heard it or not.
They didn't have any reactions.
The bus engine was quite noisy,
we sat the closest to her.
Also, we were focused on her knife, that's probably why we heard her.
That's right.
Then? Carry on.
After that, we got off the bus.
We felt the situation was too dangerous, that's why we got off the bus.
This woman who got on the bus at Gangwu New Village,
what was she wearing? Her physical characteristic?
Do you still remember?
She wore all gray.
She was skinny.
She was holding a red plastic bag
with a pot that looked like a pressure cooker.
- Is this her?
- Yes, that's her.
Actually, I ultimately decided to get off the bus
because of this pressure cooker.
Why? What's wrong with the pressure cooker?
Because when she stepped onto the bus, there was a weird smell.
I can't quite get it but it smelt like
some sort of chemical.
I didn't mention this to my boyfriend.
I was afraid he would judge me with my conspiracy theory.
Since the explosion has already come out on the news, I think
that pressure cooker is questionable. You should look into it.
Okay.
There was a man who also got on the bus with this woman at Gangwu New Village.
Do you remember him?
Yes.
After they got on the bus, did they interact?
No. They didn't know each other.
We were guessing. They didn't sit together.
So...
That's right.
You're this certain?
Did this woman interact with other passengers?
Other people?
Are you suspecting her having an enemy on the bus?
Having an enemy is one possibility.
Accomplices could be another possibility.
We need to rule them out.
If you talk about that,
I remember she spoke with the driver when she got on the bus.
- Didn't she?
- That's right.
She said something strange,
something like they wanted to die together.
I remembered she called the person.
- What was his name? Wang...
- Wang something de.
Wang Xingde.
Sounds about right. Wang Xingde.
Chief Du, Forensic team said
there were traces of objects that look like they come from a pressure cooker.
Have you thought
if we only tell them ambiguous clues,
what the police do to us?
What do you mean?
We can no longer obtain any more information at this point.
If we are a witness,
the police will not disclose any information to us.
Besides, we cannot confirm when they will be releasing the information of the case.
What if we cannot wait until the truth is revealed?
When we enter the next loop, we will once again start from the beginning.
Aren't we running around in circles?
I understand.
If we can stay at the police station longer, perhaps we can collect more information.
That's correct. That's our only chance.
Captain Zhang, these are the testimonies just now.
Both of them are still wandering around in the station.
Do you think those two guys have issues?
Those two young folks are testing the water.
The information they provided is very useful,
but they are obviously leading in a certain direction.
I don't know what are their intention is at this point,
but we will go with their flow.
Later, I will chat with them a little bit more.
How about this?
I will collect information from the outside.
You two go figure out what their true intention is.
This is Bus 45's route map.
Based on your memory,
can you recall the passenger's seating plan?
I think I can.
- Here.
- Thanks.
There were two passengers in the front.
There was a man standing, around 30 years old.
He wore a floral shirt with a bunch of keys on his waist.
He has been filming videos, he should be an internet celebrity.
Here, there was a muscly guy.
He was wearing a green shirt and had headphones.
Here, there was an old man.
Underneath his legs, there was a canvas bag. It's green.
I think the bag was holding watermelons.
A short hair auntie sat behind him.
She was curvy, short hair.
She was carrying a yellow crocheted bag. It looked like holding medications.
Two seats after her was a middle-age man.
This man was bald on top.
He also had a big suitcase next to him. We were sitting over here.
There was a man who got on the bus while we were getting off.
He was wearing black clothes.
And the person sitting over here.
The woman with the gray suit, I should call her suspect.
She had a red bag underneath her seat.
Young man.
Your memory is amazing.
I'm a game designer.
I am used to memorizing all the characters and scenarios.
Did you study game design?
Yes.
When you were at school, you must have done this kind of training.
Not really. It's my subconscious habit.
This kind of training is quite useful.
I remember when I was at the police academy,
I did this kind of detective training.
Isn't it, Ye Qian?
That's right.
Is it the case that for anywhere you go,
after going there just once,
you can memorize everything about it?
Just about.
From when you entered the police station earlier,
until you walked all the way in here,
can you use your memory
to draw the layout of the police station?
I can try.
Here. Let me see what you can do.
[Loyal to the party, serve the public, uphold the law, follow the rules]
[Reasonable analysis, reality based testing, scientific leadership, correct management]
[Serving the Public]
[Technological policing, strict procedure policing, politically correct policing, reformed policing]
[In working]
[Investigation Area]
[Conference Room]
I don't remember all of it.
Young man.
This is what we've found so far
in relation to the passengers who were on the bus at the time of the explosion.
Unfortunately, the pictures are very blurry.
And they're all images of their backsides or side profiles.
Could you use your memory
to identify them for us?
Sure.
Look at this.
Hello?
What's wrong?
It must be because she saw these pictures of the victims.
Earlier, she felt very guilty because she felt like something was wrong on the bus,
but she didn't do anything about it.
Do you want to go to the visitors' area first? There's a sofa there that you can lie down on.
We can ask you again later.
I'm fine.
I'll take a look myself.
Captain Zhang. We've identified the primary suspect.
Tao Yinghong, age 56. She's from Jiaodao.
She lives in Gangwu New Village, and she works at a chemical plant.
Okay.
Okay. I understand.
Captain Zhang.
Tao Yinghong and Wang Xingde are married.
[Jialin Police]
What's wrong with the girl?
I think her reaction looks like survivors' guilt.
The information they gave us was quite accurate,
but some of their reactions were very suspicious.
This case is currently in the investigation phase.
These two must stay at the police station so we can keep a close watch on them.
Old Zhang, you'll be responsible for them.
Has Jiang Feng found anything?
I already told him that the husband and wife were working together.
Currently, he's mainly investigating where the explosive materials came from.
Chief Du, we found it.
Before Wang Xingde came to Jialin, he was a transport squad leader at Jiaodao's Factory 27.
He's very experienced in driving large transport vehicles
and his record is perfectly clean. He's always been a model employee.
Tao Yinghong works at the Jialin chemical plant in the quality inspection department.
Before she started working here, she was a chemistry teacher at Jiaodao High School.
She has a lot of theoretical knowledge as well as practical application experience. She's even written teaching materials.
The bus company employees said that after starting at this job, he applied several times
to drive the Bus 45 route.
After his application was approved, he rejected
the company's offer to move him to other routes several times. He even turned down a promotion to the manager level.
He was determined to drive the Bus 45 route until he retired.
After Tao Yinghong started working at the Jialin chemical plant, she underwent professional training and passed the exam
before starting to work in the quality inspection department. There, she mainly worked on
sampling chemical materials, quality control analysis, and disposing of defective products.
At work, she was a model employee every year.
Her coworker said that she would voluntarily work overtime every day.
She was often the last person to leave.
Wang Xingde lives at the bus company employee dorm.
It's not far from here. I've already asked Xiao Yuan to head over there.
While working at the quality inspection department, Tao Yinghong had direct access to chemical products and raw materials.
And the way that chemical plants dispose of defective products is different from other industries.
They cannot be directly destroyed. So in this process,
it's normal for the materials to be diminished in quantity.
So I suspect that Tao Yinghong took advantage of her job
to obtain the materials needed to create the bomb.
Okay. I understand.
Tao Yinghong has a background in chemistry and the practical skills needed.
She also has access to raw chemical materials.
It's very possible that she created the bomb herself.
One took care of the transportation, and the other was responsible for creating the bomb.
From the looks of it, it's very likely that
the two of them had been planning this crime for a long time.
Yezi, notify the rest of the team of what we've found so far.
Got it.
Also, notify the Jiaodao police department.
Ask them to cooperate with our investigation and provide the information we ask for.
Also, ask them to start conducting personal interviews
ao that we can understand what Tao Yinghong and Wang Xinde's lives and jobs were like in Jiaodao.
I understand.
A homemade bomb.
1:45 p.m.
Why choose this time?
Come, please sit.
You can rest here.
There shouldn't be anything else for the time being.
Is there anything else that we can help with?
Just rest for a bit.
Thank you.
If you have any problems, you can come directly to me.
When I heard the ringtone earlier, I couldn't control myself.
It was a reflex reaction. I felt like an explosion was about to happen.
- It's okay.
- It's all my fault.
Now that we're sitting in here, we won't be able to find out any other information.
It's not your fault.
We can't only assist the police in solving this case.
We also need to find a way for ourselves to stop the explosion.
I-I don't want to slow us down.
We still have a chance.
♫  Extinguish the faint light  ♫
♫  City wall, outside is the city wall  ♫
♫  In the midst of confusion, there’s confusion  ♫
♫  We won't give up  ♫
♫  Wait for the light  ♫
''My Only'' - Zhou Shen
♫  You are the only  ♫
♫  The only one who heals me  ♫
♫  When I look into your eyes  ♫
♫  I heard my heart beat  ♫
♫  You are my only  ♫
♫  Always believed in me  ♫
♫  I will never be that weak-willed me  ♫
♫  I'll be strong with you by me  ♫
♫  How can I let you go away  ♫
♫  You are my only  ♫
♫  Always on my mind  ♫
♫  But it's so hard to find out why  ♫
♫  Dreaming of you every night  ♫
♫  I wonder why you never know  ♫
♫  You are my only  ♫
♫  Always be there waiting for me  ♫
♫  I will never leave  ♫
♫  I will be right there for you  ♫
♫  It seems like the real meaning  ♫
♫  To me  ♫