[Reset]
[Police Station]
Today, 1:43 in the afternoon,
Bus 45 was going
between the intersection of Yanjiang East Road and Qiu Shi Road,
and it collided with an oil tanker, resulting in an explosion.
The initial conclusion of the explosion
was the collision of the bus and the oil tanker,
which resulted in an oil explosion.
However, on the bus, the investigation team
found signs of bomb residue.
We highly suspect that this explosion was man-made.
So we've set up an emergency task force.
I am the team leader of the task force. Old Du will be responsible for specific work on this team.
To avoid panic in the community,
while we look for any suspects,
we must not leak any information.
We must alert the relevant departments as soon as possible
to secure safety.
Can the surveillance on the bus be confirmed to be completely destroyed?
The technical department has tried their best to retrieve it, but they couldn't.
And, the company's maintenance checklist showed
that Bus 45 was running normally
when it left the bus stop.
How is the investigation going for the passengers that passed away?
All the passengers have been identified.
Next, we need to investigate in two directions,
one is to find the social background of all the passengers,
and see if there are any motives against the people on the bus.
Apart from the passengers that were killed, the other direction we can search is
all the passengers of Bus 45
that came on and off the bus, starting from the bus stop.
We must find them and see if there are any clues.
All right, gather all the clues,
and solve the case soon.
[Episode 6]
[The Happy Planet]
Hello, please come in.
I'm back!
Lucky!
Did you miss me?
Come over here.
How are you, Lucky?
Are you feeling better today?
Feel free to sit anywhere.
Help me hold her.
Don't you have asthma? Why are you still raising cats?
I like raising cats. I've loved cats since I was young.
But, my mom has always forbidden me from raising them.
When I was younger, I secretly raised one
and she secretly gave it away. I cried a lot because of it.
So, when I got old enough to work and earned my own money, I rented this place
and adopted them. Every day after work,
I'll feed them and then I'll go home.
My parents still don't know about this place.
- How can they...
- There's a cat fur cleaner over there.
Every day, before I go home...
how did you know that I have asthma?
No, can you tell me what happened?
Why don't we tell him? What if he actually entered the time loop?
Time loop?
What loop?
Say it.
It is like this.
We pulled you off the bus today because we wanted to steal your bag,
not because we lost our bag.
We wanted to check what you had in your bag.
If I told you, you may not have believed it, but we already checked you twice before.
For the first time, you fought with each other.
We didn't even open your bag, the bus exploded.
The second time, you had an asthma attack.
When we got you off the bus, it exploded.
So the third time, we decided to stop you before getting on the bus.
It's the way you were protecting your bag that made you suspicious.
So we thought that you had a bomb in your bag.
It's like this. We also don't know how we got into the time loop.
During the loop, we found out that the bus will explode.
The suspect is on the bus and we need to figure out the suspect one by one.
You are the first person we checked.
Right.
But it is not even August.
Why did the time loop happen?
August...
What's wrong with it?
[Situation, Characters, Time]
[Infinite Loop]
August is when loops usually happen.
But it is only May now.
Do time loops only happen in August?
No. Time loops usually happen in the summer in an anime.
For example, "Summer Wars",
"The Girl Who Leapt Through Time", and "Your Name".
No, no. But why August?
Look. Eight.
Once you flip the eight horizontally, it's the infinity symbol.
Right.
So you believe us?
He not only believes in us, but he also looks forward to being in it.
Actually, a continuous loop is fine.
You both are three-dimensional, and you are not a part of a supernatural group either.
The most important is
you both are good-looking.
What is a supernatural group?
A technical term in anime.
- You also understand this?
- He is a game designer.
A game designer?
I always wanted to be a game designer.
- Here.
- Thanks.
Have some water.
Thank you for trusting me.
After drinking this water, we become time loop teammates.
Okay.
No. You might not be in the loop.
I must be in it.
The opportunity to save the world is kept for those who prepare for it.
Clearly, I am already ready.
We don't save the world but the bus.
What is wrong with the bus? There are so many people on the bus.
Don't listen to him.
That's true. If we could go farther,
our freedom will increase.
This way, we have more weapons and abilities.
We go to school or work during the day.
And we can date. At night, we go into the battles.
Like P5.
What is P5?
- It's a game.
- You need to say it right.
P5 is the best game in the world.
The Legend of Zelda is the best game.
- No! Have you ever played games?
- Wait, wait.
It's not time to discuss games.
We should think about what to do next.
Look. He trusts us now.,
And he is no longer a suspect.
Should we think about who to check next?
I have a question.
I didn't get on the bus today.
I don't know who is on the bus either.
Let's draw it for him.
Are you drawing or am I?
Here's the entrance of the bus.
Once you enter the bus, there's a muscular man on your left-hand side.
After that, there's a live streaming host wearing a bright-colored shirt.
The two of them don't have a suitcase,
besides, this person also has a good sense of justice and has a very positive energy.
So, I'd say we can eliminate the two of them.
Then, there's an old man sitting on this side.
I don't know what's wrapped up in his bag.
There was a hole in the bag, it should be a watermelon.
Then there was an old auntie sitting here.
There was a red bag under her feet.
We don't know what this could be.
And here, there is an old woman.
Inside her bag, there's only medicine.
Another man was sitting here.
That man brought a suitcase with him.
Wait a second.
Suitcase?
That can't be, that can't be.
From this place, even if they were going to the airport or the train station,
there is another bus that goes straight there.
He doesn't necessarily need to ride Bus 45.
He would need to change buses in between.
Could it be that in his suitcase...
How come you're so familiar with the public transportation routes?
Of course, I'm from Jialin.
But even if he took a suitcase with him,
it doesn't necessarily mean that he's going to the airport or the train station.
Excuse me.
Hello, Mom?
I'm off work. I'll come back right away.
No, why are you waiting for me? Eat first, don't wait for me.
Okay, I got it. I'll go home right away.
Bye-bye.
I'm sorry, I need to go home now.
My mom urges me to come home.
I haven't fed them yet, I need to hurry and feed them.
I have a question.
How was my cat doing
in the loops when I died?
When I wake up tomorrow,
it'll either be my normal everyday life or I'll enter the loop.
But if I'm in the next loop and still
die...
Forget it. I still need to go back home first, otherwise, my mother will be enraged.
What is it?
It's too strange.
They usually aren't like this.
They are usually cold and indifferent to me. How come
they are so clingy today?
Tell me, do they know that tomorrow I won't be in this world anymore?
Isn't it even more reasonable that you will enter the loop, then?
That's right.
I will head back home then. Where are you going?
If you really don't have a place to go,
I'll let the two of you stay in my secret base for a night.
My code is 666666.
Thank you.
But it actually doesn't matter where we go.
Actually, even if I haven't entered the loop, I can still help you.
As long as you summon me,
I will trust you.
Okay.
During that time, if I tell you
that I know that there's a cat inside your bag and that I know where your secret base is,
and that there are a lot of cats inside your secret base,
will you believe it?
I will.
By the way,
actually, you can address me by my name.
I will immediately believe you then.
What is your name?
Lu.
Cat Apostle. Asthma Conqueror.
A person chosen by the light.
Di.
Remember it well!
Bye-bye.
Wait. Who can remember such a long name?
Don't you think he's quite cute?
Is that cute?
In any case, he's probably the only person in this world that will believe us at this moment.
[Tiger Internet Cafe Hotel]
Hello, I have a reservation.
Show me your ID cards for a second.
Both of you need to show me your ID card.
Okay.
[Tiger Internet Cafe Hotel]
It's an internet cafe.
I know.
Okay, thank you.
Take your ID card and your room card.
How about you get two bottles of sparkling water? I'll go get some instant noodles.
Instant noodles?
I'm hungry.
[Tiger Internet Cafe Hotel - Room 8513]
[Tiger Internet Cafe Hotel - Room 8607]
It feels complete when you stay up all night playing video games while eating instant noodles.
It's the first time I heard someone say that.
That one.
- Son! You're finally back!
- Mom!
Give me the backpack.
Thank you.
Didn't I tell you to eat first? Don't wait for me.
How could we not wait for you？
How could we eat without you?
Dad.
Stop right there.
What is this?
Have you secretly played with a cat again?
Forget it. Just go and wash your hands before eating.
- I am going to wash my hands.
- No way! You stay right here!
- Mom I said I'll go wash my hands.
- No! Stay right here!
Fur! There's fur! You are already a grown-up!
How could you give me so much trouble? I said don't move!
Look.
I am asking you, did you play with a cat again?
I am asking you a question!
Have you?
Yes! I did play with the cat!
But I am just fine! I don't have any symptoms!
My condition has been under control for a long time already!
Cats have not affected me in any way.
I have been listening to the doctor's advice ever since I was little. I kept taking medicine,
I didn't engage in physical sports activities such as basketball or even swimming.
Since I was little, I've had no friends, Mom.
Each time I go out, I would listen to what you're telling me.
I always wear a face mask. Do you even know how others look at me?
They all think I am super weird!
You lock me up in my room every day. But I don't care about all of that.
My only wish is to have a cat.
What should I do so you would let me raise a cat?
Mom, Dad.
If one day, I run into big trouble
and somehow survive it,
will you let me keep a cat?
It's for your own good not letting you keep one!
It's for you to have a good life!
Stay there!
Open the door!
I told you to open the door!
Can you hear me?
Son, are you all right?
Son, what is going on?
Lower your voice!
Son, open the door! Let me help you!
Stop being so noisy!
Son, are you all right?
Find these people.
Understood.
[Unrecognized number]
Hello?
Hello, are you Lu Di?
- It's me.
- I'm from the City Criminal Investigation Team.
I want to talk to you to understand some things.
Today at around 5:30 p.m.,
at the bus stop at Yanjiang East Road,
did you get into an argument
with a boy and a girl as you were about to get on Bus 45?
Yes.
This bus got into a severe accident.
Did you know that?
Yes, I did.
Where are you now? Could you come to the police station now?
Or is it better if we come to pick you up?
We need your cooperation for an interrogation.
Right now?
Yes. Now.
All right.
What is going on, son?
I heard you were heavily breathing. Was it because of the cat fur?
No. I am going out.
Where are you going to at this hour?
To the police station.
To the police station?
Why are you going to the police station?
What happened?
The police wants to understand a situation.
I was about to get into Bus 45 this afternoon.
Was it the bus that exploded at the intersection?
- Yes.
- My gosh.
How could you not tell me about something so serious?
You don't tell us about anything! Really!
But, why are the police looking for you?
Just to understand the situation.
- Then we will come with you.
- There's no need.
- No way! We must come!
- Calm down!
You don't have to go. If only I go, it's enough.
- No!
- He only has to cooperate with the police and will soon be back.
No one has to come with me. I can go by myself.
Son, let me drive you.
On the way there, think about what you did recently.
Why would the police be looking for you?
I will take my headphones.
Calm down, calm down.
Let's go!
Dad, Mom.
Today, I almost got on the bus that exploded.
I was just about to get on.
I was thinking,
if the God of Death laid his hands on me,
how would you keep me in your memories from now on?
An undisciplined son who wears weird clothes.
Who has no friends.
Who always complains to you.
He is a misfit in society,
and is also an asthma patient.
Compared to your coworkers' children,
my heart is colorful and meaningful.
I have already found the meaning of life.
I will protect and devote my heart to the 2D world.
(T/N: two dimensions = anime)
My only regret
is that no one will reward me with a medal.
I cannot hang them on the living room wall
and allow you to show off my achievement.
If one day,
I can’t come home.
Please go to this address
Animation City, Building 9, Room 201.
The password is 666666.
Once you go inside, you'll know my secret.
Don't be disappointed in me.
You have to think of it this way.
I have already experienced the life that I wanted.
I once had happiness.
Thank you for protecting me.
I just wanted to say that I love you guys.
I'm very happy and grateful.
I'm already very satisfied with my life.
Honestly, my biggest wish
is for you to see the world that I see.
It is so wonderful.
Oh right, today I made two new friends]
They are really cool.
Perhaps, in another parallel world,
we can battle together side by side,
and save all the passengers on the bus.
In this world, I will no longer be your burden.
I can finally become someone who you can be proud of.
Everyone will remember my name.
Lu. Cat Apostle.
Asthma Conqueror.
A person chosen by the light.
Di.
[Oh right, today I made two new friends. They are very cool.]
[News update regarding the police's investigation of bus explosion]
[Related Posts]
[Official Police Report]
The official police report came out.
"Today, on the 13th..."
I saw that too.
Wang Xingde.
[Pictured: Wang Xingde]
I've known the driver for so long, but I've only just found out his name.
[Official Police Report]
[Comments]
"An accident-free and outstanding driver continuously for four years,
he, selflessly, returned a handbag
left by a passenger on the bus, which contained ¥30,000 in cash."
I frequently ride this driver's bus.
He's really nice.
He has also helped me before.
We still have loops left.
We have the chance to save the driver and everyone else on that bus.
That's right. We still have a chance.
We can do it.
Every day without being lively is a betrayal to life.
Life is like a mirror. If you smile, it'll smile. If you cry, it'll cry.
Brother Yi's voice is so contagious.
Why aren't you happy? You have to be happy, right?
My saying still goes: if you never betray others, you'll be dependent on life and death.
What's wrong?
There will always be more happiness than trouble. If you want to be happy, come find your Brother Yi.
I'm live tonight at 8 p.m., see you then!
No, why are these netizens saying these things?
- Look at this one.
-I'm still healthy.
Healthy travel that does not hurt the waist, the happy Brother Yi decided to take the bus.
As long as your heart is beautiful, everyone else will also be happy.
How did that saying go? Life is like a mirror.
If you smile, it'll smile. If you cry, it'll cry.
There will always be more happiness than trouble. If you want to be happy, come find your Brother Yi.
You say, is there really something wrong with that old man?
He doesn't look like the type to blow up a bus.
Think about how we saw Lu Di before.
Wearing a mask and hat,
he looked like a dangerous person. However, we were wrong.
So, judging people simply based on their appearance is inaccurate.
- Is it the police?
- I think so. I remember this number.
Should I pick it up?
- Hello?
- Hello.
- Is this Li Shiqing?
- Yes, it is.
I'm from the City Criminal Investigation team.
May I ask if you got off at Yanjiang East Road stop this evening
and disputed with a passenger named Lu Di?
That's right, but that was a misunderstanding. We've already explained it to him.
We also want to know,
are you with Xiao Heyun right now?
We are together.
We hope you can both come to the police station.
We are conducting an investigation
on the citizens who rode Bus 45. I hope you can cooperate with us.
Sure, we will be there.
Okay.
It's so late and they still want to interrogate us.
They definitely found explosives on the bus. Otherwise, it wouldn't be as urgent.
They won't suspect us again, right?
I don't think they will. If they did suspect us,
they wouldn't have called us. They would have gone to find us directly.
That's true.
What are you searching for?
I'm going to check if there's any new news.
[Posts]
It's still the same things from the evening.
It says the bus collided with a tanker.
No one mentioned anything about explosives.
The other media are all just making things up.
No one is telling the truth.
If we talk to the police now,
we still can't mention anything about the explosives.
We have to talk around the truth, or we'll be suspected again.
It's okay. Didn't you tell me earlier to look at the problem positively?
If we go to the police station, we might be able to collect some valuable information.
For example, the old man. Aren't we trying to get to know his background?
- Don't you think so?
- Wait a moment.
The police found us through the cameras, right?
I think so.
Didn't she mention earlier that she knew about us getting off at Yanjiang East Road stop
and our dispute with Lu Di?
Since they found us, they can also find Lu Di.
We don't even know how to deal with the police, so he...
With that temper of his, he'll tell them about the loop.
We forgot to save his phone number.
Actually, I'm quite grateful for those two.
If they didn't push me off the bus, I would've died in the accident.
What happened next?
We got off the bus.
- Master.
- Sit.
What's wrong? Are you nervous?
A little bit.
There's no need to be nervous. Here.
Your father brought this for you.
No, I also brought my own medication.
If it's okay, can you go outside and tell him
to go home first? I can get back on my own.
Poor parents.
Your father insisted on waiting to go back home with you.
How's the questioning going?
I've cleared everything up. The other two passengers mistook Lu Di for carrying their bag.
Because a few days ago, they lost their bag on the bus.
They went up to check on the bag and then left.
Listening to his description, they don't know each other.
When they separated, they didn't leave any forms of communication.
Young man, not bad. Broad-minded.
Actually, back then I was pretty angry.
There's something that you guys don't know.
I lost my cat. They were trying to help me find my cat.
When the girl hugged the cat, she was super gentle. I could tell she was a cat lover.
Between cat lovers, all misunderstandings can be cleared.
I'll ask the other two later. If everything matches up, then they can go home.
Understood.
Both of them came here?
That's right.
Sit here for a while.
Master, what questions do you have?
The relationship between those three is not that simple.
Lu Di didn't get on the bus, so he doesn't understand the situation.
Ask about what the other two encountered on the bus.
Understood.
Let's go.
''My Only'' - Zhou Shen
♫  You are the only  ♫
♫  The only one who heals me  ♫
♫  When I look into your eyes  ♫
♫  I heard my heart beat  ♫
♫  You are my only  ♫
♫  Always believed in me  ♫
♫  I will never be that weak-willed me  ♫
♫  I'll be strong with you by me  ♫
♫  How can I let you go away  ♫
♫  You are my only  ♫
♫  Always on my mind  ♫
♫  But it's so hard to find out why  ♫
♫  Dreaming of you every night  ♫
♫  I wonder why you never know  ♫
♫  You are my only  ♫
♫  Always be there waiting for me  ♫
♫  I will never leave  ♫
♫  I will be right there for you  ♫
♫  It seems like the real meaning  ♫
♫  To me  ♫