[Reset]
[Five years ago]
[University Campus Bus Stop]
The vehicle is in motion, please be seated.
The next stop is Jiaming Community Hospital.
Young lady.
Do you take Bus 45 often?
Has anyone harassed you on this bus?
Harassed me?
Did any men try to touch you?
- Did they try to take advantage of you? Did they sexually harass you?
- What are you doing?
- What's wrong with you?
- Was there? Good girl, tell me.
- Driver! This woman's crazy.
- Let go of me! Tell me, was there?
Stop harassing the other passengers, or I'll call the police!
I'm not crazy.
Hello? I would like to make a police report.
[Bus 45 Route - Terminal Xueye South Road]
How many times has this happened?
If I remember correctly, this is the third time, right?
Can you stop causing police reports to be filed? Every time this happens, we need to look into the report.
Can you make sure this doesn't happen again?
I understand how you are feeling,
but your personal investigation
is a major disturbance to the Bus 45 driver and the other passengers.
Can you please be more careful?
Who have I disturbed?
How did I disturb them?
If you didn't disturb anyone, would I be here?
Please trust the police.
Stop right there!
- Police officer.
- What are you doing?
Please calm down. Please calm down.
Please listen to me.
Look at her, she's clearly not doing well.
I hope you can understand us.
I'm here, I won't let her cause any more trouble, don't worry.
Old Wang, I understand how you're feeling.
I'm a parent too.
But the case has been closed already.
If you guys keep carrying on like this, what will come of it?
Take my advice. Make sure this doesn't happen again.
When you get home, try to talk some sense into her.
This definitely won't happen again.
I'm sorry to have caused you trouble.
You guys can head back now. Thank you.
Let's go.
Old Wang, take her home. Don't stand around here anymore.
They couldn't find any evidence,
but they won't let us look for it, either?
[Reset]
[Episode 13]
Ambulance! Where's the ambulance?
[Renhe Hospital - The Affiliated Hospital of the 3rd Hospital of Jialin]
His wound has been fully taken care of.
It's not a severe injury.
He's just lost a lot of blood, so he'll need to stay in the hospital overnight.
Xiao Lu. Transfer them to the in-patient department.
Okay.
- Please come with me.
- Thank you.
[Debridement Room]
Hold on.
You're the one who called the police, Xiao Heyun, right? I need to ask you some questions about the case.
How did you know that there was a bomb on the bus?
Tell me.
Police officer.
This patient has lost a lot of blood. He needs to rest.
If you need to ask him any questions, please wait until later.
I won't take up too much of his time. I just need to ask him two questions.
- This is a hospital.
- Chief Du is calling.
- Xiao Lu. Take them to their room.
- Okay.
Come with me, this way.
Chief Du.
The person who filed the police report is extremely important to us.
I understand.
If there are any updates on Old Zhang, notify me immediately.
I will keep watch at the hospital.
Chief Du.
The two of them refuse to tell us anything.
They won't cooperate with our investigation.
Let them be for a while.
When we have more details about the case, we'll interrogate them again.
Got it.
[Emergency Room]
Why did things turn out this way?
We were so close this time.
Next time,
no matter what it takes, we need to fight for more time.
That way, no one will get hurt.
There might not be a next time.
If saving all the bus passengers is the key to breaking out of the time loop,
then we've already accomplished that.
That would mean this is the last time.
But I still feel like some things are still incomplete.
It feels like some other things must have happened after Wang Mengmeng's accident.
Can you look this up for me? On May 13th, 2014,
the car accident on that bridge
with Bus 45.
Look at this.
If Wang Mengmeng's parents
saw these comments,
how would they feel?
Perhaps,
to them,
by living, we didn't really save them.
I don't think we've gotten to the bottom of this yet.
Back then, after Wang Mengmeng's accident,
Wang Xingde and Tao Yinghong
refused to accept the results of the investigation.
They continued to ask the police to keep investigating the reason Wang Mengmeng got off the bus.
Is the bus driver here yet?
He should be here soon. I'll go to the entrance to wait for him.
Captain Qin.
- Chief Du.
- Captain Qin. Thanks for coming.
- Did you bring everything?
- I brought all of it.
These are our interview transcripts from back then. And this is the accident verification record.
I brought all the related documents.
Actually, this case wasn't very complicated.
There weren't any areas of suspicion either.
It was just a traffic accident.
The chain of evidence is complete, and the root cause and consequences are clear.
In the end, the bus driver who let her get off the bus took full responsibility for the accident.
The truck that crashed into her was also held responsible.
When the driver paid compensation, were there any conflicts?
There weren't any conflicts.
The bus company took care of the compensation process.
The victim's parents didn't file a lawsuit,
so there weren't any conflicts over the financial compensation.
Chief Du.
This is the bus driver who was driving Bus 45 at the time, Driver Zhu.
Driver Zhu, this is our Chief Du.
Driver Zhu, hello. Please sit.
- Please sit.
- Captain Qin,
- please sit.
- Okay.
Driver Zhu, sit. Sit.
Driver Zhu, there's no need to be nervous.
We just want to ask you some questions about what happened.
All you have to do is tell us the truth.
When we watched this footage earlier,
we saw that Wang Mengmeng was very agitated when she got off the bus.
And she was arguing with you and also physically trying to get you to let her get off the bus.
What exactly happened?
It's been five years since this accident happened.
The police have asked me about all the details already.
- You-you're Captain Qin from back then, right?
- Yes, it's me.
Then you know this situation better than anyone else.
Please tell them for me.
- Back then, I already answered all the questions the police asked. All I can do now is...
- Driver Zhu.
You heard about today's explosion, right?
This is a critical case. I hope you can cooperate with the investigation.
Back then, that young lady
was desperate to get off the bus.
I really didn't think
that the car accident would happen as a result.
If I had known, I definitely wouldn't have let her get off the bus.
But at the time, under those circumstances,
I had to let her get off the bus.
I'm sure you've all seen the surveillance footage from the bus.
At the time, she was pulling on my arm.
If my steering wheel went in the wrong direction, what would happen?
The aftermath would have been unimaginable.
I'm a driver. I need to ensure
the safety of all passengers on board.
And if we had been somewhere else,
I could have pulled over to let her get off the bus,
but we were on the bridge. There wasn't anything I could do.
Why didn't you ask the other passengers to hold her back?
At the time, none of the passengers were trying to help.
After the accident, did Wang Mengmeng's parents look for you
to ask about the real reason she got off the bus?
Even if you gave me the courage,
I could never face them.
At the time, I knew that,
even if I knelt down and bowed to them, they wouldn't accept it.
Especially that lady, every time she–
Yes, I know.
I did break the
regulations while driving.
I know that. I even lost my job because of this.
I've admitted my mistake too.
How much do you know about why Wang Mengmeng wanted to get off the bus?
Or did she tell you anything about it?
That young lady had gone past her stop.
I've seen that happen several times.
She kept talking while running back and forth across the bus. None of what she was saying made sense.
I didn't know what she was trying to do either.
All I knew was she desperately wanted me to stop the bus and let her get off.
At the time, I was focused on driving.
I-I-I didn't know what to do either!
It's the bridge! You can't stop a vehicle on there!
But you still stopped the bus.
Yes, yes. I know I stopped the bus, but so what?
It's been five years since this happened!
Are you going to punish me because of this forever?
- Didn't you bring me here today to interrogate me about my crimes again?
- No, no, no.
- Fine then. Give me the death penalty. I'll give my life as compensation for hers!
- Driver Zhu.
That's not what we meant. Please, sit.
Driver Zhu, please calm down.
- You don't need to be so agitated
- That's not what we meant.
We only brought you here because we wanted to ask if you remember
if the parents were very upset at the time, or if they seemed very angry or resentful.
Resent?
How could they not be resentful?
I'm resentful too.
All right, Driver Zhu.
Please calm down.
Let's all take some time to calm down. Xiao Liu.
Take Driver Zhu over there to have some tea and rest for a bit.
Driver Zhu, come this way. You can rest for a bit.
[Emergency Room]
- Mrs. Zhang.
- Where's Lao Zhang?
I'm asking you! Where is he?
We carefully studied the surveillance footage on the bus.
We also interviewed all the bus passengers.
No one knew why Wang Mengmeng wanted to get off the bus. We only found out that
she was interfering with the bus driver and preventing him from driving safely.
Other than her desperation to get off the bus,
there was no evidence to show that she had been threatened in any way.
But looking at the case record,
it seems like Tao Yinghong was very sure about this.
She was sure that Wang Mengmeng must have wanted to get off the bus
because her safety had been threatened on the bus.
Yes, she kept fixating on this idea.
Let's watch the surveillance footage again.
Who is she calling here?
Wang Xingde.
She called him, but he didn't pick up.
Driver, I want to get off the bus!
Driver. I want to get off the bus!
I can't stop the bus before we get to the next station.
Please pull over up there and let me get off. I'm begging you!
We're getting on the bridge, I definitely can't stop up there.
- I want to get off the bus!
- Get off me! What are you doing?
Get off me!
I want to get off!
What you're doing is extremely dangerous!
- Stop the bus!
- Stop moving around!
- Don't touch the steering wheel!
- Stop the bus!
I'll stop the bus. Stop moving around.
Pause it.
Look. At this point, the bus driver has already opened the doors, so she could already get off the bus.
But why is she looking back? Who is she looking at?
There were too many other passengers on the bus. Regarding who she was looking at,
we aren't clear.
But why was she so desperate to get off the bus?
We tried to figure this out before as well.
This section of Bus 45's route
is where many disputes take place.
Yanjiang East Road is the last stop before crossing the bridge.
If passengers miss their stop here,
they can only cross the bridge and then come all the way back across the bridge.
This process takes well over ten minutes.
But people often miss their stop here
and ask to get off before crossing the bridge.
Our guess was that Wang Mengmeng had also missed her stop.
So then, this case is actually quite simple.
There is plenty of evidence as well.
And after the accident, all three parties accepted the police's decision of who should take responsibility for the accident
and signed off on the police's decision.
The driver also paid the necessary compensation
- and all the financial compensation was paid out.
- That's right.
When they signed off on the police's decision,
what were Wang Xingde and Tao Yinghong's attitudes?
In the beginning, they refused to accept it.
They investigated on their own for over a month.
Every day, they would take Bus 45.
On the bus, if they saw
any girls that looked around the same age as Wang Mengmeng, they would start interrogating them
about whether they had been harassed on the bus before.
On the police decision report,
I see that only Wang Xingde signed it.
Was Tao Yinghong there at the time?
Does she know about this?
She was there. She knew what happened.
After the accident happened,
Tao Yinghong was the first to come here from their hometown,
so in the early stages of the investigation, we mainly communicated with her.
But as the investigation continued,
she began to lose control of her emotions.
This made it difficult for us to continue investigating.
So, after that, we tried our best to avoid her.
We mainly communicated with Wang Xingde instead.
When Wang Xingde signed off, Tao Yinghong was there too, and she was aware of what was going on.
After that, did either of them
question the police's decision at all?
No, they didn't.
Yezi. Is there any news from Jiaodao?
Yes. We contacted the other teachers that taught at Jiaodao First High School with Tao Yinghong.
They said that Tao Yinghong was indeed emotionally unstable.
After Wang Mengmeng's accident, Tao Yinghong's personality changed dramatically. She easily became angry.
She even physically hit students. Not long after that, she left the school.
Although, I think she was probably asked to leave
because the parents of the student that she hit caused quite a scene at the school.
After she left, she never contacted any of her coworkers.
She also blocked all of their calls.
And then, she moved to Jialin.
What about Wang Xingde?
We contacted some of Wang Xingde's old apprentices.
They said that Wang Xingde became very unhappy and morose.
It was like he aged several years at once.
But he never discussed the accident with anyone else.
Did anyone say anything about the state of their relationship?
His apprentice said that Wang Xingde always listened to Tao Yinghong for everything.
Moving to Jialin was probably Tao Yinghong's decision.
At first, Wang Xingde didn't want to move, but Tao Yinghong made up her mind.
Wang Xingde had no choice but to move here with her.
[Emergency Room]
How did you know there was a bomb on the bus?
And how did you know
Captian Zhang's contact information?
Captian Zhang told us himself.
When did he tell you?
Did you know each other before?
You can say that we knew him,
but this is not something we can explain in one or two sentences.
That...
Captain Zhang, he...
Captain Zhang has already passed away.
You must tell me everything you know, truthfully.
Xiao Jiang, let's talk outside.
You guys answer me!
We have discussed this all afternoon.
Do you really have nothing to tell us?
About your daughter,
you also have nothing to say to us?
What are the purposes of this bombing?
Except for Tao Yinghong, do you have other accomplices?
Have you planned another bombing site?
Is Tao Yinghong okay?
If it wasn't for those two police officers on the bus,
our family
would have been reunited by now.
Are the two police officers she mentioned the two youngsters that called the police?
Are the two police officers you mentioned
the two youngsters?
I want to know.
You can follow me this whole time.
But when I asked you to investigate
the truth behind Mengmeng's death back then,
why did you close the case so hastily?
Tao Yinghong,
what I'm showing you here is all the information regarding Wang Mengmeng's case five years ago.
If you cooperate with our interrogation, we will re-open the case and find out the truth.
I already said what I needed to say.
This was my own idea.
I made the bomb by myself.
I took the bomb to Bus 45.
There is nothing to do with Wang Xingde.
If you think there is an association between us, it's because we are husband and wife.
It's because I forced him to.
It's because I want him to die with me.
Tao Yinghong, I understand that you are holding a grudge.
You can understand?
Can you understand?
I can't even understand it myself.
[I have seen my testimony. It is the same as what I said.]
Tao Yinghong. Tao Yinghong!
You stay here, I'm going to get the doctor!
[I have seen my testimony. It is the same as what I said.]
Chief Du.
Wang Xingde.
We have re-started the investigation
of your daughter's case.
Thank you.
How's Tao Yinghong?
I can understand.
As parents,
when your child was at risk,
you couldn't protect her at that moment.
Not to mention
Mengmeng's last call was calling you for help.
If I could have picked up that call,
how great would that be?
If I can,
I'm willing to use my life
in exchange for Mengmeng's.
What do those people know?
How can they casually spread rumors
of those they don't know on the internet?
They wrote those nasty comments.
Mengmeng was only twenty years old.
She never hurt anyone.
At that time,
if there were any clues or slight hope,
we wouldn't come to this stage today.
Five years ago, I threatened Tao Yinghong
to move from Jiaodao to Jialin.
Regarding the entire bombing plan,
I am the person behind it.
That bomb,
I forced Tao Yinghong to make it,
but there was nothing we could do.
She was our daughter.
I need to give her closure.
I can't let her die without any reason.
Let me ask you.
Is it wrong for us to do this?
You cannot use that as an excuse to commit a crime.
Have you thought about the families of the passengers?
They also have children and parents.
You applied your hatred
onto those innocent people and ruined their families.
Do you think your behavior
was what Mengmeng wanted to see?
I caused trouble to you guys.
I'm sorry.
[Five Years Ago, May 13]
Master, after Mengmeng went to college, no one has changed your gloves.
What do you know? Mengmeng said
when she comes home for summer, she's going to buy me a new pair.
- Get to work.
- Okay.
Master, later, I'll buy you a new pair.
Let's get a nice one. A nice leather pair.
Brat.
[Mengmeng]
Old Wang!
There's someone looking for you.
[Mengmeng]
Captain Yin, Wang Mengmeng's father is here.
Hello Mr. Wang.
This is Officer Qin
and this is President Yang from the bus company.
Mr. Wang.
Mr. Wang, as for Wang Mengmeng's accident,
we are all sorry.
My condolences.
This is the accident liability determination letter and the damage compensation mediation letter.
The traffic police department takes this traffic accident very seriously.
They thoroughly investigated the reason for this accident.
The driver will be held legally accountable.
Also, the funeral cost and pension will be paid by the bus company.
We'll cover it.
The rest of the details
are in the file. Take a look.
If there aren't any additional problems,
you can sign it.
I don't agree.
I don't need your compensation.
I only want the truth.
I want to know why Wang Mengmeng suddenly got off the bus.
I want to know
what happened on the bus before she got off.
Once you find the truth,
we'll sign immediately.
- Mr. Wang!
- Mr. Wang.
- Mr. Wang?
That lady has been here all day.
Don't you think she's an idiot?
Just waiting at the front door.
Who is she trying to find here?
No one wants to see her, not even our boss.
Definitely, no one will see her. This lady,
she's a tough one.
On Bus 45,
wasn't there a girl who was harassed?
I think so. That's what I heard too.
But with this kind of thing, if the passenger doesn't speak up, the driver can't do anything.
The driver has to drive the bus, how can he see everything happening behind him?
This kind of man is a pervert.
They even have the gall to touch young girls.
They should be put in jail.
[Bus 45 Terminal - Xueye South Road]
We have arrived at the university stop. Please get off from the back door.
Please swipe your card when you leave. Passengers near the doors, please pay attention to your safety.
Has everyone gotten off?
I'm leaving now.
Mister... Mister! Open the door!
Mister! Mister!
Open the door!
Why are you chasing the bus?
Are you hurt?
[University Campus Bus Stop]
What's the use of coming here?
We're almost there.
I miss her.
Let's just sign the papers.
They already showed us the surveillance footage.
You were in the bathroom for ten minutes but no one entered the men's bathroom
and we have been going on Bus 45 investigating for so long...
Now we can't even get on the bus.
Yinghong,
listen to me.
Yinghong.
Look at me.
Let's bring Mengmeng home.
Mengmeng must want to go home.
Also, all your graduating students
are all waiting for you.
Those students all need you too.
Mengmeng is gone.
The rest of our days
we'll have to live with memories.
''My Only'' - Zhou Shen
♫  You are the only  ♫
♫  The only one who heals me  ♫
♫  When I look into your eyes  ♫
♫  I heard my heart beat  ♫
♫  You are my only  ♫
♫  Always believed in me  ♫
♫  I will never be that weak-willed me  ♫
♫  I'll be strong with you by me  ♫
♫  How can I let you go away  ♫
♫  You are my only  ♫
♫  Always on my mind  ♫
♫  But it's so hard to find out why  ♫
♫  Dreaming of you every night  ♫
♫  I wonder why you never know  ♫
♫  You are my only  ♫
♫  Always be there waiting for me  ♫
♫  I will never leave  ♫
♫  I will be right there for you  ♫
♫  It seems like the real meaning  ♫
♫  To me  ♫