Jun Nan.
Feng Xiang.
Qiang.
Hang.
Zhen Lin.
Hao Lasi Geng Lin Tong Hui Ying Le Han.
Jun Tong Ming Xin.
Liang.
Stop! What the hell are you dancing?
When can I expect to learn from you guys?
What is street god dance?
It's supposed to be soft yet strong.
Your hips,
your shoulders, your neck,
they're as stiff as freshly rolled steel plates.
Useless. Get out!
I'll have to rely on myself.
Why did you bring me here?
I've taught you so many techniques of the jaw harp.
Today, I'll teach you something more soulful.
Give it a try.
Sha Tang,
are you also distracted
by thoughts of our future?
You not only know how to play the instrument,
but you can also make it.
Craftsmen who can make jaw harps
are rare nowadays.
I've only learned the basics.
In the past, these instruments were made from fish bones.
The sound was crisper and had more texture.
It's a pity. It's been a long time
since I've touched a jaw harp made from fish bones.
Try it.
It's fixed.
Manyue.
That bear.
is gone.
I know.
I want to say,
bear migration is a natural law.
but some things
are more important than chasing dreams.
The assessment officially begins.
Please welcome the first contestant,
Mr. Zhong Ziqing.
May I ask, why are you dressed like this to perform the Lu Shen dance?
This is a grand fusion of technology and culture.
It's time for the Cyber Lu Shen dance performance.
I can't take it anymore, I can't take it anymore.
I can't take it anymore.
Esteemed judges,
Next, I'd like to formally introduce my partner.
Stop, stop, stop!
The Lu Shen dance is such a sacred activity,
what have you turned it into?
This is a combination of intangible cultural heritage and technology.
What a great idea.
Don't be so old-fashioned.
I don't see any combination.
I only see your lack of respect.
For the art left by our ancestors,
you have no reverence.
I think you don't need to perform anymore.
Get out of here now.
I've already invested.
And I can't even get on stage?
Is there no justice?
The organizing committee doesn't need
someone like you who doesn't respect art.
Your investment
Leave immediately.
Mr. Zhong Ziqing, please leave the premises.
Please exit.
Please.
It's rigged!
The art circle is all rigged!
This Zhong Ziqing
has too many tricks up his sleeve.
No, I actually admire his creativity.
Alright, let's welcome the next one.
Mr. Sha Tang, come on, let's go.
Please begin your performance.
Dongji
Charming East
Charm
Please allow us to perform an additional segment of the Road God Dance.
Although due to time constraints,
the Road God Dance cannot be
performed at the Winter Cultural Arts Festival.
There are some traditions
that, although not mainstream enough,
but
should not be buried and forgotten.
They say he's far away, high up in the white clouds.
They say he's close, right here in our hearts.
They say she's far, at the North and East Poles.
They say she's near, in my homeland.
Whether she's near or far,
her beauty is undeniable.
The first note of a boat song is the most touching.
The first breeze of morning is the sweetest.
It's not far from here.
It's just that the evening breeze of Wusuli
is a bit lingering.
It's not far from here.
It's just that the stories of the birch forest
are a bit entangling.
It's not far from here.
It's just that the melodies of Errenzhuan
have a touch of romance.