Jia Hao.
Li Jia Hao.
Mom.
I found a dad.
I've started learning photography.
You've become a father so quickly.
Mom.
What does that devil want to do?
Why won't he leave us alone?
He's back again. What does he want?
Maybe he still wants to find that white bear.
What bear?
My sister in the mountains
captured a white black bear on camera.
He found out about it.
He stayed in Fuyuan
probably because he wants my sister
to take him to find that white bear.
Finding a bear?
He's just a jerk.
He's making Yueyue do such dangerous things.
My sister has already agreed to it.
Since he's back,
I guess in the next couple of days
they'll be heading into the mountains.
Shanhai.
Do you still want to find Natasha?
Of course.
You haven't answered me yet.
Why aren't you leaving?
I've already sold the studio.
Now I'm free as a bird.
Then how did you know I was here?
Let me introduce myself.
Photographer for the Guangxi Little Brave Travelers Group.
Sha Tang.
Why do I feel like you've been planning this for a long time?
This can't be called long-term planning.
I mainly wanted to give you a surprise.
A surprise?
Alright then.
What about little Jiahao?
Why does she call you dad?
Kids playing house, you know.
She calls me mom.
Why does she call me mom?
Jiahao.
Dad, Mom.
She's calling you, Mom.
Let's take a family photo with you.
I'm afraid you'll have to work hard these couple of days.
I've worked as a tour guide before,
but I've never taken care of children.
Look at the shadows on the ground.
Don't they look like a family of three?
You...
What will you do when it's over the day after tomorrow?
Once the children are sent away,
my work will be finished.
I'll take you into the mountains to find bears.
Really?
Keep your voice down, the child is asleep.
Sha Tang has returned,
giving our story
a new turn.
This time,
I must hold onto his hand,
and also actively grasp
my own happiness.
It's cold in the mountains.
Did you bring all the warm clothes?
Don't worry.
We won't make the same mistake twice.
You two are so inconsiderate.
Not inviting me for such an exciting trip.
Why would we invite you?
A can of beef would be more useful than you.
We mainly didn't want to interfere with Boss Lin's money-making.
Cut it out.
I'm worried you might lure my boss into the mountains.
And sell her off.
I need to protect my boss.
Let's go.
You should be happy to have a free driver.
You're looking for me.
You don't answer your phone,
get drunk every day,
it's really hard to find you.
Our cooperation has already ended.
I don't need to report to you every day
about my whereabouts,
boss.
The past cooperation has ended,
but a new collaboration
has just begun.
For example?
For example, a certain devoted man
who's been desperately looking for you but can't find you.
In his heartbreak, he thought of
me, who can do anything.
So here you are today.
I didn't expect
Boss Zhong would be in this kind of business.
After all, seeing a devoted person heartbroken
makes one feel a bit of pity.
You should know,
trying to get a player to settle down
is harder than getting Tang Monk to enter the sea.
Forget it.
I have no plans for early retirement.
I'm just relaying the message as it is.
Every time he mentions you,
I can feel
the passion in his heart.
Alright,
I've received your message.
I'm going back to catch up on some sleep now.
The Long Time Coming Bar is closed.
Guess where the boss is?
What are you smelling?
A milky scent.
Really?
You two aren't even trying to hide it anymore, huh?
What's that sound?
Is someone talking?
I don't think so.
Don't scare me, Man Yue.
There's no one.
Man Yue, this is so disgusting.
Oh God, please take me now.
No way, wait until we get off the car.
Don't drag us into this.
That's not right.
It should be after he gets off the car.
Otherwise, wouldn't the car be wrecked?
Sha Tang, how can your warm mouth
say such cold words?
Still better than some people.
A dog's mouth can't produce ivory.
Look at you all united against a common enemy now.
With your venomous little mouths.
You really are a perfect match.
I get it now.
It must be our current venomous faces
that remind him of something.
Some unbearable past memories.
Since ancient times, deep love can't be kept.
Only tricks can win hearts.
Some people, you know.
They're hurt inside.
We're trying to find balance here.
Let me educate you a bit.
This is called psychological compensation effect.
Someone's angry.
The car can only go this far.
Let's walk the rest of the way.
I have a feeling
this time, we'll definitely be able to photograph a polar bear.
Should we go through the procedure first?
What procedure?
Look at you two, so inexperienced.
I'll go first.
I promise
I won't be a killjoy during this bear-seeking expedition.
I won't say 'I wish I hadn't come' at all.
Lin Shanhai.
Wait for me!
You two have no sense of ceremony.
Sha Tang, come and look.
Manyue, look.
That's it.
Yes, yes, yes.
It went in that direction.
Slow down.
What are you photographing?
I... I...
I've never seen this before.
I'm just keeping a memento.
Keep up.
Slow down, Sha Tang.
The footprints have disappeared.
I take back what I said at the foot of the mountain.
If I had known, I wouldn't have come.
Let's hurry and leave.
Let's retreat, get out of here.
What's wrong?
Have you heard this saying?
Clouds are the tongue of the sky,
Snow is the breath of the earth.
The snow is starting to blow.
There will be a blizzard soon.
It's very dangerous.
But if we leave now,
it will be difficult to find it again.
In such extreme weather,
even bears will seek shelter.
They won't move around much.
Once the new snow covers everything tomorrow,
when the bear comes out again,
you'll find its tracks more easily.
That makes sense.
Where should we go?
Over there.
We shouldn't be far from that Cuoluozi.
If we hurry, we can make it.
You stay here.