Photographer Sha Tang.
He's the boyfriend I, Lin Manyue, have chosen.
She's not lying to you.
I am indeed her boyfriend.
The weather is particularly nice today.
I have a feeling
we'll definitely get some good shots.
Manyue, you're here so early.
Morning.
Good morning.
It's been a while since I've moved around.
Yeah,
I came to warm up a bit.
I wanted to ask...
Could you take me up the mountain to find bears?
Don't misunderstand.
I don't mean to threaten you.
I'm asking for your help.
I'm sorry.
Maybe I misunderstood.
I'm preparing to go into the mountains now.
Wish me luck.
The city has issued a yellow alert for heavy snow.
It is expected to start from 16:00 today
and continue until 05:00 tomorrow.
Strong winds in some areas.
Snow accumulation and icy roads are expected.
Citizens are advised to limit outdoor activities.
Please avoid wilderness areas and forests.
Be prepared for emergencies.
Sha Tang.
You don't want the comfort of a studio that's warm in winter and cool in summer,
but insist on going to such a far and cold place.
You're just making things hard for yourself.
I really don't understand what you're thinking.
Just give it a try.
It won't do any harm.
You've got ideals.
You're something else.
Minus twenty degrees.
The easternmost point of our country.
You're from Guangxi.
Do you have any idea what that means?
I don't know.
But I just feel that this place
will have miracles happen.
Sha Tang.
Wake up.
wake up.
Sha Tang.
You're awake.
You still came.
If I hadn't come,
you would have frozen to death in the mountains.
You took them off yourself. It has nothing to do with me.
The pants are still on.
Hypothermia is no small matter.
Lie down.
What are you doing?
Stones.
To warm up.
You need to absorb heat now.
Tell me when they cool down.
How are you feeling? Any better?
Your clothes are dry. Put them on.
Why don't you...
It's not like I haven't seen it before.
Where is this place?
Cuoluozi.
What is Cuoluozi?
You don't know what Cuoluozi is?
Let me explain it to you.
Well, Cuoluozi
In the earliest times of our Hezhe people,
it was used to shelter hunters from wind and rain.
But aren't people not hunting anymore now?
That's exactly what I asked my grandfather.
This Cuoluozi was built by my grandfather.
My grandfather said,
this Cuoluozi is built here
to also help people who occasionally get lost
save their lives.
Right, lost people.
Then I should thank your grandfather.
Shouldn't you be thanking me?
If it weren't for me
coming here every now and then to replenish food,
you'd be starving today.
Thank you too.
Received.
If I had known that photo
would cause you so much trouble,
I definitely wouldn't have posted it.
I'm sorry.
I forgive you.
It's my fault for not understanding the weather.
rashly climbing the mountain.
Now you've come to rescue me,
and ended up trapped here.
That's right.
Didn't I tell you earlier?
It's quite scary in these mountains at night.
it's quite dangerous.
Since we're here, let's make the best of it.
Tell me about yourself.
Why are you so determined to find that white bear?
Actually,
it's not an ordinary white bear.
I know.
It's an Asian black bear
with albinism.
A child of the moon.
Hold on a moment.
Let me show you something.
This is what I photographed in Inner Mongolia.
An albino gazelle.
This is an albino peacock I photographed in Yunnan.
This is so beautiful, isn't it?
You think it's beautiful too.
There are even more beautiful ones after this.
An albino wolf.
An albino owl.
This is an albino chimpanzee.
An albino dolphin.
This is an albino lobster.
An albino lobster.
I know about this one.
An albino monkey.
What's wrong?
To take this photo,
I stayed in the mountains for a whole month.
I missed the only chance
to win an award in my life so far.
That's quite a pity.
It's not a pity.
Because this is my dream.
Dream.
In my studio,
from this window to this door,
there's a wall this big.
I've put a map on it.
I've pinned all the albino animals I've photographed across the country
according to where they were found.
All of them are on there.
You're planning to travel all over China.
Of course I'm going to travel all over China.
I want to fill up that map.
Then hold an exhibition.
Through this exhibition,
I want more people
to recognize these albino spirits.
I want to say
albino animals are not ugly.
I think they're pretty cool.
I think you're pretty cool now.
Sha Tang,
I'll definitely help you find the white bear.
After I find this albino bear,
I can fill in
the last blank spot on my map.
Then I can hold the exhibition.
After the exhibition,
I'll donate all the proceeds
to albinism organizations.
Because I think albinism organizations
and what they do
are even cooler than me.
I think I'm pretty cool now too.
I'm cool too.
We're a cool combination.
Cool girls.
Cool boys.
Let's have some soup.
It's delicious.
Although I previously wanted to use him as a shield,
however,
in my date with Bai Xiong,
having him join us
isn't so bad either.
Didn't you say three days?
How many sets of three days has it been now?
Give me just a few more days,
I'll get photos of Bai Xiong and go back immediately.
There's no room for negotiation, Sha Tang.
The other party has already filed a lawsuit.
You must come back and resolve this matter yourself.
But I've already found
the person who photographed the polar bear.
And she promised me
that she would definitely help me find the polar bear.
Can I come back as soon as I photograph the polar bear?
Impossible.
The studio has already been shut down.
You need to come back first.
Let's resolve this matter.
After that, you can go wherever you want.
Is that okay?
Three more days.
I'll come back whether I find the bear or not.
I'll trust you one last time.
If you can't make it back in time,
you'll have to face the consequences yourself.
Sha Tang.
Where are you going?
The brewery.
We've had over three thousand cases returned just this morning.
What are we going to do?
Dad,
what's going on?
This is all minor stuff.
You call this minor?
Take a look at this.
How many cases have been returned this morning?
Returns? What does that mean?
Someone's poaching our business.
Explain it clearly.
I heard someone's become the agent for Qianweina Beer.
They've even bought out several of our local breweries,
acquired them.
and opened up their sales channels.
They're even coming to my bar to promote their products,
saying they'll only sell their beer.
Who do they think they are?
You can go back first.
We'll...
We'll find a way to solve this.
Manyue,
the market conditions aren't good right now.
This kind of thing happens often.
Besides,
they're a big brand, a big manufacturer.
Our Liangjiang Beer is an old brand.
It's normal that we can't compete with them.
It's normal.
We'll keep going for as long as we can,
for as long as we can.
Dad.
Sha Tang.
Let me help you.
Two heads are better than one.