Next up,
actor Kyoji Tachibana has announced
that he will suspend his activities
to focus on cancer treatment…
This announcer
has a nice voice, doesn't he?
Yes, I agree.
…He is doing well
and has already begun--
Are you okay, Mr. Hotta?
My apologies.
Don't push yourself too hard.
You have the World Athletics coming up.
Okay.
There is a tumor on the left side
of the hypopharynx, in the pyriform sinus.
Our tests have confirmed
that it is malignant.
The tumor is located
close to the vocal cords.
Cancer…
Hypopharyngeal cancer.
Luckily, it was detected early,
so the tumor is barely two centimeters.
It's at stage one.
However, in your case,
it's a mucoepidermoid carcinoma.
A very rare type of cancer.
MUCOEPIDERMOID CARCINOMA
A TYPE OF CANCER TISSUE
A MALIGNANT TUMOR
THAT MAINLY OCCURS IN SALIVARY GLANDS
Do I need surgery…
on my throat?
Yes.
We'll excise the affected part completely.
Excise?
What about my voice?
Because of long-term effects,
you might not be able to return to work.
Mr. Hotta, I understand how you feel.
But, we have a great chance
of completely removing it through surgery.
This type of cancer is rare
and does not respond well to radiation.
You should undergo surgery
before it grows or spreads.
That is the--
This hospital has a General Medicine
Department, does it not?
I'd like to consult
with a general physician.
I'd like a second opinion.
Yes, the voice-over in
the World Athletics ad is my dad.
He's on a lot lately, and you can hear him
on jumbo screens everywhere.
But he hardly talks at home,
I can barely tell when he's around.
Wow, I didn't picture him that way.
People ask me things like,
"Is your dad an announcer?"
Huh? Koto, behind you.
What?
You were home!
He's so quiet, like no one is there.
You're home.
Yeah.
This is my dad, whom I'm so proud of!
I'm cheering for you
and the World Athletics.
Thank you.
Oh, did you know…
Noboru Akaike, General Physician.
Alongside his patients,
he searches for light
among the darkness of uncertainty.
He's a doctor who treats the person,
not just the disease.
Please…
Patients suffering from diseases,
other hospitals couldn't diagnose…
What kind of person do you think
makes for an excellent surgeon?
That would be someone who does not waver.
A swift decision maker
who doesn't waver upon their decision.
That's what I've been teaching him.
Not with words, but by having him
silently watch and memorize the images.
So, without me telling him,
he figured out where to look on his own.
He's my pride and joy.
He has a bright future.
The General Medicine Department?
Yes.
He wants a second opinion.
Surgery is best
for tumors in the early stages.
- I don't need third-party opinions--
- Wait.
Why not try a different angle.
Come in.
- You're from the Surgical--
- My patient wants a second opinion.
Hypopharyngeal cancer.
Yoshikazu Hotta, 53 years old.
An announcer?
He's refusing surgery.
Considering his job,
to undergo throat surgery would take
a significant amount of resolve.
Got it.
Whether it's surgery,
or some other option,
I will speak with the patient,
shining a light on all available paths
so he can come to a decision.
There's only one path.
In his case,
surgery is the most reliable option.
There are no other alternatives.
No other alternatives?
I'm not asking for a discussion,
I need you to persuade him.
He needs to get the surgery
as soon as possible.
GENERAL MEDICINE
You've really got it easy, huh?
Are you jealous?
You bet. General Medicine
doesn't have any patients.
Yes, we do.
A surgical patient wants a second opinion.
- Surgical?
- Dr. Kojiro.
Togo Junior? That's scary.
He must understand
the necessity of General Medicine.
His dad publicly stated his intent
to shut down General Medicine.
Sounds like a conspiracy.
Conspiracy?
Something's different with you.
General Medicine…
Was it working with Dr. Tokushige?
"Renewed petition for 24-hour
pediatric emergency system."
Even though it was rejected…
How adorbs.
- What?
- In one second…
- Adorbs!
- Please stop.
…the world changes.
What a nice voice.
The world will witness
a new chapter in history.
- Good work.
- Good work, sir.
Oh, thanks.
Are you all right, sir? You look unwell.
It might be a lack of sleep.
Should I reschedule this afternoon?
No, I'm fine.
Sometimes you have to push yourself.
Take care.
Thank you.
GENERAL MEDICINE DEPARTMENT
Come in.
Have a seat.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Tokushige, General Physician.
And I'm Takino, also a general physician.
Nice to meet you.
First of all, how is your throat?
It stings when I swallow saliva, and…
the longer I talk,
the more uncomfortable it gets.
I see. That must affect your work.
I watch your afternoon show.
Thank you.
I watched Dr. Akaike's documentary.
You're the narrator, right?
That show gave me the push I needed
to become a general physician.
What? Really?
Yes. "The Modern Red Beard."
I'm not sure about that…
Excuse me?
Sorry about that.
Dr. Akaike is like a mentor to me.
- Mentor?
- Yes.
Can we go back to the topic at hand?
Yes, you're right.
I'm glad.
"Treating people, not diseases."
At first, I wanted to go see Dr. Akaike.
But I didn't know where to find him.
I see.
Doctor.
Yes.
About conservative radiation therapy…
I already explained it to him once.
There are patients who lived
five to ten years without recurrence
while keeping their voices.
That's true,
there have been cases like that.
Limiting the irradiation range
can also minimize tissue damage.
It's less strain on the vocal cords
compared to surgery.
What you have
is a mucoepidermoid carcinoma,
which is resistant to radiation.
We must also consider the risk
of major surgery if it gets worse.
If you decide to undergo surgery now,
you can expect a full recovery.
I don't want surgery.
I understand the impact
it will have on your job.
But if you hesitate any further…
the cancer will worsen.
If I lose my voice…
it's the same as me dying.
It's my voice.
I've nurtured it all this time.
I'm afraid if I do this…
I might not get my voice back.
Mr. Hotta.
Have you told your family about this?
If I tell them
before I've processed everything
it will only confuse them.
Mr. Hotta, we will help you to organize
your thoughts and feelings.
But…
please remember this one thing.
Whichever path you choose…
your life will carry on.
I asked you to persuade him
to undergo surgery.
Did I have to explain in more detail?
No.
He's lucky the cancer was detected early.
He ought to have surgery
as soon as possible for a full recovery.
Exactly.
But the reason it was detected early
was that he took his voice seriously.
The slightest anomaly
lead him to get examined.
"If I lose my voice…
it's the same as me dying."
Sit down.
Dr. Kojiro,
I understand why you chose
the path that leads to saving his life.
However, you cannot perform surgery
without considering the patient's wishes.
The chances of losing
all vocal cord function
and becoming unable to speak are low.
Giving in to patients
who fear this remote possibility
and postponing surgery increases the risk.
While we're wavering,
the cancer will get worse
and chances of his voice
deteriorating further increase.
I understand how you feel, Dr. Kojiro.
However,
no matter what treatment it is,
don't you need…
his acceptance?
Acceptance?
Dr. Togo.
Has the date for the surgery been decided?
My apologies,
we should have been able
to resolve this without involving you.
Shall we cool down…
It's no problem.
If we had, we could have avoided
giving the patient any false hope.
What?
We are the specialists for this case.
All you have to do is understand
our plan and convince the patient.
That's your job. Am I wrong?
You don't have to…
You're right.
I'm glad you agree.
I'm counting on you to take the fastest
and best path to save the patient.
- Yes, sir.
- Good day.
What's up with him?
Come on…
You too!
What?
If you are going to be that loud
why bother closing the door.
Seriously?
The Surgical Department is not wrong
in suggesting surgery as the best option.
- I can understand.
- But…
Go ahead.
Isn't it a general physician's job…
to talk with patients and support them?
I wanted you to talk back.
It's difficult, isn't it.
Really difficult.
Dr. Tokushige is
a smarter doctor than expected.
If he had emotionally reacted
and rejected our opinion,
we could have claimed
he works poorly with other departments.
General Medicine is dangerous after all.
Can't we all just get along?
Wasn't it you who started
the General Medicine Department
without consulting Dr. Togo?
You know what, Toyohashi?
Sometimes, the truth hurts--
The truth is the truth.
But it is surprising
that the Surgical Department
would allow a second opinion
from General Medicine.
"We respect you,"
and, "We're not excluding you
based on our feelings."
They have to make gestures like this.
So, if Tokushige made
even the slightest mistake,
they could argue that the department
wasn't necessary after all.
I'm stumped.
Everyone has their own idea
of what's right.
Yeah.
Tokushige, whose fault do you think…
Dr. Akaike!
Sir!
Can I borrow money?
Come in.
The director was crying.
Because you don't listen.
You mustn't lie to a general physician.
You could use
your mentor's advice, don't you?
You shouldn't say those things yourself.
What?!
Why?
Stop looking like you just saw a ghost.
You do look like one.
Boo…
What's that for?
The island is still lacking in everything.
It hasn't changed since you were there.
There are no nurses.
No transport helicopters, and no boats.
You came to talk to the director about it?
What I could use now
is an excellent subordinate.
You're just saying that to get your way.
Well, I'm almost done doing that, too.
What?
Tokushige.
Yes?
How wide is this path?
You're right…
An ambulance can't get through here.
There too.
Huh? Excuse me…
The diner's this way!
They're going to get lost again…
Talking to the street.
Wait! If you go any further,
you can't turn back!
This way, Doctor. This way.
It's this way!
It's now obvious to me
that you're master and disciple.
Sorry.
I also finally understand.
A master and disciple resemble each other.
What?
Furrowing eyebrows.
Mr. Yokobuki!
Here's your order!
- Thank you.
- Sure.
His did that a lot on the island.
Dr. Tokushige too?
He was so eager
to become a general physician
he came looking for me.
Really?
Let's not bring up the past.
- I want to know!
- I'm good.
You can talk about it while I'm gone.
- He ran off.
- Can I use the restroom?
- Sure.
- Yeah.
Tokushige hasn't changed a bit.
He's all smiles on the outside
and burning brightly in the inside.
Here you go.
You're in a dispute with Surgical, right?
I guess you could say that.
We want to respect the patient's wishes,
but as doctors, we can
also relate to Surgical's opinion.
It's difficult, right?
I totally understand Mr. Hotta's fears
about losing his voice.
Yeah.
I want to be there for him.
But he might end up dying by your side.
The role of a hospital's general physician
is supported by three pillars.
- Three pillars?
- Yeah.
The first one is that of a gatekeeper.
A hospital gatekeeper identifies a disease
and diagnoses based on consultation.
The pain you've been feeling…
is from a legitimate disease with a name.
Next is family medicine.
You'll work with local communities
to watch over patients post-discharge.
Okay, I'll get to it.
That's what social workers are for.
Last but not least, conductors.
This applies to your case.
Collaborating with specialists
to treat the patient.
Specialists tend
to have strong personalities.
It's not uncommon among
surgeons to be "scissor-happy."
We clash because we share
the same desire to help as they do.
Desire to help…
Her face looks all squished up.
Really?
I wouldn't call her a young lady.
This is on the house, Doc.
Thanks.
I think Rokuro feels the same way.
Rokuro?
Togo Senior.
His approach is a bit rigid.
This is on the house.
Dr. Tokushige.
I think you're overdoing it
with the diplomacy.
Oh, really?
Things won't go smoothly.
I don't believe it. No way.
Tokushige.
What do you want?
What do I want?
Yeah.
What the patient wants
and what the doctor wants…
a general physician…
stands in between those two.
That's why…
what I want the most?
I can't lose sight of it.
You're a greedy one, aren't you?
I don't want to hear that from you.
Let's eat.
Yum!
UOTORA GENERAL HOSPITAL
Let's go out and eat, Osu.
No, thanks.
But it's sushi.
Sushi…
Hey! No, thank you!
That look of scorn is so adorbs!
- I'll sue you someday.
- Oh, really?
- Let's go.
- Dr. Chayasaka.
Can you summarize Mr. Tanaka's
pre-op IC and cardiac records?
Okay, I'll do it.
Good.
Why don't you mess with Dr. Kojiro?
He's no fun.
He's only parroting his father.
A daddy's boy.
Say, "ah."
Dad.
Can I post this?
WORLD ATHLETICS! GO JAPAN!
Sure.
You're back! It must have been
a long meeting.
Your dinner…
It's fine, I had a bit at work.
Dad hardly talks at home.
He's taking care of his voice.
Speech therapy, immune system…
ARE THERE HERBS AND SUPPLEMENTS
THAT WORK AGAINST CANCER?
Supplements…
It's spreading
slightly faster than expected.
As the tumor grows,
the area to be excised will also increase.
Mr. Hotta has a family.
Could they help in convincing him
to get the surgery?
Apparently, he hasn't informed them.
Oh my…
During his next visit,
I'll bring it up again
while going over the results.
Please do.
Tell him, he doesn't have a choice.
Neither do you.
We don't have time
to waver with the patient.
I'm not wavering.
- Then…
- But…
I need to discuss something with
Mr. Hotta before we rush him into surgery.
"Treating people, not diseases"?
A doctor's job is not so easy
as to save people with ideals alone.
Stop it, you two.
- Sorry about that.
- It's okay.
I think we're in the same boat.
Really?
Indeed, a doctor who only says
what people want to hear
may be being indulgent, but…
one who imposes his version of reality
without listening to his patients…
is no better.
May I sit here?
Go ahead.
It's not like it's my property.
That's true.
All right.
I'm not going to apologize.
Neither am I.
I meant what I said.
So…
thank you.
I'm glad I got the chance
to speak openly with you, Dr. Kojiro.
Saving his life
while preserving his voice.
That's just empty rhetoric.
No matter how much you worry…
it probably won't change
the outcome of the surgery.
However…
it doesn't end with the surgery.
Mr. Hotta's life will carry on.
Is that why you're saying
we need his acceptance?
Yes.
And the same…
goes for you too.
Even if you push your opinion
just to get that lesion out,
you cannot say
that you've cured the disease.
Wouldn't that be sad?
It may be hard
to get both the patient and doctor…
to take the same path.
But I believe that it's
our responsibility as doctor's
who deal in life and death.
My father once told me something similar.
"What kind of work does a doctor do?"
When I decided to study medicine…
You can be whatever you want.
But it's not easy being a doctor.
You'll be dealing with lives every day.
That's a responsibility…
you can't run away from.
Our methods may be completely different,
but we're both talking
about the same life.
Surgeries…
are the responsibility
of the Surgical Department.
I fully understand that.
Therefore…
I'd like you and Mr. Hotta…
to talk again without fear.
To gain both sides' acceptance?
We connect patients with specialists.
We work together to ensure that
everyone moves in the same direction.
That…
is the job of a general physician.
Kotoha.
I didn't see anything.
I don't know your password.
Yeah?
You can't just come in like this.
I have my work stuff here.
Tell me.
I know that you've been
feeling down lately.
I need to prepare
for tomorrow's recording.
This place…
When I failed my entrance exam,
you took me there.
Mr. Hotta.
Based on the test results,
I believe that surgery
is the best option for you.
Please, allow me to explain
the post-op recovery process to you.
Depending on the severity
of post-op long-term effects,
you'll have to stop speaking for a while,
so you'll need to take time off work.
Should any long-term effects remain
such as vocal cord paralysis,
you might require long-term rehab
or additional surgeries.
But…
will my voice completely recover?
I cannot say for sure.
The tumor is located
near your vocal cords, but…
given its current size,
the odds of total removal are high.
The speed of your decision
will heavily influence your future.
I understand that it may seem scary.
That being said,
you can only do your job
because you're alive.
If you lose your life,
you lose your voice too.
I know that!
You don't have to tell me that!
We all know that!
Nevertheless…
Are you okay?
I'll get you water.
I'm fine!
I have a wife and a daughter.
Sorry.
As I thought.
When you go all out,
you're voice is very powerful.
My voice…
is my treasure.
Treasure?
No one has ever called it that, but…
It's the only thing…
that I've been able
to nurture well all my life.
I was nervous the first time
I stood in front of a mic.
My voice trembled.
But it was my moment of truth.
If I took the step,
my world would change.
Noboru Akaike, General Physician.
Alongside his patients,
he searches for light
among the darkness of uncertainty.
That's a wrap!
A lowly man like me
opened up a path with my voice.
I was so happy.
After lots of hard work,
my dream finally came true.
I wanted to tell my family right away.
I'm working the World Athletics.
What?
- As a commentator.
- What?!
That's amazing!
I'm so proud of you, Dad!
I won't be the dad she's proud of…
for much longer.
Why?
What?
I'm sorry.
It's unrelated to the treatment.
Go ahead.
Carry on.
My father is a doctor.
But, even if he quit…
he will still be my father.
We both looked at the sea.
Without saying a word.
Just sitting side by side…
Dad.
Yeah?
For some reason…
you look so cool today.
Thank you.
Doctor.
Yes?
I've used my voice…
to care for my family.
Doctor…
I'm scared.
As for your voice,
we cannot guarantee it'll make it through.
Be it surgery or treatment,
neither are easy paths.
However…
whichever path you choose,
I promise…
to be by your side to the very end.
That's the kind of…
doctor I want to be.
From now on,
your story and your voice…
Let me hear them.
Once again, I'm Yoshikazu Hotta.
Today, I have something to tell you.
Please bear with me.
I have been diagnosed
with hypopharyngeal cancer.
Hence, I will be taking a break
to undergo surgery and treatment.
To be honest, I'm scared.
It's hard for me to say that
I cannot guarantee that I'll be back.
A MESSAGE FROM OUR ANNOUNCER, MR. HOTTA
This decision…
Whether or not…
I made the right choice.
The answer to that…
will need time to be revealed.
Should…
Should the worst happen.
Even if I lose my voice.
We can still communicate.
That's how I've come to feel.
At last…
I've taken a step forward.
I…
want to live to the fullest.
SALINE DRIP
Thank you in advance.
You see, I…
Yes?
I'm a specialist in head and neck surgery.
Yes.
I have performed
this procedure 15 times before.
Is that a lot?
I have faith in my surgical skills.
I can count on you,
because you don't lie, Doctor.
Now, please inhale the oxygen.
We're now applying anesthesia.
UOTORA GENERAL HOSPITAL
Dr. Akaike!
What took you?
How could you do this
to your dearest mentor?
You can't call yourself that--
Mr. Hotta's operation was a success.
Really?
It's been nice meeting you, sir.
Yeah.
Good work.
No matter how long you live,
you will always have doubts.
No matter…
which path you choose,
there'll be regrets.
Everything is right
and wrong at the same time.
GET WELL SOON, MR. HOTTA!
THE LA 2028 OLYMPICS ARE WAITING!
Family members, please come this way.
I have paperwork to take care of.
Thank you.
Please be careful not to talk.
Take some time off.
In one second…
the world changes.
The world will witness
a new chapter in history.
The Tokyo 2025
World Athletics Championships.
Tickets now on sale…
Before the surgery, we spoke a little.
He gave me a chuckle.
Words alone cannot save lives.
Are the numbers for next month's OR
utilization rate out yet?
If you don't check the numbers,
you have no ground
to stand on during negotiations.
Understood, sir.
There are 18 departments.
All sorts of rights and wrongs
in the hospital.
That's why they have us,
the 19th department.
Yes.
What's this?
You still had such
an adorable side to you.
Stop that.
See you around.
Take care!
I will.
Dr. Tokushige,
do you like traditional sweets?
Of course.
There'll be a week-long
fair in front of the station.
Really?
Diagnosed with diabetes,
he's been seeing
an internist for six months.
We're here to treat his diabetes,
not provide marriage counseling.
Dr. Kayama will examine Kota,
and Dr. Takino will examine Sachi.
Try to empathize more.
I can't empathize with patients.
Take a step back
and visualize the invisible.
- Why are you giving up?
- I want to understand Kota and Sachi.
People suffer from both
the disease and the illness.
Subtitle translation by: Frederick