"Hot Blood & Outburst of Rage"
Look who's here.
Xun's here.
We're celebrating right now.
What a warrior.
You look different.
Way skinnier than before.
I trying to lose some weight.
Why? For what reasons.
I'm escaping the military draft.
Did you? Did you make it?
No. I give up.
Well, you do look incredibly skinny.
Really? Can you tell?
Your face looked entirely different.
My face?
Yes. It's so much different.
This is yours.
Me?
We are going to celebrate.
Magnificent, mighty, serious,
outspoken and upright.
Quiet, firm, precise.
(A man shall be drafted on January 1
of the following year)
(when he reaches the age of 18.)
(Man whose hemoglobin is lower than 12gm/dl
shall be exempted from the draft.)
(Secretly undergoing a venesection
before the army's physical inspection.)
Hey!
What are you guys doing in here?
Let's get the hell out of here. Cigarettes?
Come on.
Why're you guys here?
Come smoke.
Moron.
Don't you have any place to go?
Shit! You homeless.
I'm homeless? Go fuck yourself.
Shit man.
Hey!
Stop messing around in this room.
Higher!
Shit.
You look like hell.
I'm doing everything I can.
Right after the PLA
military drill yesterday...
they have fired eleven Dongfeng
series ballistic missiles
into the territorial Sea of Taiwan.
The scale and types
of ammunition are escalating...
comparing to the third Taiwan
Strait crisis around 1996,
the ammunition fired
by the PLA were ten Dongfeng 15.
Signifying the Communist Party of China
are taking higher measures.
Specialists of the PLA is concerned...
the purpose of this military drill...
is to take control
over the Taiwan's Strait,
and the territorial waters demarcation
also the power supplies.
According to a military specialist
believing that it's very unlikely to...
You've changed.
Since when?
Since the first year of college.
Everyone has changed.
But,
you don't see things...
the way you used to.
What do you mean?
You don't really...
hang out with friends anymore.
I remembered you used to go to parties.
You seemed to be having fun with everyone.
And you don't see yourself as different,
or excluded from others.
♪ I'm holding a rifle,
right on my shoulder. ♪
♪ I have pulled the trigger,
and how the bullet shines. ♪
Don't you want to be patriotic?
Huh?
Maybe. I don't know.
You love Taiwan?
I love Taiwan.
I love Taipei.
You should love 'Taiwan'.
Taiwan Number one.
♪ I'm holding a rifle,
right on my shoulder. ♪
♪ I have pulled the trigger,
and how the bullet shines. ♪
♪ I'm holding a rifle,
right on my shoulder. ♪
♪ I have pulled the trigger,
and how the bullet shines. ♪
Liao.
Have you seen Xun lately?
What's the matter?
The robe for the ceremony has arrived.
I had Xun's.
But he rarely spends time
at school or in the dorm.
I don't know what to do with it.
Hmmm...
I can bring the robe to him.
One more thing, when you see him, ask him.
When is he coming back?
Why?
Well, they announced that...
We have to return the room next week.
We have to clear up this room
by the end of the week.
Go have a seat.
Why is he having a seat?
♪ You're holding a rifle. ♪
♪ The rifle you're holding is really big. ♪
Come on,
this pole right here is your rifle.
Hurry up.
Is the sharper edge facing forward?
Yes.
How do I settle this?
The left side?
I am having my time here.
I think you look boring.
No.
I just joined you guys.
No, You didn't.
This shitty tank is all we have.
- We're doomed to lost the war.
- Just listen to yourself for one second.
I'm narrating the story.
Do you want to play the guitar?
I don't know how to play it.
I'll teach you.
Here's C chord.
C chord, E chord.
Use your left hand.
Here you go.
You do know how to play.
Listen, Liao is playing.
I don't know any.
5678.
♪ I had a rifle, right on my shoulder. ♪
Hold it for a sec.
Are you ready?
Easy.
I'll stop.
OK. I'm quitting.
Are you alright?
What’s the matter?
Nothing.
I want to start taking the medication
from that friend of yours.
But we have done so far. All the fasting.
You might be unqualified
in the first inspection.
What if I don't?
What if I failed to escape?
What if they want me
to do another inspection.
I must be unqualified
in the first inspection.
We'll manage.
Do you remember my sophomore year?
I was going to quit college.
Yes.
Were you painful during that time?
I came around.
Feng was talking me out of it.
He said I'm confused.
But you have always been supportive. Huh?
Including these "stealth.“
You know...
Feng, he's just being possessive.
Maybe that counts as selfish.
I guess?
I was thinking...
I like friends and all from college.
Everyone is nice.
But still, I felt lost.
Maybe it's something to do
with your identity.
Maybe that's the reason?
I guess you're right. "My identity".
To accept all the support
and be truly understanding.
Not just giving out some random thoughts.
Or tell me what's right or wrong.
Maybe it's not only about "Identity"?
Whom to trust?
It has something to do with...
perhaps... Love?
Maybe I'm exaggerating.
No, you're not.
I get what you're saying.
I really do.
I have it.
What we had discussed.
The pills to lower the hemoglobin level.
Really?
How?
Shit.
I can't believe this. Hold it for a sec.
You have to eat healthier this week.
Make sure to do all the routines properly.
And...
you might... bleed.
Bleed?
Yes.
I'm not really sure, but.
I don't think we should be too worried.
What's wrong?
It's working. Your nose is bleeding.
My nose?
Yes.
Shit.
Let me help.
What?
I'm bleeding.
I've never had a nosebleed.
Does it hurt?
No, it doesn't.
It's kind of scary. Fuck.
But it works.
Thank you. You're awesome.
Shit. It works.
Thank you.
Sure.
I mean... hmmm...
What I meant is that you're awesome, but...
I truly appreciate everything.
I'm sorry.
What for?
There's nothing you need to apologize for.
No, actually I do.
What we're doing here, it's not opened.
I'm so sorry.
What do you mean not opened.
What are you talking about.
You're acting weird.
I know that, but...
I've always known that I had this thing...
and I'm really sorry.
I felt ashamed and embarrassed cause of it.
But I know there's nothing to be ashamed
or embarrassed by.
And this... Uneasy Affection.
These might be the reasons why you
always think that I'm on your side.
And being really supportive.
You must have felt something.
Maybe it's just friendship,
but I think there's something more.
I felt lying and being dishonest...
But, I want to start from...
Being really open with you,
or even confessing that I'm...
I want to make an apology for you.
I feel so sorry, and I don't know
what just happened to me.
I just want to say that I'm sorry, and...
I really want to be on your side.
I'm sorry.
Stop.
I'm really sorry.
I should have never told you all of this.
Would you please stop
saying that you're sorry?
Are you mad?
No.
I better be leaving.
Thank you.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
I should have never said any of these.
Just forget everything.
Fuck. Stop apologizing.
Sorry.
That's Ok.
I'm off.
Ready?
Go.
I had a rifle, right on my shoulder.
I have pulled the trigger,
and how the bullet shines.
I had a rifle, right on my shoulder.
I have pulled the trigger,
and how the bullet shines.
How the bullet shines.
This gets me dizzy.
What's wrong?
It hurts.
What hurts?
We haven't even been playing that long.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
What's wrong?
Huh?
I...
Are you alright?
Sorry. I don't know what I'm doing.
Magnificent, mighty, serious,
outspoken and upright.
Quiet, firm, calm, restrained.
Join us. Come over here.
Come on.
Come.
What're you doing?
What do you mean coward?
Coward?
You're a coward.
Coward.
Mushy.
You're insane.
Are you a faggot?
Faggot.
You're tough.
Hey Liao. Are you a faggot?
Follow him.
Hurry up.
Join us.
Don't touch me.
What are you doing?
What?
What are you doing here?
That's my question? Why did you come?
What? Can't I come?
Get over here.
You're acting so weird.
You're being weird.
I'm being weird?
Are you just going to stand here?
What are you doing, Liao?
Stop it. Stop it.
Calm down. Liao!
Calm down.
Help me.
What's going on?
What's the matter with you?
Hey! What's the matter with you?
Why did you do that?
Are you alright?
Get your hands off me.
What's the matter with you?
Xun is bleeding.
Hey!