♫  Baby you, you are especially dazzling today  ♫
♫ A moment I didn't even expect ♫
[Where Your Eyes Linger]
Timing and Subtitles by the Where Your Eyes Linger Volunteer Team @ Viki.com
Did something bad happen to you?
No.
Then, why did you do that?
I don't like that bastard.
Kim Pil Hyun seemed fine.
And he's cute.
Look at yourself before calling someone cute.
Hey! Don't you remember getting caught in my armbar?
Now I might even fight better than you.
Really?
Then there must be no reason for me to keep being your bodyguard.
Didn't I tell you not to say something like that even as a joke?
Yeah, I'm sorry.
Let's have a bout today.
Okay.
Even though I was always by Tae Joo's side...
Aren't you coming?
Tae Joo was always...
above me.
Stop it!
Don't cause trouble again.
Why are you acting like this?
It's a joke.
I'm sorry.
[Episode 2 - A relationship of equals]
Wow, you have a really nice body.
We eat the same thing and hang out every day.
How is it like this?
It's not even the first nor second time you've seen it.
So what's with you suddenly?
- Who's that?
- I don't know.
- Take a look at it.
- No need.
Kang Gook?
Why did you give me a different phone number?
What is it?
Did you tell her?
- Why? Isn't it fun?
- It's not fun for me.
It's just a gift. Don't resent me later. I'm telling you to go ahead and experiment with everything you want.
Do it all.
Kang Gook's number is 010-892-3777. He said he gave you the wrong one. You can thank me later.
Is he your ideal type?
No, its a weird guy.
His name is Kang Gook, even his name is handsome.
Just give up.
Why?
It looks like a relationship that you shouldn't meddle in.
What does that mean?
When you become my age, you can see everything.
These two had a killer chemistry.
I think differently.
There's no going easy on the other, okay?
There's no way.
Did you reply?
I'm not going to do it.
Do it. It's an order.
You can't do this here. This is the only place where I can act impudently with you.
This is something I've never heard in my life.
Of course, you and I, there's nothing we—
Should I really kill you?
You'd be more at ease if you admit it. There's nothing we can do.
I'm going to touch your ear.
What's the matter?
You know I have to touch your ear to calm down.
Even then, it's a no.
But...
you should stop exercising your chest muscles.
If it's this much...
Oh...
Hey, are you okay?
I'm sorry, I didn't do it on purpose.
- As expected.
"I didn't do it on purpose."
Why? Did he call?
- He didn't do it on purpose.
- Well, of course, I'd be happy to get a handsome son-in-law.
Catch just one of the two.
My goodness...
It would be nice if it goes well for them two, though.
Mom, why are you like this, really?
My heart fluttered for the first time in a while.
Usually, when you are in between best friends,
it's uncomfortable and tiresome.
Ah, it's uncomfortable!
I said I'm sorry.
That's right. You won. You did win.
I can't study or eat properly.
Timing and Subtitles by the Where Your Eyes Linger Volunteer Team @ Viki.com
You have to make me something tasty for tomorrow.
Okay.
But what do I do about washing up?
What do you mean, "What do I do?"
You can just wash up well, making sure you don't make it wet.
How can I wash my hair with one hand?
And that too, using my left hand.
You can do it.
But you can just do it for me.
I don't want to. I really don't want to.
Why?
I want to wash up neatly. You know I hate feeling tacky.
I'm your bodyguard, not your butler.
Dammit, you bodyguard.
You sprained my arm and all. Dammit, it's so uncomfortable.
Just taking off my jacket is difficult. How am I going to do from now on?
I hate you, Kang Gook. I really hate you.
I know it's a bit too soon for that, but what are you doing this Saturday?
I'm not doing anything. Let's hang out.
[I know it's a bit too soon for that, but what are you doing this Saturday?]
[I'm not doing anything. Let's hang out.]
That's why I asked you to help me wash up.
Ah, it's cold.
It tickles.
Bear with it.
♫ I see you ♫
♫ In a time that cannot come true ♫
♫  And I feel you  ♫
♫ In my heart that lost its light  ♫
♫  Behind your back moving away  ♫
[Where Your Eyes Linger]
♫ I feel the sadness of being drawn apart ♫
♫ Even if tomorrow comes where I can't see you ♫
♫ I should probably endure it ♫