♫ Baby you, you are especially dazzling today ♫
♫ A moment that I didn't even expect ♫
[Where Your Eyes Linger]
Timing and Subtitles by the Where Your Eyes Linger Volunteer Team @ Viki.com
We fought sometimes, too.
♫ Suddenly, far away ♫
And then we reconciled quickly.
♫ In the shadow ♫
This time, too, just like before, just like that...
Your call cannot be connected, you will be redirected—
We just have to make up.
♫ Bring me out from the emptiness I am locked in ♫
[Episode 7 - Reconciliation]
Taejoo...
Don't play around.
Taejoo.
Han Taejoo!
You are being redirected to voicemail.
Chairman,
I think Taejoo has been kidnapped.
I have his last location, but his phone is currently turned off.
My apologies. I will go to his last location.
Pilhyeon, have you been in touch with Taejoo?
No, I haven't. Why? Did something happen?
Hey, meet me.
I'm not in that kind of situat—
It's about Taejoo.
Kang Gook.
What's the matter?
I don't know too well either.
Say it right now.
I didn't know that it'll go this far.
If you don't want to die, tell me what happened. Right now!
I told him.
I told him that...
I saw you two kissing in the backyard.
The chairman ordered my dad...
So, I mean, I was keeping an eye on you two just a little bit.
Damn it! This is so shameful.
That was the only way for my dad to not get fired.
I'm sorry.
That's a relief.
What?
That means the chairman took him.
Then that's a relief.
Han Taejoo is going to England.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean for this to happen,
but don't tell him that I did it.
It'll put me in a tight spot.
It hurts like hell!
This trash...
Kim Pilhyeon, you trash.
I shouldn't have made you two live together.
Please don't hit Kang Gook, Sir.
Only I was like that.
Only you?
Only I liked him.
I shouldn't have...
raised something like you in the first place.
That's true.
You always fail.
- A son that's weak just like his mother—
- Don't speak badly about Mom.
Kang Gook has arrived.
Taejoo would probably...
have known before I did
since he suffered a separation before.
♫ I see you ♫
♫ In a time that cannot come true ♫
♫ And I feel you ♫
While for me, I had to stand in front of the separation...
♫ In my heart that lost its light ♫
...to finally understand it, then.
♫ At your back moving farther away ♫
♫ I feel the sadness of being drawn apart ♫
Even if I become someone's shadow,
I don't want to lose that person.
♫ I have to endure it ♫
♫ Can't stop the loneliness in this place without you,  ♫
♫ will I be able to breathe? ♫
♫ Can't stop the loneliness, I can't stop it ♫
♫ Please wait for me ♫
And that this is called love.
♫ Dwelling in the sorrow of the time without you ♫
♫ I am waiting for the day you will come back ♫
That in front of love, you cannot hear any form of reason.
Because all of this is a first for me.
Now, I understand.
[Where Your Eyes Linger]
Timing and Subtitles by the Where Your Eyes Linger Volunteer Team @ Viki.com
I told you he's really handsome.
Hey, what if there are no seats today again?
I'm telling you, it's crazy these days.
Give me a second. I want to put on some lipstick.
Hey.
Just a second.
Wait! Wait!
- How do I look?
- You're pretty.
You're pretty, too. Come on.
It's done, Hyemi.
Your rice cakes are here.
Hey, your customers arrived.
Welcome!
I love you.
Me, too.