OUR MOVIE
ANY RESEMBLANCE
TO ACTUAL PEOPLE, PLACES,
OR MEDICAL CONDITIONS
IS COINCIDENTAL.
CHILD ACTORS
WERE ALWAYS SUPERVISED
AND FILMED
UNDER OFFICIAL GUIDELINES.
Don't move if you want to live.
Sorry…
…but I'm just too tired.
You'll have to die quickly.
What the?
Wasn't I supposed to be the one to faint?
Gosh, she's driving me nuts.
Hey, you there.
You're not the one who got shot.
Hang on. Something's not right.
We should call an ambulance.
Are you all right?
Yes, we're in Sangam-dong…
It's not like I lived in fear,
but I've known this would happen
all along.
EPISODE 2
Can you see the ocean?
There's no ocean here.
Oh?
That's strange.
I definitely see an ocean here.
What? Where did you get this thing?
I told you to rest
since you have a lot of tests tomorrow.
It's okay. I'll take her downstairs later.
Wow, the weather is so nice by the sea!
How is it this nice?
It's a perfect day for a tan.
Ta-da!
Come closer.
Are you in?
Give it to me. I'll do it.
Here, now. Say cheese.
We're on vacation at the beach.
My mom was sick.
Not any normal patient,
but a strange one at that.
It's all right.
It's only us here because of the rain.
I know! It's so fun!
Then do you want to do something
even more fun?
♪ La, la, la, la. ♪
♪ La, la. ♪
Is that the medicine
that makes you feel better?
- That's not medicine.
- What?
It's grape juice.
That's grape juice?
Sure.
Mom.
Grapes are purple.
And bananas are yellow.
But when they're peeled?
Hmm.
White.
That's right.
Grapes are purple,
but they're that color when you peel them.
You're always trying to trick me, Mom.
What, you're too grown
to fall for it anymore?
It's so hard to make my daughter laugh.
It's not funny.
You shouldn't laugh either.
It hurts you when you laugh.
Daeum.
I read somewhere
that the DNA that makes you cry
when you're sad
is the same as the one
that makes you smile
when you're happy.
You have to eat, Mom.
Daeum.
It's going to be okay,
for you
and for Dad.
Dad.
Yes?
What's "genetics"?
Lie down now.
I hoped she'd get
the best of her mom, not this.
My mom still lives inside me,
and that's the one special thing
that only I get to have.
That's how my doctor father
taught eight-year-old me
about genetics.
THE WORLD OF CONTEMPORARY
THEATER THROUGH FRIDA KAHLO
May this journey
bring happiness.
And…
may it never return.
For a moment,
I felt like I had become Frida Kahlo.
No,
I actually did become Frida Kahlo.
You're awesome, Daeum!
You're the best, Daeum!
In a life too short to live my own story…
Ladies and gentlemen…
…the chance to perform
many different lives
is exactly what I wanted to do.
I'll run with everything I've got!
Great. Good luck. Let's do it!
- Let's do it!
- Yeah!
Don't move if you want to live.
And so…
although I tried hard not to live in fear…
…I've known this was going to happen…
all along.
In the end,
I couldn't escape that grape juice either.
Drip.
On October 14, 2019,
Lee Daeum is drinking grape juice.
Slurp, slurp, slurp.
I still think I look cute today.
I knew death was around the corner for me.
I learned about the disease
when I was eight,
and had it by the time I turned 20.
Okay.
One, two, three.
And yet, the thing that keeps me going…
might just be the special part of my mom
she left behind.
Freestyle acting, Lee Daeum.
♪ Ari-ari sseuri-sseuri
Arariyo ♪
Lee Jeha.
LEE JEHA
PROFILE
LOVE IN WHITE
THE LATE LEE DUYOUNG'S
"LOVE IN WHITE"
NOW SHOWING AT CINEMA JONGNO
RESERVE TICKETS AT CINEMA JONGNO
Cinema Jongno?
You don't know me.
No, no.
I found him.
Yes?
Doc-doc-doc Doctor!
Hey, Da-da-da Daeum.
Thank you as always.
LOVE IN WHITE
Lee Jeha?
What's this, Doc?
Oh, just a movie
I was asked to consult for.
Put it down.
- Put it down.
- Can I meet him instead?
- Meet him? No. You take this back.
- No thank you.
Why are you being like this?
Please, just once.
Once or twice, I don't care.
I told you no!
I'm your consultant,
the terminal patient, Lee Daeum.
Your name,
it means "next"?
Yes.
Lee Daeum.
Ah.
GRAPE 100
Oh, grape juice. That's why.
You must really like grapes.
Dr. Kim said I should bring this for you.
Not grapes. Grape juice.
Especially when it's
on a "buy two, get one free" deal.
But someone happened to take it from me.
I actually told you I didn't need it.
Why didn't you say hi in the funeral home?
I wanted to focus on my sadness.
Focus on your… Okay.
Actually,
would you mind if I record this session?
I'd need to listen again
while I'm writing.
Actually,
do you mind if I film this?
It's a little hobby of mine.
All right.
Okay.
I heard from Dr. Kim
that you're very sick.
Do I look sick to you right now?
No.
I feel okay right now,
but when I'm really sick, it shows a lot.
That's why I can't do
everything I want to do.
What is it you want to do?
Adultery.
Premeditated serial murder.
- Sorry?
- I'd like to die sometime.
Maybe even become a ghost.
And then be reborn again.
Why do I have so many things
I want to do?
There is one job
where you can do all of that.
Yes, and that is my dream job.
Ah.
So you want to be an actress.
What do you do now?
Now? Well…
not much, as you can see.
I don't see a big film career
coming anytime soon,
unless I star in a hospice documentary.
Or if I'm playing a terminal patient.
The film, Love in White…
Well, you've seen it
at Cinema Jongno that time.
Not just that time.
It's my favorite movie that I regularly
go back to whenever I need to.
Every time I watch it, I bawl my eyes out.
It's my go-to tearjerker flick.
That's what melodramas are for.
Crying your heart out like that
makes you feel
like you had some epic love.
It's an illusion, I guess.
It tricks you into that illusion.
It's not an illusion.
Falling in love, and sharing that love…
Even if someone leaves
and someone gets left behind,
it'll all be okay
as long as there's love.
Watching that
gives me the strength to go on.
If that kind of love really does exist,
I want to experience it too.
And to do that, I have to stay alive.
So basically, Love in White is my chemo
and my radiation therapy and so on.
Is that really something to cry over?
My eyes are teary just talking about it.
I don't get it at all.
Aren't you leaving?
I'm bored, so I thought I'd walk you back.
- I'm okay.
- I'm okay too.
I said I'm fine.
I said I'm fine too.
If you really don't want to go,
how about a walk with me?
It wasn't even my funeral,
but I found myself taking in every detail.
What kind of face the family was making,
who was grieving.
I took the funeral director's card…
…and I started getting scared right then.
I'm not even dead yet,
but the thought of dying
felt like death itself.
Once you get sick,
your life is completely different
from before your illness.
There's a reason why
they say ignorance is bliss.
Slowly sinking into death,
being suffocated by fear…
You don't know what that is, do you?
I do know that not knowing is bliss.
Can I ask you something too?
Yes, go on.
In your version of Love in White…
does the ending…
stay the same?
No.
In the end…
In the end, she'll probably die.
That was the moment I realized…
maybe I can be the star of my own story,
as long as I
cast Lee Jeha into my life.
This voice-over
is hogging too many scenes.
I need to trim it down.
Director Lee?
Yes?
I like it.
- You do?
- Yes.
Especially the scene
where the terminal Gyuwon
stops Hyunsang from dying.
You reversed it from the original.
Why the change?
After meeting terminally ill people,
I realized nothing
is as strong as their will to live.
I wanted that to come through.
Seoyoung's hot right now,
so now's the time to take her to Cannes.
This film has a clear purpose,
and it doesn't work at all without her.
Let's talk in person, Ms. Go.
This script better turn out well.
Ms. Go is a bit off.
You read the same draft, right?
Wouldn't Seoyoung be
a better Junghwa than Gyuwon?
Though I bet Ms. Go will shut that down.
Let's forget Ms. Go's obsession
with lead roles
and say the fairy tale of a superstar
taking a supporting role comes true.
Our main problem? The investors will walk.
They're going to leave us.
Then why bother holding auditions
if the role has been cast?
It's all about the optics, man.
An unknown actor lands the lead
after a tough audition?
It's a romantic story. Like La La Land.
Of course, that never happens here
or in Hollywood.
LOVE IN WHITE
AUDITION
Hello, my name is Kang Seoha.
Okay, Seoha.
Go to the last page
of the audition script.
You'll see your sides there.
"Hyunsang."
"Hyunsang!"
"There is no such right!"
"You've got to try living,
even if it kills you."
"Only then"…
"Only then your tomorrow will come."
"Do as I say
for just one month."
"If you still want to die after that,
then go ahead. Do whatever you want."
Okay, thank you.
My brain is about to shut down.
How many do we have left?
The next one is our last one today.
Hey, even her name means "next."
LEE DAEUM, 25 YEARS OLD
Yes, come in.
Hello!
My name is Lee Daeum, and I'm an actress.
What's that camcorder for?
Could I just point it at me
and keep it on?
You can't for security reasons.
Okay.
That darn camcorder.
Do you know her?
Do you know Director Lee?
No, I've never met him.
Nice to meet you, Director.
I'm not looking to cast
for a documentary film.
Yes, I know that very well.
I'm just desperate
to take on this terminal patient role.
Shall we start with the sides?
"Ms. Gyuwon,
just calm down."
"It wasn't even my funeral,
but I found myself
taking in every detail."
"I wanted my funeral to be different."
"So I took the funeral director's card"…
That's enough for that.
Let's go to the last page.
Read the part where Gyuwon
stops Hyunsang's suicide.
"Hyunsang."
"I won't…"
"I won't say a single word."
"Just…"
"Just stay for a moment."
Okay, that's great.
I like your reinterpretation of the lines.
Yes, well, I think that's enough.
You can leave now.
Thank you!
She's incredible.
She wasn't forcing it. Just pure feeling.
Shame the role is already cast, no?
Director Lee,
is there anything left to discuss?
The perfect lead just came to us.
Doors are opening.
Mr. Bu!
What's all this?
I told you to just come hang out!
You must be exhausted from the auditions.
Thought you might be hungry.
- What's this?
- Oh, wow! What is it?
A handwritten letter?
I know we've only just met,
but you're just as praiseworthy
as they say you are.
Can you tell the whole world that?
Jungwoo.
Thank you so much for doing this with me.
Don't even say that.
We go way back since The Lonely People.
He's so loyal, isn't he?
WAIT THERE FOR A MINUTE
I want to live.
I want to live right now.
Are you a patient or an actress?
I'm just Lee Daeum.
Why did you come here?
What were you thinking?
Are you serious about this?
Yes, I'm very serious.
You said that you were dying.
You said you only have a year left.
This is a film, not a hospice documentary.
And it's an audition.
You knew all that when you came in, right?
Yes.
You debuted with The Lonely People.
You've won a lot of awards.
You're obsessed with realism.
Infamous for having
a difficult personality.
Was involved in a scandal.
More famous as Lee Duyoung's son
than for your own work.
I looked it all up online.
Honestly, I didn't have to prepare much
in terms of acting.
I am that character.
What if you die?
What if you die during production?
Who'll die?
You.
Guess I was also desperate,
showing up here.
I'm sorry.
Let's pretend the audition didn't happen.
Wait!
Let's look at this
from a broader perspective.
What if I die during filming?
It'll go viral.
A terminal patient
playing a terminal role?
Even I'd want to watch that.
That's a big win for the investors.
Big win for you too.
Yeah. As long as I'm okay with it,
you or anyone involved
shouldn't have a problem, no?
How is it not a problem?
This is your life on the line.
Yes, and I'm fine with it.
I want to do this. Even if I die.
That's reckless and also selfish.
Not true. The film becomes a hit,
I get to have closure before I die,
and you'd make a comeback,
ride the success train to eternity.
Wow, look at that. Everyone wins, right?
It's also a bit…
bittersweet, I guess.
I don't know how you're so confident.
I get that you're sick,
but this is where I draw the line.
Find another way to get closure.
It can't be my movie, sorry.
I saw your face earlier.
To put it bluntly,
it felt like you totally fell for me.
Okay, I'll give you that.
You were good, but--
I can't really run,
so I can't really do action scenes.
Actually, even normal, everyday life
would be tough for me.
But this character is a terminal patient.
This is something I can really act well.
I want to do it,
even if it costs me everything.
Even if that's your life?
I don't have much time left anyway.
Would you rather die trying
or die full of regret?
If the roles were reversed,
would you answer differently?
So tell me…
How long do you think you have left?
How long do I need to live?
Were there any new scripts that came in?
Well, actually…
I heard Kim Jungin's script
is going around,
but it didn't reach us.
Anything from Lee Jeha?
I'm not sure.
I think I heard
he's doing a Love in White remake,
but it's not going so well.
I guess no one wants me anymore.
What do you mean? You've still got it.
You're the first one who got his script!
I knew it. It must've come to me first.
I'm sorry. I knew I should've come to you.
Forget it. What did you tell the studio?
What do you mean,
she's going to Hollywood?
It's what Ms. Go said.
She can't even speak English
and she's working abroad?
- Is it a silent film?
- A Korean character.
Oh, man.
Who's the director?
Damien Chazelle.
What? Cha-what?
Are you sure?
I couldn't push her
to go for Lee Jeha's film
when she's working with Damien Chaz…
- The receiver is not available…
- Oh, come on.
What should we do?
The investors think both Kim Jungwoo
and Chae Seoyoung have been confirmed.
Don't tell this to Jeha yet,
but let's focus more on the male lead
since Jungwoo is the star.
I guess the female lead
could be the one we saw at the audition.
That's the worst-case scenario.
Try persuading Seoyoung
right until production begins,
and if she's in, then the rookie is out.
Yes, I'll make it happen.
- What about Ms. Go?
- She can't be in the picture.
We have to get Jeha
to talk directly to Seoyoung.
Okay?
Something wrong? You seem down.
I just came from the agency,
and now I have to go back.
I guess Ms. Go pulled something again?
Something like that.
I'll tell you when I get back.
Oh, I heard you went to see
the Love in White auditions.
Yes, they made a big thing out of it.
Should I do that too?
Why the face?
You wanted to do it with me.
Of course.
Let's just go.
HOW LONG
DO I NEED TO LIVE?
Lee Daeum.
Adultery. Premeditated serial murder.
Maybe even become a ghost.
How long do I need to live?
Six months?
A year?
Can you please tell me?
Well…
I guess…
Sorry, could you pass me that ball?
Oh, of course.
So how long do I need to live already?
What, you think
you're in Autumn in My Heart?
Here's your Americano.
Yes, thank you.
Mr. Lee.
I heard you want to be a writer.
What do you think is wrong with my script?
You can be straight with me.
Well…
Can I be frank then?
I'm not sure why you're doing a remake.
Love in White came out
right in the middle of the '90s
melodrama boom in the industry.
I think that classic sentiment
transcends both time and age.
I've never even been in love,
and even I get giddy.
Go on.
The way you've twisted Gyuwon's character
is really fascinating, but…
it feels hollow.
Like something essential is missing.
Let me guess. Love?
Of course, it's love.
Take away love,
and you lose the foundation
and the reason to remake the film
in the first place.
Oh, one more.
I want to know what Gyuwon wants to do
besides saving Hyunsang.
What were her dreams before she got sick?
It'd be even sadder
if she has a lot she wants to accomplish.
You scared me.
What are you doing here?
What about your shoot?
Obviously, I didn't go.
That darn Ms. Park.
Did you read the pitch?
Do I have to read it?
I know the original.
Of course you didn't.
Did you forget that I choose the scripts
that come to me?
Now that's a bit harsh.
We've been doing that all along.
Love in White was just an exception.
I want to do that movie.
You have no good reason to do that
when there are better directors
with better scripts who want you.
Better directors?
Better scripts?
What exactly makes them better?
Something worthy
of the actress Chae Seoyoung.
Yes, I'm an actress.
So I need a movie that I want to do.
Let's do that. Next time.
No, this time.
There's no good reason?
I want to do it, and that's reason enough.
That's how I work as an actress, Ms. Go.
Once you get sick,
your life is completely different
from before your illness.
There's a reason why
they say ignorance is bliss.
What is it you want to do?
Why do I have so many things I want to do?
Yes, and that is my dream job.
LEE DAEUM
THIS IS LEE JEHA
Hello?
Mr. Lee, this is Ms. Go.
Can I see you tomorrow?
You work in places like this?
Yes, I need
some background noise to focus.
That's good.
This situation we're in
is getting a lot of noise, so focus.
I don't have any personal feelings
for or against you.
You know that, right?
I know what you're talking about,
but the script has…
been changed these past few weeks.
Especially the character.
I'm sorry to tell you that these changes
don't make Seoyoung
suitable for the role anymore.
That's good.
I didn't need to come at all.
Sorry I can't give her the lead role,
but I want to suggest
the role of Junghwa.
I think…
Seoyoung would want to do it.
Are you kidding?
I'm saying this
with my sincerest apologies to you.
Director Lee…
have you forgotten everything
or are you just pretending to?
You're the one who abandoned Seoyoung.
The nerve.
Mr. Lee,
you know how this industry works.
Why are you doing this?
You know if a scandal hits Seoyoung now,
it would tank her career
before it even takes off.
Ms. Go.
Why are you leaving me out?
Let me hear it too.
You've got to be kidding me.
You've already got four ad deals signed
and over five more lined up.
So what's the problem?
It's not like dating him will ruin me.
Just acknowledge it.
No, stop the press.
Director.
Yes, we're friendly.
But we've never crossed the line.
I'd like to apologize if I did anything
to make her think otherwise.
That was the first time
that Seoyoung got completely wrecked.
She should've been the one to dump you.
I won't…
be fooled by you a second time.
LOVE IN WHITE
Love in White.
Do as I say for just one month.
DIRECTOR LEE JEHA
THIS IS LEE JEHA. I KNOW
IT'S LATE, BUT CAN WE MEET?
Hey there, little girl.
Want to see something cool?
SEAWEED SNACK
That act is a bit too much,
don't you think?
What act?
That's the snack they normally eat
at funeral homes.
I tried these there last time
and got totally hooked.
Do you stay at the hospital,
or your own place?
I don't give my address to men.
You see me as a man?
Well, you're not a woman.
You're not even offering me those?
Mmm.
How should I put it?
A subtle taste…
that really hooks you.
A subtle taste that hooks you.
How did you do
that drinking thing earlier?
Want me to show you?
No, it's fine.
I wanted to consult…
…you…
There's something I wanted to ask you.
I failed the audition,
but you still want to consult me?
Go on, ask me anything.
Was there something you wanted to do?
I told you last time, didn't I?
Adultery, murder, ghost.
No, not what you'd do in movies.
You know, a normal dream you've had.
Dream?
I want to tell you
something ambitious, but…
I want to leave something
for the people I love.
Like what?
Memories of me they can always bring up.
Ah.
So now we're in…
the "dream" phase
of that closure you wanted?
There's just so much left undone.
That kind of regret
makes you go a little too crazy.
There's so much I haven't done,
but it's not like I can do it "later."
So that's why you want to be in movies.
Because I can do everything in there.
The love I never had.
Goodbyes I don't want to say.
And I want myself to live free
and go wild like this…
in those movies
so people can see that whenever they want.
- Like who?
- My dad.
My mom passed a long time ago,
so if I leave, too,
then my dad is really alone.
You can consult me, too, if you want.
I'm also alone.
Hey, now.
This is getting too dark.
Let's not talk about my dad, okay?
I didn't.
You were the one who brought him up.
Hang on.
That was the first audition I passed
for a role with a name and lines.
It was just the first round,
but I felt good about the second.
I had prepared so hard…
That's when you first got sick?
The day I was admitted
was the day of the second round.
But I'm pretty realistic
for a terminal patient.
I knew I had to live first.
So I told myself,
"I'll survive and come back
for another audition."
So I walked away, swallowing my tears.
Is that so?
Yes, it was so.
That must've been hard.
I know hospital life isn't easy.
Not at all.
I was super busy.
I kept acting.
I had nothing but time.
I mean, sure, it wasn't
in front of those big cameras on set,
but a tiny one the size of my palm,
but I tried
every kind of character I wanted.
You live so hard.
I guess I shouldn't assume things,
since you keep proving me wrong.
Mr. Lee…
Knowing your time is running out,
it's a strange kind of rush.
Everyone!
You think you have a lot of days to live?
You think you'll live forever?
You think you'll stay healthy
until you're 40, 70, 80,
and even 100, right?
Who's she shouting at?
But life works in mysterious ways!
You always forget, don't you?
But I never forget!
I've been preparing for this
since I was eight years old,
so every second of every minute
is so precious
and so valuable to me
that they're all masterpieces!
All the moments you just let slip away
are like romance or fantasy films to me!
But you'll keep on living
without knowing that!
You idiots!
That kind of rush.
What are you doing?
Honestly,
it'd make more sense
to cast me as an actress,
instead of using me for consulting.
It'd make more sense
for you to head back in.
It's cold.
Good night then.
You know,
I really want
to make this movie with you.
Can't I be a part of it?
Wait!
Why…
does it have to be me?
- Sorry?
- Why do you want to make a film
with me?
I don't know.
I just…
had the feeling
you might give me a chance!
ACTOR PORTFOLIO VIDEOS
LEE DAEUM
THE GIRL WITH LONG HAIR
IN A WHITE COAT
WALKING BEHIND PARK HAEIL
LEE DAEUM MONOLOGUE
Hey, Hong.
Sorry to call you this late.
- Dad.
- Yeah?
- I'm home.
- Hey.
Hey, Mom.
Mom.
How have you been?
What's all this?
Vietnamese spring rolls.
Not exactly traditional for a memorial.
I want us to eat some trendy stuff
instead of the usual.
I like it.
You know, Gyoyeong says
you and I have "cool syndrome."
What's that?
Well…
Pretending to be too cool with each other,
and overdoing it.
How can I be cool
when my daughter is about to die?
Cool?
Freeze me to death, will ya?
Hey, I want to be cool, too, you know.
So then, in the spirit of being cool,
could you make me an outpatient
and let me act again?
What are you saying?
I want to act.
I want to act again.
No.
- Dad, please.
- I said no.
- Just once, please.
- No.
What if you pass out like last time?
How could I
face your mom again
if I go easy on your treatment--
That's just your perspective, Dad.
I won't allow it.
Dad.
Your view is different
from mine and Mom's.
You still don't get that?
Mom always wanted to come home.
But…
She couldn't.
She wanted to die here at home,
but she passed away at the hospital
while you were in surgery
and I was at school.
She died all alone with no one there.
Dad.
I'm her daughter.
Maybe that's why
I don't want to die in a hospital either.
No.
I said no.
CONGRATULATIONS ON PASSING ROUND
1 OF "WHITE IN LOVE" AUDITIONS
My goodness!
Yes! Yes!
Great, you're here.
Say hello.
- Hello.
- Yes.
Great to see you.
I've been hoping to meet you,
so I've been pestering Mr. Bu for a while.
HAN SUNGHO
Actually,
I don't know much about movies,
to be honest.
I leave that part to the artists.
I'm just a businessman who cares about
whether this will make money,
and how much money it'll make.
That's what matters to me.
Why would you talk yourself down?
He's being too modest.
A movie just on its own
is not enough anymore these days.
You know what I'm saying, right?
I'm curious, what did you think
of the original Love in White?
Never seen it.
Then…
Have you seen my adaptation plan?
Well,
I heard the gist.
I'm not copying some dusty old film.
It'll be something completely new.
I wanted to be up-front about that.
I see, but do I really need to know that?
Do you think that's important to me?
You're only investing because…
I'm Lee Duyoung's son, right?
That's all that matters to you.
Ah. Our director here sure is candid.
Says it like it is.
Most people wouldn't agree to do this.
My father made the film
a year after my mother passed
with the very actress he was rumored
to be having an affair with.
They shamelessly pour out this ode to love
as if they were finally free.
People think…
it's a heartfelt tribute to the dead wife
that he made in grief,
and they praise it
like it's something noble.
Forget the film.
It's the story behind the film.
That's where the real fun is.
I know this film and what needs fixing
better than anyone.
And I promise,
you won't lose a cent.
AWARD
COFFEE BARISTA LICENSE
It's me, Daeum!
Could you wake her up?
Leave her. She must've come in
in the morning again.
Take some of this food when you go later.
About time for a refill.
Aren't these elephant bush stems?
Are you marinating them in perilla oil?
I'll stir-fry them
with a ton of perilla oil.
Thank you.
Instead of me…
Oh, she's driving me nuts.
Can you just go and wake her up?
Gyo.
What happened to you?
- Huh? Daeum.
- Yeah?
I told you not to wake me up like this.
Why are your eyes so puffy?
I dumped him.
You're such a sucker for cute faces.
What did I tell you?
You have to get to know them first
before dating them.
Who asked for your two cents?
I'll have you know,
that's a hereditary trait.
My mom fell for my dad's face too.
Oh, right.
- Did you go back home?
- Yeah.
How's your dad?
Fine.
I told him everything, you know.
How you said we're both
riddled with "cool syndrome."
What?
Jeez! Why would you tell him that?
Seriously!
I can't even slap you.
Well, anyway.
Just make sure
your next relationship goes well.
What?
Hmm?
Spit it out. Something happened, right?
- The clinical trial?
- My audition!
What did you say?
I auditioned for a movie.
How did you do that?
I just barged in and did it.
You know what happened?
CONGRATULATIONS ON PASSING ROUND
1 OF "WHITE IN LOVE" AUDITIONS
What is it?
What happened? What is it?
Is it a cockroach?
- Mom.
- Let me see.
CONGRATULATIONS ON PASSING ROUND
1 OF "WHITE IN LOVE" AUDITIONS
Congratulations!
I'm so happy for you.
Please tell me two things.
"Well done."
and "Good luck."
Well done.
Good luck.
Well done! Good luck!
I see you've mostly worked on short films.
- Yes.
- Right.
What do you do in your free time
when you're not acting?
I work as a freelance translator.
How have you been after the first round?
I've been well, thank you.
What have you been up to?
I went to some university hospitals
to do research on Gyuwon.
University hospitals?
Okay, Taerin.
That's enough for today. Thank you.
Okay, thank you.
- Take care, Mr. Lee.
- Goodbye.
Oh, no.
I'm sorry, Dr. Lee.
Why? What happened?
Daeum is gone.
Lee Daeum is coming in.
- Thank you.
- You got this.
I got this.
Hello!
Yes, hello.
Take a seat.
So I've analyzed the character.
You're not here to act
or analyze the character today.
Instead,
let's have a chat.
Just the two of us.
Just the two of us?
Yes.
You know,
just chat like you normally do.
Okay, Mr. Lee.
Don't let the camera bother you.
We won't use this footage for anything.
Relax, and talk how you normally do to me.
Don't you think this character
and this film are too cliché?
I do.
You do?
Some people might even find it boring.
Seems like you find it boring too.
But it'll never be boring to me.
When that "terminal illness" cliché
is your life,
every day feels like
the climax of a movie.
This will be real method acting.
It sounds like you're okay
with this movie using your illness.
But you already did.
You used my words in your script.
I'll change the lines then.
Have you found someone better than me?
We're searching.
Don't waste your time like that.
I just don't see this happening.
I want to forget about my illness
and live as an actress.
There's a difference between forgetting
and overlooking.
I'm attending an audition right now,
so please see me as an actress,
not a sick person.
There were over 200 videos
of you doing monologues.
I wanted to ask…
what drove you to come this far
even while you were sick?
When I was eight,
I asked my mom lying in the hospital bed
what her dream was.
I still remember the face she made.
If she ever got to leave the hospital,
she said she wanted to find
the dream that she had forgotten.
I don't know what her dream was,
but it sure wasn't being a patient.
Same goes for me.
That's the kind of thinking
that brought me here.
I don't know if that makes sense.
Are you hungry?
Give me 10 minutes.
Mr. Lee,
even though I'm sick,
I can still watch movies,
go to auditions, and even love.
So I can make movies too.
I can do everything. I really can.
Just let me prove that to you.
That's enough for today.
You may leave now.
We'll let you know the results.
Thank you.
Mr. Lee.
Yes?
Put your faith in me.
What exactly do you have
that I can put my faith in?
A plan…
and guts.
Looks flimsy to me.
But I like your spirit.
I have one condition.
Don't die.
Everyone knows
Chae Seoyoung should get the part.
Why are you so stuck on Lee Daeum?
What is it about her?
A rookie?
You just need to do it.
I'll make it happen.
What's this?
We're deciding if the role of Gyuwon
should go to Chae Seoyoung
or you, a rookie.
Did you read the script?
Are you interested?
Yes, I am.
Translated by Yenny Kang