If the smoke can't go side-by-side
Think of someone to be your mercy
Don't let him find you
My favorite
Let him be a soldier
Not a man
only to enrich me.
Doctor.
Are you going to collect herbs?
Come on.
Let me help you.
I'll collect herbs as you want.
I'll help you.
Luckily, you didn't refuse me.
I'm afraid that I can't see you
when the night falls.
Remember.
When you find the doctor,
you must be careful.
He doesn't like to talk too much.
I'd better be quiet
in case the doctor will feel disgusted with me.
Let me help you.
You want this?
I'll do it.
Don't move.
Let me help you.
Be careful.
Don't break the root.
Water.
Don't be afraid.
Although these snakes are poisonous,
they won't hurt you.
You raised these poisonous things?
What a pity.
It looks like a fairy,
but it hides dangers everywhere.
Let me help you.
Don't move.
Be careful.
It's okay.
Jinxia and the others came here.
Really?
This is the mark
Jinxia left.
That way.
I'll go to Zhu Fa.
The smell of herbs is so good.
It's the smell of these herbs.
Do you understand?
What do you mean?
Aren't you curious
why there are so many poisonous things here?
You mean
the poisonous things are the smell of these herbs?
Yes.
Let me do it.
Give it to me.
Tell me.
What do you need?
Let me do it.
You clean these roots
with water.
Then put them on the shelf.
Okay.
Water.
Hold on.
Hold hold.
Got it.
Your Highness.
Let me do it.
Grand holes.
Your Highness,
what're you doing?
Don't move.
Let me do it.
Hold on.
I'll go.
The spring water by the river...
Here we are.
Wait a minute.
What?
Did you forget to bring your things?
Do you want to go to the beach?
I also want to go to the beach.
I'll give you a ride.
I'll take you there.
What?
What's wrong?
This is the secret watch that Jin Xia left.
We didn't go in the wrong direction.
Let's go.
I'm back.
Wait.
Don't pour it yet.
This water can't be used.
Go get two more barrels of water.
You can only use spring water.
Oh.
Yin Xiang.
Look.
Is it okay?
No.
I can't go any further.
I'll go get another one.
You...
Yes.
He's not satisfied with so many barrels of water.
What does he want?
Aren't these all the same water?
Master fell asleep.
So he needs to calm down.
Observe.
Judgment.
He even said that he's good at tracking.
He almost ruined his own factory.
Water.
Is there anything special about using water?
The water just came out of the well.
It won't be dirty without flowing.
Is this the spring water that Yin Xian wants?
Yin Xian.
Is this okay?
It's okay.
Pour it in.
Thank goodness.
I finally know
what spring water you want.
It's the water that just came out of the well.
It's okay.
I was wrong to hit the river.
Are you blaming me
for not making it clear to you?
No, no, no.
I was too stupid.
I was wrong about what you meant.
Two buckets of water is not enough.
Get two more buckets of water.
Okay.
He is so persistent.
He is really like a person.
Okay.
Lan Ye.
You are a good singer.
There is no one in the whole capital
who can match you.
If you change your mind
and take me back to the capital to serve you,
I will accompany you every day.
You'd better stay here.
I will go back to the capital later.
You need to take care of things here.
Yes.
Keep an eye on Mao Haifeng for me.
If he makes any small movements,
let me know immediately.
Don't worry, young master.
What you told me is
that I will do my best.
One more song.
Okay.
Time is getting shorter.
Doctor.
Just call Dr. Lin.
Dr. Lin, please check him.
Okay.
How is he?
He just needs to step on one foot
and he will be in the coffin.
Doctor.
Dr. Lin.
I beg you.
Please save him.
Save him.
Go to the forest and catch some snakes.
And put them in the
house outside the door.
Snakes?
Okay.
Any snakes will do, right?
Do you dare to catch big snakes?
Let me see.
Small snakes will do.
I know.
Although the girl is young,
she is very patient.
Very affectionate.
Flying fish leg.
Have you given her any medicine?
Purple medicine.
The hand gun you just used
is the fire weapon of the officials.
The hand gun?
It's the Imperial Guards.
Master.
Father.
Kill them.
It's Uncle Gai.
Senior sister.
I found it.
Uncle Gai.
Don't say.
The code of this girl is really useful.
I found it all.
Where are Jinxia and others?
Jinxia?
She went to find the doctor of the first line with Lu Yi.
There.
Let me tell you.
In the forest of Feng Liyao,
it's very dangerous.
I'm afraid that they will be killed.
It's very dangerous in the forest.
Don't run around.
Lu Yi and Jinxia can enter.
Why can't I enter?
Besides,
don't you worry about their safety?
And
they saved your life from the Suolong well.
Do you forget?
I...
I'm worried.
But
you can't go in.
I can't care so much.
No.
Why don't you listen to me?
What do you mean?
Are you hiding something from me?
I'm really afraid that you will be in danger.
Don't you believe me, okay?
Xie Xiao, calm down.
I'm Yang Yue.
I'm Jinxia's colleague.
Jinxia has been with you for so long.
Will something happen?
I guess
they have found the doctor.
Maybe
they have started to treat.
So
don't worry.
Just like me,
wait here.
Don't ruin
the peace in the Suolong well.
What if they are angry
and don't want to save my grandson?
It will be a disaster.
No.
I'm worried about Jinxia.
Uncle Gai.
You know that place.
Come with us.
Go.
Uncle Gai, let's go.
What are you doing?
Go.
Let me go.
Uncle Gai.
Don't yell.
It's not good for you to do this.
Uncle Gai.
Don't move.
Dr. Lin, I got the wound you wanted.
Hold it.
The wound
can't be healed, right?
Yes.
Give me the snake.
Okay.
Hurry.
How is it, Dr. Lin?
Is the poison already cured?
It's more powerful
than I thought.
Then...
This poison is very powerful.
If you give it to me for a while,
maybe I can
cure it.
Okay.
Go.
Maybe I can
find a way to cure it.
But now he's dying.
I'm afraid that...
No.
The lord said
he's not a short-lived man.
Doctor,
you must have a way to save him, right?
Your highness.
I know you must have a way to save him.
I beg you.
Please save him.
He can't die.
I beg you.
Get up first.
There is a way.
But it's very dangerous.
It's very expensive.
Maybe you can save him
and another life.
So he may die.
What do you mean?
The poison in his body has entered the high desert.
It's the only way to stop it.
Only by detoxifying his blood
can we save his life.
Defecting his blood?
Where is it?
I'll find it.
It's not that easy to get.
I know.
To detoxify his blood,
we must put the poison
into the blood of the living.
The poison is the medicine.
The blood is the medicine.
Then the blood is purified.
The patient can only be detoxified for three days
to detoxify his body.
Do you understand what I mean?
You want the medicine?
Yes.
I'm going to the hospital.
I'll call you when I arrive.
Okay.
See you.
I don't know if you're lucky or not.
This golden snake
is the son of the King of Poison.
I thought the King of Poison had been eliminated.
But I accidentally found an egg
and hatched it.
This golden snake
is the most important poison
in the hundred poisons I mentioned.
Without it,
your beloved husband
would have died.
I'm so lucky.
Lucky?
Do you know that to make this medicine,
you have to let this golden snake bite you?
If it bites me,
what will happen to my body?
There will be no reaction at the moment.
But if the snake poison is really strong,
it will be paralyzed in a few days.
Then it will spread all over the body.
It will be difficult to breathe in the end.
It can't walk.
Can we still save our lives?
Everyone has different ability to bear it.
If there's really a problem,
I can only say I tried my best.
But I can't guarantee that
the poisoners will be killed.
Yuan Jin Xia,
are you really going to risk your life for your husband?
I was just excited for a moment.
But now I think about it,
you haven't found your family yet.
Your mother is still waiting for you in the capital.
You don't even have a loved one.
What if you die like this?
Are you willing to do it?
You were just a good person before.
You hit your head with a handgun.
What?
Now you're hesitating?
To be honest,
I was able to control the handgun at that time
because it was in my hand.
So you were acting.
Yes.
But I didn't expect that he would rush out of the house
and scare me.
So he...
You dare to lie to me.
I'm sorry, Dr. Lin.
I lied to you.
But he didn't.
You can punish me if you want.
Please, save him.
I can save him,
but I may not save you.
Save you?
Have you thought it through?
Let's go.
Where are we going now?
I'm hungry.
Let's eat something.
Although you're cold and cold sometimes,
you're not kind and annoying,
but sometimes you're very warm.
Sir, Wang Qianqian.
You want to die?
I'm afraid that Lord Yan doesn't want to take you.
You...
Besides,
if it weren't for you,
I would have died long ago.
Yuan Qianxia,
what are you thinking?
I asked you to rescue you from the Ghost Gate,
but you refused to save me.
Do you want to be unhappy for the rest of your life?
Besides,
Dr. Lin said it was serious as Lord Yan's medicine.
But I believe he will save me.
So it may not be a failure.
But if no one helps him make blood,
he will die.
It's too late.
Have you made up your mind?
If you want to die, die together.
If you want to live, live together.
I want to live with you.
Does it hurt so much?
It's scary.
Brother Qi.
Be careful.
Don't cut your tongue.
Jinxia.
Let's take a break.
So many snakes.
We can't finish them all.
We can't do it.
Why do you grab my pot?
No.
What are you doing?
Take it.
I want to set fire to burn this forest.
Set fire.
Hurry.
Go back to your room.
Go.
You bastard.
You almost got into trouble.
Is there any other way?
Oh, no.
We are in trouble.
Run.
Stop.
Are you the owner of this forest?
Yes.
Then you must be the doctor.
I'm Yang Yue.
I'm here to find my sister.
I offended you just now.
Please forgive me.
Your sister?
Yes.
Her sister asked someone to leave a message.
She said she was here to find the doctor.
Have you seen them?
So what?
You set fire to burn this forest?
Thank you.
I set fire to burn this forest.
I can bear it alone.
As long as you take us to see Jin Xia.
You almost ruined my favorite forest.
You even bargain with me.
How do you want to bear it?
I...
Doctor, we are also looking for people in a hurry.
We will compensate for all the losses here.
Yes.
Come out.
You brought them here?
Yes.
Ling.
I know your habit.
But I have no other way.
I'm sorry.
These years,
I've been looking for you.
But I dare not.
Come with me.
Let's go.
Senior.
Yuan.
Jin Xia.
Xie Yuan.
Sister Shangguan.
Why are you here?
Of course, because someone brought us here.
Uncle.
Girl.
You brought them here?
They forced us.
We can't stop them.
Didn't you bring Lu Yi here?
Where is he?
He is inside.
I'll take you to see him.
Okay.
I'm not here to find Lu Yi.
I'm worried about you.
You have never been afraid of the sky or the ground.
You are afraid of snakes.
There are so many poisonous snakes in the forest.
You are not scared, are you?
How could it be?
Just a few snakes.
A few snakes won't be afraid of you.
Otherwise, you can't be a fast-repeater.
Right.
By the way, Zaya.
Although I left a mark,
I didn't expect you to find the book so soon.
You are making progress in the investigation.
I'm worried about you.
I'm relieved to see you are fine.
I'm fine.
But,
Mr. Lu is not good.
I'm afraid he can't cure the poison.
You are talking about Mr. Lu.
When did you become so concerned about him?
I think the doctor here is not good.
How about we go back to Yangzhou?
The doctors in Yangzhou are so generous.
They can cure any poison.
Let's not waste time.
Let's go now.
Xie Yuanyuan.
Don't talk nonsense.
Mr. Lu is not a normal poison.
Only the medical fairy can save him.
Don't go.
Doctor Lin.
My junior brother never knows how to talk.
If there is an offense,
I apologize to you.
I'm sorry.
I heard you are good at medicine.
I believe that as long as you are here,
Mr. Lu will be cured.
Don't be so formal.
It's not the end of the world.
It depends on his luck.
Yes.
He is not so formal.
There is no poison that you can't cure.
This poison is so strange.
I don't know who is the crazy person who can make it.
It's my first time to see it.
I'm not sure.
Lin.
You are good at poison.
Why don't you follow me to see it later?
See what poison Mr. Lu is talking about.
Maybe you have seen it.
No need.
That poison is from the book.
What?
It's you.
Come with me.
No.
I can't go alone.
Don't talk nonsense.
Go.
Yuan Daxiang.
This is the medical fairy you mentioned.
Why is it so different?
Don't talk nonsense.
I think she is not good at it.
She can't save Lu Yi.
And there are poisonous things in the forest.
If she is poisonous to us,
we won't have a place to hide.
Yes.
She is hiding here alone.
She is not afraid of so many poisonous things.
It's really strange.
If she is not a person from the Yan family,
she must have some secret.
I thought about it before.
She is the reason for this.
But aren't all the masters sleeping?
What's wrong with you, Yuan Daxiang?
Where do you feel uncomfortable?
Do you want to go back to your room?
I want to talk with you.
I'm fine.
Xie Xiao.
How about you and Shangguan and Dayang?
You go back to Yangzhou.
I'll take care of Master Lu.
I won't go back.
Why did I meet someone
who is worse than me?
Where are you going?
I'm going to see how Master Lu is doing.
I'll go with you.
Xie Xiao, can you stop making trouble here?
After Master Lu's poison is gone,
I'll go back to Yangzhou and meet you.
Lu Yi is a little bit of a follower.
He won't show up when Master is in trouble.
So I said, Yuan Daxiang,
you don't have to spend so much time
to take care of him.
Master Lu was poisoned to save me.
I should take care of him in all circumstances.
What's wrong?
Are you cold or what?
Why are you so cold?
What's wrong with you?
Yuan Jinxia.
Miss Shangguan.
Are you okay?
Don't follow me.
I'm fine.
I just caught a cold.
I'll go to see Dr. Lin.
He'll just eat some dry grass.
No, no, no. I'll go with you.
Can you stop following me?
If you keep following me, I'll hit you.
Then I'll go see Master Lu.
He's not feeling well.
Don't bother him.
And your senior is angry.
Can't you see it?
I'll go with you.
Go.
Ling'er.
I was wondering how they could
get into the fengling forest to find me.
It's you.
Ling'er.
I know you don't like
to interact with outsiders.
But it's urgent to do something.
That kid was poisoned.
I can't bear to see him die.
I can't even stop him from following me.
You're the one who made the hole.
You can't clean it up yourself.
And you're pushing me here.
Who do you think I am?
I know you have a way.
Wu Jie.
Really, Wu Jie?
Ling'er.
Do you remember
the bet we made that year?
The poison at that time
is not something I can't cure.
If I can't cure the poison
you can't cure.
Then I'll make you a wish.
Really?
Any wish is fine.
Of course it's true.
Don't regret it.
What's there to regret?
Okay.
It's a deal.
I remember that year
we followed Master.
I learned to cure the poison.
You learned to detoxify the poison.
We always competed against each other.
But
you're smarter than me.
Every time I cure the poison
you can break it.
So Master
especially values you.
You were the first doctor, right?
I just want to ask you
if you can cure the poison
or not.
Can you cure the poison
of Lan Yu Zan?
Ling'er.
If you can't cure the poison
you promised me
you would marry me.
Even so
you shouldn't leave the sect.
I was young
and impulsive.
I just wanted to win you.
I wandered the world
to find the most poisonous thing.
Finally
someone who is not as good as me
made me cure the poison.
But I know
there must be something wrong
with the poison.
So I kept it.
Even if you kept it
the poison on that child
wouldn't be so hard to cure.
It's just an accident.
The poison on him
is on the basis of my poison.
It's on the basis of my poison.
So I can't cure it.
When he was poisoned
the first thing I thought of
was you.
Because I knew
you could cure it.
I don't want to
fight with you.
You are my last hope.
To cure the poison
we have to test the poison with people
and use his blood
as a medicine.
Test the poison?
That's dangerous.
Are you going to use Jinxia
as your medicine?
Yes.
How could you do that?
He sent it himself.
I didn't force him.
It's been years
but you've become so cruel.
You use Jinxia as your medicine?
You said I was cruel.
You know I never
treat people with care.
What's more,
the one lying there is a guard.
Have you forgotten?
Ling'er.
You can't harm Jinxia.
I beg you.
Jinxia is right.
I'm sorry.
I have a savior.
Don't let anything happen to her.
Okay?
It's all for this.
I can only say I'll try my best.
As for the result,
it's up to God.
Go.
Dr. Lin.
What's wrong?
Sit down.
I'm cold and hot now.
My chest is still full.
I can't breathe.
Now I can't even
hold it.
Take this medicine.
It can relieve the poison in your body.
After three meals a day,
take it six times a day.
Thank you, Dr. Lin.
Can my tongue be cured?
After three days,
when he gets better,
I can cure you.
Here.
Give me your hand.
Take this to him.
Make sure he drinks it all.
Don't waste time.
Thank you, Dr. Lin.
Uncle Han, you're here too.
You're here too.
Here.
Slowly.
It's done.
Okay.
Let me help him up.
He's heavy.
Here.
Feed him.
He can't drink it without a mouth.
What should we do?
Here.
Let me put his mouth here.
Here. Try again.
No.
I want to spill it.
I spilled it.
What should I do?
What should we do?
Sir.
You can't drink medicine.
Try again.
Open your mouth.
Be a good boy.
It's not good to take medicine.
Little boy.
You must take medicine.
Open your mouth.
Sir.
No.
Still no.
Still no?
What should I do?
What should you do?
How about this?
You can take his mouth.
Take his mouth?
I'm here.
Who is born out of the world
is better than fate.
Close your eyes.
I can see your face.
Open your eyes.
The back is dark.
The sword is full of sweet.
In the mortal world,
who has the power to fight against the wind?
No sound.
The dark cloud is rising.
The fate is turning.
It's a change of time.
It's like parting.
The parting is too deep.
The willow is golden.
The day I met you,
my hair turned white.
We spent years together.
In the dream,
a word is said.