YoYo English Channel YouTube
The song is over
I hear
Your heartbeats are still in my ears
Just a moment
Separate two sides
Never to be found again
I see
Your tears are falling in my heart
I'm afraid a blink of an eye
Will disappear
Ah
No
This knife is used by the martial arts master
To hide his body
And is used for the purpose of the unknown
You can't have it
Who gave it to you?
Speak! Who gave it to you?
You want to know?
I'll tell you
Yan Shifan
Yan Shifan?
What? Are you afraid?
Yan Shifan
I'm not surprised that he wants to kill me
But have you ever thought about it?
If he really wants to kill me
He can just find a killer
Why would he want to find a martial artist
Who doesn't know how to fight?
Because you are Lord Lu's cousin
Whether you kill me or not
You will be distracted by the military camp
If he leaves the military camp
He will violate the royal camp
This is the purpose of Yan Shifan
I don't care about that
As long as I can live
I can kill anyone
Even if I kill my big brother
I will do it
Do you know what you are talking about?
Your big brother is your only family now
He is the only one who is good to you
You almost made me marry Sima Chang'an
He didn't blame you
Your Chunyu family had an accident
He took you in
You are not worthy of him
I can pretend that
This didn't happen today
I can not blame you
And I don't hate you
But I hope
You can think about
How you should go in the future
People still have a breath
Life is yours
Of course
If you want to kill me again
I will do it
But next time
I won't be so polite
Let's go
Go
General
To be honest
I have studied the war records for half a year
I know the location of this Ceng Gang
And I have calculated the consumption of gunpowder of several war camps
According to my calculations
The supply of gunpowder in Ceng Gang
Is not enough to support Mao Haifeng
He has fought for so long
What do you mean?
Mao Haifeng must have a way to transport gunpowder
Otherwise, this Ceng Gang
Mao Haifeng has no external source
But he still has no water and food
Even the gunpowder is not short-lived
General
Don't you think there is something wrong?
When I first arrived in Zhou Shan
I have thought about this
So I have fully arranged the defense line
And cut off the Japanese and Western routes
All the routes
I have sent troops to block them
All the roads
As long as they can be used for the case
They are under our supervision
And there is no ship
Which can secretly send the supplies to Ceng Gang
In fact
Just a few months ago
I have fought with Mao Haifeng in Yangzhou
But at that time
Everyone thought Mao Haifeng was in Ceng Gang
I once suspected that
There is a secret passage between the mountains
Which connects the secret passage of Mao Haifeng's band
It seems to be true
General Yu
Mr. Lu
General Qi
You asked me to wait for the clue yesterday
What's your idea?
I plan to send small troops every day
To call the enemy
Our army will not move
So that Mao Haifeng thinks
Our army is not going to fight
You mean stop the battle?
General Qi wants to use the plan to control the situation
To reduce the alertness of Mao Haifeng
And then find a chance
Yes
Now this is a way
But the emperor is very strict
If you use this way
Then let people have a chance
To participate in the emperor's meeting
This is not just
To withdraw the order and investigate
I understand what you mean
General, don't worry
After I go back to the capital
I will definitely report to the emperor
How can I believe
Mr. Lu can speak for us in front of the emperor?
Such a small thing
It's not my character
Besides
I have no conflict with the general
And I have no reason to fight on the battlefield
What I report is also the truth
We are all the people of the Ming Dynasty
We should unite to fight against the enemy
If those ministers
Can have the same belief as Lu Qianshi
General Yu and we
Will not fight so hard
General
General, you are here
Master
Xianer
What's wrong with you?
Nothing
I met pirates on the way
They cut me
Fortunately, I have checked
The wound is not fatal
So I sent my father back to recuperate
I am sorry
Do you know that
I have been worried about you these days?
I locked myself in the room
I didn't eat or drink for days
Father
I am sorry
It's ok
It's all over
Master, have a good rest
Ok
Come out
What? Why did you hit me?
I hit you for myself
I promised master
As long as you come back
No matter how he punishes you
I won't speak for you
But master didn't punish you
So I have to do it myself
Do you think you should hit me?
Yes, yes, yes
Hit me, hit me
Your wound is much better
Yes
The doctor said
If you go home several times
You may recover
Really?
He is so good
By the way, Jinxia
Aunt Lin prescribed a prescription for father
You go to take care of father
I will go to the pharmacy to get the medicine
Come back, come back
You are tired
You go to accompany master
I will go
She is considerate
Come, come, come
Jinxia
What's this?
Look
Huang Mazi
Why does he appear here?
How about this?
Try this
This is good
This is cheap
Try this
This is a pastry
You try
My pastry is very sweet
It's sweet and sweet
It's crispy
I can't eat it for two days
What do you want?
Miss
Come
This is delicious
Boss
I want to go to the General's mansion in the east of the city
This road is closer
This road is going to Qingbo River
If you go to the General's mansion
You will go far away
Qingbo River
By the way
I want to buy fish
When does the fish market start?
Where?
Fish market
Follow this road
You can see the fish market in the east
If you want to buy fish
You should start early
The fish market here
Starts at the beginning of the month
It will be sold out before the morning
I can't catch up today
How about you come here?
No, no, boss
I have something to do
I wish you a good business
Ok, ok, ok
See you
Miss, have a try
This is our General Yu
General Yu
I am Shangguan Xi
This is my junior Xie Xiao
We are the disciples of the Southern Shaolin Temple
We are here to help you
To fight against the pirates
Thank you
I am very grateful
You are welcome
Those pirates are on the land of Ming
They are violent
They are the people
They are evil
They will be in peace if they don't get rid of the coastal area
Now everyone wants to make a contribution
We should drive them out
Be careful in front of the general
It's ok
Sir Lu
Miss Shangguan
What's up? You know each other?
Yes, general
Kid
Here comes the book
General
These two are the two doctors I mentioned to you before
Thank you for coming
I heard you are here to save the wounded
Yes
My junior and I have been working in the medicine valley for decades
It's no problem to save the wounded
Great
Many soldiers are seriously injured
It's good that you are here
We can't delay the matter of the people's life
Please
Kid, take the two doctors to Shangming Camp
Yes, sir
Ok, you talk first
Ok
You are here at the right time
It's time
We should discuss the battle with the pirates
We should attack them in two ways
The Shaolin monks are good at fighting
Who said that?
My water quality is top-class
No one can compete with the whole Wu'an Gang
Besides
Even if we attack from the sea
The water quality is not good
You mean you have a better idea
I have an idea
But I have to lose a warship
No
We are not brave enough to lose a warship
I am afraid I can't take the responsibility
Unless
Unless this method works
We can defeat them in one move
Do you remember the ghost ship you met when you first came to Yangzhou?
Ghost ship?
Your masterpiece
Of course
I am not only good at water quality
But also good at woodworking
Do you remember
When your warship was approaching the ghost ship
You were out of control
I remember
You put the magnet around the turntable
Use the magnet to make the turntable
Use the magnetic force to absorb the current
So the current can't control the direction
You know a lot
What do you want to do?
We can change the design of the warship according to the design of the ghost ship
Put the water thunder under the deck of the warship
Become a super thunder bullet
Then let the warship approach the ship
And take the warship out of the port
Then when we meet them
We will make a water thunder
Then
All the warships will be destroyed
It's a feasible plan
But it's too dangerous
Yes
If the pirates don't go to the port
The time to make a water thunder is not right
Any mistake can cause failure
Lu, what do you think?
I think it's ok
According to our original plan
Pretend to surrender
Reduce the attention of the pirates
Before the ship arrives
They will go out of the port to check
To make a big deal
They will go out together
As long as we catch the time to make a water thunder
We can make a big deal
To catch all the ships
But Lu
The problem is we don't have the thunder and fire
Then we can only put the gunpowder in the ship
No
The person who wants to make a thunder will die
Give me the water thunder
Ten days
Can you fix the ship?
Can you?
Since you want to make a water thunder
I can help you
Ok
General Qi is good at fire
If you can help him
The water thunder will be more effective
I will leave the ship and the water thunder to you
No problem
What's wrong?
I met someone
Who?
A pirate
His name is Wang Mazi
Are you sure he is a pirate?
We met in Longdan village
Wang Mazi
Later, when I went to find my body
I found a village
He is in it
How did you find here?
Did the soldiers bring it?
But later the soldiers went to check
And he was gone
He is here
It's not that simple
In my opinion
We should report to Mr. Wu as soon as possible
This is his territory
It should be easy to find him
But we are not sure
I am afraid Mr. Wu won't believe us
I think we should figure out
His purpose of coming to Hangzhou
Then we can make a plan
I saw a fishing rod in his hand
I think his residence should be not far from the city
Then we should go to find him
No need
We will go to the fishing market by Qingbo river tomorrow
He should be there
Why?
When he passed by me today
I smelled a strong fishy smell
And he has fish scales on his blood
More than one kind of fish scales
I think he should be in the fishing market
I have asked around
The fishing market is near Qingbo river
By the way
He has a wave drum in his hand
Wave drum?
Does he still have a wife and children?
I think so
So he is trying to hide the truth
I think he is trying to hide the truth
Maybe
He is trying to get back the evidence
And he is far from the pirates
If he really wants to get back the evidence
He should take his wife and children
And leave the city
Right
Then what is his purpose of hiding here?
We will know when we find out
Brother
You were in the Medicine King Valley
You were so interested in it
And you like to study poison
How many times have you made him angry?
If he sees you now
He will be so angry
I will go to find him
Brother
You are so good at it
I have never seen you like this
Brother
He sees you now
He is so serious about treating the wounds
I think he will be very comforted
Ling'er
Are you ok today?
You can't laugh at me like this
It's not a joke
I think you have changed
Ling'er
In the past
I was so naughty
I wanted to get your feet
But now I know
As long as you can be safe
I will do everything
It's not like what you said
I know
What you said
You don't know
If it wasn't because
Lu Yi was poisoned
I wouldn't have bothered you
Since you came out of the honey
I have been so worried every day
I was afraid you would be caught by Yan Shifan
I didn't expect
I was so worried every day
I almost
This time
Although I was lucky to avoid Yan Shifan
I still didn't find
my sister's daughter
This is my worry
Anyway
I must find her
Ling'er
Don't worry
After the battle
As long as you find her
I will be with you
Tomoko
You are back
I'm back
Welcome back
Dad will be back
How are you today?
I hope you can trust me
Come on
It's okay
Mom is here
Dayou
Wait
Take this
Mohan medicine
Why do you give me this?
Wang Mazi is a thief
You are too honest
I'm afraid you can't handle it
If you find he starts to suspect you
You can use this to make him dizzy
Then he will run away
Of course
It's better to let him know
Don't worry
Be careful
I will be back
Mom
I'm back
There is a corpse on the wall
It should be put on recently
The ashes are not dried yet
It must be very important
It can't be seen
So the room is next to the bed
If someone is outside
They can hear it
Mom
Don't worry
I will take a look
Take this to the bathroom
It's open now
Okay
Brother
We just caught a little
Everyone caught a whole boat
We have been busy all night
We are not in a hurry
Can we make money?
Not enough money?
We should talk to the boat owner
I don't mean that
I'm quite good with you
I'm just curious
how they do it
I just came here
I'm not familiar with it
I am more
powerful than them
Do you want to know how to catch so many fish?
I don't know either.
Go. Let's start.
Okay.
You're going to be in jail.
Don't let the fish fall.
Don't worry.
Let me see the fish in the cage.
Look at that person.
There's a big one on my boat.
Let me see.
I'll go.
There's fish!
Hungry? Want to eat?
Let's get down to business. I'll cook for you.
Yes, yes, yes. What did you find out?
I found something very strange.
This Wang Mazi didn't seem to focus on fishing all night.
It was almost dawn.
There was a boat on the opposite side.
There was a light on the boat.
The boatman was dancing with the light on.
He was spinning in a circle.
I thought it was strange at that time.
But you can only pretend not to notice.
After that, Wang Mazi took the light and did the same action.
Then the boat left.
Isn't it strange?
This must be some kind of secret code.
You're thinking about it.
No matter what the secret code is,
don't think about it so much.
I'll go and make a fish for you.
Wait until we fill our stomachs and think about it.
The gray dance light is spinning.
What does it mean?
Let's think about it after we're full.
Dairou, I'm so hungry.
Everyone, speed up.
It's not far from the teaching day.
Okay.
Come on, lift this up and take a look.
Speed up.
Be careful.
Come on.
It's still stable.
Take a picture and let them sit in line.
Okay.
Come on, I'll put it here.
I said, Lu.
You either go away.
Or don't just stand here and look.
You can't even do it with your hands.
I can't.
If you can't, then just stay where you are.
Don't act like a supervisor.
What?
I can cut the material with my head?
That's not necessary.
You sit here.
Where's your water mine?
Don't make people laugh if you can't get it out.
Don't worry about my business.
Just do your job well.
You don't have to worry about my business.
Let me tell you.
Just do your job.
Don't bother me.
Did I bother you?
You're doing it wrong.
Move aside.
See?
It's a signal.
I know it.
What is this thing?
How to get it by carriage?
They're full of fire.
Fire?
What do they want?
You help the pirates with so many fire.
It's not good.
Easy.
Let's go.
Where are you going?
Catch them.
Or we'll wait for them to run away.
What?
How can we catch them?
You don't know how many people they have.
And so many fire.
If we really get them,
we won't win.
If we fail,
we might lose our lives.
What should we do?
The ship is leaving.
Go.
Let's go down now.
And catch that bastard.
Don't worry.
You've been with him for so many years.
Don't you know I always catch people by this way?
He can't run away.
Catch people by this way?
Yang Mu Yu took his head away.
Go.
Mr. Xia.
You've been thinking about it all the way.
Have you thought of a way?
Of course.
Then go catch them.
Go.
Why are you in a hurry?
You can't run away from the temple.
You have to choose a good time to do it.
Well...
Here, have some tea.
Okay.
Report.
What's up?
General, a scout reported that
a group of bandits moved to Cen Gou.
They will arrive in five days.
How many people?
About 400 to 500 people.
Any fire?
No idea.
Keep investigating.
Report if you have any situation.
Yes.
It seems that the pirates can't hold on.
They want to attack us from the inside and outside.
They want to defeat us.
It's not enough to have hundreds of people come.
But under the pressure of the emperor's seven lines,
people are in panic.
If these two bandits meet,
it will be the last straw to crush our army.
Maybe the crisis is the turn of the tide.
Xie Xiao.
How many days to the ship?
It's five days ahead of the current progress.
No.
If the reinforcements of the Japanese are arrived within five days,
our plan will also change.
You only have three days now.
Can you finish it within three days?
You test me so much.
How can I say no?
I will help him.
I will finish it within three days.
Be careful outside.
I know.
Follow them.
My target is him.
What does it have to do with Wang Mazi's wife?
Wang Mazi is hiding the fire weapon.
How can he be fine?
But it's not enough to catch the bad guys.
We six gates catch the bad guys.
We never harm others.
I also know that this method is a little bit clumsy.
It's not like the way I do it.
But it's special.
It can only be like this.
Who are you?
You are Wang Mazi's maid.
We are the
I didn't expect that she married a person from the East.
But you don't know it's fake.
Let's go in and see.
I'm sorry.
What?
What are you going to do?
Did we make a mistake?
What's the hurry?
There is another box.
This box can't be opened.
Master said that.
You?
Move.
This box can't be opened.
So many fire weapons.
Dayang.
Take all the things away.
Master,
Yesterday,
We deliveredod artifacts to cook prayers
We have twenty-five of them,
And a heavenly hole.
There are eighteen mines.
Overall, the horses of fire are-
restaurants a
Master.
The Javelin was momento
Retreat?
They are afraid.
Master,
Should we by all means.
Kill them?
No need.
Guards.
Let's go back.
Well...
I don't understand.
The people's army is being beaten by us
without any advantage.
Well...
Learn to be patient.
When all our plans are arranged,
we can beat them again.
You're so wise, Chief.
Go tell Wang Mazi
to arrange everything
and wait for my order.
Yes, sir.
I'll go right away.
Wu Shouxu, Wu Shouxu.
You'll never expect
I have this trick.
Hello.
We have something important to see you.
Can you tell us?
I'm sorry, sir.
My master has received the imperial edict.
He went to Cen Gang a few days ago.
What a coincidence.
What should we do?
Do you have any emergency?
Sir,
do you know
who knows Dongying dialect in Hangzhou?
Dongying dialect?
I don't know about others.
I only know that
Mrs. Qi knows Dongying dialect.
Mrs. Qi?
Yes.
She's the wife of Qi Weigang,
from Wang family.
Thank you, sir.
Goodbye.
See you.
Why is it so long?
Come on.
How is it, miss?
Are you from Lushan Sect?
Yes.
Show me your token.
Follow me.
The maid is so polite.
I think Mrs. Qi is not easy.
You're right.
Let's go.
Madam, someone is here.
Mrs. Qi.
Check it for me.
Yes, madam.
Thank you, madam.
I heard that general Qi is a master of formation.
The Yangtze River and Langxian
are necessary weapons, right?
You know general is good at formation in the capital.
Yes.
My head
favors general Qi's formation.
He told us
many changes in it.
For example, the five-shaped formation
used in the general battle
and the three-talented formation
used for the pursuit.
I heard you're from Lushan Sect.
What's the matter?
I heard that Mrs. Qi is good at form.
We have a favor to ask.
General Yu.
You must have received
another imperial edict
to exempt us from
the imperial edict.
Yes.
His Majesty also said
he would not pursue the case for now.
His Majesty is really anxious this time.
He even pursued the imperial edict
for less than a month
before he was released.
If we fail to attack Cenggang again,
I and general Yu's head
will be lost.
I'm worried about
your concern.
The reason for the failure
is the complicated geographical environment.
Mao Haifeng has been hiding.
Although we have been
trapping the bandits for a long time,
we have some reinforcements.
Before you come,
we have decided
to fight with the bandits.
You're so clever.
You've got so many
black fire medicine.
How can we do without them?
The water thunder
opened my eyes.
Don't touch it.
It's okay.
What's the big deal?
But, Lu,
you were the supervisor
when I changed the ship.
I told you to help me.
You said you couldn't.
But you're good at it.
It's different.
You're just a rough man.
What's the use of the cowhide bag?
To prevent the hidden heart from being teased.
The cowhide bag is not water-proof.
Why didn't I think of this?
Only a guard like you
can think of this.
The fire is very dangerous.
If you're not careful,
it will be a big trouble.
Xie Xiang,
follow me to check the ship.
Don't be a nuisance here.
Don't be a nuisance.
What are you doing in the water?
What's the purpose of the water?
Why are you here?
Master goes fishing every day.
He works as a fisherman.
A fisherman?
Then,
where did you get the oysters
from?
What do you mean?
I'm sorry.
I really don't know.
The owner of the box
was the one who took it home the other day.
He told me not to touch it.
I didn't see the contents of the box.
I really didn't know
the oysters were in it.
Master,
you're a man.
What are you doing?
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
Master goes fishing every day
and comes back when he sells out the fish.
I don't
listen to the work.
I see.
Is that so?
You're hungry, right?
I'll make you some food.
My lady,
please.
Let me and Sadoko go home.
She's begging you to let them go.
My lady,
does she know where the oysters are from?
It's okay.
She knows nothing.
She doesn't even know what her husband does.
Guards,
take her to rest.
Yes.
Please.
Hey, Thomas.
Take a rest.
I'm leaving.
How could she
not know what her husband does?
It's the tradition of the Eastern Yang people.
Women can't ask what men do.
The rain falls, I'm lost.
My mind is messed up.
The wind blows, I'm shocked.
My heart is blank.
Thousands of miles of ambush come and go.
Who is out of the city
can't compare to fate.
Cities crews are in battle every day
foi zi xiu
HAN
Y
Orchestra
Audins
The
arrangement
and ton
can turn your snow
I've seen through the changes in life.
It's like saying goodbye.
It's too sad to say goodbye.
I remember the day
when I met you.
My hair was grey from the rain.
We spent our years together.
In the dream, we talked for years.
The Long Ballad
Episode 18