YoYo English Channel YouTube
The song is over
I hear
Your heartbeat is still in my ears
Just a moment
Separate twice
Never to be found again
I see
Your tears are falling in my heart
I'm afraid a blink of an eye
Will disappear
Ooh
Seven stars come to light up
Seven stars guide the direction
Doubing east is spring
Doubing south is summer
Doubing west is autumn
Doubing north is winter
One two three
Three two one
One two three four five six seven
Seven six five four three two one
Seven stars come to light up
Does it sound good?
I'll read it for you
Read it
Seven stars come to light up
Seven stars guide the direction
Ling
What's wrong?
Brother Yang
What happened?
When I was delivering the medicine to Lu Yi
I heard Jin Xia sing a song
This song was written by my sister
We taught the child to sing
Did you hear it wrong?
No, I heard it very clearly
There won't be any mistakes
It may be a coincidence
Maybe your sister taught someone else
Maybe someone else heard it
And learned it
Impossible
Only my sister and I know this song
No one else knows it
Brother Yang, tell me
Is Jin Xia my sister's child?
Is she my sister's child?
How could it be Jin Xia?
No
Ling, I told you
Your sister's child was kidnapped by a human trafficker
You have to believe me
But
It's late, go back and rest
You are wrong
Maybe you have some reasons
You don't want to tell me
But it doesn't matter
I will find out the truth
One, two, three
Three, two, one
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven
Seven, six, five, four, three, two, one
Seven stars shine
Seven stars guide the direction
The east is the spring
The south is the summer
The west is the autumn
The north is the winter
One, two, three
Three, two, one
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven
Seven, six, five, four, three, two, one
She is asleep
Sister, tell me
Is Jinxia your child?
Lord Xu
Priest Lan
Please
I think Yan Song didn't expect that
Liao Wenhua was expelled
and died in the way back home
Yes
Liao Wenhua is brave but he doesn't dare to be
I heard that the emperor wanted to punish him
but he died
We are one less opponent
after Liao Wenhua died
Lord Xu, if you need anything in the future
just tell me
If he is not mature enough
and doesn't have any new moves
we should be more careful
in case Yan Dang notices it
and we will be in a tight spot
Although we failed to defeat Yan Dang
I'm afraid Liao Wenhua's reputation
will be ruined
The first one to be expelled
should be Wu Shouxu
I'm sorry
Aunt Lin
Jinxia
Come, have some chicken soup
You must be tired from taking care of the wounded
I saw you were in a bad mood yesterday
I asked Dayang to make chicken soup for you
to nourish your body
Jinxia, thank you
You are welcome
I always see you as my own family
You are an elder
but you treat me so well
I don't think you can do it
By the way
the song you sang yesterday
where did you learn it?
Tong...
You mean the seven stars in Beidou?
I learned it in the hall
Hall?
My mother brought me back from the hall
Who taught you to sing in the hall?
Who else can do it?
I really don't remember who taught me
Anyway, all the kids in the hall can do it
What's wrong, Aunt Lin?
You know this song, too?
This song
is a very important person in my life
What a coincidence!
Where is he now?
He has passed away
I'm sorry
I sang this song
and reminded you of your old friend
It's okay
Thanks to you
I can remember him
It's been so many years
I can't remember his face
Aunt Lin, don't be sad
If you're like this
your old friend in heaven
will be sad
Drink the chicken soup
It won't taste good when it gets cold
Okay
Where is the medicine?
It's for Xie Xiao
I'll send it to him
Okay
Is it ready now?
Yes
I'll take it out
Take it out
It must be bitter
Take it
Okay
Drink the chicken soup
The light and the dull
can be a beautiful lake
Its day and night
is filled with lightness
Its beauty...
I heard that two heroes
have broken their records
Hero
Tell me about your battle field
Warrior Yuan
Can you knock on the door?
Can you be more reserved?
Why are you shy
today?
I think you're not only
injured
but also hurt your brain
Who said I was injured?
Who?
Who slanders me like this?
It's not a shame
to be injured
Why can't I let others know?
Let me see your wound
No, no, no
What?
Is this my wound?
You think I'm under the
treacherous fire of the pirates
I'm not afraid of death
I'll use the water thunder
to destroy the pirates' old nest
and turn the war machine around
Is this wound?
This is honor
But I heard that
someone almost died
If it wasn't for your effort
you would have died
I don't need to save that person
I can't save Lu
If he didn't drag me
would I be injured?
Listen
I'm the most powerful
in this battle
When I was badly injured
and killed by the pirates
Lu was waiting for me
to save him
I used my power
to protect him
with my own life
It must be
Lord Lu who lied to me
He told me
you were begging
to owe him a life
Fine
I admit that he saved me
How can he do it
without my help?
Lord did say that
you did the most merit
If he didn't help you
he couldn't do it alone
See, that's right
How can he win
without me?
Right?
Xie Yuanyuan
I really admire you
Of course
You didn't have a chance
to see my ability
Think about it
Two years ago
I was wandering around
and fought against the black coffins
with Brother Sha
I helped the poor
I was so proud
I don't know
how many people admired me
Hero Xie
Even if you are a rich man
whether it's a black coffins or a white coffins
you are just a robber
You are breaking the law
How dare you say that in front of a rich man?
Aren't you afraid that
I will arrest you and punish you?
Those black coffins
won't admit it
If you do this again
don't tell me
Here, take the medicine
What? What's wrong?
It's bitter
Bitter is a good medicine
It's ok
I told aunt Lin
not to make medicine with you anymore
Otherwise, you will be in pain
I will drink it
Does it hurt?
It's a fist
Take a good rest
I don't know what to do
I am in pain
I see that
the emperor is so happy
The two families are in a good mood
I think that
the emperor has been
in a good mood recently
He is in a good mood
Yes
But the recovery of Ceng Gang
has finished me
It's a big deal
I feel relieved
I feel much better
I am so surprised
I didn't expect it
I am flattered
I just want to tell you
The emperor has been practicing
The emperor will be back
But now
Ceng Gang is in a bad mood
The two families are in a mess
Liao Wenhua is dead
The army is back
But in my case
the most important thing is
the report of Tan He and Wu Shouxu
Many people have doubts
about Wu Shouxu
Lu Aiqing, what do you think?
Your Majesty
It's a big deal
I don't dare to say it
I think we can
leave it to the cabinet
Lord Yan and Lord Xu
will give you
a satisfactory answer
Forget it
You
You are so clean
It's a waste to ask you
Li Fang
Yes
Take care of him
Father, you want to see me?
You are here
Come and see
The imperial edict just sent by the emperor
It seems that
the report of Tan He and Wu Shouxu
has been effective
The emperor has decided
to withdraw the post of governor
The emperor means
to withdraw Wu Shouxu
but there is no suitable candidate
Let me recommend someone
I'm going to
be selected by you
Father
The emperor doesn't want you
to recommend a candidate
He has already
decided the candidate
He wants to ask you
The aunt here
refers to the imperial censor Wang Yi
The emperor wants Wang Yi
to replace Wu Shouxu
Father
You don't have to recommend a candidate
You just need to follow the emperor's will
There will be no mistake
Go
I'm sorry
Aunt Lin, how is she?
She was weak in the beginning
It's not easy for her
to survive until now
She has something to tell you
Jinxia
Big brother
I know I'm dying
This is the retribution I deserve
What retribution?
Don't talk nonsense
Jinxia
Listen to me
I saw you and Mrs. Qi
these days
I just found out
that women can live like this
I really envy you
You can face difficulties so bravely
I'm so happy
to see you
To face difficulties
I envy you more
You live so freely
And you have a group of friends
who stand up for you
You are a good girl
I have done so many things
that hurt you
I hate myself
Miss Lin
I'm sorry
She's gone
Maybe it's the biggest relief for her
I'm sorry
Zengfu
bury Ming'er
Yes
I hope she can be free in the next life
Your Majesty
This is the reply from Yan Ge
Read it
Yes
The officials are talented
Don't run away from the holy sword
Help the people to be wise
I dare not doubt
The one who knows the battle
Yan Songye
Good
Your Excellency
Your Excellency, you are dying
I was wondering why you were not in the room
You were practicing martial arts here
I'm fine
What?
You don't know your injury is serious?
I should move more because of the injury
It's good for recovery
I know my injury
You don't have to worry
What's your excuse?
You should rest when you are injured
You can recover fast
Come on, drink the medicine
You feed me
Why do you need me to feed you?
Maybe I was not able to stand up
because of the practice
I can't even lift my arm
Stop lying
Really
The wound may be broken
Let me see
It's okay
It's just a small injury
I told you not to move
You are so annoying
Come on, drink the medicine
After you drink the medicine
you should go back to your room
and have a good rest
Don't move
Sir
What's up?
General Yu is here
General Yu is here?
Let's go, I'll take you to see him
Drink the medicine first
The last sip
Okay, sit down
General, you are back
Brother Lu
Are you feeling better?
Thank you for your concern
I am fine now
That's good
General
I am fine now
That's good
General
This is Yuan Jin Xia
Jin Xia
Yu Dayong, General Yu
Miss Yuan
I have heard that you are a man of great martial arts
I am so honored to meet you
Miss Yuan, you are too kind
You are the one that Mrs. Qi mentioned
the one who can stop the female
I am here to see Brother Lu's injury
Secondly
Mr. Wu has given me a lot of instructions
He asked me to tell the members of the Six Faction Sect
to come here
Miss Yuan
Where are the other members?
General, please wait
I'll go and ask Master and the others to come here
Okay
General, please
Please
I heard that General Qi has captured Dong Qisheng
Yes
He has already been handed over to Mr. Wu
He is now in the prison of the capital
General, I want to see him
Okay
I'll arrange it
You can go now
Yes
I'll go now
I'll arrange it
General Yi
Yang Li
Brother
It's really you
Yang Li
You have no news after you left
I have missed you for a long time
You even asked me to find you
I didn't expect to see you here today
We are not meant to be
Yes
Master, he...
After you left
Master has been missing you
He took me to find you
But he had no reason
He kept missing your name
until he died
I feel sorry for him
Okay
It's all in the past
If he knew it
he would forgive you
So he and General Yu are old friends
and they agreed to be a family
Yes
He said he would enter the capital
and get a title
He even changed his name when he left
At first, we knew you were in the imperial guard
But we didn't know you were there
Brother
It's all in the past
Forget it
Let me introduce you
Yu
This is your uncle
This is Yang Yue
Hello, uncle
Don't stand on ceremony
You are a child
Yes
Time flies
This is my apprentice Yuan Jinxia
Uncle
Okay
I like your apprentice
He is more beautiful than me
The Empress Dowager's Residence
Young Master
Yan Shaoqiong is here
What do you want?
Young Master
You falsely claimed the name of Yan Shang, Sima Chang'an
and dug up the mine in Hangzhou
Now it's a mess
Although the government has sealed the Sima Mansion
Sima Chang'an has been imprisoned
But his name is out
As the president of the Four Salt Depots
I will be involved
Young Master
Please think of a way
If His Majesty blames us
You, the Four Salt Depots
can charge 400,000 taels of salt tax every year
Why would His Majesty
take your position because of a small salt merchant?
Can't you get along with Ku Ying?
Besides
Father and I are with His Majesty
What are you afraid of?
I'm worried
About what?
About my selling you
I dare not
Enough
Go back and be your Four Salt Depots
Don't bother me with these important things
Thank you for your advice
Young Master, you're so smart
When will you finish the mine I told you to build?
It will be completed in a short time
Hurry up
It will be completed before the treasures in Hangzhou are delivered
Don't worry, Young Master
I will make it happen
Zhi Han
Sir
How is it?
Did Dong Jisheng confess?
No
He didn't
But
He offered to let himself go
as a replacement
Send the tiger back to the mountain?
How is that possible?
It's clear that
he is colluding with Mao Haifeng
It seems that
the food and food case
must be found by Yan Shi Fan
who was mentioned by Mr. Lu
to find the truth
The Imperial Guards have sent people to investigate
But the whereabouts are unknown
In this situation
it's likely that he has been killed
Forget it
As long as he is brought back to the capital
the court will stop
the talk about me
At least
my internal worries
can be solved for the time being
Mr. Wu
Do you really think that there is no danger?
Mao Haifeng has started a war
to rebel in the southeast
The ambitious people
will surely come to the rear
We have to be careful
Mr. Lu's opinion
is exactly what I want to say
The
chaos of the Japanese is not
easily eliminated
These weapons
were collected
from the military camp by General Yu
I just checked
Most of the weapons
have the symbol of the Japanese
Obviously, it was provided by the Japanese
Since the Japanese can support Mao Haifeng
they can support others
Mr. Wu
I have always been very well-educated
in the fire department
I wonder if you
can let me take back a bird's nest
and study it
Please do
Sister Shen Wen
What are you doing?
I'm going to the capital
I thought you were just practicing martial arts
I didn't expect you to know how to do the female martial arts
I admire you
It's my first time to try it
I've never done it before
You can sew it so delicately
It's amazing
Dayang is really lucky
Don't praise me
I'm not as good as Dayang
It's okay if he doesn't dislike it
How can he dislike it?
He's too happy to be late
Sister
Dayang is an honest person
He may be a little bit
ignorant of his daughter's feelings
Please forgive him
He is indeed ignorant
He is not as clever as Mr. Lu
He knows how to look down on his daughter
Why did you mention Mr. Lu?
I think you and Mr. Lu
don't have a normal relationship
Look at each other's eyes
It's different
Really?
I can't hide it from you
But Mr. Lu and I
are not as good as you and Dayang
We can be together without any worries
Lu is a high-ranking official
I'm just a small supplement
I don't have a fancy family
My master also said
I have a different identity from you
I should stay away from you
What does he mean?
He said he didn't care about the family
I don't know
According to Mr. Lu
he said he didn't care
He must have no family
I believe him
So even if the future is full of unknown
I'm not afraid
Cherish the future
Who knows the future?
Aunt Lin
Aunt Lin, come and have a look
Sister Shangguan is sewing clothes for Dayang
Let's see how she does it
Let me see
It's her first time
Look
The thread is a little crooked
It's not the same size
Let me teach you
It's really the same
I just know a little
You're too modest
Dr. Lin
You're so good at it
You should teach me more
Okay
Jinxia
Why is your neck red?
Did a mosquito sting you?
I'm very sensitive to mosquitoes
My brothers in the Sixth
Are you talking about the Seven Stars of Beidou?
I learned it in the pond
Pond
My mother took me back from the pond
Aunt Lin
What are you thinking?
Nothing
I'm a little confused
Jinxia said she was an orphan
It's just a coincidence
I'm not an orphan
It's the same
The parts of Yan Shi Fan's mine
are stored here
No wonder he wants to hide his identity
Ning Feng
Add more people
and open up the iron mine
we found before
We must keep up with the production
If the ore in the mine is mass-produced
and the parts are used on the fire
the power of the fire
will be much greater
It's okay to dig the iron mine
It's a crime to create weapons
in the mine
It seems that Yan Shi Fan
and Mao Hai Feng
are related to this
It seems that Yan Shi Fan
and Mao Hai Feng
Come, eat
Great, the food is here
The food is here
Sir, sir
Thank you, sir
Come, eat
Sir
Sir, here
Here, here
Come, eat
Sir, sir
Here, put it here
Thank you, sir
Come, eat
Sir, I don't have it here
Sir, sir
Wait
Sir, this way
Here, yours
Mine
Come, eat
Here, here, here
Here you are
Help, help
Help
Hurry, help
Hurry, open the door
He's dead
Report to the officer
Yes
He's dead
The two states are in chaos
That's why the Shao family is at peace
If this is to change the governor
I'm afraid it will cause chaos
Sir, the news just came
Dong Qisheng died in the prison
Died
Yes, he was poisoned
It's not an accident
His death can do a lot of things
It seems that Wu Shouxu wants to keep his position
He has to put some effort into it
Should we go and check
Who poisoned Dong Qisheng
Wu Shouxu has Xu Wei by his side
Of course we will go and check
But Dong Qisheng
Died in the prison of the Governor's mansion
It seems that the man in the mansion
Has been arranged by someone
I'll go to the Governor's mansion
I'll go with you
No, I'll go by myself
Yes
Sir, Dong Qisheng died in the prison
Did he spit something out?
It's said that the man in Wu Shouxu's mansion
Didn't do anything
But he had a deal with Lu Yi
He wanted to use a confession
To ask Lu Yi to release him
Luckily, Luo Longwen acted in time
Before he said anything
He killed him
Lu Yi is not a fool
Mao Haifeng ran away
Wu Shouxu even wanted to use Dong Qisheng
To get the credit
How could he let him go so easily?
Where is Zhai Lanye?
Since Mao Haifeng burned down the mansion
He has been missing
He will see people and dead people
Yes
By the way, sir
The man you asked to find has arrived
Let him come here
Yes
I've been looking for a long time
I can't see it
What's wrong with this painting?
Sir
This painting is not a real one
It's just a copy
Tell me
How can it be a copy?
From Wu Jiao
We can know if it's a copy or not
You are not Zhang Zhengdao
How can you know what the bird should draw?
If you say so
It's a fake
How can I believe you?
Zhang Zhuo, who is the master of the Jinren's mansion
He has studied the painting of Qingming Shanghe
He has written a lot of details about Qingming Shanghe
It's written in this book
Sir
About the real painting of Qingming Shanghe
Many people don't know
Song Huizong wrote it in the paper
Zhang Zhengdao took it to the mansion after he finished it
After that
Song Huizong did write the five thousand in the paper
And added the Double Dragon Seal
Then many people have many books
Many people don't know that the real one is left out
But the paper was removed
You mean
If the real one doesn't have the poem
The poem of the painting of Qingming Shanghe
Yes
Nianfeng, take him to get the reward
Thank you
Please
Good
You dare to lie to me with the fake one
Huang Yu
I can make you the official
I can also make you die
Sir, Mr. Lu is here
Mr. Lu
I have heard about Dong Qisheng
I have sent someone to investigate who did it
If the imperial guards want to take it
I can ask Zhihang to give you the files
I am here not to investigate Dong Qisheng's death
But to remind you
Although the situation in Cengang is serious
But you may not be able to take the position of governor
I know
You are in the army
You are fighting against the pirates and are for the people
You have some prestige
If you are removed
You will involve the soldiers in front
Then the army will be unstable
The pirates will be in danger
The people will be in danger again
Mr. Lu, you are not just here to remind me
You must have a way to solve this problem
Right?
The emperor likes to listen to the order of the heaven
I think you know
I have heard that in the Tiantai Mountain in Jiangzhe
There are often beasts in the mountain area
Mr. Lu, you mean
The Cengang Festival is a good thing for the emperor
The country is going to be prosperous
If we can find a good thing
To offer to the emperor
It will be a great success
Then we will change the governor
And we will reconsider
It's a good idea
But the thing about the beast
It's just a rumor
We can only listen to the order of the heaven
The heart is in a whirl
A thousand miles of ambush
Who is born out of the world
Can't beat fate
Close your eyes, I can see your face
Open your eyes, the north is cold
The sword is full of sky
Who has conquered the world
No sound, the dark is coming
Fate is turning
See the change in the world
Like farewell, farewell is too sad
The yearning is golden
The day I met you
White hair from the old days
We spent the years together
In the dream, a thousand years
I want to tell you