YoYo English Channel YouTube
The song is over
I hear
Your heartbeats are still in my ears
Just a moment
Separate two sides
Never to be found again
I see
Your tears are falling in my heart
I'm afraid a blink of an eye
Will disappear
The Untamed
YoYo English Channel YouTube
Lord Yan
What brings you here, Lord Lu?
Did Yuan Bu Kui come to Lord Yan
To find Doctor Lin?
No
Lord Lu, why do you ask about Yuan Bu Kui?
What's wrong with him?
I heard that a few days ago
Lord Yan caught Doctor Lin again
You are a doctor
It takes evidence to catch a criminal
This is the rule
Since Yuan Bu Kui didn't come to find Lord Yan
I'll leave now
Next time, bring me some evidence
Bring it on
Lord, you know that
Yan Shi Fan won't admit it
Why do you still come here?
I came to let him know
I already know
Since he doesn't admit it
Then I'll use my own way
Lord Yan
Yan Shao Qiong was caught by Xu Jing and Lu Yi
In the prison
You can bear this?
Bear?
Why should I bear?
I've prepared a play
Waiting for the people to gather
So that we can start the show
Yan Shi Fan, what are you doing?
Let me go
Don't touch me
Life and death are impermanent
Disperse and never come back
You can't be with your loved ones
You have to love and hate each other
I'm sorry
I really enjoy this kind of pain
But I don't know if Lu Yi
Likes it or not
You're crazy
Let me go
What is this?
This is a small gift for you
Miss, to be honest
I like you
I wanted to keep you
And accompany my Ling'er
To be her partner
But your lover is so despicable
He dares to go against my Yan family
If you want to hate him, go ahead
I don't have a lover
Lu Yi and I have been separated
He won't be threatened by us
Really?
Then who came to me today?
To ask me for someone?
Well, girl
Let's make a bet
See if your life is important to him
If he has feelings for you
He will try his best to save me
If he has no feelings for you
It means that your life is over
Bastard
What are you doing?
Yuan Shifan
I haven't seen anyone
Who can come down alive
When being targeted by this
No
Bear with it
Bastard
I will never let you go
Go on
The people who were tied up here
And told you the same words
They are so beautiful
But I haven't seen them
They become something else
To come to me
If you want to kill me
Just give me a beating
I like you
Seeing others suffer
And torture me
It makes me happy
You'd better not let me live
Or I will kill you
And avenge our family
Avenge your family?
Well
You must not know
Except for our family
You have a bigger enemy
The one who forced Qiu Cheng to write the negotiation letter
It's not me
But Lu Ting
You think I believe you
Just because you said so
I can't help it if you don't believe me
But as long as you are alive
You can ask Lu Yi
By the way
I remember it all of a sudden
Miss
You must hold on
You must live well
I'm looking forward to
Seeing your disappointment to Lu Yi
Hold on
Why didn't I
Put you in front of the camera
What are you doing?
Give it back to me
Let me use it
Yan Fang
Young Master
You take care of the rest
Take care of it
Yes
Yuan Shifan
You are so stupid
You can't die
Brother Lu
How is it?
Where is Xia Er?
I don't know
Where is Yan Shifan?
Take this girl away
Yes
What are you doing?
Let her go
Don't move
Let me go
Yan Shifan knows
Jin Xia's identity
He won't spare her
I'm going to beg Yan Shifan
I'm going to beg him to let her go
Dr.Yun
Ming'er
You are going to be
In danger of Yan Shifan's death
What should we do?
We can't wait for him in vain
I will go back to Beizhen Prefecture
Send someone to check
Where is Jin Xia
Thank you, Mr. Lu
Yan Shifan
Yue'er
You should keep them safe
Then inform Xiao'er
I will go back to Lushan Gate
And bring someone to find Xia'er
Okay, father
Be careful
Uncle Gan
I'll help you to my room
Come
Young Master
Last night someone broke into the villa
And saved Lin Ling and the guy
Called Uncle Gan
What happened?
Isn't the guard there very strict?
He is not weak
And he takes a break
So they didn't take good care of him
You are all useless
You can all die
Take this hairpin
And give it to Lu Yi
Yes
Yan Shaoqiong
Although he didn't make much progress
But Yan Shifan is not a good person
Give this to the commander
Yes
Sir
Yan Feng sent this just now
And I will give it to you
Yes
Yan Feng
This hairpin
Yan Feng will give it to you
What did he say?
Nothing
Sir
I want to see Yan Shaoqiong
Please come in
Mr. Lu
Sorry to keep you waiting
Sit down
Where is Jin Xia?
That girl
Mr. Lu
Yan Feng just sent you the hairpin
And you followed her
And you are so anxious
It seems that you are so fond of her
What happened to her?
I prepared a surprise for you
What do you mean?
My stuff
Is not like the rough torture
In your prison
The blood
Will be dropped
By the long nail
That is covered with blood
And it will be cut
And it will be dropped
And spread to the foot
And by adjusting the length of the nail
People will not die immediately
But they will wait until the blood is dried
The more blood is left
The colder people will be
What do you want?
What do you think?
What is your condition?
Yan Shaoqiong's statement
Don't stare at me like that
You should think about that little cutie
She must be cold now
Dad
Yan Shaoqiong's statement
You haven't finished it yet, right?
Why are you in such a hurry?
Yan Shi Fan
What does he want from you?
Nothing
You haven't finished it yet, right?
I will give it to His Majesty tomorrow
Give it back to me first
I have urgent business
What urgent business?
Anyway, it's urgent
Give it back to me first
Those statements
Are evidence that His Majesty wants to investigate Yan Shaoqiong's corruption
How dare you take it to someone else?
Dad, it's a matter of life and death
It's too late to eat it
Give me back the statement first
No
Dad
I beg you
I have never seen you like this since I was a child
I heard Yan Feng gave you a hairpin
You really did it for women
Yan Shi Fan threatened you with it
Let you give Yan Shaoqiong's statement
When did you become so feminine?
It's a matter of liking a girl
But it can't delay the business
Dad
Dad, let's talk about it after I come back
Give me the statement first
No
Dad
He might be dead for real
Now he is being held by Yan Shi Fan
If he drags on and blood flows down
He will die
I know Yan Shi Fan's whereabouts in the city
You can send someone to search
But you can't take the statement
Besides, it's impossible to let Yan Shaoqiong be convicted again
I can't care about it anymore
I have my own way to deal with Yan Shaoqiong
Yan Shi Fan wants to take Yan Shaoqiong's statement
Just to save him
Do you think he will be stupid enough to be convicted again?
Besides, you think Yan Shi Fan will release Yan Shaoqiong
after you give him the statement?
I have no other choice
I have to do this
I have to make a bet
You really let me down
Dad
Have you forgotten how mom died?
Mom
I can't forget the pain of losing mom
I don't want anyone to die because of me
Yan Shi Fan took Jin Xia
and threatened me with her life
I know Yan Shi Fan's intention
Besides, do you know who is the girl Yan Shi Fan took away?
She is Xia Ran's granddaughter
You know how Xia Ran's family died
Now her granddaughter is in danger because of me
You just let her die because of me?
Well, you go to find Yan Shi Fan
I will send someone to search
Please
I hope this girl can be blessed
You are lucky
Thank you, dad
You can't die
I can't sleep
I have to live
I really understand this
I can't die
But who can save me?
Who can save me?
Supervisor Lu
You are so quick
I took what you want
Tell me where is it
I will give it to you
You have to show me first
Tell me where it is
It's late
Do you know
The long nail pierces into the body
The blood flows down
How long will it take for people to die?
I know
People won't die when the blood flows dry
They can't live for two days
But I think
The girl's body should be more than tonight
Tell me where is it
I will show you
I'm not in a hurry
Because you are more anxious than me
Then wait
But wait for a while
When it's dark, you don't have to worry
Because it's useless even if you find it
Tell me where it is
Don't yell at me
I will tell you
Where is it
Don't yell at me
I will tell you
Will you give it to me?
It's true
Now
You have to beg me
You beg me to tell you
Where is Yuan Jinxia
Maybe I will tell you
When I feel soft
You beg me
I beg you
Tell me where is Jinxia now
Begging
Do I need to teach you?
Do you want to die?
No
Please
Sir
I'm so happy.
Lu Yi.
They say men have gold under their heart.
You kneel down to me for a little girl.
I'm really moved by you.
I thought that even if she died,
she would die with her family.
As for the real location,
you can guess it yourself.
You have to guess it well.
If you guess it wrong or it's too late,
you'll be dead.
Don't blame me.
I'll die with my family.
My family.
Xia Ran.
Xia's Mansion.
Lian Yi.
How's Uncle Gai?
He just took the medicine and fell asleep.
Any news about Jin Xia?
We've got the news.
Lu Yi has gone to Xia's Mansion to find Jin Xia.
My father, Xi and Xie Xiao have gone there.
Let's go.
Search.
Don't let go of anything.
Yes.
Go.
Go there.
Yes.
Go.
Senior.
There's nothing there.
Let's go to the villa.
Okay.
Go.
Yes.
It's fine, Wen'er.
Really?
I feel I need this precious energy 갚先帐,
take care of Wen'er.
Okay.
Do you still remember?
Remember me?
Each of us..."
Everyone against his own will
Sir, he is bullying you
Sir.
Do you want me to carry you?
No, you can't.
I'm not that afraid of people.
When I was about to lose hope,
you appeared.
Is it worth it
if I offend him?
I can tolerate him
to trample me under his feet,
but I can't
hurt you.
Sir.
I've been thinking for a whole night.
If I can marry you,
I'll be happy.
If I can't marry you,
I'll be scared to death.
It's my destiny.
You know my woman is generous.
You won't take this little grudge
to heart.
Of course.
Who is your husband?
Yuan Jinxia.
I told you not to move.
Why are you so unfamiliar?
Huh?
So you really want to marry someone?
You keep second guessing.
Who do you want to marry?
Sir.
Creamed meals have no withered fruit.
Sir, I've searched several secret rooms,
but I didn't find Jin Xia.
You didn't find her?
If something bad happens to Jin Xia,
I'll behead Yan Shi Fan!
Lu!
Didn't you promise to take good care of Yuan Jin Xia?
Now, how did you treat her?
Your identity will be exposed.
It'll be the shame of our Lu family.
I'm the one who killed her.
Xie Xiao, calm down.
Father, how is she?
Yue.
Where is Jin Xia?
Where is she?
Did you find her?
I think it's open now.
And they look strange.
No wonder.
But he named it starred star!
His Dhola...
Yuesheng?
He's the man so why ask you to place he here?
Doctor Lin.
Tomorrow morning,
we'll take theLao movies.
There, you can tell me.
Ruo Qing and Doggie?
Yes.
Go to see him.
Go to check him.
Do you know where the mechanism of the water flow is?
I don't know.
My lord.
Did you find anything?
Someone must have touched this place.
We lost our loved ones.
Didn't you two.
I don't have to be worried.
Jinxia.
auspicious.
寡人心兮em добав2不知道的
Gauze
Bren вами
How could your son achieve so far?
The blood has stopped
We need to use medicine to cure the blood
When will he wake up?
I don't know
We need to observe for a few days
Well
We have so many people here
It will affect Xia'er's rest
We can leave one or two people to take care of her
Others can leave
Sir Lu
You have been looking for Jin Xia all day and night
You should go back and rest
We will take care of her
I should stay
I am worried about giving Jin Xia to you
So we should take care of Jin Xia
We should all go out
Let Jin Xia recover her blood
Doctor Lin has said something
Let's go out
Go
Jin Xia
The cat is afraid of water
It's so sad
Sir
Don't you think I am sad too?
You are sad
It's so painful
Sister Yuan
You have been busy all day
You should go to bed early
I will go back to my room
How is Jin Xia?
Is she safe?
Sister Yuan
Don't worry
Her breath and pulse are stable
She will wake up soon
Lu Yi
He is so kind
He saved Jin Xia
He has been watching Jin Xia all day
I hope these two kids
Sister Yuan
You are so kind to Jin Xia
Go to bed early
Although Jin Xia is very poor
But I am lucky to have you
I am lucky to have you
Sister Yuan
I really thank you
I heard Lu Yi
He kneeled to you
To save his subordinate
You have got your face back
It's nothing
Sir, Lu Yi found Yuan Jin Xia
And he saved her
I am so happy
Love
Sir Lu
You have been unconscious for two days and nights
You will fall down
I am fine
I will not fall
I must accompany Jin Xia
I...
Jin Xia.
You're awake.
Sir.
You're finally awake.
I...
Sir saved me.
I've separated from Lu Yi.
He won't be threatened by you.
Really?
Then who came to my house today
and asked me for help?
Let's make a bet.
See if your life is more important to him.
If he's kind to you,
he'll definitely try his best to save you.
Sir, aren't you going to separate from me?
Why are you saving me?
The love hidden behind the curtain
is always unreachable.
I'll be silent for the rest of my life.
I'll be helpless.
Dr. Lin,
you're awake.
I'll go find you now.
I'll be silent for the rest of my life.
I'll protect you from the
torrent of life.
Jin Xia.
I...
Great.
You're finally awake.
Open your eyes, the north is cold.
The island is filled with sky.
Who has conquered the mortal world?
I'll be silent for the rest of my life.
You're much better.
Your pulse is also smooth.
I've seen through the changes.
I want to say goodbye.
It's too hurtful to say goodbye.
Dr. Lin,
Jin Xia is fine now.
I'll leave her to you.
I'll go back first.
I've seen through
the changes..
Go...
Surely,
we'll
be without anyone.
Could you promise me
Sit down.
How is that girl?
She just woke up.
Father, why are you so serious?
I'm not that serious.
I'm old.
Today I went to the face-off.
Yan Ge asked about
Yan Shaoqiong's case.
We couldn't get any evidence to prove his innocence.
His Majesty scolded us.
So he ordered to let go of Yan Shaoqiong.
In this way,
Yan's words are more arrogant.
Young Master, Yuan Jinxia is awake.
Yan Shaoqiong
She is so hard-working.
She's alive.
I believe Lu Yi will never expect
that after she wakes up,
her feeling
will be changed very much.
Young Master, Yan Shaoqiong was released.
Do you want me to settle him?
Call her here.
I want to ask her.
If she really wants to betray us,
I won't let her off.
Yes.
What are you doing?
You're here.
I'm making pork liver porridge for Jin Xia.
She's bled so much.
She'll recover faster if she eats more pork liver.
Sometimes I care about her.
I finally found a good man.
But I didn't expect that it's fate.
That's right.
Jin Xia is usually bold and heartless.
In fact, she's sensitive.
If this happens,
she might feel guilty
and feel uncomfortable with herself.
Yes.
But I still hope
she can get through this with you.
That's right.
After going through so much,
I really think
as long as she's alive,
there's nothing she can't get through.
Right?
Yes.
I hope she can get out of her heart as soon as possible.
Oh.
I'm making a red bean porridge for her.
It'll help her recover faster.
I've prepared every meal for her.
It's important to let her recover first.
Okay.
I'll help you.
You're just like the sea of fate.
When I close my eyes,
I can see your face.
When I open my eyes,
I can see the coldness in the back of my eyes.
The sword is full of sweet words.
In the middle of the mortal world,
who has conquered the world?
The sound of a dance
does a
The Untamed
Episode 18