Gyeong seong Creature S2
I was a special kid when I was little.
Killing is okay
But it was discovered
It is not allowed
Why?
If you are a good son, you should answer "yes"
It's rude to ask "why?"
Katsuaki
It's the mother
I want my mother's approval.
Even just once
I want to feel comforted
Although it is not yet clear
Why is it that only child has tentacles?
But I have a guess in my mind
What kind of guess?
Different from other experimental subjects
Sheng Zhao inherited the Na people's
Are you a narrator?
The first person in the mother's womb
A lot of learning has been done
Then it entered the child's body
This makes the synchronization phenomenon more active
Just like
Xingqin to protect his daughter
It's like my body suddenly activated
In that child's mind
Does Akiko's motherhood also exist?
Maybe
interesting
I knew then
I'm not something special.
I just
Just a special experimental subject
Have you met Mr. Zhang?
yes
Meet
I'll leave the next plan up to you.
Katsuaki
Did you get some sleep?
How is your injury?
how?
Is it still painful?
If this is a dream
I really hope I never wake up
I miss you so much
No matter how many times I say "I miss you"
Can't fill my thoughts
I miss you so much
How's No. 71?
Not found yet
You did it, didn't you?
What on earth are you thinking about?
Set him free
free
That's not freedom
That's chaos, make no mistake.
No matter what
At least it should be more fun than you think.
What do you mean?
I know all
I know what you want to do
Very hungry
Oh, how much did you drink tonight?
I haven't sobered up yet.
Hello sir
Very hungry
Something happened
The Border between Life and Death of Beijing Monster
Part 6
Drama title: Bait
It was you who ordered the arrest of President Zhang?
So what is it that I call people...
Aren't you the person in charge of this case?
Wasn't that what you did?
Tell me what I should do.
Murders happened one after another
At every crime scene
Zhang Haocai left behind a lot of physical evidence
Start with your grandfather
Three generations of your family
Always receiving favors from the lender Jin Yu Tang
How dare you list President Zhang as a wanted criminal?
Don't arrest innocent people.
Pretending to bring justice to society
Please look for our Zonghe.
What?
Our Zonghe is missing.
What's going on?
He went to the company for training
Then he sent me 10 million won out of the blue.
Then there was no news.
I called their company.
They said there was no such training.
Which company?
Heritage Pharmaceuticals
(Sung Jun-mo is 41 years old
Researcher at Heritage Biotech)
(Wu Qixun is 29 years old
Heritage Biotechnology Security)
(An Zonghe
Joined the Comprehensive Support Team of Seunghwa Pharmaceutical for one month)
(Jongno-gu serial murder case
ruptured eyeballs and hollowed-out brains)
So it's all about...
Is it related to Heritage Biotechnology?
- Do you want me to check it out?
- Oops, I was shocked.
Please make some noise when you come in.
You met that grandmother yesterday
Is nothing wrong?
What is your relationship like?
It seems like she has a close relationship with Zhang Haocai
Detective Park, let's have dinner.
Would you like some takeout of Grandma's soup and rice?
- What do you want to eat?
- Honestly
I felt something was wrong from the beginning
Even if Zhang Hao is a capable person
But not to the extent
Just ask him to find clues about the suspect.
You asked me to supervise him.
In addition, you
Staying up all night to guard the door of the intensive care unit
Aren’t you hungry?
You have known each other for a long time, right?
We ordered takeout first.
Huh?
Hello, I'm Lv Mingjun from the Second Squad of the Serious Crime Unit
What?
That monitor
The escalator area of a subway station in Seoul
A random killing occurred
Three people died at the scene
One person is in critical condition
Now rushed to the emergency room
Yesterday morning at five o'clock
The Fire Safety Center received an alarm call
Someone is hallucinating...
According to the police
- Suspect A...
- Zong...
Random attack
B, a platform worker in his 50s
I know that kid.
This led to Seoul Railway Company employees and...
He is in the basement of Heritage Pharmaceuticals
They were experimented on
A female cleaner in her forties...
Is it true?
Um
He escaped from there this morning.
There are also men in their forties
He was taken to the emergency room...
I did it
After the incident...
I let him out.
Police arrived at the scene
Arrest him immediately as a criminal...
What on earth do you think?
The fact of ...
According to frontline reporters...
I want people to see
Modus operandi
With the recent Jongno serial murders...
If you can't see it with your own eyes
People nowadays don't believe anything.
I have less and less faith.
Three more people died.
There's a chance more people will die.
Did you know?
What does that mean?
Please explain clearly
Why are more people dying?
I don't know the details.
I just know
Mrs. Maeda seems to be planning something dangerous.
(The suspect is a male in his twenties
Randomly attacked a fifty-something station attendant)
(Citizens on their way to work are terrified
six casualties)
How dangerous is it?
You know that woman better.
Whatever she does, she will do it perfectly.
It should be like this
The current situation
Is that part of the plan as well?
Using him as bait to catch both of us?
I see you really don't like me, don't you?
I don't trust you.
Who took you out of that place?
I know it very well.
Who stabbed me, kidnapped me?
Oh, don't even mention how strong he is.
Ten people rushed forward but were thrown out.
It's just a bull.
What else can we do?
I had to stun him with a stun gun.
Then he fell
Look at him. Look at him.
Then is it still called people?
Zonghe
Look at me, An Zonghe
What's wrong with you? Huh?
- Ah, what's going on!
- Monitor
Are you okay?
I'll get you some emergency medicine first.
Do you know him?
(Fuqiang Trading Company)
Hello?
It's me, squad leader Lu
Hey, how are you?
I'm still alive, don't worry.
Are you using this number again?
Well
I'm back again
Uh okay
Can you explain to me the current situation?
It's Jong Hyuk
Crescent Cave Antenna Grandma and her grandson
He is a criminal
The company he just joined is...
Um
Heritage Pharmaceuticals
You're a piece of trash
They didn't even manage the experimental subjects properly.
Haven't you seen that the news is all over the place right now?
It seems that Sheng Zhao did it.
Why did he do that?
Should I ask Mrs. Maeda?
You mean
Was this all Mrs. Maeda's plan?
Didn't I tell you?
When she wanted to turn him back into Jang Tae Sang
I told you I didn't like this plan.
Although it is impossible to guess
What was Mrs. Maeda thinking when she gave such instructions?
But this is clearly the one who asked us to inherit the pharmaceutical industry.
Do you know that this is a dangerous move?
Yes, the former chairman
Implant a Nazi in my brain
So that I can keep the legacy
It is right to contribute wholeheartedly to the realization of great achievements
What if this incident threatens the peace of the inheritance?
Then I will
Ruthlessly eliminate the risk factor
Regardless of the risk factor
Is it Jang Tae-sang or your incompetence?
Or maybe it was Mrs. Maeda's arbitrary behavior.
Don't forget
first
You go clean up this mess first.
First, capture No. 71.
Then we'll talk to Mrs. Maeda.
Is this okay?
What are you doing?
You're not going alone, are you?
I want to go alone
What are you going to do as a wounded person?
Your body hasn't recovered yet.
Did you see it?
Can we go together at this level?
- Still no
- Zhang Daizhu
What about me
I don't want to see Miss Yin Caiyu get hurt again.
I don't want to see you in danger.
I don't want to put you in danger.
Then regret it later
I don't want to tolerate this anymore
It's the 21st century now
I guess you won't say anything.
You want to protect me or something cliche?
That's right
Don't look at my appearance.
I am a man over a hundred years old.
My thinking is pretty old-fashioned.
I still believe that men have to protect women
I want to fight or am I better than you?
Well, that won't work either.
Besides
I won't die either.
What about me
Rather than being the woman you protect
I would rather be the woman who is inseparable from you
so
Let's stay together, Mr. Zhang
Um?
How can I refuse you when you smile at me like this?
you
Give me another smile
Um
Where? Who are you talking about?
They are from the company that produces traditional pharmaceuticals.
Are you crazy? Where are you going?
Go find that kid
I said, what are you doing there?
I know that kid.
What's wrong with knowing each other?
He has been arrested by the police, what can you do?
The inheritance will not give up
They'll find a way to deal with him.
There should be only two possibilities, right?
Either capture him or kill him.
Before he encountered this accident
We have to do everything we can.
It's been like this all my life
Aren't you bored?
Fight with that gang and be defeated
Even through the gates of hell
But do you still have the patience to fight them?
How can people live like this?
Is it time to stop all this now?
- Sheng Zhao
- You might as well just run away.
You go anywhere with that woman.
Then just live your own life, ok?
I also thought about my own life
Live a happy life with her
But this is not achieved by running away
A life bought by running away
The non-existent Sheng Zhao
- Who are you?
- It's me, No Ji-su
Now a large group of people from Heritage Pharmaceuticals have come
They said they were going to take the prisoner away.
What does that mean?
You guys came to visit me so suddenly?
You want to take the prisoner away?
That person is infected
- Infect?
- I heard that the Second Division of the Major Crime Unit of the Jongno Police Station
Called our company
And asked about this nitrogen issue
Yes
We still haven't heard any response
This is for uniforms
Portable nitrogen bombs made for violent infected people
It was developed by our pharmaceutical company
Infected people are generally very aggressive
The Department of Disease Control has issued an official letter
The leadership of the National Police Agency has unanimously agreed.
Hand over the infected first.
What do you regard the investigative agency as?
It happened within the last two months.
Suspect in six serial murders
Today
Three people died at the same place.
With a piece of torn paper
You're going to take away a violent criminal like that?
Compared to investigating cases
What matters most at this moment is the safety and lives of the citizens.
If the infectious disease spreads, things will get out of control.
Police Inspector Lu Mingjun, will you be in charge when the time comes?
They moved faster than we expected.
We're too late anyway, right?
The police station with jurisdiction over the case
It's less than ten minutes away. There's still time.
So what if I have time?
What can you do when you go there?
You know there's one thing I'm good at.
make trouble
I'm ready, let's go.
I'll go with you
I said I'd go too.
Are you driving too fast?
Speed 50 mph. Didn't you see the sign?
Saw it
But I didn't follow the rules
Have you confirmed it?
Yes, the CDC says these are all facts.
There are several
There are also cases of infected people with similar symptoms.
Because it is an important case
These are all considered confidential
We also confirmed
Heritage Pharmaceuticals is studying the cause of infection
Hey Captain
They blocked the camera.
Oh shit
Do I need to release the nitrogen first?
It's too troublesome. Just open it.
(Heritage Biotech)
(Hello, Jongno Police Station)
(Lv Mingjun, squad leader of the Second Serious Crime Squad)
Yes Captain
Um where are you?
Hello, where are you?
I am following Heritage Biotech
- What?
- Feel sorry
I know the criminal was caught at the crime scene.
I know this case can be closed like this.
But I always feel something is wrong
I know you think I'm unreliable.
This time I want to act on my instincts.
sorry
You can finally help.
Don't lose it
Keep reporting to me after a while.
I have to find out something no matter what.
That's it.
I heard that our Zong He came here?
Can you let me meet him?
It's that
Not now
No, our Zonghe won't do that.
Our Zonghe is not that kind of child
Squad Leader Lu, you know
Yes, that one...
There was a motorcycle and two cars following behind.
Step on the gas
Well?
you
How much do you like my brother?
Why should I tell you?
Because I like him too
I also know
The story behind his ill-fated relationship with Mrs. Maeda
Also know
The reason why he hates Heritage Pharmaceuticals
So a year ago
When he said he wanted to raze the lab
I didn't hesitate for a second.
Just say I want to stand on Haocai's side
I was
I really feel like I could die for him.
But
Actually, it's not like that
One year ago
Actually, I didn't miss the scene.
Say it again
You said you could die for Mr. Zhang?
Did you just say that?
He was the first person to recognize me.
He said that I was originally
It's already good
He made me understand
I am a human being
So I felt for the first time
Life is not painful
I also
I recognize you.
Although you were born of a lowly prostitute
But I recognize you as my son
Even though everyone opposes
I insisted on adding you to my account
But you actually
Betray me?
Sorry, Mom.
Please let me go
Lift your head
hurry up
Within 24 hours from now
The Na people will enter a deep sleep state
No matter what happens
No one will protect you.
If you get stabbed, the wound will bleed naturally.
If you get shot, the bullet will go through your body and kill you.
You lose your ability to recover
No longer able to regenerate
If you want to go, go ahead.
I hope you understand after you leave.
How fragile and tormented the human body is
I hope you understand
Human kindness and justice in the face of death
How pale and powerless
You choose
I'll keep the door open for you
Actually, one year ago
I'm also there
But
I can't help my brother.
Because I'm afraid
I am afraid of death
You don't have to
Sorry for being scared
Some people are afraid of death
Some people are afraid to live
Everyone has different feelings of fear.
Let's talk about that matter
The lender never pursued the matter.
This means he understands your feelings.
So don't feel sorry.
Within 24 hours from now
The person will enter a sleeping state
Start now
Whether it's being stabbed
Still shot
You will all die
Why exactly?
I told you
I was scared
I'm afraid I'll die
I met you again.
yes
Haven't seen you for a year?
You're such a difficult guy.
I don't have any advantages except tenacity.
You finally met the woman you love again
How nice it is to be with her
Why appear here again?
don’t worry
I'll go back after I finish my work here.
Do you still believe in Sheng Zhao?
Um
believe
That woman is a pity.
You worry about yourself.
It is said that Zhang Taisang has been lured away
And Seung So and Yoon Chae Ok are together
elder brother
Say
After I had the surgery
Can I continue playing the cello?
Of course.
You will play better than before the accident.
When can I have a transplant?
We are choosing the most suitable match for you.
After three to six months
You will learn most of the principles
If you do a transplant at this time
It won't have much impact on the body
Definitely better than when they were larvae
Is there a higher chance of success?
After transplanting the adults
There have been no deaths so far.
Then choose this one
Three months later, the transplant was performed
You wait three more months
Then you can walk again.
Eat now
- Subtitle translation:
-Rita Huang