I... am in a romantic relationship with Kang Joo Eun.
What?
- Heol!
- Why?
Am I the only one in a relationship?
Kang Joo Eun.
Episode 10
Your name is Kim Yeong Ho?
Yes.
What is this, an interrogation?
Shut up.
You might be uncomfortable, but think of it as a rite of passage,
and I ask you for a sincere response.
So... Is your house... Self... What is it? Is it under you name?
Hmm almost.
How about your occupation?
Not yet... certain.
White hand. Another name for unemployed.
How long has it been since you broke up with your last girlfriend?
It hasn't been that long. She was a very famous foreigner.
Okay. You're in the same boat, so you're even there.
Excuse me,  Hyeon Woo.
Aigoo, all you have is overflowing sexiness...
You can't live off of a man's looks alone.
But with his looks, you could probably live off of it for about fifty years.
You wench!
Hey, ex-wife!
Ah, this guy, seriously.
My ex-husband is here to hand over some child support. Excuse me.
Isn't that Lawyer Kang?
Who is that next to her? Ah, he's something!
What are you saying? You want to die?
Lawyer Kang lost a lot of weight! Is she going to put a mole next to her eye and get revenge or something?
Hey! Is putting a mole next to her eye and meeting another man revenge?
Your train of thought is seriously— Hurry up and leave!
I'm leaving. I'm already plenty busy because of John Kim.
Ah, really. So annoying.
Ma'am and Hyungnim Yeong Ho. Wow, surprise.
And you told me I have no sense.
"I am in a romantic relationship with Kang Joo Eun."
Hyung, I think the feeling is totally different this time. Not just a girlfriend.
Ms. Lawyer is a really good person, so
Hyung-nim will smile a lot more often now.
What's this? This feeling that I feel, it's weird. It's like... How can I explain it...
Like the feeling of my mom meeting her boyfriend.
Why don't you just call your mom more often?
Wait a minute.
It seems like Director Choi's side has information on John Kim.
We can't be sure that he has enough to release to the press, but it looks like he has a definite card up his sleeve.
At a time like this... How can you be enjoying a private life?
It looks like my confession isn't over yet.
I will go.
Why are you like this, seriously?
You saw him last time, right? Here is my cherished Manager Alberto Min.
Executive Director.
This is the official CEO of my private affairs.
She is Kang Joo Eun who is in a romantic relationship with me.
It is cold so go inside first.
I think it'll take a while since he likes to nag a lot.
Please go inside and have a talk. I will go to my house for now.
Then I will go to my house.
He knows that you live here so just go inside.
And if you look at it, you two are alike in both pretending you don't know while knowing full well.
Go inside.
You'll be in a tough situation when the chairwoman finds out.
It will be more of a problem if Father knows rather than Grandma.
If you know that, why are you—
Because she isn't a woman who I can stop meeting just because I will be in a difficult situation.
For now, just watch over us.
This whole situation could be harsher for Kang Joo Eun than you.
So...
I'm asking you for help, okay?
Can't I just pretend I didn't see anything?
To do that... She's too great a woman.
Where are you running off to this time?
What did he say? What do we do?
What if your family has strange ideas about us?
You love pretending to be modest. It wasn't too long ago that you asked me to sleep with you just holding hands.
I'll just go sleep at Hyeon Woo's.
Don't wake up the little sprout who's growing up, and just stay.
You're moving out tomorrow anyway.
How about the kids?
They said they would come after working out.
How about it? Should we take this opportunity to have a properly comfortable and racy night?
Seriously. Where is this rascal?
I am a bit late.
Oh, you are here?
What is the matter?
What do you mean? We haven't seen each other much these days.
Sorry. I have an important meeting tomorrow.
Soo Jin. I have a lot on my mind these days, so
I couldn't care a lot for you. So...
So I guess you are sorry again.
- Soo Jin.
- From now on, let's say our apologies over the phone.
I will leave.
This whole situation could be harsher for Kang Joo Eun than for you.
This is the official CEO of my private affairs.
She is Kang Joo Eun who is in a romantic relationship with me.
Ma'am.
We are back.
We are coming.
Sister-in-law, good night.
I am tired.
Where are the kids?
They've come in and they're sleeping.
That's not it.
Thinking back on it, I forgot the last part of camping.
Why?  A comfortable and racy night?
"Deng!"  (Bell Ring for WRONG!)
Let's talk all night.
Because it is the last night.
This woman is wicked until the very end.
A full grown man and woman, late at night.
What are we doing?
Our negotiation isn't over yet.
Including the back hug, all hugs are off limits.
Just the hugs are off limits?
Physical contact is off limits, except for hands and feet.
What about dimples?
Dimples are off limits too.
Just five minutes after we met, I took your clothes off and ripped off your abdominal support. This is too harsh.
You're going too far.
"Your body is mine. You can't say no."
I've almost lost all my weight, so I can say no.
The more I think about it, I'm dumbfounded.
How could you stick red tape on my body?
How about it? Call?
Hands... Feet...
Okay. Call.
Beeep.
Why did you become a lawyer? You don't seem like someone who likes to use her head.
Ah. Ah.
When you grow up in an ordinary household,
sometimes you go through sad and unfair situations.
That's why moms say this kind of thing often.
"This is why we need at least one doctor or a lawyer in this household." That's why.
That's why?
Yes. That's why.
No matter what job it is, you just have to be happy to do it your whole life, be bright, and confident doing it.
Beeep.
Since you were little, you were always brave and not too smart, but you also had conviction.
You could say it's my life's motto.
I think... I'm going to be busy starting tomorrow.
I don't think I'll be able to help you move.
"Leave it to the moving professionals!" I don't want you to come and pointlessly mess things up. Don't worry about it.
Ah, I'm sleepy. Let's go to sleep now.
-  You're 62.2 kg! You did it!
♬  I didn't know that it would be so painful   ♬
♬  I didn't know I would want to see you so much  ♬
♬  Slowly my heart would be influenced  ♬
This. I haven't see it before.
♬  Before I knew it  you filled  it completely  ♬
What is this?
♬  I enjoyed the time  ♬
I wanted the prodigal son who has returned to have a home-cooked meal.
♬   I had with you  ♬
Move.
Oh. The smell.
Kang Joo Eun day.
I am back.
♬   After time stood still  I want to be with you  ♬
♬  I will stay with you  ♬
This is a bag. What we did yesterday was a kiss.
♬  I will say I will love you   ♬
I think I gave you at least that much assurance.
How is it? Should I give it to you one more time?
You must be really crazy.
♬  I'm saying I don't have a choice  ♬
♬  Why did I have to meet you only now?  ♬
♬  The person who would make the wounded me happy   ♬
♬  I will keep you with me always  ♬
She's completely fixed her sleeping disorder.
♬  I won't waver and will embrace you  ♬
♬  Because you are everything to me, because you are my love  ♬
♬   I am never letting you go  ♬
I thought you might cry too much, so I left early.
Ma'am is leaving a present for the three of you.
By the way, I made the breakfast so eat everything without complaining.
Ma'am told us to heat it and eat it.
Without complaining. All of it.
Let's eat.
I will enjoy it.
Ma'am.
Is the director home?
Hyung?
This one. This. This wouldn't let me go.
I worked too hard since early this morning.
You know that tomorrow is the Gahong Board of Directors Meeting, right?
I'm the only one going today since it's a simple meeting.
Maybe you'll be too uncomfortable because of your personal relationship with Executive Director, Kim Yeong Ho.
I am uncomfortable with you like this as well because we are friends.
By chance, are you dreaming of a Cinderella story?
I have no intention of opposing if you want to quit being a part of Gahong's external legal team.
You said it yourself. Someone has to do it.
Covering your eyes from it doesn't change anything.
As expected, you are Lawyer Kang.
Then.
Oh my thyroid.
Cinderella?
Cinderella... The girl's more brazen than I thought.
She went to the party to see the prince, even though she knew her wicked stepmother and her stepsisters would be there.
Cinderella of the legal field...
I chose the wrong concept.
What are you doing?
I'm doing so much, I'm getting fed up.
They're the files you requested for Mr. Jang Joon Seong, because the office manager was out of the office.
Thank you, Hyeon Jeong.
She looks like a very stubborn person.
Jae Soon Ja?   Jae Soon Ja...
I've heard the name somewhere...
Ms. Lawyer, a client came for consultation.
Please bring him in.
I don't know if she's spiteful or just thick faced.
Even if it's Gahong, I couldn't live there like her, with the son-in-law.
I found out that no matter what company it is, she's going to walk away with nothing.
Of course, since there's a new executive director who's the grandson.
- But, where did he come from?
- I don't know.
My word. How could she—
Oh, Chairwoman Lee.
Hello, you're here.
- I'ts a long time since I've seen you.
- Have you been well?
Since I'm old, I don't do well in cold weather.
Oh, you don't say.
Mother-in-law, you are here?
I didn't know you came.
Then.
Son, I am at the art museum with your grandma.
Of course, I am doing well.
Excuse me, Madam. Chairwoman told me to prepare the meals from now on.
Since I will take care of it you two go inside and rest.
Gahong Group
Ah, I think I have to learn math all over again.
There's a short meeting with the board members of Gahong in an hour,
and after that you have a dinner meeting with the Chairwoman. Tomorrow you have a board meeting—
Aren't you tired of saying the same thing many times?
Just help me pick out a tie. A pretty one. You're so countrified.
How's the move going?
Moving company ajussis are doing it!
What are you doing?
I am eating. Did you eat?
Hurry up and eat. I am on my way to the company.
I am done eating.
Should we do a video call? Finish eating first.
See you in a bit if we can.
We've seen each other every day. It won't hurt to miss one day.
Work hard. I'm tired from cooking since early this morning.
We have arrived.
Please put your phone on silent mode.
You're so jealous.
I'm here.
Let's get out, let's fight, let's win. Yup.
Fighting.
We can't make any judgments on whether the executive director, Kim Yeong Ho, is amicable,
so let's test him a bit. If he wants to take part in business management it'll be a war,
but if he's just going to be a figure head, we'll have to let him be. What else can we do?
He is the only grandchild of Chairwoman Lee after all, don't you think?
Go back to work then.
Then, let's end it.
Chairwoman Lee Hong Im will hand over her shares to Kim Yeong Ho in a short while.
Then he will become the major shareholder, and when that happens,
we have no basis for restricting or blocking his taking office.
No matter what it takes, making the best of it
might be the best way to take a step back for the sake of taking two steps forward.
Mutual aid?
Then this world would be so beautiful.
You have to remember that taking a step back could mean
that you could be pushed further back or be thrown out completely.
You know how competitive this world is. Even if we can't stop it,
we can make it difficult.
It's not easy for him to take office without approval from the board of directors.
Come in.
- Executive Director.
- Please sit.
Let's sit down. Sit sit.
Over there.
I should have come to say hello first, but it's been hectic while getting adjusted.
It's a given that things are hectic when you're new here.
That person is the external legal team leader.
I am Lawyer Oh Soo Jin.
These are the VVIP examination center files that we've been working on.
Since you'll sign it anyway, you can just look through it first. It's all here.
Ah. I'm going to reexamine this proposal.
Pardon?
It's a project that has been in process for years already.
We've reported it to Chairman Kim Seong Cheol already.
We have a lot of time, so let's take our time looking through it.
Just because the wealthy clientele's examination center project falls a little behind, I don't foresee any problems.
It's an organic tea. It's supposed to be calming.
I didn't get anything ready. Thank you.
Excuse me.
Before, about Lawyer Kang and General Manager, Im Woo Sik—
Yes.
I hope you don't have any misunderstandings.
We've been acquaintances for a long time. I won't let it interfere with my work—
Lawyer Kang Joo Eun said different things.
Excuse me?
The two of you were friends. Close ones.
Yes, well...
I understand. You won't let personal business interfere with your work.
Do you have more to say?
No. Then, I will see you tomorrow.
Let's talk.
Why didn't you tell me?
Do I have to tell you about my work, too?
Are we in that kind of relationship?
Oh Soo Jin.
Did we do more than hug a few times and kiss a few times?
I don't think I have to report my business to you.
The same goes for you too.
How can you do this when you know what position Kim Young Ho and I are in?
Does this make sense?
You and Joo Eun were each other's first love and dated for 15 years.
But, you are here with me.
- Does this make sense to you?
- Soo Jin.
Even with a relationship of 15 years, you guys are strangers after one day.
But now, why did you think we would last forever?
Grandma, I'm here.
Hello.
Hurry up and sit. Grandma is hungry.
I said I would get mad if you lied to me.
Enjoy your meal.
Have some wine too, and take your time with dinner.
It's hard for people to meet even once,
but since you guys have met three times
Grandma.
Oh, I'm not that keen on Italian food.
The two of you enjoy your meal.
Today, I think these are for me.
Of course,  Chairwoman.
Go safely.
You're way past your marriageable age.
Your grandma is going to suffocate (and die waiting for you to get married).
Let's have a cup of tea instead of having a meal.
Yes.
I don't expect you to be sincere from the start.
I am now expecting that kind of stuff.
Do you have someone else you want to marry?
I don't have any intention to marry since my circumstances will make it very difficult.
- To the elders...
- Yes, we shouldn't tell them.
I have at least that much sense.
I'm very sorry.
Were you well during your business trip?
Would there be anything special?
Yeong Joon wanted me to ask his father
what he should major in.
Whatever he wants to do.
Kim Yeong Ho.
You weren't like this to your other son.
You didn't let him do anything he wanted.
Our Yeong Joon,
what kind of son is he to you?
You're saying stuff you didn't use to.
Of things I never used to say,
let me say one more thing.
For a year, receiving cancer treatments...
Since when did you know?
I don't need to know about the company matters.
But, I need to know your sickness,
because I'm still
your wife.
I'm sorry. I don't usually complain.
But,
I wanted to do it at least once.
Please rest.
Welcome.
I'm sorry I couldn't help with your move, but instead, this.
It's good that Hyungnim Yeong Ho  is not here. We can eat this kind of stuff.
Ah, we went around the block a few times,
so stalker-like guys won't come again.
Sister-in-law, it's heavy.
Hurry up and come inside.
- It's heavy.
- Go inside.
So heavy.
The way I see it, he's not very loyal.
It's spiteful how you don't gain weight even though you eat.
Sister-in-law and champion, you guys need to take care of your body, or else Hyungnim Yeong Ho will kill me.
Then why don't you eat all those greens with us?
No, no. When you move, you have to eat jjajangmyun.
Ah, I like the gift. Superwoman.
Wonder Woman. She's exactly my style. You're the best, Sister-in-law.
Sister-in-law seems too old.
Just "Ma'am" is better.
I adjusted to it  as well.
Hyungnim might not be able to come today.
Ah, I know. Today's not the only special day.
Faster, faster. Go.
Hip, hip. Butterfly, butterfly.
Wow, you're like a really cool dolphin.
Hey, how can you be afraid of the water if you're going to the marines?
Oh, wait. Hyung, I'm sorry.
Oh, okay, okay.
Stop.
Ma'am told me I can do anything if I put my mind to it. Resolve.
Resolve.
Hyung, is your shoulder okay?
Ah, well. It feels a little more comfortable.
Ji Woong!
Yes.
It is her again.
Jang Yi Jin. Jang Yi Jin!
Hyung, Yi Jin might die. Mouth to mouth.
One, two, three, four, five.
Whoa.
We kissed.
Yeah!
Kim Ji Woong, you bastard.  Seriously.
Sorry, Hyung!
You're doing the acting of your life here.
Why don't you do this in dramas?
I'm seriously unable to even look at you.
Ah, get up quickly!
At your Gahong, the director candidate Kim Yeong Ho... he's John Kim, right?
What are you saying? Do you have proof?
I got in touch with the paparazzi in the U.S.
Gahong must have blocked it for quite a large sum of money.
And well... It seems like you know something.
Isn't that why you told me not to do a report on suspicion, because you'd get me the facts?
It's not the kind of thing to be revealed easily.
If you don't have solid evidence, it can actually become a backlash.
That's right, because the other party is Gahong.
Star Im, that bullet, how much could it be worth?
Who is it?
It's the snack shop.  You just moved here, right?  I'll give you some fliers.
Just put it on the door and leave.
Yes, you've worked hard.
Who is it?
It is me, the guy who is in a romantic relationship with Kang Joo Eun.
It is late. Why did you come?
Because you left something.
Come in. How was it today?
You have to leave right away, huh?
Manager Min is downstairs.
Well, it's not like today is the only day.
You introduced Joon Seong and Ji Woong to girlfriends.
But I gave you a book instead.
"Romance Cafe?" It was so like you.
Why? You should have got me "Romance Restaurant," or "Romance Buffet" instead.
You said the board of directors meeting is tomorrow.
You should hurry up and leave.  You're tired.
It will be hard tomorrow.
Isn't there anyone who can do in lieu of you?
For you, Yeong Ho, as well as for me, our work is our life.
Who will do it in lieu of us?
As for the outside legal team,
I only have to do it until you're inaugurated as the Director, so don't worry about me.
Did you forget? I am Kang Joo Eun who can do anything as long as I put my mind to it?
That's right.
Since I saw your face, I will leave.
Ah, what is this Gyeon Woo and Jing Nyeo story (star crossed lovers) that wasn't in my plans?
Now leave.
Lock the door well.
Oh yeah, before you sleep, do three sets of planks.  Okay?
Yes, Mr. Coach.
And this... is getting confiscated.
I will leave.
♬   Such a woman might not exist anywhere   ♬
♬   She only knows one person.  A woman who loves that man.  ♬
♬   I'm searching for such a woman.   ♬
♬   If perhaps that love comes to me   ♬
♬   Maybe you are that love.   ♬
That person is the team leader of the outside legal team.
I am Lawyer Oh Soo Jin.
Yes, PD Go.
Star Im, I caught John Kim.
Hey, that paparazzi guy does good work.
As soon as I sent the money, he sent me the picture.
The scandal picture with Anna Sue.
If I improve the quality of the picture, it will be a jackpot. Right?
How long will it take?
You must feel anxious, Lawyer Kang.
It's not like I'm the Director.
Regular Board of Directors' Meeting of Gahong Group.
It seems like the directors are very busy.
Chairwoman Lee, I think it is better to reschedule the meeting. It is better to go for today.
Let's do that.
See you again.
Yes.
It's one to zero.
Wow, it feels like ice in here.
Our team should go. Vice CEO, let's go.
I guess Director Kim Yeong Ho has already dropped Cinderella's glass slipper.
What did you say?
If not, are you barking up the wrong tree?
Would you like to become the chicken that gets chased and driven out...yo? (yo is for honorific)
Ah, seriously.
Diet
I didn't know that Director Choi would influence the board directors to move that way.
It is all my fault.
Please get me the documents for the VVIP medical center.
Yes, I will prepare them right away.
I guess he is greedier than I thought.
Daegu Venus
How can he not call or Kakao Talk even once?
He must be fine.
Whoa! Oh my God!
Wow! Fantastic!
Fantastic!
Omo, omo. How can this fit so well?
Hold on.
Ah, shoes.
Madam Kwon Ok Boon
Mom.
What? What's going on?
Why do you ask what's wrong every day?
Mom, I lost a lot of weight.
I'm the same as I used to be. I'm totally pretty.
Of course. Because you are my daughter.
Where do you think you got your beauty gene? Did you eat?
You ask about eating every day. That's why I got fat.
Mom, why aren't you sleeping?
Aigoo, I should sleep.
I am trimming the anchovies to make broth.
Must you trim them to make broth?
You became overemotional about the pig last time.
Is this time about anchovies again? Girl, watch your temper!
Mom.
Say it.
Thank you for raising me this prettily.
What's wrong? Is today Mothers' Day?
You were originally pretty.
Stop saying nonsense and sleep.
I got it. Sleep well, Mom.
Get the treatment for your wrist. Don't just put the pain patch on it everyday.
All right.
Aigo, what on earth is this?
Is she psychic?
Lee Hyeon Woo
Yes, Hyeon Woo.
What do you mean?
I am asking if the Yeong Ho you are seeing is John Kim.
How did you know that?
Who is the executive director of Gahong?
How did you know?
It is a big commotion on the Internet. Why are you like this?
Scandalous John Kim turned out to be the new successor at Gahong
Mr. Coach
The number you dialed can't be reached.
Joon Seong
Ji Woong
The party you are calling can't be reached.
Who is this lady?
Did I find the wrong house?
What happened?
You must be going somewhere nice.
Why didn't you pick up the phone?
I got shocked.
Are you okay?
How about Manager Min?
I think it is better to go to the hotel.
Because there are so many reporters waiting outside of my house
I don't want to go home. It's the same with the hotel too.
I don't want to go home.
Do you think I want to sleep at the hotel?
You think I came to the motel because I like it?
Even though there is only one room and one bathroom, come in.
To your outer space.
Boarding.
Departing.
♬  I think I love you,  ♬
♬  I think I like you,  ♬
♬  Though I am quite afraid of the love that's found me again,  ♬
♬  I can't avoid it,  ♬