"Episode 12"
I'm sorry.
Coach?
What is the star of
the ceremony doing here?
What should I do?
I think...
I'm going to be very late.
People are waiting.
Your father and grandmother.
Junseong, Jiwoong and everyone.
Get up.
Kang Jooeun.
You're still hanging in there,
so you haven't reached your limit yet.
What?
I can still do it.
That means I haven't reached my limit yet.
Look at me.
If you believe it, you can do it.
Because you believe that you can.
If I believe it, I can do it.
I believe that I can.
Where is he?
What's happening?
Executive director, Kim Youngho...
...has just arrived.
Please welcome the new executive
director, Kim Youngho.
Hello, everyone.
I am Kim Youngho,
the new executive director...
...of Gahong Medical Group.
Oh! Yijin!
Hi.
What brings you here?
No, no. It wasn't me this time.
You didn't look me up. I'm the commercial
queen and my parents own Jang Foods.
Really?
If there's anything we want to eat,
we should ask her.
We're all friends now, aren't we?
Are you upset because I'm rich?
You dislike so many things.
But whatever.
We've slept together already.
What?
What? Junseong.
You are a man.
Please keep your distance.
People will stare.
Does that bother you?
Isn't that how your job is?
Oh, my. You're so cool.
Hi, Namcheol.
Is it over?
No one told you not to come.
Why are you at home?
Why do you keep doing that?
Where's Youngjun?
He should have come.
The States isn't that far.
It's not like this is a place
where he can't set his foot in.
Forget it.
Kim Youngho...
...was inaugurated as
the executive director.
I am fine, Youngjun.
It's okay.
-He's coming.
-He's coming!
-Are you now the executive director?
-Do you admit to being John Kim?
-Is it true about Anna Sue?
-Is it true?
-Please give us a statement.
-Mr. Kim!
If you submit your questions to
the secretary's office in Gahong,
we will answer all your questions.
-Good work.
-Thank you.
-I'll see you tomorrow.
-Yes, Ma'am.
-Good work today. Bye.
-Thank you.
Good night.
I thought you left.
There was something I forgot to tell you.
Today,
you looked very pretty.
Enough for me to dream of you every night.
Was that it?
It doesn't look like you're
going to be Cinderella,
if you take your shoes off
instead of putting them on.
It doesn't look like you'll
be the prince, either.
The valiant prince is supposed to
help the princess put on her shoes.
Are you okay?
Look who's talking.
Why are your feet so big?
It's because I'm tall.
My shoulders are wide, too.
My hips, as well.
Exactly.
Why is this woman so big?
You'll need an X-ray to be sure,
but I think you pulled a ligament.
Go home and get some rest.
I'm going to the hospital
in my pumpkin carriage.
Thank you for bringing me home.
You should go.
You didn't drink a drop of water
the entire night.
That's why you're like this.
I heard from Producer Ko...
That you made sure I
didn't get in trouble...
...for disclosing the information
about Kim Youngho.
I didn't want things to get out of hand.
That was why.
Thank you.
First, you say you're sorry.
Now, you say thank you?
Don't look at me like that.
I'm not a nice person.
I'm cruel and heartless.
I'm an evil witch who
steals her friends' boyfriend.
No, you're not.
You're nice.
No, I'm not.
I'm not nice.
I'm not nice. I'm not nice!
So...
Don't look at me like that.
Do you remember that day?
You passed your exams
and went on that blind date.
Your pride was hurt and you were crying,
but when you saw my wounded hand,
you said something.
Let's go.
Woosik, you're hurt.
Do I look like the same person now?
Don't you see me now?
I'm sure you hated me because of
the stalker incident,
but you were the first
one there to help me.
You knew what a jerk I was,
but you waited for me,
and protected me.
Oh Soojin.
You are the same...
...as before.
What to do?
The only thing I can say to you...
...are sorry and thank you.
That's all I can do.
Mind your head.
-Wait, it hurts.
-I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
There you go.
Are you okay?
They said it'll get better
after a few days.
My shoulders and arms hurt more
than my ankle.
I'm sorry, Ma'am.
Thank you for being overprotective of me.
Who's here?
Mom.
Jooeun.
These are the guys that I work out with.
I sprained my ankle.
-What?
-They brought me home.
-Hello.
That means, she's ma'am's mommy.
-I love you. Come here.
-Goodness. Welcome to Korea.
Nice to meet you.
We'll see you again.
Where are you going? I can't let
guests leave that way. Wait a moment.
Ma'am, is she wearing Youngho's clothes?
Mom, why are you wearing that?
It's so comfortable.
Is this what you wore when you were fat?
-What are you going to make?
-Just wait.
The guests need to eat something.
Nice.
-Here it is.
-Wow.
Mom.
They need to watch their diet.
They work out.
That's good.
They need to eat well, then.
It's not like that.
We'll eat the lean part of the meat.
Thank you.
-Which part is...
-This part.
My goodness.
It tastes better when you eat
it like this. Here you go.
-Here you go.
-Yes.
Thank you.
My goodness. Look at the two of you.
You are both so adorable.
-This is delicious.
-Yes.
Why don't you eat?
No.
You look fine. All the girls on
TV look like they're starving.
That's not true.
You should eat a little.
My goodness.
Then...
Should I eat just a little bit?
I'll eat the lean part, too.
You can dip it in salt.
-Junseong.
-Oh, I almost forgot.
We have some gatkimchi.
Did she just say "god kimchi"?
No, that's not what she said.
I should be thankful that I didn't
gain more weight. Look at all this.
The kimchi is just right to eat.
-Let's eat.
-Wow.
Try it, Jiwoong.
Is it spicy?
My leg is okay. How is your leg?
I heard you ate chicken.
Bad girl.
There's an exception
when I'm with my mom.
If I don't eat what she gives me,
she bugs me all day.
I'm officially starting work tomorrow.
Tell Minjun's mother,
that I'm no longer unemployed.
Now you get to earn your keep.
As someone who has been working
longer than you, here's some advice.
It's not easy to make money.
I hope your leg won't bother you.
I'm going to beat that...
...neurosis thing that you have.
It's not something you can cure.
So I can't be concerned about you?
Even when he's in pain,
he's still so consistent.
That's what the doctor said.
He might have been wrong.
Put a pillow under your sprained ankle
when you sleep.
Not too high, though.
Yes, Coach.
Good night.
Today,
you looked pretty.
Enough for me to dream of you every night.
I have to sleep, but I can't help it.
I can't stop envisioning you.
I guess I don't need
to text Woosik anymore.
You stay up to text him
and he makes you smile.
That's enough.
I'll cook some ox knee soup
before I leave.
Make sure to eat it to the last drop.
Oh my goodness.
I'm so exhausted.
You should take care of your knees.
Have your wrist treated, too.
Come to my office tomorrow.
-I'll accompany you to the hospital.
-They have hospitals in Daegu too.
Let's just go to sleep now.
What's that?
Ma'am's mom gave it to us yesterday.
It tastes incredible.
"Here you go. Eat up."
Lawyer Kang looks exactly like her mom.
Really?
Well.
It's a bit salty.
You need to reduce your salt intake.
That's right.
Students who get bad grades
always cram the night before their exam.
Don't overwork yourself before the game.
I won't.
-Keep monitoring his condition.
-Yes, Sir.
I'll only be available on weekends
from now on.
Youngho, we are not babies.
Don't worry.
You don't have to worry about us so much.
Are you saying you don't need me?
Since I'm eating the dish that Ma'am's
mom cooked, I'm starting to miss Ma'am.
Oh my Venus.
She's mine.
I'm leaving.
He's changed.
I'm sorry about your ankle.
Is it serious?
No.
They said it would get better
in a few days.
The morning meeting has been canceled.
-Why?
-Miss Oh is absent.
What's wrong with her?
She didn't mention anything yesterday,
but she isn't answering her phone.
I see. She must have her reasons.
-I'll get you coffee.
-Thank you.
What happened to her?
I'm not in a position to worry about her.
Congratulations!
It's officially your first day.
Goodness.
That's too sweet of you.
The public relations team
and the legal team...
...are working on paper work
to deal with the scandal.
The legal team is also dealing with
exaggerated and speculative reports.
We've controlled...
...what's being said
outside the company...
What's being said inside Gahong
depends on how I do.
I was born with a silver spoon in my
mouth and that's how I got this position.
This is the business plan for next year.
Also,
the chairman...
...seems to know about Jooeun.
The board members are here for
the morning meeting.
Please let them in.
-So we are now...
-I'll see you tomorrow.
Mr Choi, listen to me.
I wasn't done talking.
You look like you've been
working out for quite some time.
I looked like that
about 10 years ago.
Oh! Do you play golf?
We should hit some balls.
I prefer...
...contact sports.
And I prefer to lift rather than hit.
Well, then.
Did you eat?
I just finished.
How did you know?
Was it too obvious that
I was waiting for his text?
I should video call you.
I can just screen your call.
How's your ankle?
It's better.
I'm working now sitting decently.
I'm fine.
Yes, Hyunjeong?
You must be redefining
the word "decently".
I thought you finished eating. Liar.
Lunch time isn't over yet,
so get up.
What is this?
Is he really here?
-Lawyer Kang, are you all right?
-Yes.
It isn't my ankle that is
making me uncomfortable.
Jooeun feeling uncomfortable is
my business.
Jooeun's ankle is also my business.
I'm going to be busy.
Hi, Hyunjeong.
Lawyer Kang.
This is Jo Hyunjeong.
She works with me.
Hello. Please take good care of her.
I will.
You may go.
Okay.
Are you running for office?
Where are we going, anyway?
Since we started it,
we should see an end to it.
Let's have our restful
and erotic night another time.
It's still daytime.
Lift your arm higher.
I shouldn't have gotten my hopes up.
But...
Please, don't speak.
In accordance with Article 12 of
the constitution...
What else could I do?
Do you want me to measure you? I told you
that I wouldn't take no for an answer.
Your body belongs to me.
It belongs to me.
It's up to me now.
-Let's move to the next station.
-There's more?
What is it?
I need to see some blood.
Let's go.
I have a lot of consultations
scheduled today. I need to go.
Hyunjeong said you don't have any
until the afternoon.
You can work late tonight.
I don't want to.
You can't avoid this.
You have to go. Okay?
Darling.
No.
Let's go.
-I hate blood.
-It's okay.
-I'll buy you sweets after this.
-Darling.
Tell me when you're going to
stick the needle in.
Okay, I will.
I'm going through all this
because of you.
Hang in there.
You're doing great. Hang in there.
Breathe.
Slap her hard, so that it hurts
more than the needle.
Wow.
What's gotten into you?
You saw blood, so I want you
to taste some sweetness.
It's like candy after
a dentist appointment.
"Body Fat Percentage"
I lost all the weight that I had to lose.
You said I was pretty.
You should be pretty on the inside, too.
"Body Fat Percentage"
Goodness.
You didn't throw that out?
I told you, your body belongs to me.
Why would I throw out what belongs to me?
Name, Kang Jooeun.
-Age, 34. Height 172 centimeters.
-Don't...
-Weight...
-Hey!
Come on.
You have the perfect build.
Build?
Your build is perfect for sports.
How did you end up studying?
Your body fat percentage is
normal. That's good.
It's good that you have more muscles now.
That best news is...
that you don't have
abdominal obesity anymore.
Really?
Good job.
What did I say?
I can do anything if I put my mind to it.
May I say something?
The most important things are,
your hypothyroidism and cholesterol.
If you work a little harder,
you won't need to take your pills.
Would you like to say something?
All the glory goes to Coach John Kim.
Don't be too happy.
Your hypothyroidism and
cholesterol must return to normal.
What's on the inside matters more
than what's on the outside. Okay?
Yes, Coach.
-May I eat this now?
-Just a little bit.
I made that halibut rice drink that
you enjoy.
It'll take some time for it to set.
Whenever your stomach isn't well, just ask
for the plum tea. They'll bring it you.
Thank you for everything.
Once I find a place to live,
I'll leave.
You can't lose the executive director too,
because of me.
It seems...
...fortune has turned its back on you.
Mother.
Although you didn't let me
into your heart,
I know you looked after my family...
...and my brother.
I owe you a lot.
It would have been nice...
...if your brother wasn't so greedy.
I apologize.
I'm a wicked old woman...
...who outlived her own child.
I'm a cruel old lady...
...who is trying to protect
her own blood line.
Think of me that way.
This is...
...to compensate...
...for your hard work.
-It's okay, Mother.
-Please, take it.
I couldn't give you my love,
but you took care of me
for the past 20 years.
Please, take it.
If I can't do this much for you,
I am...
...not even human.
Minjun went to Yoona's
and Sunja is in the kitchen.
What about your restaurant?
Does that matter right now?
I've been thinking it over,
and I think we should tell her.
-Stay here.
-Okay.
What happened?
Well...
It's okay.
Here.
You know...
...Jang Junseong,
don't you?
I was shocked, too.
I know...
...Junseong.
And what happened in the past,
Hyunwoo...
...knows about them too.
You don't need to worry about that.
This is why...
...you shouldn't sin.
Sunja.
A few years ago,
I heard a young man...
...came looking for me.
I thought...
...it was the person
taking care of my son.
I was so grateful.
I had...
...no right.
A mother with the worst luck.
It would do him no good to meet me.
It's not that I won't see him.
I can't see him.
Just...
Please pretend you don't know anything.
Junseong...
...grew up to be the
strongest man in the world,
and he's also a champion.
Why don't you...
...make up for it...
...by loving him more?
When you're ready.
And...
...it isn't all your fault.
Anyone in that situation,
could've done the same.
A few years ago,
I heard a young man...
...came looking for me.
I thought...
...it was the person
taking care of my son.
I met Junseong's mother
because he asked me to.
But I guess you already knew about her.
I'm very happy that
you are the man,
that I am dating.
Aren't you busy?
-If you're busy...
-I'm busy, so stop talking.
Be fast and precise.
How happy are you to be dating me?
Hang up.
I'll tell you in person.
Okay.
You could've just sent word
through Mr. Min.
If there is a next time,
I'll make an appointment.
What is it?
I can't sign off on the
VVIP medical exam center.
The location and subcontractors
seem problematic,
so I need to take a further look.
Too much is being invested, I can't
decide purely based on the documents.
It's in your discretion.
There's no need to ask.
Okay, then.
Your birthday is in two days.
The chairman wants to have dinner.
I'll meet you at home.
Yes, Sir.
You are invited to Youngho's
birthday and our Christmas party.
Youngho's birthday is on Christmas?
See you tomorrow.
-Okay.
-Me too?
Thank you.
I don't know.
I'll attend if I'm not working.
Christmas is busy for hot celebrities.
I have a shoot to go to.
Where are you guys?
Where did Ma'am say she is?
Hyunwoo.
-Where are you?
-I'm feeling a little pressured.
What should we do? It's Christmas Eve.
Should I bring some cards and games?
Minjun, pick something.
Let's just play Yut. It'll be exciting.
It isn't New Year.
It will be fun.
I'll head over after I buy the cake. Bye.
Mom, I want this.
That?
I'll take that.
-Mom, I want that too.
-What?
Not if it's expensive.
How much is that?
You always ask for new toys
but you lose interest in a day.
That's it for your
Christmas present, okay?
Get over here.
-Merry Christmas!
Hello!
When will I get to live
in a place like this?
Minjun, let's eat until
our stomachs burst.
Are you looking for me?
You startled me.
-Hello.
Minjun.
Hyunwoo.
What is that?
I couldn't come empty-handed.
It's not much. It's just a cake.
Wow. I forgot. Thank you.
Okay then, please come in.
-Let's go. Come on.
-Where's Mr Min?
He's a very private person.
He also has to go to my
grandmother's house later on.
It seems the reporters
have gone to Christmas Eve parties also.
-Enjoy yourselves.
-Wait a minute.
Come here.
-Merry Christmas!
Merry Christmas. Goodbye.
Bye.
Okay, everybody.
Let's go party!
Let's go, come on.
-Go, go!
-Cheers.
-Cheers!
What's with the juice?
Instead of turkey,
we went Korean style. It's samgyetang.
-Wow.
-How's that? You like that?
Who made all this?
Really?
You both are really...
Your girlfriends must be so lucky.
-Wow, that looks good!
-Good choice.
My kid's right there.
It's Christmas.
Thank you.
-Try it.
-It's okay.
No!
We need to capture this moment.
Hold on.
-Get together. Minjun.
-Come here.
-One, two, three.
-Happy.
One, two, three, four.
♪ The shoulder carrying the bag.
♪ The shoulder, the shoulder.
The shoulder is beautiful.
Nice!
♪ I walk without a thought...
-The horses...
-The horses piggyback.
-Piggyback. Go!
-No.
-Gosh.
-Don't do that. Come down.
Yes!
-Yut!
-You did it?
Yes! Champion!
-It's Do!
-Do!
-Give me a Do!
Oh, yes!
-Okay, that's enough.
-Ouch.
You can hit Minjun, too.
What is my mom doing on Christmas Eve?
I'm cooking.
What about the others?
They're working.
It's a major holiday.
Is something wrong?
If something were wrong,
I'd be too crazed to call.
And if something is wrong,
will you fix it for me?
Are you an attorney?
Are you kidding me?
I'm the mother of an attorney.
I'll go to Daegu in the new year.
I'm sorry you have to spend it alone.
My goodness. I'm busier than you
on Christmas Eve.
Have as much fun as you can
while you're still young.
Bye.
-Don't feel pressured.
-No, no.
Why can't you do something...
Just because it's a day
when everyone should be happy,
doesn't mean everyone is happy.
Because everyone else is having fun,
someone feels lonelier.
Some people feel lonely,
but act like they are fine.
This is Junseong's number.
Just in case.
Have a Merry Christmas.
For some reason,
some people can't meet
the one they want to.
Some people
can't go because of some reason.
The person you have called is
unavailable right now.
Please try again later.
And some people...
...wait for somebody, regardless.
That's what this day is.
We all act happy and fine,
but...
...Christmas may be a day when
we miss somebody the most.
I should go.
It's my birthday tomorrow.
I saved you and helped you.
Didn't you max out on owing me?
You are an ingrate.
If nothing happens when you go
to your grandma's house today,
come straight home.
To continue...
...our restful and erotic evening?
I'll wear a ribbon and wait for you.
I'll be looking sexy and lovely.
What am I going to do with
this bewitching woman?
What's wrong?
My mom...
My mom wants to meet me.
Hold on.
Take my car.
And...
...buy her a nice dinner.
The best possible.
I will.
Thank you.
Go on.
"My son, Youngjun"
-Youngjun, why couldn't I reach...
-Are you Kim Youngjun's legal guardian?
-Yes.
-This is the emergency room.
Excuse me, are you his legal guardian?
Yes. What happened?
Well,
he was brought here
because of an overdose.
It was critical.
We pumped his stomach,
so we'll see how he is once he wakes up.
Youngjun.
Why did you do it?
How am I supposed to live?
Youngjun.
What is this?
What...
I'll call the hospital director...
...and have him check on him.
My sister...
...went into that rat hole...
...and worked as
a housekeeper, like an idiot,
and raised her son.
But...
But what is this now?
Once Youngjun wakes up,
I'll get the whole story
and take care of it.
Namcheol.
Do you know why Kim Sungcheol married you?
If he hadn't married you,
he would have gotten half of
the shares for Gahong.
He married you so he could
hand down the whole company to Youngho.
Unless something happens to Youngho,
nothing will go to Youngjun.
Where is Kim Youngho?
Find him right now!
Where are you now?
I'm home.
I was about to get dressed and leave.
What?
My mom...
My mom wants to meet me.
Hold on.
Take my car.
Junseong.
"Youngho"
"Junseong"
Hello.
I got it.
Youngho, darling.
Youngho!
Youngho.
Youngho! Youngho!
Youngho!