I...
even put the flower pot that you like.
Please save me...
Do you know this man?
Are you okay?
Let me go, you bastard!
So why didn't you answer your phone?
- I'm sorry...
- Ow, let go!
Report him.
Episode 5
Huh? You live in Apt. #101.
Yes.
You live in Apt. #201, right?
I'm your downstairs neighbor.
I'll leave your package here.
- Lee Hyeon Woo.
- Huh?
Did you really not put the flower pot here?
It's me, Miss Joo Eun.
Look. So it seems like there was a misunderstanding among neighbors—
A misunderstanding?
You're calling this situation a misunderstanding?
Well, it's not like you were assaulted, and there are no threatening texts or mail.
The fact that this is a recurrence is just your assumption.
To be honest, why would this person stalk you?
Don't you think so?
Excuse me. If you're an officer, shouldn't you be obtaining evidence from the victim in this situation?
I... realize you're in shock, but the law isn't that easy.
Then what about the victim? I guess I look like a pushover?
That's not what we mean. Don't be so sensitive, and—
Are you happy?
That's what it says over there.
"Our city where women are happy."
Excuse me... Are you her guardian?
If I had known she would have been
using me this often, I should be.
Don't you remember?
I remember.
Excuse me.
Oh! Please save me!
So, this person got injured too,
and in the case that he hires an attorney,
then you could get charged for assault instead.
Being detained is difficult too.
The law is such that—
It's pretty crappy.
You might need sincerity when you're comforting someone,
but in order to understand something, I think all you need is not to misunderstand.
"Are you okay? I understand."
"The law is so crappy that it may be hard to punish him, but I will try my very best."
To all the other victims, please tell them that.
Then, work hard.
Oh, Miss Kang Joo Eun!
Stop right there!
Really, thank you so much.
It's a relief that you remembered his face.
Then...
Kang Joo Eun, what happened?
Why didn't you tell them you're an attorney?
Was it because of me? I was acting in self-defense!
Ah.  Did you get hurt anywhere?
It's a relief.
Why did you become a lawyer
when you can't even protect yourself?
I know.
Do you want me to beat him senseless?
It would be better for you to be my attorney.
Wait.
Just to punish that person for being a stalker,
I can't get hurt or die.
Even if I have repeated and clear evidence,
at best, he'll be detained for maybe 24 hours.
A penalty of under 100,000 won?
Even that fine isn't given to the victim.
Since I'm a lawyer, because I'm a lawyer,
I know how it works, and that's
why I don't have any expectations.
It really is crappy.
To one person it's a life and death situation,
but to another it's a trivial matter.
I guess that's how the law works in this world.
In your past life... you must have been indebted to me.
Thanks to you, I lived again like this.
I'll give you back your clothes next time. Then...
Where are you going?
My friend's place is near here.
Don't worry and return to your home.
If I had a prior incarnation and were indebted to you, it must have been a tremendous debt.
Hyeon Woo, it's me.
Is it urgent?
Is something wrong?
No... Min Joon's grandmother has a bruise on her face again.
Again?
She says it was an accident this time too,
but it's not. It's definitely domestic violence.
Min Joon! Stop it now and go to bed.
Oh. Okay, I'll be right there. Yes, okay.
She's waiting up for me.
You just have to go a little further.
Every time, I'm upgrading my debt to you.
Ah! H-Here. Right behind it is my friend's home.
How much is it?
This time of the night you can only do overnight accommodations. It's ₩50,000.
By any chance, do you do account transfers?
It's better than a card.
Are you by yourself?
Yes.
How did you...
Your friend has a lot of rooms in her house.
Without a man, a woman shouldn't come to a place like this.
Just leave me alone!
Even though I've shown you all kinds of things,
I'm really mortified, shy, and embarrassed.
I'm fully aware that you have a weakness for those who are hurt,
and even more so for those who are in danger.
I also know that you're nicer than you look.
You can't fall asleep after leaving a woman like this out on the street. I know that, but—
You know that, but?
I...
I don't want to go home.
I'm scared.
I don't even have anywhere to go.
Do you think I came to a motel because I wanted to?
Then let's go.
Let's go. To the outside of your world.
The suite. My room. You asked me to take you outside of this world.
I'm sure tomorrow I'll regret it.
So with me... to the hotel's suite?
Do you want me to take you to the suite?
If you want, I'll do that.
No, it's not that.
Then, where is the outside of my world?
With someone like me, under that same roof, sleeping.
- What?
- I think safety is more important than something erotic. For tonight.
"What?"
Erotic?
He really doesn't give me a chance to be grateful.
I didn't plan to have a guest over, so I don't have new ones. Just use mine since you need them right now.
Omo. Then Yeong Ho Hyung-nim—
I mean, what about you, Mr. Coach?
No way would I have given you what I lie on and cover myself with.
Get some sleep. I'll tell the kids tomorrow.
I've done it so much that I'm sick of it too, but thank—
Thank you, sorry, I'm embarrassed. Those are your buzzwords.
I know, so let's do without them.
But still, thank you.
Just don't say, "Save me."
I'm too tired, so tonight, I don't think I can save you.
No way would I have given you  what I lie on and cover myself with.
Of course not!
Hey there! Please save me!
Cramp! Cramp! Cramps in my leg!
Wait, wait, wait.
By any chance, are you doing this because you're too embarrassed to just come out?
No I'm not! I really have a cramp!
Hurry! Hurry!
Then why don't you say once, "Mr. Coach, you're cool."
Mr. Coach, you're cool. You're the best.
Hurry. Hurry! I even want to call a cat right now!
Mouse (homonym for cramp). Catch it.
- Ahh!
- It's ridiculous!
Why would someone even do that!?!
Ma'am, seriously, it's a relief.
Oh, stalkers like that, you have to catch them and go,  " Pow, pow pow, push push push! " And slice them.
You must have been really shocked.
Yes. A bit—
If it hadn't been for me, it could have been really terrible.
Oh! I told you to stop.
You just have to go and pat yourself on the back.
We are a bit...
Eat this, Ma'am.
I'm sorry, but don't you have any salt marinade?
You're not here for a get-together at a meat restaurant.
Oh.
Take this first.
Omo. How did you—
Since you're known to be a meticulous person.
Thank you.
I miss soup.
You know, something spicy and comforting.
Something with some color. That kind of soup.
Since there's color, it'll do, right?
Wow! Fantastic!
Oh! Please keep excessive compliments to yourself!
Oh! Is she an actress?
Well, that's not totally untrue.
I think I've seen her somewhere.
All of you already know.
Ahh!
Long time ago,
there was a Chinese actress named, Shu Qi.
Since she was around a long time ago, you guys wouldn't know.
Shu Qi?
Oh! I found her! Shu Qi.  I found her.
Ah, are you really going to act like this?
It's me. Me. Kang Joo Eun!
Right now, intelligent and beaut—
A lawyer with a beautiful smile, Daegu Venus.
Let's see...
You do look a little similar. Do you have proof?
I'm telling you that it's me, since it is me. What? Proof?
Wow. Seriously.
See what happens when I lose weight. All of you will fall for me.
Eat up. Eat.
You don't believe me now.
Just wait and see. There will be hearts pouring out of your eyes!
- Excuse me.
- Oh! Oh! Oh!
Come on!
What? Why are they laughing?
It's okay, Hyeon Jung. Thank you for the shirt.
Let's walk as quickly as possible.
I... My nickname once used to be Daegu Venus.
There was almost no boy in South and North Gyongsang, for whom I wasn't his first love.
Do you suffer from mythomania? (compulsive lying)
It's me. Me. Kang Joo Eun!
Just wait and see. There will be hearts pouring out of your eyes.
Was it really true?
- Yes.
- Oh, you startled me!
Are you only waiting for me?
Day and night. What do you need?
Daegu... I have to go there, but I need a guardian.
By any chance, is there something wrong with your leg?
Where are you right now?
I should see whether it's wrong or not after I go down there.
I'll call you back after setting up a doctor's appointment. Then.
Okay...
I think you've been absent from your restaurant too long.
Thank you. You're really...
It's a relief that you'd already put it on the market, but call the landlord.
Ask him to take  care of it as soon as possible.
I did it earlier.
These are Min Joon's dermatitis cream, and the things I bought you at the Duty Free.
Why should you be the one to avoid him? Ask mom to come up and have her stay with you.
I'm sure mom will be so happy to hear that her daughter is being stalked!
Well, it's true. Mom might stalk the stalker instead.
That's right. Don't you avoid it, and let's call your mother!
I'm not avoiding, but living above and below each other makes me feel really uncomfortable.
I don't think I can fall asleep either.
Oh, that's true. It's crappy.
Jae Hyeok! Move all her things into my house.
No, it's okay. You only have two rooms.
You have Min Joon and his grandmother there too.
I'll figure it out on my own, so go back to work.
What can you figure out on your own?
I told you I will! Hurry up and go.
Ah! Seriously...
Anyway, thank you so much, Ms. Lawyer.
Call me if anything happens. Okay?
Don't get married. It's a crazy thing to do.
Also, stop picking at your sister's spine (squeezing money out of someone)! It's all crooked now!
Hurry up and leave!
I got it. I'm leaving.
Thank you!
Hey.
What is this?
Do you want to get married with just some lustral water? (water infused with magical powers)
You're going to marry someone's precious daughter and just suck your thumb? What about my niece or nephew inside the belly?
Noona.
Prepare a simple ceremony and set up shop. You have to do something to make a living somehow.
I'll send you more money as soon as my apartment has been rented.
I'm sorry! I'll earn a lot of money and pay you back double!
A lawyer isn't someone who rakes in money.
There won't be enough. Prepare simply.
We decided to do the wedding some other time. I'll look into a business first.
With Hyungnim Woo Sik ...
Ah! I told you we broke up! Why do you keep asking? Hurry up and go!
Work hard.
Athlete Im Woo Sik! Nice to meet you.
So from a request from the man who is sort of like her guardian,
we discovered it while going through the CCTV.
What is your relationship to her?
She's someone I know well. Someone I've known for a very long time.
If you appear in front of Kang Joo Eun once more, I will kill you myself.
What right do you have?
I saw everything. You breaking up with her.
You'll know well what right I have since you've been watching.
Stay away from Kang Joo Eun. It's not a warning but an order.
Sorry. See you tomorrow. I have an important meeting today.
Please tell Lawyer Kang Joo Eun to come to my office.
Yes.
Why did you tell me to get dressed up to come see you?
You passed your bar exam!
As a second year student at that.
I'm going to give you a present in celebration.
Hello, Oh Soo Jin!
Hello, Woo Sik.
How did you get here so fast?
How do you think?
Here.
It's Soo Jin's.
Ah.
Chocolate.
It's chocolate for the brilliant mind. Congrats on passing the bar.
When will our Joo Eun graduate and pass the bar?
I will soon. Soo Jin doesn't like chocolate.
No.
Thank you. I will enjoy them.
Am I a religious person? I can't show up anywhere in this.
Look at you. Where and what are you going to show?
He's here. He's here.
I've looked into him, and he's at the top of his class at his engineering college.
He's really nice and really genuine.
You came?
Joo Eun...
This is Soo Jin, the one I told you about. Oh Soo Jin.
Then, have a nice time together.
Tell Joo Eun. I heard it loud and clear.
What? What are you...
This is her way of rejecting me.
You and me. Here. This situation.
What?
Well, I realize she's doing this because she feels sorry for you,
but there's no need to make me pitiful too! Huh?
Also, your clothes— I thought someone died.
Did Joo Eun really say that?
She said she felt sorry for me?
Do I have to tell you that aloud?
Also, when someone looks like you,
you need to be quick on the uptake.
Don't hang around in places like this, and go home!
Joo Eun...
Joo Eun... How could she... To me...
What?
I won't be an attorney who makes house visits,  Vice CEO.
It's something I already mentioned to the CEO when I first got hired by Guntoo.
Working overnight, working outside the office, and staying up all night are fine, but I will never take on molester or rapist cases.
I don't want to make hospital visits to all the presidents of major companies who are lying in bed after doing corrupt things.
That's a relief then.
It's not the president of a major company, but it's his daughter.
It's that woman who assaulted an employee at a department store, isn't it?
Then, I really can't do it.
Our firm and Myung Hoon Electronics have a long standing relationship.
There seem to have been times where you've been a part of an external legal team.
I will give you a formal response. Vice CEO, I reject your offer.
I'm returning to you exactly what I got. I will give you a formal order.
You're in charge of it, Lawyer Kang.
Someone has to do it. If you don't, then someone else will.
If you cover your eyes and get mad, will it make a difference?
The CEO said it once, fulfill your dreams through mercy.
I'm done here. You may go.
No! If you eat all that sugar, your body will curse at you.
I will too.
Did I just have an ... auditory hallucination?
On top of stress, I'm hungry too!
My hypothyroidism...
Air fresh! Fresh!
Yeah!
Come on!
Go!
At that rate, he's has the championship title in the bag.
Since the welterweight division is vacant.
if he wins the RFC this time, he'll probably go on to the grand slam.
But that fool keeps lowering his weight class. To lightweight.
What? Why?
He doesn't want the title for free.
He wants to go after Akira who lowered his class in order to avoid him.
Seriously... He's the type to take the long way around even on the easy path.
Hurry! Hurry!
Good job.
The smell of organic grass that's healthy for my body.
Ah! Really...
Abdominal obesity. Adult diseases. Vigilance. Danger. Alert. Requirement.
Aren't you busy?
Look at this wicked woman.
Eat this.
Is this a side effect from dieting?
Eat.
By any chance, did you eat stir-fried marinated pork earlier?
Do I smell?
Jjamppong! You ate jjamppong!
You already ate earlier. Fancy grass and high protein.
Oh, I'm so hungry... Ah.
Do I have to go this far?
You do look similar, but do you have proof?
I am saying it's me, but insufficient evidence?
I won't eat! I won't!
Excuse me... I have something to talk to Mr. Snake about.
Could you please give us room?
Jang Yi Jin? What's up!
I'm not Ja-Jang Yi Jin.
You are Jang Yi Jin.
Even so, you know not to post it to social media, right?
You need me to leave?
Okay. See you later!
I decided to do that CF.
Why are you donating the full amount?
If Mr. Snake does a good deed before I do and makes a good impression,
how will that make me look?
I will look like a star who only cares about money!
That is... If you want to do it, let's do it together.
If not, tell me ahead of time.
By any chance, do we know each other?
Really, I'm dumbfounded.
You're saying you don't know me?
I've seen you on TV once in a while.
Once in a while? I'm on TV a lot!
Anyway!   That donation, let's make it so that we're doing it together.
Don't say anything different to the reporters!
But I am just curious...
If you're an orphan, why are you donating to a charity for single mothers?
Shouldn't you be donating to an orphanage?
Are you interested in me? No, I'm sure you are. You're a man after all.
I'm not.
By any chance, are you gay?
Hey lassie,  why do you keep getting thin?
Oppa, how can you call me that in front of my son?
Just because you're Gahong's Ma'am,
are you a Ma'am to your older brother too?
Why isn't your husband coming?
I know... He said he'd definitely be here.
It's okay. Oh, Uncle. I have to go to the bathroom.
Yes. Okay.
I'm so upset.
How much did you dampen his spirits while raising him?
In time for the upcoming 61st anniversary,
I think Chairwoman Lee is  going to make Kim Yeong Ho the board president.
What did I tell you?
In that Gahong household, Yeong Joon is considered  to be someone else's son.
Don't say such things.
You're such a fool!  He's not blood related on the  family register!
His father, Kim Seong Cheol, is Chairman Lee's son-in-law!
After kicking out her only daughter, there wasn't anyone appropriate to take over the company—
No matter what anyone says, our Yeong Joon
is my husband's son, and my mother-in-law's grandchild.
Hey, Choi Hye Ran!
Wake up!
Don't be caught off guard later and create drama about living or dying over it.
Eat a lot.  You're so thin.
Deok Seon Pharmaceutical's Miss Cha Seon Yeong is going to be a little late.
Are you sure she's running late and not that she is not coming?
Eat by yourself.
I got dumped, so I'm sulky.
I'm sorry.
Awesome! It's like heaven.
Did I come too early?
Would you like to order?
I... Caramel macchiato. No, no. White chocolate?
Give me caramel mocha with a lot of whipped cream.
Peppermint, please.
Warm.
What are you doing?
He's real.
Are you emigrating somewhere?
Yes. To the outside of this world.
Did someone say they were giving you permission?
I already heard from Ji Woong to stay there until I find a place.
That the house is big and there are lots of rooms.
You are a lot quicker than you look.
Anyway, I'll pull the car around, so when you get your tea carry your tea and come out to the car. (tea is homonym for car)
What?
But... why do you want me to hold this?
I didn't want them to fall from the backseat, since someone precious gave them to me.
Do you want me to put the heat on under your butt?
No. It's giving off its own steam.
Isn't the flower pot in the backseat  from the stalker?
Someone must be happy to receive flowers from a precious person,
when someone else has a stalker who shoves a flower pot in her face.
How long has it been, since you had symptoms in which whatever you think comes out through your mouth?
I only brought it since they say that you shouldn't dislike the flowers, even if you dislike the person.
You're nice.
But why did you buy the blanket and pillow?
By any chance, because you didn't have any after giving me yours?
- Since women might come and sleep over.
- Oh!
Why? Can't they sleep over?
Well, why not? With Anna Sue too... Hah!
By the way, congratulations Mr. John Kim.
The scandal you had with Anne Sue dropped a little in the ranking of real time searches.
Maybe people are starting to forget it a little.
But... Where are we going right now?
To my ideal woman.
Ideal woman?
Jiu-jitsu?  Why here?
I want to introduce you to my ideal woman.
So, why do I have to meet your ideal woman?
So you can watch and learn a little.
Omo. Why should I?
This is what's called the cross guard.
She might look like she's at a disadvantage, but actually it's not true.
My ideal woman.
My ideal woman's husband.
Excuse me. What about the Directors?
They've left work.
Come close.
Pardon?
There's no law saying you wouldn't run into a stalker or drunk again,
so if you can't deal with it through law, we should do it with our fists.
Ahh... That's why today...
Jiu-jitsu is almost the only sport where a woman can win against a man.
Since, through skill, you can break the joints.
Now, get on top of me.
Huh?
You saw the Director's position earlier, right?
I am Kang Joo Eun, and you're the drunk.
I am?
Attack me. As much as you'd like. As much as you wish.
You just said as much as I wish.
Here I come, you stalker bastard.
You saw, right? Do it again.
Again.
Stalker bastard.
♬  1-2-3-4  ♬
♬   That's right, why don't you come over here right  now, girl?    ♬
♬   Doop Doo Ah, Doop Do Ah. Nobody get in my way!  ♬
♬   I’m feeling so good, everything's so fine, I feel like I'm flying,   ♬
First warning for excessive physical contact
No, that's not it...
♬   Thinking of her every morning, I  ♬
♬   Even when I fall asleep, ooh hoo hoo.  ♬
Cross guard, close your opponent down with your leg strength.
♬   Yeah, I think it keeps showing,   ♬
Strength.
♬   She is my beautiful, beautiful lady   ♬
Don't avoid eye contact and look at your opponent.
Strength.
♬    You're my beautiful beautiful lady. .  ♬
Tap.
♬   Girl whom I just can't take my eyes off.  ♬
♬   The inside of my head is always so complicated,  ♬
♬   I'm afraid that she'll leave, but still I don't dislike it,   ♬
Tap tap.
Why, do you not want to let me go?
What?
When a person tap taps, you're supposed to let them go.
♬   So baby  I've got to hug you in my arms  ♬
♬  Beautiful, beautiful lady,  ♬
♬   Even seeing her again and again she's beautiful. Yeah.  ♬
Breathe.
♬   so beautiful, so beautiful lady,   ♬
♬   Girl whom I just can't take my eyes off  ♬
♬   so beautiful, so beautiful   ♬
♬   To me you are too perfect, Girl  ♬
Uh, well...
Is your ideal type really a martial artist?
A strong woman is sexy.
Even if you can't see her, you worry less about her.
For me also, I thought you liked the Anna Sue type.
Are you interested in my type?
Oh, a question related to the kiss earlier?
What kiss?
Oh. Hey, I lost 4.5 kg (approx 10 pounds).
I think I've become a bit skinny.
Earlier, from what I felt...
That's enough, that's enough.
I'll take care of my body as I see fit.
Have you forgotten?
Kang Joo Eun's body is mine.
Skinny?
My score is... Well...
Well, anyway, congratulations on your first digit changing.
Oh, Daegu Venus.
It's been a very long time since the first digit changed...
♬  Love is you,  ♬
♬   This excitement today, I am getting a good feeling for some reason ♬
♬   I’m getting a good feeling   ♬
♬  If you see me and call my name,  ♬
♬  I don't have the confidence not to smile,  ♬
♬  Come to me, look into my eyes,  ♬
♬  My heart trembles and I waver at the thought of you,  ♬
♬   This excitement today, I am getting a good feeling for some reason ♬
♬  When you come closer, when you you look at me,  ♬
♬  When you call my name,  ♬
♬  I feel like I've fallen   ♬
♬  in love,  ♬
Everyone come to eat.
Wait one minute.
If we're going to have to eat these roots and bland meat
let's at least eat it in sufficient quantities.
but Ma'am, why are we speaking so softly?
In case Hyungnim Yeong Ho makes a fuss again.
Don't you know that an elephant is also an animal which eats bland food?
Hyungnim isn't here.
Where did he go?
He had something to take care of so... a bit far.
He'll be a while.
That's good. Let's eat a lot among us.
Why?
Thyroid medication.
Anyway, since you are known to be meticulous.
Just a moment.
What's with him? Without even saying anything?
The backseat will be safer.
I'm not the director yet.
I never hired a driver like you either, Manager Min.
About Deok Seon Pharmaceutical's Miss Cha Sun Yeong. Think about it carefully.
You two are well suited.
Think about it carefully.
We're better suited.
But why is there no flower bouquet today?
Starting tomorrow it'll be quite tiring. Try closing your eyes.
Hey, is this the sound of deliciousness right now?
Of course I did lose something.
My pants are bigger and my jacket's looser.
Producer Go went to the US?!
To find John Kim?!
When is he coming?
Hey, as his ex-wife do you not even know that?
No, no, no. Hang up for now.
What do I do?
Where did this man go?!
Did he go to America?
Fourteen.
Sixteen.
Mr. Coach.
Yes. Who is it?
It should be saved as Mr. Coach.
Oh, it's Mr. Coach.
I heard you went somewhere.
I'm having a glass of wine after such a long time.
Hang up for now.
Where is there such...
Oh no, oh no.
Since not being able to lie is your strong point.
How much did you exercise?
Has it been about 30 or 40 minutes?
What about stretching? Did you do enough?
None of your business whether I do it or not.
Remember the 1-10 I mentioned earlier?
Among those 1, 4, 5.
Oh, the nagging, the nagging.
What's the point of video calling? As if it's a face I miss so much I could die.
What's all this fuss about missing me now?
Then why don't you act a little more prettily normally.
What?
Me too. Said from the heart.
Oh, if you just leave what am I supposed to do?!
One, four, five.
Take videos of them and send them to me. I'll give you remote support.
Videos?
Not porn. Evidence videos.
Since you're not in front of my eyes, can I trust you to do them?
And that...
Move your cheek since I can't see.
But then,  are you by chance in America?
And if so?
To see Anna Sue?
If so?
Take care of yourself.
My friend's ex-husband, Producer Go, went to America to find John Kim.
Oh, is that right?
Then shall we hang up?
Whatever.
I think Anna Sue is here.
Then have a comfortable and racy night.
This is a medical exam questionnaire.
I thought it would be more comfortable if I filled it in for you.
The head of the hospital will be here in the morning.
Then, please rest.
Manager Min.
Just... Have a comfortable and racy night.
CT, MRI, PET-CT
Hyeon Woo's ex-husband, PD Go
Go PD, have you found John Kim?
PD, have you found John Kim?
One, two, three, stop.
November 21st, my last exercise for the day.
It's the number 10
Oh, it's hard! Oh.
What is she doing?
Since it's such a rare disease,
and until you come here more often, I can't give you a definite answer since it's a special case.
but in my opinion, you're 99.9% free of tumors.
Congratulations.
By the way, you have pain periodically? How intense?
Probably. It seems to be a nerve issue.
Once in a while, it's hard to withstand it.
There's a chance that the  primary cause is psychological.
It's like fear. Since all those operations were probably too much for a child to handle.
Father! Please stop this!
Dad, save me!
Dad, I'm really scared!
Mom. Mom.
It really hurts.  Please save me.
After I become an adult, after I get a little older, couldn't I do it then?
Please, Father.
There's no cure for a nerve issue.
It'll probably disappear one day or continue until I die.
If you need my help,  call me at any time.
Yes, thank you.
The rehabilitation must have been painful.
Almost as if you did too much, you did very well. In today's terms, you have an awesome physique.
I made a desperate effort to survive.
You worked very hard.
To say it's a miracle wouldn't be an exaggeration.
It's all thanks to you. Thank you.
Where should I take you?
Manager Min... I want to rest a little.
I'll take you to the closest hotel.
Anna Sue is begging me to play a few days longer. Today is number 2, 5, and 10.
Good morning, Manager Min!
It's good evening.
Let's go, okay?
2014. 11. 25.
8:15 PM
Eight... Nine...
Ten...  Eleven...
Yes, I'm doing it.  Twelve...
Did everyone go somewhere?
Can't you hear me?
This... is something I haven't seen before.