"Episode 11"
When it comes to timing,
it's better to be early than late.
Producer Ko,
release it.
-I'm here waiting for him.
-It's Kim Youngho!
Kim Youngho!
Are you Kim Youngho of Gahong Group?
-Kim Youngho!
-Is it true that you are John Kim?
Is it true that you are John Kim?
Is it true about you and Anna Sue?
Please give us a statement.
What is it?
What?
Stop it!
I'm sorry, Sir.
An article about you and Anna Sue has
been released.
We should go somewhere else for now.
John Kim!
Go after him!
-Isn't this John Kim's house?
-Kim Youngho!
-Please calm down.
-Is it true?
Yes, Sir.
Anna Sue's people will
release their statement tomorrow.
They will be stating that
the scandal is not true.
Were you prepared for this?
I already decided to accept
the bitter cup.
But
people won't care
whether or not it's true.
People care more about...
...what they hear rather than the truth.
The more people talk about it,
the more they'll believe it's true.
It's not just your house in Nonhyeon-dong,
your grandma's house and the office are...
...all bombarded with reporters.
Is there somewhere quiet you can go?
Just for one day.
Just for a couple of days.
I can't run away like this anymore.
I was the one that told her...
...not to run away.
"Coach"
The call cannot be connected.
Please leave a message.
Who is this woman?
What's going on?
You must be going somewhere nice.
Why didn't you answer your phone?
I was so scared.
Are you all right?
There are too many reporters
in front of the house,
so I don't want to go home.
The same goes for the hotel.
I don't want to go home.
Do you think I'd want to sleep at a hotel?
Did you think I wanted to come here?
I only have one room...
...and only one bathroom.
But come in.
It's going to be a place...
...outside of your earth.
Boarding.
Take off.
Today, it's Kang Jooeun,
who is sexy all over.
Gosh.
You thought you were the only one
who could be sexy?
Anyone can be sexy.
I...
...can't sleep unless it's a suite.
The bed springs...
You should be thankful.
I should have you sleep on
the floor with Rascal.
If you're not going to be sweet,
you should leave and let me sleep here.
Don't think about anything
and go to sleep.
You can worry about it tomorrow.
You're going to worry about it tomorrow
anyway, so don't let it bother you today.
I'll call you if I want to spend...
...a restful and erotic night.
I need to wash up.
Good night.
Didn't you forget something?
Are you happy now?
I am.
Leave me.
It's not something...
...someone can cure.
It's neurosis.
My body still remembers it.
A human body is smarter than you'd expect.
It'll probably continue until
it disappears one day.
Or it will continue until the day I die.
Junseong.
It's me.
I wanted to let you know that
Youngho is in my place,
so you don't need to worry.
Is he...
You know, don't you?
What...
What should I do?
He's in so much pain,
but there's nothing I can do.
Just...
...act like nothing is wrong.
It pains him to see people who
he cares about suffer.
It pains him more than his own suffering.
Youngho is like...
...a father to me.
Please take good care of him.
He is...
...really important to me, too.
Please take good care of him.
I will.
-Hurry up. He's getting away.
-Faster.
Shoot. Where is he?
Shoot.
-Fast. Where is he?
-Shoot.
-Go this way.
-Move, man!
Press down on it.
If you move, you'll destroy your leg.
Did you run with your leg like this?
I don't know if you're stupid or brave.
What's it to you?
Your leg is broken, you punk.
-Where is he?
-Shoot!
-Where is he? Where did he go?
-Shoot.
Your blood pressure is normal.
Your face shows that
you aren't lacking blood.
You took painkillers.
Who are you?
Is that how you say thank you?
Where are your parents?
Did they pass away?
You don't have parents, so you must
not be a student studying abroad.
Are you adopted?
Where are your adoptive parents?
Do you have anywhere to go?
Why you!
What's it to you?
Who are you, jerk?
You have a temper.
I'm not a jerk. I'm Youngho.
I'm weak when it comes to people in pain
and even weaker towards people
who are in danger.
Shut the...
I don't need your pity.
I don't need it!
Pity?
It isn't pity.
I can relate, that's all.
You're angry and want to fight.
If you want to fight you should,
but don't use guns or knives.
Fight where there are rules.
Wipe your hands, kid.
I'd like you...
...to leave me alone today.
Did I say anything?
I'll just stay quietly here.
Next to you.
It is a cold winter for lonely people.
Let's help the needy and share the warmth.
Be strong, everyone.
I'm a celebrity specializing in comforting
and cheering people on.
Gosh.
Isn't it comforting just to have someone
lying next to you?
Especially since it's me, Yijin,
the queen of commercials.
How can you comfort me
when you don't know anything?
That doesn't mean I can't comfort you.
Sadness is all the same.
We're moving pretty quickly.
We kissed and now we're
already sleeping together.
Nice weather.
I feel great today.
-Right?
-Yes, you're right.
I feel like nothing happened.
My shoulders feel light.
What are you doing here?
You are such bad actors.
Ma'am said to act normal.
She did.
You call that normal?
Let's eat.
My apartment looks smaller
since you guys are so big.
I don't think you needed
an apron to prepare this.
I did.
I threw in everything that was
in the fridge, so be grateful.
And a drop of sesame oil.
A drop...
How fermented is that sesame oil?
My mom sent it to me yesterday.
Open wide.
Ma'am, it's fantastic.
It tastes incredible.
White rice makes all the difference.
I'll just have one bite.
After breakfast, get your clothes
and equipment ready.
We need to work out.
Don't you always work out
rain or shine?
-Equipment?
-What are you talking about?
I'll show you what
Korean training is all about.
Ma'am, we look like Robocop.
It's strange that I can
see through this thing.
What are we doing here?
You really shouldn't be exposing
your face in public.
Here we go.
Please follow me while clapping your hands
as hard as possible.
Ma'am, wait for me.
-Hello.
-Good morning.
-Junseong.
-Yes.
What was it?
Let's just think of this as a warm up.
Why are we doing this to the tree?
Did it do something bad to us?
-It's...
-It's good for blood circulation.
I've been doing this for 10 years.
I'm so healthy that I haven't
even gotten a cold.
Why are you guys so weak?
Why don't you hit it harder?
The girl is doing a better job.
Do it like she's doing it.
It hurts.
-You want to try, young man?
-Where are you going?
It hurts.
This improves blood circulation and
eliminates wastes from the body.
I shouldn't because of my muscles...
This has nothing to do with muscles.
-It's all tight here.
-It hurts.
-You need to relax them.
-Wait.
Take a deep breath.
You'll see tomorrow. All the wastes
from your body will flush out.
Come over here.
Where are you going?
In my professional point of view,
I worked hard to make these abs.
It has nothing to do with abs.
You'll see tomorrow.
Your body will flush out all the wastes.
You'll take responsibility
if my abs are ruined?
Your abs belong to me.
You can't say no.
Hold on.
Ready, go!
Oh, no. Are you okay?
Did you bring me here
to cheer me up?
Why would I cheer you up?
This all happened because you're a
part of Gahong and you're John Kim.
-What?
-You told me before.
Exercising can take your
mind off of your worries.
What are you doing?
The boys are watching us.
Let go of me.
Oh, no.
Let's do it again.
You're making me shy. Do it again.
I'm glad I forced myself to study.
I will support you if you're unemployed.
You can count on me.
Please look after the house.
I'll go make lots of money.
You're going to be late.
Have a nice day.
I will.
As you mentioned before,
Anna Sue's people released a statement
that refuted the scandal.
This morning, I also met with
the reporters.
We can't prevent everything
from appearing on the news,
but we have controlled speculative rumors
from being reported.
You are not a morning person.
Your grandmother and father...
...are waiting for you.
I've brought some clothes that
you can change into.
No.
I'll go just as I am right now.
-Kim Youngho!
-Mr Kim!
-Show us your face.
-John Kim!
-Kim Youngho!
-Look over here.
Young Master...
...has arrived.
I'm relieved...
...now that he's finally back.
My baby.
Who was that girl?
Is she an attorney?
Why didn't you report to me?
Are you looking down
on me because I'm old?
I'm sorry.
Since you know Youngho's situation,
you shouldn't let this happen.
He needs a spouse who can help
strengthen his position.
I think the daughter of Deokseong
Pharmaceuticals'...
...is good enough for Youngho.
As soon as the construction is finished,
get him to move in.
Yes, Chairwoman.
Please bring the bell-flower root tea
instead of that.
Yes, Ma'am.
Please prepare green plum tea for Mother.
She isn't feeling well.
I'm sorry that I've made the elders worry.
You've come back.
I'll understand this...
...as your will to keep your position.
Stand up.
I never spanked you...
...because I didn't want anything to
happen to your knee.
You need to toughen up.
Defend...
...your position.
You may not have much time.
Yes.
Father.
Until the 61st anniversary of the company,
and until your inauguration,
keep a low profile.
Why don't you eat with us?
It's been a while since you've come.
No, thank you.
Please take care of...
...Grandmother and Father.
"Attorney Kim Yeonghan"
A pregnant woman killed her husband.
But if you look into it,
the woman had been
severely abused by her husband.
If I recall correctly,
I think she was trying to
protect her baby.
She pushed him as she was running away.
Back then, people weren't educated
on domestic violence or abused wives.
The judges were not interested...
...in her side of the story either.
She was just a woman that
killed her husband.
I think she has probably...
...served her full sentence.
The last thing I heard about her,
was that she gave birth while in prison.
Why did you leave this in
front of my house?
It's not that, it's just that...
You looked cold.
Why do you care?
Don't do this again. Never again.
Never...
...come here again.
Mr. Sexy!
Please open the door. It's me, Hyunwoo.
Jooeun is not here.
Ready and bow.
Hello.
Mom, I need to pee.
Go to the bathroom.
You're John Kim and the heir of Gahong.
You're also a sexy guy.
I said you were unemployed.
I didn't know you had three jobs.
It's all right.
I couldn't let Jooeun stay alone
with a man at home.
That's not quite true.
No one else could look after Minjun.
I heard you are currently unemployed.
Don't let the fact that Producer Ko is my
ex worry you. I can't stand him either.
Minjun, I'm leaving.
See you. Thank you.
Excuse me.
I can't come down from the toilet.
Do you have to come down?
Was it the big one?
That was quite a welcoming party...
...for the new executive director.
The board members didn't come to
the meeting and now this scandal.
You must be very worried.
I've been through much more.
The decision of the board members
remains the same,
but the new executive director
disagrees with us.
If you sign this before the
61st anniversary of the company,
it would benefit the both of us.
We would be helping each other.
"VVIP Medical Exam Center"
I think that's out of my jurisdiction now.
Is that right?
I hope our board members
will accept Youngho...
...as the new executive director.
I'm looking forward to
the 61st anniversary ceremony.
I told you to move into a house that
would be easy for guys to access.
And you did just as you were told.
Hi, Minjun!
When will you be home?
He's been making me work out all day.
That's what he does all the time.
Hang in there.
I'll bring you snacks.
You remind me of somebody.
She was very pretty.
Uncle, I need to pee.
I'll be right there.
That growing child knows how to climb up
the toilet seat but can't climb down it.
It sounds like he has a promising future.
Think of this day as another
Kang Jooeun Day.
You're learning a different kind of
sweetness in life.
You're just making that up.
You're using me as a babysitter.
Sometimes, you need to think things over
and make the right decision.
Other times, holding on and wait
for time to pass is another way.
My unemployed man,
good luck!
Uncle.
Hang up. He needs me.
Uncle, I need to poop.
I thought you said it was
going to be sweet.
I feel so bad for Sunja.
She's working so hard.
She even supports her abusive husband.
Apparently, Sunja doesn't want
to meet her son, Junseong.
She gave her son up for adoption.
She might feel bad about that.
From my point of view,
I can't tell Junseong everything.
I can't convince Sunja either.
What if Sunja just disappears one day?
Exactly.
It would be bad for Mr. Muscles,
but it would also be bad for Minjun.
I can't raise Minjun without her.
Honestly,
I was worried that it would freak you out
when I told you that she had a record.
Are you kidding me?
Sunja raised my son
since he was one year old.
Not even my mom or
my mother-in-law did that.
I can't believe you thought that.
We'll wait and see for now.
As expected from Lee Hyunwoo!
I'm proud of you, my friend.
Here comes another friend of yours.
Producer Ko?
What is he doing here?
Gosh.
Hey, ex-husband.
Are you getting legal advice
from Soojin herself?
Ex-wife.
Just ignore me.
What are you up to?
I'm working now,
so you need to respect your superior.
Respect your superior?
Are you joking?
-Please don't. Let's go.
-I'm going to...
What are you looking at?
Minjun, I'm ho...
Did you make a lot of money?
You know nothing since you were born rich.
I'm an attorney at a firm.
I get a monthly salary.
When was the last time
you washed your hands?
Are you a baby?
By the way,
don't even dream about a restful
and erotic night while you're here.
That is not allowed here.
Even when Minjun is not here, think of
this place as a child-friendly zone.
Your world is totally
beyond my expectations.
I'm in a tough situation.
You must like rhyming your words.
"I'll go get the car. When the tea
comes out, bring it to the car."
That's a masterpiece.
I saw a ring on your dressing table.
Do you still have feelings for
your ex-boyfriend,
or are you keeping it
because it's expensive?
I once threw it away,
but I went back to pick it up.
Wooshik was the one who gave it to me, but
I was the one who wore it for 15 years.
It belongs to me, too.
But...
If you want me to, I'll throw it away.
If you don't want to throw it away,
you don't have to.
There's nothing to throw away about you.
I told you that this wasn't allowed.
Don't forget the stretches that
I taught you.
-The forward stretch. Got it?
-Okay!
Will Minjun become as sexy as you?
I can't guarantee that.
I see.
Anyway, thank you. Bye.
Minjun.
Goodbye, my little puppy.
We're leaving. We'll leave you alone.
What's wrong with you? Go on. Bye.
Do you realize that because of
the John Kim news,
your position as executive director is
on the line?
Wanting to spend a restful and
erotic night at a time like this...
...isn't a good idea.
I'm also a chaste woman.
Anyway,
I believe the mind can control the body.
I hope you will control your
mind while you are here.
Okay?
Did I say anything?
The mind controls the body.
Can you guarantee that?
Yes, I can guarantee, promise,
and assure you of that.
Okay.
Oh, dear.
At least button up first.
The inauguration of the new executive
director and 61st anniversary of Gahong...
...is expected to carry on as scheduled.
Sources say that the executive
director's inauguration is set,
but nothing is confirmed.
They request that people refrain
from reporting speculative rumors.
"Mr. Min"
-Yes?
-I'm controlling the situation,
but the media and board
members aren't making it easy.
Consider it spilled milk,
and watch what happens.
Okay.
It may be better to dry the area,
rather than try to put
the milk back into the bottle.
By the way,
how long will you be
staying at Jooeun's house?
Don't be jealous.
Good night.
Soojin.
I saw your car out front.
Let me in.
I'm sorry.
I'm coming in.
Who said you could come in?
Get out.
If you didn't want me to come in,
you should've used a different passcode.
Did you think...
...that I didn't know my
girlfriend's birthday?
I heard you found out about...
...Producer Ko?
I'm the external counsel for Kim Youngho.
If my client has a problem,
it's my job to fix it.
I'm sure that he obtained
Kim Youngho's license...
...illegally.
Soojin.
Please leave.
Please.
Why is life...
...like salt water?
I drink and drink,
but...
Your desk...
...is still so cluttered.
You must have time to kill since
you're on the cleanliness squad too.
Right.
I was thinking about what to wear.
For tomorrow.
It's Gahong's 61st anniversary ceremony.
But we may not be able to go.
The executive director hasn't said
whether or not he will attend.
Did you know that Kim
Youngho was John Kim?
I see.
That's how you lost so much weight.
I'd like you to ask
your questions in writing,
so that I can crumple them up
and throw them out.
I'm the head of the external counsel team.
I should know that so that
I can handle the crisis.
We will be requesting Producer
Ko to certify his sources.
-That's why...
-Of course,
we'll be asking Im Woosik as well.
-What?
-The one who provided Kim Youngho's...
...license was Im Woosik.
He's the one who leaked
the conclusive proof that...
...Kim Youngho is John Kim.
Why would he do that?
I don't know.
I'd like to know, too.
I'll feel bad for you if you can't
go to the ceremony.
I thought...
...it would be a chance
to see the old, pretty you.
Okay, then.
What the...
What's going on?
Where is he?
I'm home.
Cleaning isn't about shoving
things somewhere, it's about...
What's this?
You have a lewd look on your face.
Wake up.
Are we done with
the child-friendly zone?
Why did you raise the heat so much?
Just because you're not paying...
You have a bed scene tomorrow, right?
Did you mean to say a party scene?
Gahong's 61st anniversary ceremony party.
Are you sleeping here again tonight?
Was my sexiness too overwhelming?
This woman can't contain herself.
Your pulse is rushed.
It's not just my pulse.
I may jump all over you,
so let's decide here and now.
What?
I mean,
the Venus of Daegu...
...spent several days with Mr. Sexy.
I'm not saying I won't be chaste,
but even on children shows,
they kiss each other.
We're practically 80,
if we add up both of our ages.
I'm sorry, but I'm a little tired.
Go to sleep.
Sleep tight and look pretty tomorrow.
You're the one that seduced me.
Wasn't it mutual?
It's no fun if you're too aggressive.
-Pink.
-It's cute and lovely.
Sir.
It's the timing for me
to leave this place,
that is outside of my earth.
Mr. Min and I don't seem to get along.
Youngho,
you'll be at the ceremony tomorrow, right?
I probably
won't be able to kiss you
even if I'm glad to see you.
We need to be professional anyway.
Even if I do go, I'll be there as
part of the external counsel team.
I'll go now.
Let's have our restful and
erotic night another time.
What are they going to
do about Kim Youngho?
I think they'll announce him
as the executive director.
They'll push forward?
Did the board members turn
their backs on us?
I think the external counsel got to them.
I see.
Ma'am.
You should eat something.
I'm sorry I'm late.
Wow, Lawyer Kang.
You look good.
Thank you, I tried.
Are you nervous?
Why? You're not the executive director.
You're right.
The chairman is entering the hall.
Please take your seats.
Why aren't you here?
"Why aren't you here?"
What happened to Youngho?
We can't reach him.
Look into it.
I guess he isn't here.
I'm sorry.
Coach?
What is the star of
the ceremony doing here?
What should I do?
I think
I'm going to be very late.
People are waiting.
Your father and grandmother.
Junseong, Jiwoong and everyone.
Get up.
Kang Jooeun.
You're still hanging in there,
so you haven't reached your limit yet.
I can still do it.
That means I haven't reached my limit yet.
Look at me.
If you believe it, you can do it.
Because you believe that you can.
If I believe it, I can do it.
I believe that I can.
Where is he?
What's happening?
Executive director, Kim Youngho has...
...just arrived.
"Oh My Venus"
It doesn't look like you're
going to be Cinderella,
if you take your shoes off
instead of putting them on.
You are invited to Youngho's birthday
party and our Christmas party.
I'm very happy that you are the man
that I am dating.
Youngjun.
What am I supposed to do?
Where's Youngho?
You looked pretty today.
Enough for me to dream of you every night.