I'm going to be a little bit of a
little bit of a
little bit of
a little bit
of a
There's certain employers who
Why did you eat the fish?
Your highness picked the fish yourself.
It's very good.
If I don't eat it,
I will not let him down.
But luckily I don't eat too much.
It will be fine in a few days.
Oh, right.
When you return,
you should pack up all the things you haven't used in the past two years.
Use them as much as you can.
You don't need to spend money to buy the same things anymore.
Yes.
Your highness, you have to go out tomorrow.
You should rest early.
I will serve you to wash and change your clothes.
I'm leaving.
Go.
Your highness.
The money and food sent by the Ministry of Revenue has been cleared.
There is no mistake.
Okay.
Let's go.
Yes.
Go.
Father!
Yu!
Lord Xu.
Why are you here?
I heard that father is in danger.
So I came to see you off.
My wife is worried that Lizhou is cold.
So she sent you to save her.
Beile Gu is a naughty man.
Please take care of yourself.
And return to the capital safely.
Tan'er is a child.
She is afraid of separation.
My wife Yang Xilu didn't come to see me off.
But she sent me a tiger.
She said that tiger can be with father every day.
Yuanzhang.
There are some antidotes for the poison.
There are several other hidden weapons.
I have prepared them for you.
Maybe.
You are so thoughtful.
I'm sorry to see you go to Lizhou.
Now that the doctor of Yang Xilu is in danger.
The army is in danger.
I hope you can be careful.
Take care of yourself.
Yuanzhang.
Be careful.
Liu Bu.
Go.
Your highness.
What's wrong?
I'm here to give you medicine.
You can't eat the lotus.
You will get sick.
I know you care about your health.
So I want to give you another medicine.
So you can get better soon.
I know I can't eat it.
Why don't you eat it?
You are so kind.
Give it to me.
Liu Bu.
I look like a villain.
Like...
Stupid.
I hope you can bless me.
I will be as beautiful as a man.
I will be beautiful.
Only then can I be with you.
If I can be more than seven fingers.
I will be very happy.
If I can learn martial arts.
I will be happy.
I will be very cool.
So when we learn martial arts.
I will be happy.
Can see now.
I am your crow,
And come into the border for my continued развитion
I wish for變化為你的志
Let time take it away from our war
Principle of unity is to entangle each other
And share happiness
Jing An's 4th princess.
I, Zhe, am married to Prince Dingbei,
and I am going to marry Princess Dingbei.
Even if I have never expected it,
I can't help but feel anxious.
The flowers are only for you and me.
Now that things have come to this,
I don't know if I married you because of my love for you,
or because I wanted to marry you.
I am only able to do this because of you.
What are the other things that Princess Dingbei does during her days off?
Your Highness, Princess Dingbei can't eat smokey food,
and she doesn't like the smell of wild birds.
She is also very picky about spicy food.
She also has a lot of other kinds of spices.
Get a list for the kitchen,
and tell them to write it down.
Yes.
Are you blaming us for not taking good care of Princess Dingbei?
Be careful.
What?
This is not a blame.
This is clearly love for one's wife and one's heart.
Suxin.
Your Highness.
You're smiling.
It's all thanks to Your Highness taking good care of me for a whole night.
Your Highness's symptoms have healed so quickly.
Your Highness?
Last night, Your Highness...
Last night, Your Highness was resting in Qi'an Hall.
Your Highness took some high-pressure medicine and sent it to me.
Naturally, it was her who personally gave you the medicine.
I really don't know what to do.
Your Highness, which outfit are you going to wear when you go out today?
That's right.
I also made an appointment with Mimi today to go to the art gallery to draw.
What time is it?
It's already 4 p.m.
4 p.m.?
Why didn't you call me earlier?
It's because His Highness didn't allow me to call you.
He said he wanted you to sleep a little longer.
Your Highness, His Highness really cares about you.
He even asked you for a few things to help you with your work.
You talk too much.
Hurry up and tell me.
Yes.
What is this?
That's right.
Nowadays, people in the Shangjing District listen to songs.
The most popular song is Wen Tao Ge.
Which theater is this?
Which drama do you think of?
I've never seen this before.
I've watched it before.
I heard that those people...
Wifey.
Yes.
How is it possible?
...are preparing to save themselves.
I can't think of a better way.
I can only walk around and not look at people.
But there are quite a lot of people today.
Let me repeat.
When he was hurt,
your heartless and heartless heart
is not the real heartless heart.
You have to show the kindness of this character.
And his subtle change of mind.
And when you fight later, be careful of each other.
Work well together.
Get ready.
Everyone,
today's new drama
is the story of the old disaster
of Prince Man Ba's wife,
Princess Jiao.
The story of the love story
between Prince Xiao Xiong and his wife,
and the old disaster.
If you are interested,
please stay and listen.
Okay.
Good.
猎神的긴磅水
喀清祥
岳热水
河南坊
A Dan.
Why are you here?
You are so far away. How can you see clearly?
I am telling you, after today,
our paintings will be spread all over the world
and become the best.
Good!
I didn't make any mistake.
Wake up! Why are you all asleep?
Go back to work!
Er Bao!
Boss, you are here.
What's going on?
Normally, Wen Tao Ge is always in a state of restlessness.
Why is there no guest today?
You don't know, right?
The lady from Changgu Palace
suddenly opened her door
and wrote a very interesting script.
She has been singing in Nan Yu He Street for a day.
The guests are all new.
So they all went there to listen to the opera.
She?
What script can she have to compete with Wen Tao Ge?
I don't know.
How about you go and have a look?
You can also go to the opera house.
Er Bao, come on.
Take this fan and hit it yourself.
Xia Yu, take it.
Let them go home and rest.
You can get a few days' pay.
What about me?
You can go to the opera house.
Good!
If you like this opera,
as long as the sky is beautiful,
we will meet here tomorrow.
Good!
Tomorrow is a good day!
You are so ridiculous.
How many days can you hold on?
Lord Zhang.
Are you here to steal the poem?
I just happened to pass by.
If you like it,
come early tomorrow and take a good position.
I don't mind you coming to the so-called princesses' house.
Mimi, Tan.
The princess is here too.
Why are we so far today?
I'll take you to the restaurant.
Let's go.
But the money,
we have to use it to save the refugees.
I'm the owner, of course I have to use the money.
I can't lose my income from the painting.
Don't worry.
What about Lord Zhang?
He is a rich man.
He is a man.
Let's go.
We have a lot of money today.
I...
Tan,
we have so much money.
This is far beyond our expectations.
Come on, let's celebrate.
Come on.
With this money,
we can build a rescue team.
I'll write more in the next few days.
If I want to go back,
I have to make them happy.
I can't keep chasing them.
Although we have a hope,
we have to wait.
But if we want to build a rescue team,
I'm afraid we don't have enough money.
We can't afford to lose the refugees.
The most important thing in Shangjing is the poetry and painting.
How about we have a feast later?
We can donate together at the banquet.
These people are all very brave.
They have to donate for the sake of their reputation.
That's a good idea.
But it's not a long-term solution.
Hmm.
If the private store of our mansion
can make more money,
that would be great.
You're really not angry.
Your Highness, you have a good taste.
These jewelry
are all top-notch.
I can't take the lead
and increase the price.
You're too modest.
If we want to sell our jewelry,
we have to rely on your reputation.
Your Highness, that's a good idea.
In this way, the business of our mansion
will be very prosperous.
I'm sure.
Suoxin, go and pick some more suitable ones.
Yes.
No, it's not full enough.
It doesn't show the extraordinary temperament of the second son.
Your Highness.
The so-called poetry is good, and the difference is far.
What you're good at is the mountains and rivers.
But you can't be so careless in portrait painting.
You're a pretty girl.
Why don't you paint yourself?
If I can paint,
I don't need to spend the money to invite you.
I can paint myself.
I don't know what Miss Bai wants to do.
What does she want?
She thinks
it's a waste to report
the talent of the second son
without his permission.
But she invited the most unruly painter
in Shangjing.
Don't worry, the second son.
Others won't recognize you.
The most unruly?
Why should I
paint myself?
You're a good painter.
You should paint yourself.
What did you say?
Nothing.
This is good.
The fan and jade
are very similar to the second son's.
Put them together.
Give it to the second son.
Yes.
If such a painting
is popular in the capital,
nobody will be able to
make it.
Thank you, second son.
You're welcome.
Ah Xu?
I'm leaving.
I'll come back to see you.
Tan, don't worry.
I'll go to the painter
and help you.
Why are you back so early today?
I'm going to the painting studio.
Why are you back so early?
I came back earlier
because of military affairs.
I want to...
I'll let Su Xin invite you.
No.
From tomorrow,
you must go to the painting studio.
Yes.
And remember to put the same
painting as the second son.
And make sure it's limited.
Your Highness is so clever.
Your Highness.
The account book is ready.
Here it is.
Your Highness.
What's the matter, Your Highness?
Today, the Princess Consort
invited me.
You want me to help you?
Yes.
What do you want me to do?
The number of people in the capital is increasing.
The income of our paintings is not good.
So I want to improve
the sound of the painting studio and the painting studio.
And then I'll raise some profit
to save the people.
What does this have to do with Shu Er?
Shu Er
is the most favored son of the princess.
Every time he goes out,
he's always been watched.
If he wears the jewelry of the painting studio,
he can lead the children
to dress up.
And he can let the princesses
come and go to the painting studio.
I remember the jewelry of the painting studio
is very expensive.
The Princess Consort is so generous.
Of course not.
She just let Shu Er wear it for free.
Mr. Shu Er
is a famous painter.
If he wears our jewelry every day,
he can show off
and attract people.
Why is it Shu Er?
He's the one who has the daughter, Huaichun,
and the baby.
Or else, what other
suitable person would you like?
Princess Consort, this is the tea you just got.
Please try it.
Is it okay?
Not bad.
Su Xi,
I'm going to go to the bathroom.
I'll be back soon.
Okay.
Su Xi,
do you think
His Highness is a little strange today?
He's half talking,
but he's not answering.
Look at His Highness.
Is he jealous of
Mr. Shu Er?
No way.
He's jealous
of Princess Consort.
If he's jealous,
His Highness will eat it too?
If that's the case,
he's being petty.
Princess Consort, think about it.
Why did His Highness come back so early today?
He must want to give you a surprise.
Who knew that when he came in,
he saw you invite other men
and gave you so many precious jewelry
in front of him?
His Highness is not jealous.
He's just being petty.
He must be jealous
of you.
He's jealous of me too.
His Highness
is jealous of me too.
Should I
show him my love?
Of course.
Princess Consort has never
given you anything before.
Today, you gave so many
jewelry to other men.
I don't mind.
Did I really
not give anything to His Highness?
I'm always
self-righteous.
How could I forget everything
when I'm with His Highness?
But what should I give him?
What should he give me?
What should I give him?
Su Xian, do you remember
the black belt
that I was wearing when we were
being attacked by bandits?
I remember. Where is it?
It should be in the Zhaoshui Courtyard.
Go back to the Marquis's mansion and get it.
His Highness is not fond of making a mess.
He's used to it.
The belt is the most suitable for him.
Princess Consort gave you
something of her own.
Is this called a suitable gift?
You don't understand.
Go and get it.
Yes.
I want this one, too.
It's a gift for the one who gets the flower.
It's for the one who gets the flower.
I like it.
Next one.
Let's put it on the table.
Miss, here you are.
Su Xian, you're just in time.
Nan Chu and I are too busy to come.
You're really popular.
Come on.
We'll have more painters to come.
We have Mo Jie.
Didn't Miss Miao say that she's the best
at drawing pictures?
It looks like you're the second son.
If you can't tell who wants the flower,
the plan I made with Tan is in vain.
Stop standing there.
Give me your hand.
Here, I'll give you two.
Do you like it?
What's wrong? Why are you so upset?
It's not my daughter.
She's going to see her tomorrow.
But she's not concerned about her own business.
What she wears tomorrow,
what she wears, what she draws,
it's all a mess.
You're not worried about your daughter.
You're worried about your maid.
My princess consort is here tomorrow.
Don't worry.
The fragrance of the flower.
And...
A part of the dragon's brain.
Lv'er, go to the incense room
and get all the clothes for the prince.
There are many mosquitoes in the market.
Bury the clothes.
So he won't be bitten by mosquitoes.
Yes, my princess consort.
I didn't see the princess consort.
Miss Mimi wants to see everyone in the capital.
Everyone in the capital.
Everyone has a picture of the second prince.
I almost got a beating.
This thing
has to be done by her.
Her shot
will make our jewelry
red.
The fire of the night
shatters.
Because of the firmness
in each other's eyes,
the heart is forever.
With the girl, Huaichun,
and the fruit,
I am the second prince.
I think our Tan
is gentle, virtuous,
and educated.
He is talented and good-looking.
He is very compatible with the second prince.
With the bandit,
he is as good as his wife.
He is as good as his wife.
My lord,
this is the new clothes
that the princess consort
specially prepared for you.
I won't wear it.
Take it away.
You don't like this style?
The princess consort
specially made the same style.
Take it.
The shopkeeper said
that the princess consort
wears the same clothes.
The pattern, color, and style
are all ordered by the princess consort.
Look.
The purple cloud pattern on this dress
was just mentioned by me.
The princess consort remembered
that you like this pattern.
My lord,
you are just a man.
The whole mansion is used to it.
But you can't
treat the princess consort so coldly.
I have been a painter for a year.
I hope I can have a few
heavenly nail art shows soon.
The wrong military style
is not the right one.
I think it's the wrong one.
The rest of the jewelry
in the wrong style
is suitable for me?
Yes, definitely.
Make it more.
Okay, I'll do it.
Princess Consort,
the prince is here.
The prince goes to the dance hall at dawn.
It's not surprising
that he goes back home at this time.
But the prince...
The princess consort sent you
a new dress.
She wants you and me
to wear the same one.
I'm afraid
I can't.
the princess consort
will be sad.
I hope you can understand.
I'm afraid
that the princess consort
will be sad.
I hope you can understand.
Thank you.
You're used to
the formal dress.
Today the dress
looks like the one you wear.
What do you mean
by wearing the same dress
between the couple?
There's a saying
that if a man and a woman
play together,
I can't forget the glorious
soldiers who fought together.
Tan was not lucky enough to
work with my husband
and work with him.
So I can only wear the same clothes
as my husband
to make up for the pain.
This dress is good.
A good match for a married couple.
Let Jin Xiu Fang
prepare more clothes.
Yes.
As long as you like it,
it's enough.
But today is a little later.
You need to wear this dress
to sing the Spring Spring.
Take Tan back to the mansion.
What did you
sell in the queen's gourd?
Tan wanted to borrow this dress
to make up for Jin Xiu Fang's business.
To help the refugees to raise money.
Changchun Garden is a royal garden.
For those who go to travel,
it is a noble place.
If you and I wear the same clothes,
we can kill others.
It will make all the ladies laugh.
Thank you.
After I finish my business,
I will go to Changchun Garden to see you.
Wait a minute.
Your Highness,
you saved me twice with this book bag.
I thought
it was a witness to our fate.
So I made a match for you
and made this bag.
I gave it back to you.
The fragrance is very strong.
You can use it to cure your fever.
This gift is good.
It is said that the gift is good.
Tan gave you a gift.
So you should give back something.
I have a gift for you.
What is it?
You can have it.
Thank you.
I will keep it.
It's a bit of a coincidence.
Don't worry.
By the way,
tell the crown prince
that you will go to the Spring Garden today.
Why should I tell him?
He will listen to me.
Is it pretty?
Okay.
I will pick you up after I finish my work.
A man in a mask!
What?
How about I put on makeup for you?
Smile.
You're still friends with Mr. Shu?
Madam told me to keep an eye on you no matter what.
I'm not in the business. I'd better not do it.
Mimi, do you have someone in mind?
Of course not.
Then why are you running away?
It's just an opportunity to make friends.
If you meet someone, you'll be happy.
It's not worth it to be together.
As you said, Mr. Zhou is very important.
I don't have enough water in my stomach.
I don't have enough fish in my pond.
How can you be together?
Besides, my parents really look up to me.
They're not afraid of me being rude.
Then you have to go.
You have to make your uncle and aunt realize the situation.
Understand that it's not that you don't want to.
It's that those noble gentlemen are too high-minded and picky.
Only then can they stop wanting you to continue to look at each other.
Tan, you're very reasonable.
You're really...
All right.
When you look at each other, there are outsiders around.
I'll wait for you in the pavilion.
Let's go.
The jewelry store in the city is still good.
Let's go tomorrow.
Okay.
Su Xin, go ask around.
Did Lord Zhang come to Changchun Garden the other day?
If you see him, tell him to go to the west side of the well.
Why are you asking about Lord Zhang?
If he comes,
Uncle and Aunt don't have to worry about Mingming's wedding anymore.
What if he doesn't come?
If he doesn't come,
it's good to be friends with Mr. Zhou.
But I think Lord Zhang must have moved by the wind.
He came early to plan with Ziwei.
Yes.
Princess, are you all right?
Why do I feel a sudden pain in my stomach?
Aunt, let's not look at this for now.
Yes, Aunt.
Princess, you can't fool my wife with your tricks.
I...
Princess, the old lady of Empress Dowager
is worried about the Su family.
You should understand her.
The marriage between you and Young Master Gao
is also a good thing for Empress Dowager.
No matter how hard Gao Chen tries,
he will be defeated in the future.
By then, you will be the wife of the Marquis.
The whole Marquis's mansion will be yours.
I can't help it.
I really can't help it.
Then, I'll go instead.
Let's go.
Why is he here?
Aunt, I was not sensible before.
I didn't understand the hard work of the grandmother.
Your words just reminded me of something.
Since you are here, why not meet me?
It's good that you can figure it out.
Young Master Gao will be here soon.
I'll go with you to the room and wait for you.
The thing between men and women is to open up.
We should talk about our personal matters.
Only then can we understand each other.
If you are here,
Young Master Gao will definitely see you from the outside.
It's hard to show your true feelings.
You should wait outside.
I'll go with him.
Aunt, I'm here.
I can't just run away.
Besides, whether you want to see me or not,
grandmother will know.
Why should I lie to you?
You don't have to rush out.
You can talk to Young Master Gao.
Let's get to know each other better.
Okay, aunt. Don't worry.
You are so clumsy.
You are so talented.
Lanzhi, let's go.
Miss Bai.
Miss Bai, I'm late.
I was walking around the place
and saw a wine tree.
I saw it.
It's a very rare tree.
It's very rare.
It's a rare tree.
I was in the place of teaching.
I saw a wine tree.
I was so late.
Miss Bai, please forgive me.
What is a wine tree?
The fruit is here.
It's a rare tree.