I'm going to be a little bit of a
little bit of a
little bit
你儿郎
的是
蒙恨故里
妖蛮跋扈
那护儿郎
甘饮去
Linux计成
作作亲富
Yin Fu?
How dare you call me a girl?
I am a noble and noble man,
and I am a man of pure and pure blood.
And you are even imprisoned here.
You should report to the government.
I will wait for the government to investigate this matter.
I will wait for you to compensate me.
If you insist on taking the medicine for me,
it's not impossible.
I will go.
I have a banquet for you.
I will give you a letter of my love.
I will tell the whole family to teach you.
I hope you will understand my feelings.
I will do my best.
You are a noble and noble man.
You don't know how to love.
I will give you a letter of my love.
I will wait for you to understand my feelings.
Thank you for your birthday.
I am very happy.
Miss, Zhang Shizi is really considerate.
He is a fool.
He would not say anything directly.
Report!
The Crown Prince of the Prime Minister of the State of Ping is killed in Lingzhou!
What is going on?
The Crown Prince of the State of Ping is killed in Lingzhou!
What did he say?
Did he hear it wrong?
The Crown Prince of the State of Ping
is not Zhang Huaiyuan.
We don't know his identity.
Lu Dianshui, Zhang Huaiyuan...
Miss.
Miss, don't scare me, Miss!
Miss!
What should I do?
Don't scare me.
How could this happen?
How is this possible?
He's not the Emperor's son, who do you think you can harm him?
He's just going to Lingzhou to work. How could he...
His Majesty has ordered the investigation to be completed.
His Highness is also arriving in Lingzhou soon.
This matter will be settled.
Xiaoqi!
Miss Yun!
Your luggage is ready.
Stop!
Young Master, according to His Highness's order,
we must leave immediately and meet with Grandfather in Sha Xi.
The news of the death of Crown Prince Zhang has been reported to Shangjing.
With His Highness's plan, we must return to Lingzhou as soon as possible.
Prime Minister, a spy has reported that
Prince Dingbei and Ling Qingxian were on separate routes.
On what routes?
I don't know yet.
The spy reported that Prince Dingbei took Princess Consort to go alone.
The two of them went around a few places and then left Ding Shao behind.
Afterwards, they were sent to the south.
How is the arrangement in Lingzhou?
Miss Yun has already followed the orders of the Prime Minister.
Everything is well arranged.
This trip will concern the entire Su family.
I will use my full strength to help Er Rong.
Stop!
Stay in the carriage.
Don't come out.
Go!
Jin Yunwei, I will kill you!
I won't spare anyone who tries to save His Majesty.
Go!
Your Highness, I am Xiao Anqi!
Die!
My Lord!
My Lord, are you hurt?
I am fine.
Be careful, Your Highness!
Your Highness, go back to the carriage! It's dangerous!
Go!
Yunyi!
Your Highness!
Are you crazy?
Protect him.
Go!
We have been ambushed here.
We should be on guard.
Hold on!
Your Highness, I will train more.
Retreat!
Young Master!
Your Highness, you go first!
Yunyi!
Go!
Leave me alone!
My Lord, it's far.
It's very deep.
It will hurt a little.
We are on guard.
We are searching the way to Lingzhou.
If there is no clue, we will continue to investigate Lingzhou.
We must find Yunyi.
Yes.
Yunyi fell into the hands of Haiyou Sect.
Could it be...
No.
Yunyi will not be in danger again.
They are threatening my husband with Yunyi.
Ayu is missing outside Lingzhou.
The Su family is very close to him.
Why do they have to search everywhere?
It seems that Ayu has the Lingzhou Department of the Ministry of War
and the evidence of the tax on the tax.
Haiyou Sect took Yunyi away.
Or they want to find clues from him.
So they are looking for evidence.
But...
Yunyi fell into their hands.
They will suffer a lot.
Ah Xu!
The Su family even dares to kill you.
What else can they do?
Yunyi fell into their hands.
It must be a terrible death.
We must go to Lingzhou immediately.
We must find the Su family.
Calm down.
We must find the evidence first.
What's the use of me being calm?
I know he is suffering.
I know he is in danger.
But I can only do nothing for him.
I...
I hate to have no right to listen to you.
I hate to have no right to learn martial arts.
In the end,
I can't even protect the one I want to protect.
To protect my master and uncle,
what's the use of being a gold medalist?
In the end,
it's all a lie.
If you don't go,
I'll go myself.
If something happens to you,
what should your parents do?
What about Yunyi?
If something happens to her,
will anyone think for her?
If you delay for a moment,
she'll be in danger.
Jiang Qizhi,
there's no time to remember.
If you stop her,
the love of the Su family will be broken.
Yunyi and Beile,
both of us are very anxious.
It's just about Yunyi's safety.
We can't act on impulse.
Otherwise, it's very likely to harm Yunyi.
If we go to the Su family to save people,
we'll only alert them.
Because we can't prove that
Yunyi is in their hands.
They may also kill
and destroy the evidence.
I know that the second young master is very worried about saving people.
But the more dangerous it is,
the more we can't mess up the situation.
What my husband said just now,
is not to abandon Yunyi and be indifferent.
But to make sure that everything is fine.
Dongshen,
stay in Lingzhou tonight.
why
darling
possibly
You and Shun'er are close friends.
Why bother to be so gloomy over a few words?
Moreover, you are not from the capital.
We've been friends for years.
You still don't understand what I think.
You think that I am cold-blooded.
I'm the one who's cold-blooded.
I was wrong.
You're worried about the chaos.
You're not saying anything when you're in danger.
He wanted to save Yunyi as soon as possible.
If he's captured by Atan today,
you must be more anxious than him.
What are you waiting for?
Go!
Aren't you a very capable person?
It's not right to delay the task of saving people.
You shouldn't rush it.
It will take you more time to take the carriage.
Your Highness, you're not saying it right.
Don't worry, Young Master.
The King's Command
Do you have an answer for your wound?
Where's the anger you had just now?
I'm not sure.
There's one condition for a man to die in peace.
It's that I have to live in Lingzhou first.
You want to live?
I was in a hurry just now.
I didn't think carefully.
If I'm in trouble,
my parents can't take it.
I think the cold-blooded Qi Zhi can't take it.
So the fight between you men
is more dangerous than the fight between us women.
Your Highness, you're laughing at me.
I'm laughing at you.
You're so childish.
Your Highness,
I'm sorry.
The next one.
Here you are.
Get in.
What are you doing?
To be honest, I have no reason to.
Get in.
This is mine.
Let's go.
Thank you.
Go.
Next one.
Thank you.
Go.
Stop.
Lock it.
Hey,
is this your first time in Lingzhou?
There are rules in Lingzhou.
It's easy to follow.
What rules?
Are you pretending to be poor or stupid?
You have no money, right?
You can't get in.
Stop talking nonsense.
Why can't I get in?
Because you don't know the rules.
Who set the rules?
I did.
I'm the boss here.
Get in.
Go.
Don't move.
Go away.
Go.
Sir, you haven't paid yet.
Sir.
Stop him.
Don't move.
Sir, you haven't paid yet.
Go away.
You...
Go and ask around.
I've never paid in Lingzhou.
Who dares to argue with me?
Listen,
my sister
is going to serve the nine girls of the Su family.
I'm not going to serve them.
After she gets the money,
she'll be afraid that
she can't afford you.
My sister
is very popular
in front of the nine girls.
Don't you look down on her.
Get out of here.
You're so arrogant
for eating white food.
I want to eat white food.
Get out of here.
You're so arrogant.
How dare you argue with me?
Sir,
forget it.
It's better to take one thing than one thing.
I don't want to cause trouble.
The boss wants to keep his reputation,
but he can't keep the money.
It's not the way to solve
the problem.
You're so arrogant.
I'm so arrogant.
Enough. Let him go.
You're still waiting for me?
Boss,
do you have a toothpick?
I've already given
your two people the
money.
What do you mean?
You're in a hurry to get to the Su family.
I'm going to follow you.
Besides, the Su family will treat you well.
I'm under their eyes.
I know.
We're good people.
You want to investigate the case of the Su family?
How do you plan to do it?
There are many women in Lingzhou City who are injured.
So I plan to be a merchant.
I'll do whatever I can.
As for Princess Dingbei,
she's weak.
She can't stand the long journey.
When she was killed by the assassin,
she was frightened and went back to the capital.
What do you think?
She's been out for only a few days.
She's getting more and more tired.
You must save Yunyi.
I will.
Don't worry,
I'll stay in the best hotel in Lingzhou.
There are many people in Lingzhou.
It seems that everything is peaceful.
There are many people who are like the previous one.
I'm worried about your health.
I've thought about it.
I'll let Zhuyu follow you.
It's good.
I'll go.
You're a good man.
Princess Dingbei has never been to Lingzhou.
If you lose this status,
you'll be in danger.
I'll be careful.
Take care.
I'll wait for your good news.
What's wrong?
There's some tea in here.
I ordered local tea.
Yunxian House is one of the most famous tea houses in this place.
Why is it so crowded?
I'm sorry.
I'll go to the kitchen.
Where did you buy the tea?
What can I do for you?
I think it's good.
I want to bring back some.
We buy tea from Ding Sheng Tea House.
Ding Sheng is a cheap tea.
They sell good tea.
The tea you ordered is the best.
Ding Sheng Tea House?
Yes.
Thank you.
Enjoy.
Stop it.
Don't touch my tea.
I'll kill you.
I'll pay you back.
Let us go.
You're a bastard.
I'll kill you.
You're still alive.
You don't know who's boss?
I'll kill you.
It's him.
How dare he stay here?
I must let you know
who is the boss of Lingzhou City.
Guys, kill him.
Kill him.
Get out of the way.
The governor is here.
Mr. Zhao, help.
Help, Mr. Zhao.
How dare you make trouble in my house?
You want to die?
Those foreigners
are not even close to you.
You don't even know them.
You still want to be the boss?
Stop it.
It's him.
You make trouble here.
You're not related to the governor.
Governor,
he's my uncle.
Where's the manager of Yunxian House?
I'm here.
Yunxian House is in the middle of the road.
The manager is on the second floor.
I'm innocent.
You're here to make trouble.
You're not even close to him.
You make trouble here.
Yes.
You make trouble.
Arrest him.
You'll be sentenced to three months of jail.
Hurry up.
Wait.
The big trial law
will be passed by the author.
He didn't say a word just now.
How can he make trouble here?
In the big trial law,
you'll be attacked
and your wealth will be lost.
Although others can make it up to you,
But these people beat the shopkeeper to destroy the property
We did it on purpose
How could we be trusted
when we sent them off?
The store was taken by Baishi
The shopkeeper was attacked by someone
He is a bitter master
But you betrayed him and hid the money
You solved the case so easily
It's a mistake
I made a mistake
What are you talking about?
How did you make a mistake?
You taught me?
I am Shu Jingran
I work in the border of Hanlin
I am not sure if I can help you
with the law
You are the second son of Prime Minister Shu
I am sorry for my rudeness
Please take back the crime
and settle the case according to the law
Sure
I will take them back first
and make a decision after the trial
I will do it right away
It's my duty to interrogate
How can I let others do it?
I don't know who is the one who
was ordered to go to Lingzhou
Who is he?
Are you King Dingbei?
Your Highness
Take them all
and go to the Su family with me
Go
Why haven't they arrived yet?
They came from Yunxian House
It's only two hours
Madam, why don't you go to rest?
The servants are here
I will call you later
King Dingbei is going to marry you
How can I not go with him?
I think you want to
make a big mistake in the Su family
You don't know the importance of the family
You have been busy these years
I was not careful enough
Please don't worry
The Su family welcomes King Dingbei
I greet Your Highness
and Shu Hanlin
I am Yu Bozhong, the Prefect of Lingzhou
I greet Your Highness
and Shu Hanlin
I didn't make any connection with anyone
Miss Su
has a good reputation
It seems that the Su family
is really in Lingzhou
How dare the Su family
not welcome you personally?
I'm afraid that
I have broken the etiquette
and offended Your Highness
I have already asked for your permission
Miss, they are here
This is the servant
that Your Highness summoned
Please greet Your Highness
I greet Your Highness
Is this your brother?
Yes, Your Highness
Do you know that he
is making a big mistake
when he saw your name outside?
I don't know
Have you ever taken care of him
when you were in the Su family?
I have never done that
How did you do that?
You are just a maid
How dare you take the opportunity to steal the Su family's name?
You not only implicated the Su family
but also offended the Prince
Take it away and make it into a new one
and sell it to the Gou Lan Academy
Yes, Your Highness
Miss Su, you are taking the responsibility for me
Your Highness is joking
In the end
the Su family is the one who teaches the servants
I am thinking that I should punish them
and give them a good lesson
so that I can give an explanation to Your Highness
Miss Su, you are right
This is the family matter of the Su family
I have made a big mistake
by taking the initiative
But Lingzhou is not a strict school
It is necessary to punish them severely
It is not just the family matter of the Su family
Go after them
This is the guard of Lingzhou
When the Prince entered the city
he said that the city of Lingzhou had its own rules
If you have no money, you should not follow the rules
and do not allow the entry of the city
And he is the one who decides the rules of the city
Your Excellency
I am just laughing at him
This person only has the power to eat white food
and act recklessly
because of the Su family
This person
eats the food of the royal family
but he is not good enough to be a good citizen
and he is not good enough to be a good citizen
I have just entered the city of Lingzhou
I have already seen it
Is it possible that
this place is not a strict school
and the citizens only know the Su family
and do not know the strictness of the Su family
Your Highness, you are too serious
Your Highness, what happened today
Even if these two people are talking nonsense
the Su family is being bullied by the innocent
I hope Your Highness can be the one to punish these two people
so that they can prove the Su family's name
and solve the problems
The matter of Lingzhou
is up to Zhang's family
Right?
Zhang's family
According to the great law
these two people
should be punished by the law
20 times per day
The former person will be double compensated for the loss of the restaurant
The latter person will be suspended from work
and will be fined
and will be sent to the city of Yuji
to be a good friend
Approved
Your Highness is wise
Your Highness has been working hard all the way
and you have to personally investigate the case
It is really hard for you to investigate the case
I hope Your Highness can spend some time with Shu Hanlin
and have a rest
No need
I and Shu Hanlin are in the Su family
and we can discuss
the issue of tax evasion
Your Highness is willing to live in the house
The Su family is lucky
I will call someone to prepare dinner
Yes, yes
Your Highness
After the murder
the Oman Sea will not find the time
to bring Prince Dingbei to Lingzhou
I have heard
that they should be treated well
and be treated well
If they just pay the tax
they can deal with the tax evasion
It is okay to break some money
Tell them to hurry
Don't let them stay too long
to avoid long nights and dreams
Yes
The Su family is in the Su family
and we can discuss
the issue of tax evasion
The Oman Sea will not find the time
to bring Prince Dingbei to Lingzhou
I have been wearing this jade pendant since I was a child
No matter what you encounter in the future
you can use this jade pendant to go to the Duke of Pingguo
The house will help you with all your might
I am a noble and noble person
and I am innocent
and you are even imprisoned here
I am waiting for the government to investigate this matter
and you to compensate me
I hope you have this chance
I can feel your love
and I will choose a new one
the day after tomorrow
to show my gratitude
to your beauty
No need
My girl, you are a pure and pure girl
and you don't need to show your affection
You and I are both pure and pure
I understand
I know you like to read
and I can open the whole Wentao Pavilion
for you
Zhang Huaiyu, why do you think I don't match with Shuer?
If Shuer doesn't match with me
who else can match with me?
You...
Then I am more compatible with you
You are rude and rude
You don't know how to treat me
If I can't marry you, you marry me
I will marry you
Miss Bai, will you come to see me off tomorrow?
Please come to your hand
Don't scold me
I will make you a good wife
Is that so difficult?
I will love you forever
Leave this greedy business
It's more troublesome than Yinzi
You are always so impulsive
You don't have any sense of accomplishment
How will you keep your place in the Wentao Pavilion?
How can you keep people from making mistakes
and make mistakes?
I am afraid that I will follow you
to the end
Er Bao
Miss Bai
Tell them
to reopen the Wentao Pavilion in three days
There will be new pieces and new rehearsals
and the best Juerracheng noodles in Shangjing
What?
Your boss can leave
I can't
Since everything is under Yin Cheng's control
I have no other choice
He doesn't believe that I can keep the Wentao Pavilion
I have to fight for it
Not only keep it
I have to make it more important
Shangjing
Shangjing is more lively than the place of Jin Shang
Look
It's so beautiful
It's surrounded by five lakes and four seas
It's hard to get used to it
The way it's done
is like being in a flowered mirror
with the light of the five suns
It makes people can't see
Take a look
Put it on
Madam, it's not appropriate
What madam?
What's wrong with it?
You are the guardian of the mountain
How can you be so cold-hearted?
Relax
Don't be so cold-hearted
Madam
Thank you
Madam, what's your plan?
I am Miss He now
I don't have any plan
There are many treasures in Linzhou
Shangjing doesn't have many things
Since I am here
I have to make a lot of money
Put this set of dishes away
and put on my Chinese porcelain
Yes
These flowers are not suitable for the wedding
Let the bride dress up again
Yes
Miss He is not trying to entertain the King of Dingbei
She even used your favorite Chinese porcelain
I just don't know if this Prince Hangwu is in trouble
It doesn't matter if he is in trouble
The key is whether he understands the situation
I have also told him
As long as we can coax him
the tax in Linzhou will be fine
But he is not as easy to deal with as the Crown Prince Zhang
The King of Dingbei is cold-hearted
I heard that he even dares to take away His Majesty's dignity
I don't know how to show him off
There must be a weakness in the world
Men are nothing but money and women
But now I don't know the happiness of this Prince
I still have to work hard
You should be careful
You can't make any mistakes tonight
Yes
The Su family in Lingzhou is indeed famous
I don't need to tell you
But a guest room should be more exquisite than my Qi'an Hall
I just hope you can live comfortably
I can live comfortably if you don't think too much
I am stupid
I don't know what you mean
Why did the Crown Prince Zhang die?
The Su family in Lingzhou is indeed famous
I don't know what you mean
Why did the Crown Prince Zhang die?