Get down! Get down!
Kneel down!
Please spare me.
Please spare my life!
Your Majesty.
Tell me your name.
Fan Zi Xu from Hanlin Library.
Cheng Fan from Hanlin Library.
Xu Qing from Hanlin Library.
You're doing evil in the library.
His Majesty has ordered
to deprive all your aristocrats
and demote you to civilians.
Your Majesty! Your Majesty!
demoted to civilians,
how can we live? Your Majesty.
That's right.
Take off your clothes.
we are nothing.
Please spare my life.
So you know that too.
Your Majesty,
As long as they don't demote us to civilians, we'll be fine.
Please spare us, Your Majesty.
We're willing to do anything.
Okay.
Kowtow to His Majesty.
until he's satisfied.
How can he be satisfied?
His Majesty is talking.
Even if he's satisfied,
Your Majesty, you're not a good person. You're a good man. You're a good man. You're a good man. You're a good man.
"Read a poem at the age of three." "Read a poem at the age of three."
and composed poems at five.
When I was nine, I read sutras and philosophies.
At the age of 18, I mastered the art of literature in Chongning.
Everyone said I was a scholar.
So what?
He's still buried among the ministers.
I can't assist His Majesty.
Only by becoming the chief painter of Hanlin Library
can I really stay by your side.
I want my father and brother to see
what they can't do.
I can do it.
Unexpectedly,
I was finally summoned by His Majesty
to help that ant return me a plum blossom.
It's my first time to see His Majesty.
It's like this again.
How can I be content?
All the officials thought His Majesty was devoted to calligraphy
and neglected the court.
Only I understand you.
You ascended the throne at 18.
The ambition of a young man
and ambitious.
Change the state name to Chongning.
What is Chongning?
It means to worship Wang An Shi Xi Ning reform
This is the true ambition of Kun Peng
Let us fly birds pursue each other.
Whether it's painting or politics,
whether you need a pen or a knife,
it should be me.
But now,
I lost to a commoner born out of nowhere.
Young Master.
Your Majesty.
I was just one step away.
Your Majesty,
to withdraw his decree.
Fan Zi Xu.
You only care about yourself.
You can only see
what you never had.
but you can't see what you're born with.
It's not that you're not talented.
but your desire.
blocked your wrist swinging.
how can you draw true love?
I'll use this
for you today.
Today, I'll use this scarecrow
to awaken your fear.
He kowtowed here all night.
The old scholar sacrificed his life to protect his pride.
I want you to live.
and experience the shame of being crushed.
karma will come.
Ah Ji,
What do you think of my painting?
Why are you here?
Didn't you ask me to stay with you
You taught me how to draw?
What?
You broke your promise?
Yes.
Your Majesty.
It's fine.
Pass my order.
Before the architectural assessment,
before the architecture assessment.
Yes, Your Majesty.
By the way,
Arrange an imperial edict.
Tell him
the exact location of the secret room.
Your secret room?
Only you can do that.
You don't understand.
what the empire is.
What is a bosom friend?
What is friends?
In life,
if you haven't tried these,
I would have lived in vain.
Your Majesty.
Do you trust Ximeng that much?
Your villa is a forbidden place.
What a coincidence that he barged in.
and wants to see His Majesty every day.
Ximeng, Zhou Lijie,
The old scholar, Feng, Xiang.
Chancellor Cai, Xu Zhe.
Soldier, Xue Hongyu.
Master Silver Needle, Song Jinwei.
The owner of the snack stall, Wen Xian Yu.
Mysterious man, Star Wang.
Circus troupe, Zhou Feilong.
Circus, Du Ruixiang.
Zuo Hanyu, a football man.
(Roh Han Yu)
Fan Zi Xu's attendant, Kong Jinyun.
Commander of the soldiers, Dou Zhi.
to perform.
Wang Yin, Lü Ying Ping, Li Zine, Zhu Shuaidong. Zheng Qingyue, Sun Tao, Zhu Qing, Ma Yunfeng. Qin Long.
Buwei, Yicim Elva. Angel Abbas. Acucucuculi River Abbas.
Wang Zhe, Jang Haibo, Sang Chunbo, Seok Hyo-sung, Yoo Yun-taek.
Staff table.
Liu Xiaofeng.
Producer Hu Yudong
Meng Yijie.
The manager of the venue, Kong Shilong.
Affairs, Qu Dong Xu, Guo Weiwei.
Lü Yishu.
Director team.
Executive Director Zhang Xiaofei
Planner Chen Yonglu
The audition team.
Audition: Bai Yu Qian.
Actor assistant director Ping Xiaomeng
Photographer group.
Photographer Du Yachun Zhang
Art Director Zhong Weixi.
Lighting Team.
Lighter Wang Xiuhua Wang Zuyu
Costume team.
Makeup instructor, Wei Zhiwei.
The main focus is Chen Chao.
Li Yunge.
The team leader of dressing, Kan Lily.
The main focus is Wang Xiu Juan.
Cheng Tingting.
The post-production team.
DIT Choi Qian.
Visual effect production.
Mentor of color tone, Li Sining.
The recording team.
The dubbing team.
Recorder Jia Yaotian.
PR team.
PR Director, Hot Pot, XIN Li.
PR execution, Little Monster, Sia Tang.
Driver, Xu ChangBrigade, Wang Jiaxin.
Zhao Bao Tong, the prop team leader.
Action guidance Wang Bingbin
Product.
Zhijiang Film Group Co., Ltd.