The topic is
A vast land
is green.
can make the water flow and mountains move.
The color is no longer the color itself.
Fan Zi Xu, what are you doing?
Why didn't I write such a good work?
Why did it have to be you?
You didn't lose.
I didn't lose. I didn't lose.
Fan Zi Xu.
Why did you tear up your painting?
The scenery in the world isn't just green.
Your drawing skills are originally excellent.
If you have a tolerant heart,
and see the world,
and landscape
might be different.
Brother Ah Ji.
Hello. Hello.
You're here.
I couldn't find you since we parted last time.
Are you hurt?
I'm fine.
I heard that
a talented man broke out in this exam
and won the first place.
Really?
Then we should celebrate.
Do you remember what day it is today?
You idiot.
Don't you remember your own birthday?
Today,
I'm going to
for you.
and be crowned.
But isn't Song going to reach the age of 20?
I just turned 18.
It's a lucky day.
Add your head
Abandon your childish childhood.
and behave yourself.
and live a long life.
Wish you
a great fortune.
The auspicious moon, Ling Chen, will wear it again for you.
Behave your dignity.
and your morality.
Long live!
and live a long life.
and live a good life.
By the order of the moon,
I'll give you three plus.
We are brothers.
to achieve their virtue.
The elderly is infinite.
Let's go. Let's go.
to celebrate.
In the future,
you'll learn drawing with His Majesty.
I hope
you can enter the library
and realize your dream of becoming the chief painter.
Remember.
I will always support you.
Ah Ji.
I promise you.
When I become the chief painter,
and meet the emperor,
When I finish what I should do,
I will come back to you.
Ximeng, Zhou Lijie.
The old scholar, Feng, Xiang.
Chancellor Cai, Xu Zhe.
Soldier, Xue Hongyu.
Master Silver Needle, Song Jinwei.
The owner of the snack stall, Wen Xian Yu.
Mysterious man, Star Wang.
Circus, Zhou Feilong.
Circus, Du Ruixiang.
Zuo Hanyu, a football man.
(Roh Han Yu)
Fan Zi Xu's attendant, Kong Jinyun.
The painter of Hanlin Library, Liu Shiyang.
Commander of the soldiers, Dou Zhi.
to perform.
Wang Yin, Lü Ying Ping, Li Zine, Zhu Shuaidong. Zheng Qingyue, Sun Tao, Zhu Qing, Ma Yunfeng. Qin Long.
Buwei Ayi Zem Elva. Angel Abbas. Acucucuculi River Abbas.
Wang Zhe, Deng Song of Hanqiao Mountain,
(He's a man of the same age.) (He's a gentleman.)
Staff Form.
Come on. Come on.
Liu Xiaofeng.
Outer Producer Hu Yudong
Life producer, Meng Yijie.
Director of the venue, Kong Shilong.
Lü Yishu.
Director team.
Executive Director Zhang Xiaofei
Planner Chen Yonglu
The audition team.
Audition: Bai Yu Qian.
Actor assistant director Ping Xiaomeng
Photography team.
Art Director Zhong Weixi.
Lighting Team.
Lighter, Wang Xiuhua, Wang Zuyu.
Costume team.
Makeup instructor, Wei Zhiwei.
The main focus is Chen Chao.
Li Yunge.
The team leader of dressing, Kan Lily.
The main focus is Wang Xiu Juan.
Cheng Tingting.
The post-production team.
Choi Qian.
Visual effect production.
Mentor of color tone, Li Sining.
The recording team.
The dubbing team.
Recorder Jia Yaotian.
PR Director, Hotpot, XIN Li.
PR execution, Little Monster, Sia Tang.
Driver, Xu ChangBrigade, Wang Jiaxin.
Zhao Bao Tong, the prop team leader.
Action guidance Wang Bingbin
Product.
Zhijiang Film Group Co., Ltd.