[English subtitles are available]
[To Ship Someone]
[Episode 8]
This Cantonese breakfast restaurant is really good.
Do you often come here?
Are you still with Shan Hang?
Yes.
What's wrong?
Nothing. I'm just asking.
Have more.
Mr. Ji?
Are you camping here too?
Me too.
What a coincidence.
Do you mind if I set my tent up next to yours?
You don't mind, do you?
You got it wrong.
I got it wrong?
What's wrong?
Here.
Song Yanqi.
I don't think you're camping here.
You are actually stalking me, aren't you?
Lu Qiyu told you my schedule, right?
How is that possible?
It's really a coincidence.
Camping is popular now.
I'm following the trend,
not you.
Isn't it easy?
It's not that difficult.
Ji Shu.
Ji Shu, what's going on?
Pass me the hammer.
Why are you looking at me?
Watch how I do it.
My heart was racing just now.
Song Yanqi, calm down.
Beauty will mislead you.
Don't get yourself into trouble
before you get him.
Thank you, Mr. Ji.
Ji Shu.
Why are you with her?
It's a coincidence.
Lin Qingmiao, why are you here too?
Ji Shu.
Long time no see.
A coincidence?
I think she has an ulterior motive.
So what?
So do you!
Have a seat.
Mr. Ji,
since I had tea at your house last time,
I suddenly realized the beauty of drinking tea.
Teach me how to make tea.
Use mine.
Wait a minute.
Okay.
Song Yanqi.
We haven't seen Ji Shu for a long time.
We want to catch up.
I'm afraid it's inconvenient for you to be here.
Mr. Ji.
Am I interrupting you?
No.
Ji Shu.
After so many years,
your temper hasn't changed at all.
It's impossible to change.
This is a scene where an ex and current boyfriend meet.
I called you earlier,
but you changed your number?
I did, long ago.
But why did you call me?
I encountered something before
and would like to ask for your help.
But it's all solved now.
Why don't you exchange your contact information now?
After all, you've known each other for so many years since you were classmates.
Exchange your phone numbers in case you may need it.
Sure.
It's quite hot today.
I brought ice cream.
I'll go get it.
Ji Shu.
You haven't introduced who this is.
Girlfriend?
A friend.
It's rare.
After so many years,
you finally have a new friend.
You're much better now?
Mr. Ji.
It seems that
you're not that close with this friend.
No one asks about others' illness
right away.
Aren't you obviously
healthy?
Qi, I only brought three.
Sorry.
Ji Shu, here.
No, thanks.  Give it to her.
Since Mr. Ji insisted on giving it to me,
I have to accept it.
If you don't want to,
I won't force you though.
Here you are.
Since you want to give it to me,
I'll take it.
Don't eat too much cold food.
It's bad for your health.
Thank you for your concern.
So ugly.
You look like a kitten eating secretly.
You're ugly.
Stop it.
It's embarrassing
in front of others.
What are you doing?
Now you have really become a kitten.
Let me take you to wash up over there, okay?
Okay.
Let's go.
Are you angry?
Do you want some?
I'm not eating. You can have it all.
Is it good?
Wait.
You got it on your lips.
What are you doing?
Come on.
They didn't need to do that.
Why were they showing off their love?
Why bother?
It's almost written on her face
that she has lived a better life
after breaking up with you.
Mr. Ji.
As the saying goes,
there are other fish in the sea.
Why waste the whole forest
for a crooked neck tree?
No wonder he wrote a supporting character like that.
He is like writing about himself.
People who are named Ji Shu are so miserable.
You think too much.
You are just reluctant to admit it.
Alright, I thought too much.
Mr. Ji.
I brought barbecue tools and ingredients.
Do you want barbecue?
-Oh you want it? Then I'll grill some for you.
-No.
Here, Mr. Ji.
I just grilled it. Try it.
Thank you. I don't eat barbecue.
Well...
The barbecue contains heterocyclic amine and benzopyrene.
There are cancer-causing risks.
Ji Shu never eats these.
We can't talk about the amount of toxicity aside from the dosage.
It's okay to eat it once in a while.
Ji Shu doesn't eat that.
What's wrong with eating it occasionally?
Song Yanqi.
A person's lifestyle
won't change.
So what if he tries?
Don't make yourself feel so wronged.
You need to learn to fight fire with fire
to stimulate her inner jealousy,
and let her know that she cares about you
so she'll be regretful.
You...
How is it? Is it good?
Not bad.
Not bad, right?
I'll grill some more for you.
I want a drink.
The iced one.
It's bad for your health.
I just want it.
Okay.
Wait a moment.
Ji Shu,
I want to talk to you alone.
His ex-girlfriend is so powerful.
Don't give her the copyright.
Mr. Ji,
the newly grilled ones are for you.
I'm not interested.
Take them away.
But you just said it was delicious.
Don't follow me.
Do you want barbecue?
What's wrong?
Song Yanqi.
Are you following me?
I didn't follow you on purpose.
I was worried
about your condition.
I'm fine.
Mr. Ji, I'm in a bad mood.
I may not be able to
get the copyright anyway.
Why don't we find something to do and relax?
What are you going to do?
Come with me.
Mr. Ji, get on and try this.
♫I want to be around you like stars♫
♫Blinking and telling you secrets♫
♫Approaching a wonderful scenario♫
♫The starry sky is the place where wishes belong♫
♫Although we're ordinary♫
♫We won't be replaced♫
This is fun.
Get on and have a try.
♫In this relationship♫
Get on.
Enjoy it yourself.
♫I am touched by your tenderness♫
Try it, please.
♫You made me forget to leave♫
♫If it's not your choice♫
Get on.
Come on.
Hold tight.
♫Loving you, can I accompany you to the place where you belong?♫
♫Spending every dusk and season with you♫
♫Before I run run run, running♫
♫I love you♫
I told you it was fun.
You didn't believe me.
Sorry.
I... I didn't stand properly.
It's OK.
You smiled?
Get up.
Look at this.
Does it look like me?
This is for you.
You'll feel better when you see pretty things.
Let me add some magic.
Just say what you want to say.
The stars tonight are beautiful.
So what?
It doesn't matter whether they are beautiful or not.
They're all things that can't be touched.
Not really.
Although we can't touch them,
the brilliance and beauty of them
are worthy of our admiration.
Well, Mr. Ji,
don't mind what happened during the day.
It was an accident.
They don't deserve it.
I didn't take it seriously.
That's good.
It sounds like I cared about it.
Mr. Ji,
can I ask you a question?
Why do you have so many questions?
Go ahead.
I've been wanting to ask this question for a long time.
Why do you always write tragedies?
Is there a special reason?
Tragedy is reality.
I just ended the novels with reality.
But you can't tar everybody with the same brush.
In my opinion,
if a couple really like each other,
they should trust each other.
No matter what conflicts and misunderstandings there are,
all can be solved.
There are many things in life that have nothing to do with misunderstandings
or right and wrong.
Even if the previous misunderstanding was solved,
there are still obstacles of reality and interests.
The two may not be equal in their relationship,
or even family status.
Even if these are all solved,
sometimes, the answer that suits them
are not in it.
I don't believe it.
Life is like making choices.
There are indeed many misleading choices.
We just need to eliminate the wrong options
one by one.
It's natural for people to make the wrong choices
or take the wrong paths.
Mr. Ji,
if you judge
people's life one-sidedly,
that would be a tragedy.
But some people
don't have any choice since birth.
Their lives are not choice questions,
but arrows.
They do their best
just to make a living.
It's already hard to survive for them.
Like,
love
and happiness
are
far away from them.
You have nothing to say, right?
When are you going to update your novel?
Soon.
I'll finish the novel in advance.
If you still want the copyright after that,
we can talk on it later.
Really?
Yes.
Thank you, Mr. Ji.
So,
do you still want to end it with a sad ending?
What's the secret between Yu Le and Xining?
You are so obsessed with the story
just because of your company?
♫There is like a star in the dark♫
Is there any other reason?
I'm your loyal reader.
♫You should always remember near or far♫
I can feel the power from your writing.
I also hope I can yearn for life
♫You've got family to share your load♫
and love,
instead of just accepting my fate.
Is that the only reason?
♫Just remember to take your way♫
Of course not.
♫Don't forget your own type♫
You don't know how bothering it is to wait for your update.
I'm really burning with anxiety.
♫That is just how you live♫
We all want to know the follow-up development.
Since I have the chance now,
of course I want to inquire.
♫Our life is not just rain and tears♫
You really want to know?
♫So you can take it all♫
Wait for it.
♫I could be your sea of sand you know♫
♫And I will keep you safe and strong tonight♫
How long?
One day?
♫I see there's a rainbow in the sky♫
A week?
♫I see the life I never had♫
Good night, Mr. Ji.
♫Before I run run run Running♫
Good morning, Mr. Ji.
Morning.
You're up so early.
How is it?
What is it? Let me see.
Let me take a look.
You stayed with Ji Shu all night.
Did he agree to sign the contract with you?
Qingmiao.
Did you install a CCTV on me?
How did you know
Mr. Ji agreed to talk about his copyright with me?
No way.
Why not?
How is it?
Tell us about the progress.
Good news.
Ji Shu agreed to talk to me about copyright after the completion.
So he agreed?
Not exactly.
But the success rate is at least 50%.
I thought he had agreed.
It's much better than before.
He refused to see me before!
It's 50 percent.
Fine. You're awesome, okay?
But why only 50%?
Because I have the other 50%.
He must be flattering the boss again.
But Qi,
I have faith in you.
Me too.
You have good taste.
Look!
Mr. Ji reported back
and suddenly updated three chapters!
Let me see.
What did the netizens say?
The netizens are very dissatisfied with the plot,
and decided to give up reading it.
What? What's going on?
That's not the point.
When I came in,
when I came in.
I overheard something.
Mr. Jia might have seen the dissatisfaction of the netizens.
They're talking about
Lin Qingmiao's project.
He also asked her to speed up the contact with the platform.
Lin Qingmiao also suggested
to combine two groups
and reduce unnecessary personnel.
If we carry out her original project,
the person who leaves will be...
I'll go find Mr. Jia now.
Come in.
Let's talk about it another day.
Mr. Jia, I have something to tell you.
By the way,
I was about to call you.
Stop the copyright negotiation with Mr. Ji.
But Mr. Jia,
Mr. Ji agreed to talk about the copyright
after the novel is completed.
But I don't like the current story and plots.
Did you read it?
I just got the news.
I didn't have time to read it.
But Mr. Jia, trust me.
I can persuade him to change the story.
Mr. Jia, that's impossible.
I know him well.
He is stubborn.
He won't change his mind easily.
Just as you said,
he won't change his mind easily,
instead of refusing to change at all.
As long as we find the cause
and persuade him in the proper way...
And Mr. Jia, I've found the best way,
so I don't want to give up easily.
I believe it will become a hit.
Please trust me one more time.
Okay, I'll give you a few more days.
If it doesn't work,
just give up.
Thank you, Mr. Jia.
Go back to work.
[Brighter Than Stars—Love in the Life of a Best Actor]
[Chapter 46]
How could this happen?
This has crossed the line.
[Youth always loses to reality. Love always loses to profit.]
Why isn't the bus here yet?
Since the world of fan fiction
has affected Ji Shu's novel several times...
He refused to listen to me no matter what.
How about...
[Bifengge.com]
[Chapter 48]
No, I'll protect the couple of Xi-Le I ship.
Where are you going?
Can't we talk tomorrow?
It'll be too late tomorrow.
The vicious supporting actor must have done it on purpose.
He deliberately created conflicts for Yu Le and Xining.
And now he's stopping me from informing them.
What a tactic!
Mr. Ji, you're right.
It's late. I should go back early.
Sir.
I'm not those stupid supporting roles.
They have to imform them in person.
My phone is not a decoration.
Qi,
I dropped my phone.
Hurry up.
Mr. Ji, you're a president.
You should have enough money for another phone, right?
But I suddenly remembered
I have an important call to make.
Or I'll lose a lot of money.
Really?
Do I have to lie to you?
Yes, you do.
Give me your phone.
I'll give it back after I call.
Are you going to throw my phone into the drain
when you make the phone call?
Of course I won't!
What?
Go ahead.
As for the first requirement as an assistant of me,
you should respect my privacy.
When I'm on the phone,
you are required to keep a proper distance.
OK. A proper distance.
Appropriate distance.
Turn around.
I won't listen to you.
You're so annoying.
Are you done?
Qi!
It slipped down by itself.
My phone.
Mr. Ji, you did it on purpose!
You...
It slipped down by itself.
How do you know I did it on purpose?
I saw it with both eyes!
Do you have nothing else to do?
You...
My phone.
How can I open it?
Qi.
What are you doing?
Since it has fallen,
let's destroy it
in case someone
will steal the information on your phone.
You...
I...
Don't worry.
I'll buy you a new one tomorrow.
You're welcome.
Let's go.
Tomorrow?
The fight is over tomorrow.
Everything will be too late.
How can I inform them?
Qi.
Get in.
Mr. Ji,
what's done is done.
Let's go back.
Let's go.
Mr. Ji, good night.
Good night.
Miss,
can I borrow your phone?
I left my phone at home.
I want to call my boyfriend
and ask him to pick me up.
Okay.
Thank you.
Hello.
The number you have dialed cannot be connected for the moment. Please...
The subscriber you dialed cannot be connected for the moment.
Xining, this is Qi.
Inform Yu Le now
to sign the contract of the Track as soon as possible.
Ji Shu asked Zhen Yingjun to pretend to agree to your request.
But he then asked him to talk to the film crew.
They let Wang Ziheng take the role of Yu Le
and be your partner.
Inform Yu Le and his company immediately.
Thank you.
I couldn't get through so I texted him.
Okay.
Here's the change.
Thank you.
Okay.
It's okay.
Let's cooperate later.
Okay, bye.
Yan.
Have you signed the contract of the Track?
Can you tell the producer
to give me the full script?
I want to prepare in advance.
What's wrong, Yan?
The male lead has been decided.
What?
But didn't you say that we just need to sign the contract?
There are always variables before signing the contract.
Now here comes a variable.
The film crew decided the leading role overnight.
The contract has been signed.
So,
who's the leading role now?
Wang Ziheng
and Ye Xining.
What?
Wang Ziheng and...
Ye Xining?
But she told me she had rejected.
How did this happen?
You should ask Ye Xining this question.
I heard Sheng'an Entertainment
contacted them proactively.
They said the film crew could also get one actor free.
Ye Xining's pay is much lower than before.
They even proposed
that Wang Ziheng can sing the theme song for free.
They will sing the OST  together
and cooperate with all the publicity.
How could this happen?
Don't you understand?
Sheng'an Entertainment snatched your role.
Yu Le.
Why are you so silly?
You were happy to work with her.
In front of you, she told you that she would refuse
and wouldn't take advantage of your popularity.
But later she conspired with her company
to snatch your role.
No.
Xining is not that kind of person.
What kind of person is she?
The truth is right in front of us.
It's impossible.
Even though Sheng'an Entertainment snatched my role,
she wouldn't know about it.
It better be.
This is the compensation for you.
Thank you, Mr. Ji.
Why don't you open it?
Later.
Xining, your phone.
Thank you.
I just want to know
whether you know what happened
to the contract of the Track?
I...
You knew it, didn't you?
Xining.
If you're worried that if we play the roles together,
it will affect each other,
you can just tell me.
You don't have to do these things.
I'm sorry.
Do I look funny
in your eyes?
I don't think so.
You didn't?
I came here
to let you explain like a fool.
I don't even know
what you said is true.
Yu Le, I...
Things are already like this.
It's useless to say anything.
Mr. Zhen,
why did you give Xining a new phone?
What's wrong with her phone?
She lost her phone yesterday.
What?
Oh no. It's over.
What is over?
Their love is over.
What are you talking about? It's weird.
Damn author.
I am irreconcilable with you!
Let's calm our relationship down.
Yu Le,
it's not what you thought.
Then what is it?
I don't want to quarrel with you.
Go back and rest.
Xining.
Yu Le.
There shouldn't be any problems this time.
The ending is predestined.
There's no need to be so stubborn.
Ji Shu,
why are you so heartless?
You bastard!
Why did you use this method to break the couple I ship?
Let go of me first.
It's all because of you!
If you hadn't helped Wang Ziheng snatch the role,
they wouldn't have quarreled.
Can you be reasonable?
Their quarrel
was their own problem.
The couple I've been shipping has a bad ending.
I can't get the IP of this novel.
I lost my job because of you.
Both of the Ji Shu are so bad.
I told you
that all relationships
will end unhappily.
You were too obsessed.
That's why you got hurt in the end.
I worked so hard to live.
Why are you doing this to me?
Why did you
name the character Ji Shu?
You bullied me in this world too.
Are you really crying?
You, you broke them up.
Now...
You even maliciously speculated on me.
Stop crying.
They are breaking up.
My life turns to be boring now.
Does their breaking up
affect you this much?
Yes.
If they break up,
I think all the good things will be gone.
I can't eat well.
I can't dress well.
I can't sleep tight.
My heart is broken.
I think life is meaningless.
I will eventually go to darkness
and destruction.
Let go of me first.
No.
If they really break up,
I might as well end my life.
Fine.
What can I do to stop you from crying?
Really?
Yes.
From now on,
I want you to stop destroying
Yu Le and Xining's realationship.
OK.
I promise you.
But do you think
there will be no problem between them
if others don't intervene?
At least there are no external obstacles.
The problems between them
were never created by others.
It's their own problem.
I don't care.
Fine.
I promise you.
Mr. Ji,
you are the best person in the world.
Who just said
all Ji Shu in the world
are bad guys.
That's because...
I...
Why are you pulling my hair?
Don't move.
Don't move now.
What happened?
What are you doing?
I'm not that easy.
If you don't want me to take off my shirt,
you must cut your hair.
You choose.
Take it off then.
Step aside.
Mr. Zhen.
I have something to report.
♫Just remember to take your way♫
♫Don't forget your own type♫
♫That's just how you live♫
Mr. Ji.
I didn't mean it.
I'm sorry.
♫Our life is not just rain and tears♫
Go on.
What's the matter?
It almost slipped my mind.
Xining is missing.
She's missing?
How come?
How can you be sure that she was missing?
I can't find her anywhere.
Did you call her?
I just got her new SIM card.
Oh my.
It's OK that people can't be contacted
for no signal or running out of battery.
It's the first time I see a person can't be connected for this reason.
She's a grown-up.
Why can't  you find her?
Mr. Ji,
I just received a notice.
Her notice tomorrow is put forward.
Besides,
Xining is already on the cusp.
I don't want her name to show up on the hot search for acting like a diva.
Don't worry.
Have you searched the places Xining likes to go?
I did.
I also went to her house.
Where else can she go?
Mr. Ji.
Are you really not worried?
You know something, don't you?
Why should I worry?
Instead of just guessing here,
you'd better go to the places she often goes.
Did you find Yu Le?
I don't want to see Fang Yan.
Look at the situation now.
Why are you still spatting with Fang Yan?
I'll go to his studio.
I'll go with you.
You can't.
Why not?
You have to work.
Mr. Ji,
which is more important now,
working or finding Xining?
It's none of your concern.
You just promised me.
Let's go.
Mr. Zhen.
Go and find Yu Le first.
I'll look for her somewhere else.
Let's split up.
Okay.
-Be careful.
-Good luck.
Hello.
I'm Xi Ning's agent.
Is Xining here?
No.
Can I talk to Yu Le?
Wait a moment.
Yu Le is practicing dancing.
He doesn't like to be disturbed while practicing.
I have something urgent.
How about this?
Tell him
Xining is missing.
Xining is at Qin Hai High School.
Come quickly.