1,01.
1,02.
Sir, your class is finally over.
Thank you, sir.
What is it?
Sir.
Can I learn to make incense
like them?
Sure.
But you have to pass the test first.
OK.
Sir, please answer the question.
Yurong's loneliness and tears are dry
A pear blossom brings rain
Try to understand the meaning of this poem.
and meaning.
to make a fragrance.
Yurong's loneliness and tears are dry
A pear blossom brings rain in spring
Sir.
Why are you here?
What are you doing?
I...
Perfect.
Sir.
Smell it.
How is it?
Smell it again.
Are you crying?
Sir.
You really shed tears.
Does that mean I passed the test?
Yurong's loneliness and tears are dry
A pear flower brings rain
You're not happy
Aren't you happy?
Sir.
Did I pass?
Right?
I passed the test.
Maybe
this is fate.
The Lunar Bind can reveal any secrets
and kill in the illusion.
and weaken one's power.
There are countless people
want to get the Lunar Beam.
Whether it's inside or outside,
many people
have broken the gate of our Jiang family.
Some people who can't wait
started to act.
Within half a year,
the toxin
will spread widely.
Who did this?
Fold the willow.
The one who killed me
will eventually appear.
And you
the best assassin in Licha Pavilion.
No matter who placed the order,
in the building,
will definitely send you to do it.
By then,
don't worry about our relationship.
Kill me.
kill me yourself.
But...
I'm the only one
is me
except me.
If people know our love,
I'm afraid
you will be killed too.
By then,
who should take care of Chan?
Only when I die,
can Chan be safe.
Chan has been clever since childhood.
Although she didn’t use the Lunar League well,
she was very prepared.
If I die,
I have three things to tell you.
First,
take Chan to Floral Fairy Valley
and get the owner to erase her memory.
I don’t want her to live in pain.
Second,
you want to take Chan into Licha Pavilion.
Licha Pavilion has strict rules.
No place is safer
Nothing is safer than there.
Third,
take good care of Chan for me.
Remember
what I said.
Okay.
Jiuniang.
I know.
It's time to act.
Half a year ago,
she suddenly recalled her past
and delayed her schedule.
I'm afraid
who is the buyer behind the scenes.
Fortunately, Jiuniang understands me.
Although the leader
lost her memory for Chan,
But if she remembers it again,
Don't worry.
I will find out the truth
before she remembers.
The journey is still dangerous.
I want to see him again.
We finally meet again.
This time,
no matter what we say,
we can't be apart for so long.