Dear X Who Doesn't Love Me
♫  Where the light goes between  ♫
Whoa! It's so pretty! The winter sea!
Eonni, look there!
It's so pretty.
It's really pretty.
Let's take pictures together and eat something delicious too.
Okay.
Great. It was my wish to have a double date.
Double date, what the...
Why am I here?
Jeong Si Ho! Let's talk.
Let's talk later. I'm a little bit busy now.
Are you really going to keep avoiding me?
Why? What is it?
Hyeong. Hello.
You're Si Ho, right?
I've heard a lot about you from Hui Su.
Hui Su, did you ask him?
Ah, well...
I was about to ask him. But it seems Si Ho won't be able to go.
He says he's busy.
Really?
What a shame.
I heard you've been best friends since high school.
I wanted to be close with you too.
Se Jin's parents run a pension.
There are no customers in winter. They told us to come and have fun.
I guess we'll have to go by ourselves this time.
I'll make sure you won't be bored.
Since you're busy it can't be helped.
Let's go.
Hey, wait!
I should've just ignored them...
Are you taking a picture? Take mine too.
Okay.
I'm done taking them. That's enough.
Yes.
But what's going on?
You said you weren't coming, but you even ended up bringing a camera.
I'm glad you're here.
A present.
Thanks.
It's cold.
It would have been better if we had come here in summer.
I like the winter sea.
When there's a summer sea, there are lots of happy people, so
I feel a little jealous.
At the winter beach, the are many people who look lonely, so
I feel comforted.
Nuna. I'm kind of upset.
Does that mean you're not happy now?
It's not like that.
Let's go to the sea in summer next year.
Next year?
By that time... it'll be 200 days, right?
Yeah. You're right.
How long will you be able to love me?
So nice! The scent of sea.
Right, Si Ho?
Promise me this is the last time.
What?
The notebook.
Promise me you'll never use it again. It's not for you.
It's because I'm really worried. Please.
- Si Ho—
You dating random people and being hurt by those random people...
I don't want to see that.
We're best friends.
You can listen to this request from a close friend, right?
Alright. Don't worry.
I'll make sure this is the last time.
Wait a second.
What?
Done.
When did you grow up so much, Jeong Si Ho?
What are you saying when you are short?
I'm not short! I'm average height.
Ta-da!
What are you guys doing?
What do you think it is? When you come to a beach!
You got to light fireworks!
♫  Slowly it's seeping through me, like the feelings   ♫
♫  Hold still. Don't let it show, they'll never know  ♫
♫  Is this a dream of a dream?  ♫
♫  I'll let it come.  I'll let it out.  ♫
♫  One at a time  ♫
♫  The light is rushing in my veins like never before  ♫
♫  I see it clear. I feel it real. It's working   ♫
♫  The words are flowing out. I can't make it stop  ♫
What were you talking about with Hyeong Si Ho before?
Oh, we didn't say anything special.
So are those two going to start dating?
Who?
What do you mean by who? Of course, I'm talking about Se Jin and Si Ho.
I don't know. I didn't hear anything about it.
Did you hear something about it?
I'm sure that Se Jin likes him.
I thought he wouldn't come, actually.
Honestly, I wanted to be just two of us.
What?
Did you not feel that way?
Hold on.
I'm sorry. But we are outside, and our friends are all around here.
No, it's okay.
I think I was rushing too much.
Aren't you hungry?
Shall we go eat now?
Yes, let's do that.
It's coming!
Welcome to my place!
It looks delicious!
Let's do a toast!
Cheers!
Thank you, Se Jin!
Thank you for the food!
- There's no time...
- to eat food!
Aren't you drinking too much?
Oppa, are you not good at drinking? You should've told me first!
Si Ho's not good with drinking. You better drink that in multiple sips, kiddo.
What? Were you not good at drinking?
That's not true!
I'm good at drinking!
I'm a total heavy drinker.
Hyeong, don't overdrink.
Mind your own business.
Cheers!
If you don't play, you lose! Rock, paper, scissors!
What is this?
Bottoms up!
Really?
I mean, what is this?
Nuna, I'm going to the bathroom.
Okay, be careful.
I can't hold it anymore either.
You are on a different level.
You are such a great drinker.
That's not true. I'm a bit tipsy as well.
Eonni, do you like Jun Yeong?
What?
Of course.
Why aren't you dating Oppa Si Ho?
Hey, what are you talking about it out of the blue?
I bet you get this question often.
I was also just wondering.
You are dating all the other guys except Oppa Si Ho, so I wondered if you had a reason.
Hey, Si Ho and I are just friends.
It's beyond friends. It's more like comrades.
Comrades?
Then, he's more than a friend to you.
I just mean that we aren't in a romantic relationship.
But he's a very important person to me.
Also, he's a very good person that you can't even compare to me.
He's someone you are not dating but an important person to you.
Yes.
Then...
It's okay for me to date Oppa Si Ho, right?
Hey, why are you asking me about that?
I wanted to make sure.
What's the point for you to ask me? You have to talk about it with Si Ho.
I will.
I'm going to confess my feelings to him this time.
What?
It's okay with you, isn't it?
Of course, it's fine.
Thank you, Eonni.
It's late. Let's go inside as well.
Oh, that's right.
We had so much fun. Thank you for having us!
Come again next time.
Mom and Dad!
My daughter.
I'll come again soon to see you.
That oppa is the guy I have feelings for.
Restroom
Where do you think you are going?
So what, you bastard?
Look at this s**t!
S**t. Do you have your f**king eyes behind you?
You f**king bastard!
F**k!
Do you like it, you son of a b**ch?!
F**k.
You f**king piece of s**t.
But why is Oppa Si Ho taking so long?
That's true. Didn't he leave almost 30 minutes ago?
Right.
I said, let's go together!
There are so many kids. Do you think they came for a school trip this winter?
Guys, I'll go to the restroom real quick.
Where did he go?
Jeong Si Ho?
Jeong Si Ho.
It's okay.
It's safe here.
Seo Hui Su?
I'm Se Jin.
Are you okay, Oppa Si Ho?
I'm sorry. I'm fine.
It's a temporary thing.
Let's go. I'm okay.
You surprised me!
Are you sure you are okay?
Yes.
Thank you. Thanks to you, I've calmed down a bit.
- Let's go.
- I like you.
Now I know it clearly.
When I thought you were going to faint, my heart dropped.
Let's go. Others will be waiting for us.
Is it because of Hui Su?
What?
You are just watching her and not even telling her how you feel.
Like an idiot.
I don't expect much. Just give me a chance.
Let me go into the ring, at least.
I'll throw the punch.
Se Jin, I—
No more, no less, let's just date for one month.
How does that sound?
Nuna.
Nuna, what's going on?
Nuna, why don't you come to my place later?
I really want to be alone with you.
I'm sorry.
Why is Park Se Jin not coming now?
The reason why I can't confess my feelings to you.
It's because unrequited love can last forever.
♫   Before I knew it   ♫
♫   you became more than a friend   ♫
♫   My feelings which grew silently   ♫
♫  won't diminish. Oh   ♫
Si Ho.
It's okay.
♫   Even if I approach   ♫
Calm down, Si Ho.
Let's breathe in and out slowly.
♫  just one step closer  ♫
It's okay.
♫   as if you're moving farther away   ♫
It's safe here.
♫  So always just in the same place   ♫
♫  I'm hovering around  ♫
♫   The words I've swallowed and swallowed as much as I could  ♫
But can unrequited love really last forever?
♫  While I look at you smiling today too  ♫
Can it be?
♫  I suppress my feelings  ♫
♫   Countless times to you   ♫
♫  I've made confessions you couldn't hear  ♫
Dear X Who Doesn't Love Me
I like the winter ocean. It's because I feel a bit jealous of the summer ocean since it has so many happy people.
At the winter beach there are many lonely-looking people, so it comforts me.
How much can you love me more?
I can't watch you dating anybody
and getting hurt by  someone.
We are best friends. You can listen to this request from a best friend, right?
I don't expect much. Just give me a chance.
Let me go into the ring, at least. I'll throw the punch.
The reason why I can't confess my feelings to you. It's because unrequited love can last forever.
♫   The person who receives your love  Oh  ♫