If you go this way, the swimming pool will appear.
Thank you.
Joon Hyeong!
Bok Joo!
Joon Hyeong...
Do you recognize me?
It's me. It's Mom.
Are you really my Joon Hyeong?
My goodness.
I really wondered
how you grew up.
You grew up better than I thought.
Do you think Joon Hyeong met his mom yet?
I guess so. She said she'd go to the school today.
Honey, you don't think she'll mention the postcards, right?
She begged us so earnestly.
Is Joon Hyeong's mom a fool? Why would she mention that? It'll just hurt Joon Hyeong's heart.
I wonder whether she'll even recognize his face.
I asked her because I didn't know where anything was,
but how can that student turn out to be your friend?
Are you guys really close?
Yes.
What about food? If you're hungry, we can go out and—
No, I... I'm not hungry.
Is swimming hard?
Can you handle it?
Yes, I guess.
I brought this to give it to you.
I didn't know what you needed.
Since you exercise, I thought maybe you needed some athletic shoes.
I'm not sure if the size would fit. I bought it with a rough guess.
Thank you.
I'll wear them well.
As I bought these, I thought of you a lot.
I wonder how tall you grew, how your face changed.
I'm sorry, Joon Hyeong.
I should've come to see you earlier.
I was so busy living.
Okay.
Yes, Mom?
Episode 15
That's How You Become an Adult
I prepared this so suddenly. I'm not sure if it will fit your taste.
It's delicious. You have always been a great cook.
No, she's not. Her food has become saltier each day she gets older.
Father, you should consider a storm to come afterward.
The croaker is really good today.
You really picked a good one!
Thank you.
Mom, can I have some water?
Yeah.
I...
You can give it to him.
Okay, Sister-in-law.
Here, Joon Hyeong.
Are you okay?
Yes. Thank you.
I can get a taxi by myself.
Get in, quickly. It's cold.
Okay.
Joon Hyeong. Do you want to come over to where I'm staying tomorrow?
Before I leave, I want to feed you a meal that I make with my hands.
If you don't have any time—
I'll go after my training.
Can I have your phone number?
Okay.
See you tomorrow, Son.
Go safely.
You came?
Seeing your expression, you seem happy. Did the meeting with your mom go well?
Is it something that would go well or not?
No. Your expression looks better than before.
Is it obvious?
Yes. It's totally obvious.
What did you do today with your mom?
I just went home and had dinner with Mom. And I went to the main street with her and got a taxi for her.
That's it?
Also, I'm going to meet her tomorrow at her place.
And?
I held her hand like this, and her hand was really warm.
I'm about to get jealous but I'm holding it this time because she's your mom.
It seems like your mom missed you a lot, too.
She came all the way from Canada to see you.
Of course.
How can she not miss her super handsome son?
You got some strength on your shoulders since you've seen your mom!
I'd be losing if I was jealous, but I wish I also had a mother who came to visit me in school.
♬  I dream of it  ♬
Hey! Instead, you have a trustworthy dad and a fun uncle.
♬  Please let us be eternally happy  ♬
Also, you have the most precious and important me.
♬  I dream of it.  Please let the days we smile be more   ♬
You're right. I have you.
♬  than the days drenched in tears  ♬
Spring Residence No. 1803?
I'm going out right now, so it'll probably take about 30 minutes.
Okay. Come safely.
Oh, Joon Hyeong. If you have any photo albums, can you bring them?
I want to see some pictures of when you were younger.
I'll stop by home and bring them.
Okay. See you soon.
Oh, they're small.
I'll just make my feet fit in them, then.
I put  $10, 000 in your account, Mom.
Alright. If you add what you have to mine, it makes about $20, 000.
Thank you. You probably also have a lot of things that you need to pay out for.
No. It's not money that I'll be using right away anyway.
But did she say that the child is in really bad condition?
If she gets the money and goes back to Canada, then is it possible for that child to get surgery right away?
I'm not sure, since her first priority is to get the money for the surgery.
How did the poor child who she bore in her late years get such a rare disease...
It seems like she came here because she was depending on her older brother's help,
but land isn't something that can be sold right away.
Would she have asked us for money if it wasn't that bad?
What money?
J-Joon Hyeong.
When did you come here, you rascal? You didn't even give us any notice.
What do you mean, money?
What are you talking about?
Joon Hyeong, sit down. Sit down and...
Did Mom come because of money? Was it because she needed money?
Is that why she suddenly...
But then, why is she asking you and Uncle for it?
She should be so grateful that you're the ones who raised me and fed me up until now.
How could she? How could she be so shameless as to ask you and Uncle something like that?
Joon Hyeong, that's not it. It's because she has some personal circumstances.
No, it doesn't matter if she has personal circumstances! This isn't right.
She's way too brazen.
How could a person who never got in touch with us for ten years
do something like that? How?
I knew everything.
The postcards that I got every year and the presents...
You're the one who sent them, Aunt.
You should have just told me the truth. How long do I have to pretend not to know?
When do I have to stop putting on this act?
I felt so ashamed because I saw how much you were enduring and how much effort you were putting into it.
So why would you give her that money? Why? What? Do you think I'm pitiful? If that's not it,
then do you think that since you've already paid so much raising me until now,  you're making a donation one more time?
Is it because you want to pretend to be a good person until the end? Is that what it is?
That's right! I did it because I wanted to go to heaven.
That's why I raised you with that kind of heart. Are you satisfied?
You rude little boy! How could you say something so mean?
I... Oh, you mean child!
Joon Hyeong!
Hey, Kim Bok Joo! You're not practicing hard.
Why do you still keep wrapping with bandages? Are you a mummy?
- No, I'll get started right away.
- You little rascal.
You're slacking off just because you did well at one competition.
If you're going to be like that, then just quit, you rascal! Go to Taereung (Korean national training center)!
Taereung wants you to come to them, you rascal.
Go to Taereung now, you little rascal!
KWF (Korea Weightlifting Federation) came to an agreement and made the decision today.
You rascal, you have to be admitted by this weekend!
What?
Daily Sports will come for an interview tomorrow.
They'll come to find out the secret of how we did well in the last competition.
Thank you so much! Thank you, thank you. Thank you!
Oh, this rascal! I...
What is this?
- Kim Bok Joo, fighting!
- Fighting!
You've got a delivery.
Yes, leave it there.
Three radishes, three Welsh onions, and one Wakegi onion, right?
Boss Kim didn't come in today.
Oh, that man went to get a vasectomy. He said that it'll be the death of him when he has a fourth child
because the couple's relationship is beyond good.
I'm asking because I'm thirsty. Can you get me a bottle of soft drink?
Yes.
♬  I'm saying I like you.  ♬
♬  I'm saying I love you.  ♬
I enjoyed the drink.
Thank you.
Get a hold of yourself. I guess you haven't gone through enough yet, you weird thing!
Wow, you were accepted into Taereung. Wow, Our Bok Joo is so amazing.
I guess your dream is finally coming true.
What did your father say? He's really happy, isn't he?
He is really happy. My dad's dream was actually to become a national team weightlifter.
He's probably thinking that it was worth it to support you by selling chicken.
You're being really good to your father right now. Where would your father find a daughter as good to him as you are?
I don't know. It still doesn't really feel real.
I keep asking myself if I really became a national team member and if I'm really going to Taereung.
It doesn't feel real to us either that we'll have to be apart from each other.
We're one thing. But what are you going to do about Jeong Joon Hyeong?
It hasn't even been that long since you guys started going out, but you're already separating.
I know, right? It's something to congratulate you for, but it would probably kind of sucky for Jeong Joon Hyeong.
The person you called is not available. Please leave a message after the beep.
Why? You can't get in touch with Joon Hyeong?
Ah... no...
No. He usually doesn't turn his phone off.
That's what the swamp of dating is like. You get worried if you can't get in touch with the other person,
and if their voice changes even the slightest bit when they pick up, then you wonder if their feelings for you changed.
Ah, I don't think I'll be able to date. It makes me way too worried.
Do it while you can. This is a good time for us.
He's not answering. His phone is cut off.
We were wrong.
We should have told Joon Hyeong everything much earlier.
That little child accepting the presents we got while pretending not to know...
How hurt must he have been?
You did it because you were trying to be good to him. Don't torture yourself too much over it.
Joon Hyeong will be okay, right?
Of course, he will. Do you think he is a child?
Hello?
Sister-in-Law, it's me.
Yeah, yeah. Okay.
I was wondering if something had happened to Joon Hyeong.
He agreed to come here, but he's not coming. His phone is turned off, too.
My face is kind of swollen, isn't it? Then, it won't look good in the picture.
Hey, Bok Joo is keeping calm even though she's the one having an interview. Why are you making a fuss?
We're going to be in a group picture. I'm doing this for the revival of our Weightlifting department.
Look at this. Figure skating is Kim Yuna. Rhythmic gymnastics is Son Yeon Jae.
We need a representative for weightlifting too.
Then what about you? What is this?
- Bok Joo! Hey!
- Oh, Comrade Tae Gwon!
- I was wondering if I should call you anyway. You were with Jeong Joon Hyeong last night, weren't you?
What?
What are you—
Jeong Joon Hyung didn't come back to the dorms yesterday?
I thought that he was out with you since his phone was cut off.
Where did that guy go? Something feels off.
When did you last talk on the phone with Joon Hyeong, Bok Joo?
Yesterday afternoon.
Then has Jeong Joon Hyeong been missing since yesterday?
What in the world happened?
Then after he left like that...
We can't make calls to him, either.
I thought he would have at least gone to school.
It must have been a huge shock.
The mother he met after ten years came here because of money, not because of him.
Ah, but why would he go to hide because of that? Such an immature guy.
He's a really soft-hearted guy.
He's like that because he matured too quickly and it became a habit for him to pretend to be strong.
I know.
Mom couldn't even sleep a wink last night
because that was the first time she hit Joon Hyeong.
I'll continue to look for him, so if he calls you please call me immediately.
I'll ask you this favor.
Goodness, you're all working hard.
Hey, why are you so self-conscious about it? Didn't you hear the Professor's words?
There's nothing special just because the media is coming.
Do what you always do, what you always do—
- They're here! They're here!
Ah, I washed my sweats but they didn't finish drying so...
You rascal!
You should go in.
- I mean, that suit...
- Goodness.
- That's hilarious.
- What is he doing?
- What's wrong with him?
- I don't know.
- How ridiculous.
- Professor!
- Bok Joo!
- Let's just do what we've always done.
Hey, are you not allowed to tell me what's going on?
By any chance, did Jeong Joon Hyeong's family go bankrupt?
Hey, hey, Jeong Joon Hyeong's family runs a pharmacy. There's no reason a pharmacy would go bankrupt.
I don't know what's going on but don't worry too much, Bok Joo. I'm sure nothing's wrong.
Yeah, he could just be drinking alcohol somewhere. Maybe overlooking the Han River on the bridge—
The person you are trying to reach has their phone turned off. Please leave a message after the beep.
Joon Hyeong, I heard. I know that you're having a really hard time right now,
but I'm so worried, so please call me just once. No, forget the call, just send me one message.
Okay? Okay, Jeong Joon Hyeong?
Woon Gi, straighten your back. More, more, that's good.
Hey, Nan Hee! One side is shaking! Like this!
Like this!
Ye Bin, Ye Bin, your shoulders might pop loose.
Your shoulders might pop lose.
Okay.
Hey, Ha Chaeng, stand straight!
- Ye Bin.
- Mom, mom, I'm on TV!
Athlete Kim Bok Joo. First, congratulations on your advancement to the nationals.
I heard that after winning the competition, you had a slump. May I ask how you overcame that?
Oh... I just rested and thought about many things.
I also received help from the people around me.
More specifically, who helped you?
There's my family, the professor, the Coach, my best friends Lee Soon Ok and Jeong Nan Hee,
and...
Kim Bok Joo.
Haneul Sports University's Weightlifting Department's Ace!
You won't make a mistake. You worked hard and your mental state is stronger than anyone's.
♬   I'm hesitating for so long   ♬
♬   ahead of the time that will come   ♬
Reporter, I'm sorry but I have to end the interview here.
Something really urgent happened. I'm sorry, I'm really sorry.
♬   while going back and forth   ♬
Bok Joo!
- Bok Joo!
- What's wrong with her?
♬  countless times  ♬
Kim Bok Joo!
♬   between faint hope and worry   ♬
♬   Time continues to go faster   ♬
♬   and one day, we find   ♬
Jeong Joon Hyeong! Where are you, seriously? Do you know how worried everyone is because of you?!
I'm worried too!
♬   ourselves at the end of the world   ♬
Call me immediately when you receive this message. I'm really about to get angry. Call me!
♬  I dream of it   ♬
♬   Please let us be eternally happy   ♬
♬   I dream of it. Please let us have youthful days   ♬
Where did he go, seriously?
♬   Even if there is   ♬
That bastard Jeong Joon Hyeong, seriously...
♬   a chilly wind   ♬
Where are you?
♬  stinging us   ♬
♬   I dream of it   ♬
The person you are trying to reach is not available at the moment. ♬   Please let the days we smile    ♬
Please leave a message after the beep.
♬   be more than the days  ♬
Hey, seriously, where are you?! You're not even picking up your phone!
Hey, I didn't know that you were someone so selfish who only thought about yourself.
♬   drenched in tears  ♬
Let's break up! If you're going to be like this, let's break up! Jerk...
♬  drenched in tears  ♬
Did he get into an accident somewhere? Where is he?
Here.
Um...
If you take these two out, how much is it? I didn't bring my wallet.
I'll pay for what he's short on, this included.
Bok Chicken, right? Let's call it even for the soft drink with this.
You drink so well. I guess you're a soju-lover.
Yes, beer is so bland. I guess you're a snack-lover. You're not even a kid but you're really cute.
Well, I don't think I'm at an age to hear I'm cute.
But you're really cute. Your face is
my style too.
Is Bok Chicken yours? Are you the boss?
Well, it's not mine, it's my older brother's.
I'm an actor, although I've only taken supporting roles.
Goodness, really? Which shows have you been on?
Well, that, r-recently, I played a crew member in the movie "Train to Bucheon" and
Sawing Man #3 on the "Insiders."
Ah... sawing? Now that I think about it, your face is familiar.
Oh, you were the sawing man! You were so frightening!
I mean, I'm not even included in the list of good actors but you even remember me.
I'm sorry but can't you show me your sawing scene? It just left such a huge impression on me.
Ah, how can I act here? Now, cut here and here.
Awesome! Awesome! It's exactly the same!
Of course, it's the same, I'm the same person. Now, one-shot.
You're a celebrity.
Let's go to my house and just drink one more shot, Sawing Man.
Um, w-we can't do that yet. It's too soon to go to your house.
I won't touch a hair on you and we'll just drink, okay? Okay?
Wait, my ear! Wait, my ear!
Let's go!
Oppa, charge!
Yes, Doctor. I still haven't heard from him.
I've been to every place he could have gone but he's not there.
Yes, I'll call you if I find him.
Yes.
Hey, Jeong Joon Hyeong!
What are you doing here? Aren't you going to come out quickly?!
Hey, you jerk! Are you dead?!
If you're dead, at least tell me you're dead, you bastard!
I said, come out here quickly...
You're seriously dead when I get there.
Do you know how worried I was?
I even went the Han River because I thought you might have jumped in.
Why did you turn off your phone?
You bastard, you have to be hit to regain your senses, don't you?!
What are you doing, Jeong Joon Hyeong?!
Jeong Joon Hyeong.
Are you okay?
Bok Joo,
they said that my mom didn't come to see me.
They said that she came because of money.
She came to borrow money.
I got ahead of myself.
Just as I endured even when I wanted to see my Mom to death,
I thought that she would have done the same.
I just got excited by myself.
I'm so embarrassed.
I'm em-embarrassed of myself
and I'm embarrassed to my aunt and uncle.
I'm even sadder now than I was
when she abandoned me back then, Bok Joo.
Fatty: missed calls 18
Connecting to the voice mail.
Hey, exactly where are you?! You're not even picking up your phone!
Hey, I didn't know that you were such a selfish person who only thought about yourself, seriously.
Let's break up! If you're going to be like this, then let's break up! You jerk...
This smells like old rags and it's too big. Don't you have something smaller?
Hey, that's the smallest one I have.
Just think of it as hip-hop fashion and wear it.
Hey, your hair is still wet.
-There. You're so pretty, my baby.
- Hey.
Why am I your baby? Did you give birth to me?
Yeah, I'm your real mother, you immature rascal.
Do you know how worried I was?
You were really bad this time.
I know. I listened to your voicemails.
Are you really going to break up with me? Are you now going to cut me off?
That was a warning.
If you disappear without a trace again, I'm not going to show you any mercy.
You really like me a lot, don't you?
Even at a time like this! Even at a time like this, you can say something like that?
That hurts.
You need to be hit more. This is your aunt's This is your uncle's.
This is your mom's. This is the doctor's, and this is mine!
Hey, your hands are really strong. It hurts.
Let's leave quickly. I'm uneasy thinking that we could get caught by the night watchman at any time.
No, I can't leave.
What now?
I don't have shoes.
What?
I threw my shoes away.
Hey, you child! How could you throw away your perfectly good shoes?!
You walked around school barefoot?! You lunatic, seriously!
No, I was just so pissed off earlier.
This won't work. Going to the dorms like this is impossible.
No, it's fine. I can just walk there. I walked here before just fine.
Forget it. You're doing all sorts of things in the middle of winter to get frostbite.
Over there. There. Sit down on that bench over there.
Hey, where are you going?!
Here. I went to the Weightlifting Department's locker room and stole my senior's shoes, so you have to give them back tomorrow.
Thank you.
Aigoo. I'm even stealing shoes now, seriously.
You're cold, aren't you?
Yeah, right. You're quite considerate of me.
At least you have a mom to call "Mom."
There's even me, who doesn't even have a mom to call "Mom."
Anyway, the ones with are always worse than the ones without.
I'm sorry.
Forget it. I don't think I'm the one you should be feeling more sorry to.
You may feel upset hearing this
but to be honest, I can kind of understand your mother.
They say that each and every finger hurts if you bite them.
You're a finger in pain but she has a finger in more pain.
You should handle the finger in more pain first.
But that doesn't mean that you're not in pain.
Putting your mother aside, imagine how upset your aunt was.
You should go quickly and assure her first. I heard that she couldn't sleep a wink last night.
How did you know that?
You met my older brother, didn't you?
What else could I do?
You left the dorms without permission and you weren't picking up your phone, so the only way I could hear about you was from the doctor.
I'm about to get irritated again, you rascal.
Go home quickly. Go and assure your aunt.
Alright.
- I'll go tomorrow.
- What do you mean, tomorrow?! Go right now.
You're embarrassed that you rebelled and even went to hide, aren't you?
It'll be even more embarrassing tomorrow. Go quickly.
Let's leave after just one more minute.
I said I got it, so why did you follow me all the way here?
It's because I'm uneasy! I'm worried that you'll say you're going home but then run away again.
How embarrassing. My girlfriend just took me home.
Stop joking around. If someone can take you home, anyone can take you home. Is there a rule that says only men can take women home?
Yes, Noona.
It's cold. Go inside quickly. Make sure to beg and say you're sorry.
Promise that you won't ever do it again, and take this to act charming. Understand?
I feel like she'll be really disappointed in me right now.
There's no disappointment between a mother and son. You two just have to hug tightly and it'll be over.
Go quickly! Go, go, go!
Thanks.
Ah, it's really cold.
Shouldn't there be an electric heater in the pharmacy, too?
- What about Dad?
- Dad went home first.
What is that?
Oh, this? Roasted chestnuts.
They're selling these out front. You like these.
Why did you buy them just before bedtime?
You're acting like that because you're worried your hands will get smeared with black dirt again, aren't you?
Seriously, you've got a slight case of princess disease, Mom.
It can't be helped. Your son will just have to peel them personally and feed them to you then.
Ah, why? You have to eat this before it cools. Otherwise, it won't taste good.
Your hands are cold. I'll make you a glass of citrus tea.
Mom, I'm sorry.
I committed a sin worthy of death. I won't do it again.
That's why you should raise your children a little strictly.
Because you doted on me so much when you raised me, I got all spoiled.
What did you say? You bad rascal. I'm really speechless.
Mom. I'm really sorry.
You probably don't realize how thankful I am
and how much I love
you, Dad, and Hyung.
Our family is really
much  more precious to me
than you think, Mom.
It's Mom's smell.
Aigoo, I was so tied up in knots because of you that I didn't even wash my hair.
Aigoo, it's no wonder!
- Does it smell really bad?
- Yeah, it really does.
- Come here.
- Huh?
Aiyoo!
Aigoo, you grew up well.
Mom!
Joon Hyeong!
There was more traffic than I thought there would be.
I was worried that I'd leave without being able to see you.
Thank you so much for coming.
- Um, Joon Hyeong—
- Thank you for giving birth to me, Mom.
I came because I wanted to say that.
Also...
This.
I'm going to give this back to you since it's yours.
I think that I'll be okay without it now.
Do you, by any chance, have a picture of my younger sister? I want to see her.
Her name is Amelia.
She's pretty because she looks like you.
She's going to get better soon. Please bring her the next time you come.
She's going to love you because you're handsome.
You saw her at school before, didn't you?
She's my girlfriend.
Oh, so she was?
She's really pretty.
- Did you send your mom off well?
- Yeah.
You did well. You're pretty. You listened well.
Of course. Whose am I?
Go Joo Hwan Internal Medicine
You're still the same. So clumsy.
Won't your desk collapse like this?
Why are you here? When did you come?
If I say that I stopped by to see you on the way to some other business nearby
you won't believe me, will you?
I came to see you. I closed the clinic early, too.
What the heck? Why are you doing things that you never used to do?
I asked the nurse outside, and she told me that you only see patients in the mornings on Saturdays.
I'm your last patient, then.
Let's go out and eat. I'm hungry.
You came all the way here just to eat?
Yeah. I realized that I don't have any friends to eat with since you're not there.
Let's go eat.
- He's so handsome!
- He's really handsome.
- Awesome.
- He's so handsome.
- That girl behind him must be his girlfriend.
- I don't know, I don't know.
Oh, I'm so jealous.
I've never seen a man that handsome in my life!
Hey, hey! What are you doing?
Hey, cover up most of your face like this from now on. Okay?
Hey, I don't have the kind of looks that can be covered up just because I cover them.
Jeez, being handsome is really a handicap. Hey, have you ever thought about cutting off all your hair?
Well, I'll do it if you tell me to.
How can I separate from you with nervousness that you'll get swept away by some other woman?
Joon Hyeong, actually, I couldn't tell you beforehand because I was afraid you'd be disturbed.
I've become a national team athlete, Joon Hyeong. I'll go to Taereung next week.
Hey, don't lie.
I have a World Weightlifting Championship in China in February.
What the heck? Are you serious?
Seriously? Hey, seriously?
Aweso— Hey, hey! Congratulations, seriously! How could you become a national athlete from lifting those heavy barbells?
I'm more amazed at you, who won't sink in water.
Aren't you upset?
It hasn't even been that long since we started going out, but we have to separate. It'll be hard for me to get any nights out, either.
Hey, it's okay! I just have to follow you right there.
- What?
- I have a swim meet next week.
It's a competition that gets you selected to become a national athlete, so I'll go straight to Taereung if I make first place.
- We have a worldwide athletic competition soon, too.
- Really?
- Do you really become a national team member if you make first place?
- Yeah.
If you make second place, they judge you based on your previous competitions.
But if you make first place, you become a national team member right away.
Ah, I was planning on just taking it easy and doing it half heartedly this time,
but I'm suddenly starting to really want to win.
- Are you really confident?
- Of course, I am!
If I don't have a problem with my start, then I can take it all.
Oh, Joon Hyeong! I want to go to Taereung with you!
- Let's go together, okay?!
- Hey, don't worry. I'm going to go to that competition and win everything.
So I'll follow you right there, you got it?
I want to go together. Really!
♬    Today more than yesterday  ♬
♬    Tomorrow more than today  ♬
♬    If I only have you, I think I'll be happy  ♬
Hey, but that doesn't mean we should do additional practice right away.
Hey, you disappeared and missed practices for two days!
Does it make sense for a guy who has to make first place to do that? Let's hurry up and go practice, quickly!
Ah, let's go eat some food first.
Food, my foot! Hurry up and run.
I'll run if you give me a kiss, then.
♬  I'm going to pick you up so you won't regret it  ♬
♬  Will you wait I'm going  ♬
If you don't practice, you're dead!
♬  to pick you up right now  ♬
Hey!
Hey, make a streamline! Your head! Head!
One, two! Your speed is good! Go, go, go!
One, two! Touch!
Oh, Jeong Joon Hyeong, your condition got much better. Good job.
Hey, but did you really pack this yourself?
This is really delicious.
I'm so proud. You're eating well.
Hey, hurry up and run if you're done eating. Hurry, hurry! Quickly!
Hey, why would I run right after I ate? My stomach will hurt if I run right after eating. I can't run. I can't run, seriously!
- Hurry up and run!
- Oh, cut my stomach! I can't. Cut my stomach!
Hurry up and go! Hurry up, it won't hurt. Go, quickly!
- I'll run if you give me a kiss.
- Ah, really, you are getting into a habit.
I'll give you one if you run.
I'll give you a kiss if you run.
♬   Will you be spinning in delight?   ♬
Hurry up and run!
♬  I think you're so pretty   ♬
I love you too.
♬  but   ♬
Stop staring at me!
One, two, three!
♬ but we shouldn't do this  ♬
♬   Both the confession and regret   ♬
Please let my boyfriend overcome his start trauma,
♬   that follows   ♬
win first place, and come to Taereung with me!
♬   are clumsy   ♬
Me too, same, same! I agree with her wishes!
♬  We both have big and small concerns worrying us   ♬
Please!
♬   between dreams and love   ♬
January 6th: Joon Hyeong's competition
January 7th : Entering Taereung
♬   Following the rainbow that comes after the rain   ♬
Swim Championship Meet for the National Team
♬   we're starting to search for the wonderful days   ♬
♬   From now on when it gets hard,   ♬
♬   who cares if we give up? We can just go forward two steps tomorrow   ♬
We now have the men's 200-meter finals. The swimmers are coming in.
On the fifth lane, we have swimmer Choi Tae Hoon. He has been privately training in Australia
and returned to Korea three days ago for this competition.
Will we be able to see an outcome of his training?
The swimmer who was disqualified with a false start at the Presidential Championship Meet last time.
- Swimmer Jeong Joon Hyeong?
- Yes.
If he just does well on his start, then I think we can expect a good outcome.
He always got disqualified because of his starts, right?
Will he possibly be able to overcome that trauma at this final competition? It's very interesting.
Take your mark.
Yes, Swimmer Choi Tae Hoon in Lane 5 had the fastest start.
Swimmer Jeong Joon Hyeong also jumped in properly.
Oh, Swimmer Jeong Joon Hyeong is pushing through. He is catching up now.
Right. Swimmer Jeong Joon Hyeong is swimming with the tremendous speed on the last lap.
He's only a handspan long away from Swimmer Choi Tae Hoon. He's practically caught up to him now.
Right now, he caught up to him.
Yes, now... I feel like both swimmers finished at almost the same time!
That's right. They came at about the same time.
Ah, so
Choi Tae Hoon: 1:51:30  1st
Jeong Joon Hyeong: 1:51:33  2nd
Swimmer Choi Tae Hoon took first place, and Swimmer Jeong Joon Hyeong took second place by a narrow margin.
Swimmer Jeong Joon Hyeong was really amazing.
Yes, this is Kim Chang Geol.
What? A kidney donor?
Ah, yes. Today's not a good day for me,
but it will be possible for me to be admitted tomorrow.
Ah, yes, yes. I understand. Then we'll agree for me to be admitted tomorrow.
Yes, yes. Yes.
Why, why, why? Did they say that you should get surgery? Did they say they found a kidney donor?
Yes, well, even though I'm second on the kidney recipient waiting list,
it might be a match. They want me to be admitted immediately today to get some additional tests done.
Then why are you going tomorrow? You need to go when they tell you to come.
Hey, you rascal! Even if I go, I have to go after I send Bok Joo off to Taereung.
If I become hospitalized or what not, imagine how conflicted she would be.
Still, this is something you shouldn't hide.
Even if I decide to receive surgery, we'll set a date
and tell her then, depending on the situation.
I don't think this is something you should keep quiet about.
Won't Bok Joo resent me later?
Good job. My Joon Hyeong, you were the best!
If my arms were just a little longer, I could have won this competition.
I really wanted to win first place and go to Taereung with you.
It's fine. You can't do better than this.
You overcame your start trauma perfectly, and from now on, you'll win first place every time.
All that's left is for you to rise.
Ugh, there are thirteen hours,
26 minutes, 15 seconds, 14 seconds, until you get into there.
Bok Joo, will I be able to endure without seeing you?
I'm more worried about myself.
You made me become addicted to you without even realizing it myself.
Well, I have a quite fatal charm.
Still, you can't escape or anything because of me so I'll follow you immediately.
If you go there and put your weightlifting shoes on backward  (cheat on me) , both you and I will die, understand?
Talk about yourself. I've already stationed Soon Ok and Nan Hee as your paparazzi.
Ah, those Uglies. I'm ruined!
What time do you leave tomorrow? I'll escort you to Taereung.
No, I want to go in alone.
You said that you'd follow me immediately! To do that, you need to train whenever possible. You don't have time to take me there.
Wow, you're already so ambitious for me to become a National team member.
I'm going to go to Taereung, no matter what.
Please do so.
Whenever you have time, go check out our store.
My Uncle is there but I'm still worried about my Dad.
Alright, just trust me.
Ugh! Now it's 13 hours, 22 minutes, 12 seconds, 11 seconds—
Yeah, Nan Hee.
Your weightlifting uniform? Why are you asking me to get it for you?
Just... Fine, you wench! I'll stop by the weightlifting practice room.
Bye, yeah.
- What? Did the Uglies ask you to bring something?
- Yeah,
I think we'll have to stop by the weightlifting practice room.
Alright, let's go.
Wait. Why it so dark? Why are even the emergency lights turned off?
Hey, this is a chance.
What chance?
Hey, we can't! What if someone comes in?
Who'll come in here? There's no one here.
- Surprise!
Bok Joo, receive a drink.
I told the Taereung coach that you're a special disciple of mine so he should take special care of you.
You, be especially careful of your back. You know that you have to take care of your own body now, right?
Yes, Coach. Yes, Professor.
Thank you. If you two weren't here, I would never have been able to come this far.
Come on. Why is the atmosphere like this? It's not as if we're never going to see each other again.
It's true that we won't be able to meet for a while.
When we go for runs, when we eat, when we do snatches and clean-and-jerks, and even when we train!
Who will I partner with now, Bok Joo?
You have Soon Ok. You're just putting on a show to try to get me to stay.
But you, you've been standing there frozen since before. What's your name?
I'm Jeong Joon Hyeong who entered into the Swimming Department in 2015.
- His voice is a work of art.
- He's really handsome.
Bok Joo, you must be happy.
Bok Joo really caught a good boyfriend.
He looks exactly like me when I was 20. I used to look like that.
Professor, I don't think that's right.
Um, your lie is too severe.
I'm not lying, you rascal! I was so handsome that my nickname was—
Now! Our Bok Joo, train well in Taereung,
and I hope that you'll raise the stature of Korean weightlifting at the competition in China.
Kids, cheers!
Cheers!
♬   I don't know where this feeling   ♬
Thank you!
♬   came from   ♬
- Here.
- This is delicious.
Can we eat now?
♬   There's a small quake   ♬
Yeah, eat, eat up.
♬   only known to me   ♬
♬   Like the little boy who locked me up   ♬
♬   in the sand castle I made,   ♬
♬   I was still wandering and searching for my dream   ♬
This is the bellflower elixir.
It's good for immunity, so have it when you have a cold,
and this has some ginseng.
Make sure to take one every single day, alright?
Do well.
Dad.
Bok Joo, should I take you there on my scooter?
No, I'll just take the bus and go by myself. I want to do that.
Alright then.
Uncle, please take good care of my dad.
I'll only trust you.
Hey, I'll take care of everything so don't worry about him and just focus on taking care of your own body.
Don't skip your meals and train diligently.
Kim Bok Joo of the Weightlifting Department of Hanuel Sports University has received the order to depart to Taereung today.
Yes, I'll salute my father and my uncle. Salute!
Salute!
- Take care.
- Yeah.
I'll leave now. Dad, don't send me off. Bye!
Hyung, since we've sent Bok Joo off, let's go to the hospital now.
Joon Hyeong, I'm leaving.
To be honest, I couldn't show you
but I'm really nervous and scared right now.
Will I be able to do well?
After I open that unknown door and enter,
what kind of world will be waiting for me?
Don't worry, Bok Joo. You'll do well.
You're much stronger and prettier than you think you are.
You'll shine brilliantly wherever you are.
Kim Bok Joo, swag!
I'll wait for you, Joon Hyeong.
Don't take too long coming here. I'm quite impatient.
Wait, I'll follow you soon.
You know that this Oppa has no reverse, right?
I miss you, Jeong Joon Hyeong.
I miss you, Bok Joo.