Did you get back safely?
What about you?
Keke.
You must be tired. Go to sleep now.
You go to sleep too now. You have training tomorrow.
You go to sleep first.
I don't want to. You go to sleep first.
♬   I dream of it, please let us be eternally happy   ♬
I'm afraid we'll stay up the whole night if we keep going like this.
♬   I dream of it   ♬
Then I'm off to sleep.
♬   Please let us have youthful days   ♬
Are you sleeping?
What?
♬ Even if there is a chilly wind ♬
I can't sleep because of you.
♬ stinging us ♬
♬   I dream of it   ♬
♬   Please let the days we smile be more   ♬
♬   than the days drenched in tears  ♬
Episode 13
Love's jealousy is a rounding down.
- Hello!
- Hello.
Nan Hee, Nan Hee! Have you been well?
Wait a second.
What? Did you find a huge chunk of beef in your beef stew?
There was no meat in mine, just loads of vegetables and soup.
What's wrong with the beef stew? It was good.
What is this unusually positive mode?
Where is the Athlete Kim who wanted to run for student body president because the amount of meat in the meals was reduced?
Hey, did something good happen to you?
What good thing?
No, I'm sure there's something.
Come to the toad's house.
- What is it?
- Spam.
Yes!
Okay!
What do you want so early in the morning?
I threw the coin in your place. You can just pray now.
Hey, this is why you told me to pray, isn't it?! You only learned the bad things!
Who's calling who bad? Don't you remember what happened yesterday? You came on to me!
- Hey, when did I ever come onto you?! You kissed me first—
- Yeah,
I only kissed you but then you suddenly grabbed my face like this and kissed me roughly as if you had been starved for days—
Okay, okay!
We'll just say that I was the one who came on to you.
But that... hairpin you have on right now. Isn't that the one you wore when you met my older brother?
My brother said that looked good, didn't he? Or did he say it suited you well?
No, he didn't.
Don't lie! I know everything! From now on, don't put that on!
- Put on something else!
- I have nothing else.
- This is pretty.
- It's not pretty at all! It's really ugly! It's really crappy!
- Take it off.
- Why? This is the only hairpin I have.
Take it off! Take this off Take it off!
Take it off! Take it off!
Take it off!
Aish! You even ripped out strands of my hair!
Hey, I'm sorry...
Instead, come with me for a minute. Just for a minute.
Hey, don't grab my hand. I didn't even put on hand-cream so my hand is rough.
It's fine. I'll even get a pressure-point massage on the way, it's nice.
Let's go, Hon— No, Fatty. Let's go.
Why? Where are we going?
Hey, why did we come here?
For that.
- Pick.
- What?
Pick. I'll buy you hairpins so from now on. Only wear the hairpins that I buy for you.
Don't wear something like that ribbon from before, alright?
Jeong Joon Hyeong, you're unexpectedly really jealous.
Then would I not be jealous? I saw you crying, bawling, and doing all sorts of strange things for my brother.
You can't focus on the past like a loser. Everything's all in the past.
Like a loser?
Hey, I'm telling you this because we're already on the topic.
I'm not the type to get jealous over small things just because we're dating,
and I hate things like playing hard to get. It doesn't fit my type and it's so childish.
So from now on, don't expect those things from me, understand?
- So are you going to buy a pin or not?
- Of course I have to buy one! Which one should I get?
Hey, what about this one? It fits your image perfectly.
Oh! Oh, Bok Joo, why are you in there?
- Bok Joo, why are you suddenly in there?
- This one, the big one, the big one. What about this one?
Give it to me. Let me see.
This one, what about this one?
Oh, a strawberry!
Wow, it's so pretty even though I can't see it from here. Wow, it's pretty!
Unni! Unni! Pull yourself together, Unni! Teacher! Teacher!
Unni! What do I do?! Supervisor!
911 Ambulance
What's going on, seriously?
Joon Hyeong! Joon Hyeong! Joon Hyeong! Joon Hyeong! Joon Hyeong! Joon Hyeong! Joon Hyeong!
Ah, really! What a fuss! Why? Did the little boss summon us again?
Not the little boss! But Song Si Ho! Song Si Ho!
Hey, Song Si Ho took pills to commit suicide!
Bok Joo discovered her on the floor unconscious
and an ambulance just took her.
Emergency Center
Are you Song Si Ho's guardian?
Ah, yes, well...
We finished pumping her stomach well.
According to the results of a blood test, she didn't take a lot of pills.
I don't think this was a suicide attempt.
But the patient is in a very weakened condition.
She is malnourished but has a high glucose level.
Besides the reflux esophagitis, she seems to have an eating disorder of repeating anorexia and bulimia.
We'll get her hospitalized first to check on her condition.
Yes, thank you.
Si Ho!
Si Ho, why are you like this? What are you doing here?
Open your eyes, please?
Unni...
Si Ho, can you see me?
Mom...
Unni, it's me.
Si Ho, are you okay?
How is Unni Song Si Ho? Is she okay?
Yeah, I just came back after seeing her wake up. According to the doctor, her condition isn't dangerous.
Ah, that's a relief.
Well, they say that because of insomnia, she kept taking the sleeping pills. And she also has an eating disorder.
She has become so weak that she has to be hospitalized and treated.
Hey, are you okay? You were really shocked earlier, weren't you?
Being shocked isn't that big of a deal. I did wrong.
When I assumed that her condition wasn't good, I shouldn't have just overlooked it.
I witnessed her binge-eating at night.
You didn't know that a situation like this would occur. Don't blame yourself.
Still, she's my roommate. I should have checked on her, even just once, when I thought she was just sleeping in.
I was just so excited after seeing your text. Ah, this stupid!
What crime did your head commit? Don't do it.
Goodness.
Missed Call: Si Ho
What about this one?
A big one, a big one, a big one!
Oh, that's pretty! Santa, Santa!
Where is the Santa one?
It's pretty.
GIANT Bar
Careful, careful!
Dean! You promised me, alright?
Our Coach Choi, you have to reinstate her. Reinstate her! You promised to look into reinstating her.
Alright, alright!
No, no, no, I don't believe you. Come on, promise me.
This person, seriously! I promise.
Yes, please take care on your way back.
Watch your head.
Here, here, here.
Here, please take good care of him.
Dean, you promised me.
Please take care on your way back.
Wow, I only have $2 left.
Okay! I'm walking home, then.
Seong Eun, just you wait.
I will reinstate you no matter what! I will!
Hey!
Joon Hyeong.
Hey, why are you here alone?
My younger sister went to school and my mom went to work.
Shouldn't you be lying down?
No, I just woke up from a long sleep and I feel fine to the point of being apologetic.
Should we leave?
- Let's sit here for a minute.
- Alright.
Hey, aren't you cold?
I'm fine.
I'm sorry for not picking up your call yesterday.
I didn't know that you were in that kind of situation. I should have answered.
No, it's fine. I'm the one who made it like that anyway.
Joon Hyeong, I feel really strange right now.
Yesterday was only a day ago,
but the previous events that brought me here seem like they happened so long ago.
Is it because I almost died?
I'm sure you already know, but the only thing we've done after becoming mature is our field of athletics.
Once we get pushed out of our positions, we feel as if the world is ending. I guess that's why I couldn't admit it and held on to it.
Even though I knew I was going downhill, I held on to the end of the cliff and struggled hard.
But now, I think I'll be able to put everything down and train comfortably.
I kept clinging on to you when I knew it wouldn't work out...
I'm really sorry.
Then, I guess we're even. We both have something we're sorry to the other for.
Here, let's be friends.
Call me "noona" (sister) from now on.
Hey, when will you be discharged?
Tomorrow or the day after tomorrow. The doctor said my condition had gotten better.
But I still seem to have some aftereffects psychologically. I guess I'll need to get some psychological treatment.
Hey, I have a therapist who counsels me. He's really amazing. Should I introduce you to him?
Then I'd be thankful.
Yeah, Bok Joo?
Jeong Joon Hyeong, where are you?
Me? I'm at the hospital.
My coach told us to have individual practice this afternoon so I just dropped by.
I see. How is Unni Song Si Ho's condition?
She seems fine. Her condition is stable now.
What a relief, seriously.
I was just about to visit the hospital too, we should have gone together.
Ahh. I thought you were still in training. Do you want to come now?
Should I? Then I'll be there soon.
Yeah, take care coming here.
Yeah.
He should have told me beforehand. If he had done, I would have matched my schedule to go together with him.
What do you mean? Removing her?
I mean, this is different from what you said you would do yesterday. You promised to reinstate her.
You'd hold the personnel committee meeting again and lead to her reinstatement her with a salary reduction.
I was planning to, but the higher-ups have already decided on this issue. What can I do now?
The reason I'm trying to reinstate Coach Choi is because she knows the kids the best.
She's led them well until now, and I believe that she'll continue to do so in the future.
I'm telling you that this issue is already finished! My head hurts too, stop talking about that!
Dean! Fine.
If you ignore the professor's opinion and handle the personnel matter like this, I'll quit!
Do whatever you want!
Th-That person, seriously...
Yes?
Oh, you're here.
I just came back from outside and it was chilly here.
Ah, yes. Are you okay now?
I just came back from the dead. It's nice to see you after such a long time, my roommate.
Ah, sit down.
Come here.
Um, this. I thought that it would be too early to bring food...
and it suits your feminine and delicate image.
Thank you.
Hey, you have a pollen allergy. Will you be okay?
Well, I feel a little bit of tingle but I'm fine.
I didn't even know you had something like that. If I'd known, I would have just bought some drinks.
It's okay, we can just put them back there.
I'm a bit dizzy after talking so much. I need to lie down.
Ah, I'll adjust the bed for you.
I'll do it.
Why are you so modest today? It's unlike you.
Do I have to be talkative and frivolous all the time?
I mean, you're just unusually quiet today compared to other days.
When you don't have anything to talk about, why do you have to talk?
Bad joke fail. It's really not funny. It's not.
Hey, I have some knowledge in dad jokes because of my dad. Should we have a battle?
Forget it. It's bothersome. Stop making me talk.
Why is our Fatty getting so irritated?
Ah, I know! It's way past your snack-time!
You're getting irritated and annoyed because your stomach is empty, aren't you?
I did wrong, it was my fault.
Okay. Let's go eat something, Fatty.
Forget it, it's bothersome. I'm not hungry.
Hey, there's a time when you're not hungry? Stop lying.
There's a time when you're not hungry? Come on, don't be like this. Let's go.
Let's go eat something.
I said I'm fine!
Let's go! Now!
We'll start off with the fish cakes you love so much.
Welcome.
Yes, hello.
What should I eat?
Yeah, Song Si Ho. No, I'm not back at the school yet.
Ah, the therapist? No, he's not part of a hospital, he just offers counseling services by himself.
Yeah, he's someone my older brother introduced to me. Yeah.
No, I mean... I just think seeing a therapist will be better if you want to continue receiving mental treatment.
It's been minutes since they last saw each other. How could they still have so much to say? You might as well just date her again.
Although I'm sure following the treatment your hospital recommends isn't bad,
the therapist makes you feel at ease.
No, it's not that far from school. Do you remember the pasta restaurant we went to together in the past?
It's about a block away from that restaurant.
If you want to meet him, tell me. I'll ask him about his schedule.
Yeah.
Hey, eat slowly. You'll get indigestion.
You said that you weren't hungry before. You were born with the talent of eating.
Have you ever thought about challenging the Guinness Book of World Records, my pig?
What? Pig?
Fine, fine, I'll cancel that. Cancel the pig, you're just Fatty.
I can't even call you Fatty? Even though that's something I've called you by until now?
Fine. If you're that sensitive about it, I won't ever call you names like "Pig" or "Fatty"... never.
Hey, hey, hey, hey! Okay, okay, I'm sorry! Let's go together, wait for me!
How much is it? How much do I have to pay you?
- $16.
- What?
- How much?
-  $16.
How much did she eat? Did she eat all of this?
Yes, all of it.
Bok Joo!
What's wrong with you? Why are you getting mad over something like that? That's unlike you, Kim Bok Joo.
Stop bothering me and go away.
Okay, I'll really be careful with my words from now on, alright? Come on, don't be mad anymore.
Don't be mad anymore, alright? Don't be mad.
Quit bothering me!
That's why I told you to stop. Why did you grab onto me and make such a fuss?
Bok Joo, blood... I'm bleeding.
I'm bleeding. Blood, there's blood.
You're a man, yet you're making such a fuss over a small scratch.
Hey, what do you mean "small"? These small cuts smart and hurt more!
You have to tell me what you're mad about for me to know, you rascal!
I don't think you're like this because I called you a pig.
I said I'm not mad.
You are mad.
- I'm not mad.
- You are mad!
You keep insisting that I'm mad when I'm not mad and it's about to make me mad right now! You're such a strange kid!
Move! I have to go to training!
She is mad! What is she mad about?
If he's curious as to why I'm mad, maybe he should take a look at his actions.
Kim Bok Joo, I didn't see you like that but you're a woman by nature, by nature!
A human being should have basic manners.
What is he doing with his ex-girlfriend in front of his current girlfriend?
Does he really have to make it that obvious?
Ugh, I can't even show that I'm jealous because it'll be childish! I'm so pissed!
What?
Still, if even the professor just quits like that, what are we supposed to do?
Should we just play around? Are we not going to train?
Hey, there's no way he would have really quit. I'm sure he just said that out of anger.
What are you talking about? What did the professor do?
It seems the professor was working to reinstate Coach Choi,
but the school assigned a new coach one-sidedly today so the professor said he would quit and he left.
Hey, let's leave. What's the use of us staying in this weightlifting room when our professor doesn't even care?
That's what I'm saying!
He's saying that the coach who embezzled the operating funds is the only important person and we're nothing!
Hey, hey, forget everything. Training or whatever, let's leave.
- Come on—
- It's not the Coach's fault.
It's all because of me.
The coach used the operating funds because of me.
I have no words. I'm sorry, it's all my fault.
I should have told everyone when the incident happened, but she was so adamant about taking the blame.
See? I told you that our coach isn't someone to just use the operating funds for herself.
What do we do now? If we didn't know, it would have been fine but since we now know the reason,
are we just going to let the coach and the professor leave like this?
Shouldn't we ask them to bring back our professor? Shouldn't we plead his case?
Will it work just because we ask them to?
If it doesn't work the first time, then we should endure until it does. With all our guts.
The weightlifting department requests the reinstatement of Coach Choi Seong Eun!
We request it! We request it!
We request taking appropriate steps!
We demand reinstatement!
We demand it! We demand it!
It's so freaking cold. It's much colder than I thought it would be. Why did I suggest we protest outside?
Hey, you were the one who said that we had to protest in the cold to show them our determination.
I'm about to freeze to death.
That's true but...
I'm fine with being cold but I'm so hungry.
Hyun Cheol, are you okay? You get dizzy if you even skip a single meal.
I'm fine. My motto is that a hungry Socrates is better than a full pig.
Soybean paste stew!
I guess today's menu is soybean paste stew.
No. Although this may seem like soybean paste stew at first, seeing that the scent of the ocean is rampant,
this is crab stew made with soybean paste.
Bok Joo's correct. This is crab stew. I'm 100% sure of it.
Crab stew must be delicious! It's amazing if you mix rice in the fresh hot stew!
That's amazing...
Stop it. If you talk more, you'll get even hungrier.
I'm hungry.
Are you going to dissolve the weightlifting department?
What are those people?
The students of the weightlifting department are asking to reinstate Coach Choi Seong Eun.
They claim to be on a hunger strike.
Seriously, they're doing all sorts of things.
Both the professor and his disciples are both lunatics.
It's cold. I'm sure they'll leave after some time.
Please go inside.
Where is he going?
I forgot about this. You're still here!
I guess winter training is less harsh than it used to be. You look like you have way too much leisure these days.
I just came during my dinner break. I'm going to leave after a cup of coffee.
What about you? How is your dating business going?
You don't even come to our school to see Doctor Ah Yeong often anymore.
It's just... I have a lot of thoughts these days.
Why? Did Doctor Ah Yeong say that she can't be a sunflower anymore? Does she want to call everything off?
I guess you should set down a straw mat and become a psychic. It's something similar.
I knew this would happen. "Just friends" between a man and a woman? Yeah, right.
You're really a problem.
How can you have less sense than your younger brother at times?
I know, right?
What about you? Are you making some progress with Bok Joo?
Of course I am. Am I you?
What? You confessed, didn't you?
Hey, congratulations.
But I'm a bit miserable.
When women get angry over something, why do they hope for the man to guess what it is instead of just saying it outright?
Are we contestants on a quiz show or something?
That's the game of dating.
What? Is Bok Joo upset?
Yeah! But I have no idea what she's upset about.
I feel as if I'm stuck inside a maze.
Think about it carefully. I'm sure if you wander about a bit, the exit will appear.
You're dating amidst all this. You're much better than me, you rascal.
Of course, I'm much better than you.
Oh? Isn't that Bok Joo?
Hunger Strike 01: It's possible to earn one gold, one silver, two bronzes at 2016 Championship because of Professor Yoon and Coach Choi!! We want Coach Choi  Seong Eun to be  reinstated!
What is she doing there?
What are you doing here?
I asked, what are you doing?
Can you not read Hangul? We're protesting for reinstatement. It's a hunger strike.
We want Coach Choi Seong Eun to be reinstated.
Hey, do you know how many degrees the temperature will drop into the negatives tonight?
What are you doing outside in the middle of winter?
Why do you care? Forget it. It's a matter within our department.
Hey, care...
I can't just "not care." If you continue to do this, you'll freeze to death, you rascal.
Whether someone freezes to death or not, don't mind someone else's business.
You already have your plate full.
Contrary to your looks, you're quite nosy.
Hey!
Are you really going to talk like that?
I'm like this because I'm worried.
Yeah, fine. Who can stop you?
Do whatever you want.
You didn't answer my calls.
You chose not to answer my calls, right?
Yeah, I chose not to.
I was too emotional that day, I'm sorry.
After hearing your words, I thought about it too.
For the past ten years, you really were always by my side.
When I didn't have a friend to eat lunch with, when I needed a drinking buddy,
when I had to go to a meeting but felt too awkward to just go alone.
But I thought of that as a given.
Let's date, Ah Yeong.
Let's date properly.
Hey, Jeong Jae Yi, you're really...
Is it that dating is an event for helping the needy?
Love doesn't work just because you work hard, you idiot.
Ah Yeong.
I'll just thankfully accept your friendship.
It's cold, you should leave.
What is she doing outside in the middle of winter?
When the head is ignorant, the body is the one that suffers.
Ugh, she needs to tell me what she's mad about for me to know anything!
Woo, it's snowing again!
- So much snow—
- Hey!
Is it snowing?
Yeah. Wow, I don't think it'll stop anytime soon.
Ah, it's freezing! The roads are going to ice over.
Ugh, this tiring winter. I despise being cold!
Hey, should we rest for a bit?
- Yeah, yeah.
- Let's rest.
Let's rest for a few minutes and strengthen up.
- Yeah.
- I have to to go to the bathroom.
Come back quickly.
We want Coach Choi Seong Eun to be reinstated.
Put your shoes on.
Arms.
Protest while taking care of your body,
please.
What are two of them doing there?
- What?
- Who is that?
I don't know.
- What are they doing over there?
- Oh?
- Isn't he from the swimming department?
- Huh?
- He is.
- Ah...
I'll leave now.
Why, huh?
The mood is strange between those two.
Ah, he's a male friend of mine
but he came all the way here because his friend was suffering. He is so nosy.
You must be so happy! If I had a male friend who did that for me, I would wish for nothing else.
I envy you!
Maybe it's because it snowed yesterday but the roads are frozen.
Hyung! Go inside and rest.
Am I some corpse? I just woke up from resting. Why do you keep telling me to rest?
I rested so much that my back hurts from lying down.
I dare you to faint again.
Why did that fall? How strange.
It's fine. Ugh, I had a disturbing dream last night.
Hey, give Bok Joo a call.
I'm sure there's nothing wrong. After going back school, she is training hard—  I got it.
Yeah, Bok Joo. Where are you? Did you eat?
Of course, I ate. I ate the radish leaf soup today.
Hunger Strike - Day 2
I'm in the weightlifting training room right now. Is Father okay?
Yeah. I'll call you back later, Uncle. Yeah.
Hyeon Cheol, you can't sleep.
Hey, open your eyes, you rascal.
Hey, pull yourself together.
- Hey!
-Hyun Cheol!
Sunbae Hyeon Cheol!
- Hey!
- Wake up!
Sang Chul, I'll stay here so move him to the ER.
- Careful!
- Come on, support him!
Sunbae, please wake up quickly!
- Hyeon Cheol!
- Hyeon Cheol, wake up!
What do we do?
Ah, I really can't do this anymore.
My legs feel like they're going to fall off.
- Nan Hee, are you okay?
- Nan Hee.
No, I'm not fine.
Hey, Bok Joo. You have a nose-bleed.
Hey!
Ah, seriously. You're having nosebleeds. What is this?
This won't do. You two, go in now. I think we've done as much as we can.
No, Sunbae! If we quit here,
then everything we've done will have been nothing.
We might not be able to see the professor and coach anymore.
What are we doing because of my guilt?
Sunbaenim...
Bok Joo! Nan Hee!
- Sunbae Woon Gi.
- Soon Ok.
Lee Soon Ok! Why did you only come now?!
I was worried after receiving your text message, so I ran away while my mom was grocery shopping. I did well, didn't I?
Do you know how hard it was for me?
Don't worry for now. You know I came back.
Soon Ok.
Don't cry, come here. Goodness,
my babies.
Ah, seriously! Lee Soon Ok, I missed you!
Lee Soon Ok! You're my roommate but you weren't next to me!
Right...
Woon Gi, Woon Gi! Big news, big news, big news!
I just heard that our new coach is just one of our Dean's personal connections.
Yeah, he's never done any weightlifting before. He just co-majored in physical education. Does this even make any sense?
Since it's turned out like this, this is no longer a problem with just Coach Choi. Our weightlifting department can't become a crappy artifact.
Let's properly do this protest, all in.
- Let's do this!
- Yeah, let's do this!
I'm seriously speechless!
- Let's do this!
- Yes!
- Fighting against corruption!
Fighting against corruption!
- Is a coaching job also for a person born with a gold spoon?!
- Do you think the weightlifting department is easy?!
- Fighting against corruption!
-Do you think the weightlifting department is easy?!
- Is a coaching job also for a person born with a gold spoon?!
Ugh, what time is it?
Dean
Yes, this is Yoon Deok Man.
What? My students?
- What do you mean "hiring someone with connections"?!
- Heaven, listen to us!
Those rascals, seriously!
- What do you mean "hiring someone with connections"?!
Hey, you rascals! Are you all crazy?!
Huh? During the time you should be training with barbells, who told you to do something like this?!
Professor, we're really sorry but we can't just sit still like this any longer.
Although we wish for Coach Choi's reinstatement the most, this is more than that now.
We can't accept a personal connection coach who doesn't know the "weight" of "weightlifting".
Hey, you rascals! Still, if you get blacklisted by acting like this too,
what will you do then? Who'll take responsibility?
- Go back! Go back in now!
- No, wait!
- Go back in!
- No, we can't!
Fine, I have no other choice.
If you won't go back in now, I'll just...
- Step over me and go!
- Professor!
- Get up!
- Step over me!
- Professor!
- Professor, get up!
- Get him up!
- Professor!
- Wait, wait! I have a call. I have to take this call!
I knew this would happen, sheesh!
Hello? Yes, Dean.
I'm b-blocking the students right now.
What? Are you serious?
Really?! Yes, yes, thank you!
Yes, thank you! Yes, yes, yes!
Hey, Coach Choi will be reinstated!
- What?
- Are you serious?
- Seriously?
- Yeah.
They just decided at the board meeting that they'll finish it by
reinstating her and cutting her salary for three months.
♬   Will you be spinning in delight?   ♬
♬   I think you're so pretty   ♬
♬   However, we shouldn't do this   ♬
♬   Both confession and repentance    ♬
♬   in red-hot passion   ♬
♬   are clumsy but we   ♬
♬   have each have big and little   ♬
Yes, Professor. Please speak.
♬   concerns worrying us between   ♬
Pardon?
♬   our dreams and love   ♬
Re... Reinstatement?
♬   Following the rain and rainbow   ♬
♬   in our personal heaven, we're searching   ♬
♬   for a wonderful day   ♬
Wow, I'm so proud of you all
♬   From now on, when it's hard   ♬
that I'll treat you to all of this today, so just empty out our restaurant before you leave!
Glasses up!
After seeing our weightlifting department come together this time, I felt many things.
The will that you can accomplish something
and the certainty that there is no fear when we are all together!
As a teacher, I've learned more things from you all this time.
Now, since our comrades who've left the house have returned,
all we have left is to train diligently!
Let's cheer up. Now, fighting!
Fighting!
Stop, stop, stop, just a minute!
In celebration of our Coach Choi having returned, let's hear her speak a few words. Come out!
It's fine. What would I have to say?
It's been a while, but we'll hear some words from our coach.
Kids, I don't have the right to face you all.
I'm really sorry and I'm really thankful.
I really missed you all, seriously.
Ah, seriously...
- Don't cry!
- Don't cry! Don't cry!
You and the professor should do a love-shot on such a nice day like this.
- What love shot?
- Forget it.
Love shot! Love shot!
- Love shot!
- Stop it!
Fine, fine, fine!
You're really going to do it?
Now.
- You saw that, right?
- Second stage!
Second stage! Second stage!
- Ah, seriously.
- Second stage!
- Second stage?
- Second stage! Second stage!
Wait a moment!
Um, this arm, please just...
What are you doing, you rascal?
Um,
yes... We're dating.
- Coach.
- What are they talking about?
- What in the world?
- Goodness...
We're dating. Seong Eun and I are dating.
What?
- Coach!
- What should we do?
That's real swag.
- What do we do?
- Oh my god...
Uncle! What are you doing right now? Are you crazy?
What? What did I do?
How can you announce that by yourself without discussing it with me beforehand?!
I mean, it's not as if I made it up.
Why are you so angry?
- Bok Joo's uncle!
- I'm not Bok Joo's uncle, I'm Kim Dae Ho. My name is Kim Dae Ho!
And it's true that we're dating.
Are we not dating, Seong Eun?
Uncle, I... I'm really sorry.
I should have told you earlier but I was really drunk and—
What nonsense! We! We...
- We even kissed.
- I'm seriously going insane.
If you kissed me, you need to take responsibility. You can't do this now.
Do you think kissing is a joke?
Uncle, I... I'm really, really sorry, okay?
You can hit me once right here. Hit me here, right here. Hit me, come on.
- Come on, hit me. Just hit me and get it over with.
- What's wrong with you?!
Just hit me!
Ugh! I should really quit drinking or something...
I'm seriously going insane.
By any chance, are you like this because of the professor?
Is the professor the reason your heart
can't come to me?
What are you talking about right now?
- It's not like that.
- I-If it's not like that, then it's fine. I didn't hear anything,
so I'm going to go straight towards you, just know that.
Ah, Bok Joo's uncle!
Bok Joo's uncle!
What is this? Can she not pick up or is she just not choosing to pick up?
I hope she didn't go to the hospital because she got sick.
- Did you eat a lot?
- Of course, I did.
Goodness.
Hey, but it was a huge situation as soon as we got there!
That's what I'm saying, but when do you think Bok Joo's uncle and our coach started having feelings for each other?
I don't know. I didn't catch on at all either.
If I had a romantic couple declaration like that, I would wish for nothing else.
I'm so, so jealous! Seriously.
"We're dating!"
- Uncle!
- I know!
- They were so cute!
You rascals! Is this the time for you to date?!
It wouldn't be enough if you focused solely on weightlifting.
It won't be too late for you to start dating slowly later on in life.
Look at Bok Joo's uncle. I was worrying when he would become a proper human being
but he comes back with a nice woman.
- Yes, yes, of course.
- I'll remember your words.
- Don't ever date!
- Yes!
"We're dating!"
Why aren't you answering your phone? Who is it?
An unknown number keeps calling me, I don't know who the person is.
I guess it's spam.
Hey, it's been a while since all three of us have gotten together. Should we hang out tonight?
What about talking all night long in our room?
I even have some snacks I've hidden.
Will you two be fine? Shouldn't you rest up tonight?
I got a full-body heat massage so I'm fine.
Athlete Kim, do you not feel well?
Well, it's not bad but...
I think my arms and legs are quite sore and my head is pounding.
Yeah, let's just rest up tonight and play grandly after training tomorrow.
- I, Lee Soon Ok, will treat you all tomorrow.
- Okay, then you'll treat!
- Athlete Kim, go on in.
- Yeah, yeah, go to sleep.
Yeah, goodnight.
- Hey, if you're scared because of your roommate, come to our room!
- Yeah, I know!
Kids, I'm really sorry. I'm the wench who deserves to die.
Yeah, I know that I despise women who ignore their friends just because they have a boyfriend but let me date in peace, alright?
Hey, why didn't you pick up your phone?!
I didn't know you called.
Hey, of course, I did! I probably called you several dozen times.
Are you okay?
It's just, aside from my body being sore and my feet being frozen, I'm fine overall.
That's a relief.
Want to meet for a minute?
Ah, because we have some time left until night attendance and I have something to give you as well.
I said we should meet up at Toad's house. Why did you want to meet here?
It's cold outside. I thought you were still sick.
Here. I used it well.
What? Is this what you had to give me? I thought...
You could have taken your time giving this back to me.
Then what did you expect? I don't have to pay you back for the hot pack, right?
Hey, you don't have to repay me for the hot pack
but let me know this. Why were you upset?
U-Upset? Who was upset?
You were upset and that's why you were irritated.
When I think about it, I don't think you were upset over that pig comment.
Exactly what is it?! You have to tell me for me to know, you rascal!
Hey, I wasn't planning on telling you this because it's just so childish...
Tell me.
You were really considerate towards your ex-girlfriend.
Yeah, fine. I'll understand you being considerate to her since she's a patient,
but how can you talk about her pollen allergy and make it obvious that you two dated before in front of me?
And regardless of whether I was eating or not, you talked on the phone for so long in front of me!
It had been minutes since you'd last seen each other. How could you have so much to talk about?!
Hey, was that the reason?
Yes, that's it! You are such a player bastard!
Ah, seriously. Kim Bok Joo, I didn't see you like this.
You boasted so much about how childish jealousy wasn't your style
but you're the goddess of jealousy. Goodness, how fresh.
Are you teasing me?
For Song Si Ho, putting the fact that she was my ex-girlfriend aside,
I acted like that because I was sorry I didn't answer her calls that day
and we resolved everything before you came.
She said she wanted to remain comfortably as friends.
Your ex-girlfriend is your ex-girlfriend. What friendship?
By that logic, then aren't you the same? You also have a past.
Mine was just a one-sided crush! It's not the same as yours.
You're doing all sorts of things, Kim Bok Joo!
Ugh, you're so cute! You're so cute I could die!
What's wrong with you? I don't like skinship.
Don't lie. You love it.
- When did I ever?
- Fine, I'll be careful from now on
♬  Has the love that was once   ♬
so you have to make it obvious from now on. That's how I'll know.
♬   withered inside me  ♬
Let's tell each other everything from now on.
When we're having a hard time, when we're sad, even when we're embarrassed.
♬   come back alive?   ♬
♬   You cause excitement   ♬
Depending on what you do.
♬   to my calm heart   ♬
Wow, this pin is really pretty. Who bought you this?
Doctor Jae Yi.
♬   Today more than yesterday   ♬
I'm going to Song Si Ho.
♬   tomorrow more than today   ♬
♬   if I just have you, I think I'll be happy   ♬
Fine, come here.
Come here, come on.
♬  I'll go pick you up wherever you are   ♬
- Are you not mad anymore?
- Yes, I'm still mad.
Really?
♬  I hope I'm not late. I'll run to you   ♬
♬   I'll go to pick you up   ♬
Oh, hello.
♬   so I won't regret it. I'll wait   ♬
♬   I'll go to pick you up right now   ♬
- Did you sleep well last night?
- There are people here!
- Did you dream of me?
- What's wrong with you?!
- Our Fatty can't get a cold.
- Ah, seriously!
Hey! Si Ho's coming.
Unni!
Are you getting discharged now? Give it to me.
How's your health? Give me your bag.
It's fine. If I can't even hold a bag, I shouldn't be discharged.
You two seem quite close.
Still, you should try to not make it so obvious. You might make me relapse into my bitchery from jealousy.
No, we're not. We're not close at all.
If not, then forget what I said. I'll leave first.
Hey! Hey, seriously!
You're cold, aren't you?
Let me see, come on. Come here.
Ah! Jeong Joon Hyeong, you're doing so well! Just like you did before, don't even look at other girls,
just forget about manners,
and you can't wear low-cut shirts that reveal your chest, understand?
Yes, Noona Bok Joo.
Ah, you're so pretty. Let's go!
Ah! My arm hurts! My arm hurts.
If you don't play, you lose! Rock-paper-scissor-shoo!
- You lost.
- What? What is this?
It's a forehead hit, what else could it be? Come on, give me your forehead.
- Fine, you really want to have a go at this?
- If you don't play, you lose! Rock-paper-scissor-shoo!
Come here, come here.
If you don't play, you lose, rock-paper-scissor-shoo!
You're dead.
- Hey, wait. Wait, do it gently.
- Don't avoid it. You'll get hit twice if you avoid it.
Fine, fine. I lost on purpose.
Hey, that must really hurt! I'm sorry, I'm really sorry! I couldn't control my strength. I'm so sorry!
- Ah, that really hurts.
- I'm sorry, that must really hurt.
- Hey, let's break up.
- Come on, how can you get upset over that?
- I said, let's break up. Let's break up. Let's break up.
-Come on.
Come on, Jeong Joon Hyeong!
-Come here!
- Stop it! Stop!