- Yes, Mom.
-  Hey Jae Yi, are you coming home late  today?
- No, I won't be late.
- Then remember the dumplings from before?
- Oh yes, you mean the dim sum?
- Oh yes, that one.
- Okay, I'll buy it.
-  Alright then.
Yes.
Are you bored?
Do you want gum?
This is sugar-free, so no need to worry.
I don't think there's water in the car.
Ah, that's okay, that's okay. I can just hold my breath.
How slipshod I am, really!
Ah, the atmosphere was good too.
You waited a long time, right? I couldn't find a convenience store.
I did pull a warm drink from the vending machine.
Here.
Thank you, Doctor.
How is it? Are you all right?
Yes, I think so.
It's cold in the morning and evenings.
Your clothes are too thin.
It hasn't stopped yet. Try drinking some more.
Drink. It's okay to drink a lot.
Please drink more.
Episode 6 - If the Tail is Long, it Will Get Stepped on or Captured.
I first started swimming when I was eleven.
To the lonely, unfamiliar and uneasy me, water
was like a haven.
Almost like... in my mother's arms.
Actually, when I was ten my mom sent me to my uncle's house,
because my mom remarried and left for Canada.
Then what about your current parents?
They are my aunt and uncle. Jae Yi is my cousin.
But still it was okay,
because my mom would send a lot of presents  and postcards every Christmas,
I didn't think I was being abandoned.
because we were going to meet again someday.
But then ...
Mom, do you have a water-proof bandaid?
Did you get hurt?
Over there at the entrance to the room. Look in the drawer.
When I looked at the postcards again,
the penmanship on the cards delivered to me all the while was different from the first three.
It was almost as if someone were trying to imitate my mom's writing.
So, it was your aunt.
Then, was that day...
Yes. That was the first competition when the symptoms appeared.
Thank you, for telling me things that were hard for you to say.
Do you think it is connected to what I am going through?
I believe so. As I told you before,
panic disorder, conversion disorder, or trauma.
Hearing impairment and deafness could happen.
I think that day, the shock was quite big for you.
The connection you felt with your mother
disappeared all of a sudden.
Good!
Since we've found the reason
we can figure things out, step by step.
The fact that you were able to convey your thoughts to me may have healed you by 50% already.
Then, let's see...
What would be the best approach for you?
I think we might have to test things a bit.
When is your next competition?
Thank you for the ride. Bye.
Ah what is that? What's wrong with her?
If she's going to see him, she should dress better to appeal to him!
That way, my hyung would say, "Oh, Bok Joo, you look lovely today."
But if she goes looking like that... Aish!
I can drop you off in front of your place. It's not polite to  make a girl walk alone at night like this.
No, it's really okay. I can make it home from here with my eyes closed.
And, I have to stop by the market and pick up a few things.
Okay. See you at the clinic.
Oh, and don't forget to stretch before you sleep.
Yes. Good bye, Doctor.
Oh my, oh my. You're going to break your back Bok Joo!
Aish, what am I going to do with you Bok Joo?
You like him? You like him?
Where are you going? Where is she going? You don't ride the subway.
Toilet
Three, two, one!
Okay! She came out.
Oh, am I catching a cold? That dumb dress!
Hey. Who is this?
Our school's weightlifting fairy, Kim Bok Joo!
Are you keeping tabs on me 24 hours a day? How can we meet all the time?
I know, it amazes me too. Why do I always see you?
What's that?
It's nothing, so mind your own business.
By the looks of it, you went to a musical.
You didn't get all dressed up in a dress and heels, did you?
Are you crazy? Why would I get all dressed up?
I was just asking if you did.
My brother really hates the extra feminine type.
Really?
No. It's a lie.
What kind of a man doesn't like a girl who gets all dressed up?
Hey, you're making fun of me because you already saw me, aren't you! You, evil man!
Oh, I spent all that money and got cursed.  I'm feeling really wronged here.
Then, who told you to make fun of me?
I spent all my allowance for the month on those tickets!
Buying the tickets? Well, thanks for that.
Of course, you should be grateful.
So, was it fun with Hyung?
It wasn't bad, and I got to ride in his car.
Ooh!!! A drive! You did everything!
Bok Joo, there is danger!
♬ What? ♬
♬ What?♬
Wow, that could've been bad!
Hey, something bad could've happened if I didn't have good reflexes!
Why is he driving like that?!
Hey! Come here, bastard!
Jeong Joon Hyeong!
Why? Are you going to go? You should lie down a little longer.
No, I'm okay now.
It seems like a temporary stomach cramp, so I'm giving you some painkillers.
This is an antacid.
Make sure to take this after meals.
Thank you.
Stomach cramps are usually caused by hyperacidity induced by  stress. Are you under a lot of stress these days?
Yes, a little bit.
By any chance, because of a man?
Wait, who in the world is he?
That stupid guy who makes such a pretty girl end up in this state?
You should dry your hair first. It's soaked through right here.
Are you giving a disease and offering a remedy? You'd better shut up.
Give it here, give it. How could you dry anything like that?
Forget it!
Stay still, I'll dry it for you.
Aigoo, I'm so sorry. What should I do about this?
Forget it. You do it yourself! I don't care whether you do it or not.
Who asked you to do it in the first place, you crazy punk?!
Hey, do you think Hyung can tell that you like him?
No. He probably can't even imagine it in his dreams. I don't want to get found out.
Men don't really like women who do weightlifting.
See, look! My hands are full of calluses. Who would like hands like this?
What's wrong with that? They're like medals because you exercise. Plus you feel safe when you walk at night.
I'd really like that.
You speak so well.
But it was still a good day. I got to have something like a date thanks to you.
I took a drive with him earlier, and it felt like I was Cinderella riding her pumpkin carriage.
It was like going straight back to reality when the clock strikes twelve.
But she at least becomes the prince's wife later on.
I know, right? I don't  even see any movies that don't have happy endings because I feel kind of down.
Have you heard that there's a toad in that fountain over there that grants wishes?
- What?
- You don't know?
Heol. Are you really a student at Haneul? It's a very famous legend.
You know our school sunbae athletes that won gold medals? They all say it was thanks to that toad.
You really need to work on your creativity.
No, it's true! I'm saying this because you don't know.
It's said that if you just pray desperately, it'll grant your wishes without any questions or arguments.
Just try asking it once for things to go well with Hyung.
As soon as you open your mouth, lies just—
Hey, did you catch a cold?
I have been feeling pretty painful pressure on my sinuses since earlier.
I'm sorry, but I have some important plans later on, so I can't catch a cold.  I'll leave first.
♬   Living in a dream all day  ♬
Why are you being like this?
♬   Will you come to me,  you and I in my dream?  ♬
I told you I can't catch a cold, seriously!
It's going to last forever! My germs are super strong and my colds get really bad.
Virus, swag!
Hey, you better watch out if I catch your cold.
I'll seriously... I'll give it right back to you by kissing you! You just wait.
Should I go with you together? Why are you leaving already?
Hey, Swimmer Jeong! Let's go together!
♬  I was still wandering and searching for a dream  ♬
I guess I really did catch a cold. Ah, how annoying.
Are you sick? Your face is totally white.
I'm all right.
I have a cold too. Does this room have bad luck or something today?
Why can't I open it?
Give it here. I'll do it for you.
- It's okay. I'll do it.
- Hey, just give it here.
Forget it, I said I'll do it!
I'm sorry. I was a bit oversensitive.
If Bok Joo raises her weight class, she definitely could win.
Hyung, they are asking something more?
What are you doing right now? The chicken is all burnt!
Aigoo, aigoo. It's all burnt, all burnt! What should I do about this?
What were you doing, burning the chicken? Were you falling asleep or something?
No. I was thinkingm briefly  of something else.
I'm going to focus on his upper body for now, so I'm planning to keep the amount of weight he lifts the same and increase his reps.
Yes. He will also have to increase the frequency of his training with the pro team, right?
Let Woong Gi do that on his own. He'll be able to regulate that much.
What a relief that Woong Gi made up his mind!
But either way, it'll be kind of hard on Bok Joo, won't it?
It will be hard to talk to her about it without Sunbae's consent. It'll be hard for Bok Joo, too.
Oh, you have come.
Sunbae, why did you come all the way here? You should have called. I would have gone to you.
You clearly know why I'm here. I'm busy, so let's just get to the point.
Yes, Sunbaenim. Please speak.
About what you said before... Bok Joo's increase of weight.
I wonder what's going on?
How would I know?
Ah, I feel so uneasy.
I'm curious. I'm so curious. It's driving me crazy!
Stay still! I can't focus on anything, so just stay still.
Bok Joo, hurry up and come out!
Huh? My weight class?
That's right. You're surprised, right?
Of course, you are. Even I'm shocked.
Professor and I think that it's more than possible for you.
Of course, it's not the norm to raise your weight class a few months before a match.
But you have strength, and you've had an unofficial record title in the 63-kilo weight class.
That was when I was in my best condition, though.
So you should increase it quickly. We'll help you and take responsibility for you.
You're well aware of this, but the competition in the 58-kilo group is incredibly intense right now.
It doesn't matter how skilled you are. If your condition isn't good on the day of the match, then the color of your medal will change in your weight class.
But there is no representative weightlifter for the 63-kilo group, either domestically or internationally,
since Weightlifter Jang Geum Ran retired.
We're not telling you this to make you feel burdened, but if you do move up to the 63-kilo group,
then Bit Na or other weightlifters can also dream of getting a medal in the 58-kilo match.
That's right. This is a win-win, Bok Joo. It's advantageous to you, and it also gives the other kids an opportunity.
It's more than possible if you just raise your weight about 3 or 4 kg.
Woon Gi is also getting a program together for it, since we spoke with him about it.
If you just make up your mind, then we can really attempt this.
But I want to talk to Father first.
He's already heard about this, you brat. He gave us his permission.
What?! Father did?
Why did you give them permission without even talking to me, seriously?!
Hey, brat. Do you think it was an easy decision for me?
I couldn't get a wink of sleep all night because I was thinking about it all night.
But still, why did you decide such an important thing all yourself?!
Do you think that it's easy to raise my weight class like inflating a balloon?
You know that it's harder to gain weight than to lose because you have to make muscles!
I know, kid. I know, but life itself is a challenge.
And a weightlifter's mindset is to always challenge themselves and achieve their goals.
As your coaches said, there are more chances to get a medal.
It's a good strategy.
Father!
I have to fry the chicken! A delivery order came in, so I'm hanging up. We'll talk later.
Father! Ah, he seriously just does whatever he wants to! Even to the end, he hangs up as he pleases!
Calm down, Weightlifter Kim.
It is hard, but it's not totally impossible, right?
That's right. Gaining weight isn't that hard for you.
That's not it... I'm seriously going crazy!
What's making you go so crazy that you stamp your feet? We'll help you.
That's right. We'll eat with you in the name of friendship.
That's not it!
Why does it have to be now? Ah, seriously!
Don't run! You'll lose weight!
Hey, Weightlifter Kim! Let's go together!
Dad does whatever he wants.
Seriously! Ah!
What? Do you want to compete at the Central Bank Cup Meet?
Why? The competition is small, so it's not really that helpful to you.
Please just view it as practice.
Well, in fact, you have to try it out  frequently in the actual meets so  you can get over your problem with starts.
It's a praiseworthy thought for the first time in a while.
Hey, if you do,  you'd better get a medal with the same guts that rejected the offer of being Choi Tae Won's training partner.
No. If Roberto kicks a goal at the early morning soccer clubs' game, everybody will speak ill of him.
Look at this punk, playing around!
Alright then. Go ahead and try it.
Yes, sir. I understand.
Kim Bok Joo, I caught your cold in the end. I caught it.
Why does it have to be now, of all times?
Hey, Fatty!
Hey, how are you going to take responsibility for this?
I really caught a cold because of you! I've got a match next week, so how are you going to take responsibility for this?!
Shut up. I'm already in a super bad mood.
Is there something wrong with you?
I don't know. Everything's all twisted up.
You looked all happy just yesterday. What's wrong now?
My coach told me to raise my weight class.
Your weight class?
Oho, Kim Bok Joo! Are you finally moving up to the heavy class?
But, what's the problem?
Hey! Right now,
my situation is up in the air. And there's the thing about the clinic too.
Hey, that's not a problem!
You're going there to see Hyung, not because your goal is to lose weight.
If you're not going to quit weightlifting, then you should get yourself together and do what needs to be done.
That's true, but...
Hey! You speak really easily when it doesn't involve you!
Do you think the world is all that simple?
Of course, what would a kid like you know about life?
Your parents are well off, you're naturally talented, you're good-looking, and you've even got women lined up behind you.
I'm the idiot for trying to talk to you as if we're on equal ground. Buzz off, you well-off punk!
Wow.
Who are you getting mad at right now? Look at her, yelling at me after she gave me a cold!
Weightlifting Department
"You should do what you have to do. Do what needs to be done." That jerk, he talks so easily when it's not about him.
Oh, I'm so pissed off, seriously.
Hey, Bok Joo!
What? What is it?
What, what?
Ah... I left my training log over there.
Oh, and here I thought...
So, what about it? Did you think about it?
Pardon?
Yes, well...
To raise your weight, you'll have to get into the special program right away. Everything is already planned well.
But, then I...
Um, well, I'll... Yes, I'll try it.
You really want to?
You want to try it out, huh?
Professor! Professor!
Bok Joo said she'd try it. She made up her mind.
Oh really, Bok Joo? You really want to try it?
You thought well.
We told you last time, right? This is completely possible for you.
That's right! If our Bok Joo can't do it, then who could?
Hey, your dad will be so happy!
Then let's start carrying out the project today!
I'll take charge of Woon Gi. And Coach Choi, you take charge of Bok Joo.
Yea! It seems like the top structure is being established.
Alright, Coach. Are you confident?
Of course! I have a venomous side as well.
That's scary.
Bok Joo, you'll have to make sure you don't get bit by Coach.
Hey!
♬   Will you be spinning in delight?  ♬
♬   I think you're so pretty.  ♬
♬   However we shouldn't do it... Both   ♬
Oh!
Another tray.
♬   confession and repentence  ♬
♬   in red hot passion are clumsy, but  ♬
♬   we each have big and little concerns worrying us.   ♬
Another tray.
Coach, I can't eat any more of this. There's a lot of food on the tray too.
You won't gain more than a few pounds just with that amount.
You should have another tray.
♬   In our personal heaven we are starting to search for a wonderful day.  ♬
♬   From now on when it's hard if we give  up by turning around  ♬
♬   we will reconsider. Tomorrow we will run two steps forward.  ♬
Ah, it was going so well. Why did it suddenly increase?
No.
No, I guess I didn't control my diet well.
It's right.
I was the one that didn't do well.
It's okay. Your weight can fluctuate in the beginning.
Instead, we'll do two procedures together.
Lie down.
That's weird. You definitely went up one kilo yesterday.
Why did it go back down by 0.5 kg?
Hey, Kim Bok Joo. Did you possibly
go to the bathroom a lot today?
Yes, a little.
Hey, this won't do. Let's fill you up again.
Let's go have snacks and bosam!
Do harder. Woon Gi has already gained by 0.6 kg.
No, not yet. I have far to go yet to reach the planned amount.
Bok Joo is going to make it soon, too.
Hey, Bok Joo. You eat this meaty part right here.
Wow, your cold is dragging on way too long.
Of course, you pretty much live in the water all day because of the competition, so is there any way you wouldn't catch a cold? Aigoo, and you aren't taking any medicine.
But Hyung, why are you going to that competition?
Isn't that for kids who just started to gain some experience?
Hey, you losers! Those who don't have the good times always question the level of the meet.
Learn something, learn, you punks!
When you're freshman or sophomore—
You just eat up too, you bastard.
Hey, you're all done eating, right? We'll get up first.
I didn't eat it all. I'm not finished.
- You clueless bastard.
- I'm not finished yet!
You have a competition?
It seems like you caught a cold, so what are you going to do? You cough for a long time when you catch a cold.
You're a threat.
You've reached stalker level now. Is it fun for you?
Is there any way it would be fun?
It's exhausting, hurts my pride, and is so embarrassing I want to die.
But I want to grasp a fragment of a straw right now.
I have only you as my straw.
You're mistaken. I'm not a straw.
I'm just me.
I got it. I'll leave. Finish eating before you go.
You probably won't even be able to take medicine for your cold, so you should at least eat.
It seemed like you were rejected by Jeong Joon Hyeong in there.
Doesn't it look bad? You still have a title of our school queen.
That's why you kept rejecting me?
It's not too late for you to come to me. I'm confident I can treat you better than that punk Jung Joon Hyung.
Get lost, bastard.
I don't want to, I don't want to! I'm not eating all this today!
I don't want to, don't want to! I don't want it!
Why can't you eat it?
All you have to do is to get a few pieces of chicken legs and swallow them down with the broth, then it's all over!
I intentionally got all this together and even put ginseng and abalone in it and boiled it for several hours for you to eat it!
I ate three trays of food at the school cafeteria!
My stomach has limits too! How am I supposed to just swallow down food all the time?!
Ah, seriously.
Pick it up! Just stay still!
Bok Joo, I know it's not easy, but just close your eyes and live like you're dying for right now.
From what I can see, you definitely can win. I'm telling you, I've got a hunch about this!
What do you know just because you got a hunch, Dad?!
I'm the one who isn't confident. It's me!
Ah, just eat it! Ah, my arms are going to fall off!
We are under negotiation. Keep holding this!
- You're so loud, you damn guy!
- How am I supposed to hold this?
- Ah, you're here, Sunbaenim?
- Oh, Coach Choi!
Why did you prepare all of this? It must've been hard.
I'm also planning on feeding Bok Joo some pizza.
Oh, really? Then, let's head inside.
- Should I carry it for you?
- No, it's fine. Carrying things is my job, you know.
Hey Bok Joo, let's eat.
You didn't have to..
How the heck am I supposed to eat all that?!
Definitely, Athlete Kim, your dad is an amazing cook!
He is totally a "flav-wiz"! Flavor wizard!
That's right. But hey, you even get total support like this.
Seeing how you can eat as much as you want, it's not that bad. Right?
That's right. It's way better than having to eat like a bird like the rhythmic gymnasts.
Eat a lot. Why are you just picking at your food?
Yeah, here, have some pizza. Want me to pick out a drumstick for you? You like drumsticks.
You said you wished a chicken had four legs.
It's because I'm so sick of eating chicken.
I think if I cried, chicken broth would come out as tears!
You're right, I am quite full.
At this rate, all three of us might need to raise the weight class together?
Why are you saying such weak words?
Our forever helping friend, Noona Soda is there.
Please help us, Noona Soda!
I have some coins so I'll grab some.
Ah, seriously.
Don't worry about it. You'll lose weight. Let me do it.
I'll do it.
"Miss Kim Bok Joo, your appointment has been set for 4:30 tomorrow. The J Obesity Clinic."
They said you have an appointment tomorrow at the J Obesi—
♬  What?!  ♬
Hey, why are you going to an obesity clinic?
No. It's not that. Come here.
Hey!
Why would you go to the obesity clinic when you have to gain weight?
What have you been doing lately?
Nan Hee...
I can hold this.
- You've worked hard today.
- You too Doctor.
So, it's that man? Not Jeong Joon Hyeong?
So, that person is that jerk Jeong Joon Hyeong's older brother.
So, you... As an excuse to see him
you spent all that money to enroll in the program.
And you've been going around lying to us. And in order to keep Jeong Joon Hyeong quiet, you lifted those rice sacks.
That's what you're saying right now, right?
- Yes.
- You crazy girl!
I know I deserve getting cursed. You're right that I am totally crazy.
A person in her right mind wouldn't do this. And so I tried hard not to, but...
I kept thinking about him, and I kept getting confused, so I had no choice.
And... I just wanted to see his face.
I acknowledge it.
He's so much better than Jeong Joon Hyeong.
He's a total man. With muscles, and strong.
Right? My doctor is cool, right?
Yeah, totally cool. He is handsome as well.  And he's even a doctor!
You little rascal, pretending not to have any interest in men.
You totally have a good eye for men!
But, exactly, how did you first meet?
Don't tell me it was like Kang Dong Won in the movies... when he holds the umbrella for you in the rain
It's not like that, is it?
♬   I'm dreaming   ♬
♬   I'm dreaming of everlasting happiness   ♬
- It was like that!
- Seriously? He held the umbrella like this.
Ah, really?! Oh my god, that's so heart-pounding!
- He's totally good looking, right?
- Nan Hee wants that too!!
What do we do? Now you have someone.
For Song Si Ho
This ginger and date tea is good for getting rid of colds, make sure you drink it - Mom
Hey, hey! What are you doing? Go rest!
You have a competition tomorrow and you are still sick! You have to take care of yourself.
Just after I watch this.
Hey, watching this won't make something happen for you. Just rest.
Ah, okay! I got it.  You're not even my mom, but are nagging like it!
Hey, stop being difficult and get some sleep.
It's me Song Si Ho. Can you not tell Joon Hyeong and meet me outside for a little bit?
Sorry, you were probably surprised because I called you out so suddenly.
Here.
What is this?
It's a ginger and date tea. I heard Joon Hyeong has a competition tomorrow.
If I gave it to him, I didn't think he would drink it.
What is it?
It's hot love.
What is it? Ginger tea?
Don't ask, don't question. Just drink it all up.
Just think of it as medicine.
It's good.
I'm finally starting to feel better.
That's good.
That's why, you jerk, I told you to stay warm!
So, what I'm saying is that since your body and heart are cold you are more susceptible to viruses and, what is this... oh...
I have to go to the bathroom. It's really urgent. I'll be right back. Drink all that up.
What is he talking about?
And do you know how sexy his voice is?
It's not too high or too low. It's like honey!
It makes me think this sound should be like the prince's voice that Snow White heard when she woke up.
Are you serious? I only saw him but didn't get to hear his voice!
When he laughs, he gets a slight wrinkle near his eyes
and it shows up the whiteness of his teeth. It's really marvelous.
The heart throbs and melts
And the thing that totally made me fall for him. And this is very important.
It's none other than his... thoughtfulness.
I've never met someone with such great manners!
You know, where it's not contrived, but it's just his character.
When I'm with him, I feel like I've become the most beautiful woman.
I don't know because I've never been treated that way before.
Regardless, it's a total fantasy.
He's kind, gentle, strong,
to the point where I can't believe that Jeong Joon Hyeong is his younger brother. He's a total man!
Hey, listening to you makes feel I'm meeting him personally.
What do you mean meeting him?
No way, you're not going to fight me for him, are you? I have to be more careful.
You're the kind that always just acts on your instincts.
No matter how much I want him, do you think I would ever take your man?
My man? Ahhhh!
What are you guys doing here?
What do you mean? We came to pee.
- We were going out. Let's go.
- Did you guys, by chance,
speak ill of me? You're not supposed to do that! You two just left by yourselves earlier.
No way! What is there to say bad about you?
Of course! Don't say such nonsense! Let's go, let's go.
Hey, do you think everything will get done in one go?
If you want to gain weight, you have to eat a lot.
Thank you, Soon Ok.
Oh, Soon Ok, can you get me some water?
I think the food is stuck because I ate this meat too quickly.
Hey, here's some water.
You should eat more slowly.
Oh, it finally went down.
Oh, Athlete Kim, you look good today.
Here, have some more.
Are you going now? It's 6:00.
But you are going like this? Really?
Why? Does it look weird?
Yes, it looks weird.
You said 6:00, right? Just five minutes.
Okay. I tried my best.
Thank you, Teacher.
Let's go!
Are you really going to go?
Yes.
Okay. Let me take a look.
Since you're going this time, do well, you brat!
I got it, okay? Go back in.
If a friend is going to a competition, I should go watch. Ugh, why do I have to go train?
So go and do your best. You swim worse than me.
Ah, this little well-entitled punk. I got it, okay?
I'm going to stick my neck out there and do my best! So go you little bastard. I dare you to not win first.
You got touchy, you cute bastard.
I'm going.
Do your best for real!
Focus on the start!
It's roasted abalone this time? You fed me abalone chicken ginger soup last time!
Those were just regular abalones from the market.
These are abalones fresh from the sea this time! I called someone
whom I haven't' talked to in ten years to get this for you, you brat!
So I'm saying just make some time later and come here.
And don't bring your friends with you! Even for you, it's not enough.
Only 30 abalones were brought.
Ah, okay. I'm hanging up.
Where are you going? By any chance, to the clinic?
Why do you ask when you know exactly where I'm going?
I'm going to a competition. Why don't you give me some positive energy?
Wouldn't someone who's already well-off do good?
I do not wish for your success. Make mistakes!
That the ill-tempered! Seriously. I've already been so nervous even if you didn't say so, but you speak unkindly.
You're dead.
Hey! Joon Hyeong, seriously! Such a crazy bastard, seriously.
Ah, you gained weight again.
Bok Joo, why can't you meet my eyes?
I'm sorry, Doctor, for disappointing you.
Ah, you don't need to be sorry towards me. After all, this is all for you.
It's hard to control your eating, huh? And I bet the people around you are no help as well.
Yes.
You have to be careful of snacks after dinner. But our human culture life happens  at night in our country.
Indeed, a lot of the clinic patients say they want to be treated at on a desert island.
I know, right? It's not like I can stop seeing my friends, though.
You can work hard and bring down your weight, so let's start a procedure after you change.
Yes.
Ah, Joon Hyeong has a competition today.
I sent him a message to not be nervous and to do well.
but he hasn't sent me a message. Probably because he has no time to do.
I'm sure he'll do well. He has a lot of self confidence.
He just looks like that on the outside. He's actually very fragile.
He really had to shed blood and make his mind up to go to this match.
He was disqualified for a false start at an international swimming competition two years ago.
His training time is better than making the national team cut.
But after that incident, he kept making start mistakes at important competitions.
I think that first shock became a traumatic experience for him.
What is this? He pretends he's strong all alone.
Ah, I gave him my cold and talked badly to him without even knowing about it.
Aigoo, your mouth! Stupid mouth.
If Jeong Joon Hyeong  does bad, I feel guilty, so please let him do well.
And, what was it, a trauma? I hope that he can quickly get better and get a stronger constitution.
Please!
When those symptoms come to you, the best thing to do is to not focus on those symptoms.
When you start becoming nervous, turn your thoughts to something else.
Focusing on your breathing, or doing things like counting backwards would more than likely be effective.
Ten, nine, eight...
Seven, six, five...
Four...
Three, two...
The 11th Central Bank Cup Swim Meet will start soon...
One.
Please, Joon Hyeong, please.
Ready.
Five, four, three...
One.
In the first place, Donga University's Lee Sang Geun.
In second place,  Cheongju City's Choi Jae Hyeok.
In 3rd place, Kyeongjin  Athletics Association's Park Jun Soo.
In fourth place, Haneul Sports University's Jeon Joong Hyeong.
No, it's not here. He is not in the ranks.
This idiot! He should have done better! Doesn't that mean he got disqualified?
This little punk.
Jeong Joon Hyeong, are you all right? Cheer up!
Jeong Joon Hyeong, serves you right!
What should I write him? All these lines are so cringe-worthy.
Drink it all without leaving anything.
Drink it all.
Ah, if it hadn't been for this cold, I would have been first. Even if I am so luckless, I didn't think I'd be this unlucky.
That's why we're telling you. You should have come here before the competition.
Mom had studied the pharmacology and made this medication specially to give you.
I know, right. I think I'm being punished for thinking too lightly about this competition.
That's okay, my son. You said it was a small competition right? Shake it off and forget about it.
Did you talk with your brother?
Yes, of course. I'm going to go crazy from his nagging.
He's not even your mini-me, but he's gotten all of your worries.
Where are you?
- It's Fatty.
- Fatty?
Who is Fatty?
Someone. A very fun friend.
It sounds like a dog's name.
He said Fatty?
What's going on for you to message me?
I'm asking where you are.
Home. I'm about to go back to school.
He's going to get here soon.
What the heck, Kim Bok Joo? Why are you telling me to meet in front of the fountain?
What's up, Kim Bok Joo? What's that?
Here a toad.
It's not because you talked about a toad or anything,
but two or three color papers were lying around and I was bored.
Who knows? That could become a good luck talisman.
Ah, you really aren't good with your hands.
Look at how crinkled up this is.
Exactly how many times did you refold it?
Hey! Give it back!
Hey, how could you take something back after you gave it away?
I'll take it for now! I don't know if it'll give me good luck though.
Toad swag.
- Why are you plagiarizing?
- What?
You uglies go around saying this all the time. Swag.
Ahh, it seems different because I'm the one saying it, doesn't it?
It seems like it's become refined and cool.
What are you saying? Looking at how you're talking crap, you must have recovered from your cold a little. Are you okay?
Yeah. I'll get better. I took some medicine at home before I came too.
I'm sorry for talking badly to you earlier. I'm a little sensitive these days.
Hey, but you should take this chance to do well!
I know, right? Well, I trusted in my skills and just got too big-headed.
Hey, don't worry. In a short while, I'm going to cause a huge accident.
You just don't ask me for a hundred autographs or something later on.
I'm going to be in the Olympics around that time, though!
Possibly.
Let's go. There's a little time left until night attendance. I'll order you something to help you recuperate.
Really? What are you going to buy me?
There's something that makes you majorly strong. Just follow me with your mouth.
But why are you heading toward the school?
Ah, seriously, just wait a second.
- Hey, you want to ride it?
- Yeah! What is this?
Hey, no way, no no! The last time I gave you a ride, I was in bed for three days because my back hurt!
No, you can't, you can't.
Do you want to die, seriously?!
Aish! No, you can't!
Ah, I'm not going, I'm not going.
Ah, let's just hurry up and ride this and go!
I'm ordering food for you, but you're saying that I shouldn't ride your bike.
Jung Joon Hyeong, hurry up and ride it. Hurry. Hey!
- Hey, Jeong Joon Hyeong!
-The customer is not answering the phone. If you would like to leave a message...
Let me see whether you don't ride this in the end.
You said that you would ride it!
Hey! Should I throw this away?
Ah, seriously!
Who's this friend?
Introduce yourself. This is my dad.
Hello.
- This is—
- Ah!
- That credit bill!
- Yes that's right.
- You know him, Dad?
-Ah, from that time.
I came here once with friends, not knowing this place was yours.
What's the relationship between you two?
This is the first time Bok Joo has brought a male student home with her. This is quite interesting.
He's a childhood classmate and a swimmer at my school.
I brought him because I owe him something and am about to pay it back. You have a lot of abalones, right, Dad?
- Huh?
- Abalones.
What abalone?
The wild abalone.
You said that you got some wild abalone from Wando.
You've got a lot, right?
I didn't know you were classmates with Bok Joo.
Eat a lot.
This is  really  precious.
Hey, eat this.
No, you eat. I'm not really that hungry.
Hurry up and eat! I'm the type that can't stand having an unpaid debt.
You have to eat it quickly for your cold to get better.
- Father!
- What?
Oh, oh, oh! Eat comfortably. Comfortably.
Is it delicious?
Ah, seriously.
- Eat up!
- It's really fascinating
to see her like that with a man. Right, Hyung?
Ah, they are the wild abalones that were really hard for me to get, but a weasel-looking guy is eating them all.
Whether he looks a weasel or something, but he looks very decent even though I don't know whose family son is.
- Honestly, if you just look at their looks, Bok Joo is definitely lacking in that scene.
- Eat.
It's clear that she likes him more.
What foolishness! What's wrong with my Bok Joo?
Hey, I've got perfect 20/20 vision. How much better could it get?
Shut up, bastard.
Anyway, I don't like him.
His gaze with which he is looking at Bok Joo is sticky and tricky.
Who? Him?
From what I can see, he's in more danger. You can tell that Bok Joo likes him more just by looking.
What are you talking about? She said they were just friends.
Do you give abalone to someone who is just a friend?
Is our Bok Joo someone who would give up food to someone else?
She's giving it to that guy because she likes him.
Hey, where are we going?
Hey, stop pestering me and just follow me.
How pretty!
Our neighborhood is pretty, isn't it?
It's really pretty at nighttime. It's all sparkly.
Yes.
It's pretty.
But what's the cause of your start trauma?
What?
Ah, I heard from the doctor.
Is it something like anxiety before the match or something?
I don't know.
How did you start swimming? Your parents made you?
No. Because I liked the water.
I first learned swimming when I followed Hyung to a swimming pool one day,
and it was really comfortable and enjoyable for us.
Something about it was warm, and it felt like it was embracing me.
Oh, you're pretty in touch with your emotional side.
So your personality changed after you started competing?
It probably did.
It did. That's right.
That's why I started swimming,
but I'm now feeling a burden from it that I never even imagined I would feel because it's my college major.
I have to be concerned with the time for swimming and get pushed,  like being forced into a cockfight.
Without caring about being first place or second place,
If I were told to just weight lift, then I'd really enjoy exercising.
Hey, these damn rankings!
Hey, you damn rankings!
But... When you look at it, isn't that part of being an athlete? We should just endure it.
Hey! Cheer up!
I've got a pretty good eye for people, and you're definitely going to succeed.
There's something strong in your gaze.
Do you feel like you'll get sucked right into it?
Yeah. Totally and deeply.
It's pretty!
If it's getting colder, you can't even come here.
Aigoo, our Bok Joo's stomach is probably exploding right about now.
If she went because her father called her, then she'd at least eat some ginseng chicken soup.
But when I look at Bok Joo, I can see that gaining weight really isn't easy.
Of course not! Raising your weight class is way harder!
Bok Joo is having a really hard time gaining weight these days.
Diet Diary
My Diet Info
Name: Kim Bok Joo
Ah, with how I feel right now, I think I won't catch another cold for the next year!
Wow, so this is why people go on and on about wild abalone.
- Do you feel a bit stronger?
- Yeah, it's shooting way up.
I was wondering where your amazing stamina came from. As expected.
Let's eat together and cheer each other on. Athletics isn't something
that you see results from in just one or two days.
Your stamina has to be good for you to be able to fight mentally.
How long are you going to live that absurd double life?
I know, right? I'll have to end it soon.
Ah! Over there a toad!
Ah, seriously! Do you want to die?
For real! It's a toad this big! Ah, there it is, there it is!
I should seriously just—! You're trying to have fun because you like reactions!
If you keep doing this, there is a chance you'd be dead.
Ah, you seriously don't believe me. I told you, there was a toad this big!
Swag!
Since earlier, you... That's not it!
Swag.
Swag. That's how you do it. Do it again.
I'm saying you should try your best at it!
Oh, you're here! You must be tired, right?
Hey, I organized your bed and your desk!
Hey, okay. Thank you.
You're okay, right Joon Hyeong?
That's right. It's not like it was an important match. You just have to do well at the next one, that's all.
Did anyone say anything? I'm fine.
But I wasn't disqualified today.
Right, punk. As I expected, you're broad-minded.
It's when she does unexpected things that she's so cute.
Weightlifting Department
You should eat the meatballs on a skewer.
Bok Joo, do you want to eat more meatballs? I brought a lot.
- No, no. I'll take care of eating it myself. Thanks though.
- Okay.
Hey, but I don't see Coach today.
She was always stuck right by Bok Joo's side yelling, "One more tray!" at breakfast and lunchtime.
She must be oversleeping. Let's hurry up and finish eating. Otherwise, we'll be late for the class.
Father
Yeah, Dad. Why again? Did you make a beef soup this time?
Run over here right now. This instant.
Father,  why did you call me this early in the morning?
Oh, why are you here, Professor? Coach?
Diet Diary
What is it?
I asked what it is, wench!