Doctor, the next patient will be coming in.
Yes. Kim Bok Joo...
Oh. You, by any chance...
Yes, we met by chance a few weeks ago.
You are, right? You must be here for counseling.
Sit down, please.
Wow, I guess we do have some kind of connection.
Excuse me, Doctor.
Do you possibly like   Messi  ?
(Famous Argentine soccer player)
♬   WHAT?   ♬
Pardon?
It's my best tip.
Men are attracted to women who have interests in common with them.
What do guys like the most? Sports. Among sports, soccer!
He'll want to have a glass of alcohol with a woman who likes Messi.
Do you like Messi?
If you meant Messi, the soccer player?
Yes. Ah, yes.
I really like the soccer players. Among them, I really like Messi the most.
Of course, I like Messi.
He plays soccer very well. Even though he is small, he has an outstanding gut.
He really has an outstanding gut, doesn't he?
That's why I like Messi so much.
Ah... yes.
He also looks handso— Uh... really manly.
- Yes, that's right.
- Right?
Let's talk about soccer later. Shall we measure you first, Kim Bok Joo?
You don't need any specialized care.
Just diet and behavioral therapy.
It's more important to reduce weight healthily than to see an instant result.
Think it over enough and come back to enroll for the program when you decide to do it.
Diet therapy + Behavioral therapy = Basic program 590,000 won.
Five hundred—
Come back to enroll..
Come back to enroll.
Episode 3
Let it go.
After scanning your card, put the password...
What? Why only this much?
Uncle's last birthday present! Ah.
I bought a fall jacket needlessly. I should've bought socks!
Weight Enrollment Fee = 590,000₩; Current Balance = 395,402₩; Money Needed = 194,598₩
What should I do? I need 200,000 won more to enroll.
Should I tell Dad to pay me the wage that I've worked for as a part-timer?
No, should I lie to him I have to buy a pair of shoes for weightlifting?
Okay. That excuse about weightlifting is a good idea.
Yes, weightlifting!
- Weightlifting!
-   Check again if you left anything...
Hey, hey! Fatty! Hey!
What makes her that busy?
Look at her running.
No doubt that she is Kim Bok Joo. She has not changed a bit.
Patched here and there.
It'll become a green motorcycle.
Hyung! Let's just buy a new one. Please.
He (the scooter)  has done as much as he can if he has worked for 7-8 years.
Why will we buy a new one when we have a fine one? We can use it for fifty years more without any problem.
I didn't tell you, but how embarrassed was I when I rode this antique during delivery?
What's the difference between that and riding on the back of an old man?
Huh? Bok Joo?
What's matter at this time?
Just...  Is the scooter broken?
No, it fell by itself and only this part was broken a little bit.
Bok Joo, tell your father to switch the scooter.
What is this? Delivery is the most essential at the chicken place.
Be quiet! Won't you shut your mouth?  Talk after earning 10 won if you have a conscience.
What did you do well when you didn't get a dime, even though you worked as an extra or something?
What should I do since the head person is a wicked man?
Do I have any power? If I get on his bad side, I'm done for!
That's why you should focus on this business instead of wasting your time!
Take your mark!
Okay, okay!
Joon Hyeong, you swam well with streamline.
Just keep doing it like that.  Good job.
Okay, good job!
Here.
That's right!
Straighten your legs!
Make the large, smooth, and flowing movement with the ribbon.
Soo Bin, since your flexibility is very good, if you complement your accuracy, you'll make it to the nationals.
You know that, right? When you kick over, don't release the strength in your legs.
Just keep this up. You're doing great now.
Now, everyone! Clean up and we'll end practice here for today.
Who were the students that exceeded their weight limit?
Stay and do jump rope. If you don't lose weight by today, you can't go home.
Attention!
- Two, three...
- Thank you!
Si Ho.
You're not improving as much as I expected.
What could be the problem?
When I make  Penché Turn,  the central axis shifts a little bit.
If I strengthen the lower body muscles—
I don't think that will solve the problem.
You see Soo Bin improving these days, don't you?
She improved a lot.
That's why I'm saying this...what about receiving some special training in Russia during the upcoming break?
Russia?
Well, although it'll take up a bit of your funds,
It's very important how you spend time during winter break.
Discuss this with your mother.
Understand?
Where did Bok Joo go that she's not even answering her phone?
Did she go for delivery? Bok Chicken exploits her too much these days
There was no mistake.
Right.
Nice!
Hey, we were here first.
What's important about that? Huh? Whoever gets possession first is the owner.
What? Were you planning to watch the eating broadcast? Hey, what's the use of watching that?
You can't even eat anything because you're worried your weight will increase.
Then, why do you read fashion magazines? You can't even wear any of those clothes.
Right, Unni?
We don't read fashion magazines.
Bok Joo.
Where were you all day? You didn't even answer your phone.
- Should we go to the sauna?
- Sure, Unni.
Let's go.
Do you guys... have some money?
Money? I don't know, I have around $20. Why do you ask?
I have exactly $11. Why? Do you want to order pizza?
Ah, never mind. I'm going to go rest.
Hey, you just got here! Where are you going?
Hey! If we pool  our money, we can get at least one whole  pizza!
That's why I told you that we should have stopped her rhythmic gymnastics earlier.
It's not enough to move around from leased house to leased house after selling a house,
but if we spend any more on her, we'll have to live on monthly rent from now on. Do you understand?
So what do you want to now?!
As you said, we sold our house to come all the way here. How can we stop
when the summit is right in front of our noses?!
Whose ambition was that? It's yours! Si Ho didn't want it.
Who's going to benefit the most from her doing well?
For that poor girl, who is underweight and so nutrient deprived that she doesn't even get her periods,
do you think I'm not suffering over this either?!
What's up with you? You've been strange since earlier. Did you see a ghost in broad daylight? Why are you so out of it?
No, it's just that I thought of a question someone asked me yesterday.
What question?
She's a patient that came in for a consultation and the minute she sat down, she asked me if I liked Messi.
The soccer player? The one from Argentina?
Now that I think about it, I've always posed questions to patients,
but it's been a while since I've received questions myself.
And a question that's in line with my tastes too.
It must be a fresh experience, seeing you talk about a patient.
Was she pretty?
Well...
Well ... in my eyes, she was pretty.
Crazy wench! You're doing all sorts of things, seriously!
It's said there is no medicine for lovesickness. Come to your sense, please!
Ow, I think I'm going to die.
Ow! That hurts! Ah! Ah!
Hey, hey! You're going to break her spine! Stop!
Oh, Nan Hee! Are you okay? Hey!
Aigoo. No. It's very good, as I like being fully stretched.
What's wrong with you since yesterday, Athlete Kim? Is something troubling you?
No, my condition isn't very good right now.
By any chance, are you putting on a show so you won't have to go to the mountains tomorrow?
I smell something fishy.
Ah, that's right. Tomorrow is the mountain hike competition.
If we didn't have that, I could fly around the weightlifting room.
I don't know why our school schedules an event on weekends when we are  allowed to stay out.
I'm going to go wash my face.
Sure.
Sunbae! Hello!
Ah, what the—
I must have really gone crazy.
Why aren't you coming to enroll?
Aish. He even talks now.
I don't have any money and I have to go practice.
Please don't be like this.
Why aren't you coming to enroll?
Why are you doing this to me? Seriously, stop it!
I must really be losing my mind.
Ah! Don't smile at me. Omo, what should I do?
You don't have anything to worry about. If you just trust me and follow me—
I'm going crazy right now, I have to be—
UltraViolet rays are really dangerous to women. You should put this up.
- You have to carry a parasol. When it rains, umbrella...
-  I'm getting crazy like this.
Like this, ah ah ah...
Hold on! hold on, hold on.
I'm really going crazy.
You should stop now. I think you've drunk an entire pack already.
As expected, you're the best. You actually came out because your jerk of an ex-girlfriend asked you to.
Who was the one who threatened to wait all night if I didn't come out?
Did something happen?
Joon Hyeong, are you a gold spoon? ( She's asking if he is from a rich family.)
Or even a silver spoon?
No way, what silver spoon?
Just... around a bronze spoon?
If I could be born again, I want to be born into a rich family.
Whatever I do, I'll receive a ton of support like that, and  I won't have to be cautious of anything.
Even if I lived my life lazily, I'd still be married off to a nice household
somewhere safe and sturdy, like Pyeongchang.
A pretty house that has a garden.
Don't say things like this somewhere else. You'll lose your image.
Am I pathetic?
I'm desperate.
Do you know why you're miserable?
You always want something that's a step above reality.
Lower your greed a little bit.
Let's go. It's almost night-attendance time.
They are still warm, your hands.
Since we have things scheduled tomorrow, we have to go bed early.
Let's go.
Whenever I think about having to climb up that mountain tomorrow, I really hate it!
It's Saturday, but we can't even sleep in late. We might as well train or something.
A whole group of rhythmic gymnasts won't attend the event, using practice as the excuse.
Really?
If I knew that, I should have done rhythmic gymnastics too.
What crap are you saying right now? Joke with a conscience in mind, you wench.
Or should I lie that I pulled my hamstring in the morning?
It won't work with it. Sunbae Hyeong Cheol also got rejected earlier when he said he got hemorrhoids.
Aigh. It doesn't work with hemorrhoids.
Are there only one or two who have it in our department?
Last year, Bok Joo was even in and out of the hospital too.
Hey, why are you pulling me into this?
That's okay. A hemorrhoid is almost like a medal to people who use muscles.
In any case, unless we have a serious injury, we have to climb that mountain.
There were so many kids who made up excuses that the Dean placed a monetary prize on 1st place.
Prize?
How much?
Is it 300,000 won? The dean put his personal money into a prize.
It's a kind of event.
If it's 300,000 won, it'll be more than enough for solving the enrollment problem.
This is my chance.
A fate-like chance. If that's the case...
I will kill myself going up that mountain.
We're here.
Come down quickly!
Luckily, we recovered from food poison completely.
The weather is great today.
I know you all don't like mountain climbing
but this event is an event that we can't avoid.
At the most, it's 338.2 meters tall.
Fine, I'll place 1st and win that $300.  And so ...
So come to me, Kim Bok Joo.
So?
Have strength, Bok Joo. You can do it. Fighting!
So...
So what are you going to do? You have to overcome.
Even though the mountain is high, that can't be higher than your dream!
I"m saying that this isn't a big deal.
What is our weightlifters' strength? Even though we keep being stepped on, what is...
Spirit of the weed.
Of course. The spirit of weed! Being stepped on, it's still the spirit of the weed.
Hey. Today, I didn't expect you to get first.
All of you, don't give up in the middle.
All of you climbing to the top is today's goal and challenge.
Got it? The weightlifting club is fat or a fat club or something...
Or we can't climb or something, such nonsense talking...
We show those who speak such nonsense that we can do it, understand?
Yes.
Are you all ready?
That's right! Let's heat up our heart!
Ready, go!
- Right, go!
- Go quickly.
Let's go!
Hey, Kim Bok Joo.
Hurry up.
Ah, who are you?
Go. Go.
♬   Following the rain and a rainbow   ♬
♬   in our personal heaven we are   ♬
Hey, hey hey.
I'm so tired.
Hey, are you okay?
Senior. Senior.
He sprained his ankle when he was getting off the bus.
I don't think he can climb the mountain anymore.
Really? Is it really bad?
- Yes.
- Where?
Right here.
Senior!
Are you okay? Hey, right leg!
Don't try any funny tricks.
Jeong Joon Hyeong. Make sure you reach the peak today, and never fall behind me.
The moment you see my back, I'll punish you and your classmates together, understand?
Yes.
Go.
♬   The tree of dreams I'm growing in my heart  ♬
♬   is bearing sweet fruit  ♬
Hey, was it obvious?
It was obvious.
♬   Love unitl they open full of sunshine  ♬
Kim Bok Joo let's go together!
- I can't go any further.
- Why is she like that? Did she eat something wrong?
I don't know. I can't go any further.
Mom...
Hey. It's the crazy guy. The crazy.
My friend. I'm going first. Take care of behind.
Hey, hey, wait. I'm afraid of him.
I'm so scared.
Hey let's go together!
Fatty!
I look at you again. Looking at your size, I'm 100% sure that you'd give up in the middle
Is your mentality good, or your stamina good?
Hey! Hey! Am I a ghost?
Talk.
I don't have any strength to talk. Go.
Oh, you got determined properly.
Are you going to get 1st place at this rate?
Go, Kim Bok Joo. I'll become your strength for you.
Go on up Bok Joo!
Let's go together.
Beautiful Challenge
One. Two.
Good.
Hey, Fatty! Are you all right?
It's because I'm worried I'll have to carry you if you faint.
If I pull my back, you're not going to take responsibility. What are you going to do? Will you call for help?
Just go, would you?
Let's go!  Go up!  Hurry and go!
Leave, will you?
Don't do that!
Let's go. Find strength, Kim Bok Joo.
Bok Joo! Oh no, what do we do?
What do we do, what do we do?
I'm really sorry. I really didn't do it on purpose.
I was really trying to help. You looked like you were having a hard time so I was just trying to help.
I think it's time for them to slowly come.
Because of a monetary prize, the competition for the first place will be very intense.
Should we start getting ready?
Hey, I'm sorry.
I was just trying to help because you seemed to be having a hard time.
What? Are you going to hit my head again?
Hold on to me as you go. You're having a hard time.
Stop!
Hold on to me and go.
Hey. Get on me. I'll take responsibility because I created this mess.
Well, is it going to be a big deal that my back's getting pulled? Get on.
Bok Joo, I got injured!
My knee hurts a lot.
She won't even turn around once.
So many people have already climbed up here!
Anyhow, no doubt they are the athletes.  They all have such a will to win.
Ah... There was a monetary prize. There is no hope for that.
Hey. Let's take care of your ankle first.
Let's go to the medical nurse and ask for an ice pack.
Get lost.
- What?
- I said get lost, punk!
Classmate? My ass. When did we see each other?
Why are you lingering around me and interfering?
Please just mind your own business.
You ruined everything.
By the way, the way she talks is disappointing.
Hey. What should we eat? Pigs feet? Pork belly?
If not, then shall we eat the draft beer with pork sausage and potato chips, all together,  a lot.
Then, I'll vote for number three. Let's eat them until we die.
I also call for number three.
Athlete Kim, put in your vote.
I don't have an opinion.
Wow.
Soon Ok, did I hear her wrong?
Did Bok Joo say she doesn't have an appetite?
Hey, why are you like this? You said your ankle was fine.
Hey, it's enough if you went up to the top of the mountain.
Yeah.
Hey. It's been a while since we came out. Are you seriously going to be like this?
Seriously!
Let's go, Bok Joo. Na Hee is hungry.
My stomach skin is sticking to my back.
Hey Bok Joo,  hurry. She's at it again.
Hurry.
Na Hee, I'll go with option 3. Be quiet.
How long will I have to hear that?
One shot! I don't need anyone else except you guys! Get lost!
Now you're acting like Kim Bok Joo.
Wow Bok Joo one shot! Swag!
Bok Joo.
Bok Joo. Cheers, to your healthily losing weight.
Hey, hey. You don't have much of a drinking capacity.
She has already drunk three glasses full.
Why are you like this? Drink slowly.
Forget it. It's been so long since we've had a break.
When will we ever drink again, if not today?
- When will we?
- Ow, that hurts.
Hey. You're hitting the ahjussi.
I know. I know. Okay.
She started acting drunk after all.
Let's hurry and eat and get out here.
Na Hee is going to take a selfie.
But did you talk to Joon Hyeong?
Isn't he having a hard time because of his disqualification?
That's why he agreed to get counseling from my senior.
Oh, really? That's great!
Good job. I was so worried, although I couldn't show it in front of him.
Mental training is also important for athletes. It'll help him a lot.
Oh? This kid knows when we're talking about him.
Yeah, Joon Hyeong. Did you eat?
We're eating Octopu— No pancake-wrap. (Rhyme in Korean)
I just ate with Tae Gwon.
I won't be that late.
Even if you miss me, bear with it for a little. Mother, I love you.
Is she your mom or your girlfriend? Whenever I look at you, you're quite cringe-worthy.
It's not just "quite." I really love my mom a lot.
Oh, oh, oh? Seriously...
- Ah, that's cold!
- Oh!
- We're so sorry!
- Aish, forget it!
I'm sorry. My friend is too drunk.
We're sorry.
If you're going to drink, then drink nicely.
Hey, just leave them alone. We'll lose our appetite for alcohol. Sit down, sit.
These wenches come here and only drink uselessly.
Hey! If you're doing to drink, then drink nicely. What are you planning to become?
A weightlifter.
Ah, imagine if she were my sister...
I would shave her head bald and lock her up, ugh.
What did you just say to my friend?
What? What? What, what, what? I'm going to say what I want with my mouth, so what?
Ugh, you have no fear. Huh?
Are you majoring in physical education? Ah, no wonder.
Hey, stop it. Those losers won't know anything.
What did you just say? Los—
- Should I really do something worth being called a loser?!
- Ah, ah!
- Calm down, calm down.
- Aish, seriously.
Hey, this place is not so good. The patrons are so-so as well.
I'm tired after climbing the mountain. Let's just drink a bit here and leave.
Hey!
Don't get so worked up.
- Hey.
- Why  are you, wretches, degrading us? You cowards!
Hey, aren't those our classmates? The weightlifters, right?
- Hey, stop it. Let's leave.
- I'm the one that's speechless.
Hey, I don't want to fight with someone like you, so just apologize and get lost.
We already apologized, so you get lost.
"You"? How dare you say that to an elder? You lack basic manners.
- Get lost.
- Am I a candle? Why are you telling me to get lost?  ("Get lost" and "blow out" sound the same)
The only candle in the situation, you, deserves capital punishment right now.
Your brain deserves capital punishment more.
- Stop it! Stop it!
- Hey, just forget it and get lost already!
Look at the way he talks, capital punishment, capital punishment!
What is this? Are you a woman?
- Then am I man?
- You're uglier than a man.
Your face deserves capital punishment more!
Ah, I should just—
Is it okay to disparage women?
- Stop it.
- Let go of me.
Ah, such ugly wenches!
Hey, let's go.
Hey, do you think I'll go easy on you just because you're a woman?
Hey, do you think you can do anything if you're majoring in physical education? Huh?!
Why would that even come up right now? You were the one that cursed us out first!
Wow, if I do well enough, she might hit me.
Hit me. Hit me. I said, hit me!
Ah, how dare you?!
Seriously, do you even have anything? Ugh, you all don't even look like girls.
What? This bastard!
Hey! I'm a girl too, you bastards! Even if I'm fat, I'm a girl too!
Ah seriously!
Hey, hey, stop!
Hey, hey, let go!
Ah, seriously!
- Let's go.
- Hey, let's fight!
Hey, hey.
Hey! Stand up straight! We can't go anywhere until you become somewhat sober.
Sit down here.
Okay, I'm sober now. I'm completely sober now. Want to see?
Wear this. It's cold.
What dramatic show is this?
It's been a while since we've left school so I thought we could all lift our spirits up a bit.
Those mean bastards, ugh!
I'm sorry, I lost my temper again.
Hey, you're seriously a problem. What if you really got hit?
Even if we weight-lift, our opponents are men.
They didn't look like nice men either.
Those bastards were really careless with their words.
Ah, I'm doing all sorts of things. One of my friends is a fighter and another is drunk...
If I let her drink again, I'll be a fool.
Annoying... I'm cold.
Unnie, I'm cold.
Ugh, now, drink this and just let it go.
Ugh, I almost hit a girl today.
Watch your words. Were those kids girls? They're gangsters.
I really despise girls with strong personalities.
Even if you give them to me, I won't take them.
Hey, will you really not take it even if they're given to you?
Well, maybe one is okay.
Right, you're right! You know, those girls have a special taste of their own. They're rough now,
but later on, when they turn docile and submissive, they listen so well. That's awesome.
You know Kyung Woo Shik, right? His girlfriend is his girl crush.
That bastard said that she's killer.
Hey, what the heck? Explain in detail.
You know, instead of those stick thin women—
- Excuse me.
- What?
-Jeong, how are you? Do you think you're sober now?
Yeah. I feel much better now.
Seeing that you're able to hold a conversation, you're awake. Her eyes are coming back too. Let's go.
Yeah, let's go. Today is really tiring.
- Hey! Hey, run! Run, run, run! Run!
- What? What's going on? Why?
- Run, run! Run!
- Why? Why? Why?!
- Run! Come on, hurry up! Run!
- What in the world?!
- Run!
- If we catch you, you're dead!
- Hey!
- Run! Run!
- Hey, split up! Go that way, go!
- Run!
Split up!
Ugh! Where did those bastards go?
Seriously, where did those bastards go?
Hey, hey, what are you doing?
You guys go that way, we'll go this way.
No, instead of doing that, we should go that way.
That's what I just said. Hurry up and follow me.
They're gone.
Hey, let's go.
That must hurt!
Yeah, let's go.
Lets go...
Hey, hey, hey!
You're going to die, seriously!
I ran so much I think I'm going to throw up.
Oh, what about your ankle? Is it okay?
Hm? It throbs just a little but it's fine.
But why did we run?
You're right. Why did I drag you along and run?
I must have let go of my sanity.
When did you arrive there?
By any chance, did you see everything?
See what?
By any chance, did you get into a fight because of me?
Hey, am I crazy that I would get into a fight because of you?
Hey, I think you're acting like this because you don't know,
but I'm not someone with a strong sense of justice or someone who meddles  easily.
"Don't care about other people's  business and don't get involved in my business." That's my life motto.
Then why did you run? You ran because you got into a fight with them.
I mean, maybe it was the first time those bastards saw such a handsome man. They were so aggravating.
Well, I understand. Some squids came to have fun,
but since all the women were only staring at me...
What are you saying? I just can't have a serious conversation with you.
Well, anyway, since I ran so much, I forgot some of my worries.
Thanks, classmate.
No problem.
But, what worries?
Is there something complicated?
And if I have it, what? Tell you everything?
I don't think you and I are in a relationship where we talk about our inner thoughts.
That is, well... okay. I admit it.
Hey, let me ask you one thing.
Did your personality change or am I not remembering you correctly?
Of course, I changed.
How can I live in this harsh world being shy like back then?
Truthfully, I'm much more attractive now than then.
Right?
What are you saying? Move your face.
You look pointed...
That worry. I don't know what it is but don't try to conclude it forcefully.
With this oppa's experience, time will solve that problem itself.
You're showing off.
Hey, Bok Joo!
Hurry up and come out!
Ah, why this early in the morning?
What are doing, being so loud in the morning—
What is this!?
Uncle, what is this?
What do you mean what? It's a scooter.
Even though it's a used one, this one was used so little that it's almost new.
And I gave away the one that we were riding.
Because it's really an old one they didn't want to take it, so I barely sold it for 100,000 won.
How did you get the money to buy this?
I went to the head of Extra Guild and demanded a little bit.
to settle the unpaid payment meanwhile. If not, I'll report it to the media.
If you got picked on by the head, you told me you might not get work.
I may quit acting with this opportunity because I don't have talent anyhow.
Ah, ah, it's okay, okay.
How is it?
If I ride this and make a "boom, boom" sound, I'll look nice, won't I?
Oh, Uncle! You look so nice today! The best charismatic!
It's true that it's good.
It really looks nice.
Hurry!
Let's get in quickly. Hurry!
We're late, let's go.
Hello!
Okay, let's just see. Just see.
This must be new. Let's do it as a couple.
- No, I don't like it. Let's go.
- Why?
Why do we have to match? I really don't like doing like this.
Let's go. Go.
I got it. Got it. Let go.
- It's true, right?
- Yeah.
- Really?
Hey.
Let's go.
Okay...
Let's do it as a couple!
- Have a nice day!
- We'll come again!
What do you mean we'll come back again?
That'll go well with Joon Hyeong.
This scooter is really different. It took 5 minutes less.
Yeah, right! It's good to have a new one!
Don't speed too much, even so. Make sure to be careful, particularly when you make a turn, understand?
Yes, yes.
Thank you for dropping me off, Father.
Here, this.
What is it?
When I looked at you last time when you came, you didn't look good. Don't only do practice. Release some stress.
Eat something delicious with friends and go shopping too.
And go to places like the club.
No, I don't need this.
Ah, just take it.
I thought I had to buy a scooter.
Thanks to your uncle, I saved some money after a long time.
It's not good for an athlete to be stressed. Go out and release it. You must.
Ah, your uncle will go to the hospital with me, so you only focus on your weightlifting from now on.
There aren't many customers in the afternoon anyway, so let's do that.
Dad is going.
Father.
Daughter, fighting!
I'm going!
Here you go!
You crazy!
It's starting again. My shoulder!
That's why I'm telling you to strengthen your muscles. At this rate, it'll become a habitual shoulder dislocation.
I know it, punk. It's not that I don't know it, but it's because I'm lazy.
But still, the only person who thinks about me is you.
Be quiet, you punk!
Why? Why do you act like this?
If you're caught by me...
- Come here!
- Hey, hey! Package! Package!
- What package?
- Aww, really!
Let go!
It's true!
It's time to receive a new swimsuit from home.
Hey, did you buy something again?
You said your dad was having a hard time these days. Is it okay for you to be doing this?
Don't worry! It's said that even if the rich go bankrupt, they can still live comfortably for three years.
What is special in life? You just live today as if you don't have tomorrow.
Huh? You have something for you.
Oh. Jeong Joon Hyeong.
I didn't have anything that should have come.
It looks suspicious. No name of sender nor address. Only your name.
Yeah, Joon Hyeong.
You must have been practicing?
This.
You found out.
There is only you who would send me something like this.
You have only me who'd send it, so can you just put on this one?
Right.
For a short time, very briefly, I thought I'd put this on, but
even with my simple brain, I think that I can't wear this.
Understood. I didn't know you would have been that burdened by it.
I accept it.
I'm going.
No, this crazy wench! If you enroll with this money, you are not a human.
Father thinks only about you, whether he is asleep or awake.
To make this money, he must have run around the neighborhood several dozens of times riding on that old scooter.
Don't do a regretful thing, Kim Bok Joo.
It's too boring for us to stay like this without beer.
Are you human? If you talk about alcohol for awhile, I will kill you.
Girls...
Yeah, Bok Joo, say it.
I, from now on, will really only do sports.
You already work hard!
Right. Among us, you're the gutsiest person.
No. Recently I've totally been slacking.
I'm going to get my act together and from now on work a hundred times harder.
Woah, 100 times more? If Bok Joo does well, it looks like she's going to go to Taeneung (Korea National Training Center) this year.
Only Taeneung? She's going to get a gold medal too.
I am Kim Bok Joo ! I am the promising weightlifter, Kim Bok Joo!
I'm going to work hard and only exercise from now on! Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Hey! I heard all of your names!
I'm the promising weightlifter, Kim Bok Joo.
- Cheer up!
- Be quiet!
Yeah, when has a man ever been in my life?
I'm Kim Bok Joo! I'm Kim Bok Joo—
This is just a passing incident. Time will take care of everything.
Time, pass by! Time!
Pass!
Hey!
Hey, Bok Joo. There you go. Breathe.
Breathe!
- Fighting!
- Bok Joo, fighting!
- Hold!
- Nice!
Wow!
Wow, that was nice!
Oh, Bok Joo grits her teeth (determined).
After a long time, someone from Haneul Sports University  will get a gold metal. Let's challenge!
Hooray!
Ah, I'm hungry.
Hey, how many times do I have to tell you not to match us to your height?
Ah, I can't hear it. Sounds come somewhere?
Hey, should I get double eyelid surgery and get some strong fierce eyes? What do you think?
Wow, you'll look like a celebrity! You'll look like Park Myung Soo!
Hey!
How can you compare me to Park Myung Soo?
Don't you check your face? Look at your face.
We're going to have omurice (fried rice omelet) today!
No! Omurice again?
Ah, don't grow up more!
I like omurice!
What are you going to eat?
Hey!
Don't hold us like that!
Fatty seems to be in a good mood.
After coming back from Russia, make sure to come back here.
Of course.
Oh, Si Ho.
I'll come again in a little bit.
It's fine, you can talk now.
Yes.
Did you discuss it with your mother?
Yes, and I think it'll be difficult this time...
Why? By any chance, does your financial situation not allow you? Is it difficult for her?
Yeah, there's nothing I can do if that's the case.
It would have been nice to go together.
What a shame.
I know, right? It's a shame.
Yeah, Mom?
I heard that you told your coach you won't go to Russia.
How can you just do whatever you want without even discussing it with me?
What if I had discussed it with you? Could you have sent me?
- What?
- You know that all of the training expenses in Russia have to come from our own pockets.
How can you handle airfare, boarding, and coach fees, all?
Please, Mom! Don't bluff when you don't have anything!
I sometimes forget our circumstances and misunderstand!
What's she doing in the men's locker rooms?
- Where is she going?
- What's going on?
- Ah, she scared me?
- What?
I understand your intentions and I admit that I did wrong,
but don't treat me this way too. What's so hard about accepting this one thing anyway?
Whether you wear it or throw it away, you deal with it...
since I already gave it to you.
By any chance, do you like Messi?
Let's go, let's go!
Hey, I'm all done. Whatever, I can't do any more.
Fine, it can't be any cleaner than this. Let's go eat galbi.
Yeah, let's go before they run out of galbi.
Now that I think about it, I like Ronald better than Messi.
Have a good day.
At times, there are passionate feelings that even time
or situations cannot take care of.
Ah, Kim Bok Joo!
Hey! Hey, Bok Joo! We're over here!
- Hey! Kim Bok Joo!
- Kim Bok Joo! Hey!
One day, a mayfly told a garden tiger moth that flew in towards the firelight.
"You know that firelight is a trap set by humans."
"You're not someone who can only live for a day, like me."
"Why are you going to throw yourself into a fire even though you know you'll burn yourself to die?"
The garden tiger moth said, "That fire light is too beautiful not to dash into it."
"There is nothing beautiful in this world without pain."
Will there be a pit of fire waiting at the end of this path?
Although I'm scared, for now, I'll just go.
I'll run to him.
♬   How can I get your   ♬
Are you alright?
♬   love?   ♬
Ah, we're trapped here.
♬   How can I make you smile?    ♬
Oh, be careful. Move.
Wow,
♬   This heart-throbbing excitement   ♬
you even talk now. I must have really lost my mind.
♬  colors my feelings    ♬