[Go East]
[Episode 17]
He pointed out the problem
and offered the court a specific solution.
Yuan Mo
has finally become like Hanjing.
Yes.
We should hurry up and discuss it
before we invite the envoys of different states to discuss it together.
As long as we can resettle the refugees,
the alliance with the five states will have the support of the people.
By then, the envoys will feel the pressure from the people.
I believe there will be a new chance to form the alliance.
Yeah.
You're so far-sighted.
Just say what you want to say.
You haven't made up with Xiuyi?
Don't blame me for speaking my mind then.
Over the years, you've been busy with work
and barely spent any time with your son.
So it's understandable
that An Xiuyi is angry with you.
There's nothing wrong with you having requirements
and expectations for your son.
But you can't always criticize him.
Think about it.
Back then, you planned to get Xiuyi into the Ministry of Rites.
He wouldn't
and insisted on coming to the Sifang Pavilion.
Starting from a low-ranking official, he's climbed up the ladder step by step,
just like you did back then.
He just wanted to anger me.
To anger you?
He risked his life just to anger you?
This time, in order to save the refugees,
Xiuyi went into the lion's den
and fought with The Faceless.
He even got injured.
He's injured?
How is he now?
Ask him yourself.
Alright.
It's not serious.
Not serious.
Look.
He didn't even tell you this.
You really need to spend some time with him.
As a father,
sometimes you need to put aside your pride.
It doesn't hurt to be soft with your children.
I don't know.
Let's go have a look.
What's going on?
Refugee resettlement plan.
[Refugee Resettlement Plan]
All refugees from different states can be resettled.
It's…
Yong has adopted a new policy!
We can get a temporary travel pass.
Yes.
They'll also find jobs for us.
Great!
We don't have to be on the run anymore!
We have a home!
[Administration Office]
Quiet! Listen to me.
Quiet!
No matter which state you're from,
as long as you follow the rules of Yong,
come to the Sifang Pavilion to apply for a temporary travel pass,
and abide by the law of Yong,
you can choose freely
to stay in Yong,
return to your state,
or engage in trade.
You'll all be protected by the law of Yong
and treated equally!
Great! Great!
Long live Yong!
Enough.
Stop shouting.
Line up now.
Keep up. Hurry.
Line up.
Here you are.
Thank you.
Line up. Line up.
Once the temporary travel passes are issued,
we can consider the task of rescuing the refugees as completed.
All our previous efforts are worth it.
-Thank you for saving my life, sirs.
-Thank you.
What are you doing?
Thank you for saving my life.
-Get up.
-Thank you.
Madam, please get up.
-You get up too.
-Thank you.
Thank you for saving my son's life.
Thank you.
Sirs,
I'm the only son my mother has.
If I died, she'd have no one to take care of her.
That's why I was forced
by the outlaws of the Red Lotus Society
to do many wrong things.
I really regret it now.
Please punish me.
You had no choice.
We don't blame you.
It's good that you can correct your mistake.
By the way, Qing,
do you know
if Chen Xinliang is looking for someone?
Looking for someone?
He seems very interested in female refugees.
Every time he fooled the refugees,
he'd separate men and women
and lock women
in a separate room.
And he'd spend a lot of time in the room with them.
Guys, don't rush.
Listen to me.
You can all get a share.
Okay!
After you get the millet,
come here to write down the skills you have.
We'll try our best to find jobs for you.
Don't rush.
Everyone can get a share.
You were taken
to Green Wave Villa too, right?
Can you tell us what happened there?
I was locked up with other women.
As soon as that old scoundrel came in, he…
He…
It's okay.
If you don't want to talk about it,
we won't force you.
Actually, he didn't touch us.
He just…
He's a pervert.
He kept staring at us.
At what?
Our feet.
Feet?
He asked someone to take off our shoes and socks
and stared at our feet one by one.
We didn't know what he wanted.
In the end, he left angrily.
I've heard that some people do have this kind of fetish.
Or the girl he's looking for
has a special mark on her feet.
Thank you.
You can go.
Sirs,
come to me if you need any help.
My mother told me I must repay
the kindness of the Sifang Pavilion.
We do need help
to resettle these refugees.
Will you come to the Sifang Pavilion to help us?
Can I do it?
Of course.
Report to the Sifang Pavilion in a few days.
Great. I'm willing to do anything.
Thank you, sirs.
You can go.
[Yanle Embassy]
Have you found that person?
Deputy Envoy,
no.
Besides, Yong has uprooted the Red Lotus Society.
Yanle has nothing to do with the Red Lotus Society.
I'm the Yanle Envoy.
I only care about what an envoy should do.
There is something more important I need to think about.
Yong just carried out a policy to resettle the refugees.
If the five states reconsider the alliance with Yong,
we'll be in trouble.
Yes.
[This person from Yanle is naturalized in the 22nd year of Anping]
Ah Shu.
You...
You're writing?
261, 647…
Why are you writing these things?
I was illiterate,
but it's different now.
You can't fool me again.
Ah Shu.
I have something to tell you.
Is someone at the door?
Wait, I…
Who's it?
I have something to tell you, Ah Shu.
Tell me later.
Coming!
Ah Shu! Ah Shu!
Ah Shu.
Shen.
Yuchi.
Wang.
Why have you all come here?
We came to celebrate for you.
Celebrate what?
Yuan Mo.
You haven't given it to Ah Shu yet?
What are you going to give me?
What is it?
Why are you hesitating?
My name is on it.
Natural… Cer…
[Naturalization Certificate]
It's a naturalization certificate.
Naturalization certificate?
My naturalization certificate?
Ah Shu.
From now on,
you're officially a citizen of Changle.
Yes!
Great!
I'm a Changle citizen now!
Look how happy she is.
Mr. Yu.
It's so great!
Wang.
Congratulations.
Yuan Mo.
Thank you.
Ah Shu.
From now on, you are free.
You said you don't know your birthday.
You didn't even celebrate your quinceanera.
You're a citizen of Changle now,
so we want to hold a naturalization ceremony
for you.
Right.
I'll assign the tasks.
Let's start.
Wait, wait.
There are two more guests.
Come in. What are you waiting for?
Retainer An?
Susu?
Yes.
Back in the villa,
it was Retainer An who reminded Ah Shu to escape
and sent the signal.
Come on in.
Let's have some fun together tonight.
Welcome.
Retainer An, Susu,
I haven't thanked you yet.
Come on in.
Don't just stand here.
Let's clean up this place, light a bonfire, and hang up some lanterns
for the celebration.
Yeah. Let's do it.
Let's go.
We're all colleagues tonight.
No retainers and subordinates.
Well said!
Great.
Look at this place. So empty.
Ah Shu.
We have to hang up lanterns.
Come with me.
That's right, Susu.
The lantern you chose looks much better.
Shen.
Switch the lantern in your hand
with Susu.
This one is fine.
Just do as I say.
You usually have good taste.
Switch.
Ji.
Can't you see there's one lantern missing
in the middle?
Hang one more up.
There are no extra lanterns.
Go make one.
Xiuyi.
You two must be careful.
But the firewood must be piled up high.
-Yes.
-We need a big bonfire.
A big one.
Why hasn't anyone watered the flowers?
Brat.
You're so generous today.
Of course.
Okay. I'll water the flowers.
This Qingxi wine is 50 years old.
Are you really going to drink it tonight?
I'm happy today.
This wine is the best for the celebration.
Is it for the celebration, or do you need some Dutch courage?
You talk too much.
Open the bottles if you want to drink the wine too.
Don't chicken out later.
Go away.
Ah Shu.
Ah Shu, I need to tell you something.
Actually, I like you.
Why is it so awkward?
I know.
My clothes.
My clothes are wrong.
I can relax after getting changed.
It's been so long. Why haven't they come out?
Can Yuchi Hua do it or not?
Maybe she should let me dress Ah Shu up.
You're indeed good at that.
Yeah.
Why are you two so impatient?
The one who's truly impatient is milling around over there.
Are you talking about me?
I'm not impatient.
Why would I be?
We're coming.
They're coming.
So beautiful.
Stop staring.
Come. Come.
Sit down.
I announce that
Ah Shu's naturalization ceremony begins now!
Great!
Then, we'll move to the next step.
Sending gifts.
You prepared gifts for me?
Of course.
Yuan Mo has given you his gift.
It's my turn now.
A small congratulations gift.
Clap!
Sure.
It's a top-notch brush made of rabbit hair.
To master a skill,
you need to have good tools first.
We wish that Ah Shu could get
better and better at calligraphy.
In the future, you can see me
as your elder in Changle City.
Thank you, Mr. Yu.
Don't call me that.
Thank you, Yu.
That's more like it.
Yu.
Yu, you called me generous.
You're more generous than me.
Shut up.
Who am I doing this for?
Who's next?
Ah Shu.
I ordered this rouge for you
in another rouge shop.
It's the latest product. Try it.
Thank you, Hua.
See me as your elder sister in the future.
I'll protect you in Changle City.
Great!
So nice.
Thank you, Hua.
Ah Shu.
You're welcome in the Sifang Pavilion anytime.
I ordered two Aglaonema plants
in the West Market for you,
but they still haven't arrived yet.
Retainer Wang,
we've done you a favor.
Hurry. Yeah.
We went to the West Market before coming here
and brought the plants here.
They are here.
Take them.
Ah Shu.
Thank you.
Hold on.
Retainer Wang, as you said,
the West Court is like a big family, right?
Yeah.
We're all your brothers now.
Keep it up.
Wang.
Thank you.
Congratulations.
The gifts from the West Court are all great.
East Court, it's your turn.
Susu.
Ah Shu.
Susu and I prepared
a box of snacks for you.
Please accept it.
Great!
I love snacks.
Come on. Let's share them.
Wait.
A box of snacks is not good enough as a gift.
Let me try one.
These snacks are for Ah Shu.
Just be grateful that you can share them.
Try one.
I'll save my share for you.
Come on. Take more.
Come on.
We'll all try it.
Wait.
Delicious.
Stop!
These snacks are not for you.
It's okay.
I don't mind sharing with them.
Yeah.
So petty.
No, I mean…
these are dried grasshoppers for Poppet.
Luckily, we haven't eaten them.
You shouldn't have eaten so quickly.
You're so bad.
I'm surprised that you know about Poppet.
This gift is so special.
I like it.
I like all your gifts.
This is the first time
I've received so many gifts.
No one has held a celebration for me before.
Thank you, everyone.
I've never been so happy before.
Ah Shu.
Being happy is all that matters.
Remember.
Changle is your home now.
We're all your family.
Thank you, Mr. Yu.
Call me Yu.
Yuan Mo.
We've all said something.
Do you have anything to say to Ah Shu?
In the future, will you be Ah Shu's brother,
creditor,
or…
something else?
Me?
I'll be Ah Shu's…
I'll be whatever she wants me to be.
Alright.
Let's raise
our glasses, okay?
Come on.
I think
he needs some Dutch courage
to say what he really wants to say.
That's right.
Come on.
Let's drink to Ah Shu first.
Congratulations to her on becoming a citizen of Yong.
Cheers!
-Cheers!
-Thank you, guys!
Great!
Beautiful dance.
Let's drink.
Here.
Ah Shu,
you're so good at Yong's dance.
In the future,
I'll take you to meet the boys from big families in Changle City
for willow shooting.
I want to show them I have such a good sister!
Yes!
No!
Yuchi Hua,
you haven't got married yourself.
Don't worry about Ah Shu.
You…
Ah Shu, d-don't go with her.
Ah Shu is free now.
She can go wherever she wants.
I said she can't go, and that is that!
Guys, help me get him in.
Don't be afraid.
Careful.
Clean the mess.
Be careful.
You guys are so…
Clean the mess.
I'll make some hangover soup later.
Okay.
-Up the stairs. The first stair.
-Be careful.
-The second stair.
Look.
Walk straight.
It seems that the East Court
never has such vibes.
What's wrong?
Is something bothering you?
Do you think…
I'm really inept?
What makes you think that?
The Five States Conference
went quite well,
but it was ruined just because of something I said.
I got lost when I stalked those of the Red Lotus Society
and was recognized and caught when I tried to save the refugees.
I'm the worst.
I don't think they were your faults.
You're excellent.
Enough.
Don't try to comfort me.
I know.
No one really appreciates me.
My father doesn't.
He doesn't.
Neither do you.
I do appreciate you.
People in the East Court
respect and fear me
only because of my father.
Not to mention those in the West Court.
Even Yuchi Hua, who grew up with me,
despises me too.
Yes.
I admit that I work very hard,
but hard work doesn't always pay off.
Sometimes,
you just can't make it.
Am I right?
Yeah.
When I first came to the Sifang Pavilion and met you,
I was surprised
by how arrogant and ignorant you were.
You were conceited and imperious.
But after hearing what you said today,
I don't think you're hopeless.
You know your limits.
It's good.
Just don't forget everything
after you sober up tomorrow.
Don't go.
I need to tell you something.
I…
I like you.
I like it when you're straightforward.
I like it when you're bossy.
I like it when you're overbearing.
When I first met you,
I knew you were special.
You're different from all the other girls I know.
We're here to say goodbye.
We didn't hear anything.
We didn't see anything either.
Guys, come and have some hangover soup.
Hua, you didn't drink much.
Why are you blushing?
Ah Shu.
I'm a little drunk.
I'm going back.
Drunk?
It's my turn to propose a toast?
Yes, it's your turn.
Well, his wife has a bad temper.
She won't let him in if he goes back too late.
We'll take our leave.
I'm not leaving!
I need beauty sleep too.
I won't help you clean up.
We're leaving.
Here is to you.
No, no. Go to the door.
Drink at the door.
Careful. Careful.
Why are they all leaving?
Young Master.
You're back.
What's the matter, Father?
Which arm?
What?
Which arm of yours is injured?
Just a minor injury.
Don't worry about it.
I'm asking you!
Why can't you just
answer me directly?
Left arm.
Let me see.
I told you,
it's just a minor injury.
You don't need to see it.
I'm your father.
Why can't I check on your wound?
Since I was young,
I've recovered by myself
every time I got injured.
When have you ever shown concern?
Now you pretend to care.
Fine.
I'll show you.
I got this scar
when I fell down from a tree.
There's a knife wound here.
I got this scratch from a tree branch while I was riding a horse.
Do you want to see more?
I have scars on my legs and back too.
Do you want to see them?
I can take off my clothes and show them to you.
Xiuyi!
The front yard
is only 118 steps away
from the back yard.
When I was young,
I counted steps every time I came here.
I thought to myself,
"It's such a short distance,
but why does Father barely come to see me?
Is it because I'm not good enough
and Father isn't satisfied with me?"
Until one day, I stopped counting.
Because I realized I had grown up.
So take my advice.
Don't try to be a loving father and expect me to be a filial son.
We'll just live under the same roof
like two strangers.
It's better this way.
The bottles are still here.
Poppet is here too.
The flowers and plants are here too.
Ah Shu's things are all here.
So Ah Shu agreed?
She's not leaving?
Yuan Mo.
What are you looking at?
Ah Shu.
You're sober?
What I said to you last night
was all from the bottom of my heart.
Last night?
You said a lot of things last night.
You kept talking when you were drunk.
Don't drink so much again.
Eat.
What does she mean?
She's shy?
Or is she testing me?
Oaky, Ah Shu.
I'll listen to you and won't drink anymore.
You'll call the shots in this house in the future.
Your word is law!
I've always been calling the shots.
What are you talking about?
You're so glib this morning.
Finish the porridge.
Okay, Master.
By the way,
I'm not your little maid anymore.
If you don't want me to live in your house,
I can move out.
Take your time.
You choked on the porridge.
Let me get you some water.
Move out?
I'm sure now.
This must be a test.
I won't let you go.
You haven't sobered up?
Let go of me.
No!
Unless you say you're not leaving.
I'm not leaving!
You're going to be late.
Go to the Sifang Pavilion now,
or Yu will deduct your salary again.
You do know how to run a household.
I'll go now.
I'm leaving, Master.
From now on, I'm a man who will support his family!
Yuan Mo confessed love to Yuchi Hua?
Really?
Maybe you were drunk and heard it wrong.
Shen was there too.
Ask him if you don't believe me.
Retainer Wang, Retainer An,
and Susu were all there.
They all heard it.
He said,
"I like it when you're bossy and overbearing.
When I saw you,
I knew you were different from other girls."
That's exactly Yuchi Hua.
Yeah.
He held Yuchi Hua's hand and said,
"Don't go."
And neither of them came to work today.
So,
don't judge a book by its cover.
Guys,
don't talk about this matter ever.
You must keep it a secret.
I don't want to be killed by that she-devil.
I'm afraid the whole Sifang Pavilion knows it now.
Don't gossip when you're on duty.
Yes.
Good morning, boys!
You all came early today.
Great.
This is what the men of the West Court should be like.
-You see?
-Do we have a lot of work today?
-He's refreshed and happy.
-Do we?
It's fine.
I can finish your work for you.
I'm full of energy today.
I can't wait to get to work!
Where is Yuchi Hua?
Why didn't Yuchi Hua come?
She asked for a leave.
She caught a cold last night.
I asked her to wear more clothes,
but she wouldn't listen.
Tell me if there's a task.
I'm always ready.
He cares so much about her.
I don't want to believe it.
But this is too real.
Why are you dawdling here?
Get back to work!
Yes.
On it!
Recently, refugees from different states
have gathered in front of our embassy,
asking our envoy to reconsider the alliance with Yong
to ensure long-term peace in the desert.
This is so great.
Yes.
It seems that we may be able to form the alliance again.
This calls for celebration.
He'll pay.
All the female refugees I visited today said the same thing.
They all said Chen Xinliang stared at their feet.
Looks like your guess is right.
They're indeed looking for a young girl
who has a special mark on her feet.
The Man in White went through so much trouble.
That girl must be a big shot.
But how has she ended up in Changle?
Fortunately,
they didn't find her among the refugees.
What if he's wrong?
Maybe that girl
is not among the refugees.
You mean she's already a citizen of Changle?
It's very likely.
Anyway,
we must find her before the Man in White.
I'll go to Yuchi Hua tomorrow.
Why will you go to her?
To expand the search area.
I didn't know you were so good at using public resources for personal gain
and soldiering on.
What are you talking about?
I can't understand you.
What else does Yuchi Hua like
besides weapons?
I need to give her what she wants.
You're going to give her a gift?
Of course. I need a favor from her after all.
But it's for work.
You have to reimburse me.
How much is this?
Ten wen.
Ten wen?
Are you going to buy this for Yuchi Hua?
Why would I?
I'm picking one for Ah Shu.
This is for Yuchi Hua.
She didn't come to work again.
I guess she hasn't fully recovered.
Give this to her.
Don't tell her it's from me.
Yuan Mo.
You're buying a bracelet for Ah Shu
and prepared cold medicine for Yuchi Hua.
Do you think it's proper?
What's improper about it?
I thought you were just flippant,
but it turns out you're a total scumbag.
Give it to her yourself.
You…
You don't need to pay for the bracelet.
Wang Kunwu likes Hua, fine.
But who does Yuan Mo think he is?
How dare he like Yuchi Hua too?
He actually confessed his love when he was drunk.
He even touched her hands.
I grew up with Hua but have never touched her hands!
Retainer An.
Mr. Yu wants you to go to the council chamber for a meeting immediately.
Got it.
You two must have noticed that
there have been some changes in the situation
that are favorable to us.
All states have sent us letters
and agreed to reconsider the alliance.
To prevent the failure last time
from happening again,
I've decided to take a different approach.
Tackle them one by one.
The East and West Courts will negotiate with them separately
to reach an initial agreement with the five states.
Then, the Ministry of Rites and the envoys will gather together
to announce the formation of the alliance.
The one who contributes the most to it will be rewarded with fifty taels of silver
and promoted to Supervisory Sifang Envoy.
Sifang Envoy?
What is that position?
Retainer Wang, you were in the army,
so you may not know about it.
The Sifang Envoy of Yong
will be bestowed by the emperor with the dragon banner and the lion emblem.
He shall visit different states on behalf of Yong,
going south to Duluo
and traveling west beyond the Yanzhi Pass.
Meeting the Sifang Envoy
is like meeting the emperor of Yong.
Traveling around for state affairs
is not only a supreme honor
but also a dangerous task.
Few people are capable enough for it.
It's unprecedented
for people your age
to be among the candidates.
It's always been my dream to become the Sifang Envoy.
The East Court
will do our best to make the alliance form.
This is a serious matter.
The East and West Courts must work together.
Mr. Yu.
Are you going to make the West Court assist the East Court again?
Am I the kind of superior
who plays favorites?
I've come up with a wonderful idea.
Draw lots.
Fair enough, isn't it?
There are five states.
Why are there only two pieces of paper?
Among the five states,
Yuluo and Mobei are the most difficult to convince.
If we can sway Yuluo,
they'll just need to make small compromises
to convince Dongyuan and Xiyuan.
Yueying and Mobei are bound by marriage.
They keep fighting,
but in fact, Yueying relies a lot on Mobei.
Swaying Mobei means swaying Yueying.
Looks like
you've done your homework, Retainer An.
But I wasn't asking you.
You enlightened me, Retainer Wang.
I have a lot to learn and must work hard.
I wasn't drunk that day.
I remember
what you told me.
All right.
Is everything clear?
Pick one.
Retainer Wang.
You go first.
Yueying and Mobei.
Then the West Court will deal with these two states.
So naturally, the East Court will handle
Yuluo, Dongyuan, and Xiyuan.
Remember.
The one who makes the alliance form will get a big reward.
You may leave.
Xiuyi.
Is there something else?
Why do you favor me?
What do you mean?
I guess
on the other piece of paper,
it's also Mobei and Yueying, right?
You…
It's all wet.
You deliberately made the West Court deal with Mobei, the trickier state,
and gave me the easier task.
Is it because you don't trust me?
Xiuyi.
If I did this in the past,
I would be favoring you.
But I'm doing this now because I like you.
Think about it.
After all that's happened,
do you still not know what your shortcomings are?
You always bite off more than you can chew.
Since you became the retainer of the East Court,
you've been trying to make great achievements.
But what leads to failure
is usually these small details.
Am I right?
Think about it.
Negotiating with Yuluo, Dongyuan, and Xiyuan
seems
an easy task,
but the relationships between the three states are complicated.
There are many intricate matters.
So you must think carefully
about every detail.
Otherwise, you may repeat your mistake.
This is a test for you.
What do you think?
You can understand my arrangement now, can't you?
Mr. Yu,
I…
You don't need to say anything.
Remember.
No foreign affair is too small.
Go.
This is a great chance to form the alliance.
We're aware of it.
Yanle must know it too.
So we have to hurry.
Don't worry.
Everything is arranged.
Speaking of arrangements,
I heard that
you've given the easy task to the East Court
and the tough one to the West Court.
Is that true?
Be honest with me.
Okay.
I really can't hide anything from you.
In the past, because of you,
I favored Xiuyi.
But this time,
I want to give Yuan Mo an opportunity to improve himself.
Think about it.
No matter which state I let Xiuyi deal with,
he can handle it well.
Right?
But Yuan Mo is different.
He has been working in the Sifang Pavilion for months
and just made some achievements.
I want to strike while the iron is hot
and make him grow faster.
If you think
I'm partial on this matter,
I won't deny it.