[Go East]
[Episode 32]
Ah Fu
does the cleaning at the Sifang Pavilion
and sometimes delivers things.
He's completely inconspicuous.
If he wants,
he can sneak into anywhere.
Look.
These are documents signed by Ji.
There are a few maps
of the parade route on the Lantern Festival.
Could Ah Fu
be the Man in White?
What's this?
It looks like dye from the dyehouse.
Did you get it on your fingers when you were washing
Qing's mother's clothes just now?
-Blue dye.
Let's go.
We're too late.
Qing did all this.
He's not Qing.
The real Qing
got lost in the desert long ago and can't return.
This Qing is the Man in White.
Now that we know what the Man in White looks like,
let's hurry back to the Jingzhao Prefecture
and order a city-wide manhunt.
Let's go.
Be careful.
It's an ambush.
What should we do? Are you wearing soft armor?
I never wear it.
I'm uncomfortable wearing it.
I'm not wearing soft armor either.
If we risk our lives fighting our way out,
what are our chances of survival?
That depends on how good your martial arts skills are.
Perhaps you'll be the one who gets shot.
That's true.
While I'm here,
I won't let you get shot.
Get ready.
Three, two, one.
What if we die?
We won't.
Come on. Get ready.
Three, two, one.
Little Xiu.
I've been listening to your conversation for a while.
You were so tardy.
Well...
Magistrate Lin,
why are you...
Retainer An reported to the Jingzhao Prefecture
that Qing, the servant at the Sifang Pavilion, is the Man in White.
We rushed here
and happened to see the ambush,
so we took them down.
Weren't you always suspicious of Ji?
How did you know Qing was the Man in White then?
Didn't you tell me to calm down?
After I calmed down,
I went through the records again.
To imitate Ji's handwriting,
Qing gradually changed the way he wrote his own name,
adding a clear start and end point to the strokes.
But when he was first recruited by the Sifang Pavilion,
he didn't write his name like that.
Later, I asked other clerks,
and they said that on the day of the Lantern Festival,
Qing had helped Ji sell the maps of the parade route.
So, Susu actually wanted to tell me
that Qing is the Man in White.
Ji can finally clear his name.
You were right.
Colleagues at the Sifang Pavilion
are like family.
Susu said the same thing when she was alive.
I shouldn't have suspected my family member.
I'm sorry.
The Man in White has escaped.
I need to return to the Sifang Pavilion now
and tell Mr. Yu about this.
Magistrate Lin,
there are two bodies inside the room.
Please dispose of them.
Okay.
Yes.
I'm going back to the Jingzhao Prefecture.
I need to put up the wanted posters
for Qing and that woman as soon as possible
and launch a city-wide manhunt.
Bring them back for interrogation.
Yes.
Go.
Get up. Go.
Quickly. Go.
Let's go, too.
Wait a minute.
What?
Little Hua.
What are you up to now?
This is the last time I call you that.
Retainer Wang is a good man.
He will cherish you.
I shouldn't call you by your nickname
so freely anymore.
It's alright.
I don't mind.
He doesn't mind either.
In the past,
I didn't understand anything.
I didn't understand your feelings,
nor did I understand my own feelings for you.
I wasted a lot of time
and missed out on someone I should have cherished.
Now,
I only hope you can be happy.
I wish you two a happy life together.
Little Xiu.
Thank you.
[Inebriation Restaurant]
Can you finish all the dishes you ordered?
We found the blood letter.
Can't I celebrate?
Yes, you can. But slow down.
I won't take your food away.
Hurry up and eat.
The dishes are really delicious.
I don't have time to eat now.
Are you sure these are the names
of the loyal officials of Yanle?
I've never met
these co-signers
or heard their names.
But after all these years,
they're still hoping
that I can return to Yanle
and overthrow Long Tuqi one day.
This blood letter
must be keeping Long Tuqi up at night.
He's ruled over the people of Yanle brutally for over a decade,
yet he still hasn't made them obedient.
People ingratiate themselves with him on the surface,
but in their hearts, they've long hated him.
That's why the Man in White appeared at Lins' Depository.
He's looking for this blood letter, too.
If he gets the blood letter,
Long Tuqi can catch
all the officials loyal to your father in one fell swoop,
eliminating any future threats.
Now that we have the blood letter,
Ah Shu,
we must be extremely careful.
Got it.
Yuan Mo.
We've never had a drink together
since I became the princess.
That's true.
Here.
This is to wish you a life free of worries
and full of happiness.
As long as you're happy, I'm happy.
We must keep it safe.
We can't let it fall into the hands of the Man in White.
Let me get you a bowl of fish soup.
You haven't eaten much.
The fish soup is delicious.
The fish is tender and smooth.
It's absolutely a delicacy.
Try it. Hurry up.
How hungry are you?
We're not in a hurry.
Eat it.
Okay. I'll eat it.
You haven't eaten much.
Did you eat well
when I was away?
When I was by myself,
I'd just grab a bite.
That's not okay.
Nothing is more important than eating.
Eating is no small thing.
Alright.
I swear.
I will eat well.
I won't make Ah Shu worry.
Okay?
You're just saying that.
I mean it!
It's delicious.
And it's a new dish.
I noticed it.
That's more like it.
It's a pity
that Duomi left early.
He missed out on these delicious food.
It's delicious.
I'm full. How about you?
I'm full, too.
Let's go back then.
We need to meet them.
Let's go.
You're a princess now, yet you're still so forgetful.
Wait for me.
Oh.
I just remembered
I have a new formula to give to Manager Qiu.
Wait for me here.
No need to come with me. I'll be out soon.
That's not okay.
What if there's danger?
There won't be.
Don't worry.
Why hasn't the princess come out yet?
[Moonlight Hall]
Yuan.
Where's Ah Shu?
Princess Longshuang?
I haven't seen her today.
The princess...
Where's the princess?
Did The Faceless abduct the princess?
Here.
This is to wish you a life free of worries
and full of happiness.
Don't worry.
The list.
It's about the list.
The list?
The Man in White wants the list.
Ah Shu went to see the Man in White.
She wants to avenge Deputy Envoy Kang.
You're quite brave.
You actually came out alone.
Take me to see the Man in White.
You want to see my master?
I want to make a deal with him.
What kind of deal?
Isn't he looking for the blood letter?
I can give it to him
as long as he agrees to my condition.
Can we go now?
If we don't go now, we won't be able to go.
If the princess went to see
the Man in White alone, as you said,
she wouldn't want us to find her.
What should we do?
What are you doing?
I'm from Yong's Sifang Pavilion.
I'm requisitioning your dog.
Wait.
What are you doing?
Thank you. Thank you.
Where are you going, baby?
Baby!
Go.
Go in.
My Lord.
Qing?
You didn't know I was the Man in White until now?
Princess Longshuang.
Did you deliberately dress up as a refugee
so we'd save you when we were at Green Wave Villa?
I like to sit in the front row when enjoying a show.
Besides, if I hadn't done that,
I couldn't have gained your trust.
I heard
you have something I want,
and you want to make a deal with me.
Where's the blood letter?
As long as you agree to my condition,
I'll give you the blood letter.
What's your condition?
Cooperate with me.
Cooperate?
Long Tuqi
is just a usurper.
I, Longshuang Yueshu,
am the only living member of the Yanle royal family.
I am the rightful ruler of Yanle.
You're a smart person.
You should know who to cooperate with to gain more.
That makes sense.
But I don't trust you.
I know you're here to avenge Kang Yunhai.
Thanks, baby.
Go, baby. Go.
Baby.
Baby!
Yes,
I did think about killing you.
But what will happen if I kill you?
Long Tuqi will still be the ruler of Yanle.
The people will still be suffering.
I want to restore peace and order in Yanle.
This is far more important than avenging one person.
I didn't expect
you to have such a great ambition right after becoming the princess.
This is not my ambition.
This is my conscience.
I've seen too many people become homeless
and forced to leave their hometowns.
I've seen my loved ones
die one by one.
All of this is because of Long Tuqi.
You're nothing
but his henchman.
The most ridiculous thing
is you're the only one
who can help me achieve my goal.
If you take me back to Yanle,
help me get rid of Long Tuqi,
and help me become the queen,
I'll give you the blood letter.
You can control
those officials loyal to my father.
We'll stay out of each other's way.
This is the deal I want to make with you.
As for Uncle Kang,
I will grant him a posthumous honor
and make sure he's highly esteemed
to repay him for raising me over the years.
Longshuang Yueshu,
you truly are a member of the Longshuang family.
Okay. I agree to your condition.
But you must first give me the blood letter
as a show of good faith.
It's inside my dagger.
Inside the handle.
My Lord!
My master began learning to use poisons when he was a child.
He's long become immune to all poisons.
I advise you not to play any tricks.
I can't believe I was fooled by you.
You bitch.
Let her go!
Yuan Mo.
It's you.
Greetings, Mr. Yuan...
Don't come any closer.
If you come any closer, I'll burn the blood letter.
Give me the blood letter.
I'll give it to you
after you let her go.
Give it to me.
Let her go first!
I'll say it again.
Let her go.
Ah Shu, come here.
Give me the blood letter.
Take it.
San Niang!
Let's go.
Run!
Ah Shu.
Ah Shu, are you alright?
I'm fine.
I'm sorry.
The blood letter was burned.
It's okay.
I've already memorized the content.
Your Highness.
There's only one female corpse inside.
Her face is unrecognizable.
Only one female corpse?
Where's the Man in White?
There's a secret passage in the room,
but it was destroyed by the explosion.
He escaped again.
Have you seen this person?
No.
Look carefully. Have you seen this person?
Chief Secretary Yuchi.
We've put up notices and bolstered guard
in Anle District, Sweet Spring Square,
and the main street.
Tell our men to guard all the city gates
closely.
Yes.
Chief Secretary Yuchi.
There's news from Yuan Mo
that they've already destroyed The Faceless's hideout.
But only that female criminal was killed in the explosion.
The Man in White escaped.
The Man in White escaped?
Tell the men of the West Court
to assist the soldiers of the Jingzhao Prefecture
in searching all the foreign merchants' shops.
Yes.
Let's go.
The bounty for capturing the assassin is 30,000 taels.
Who is she? I've never seen her.
There's another one over there.
Another one?
The world is in turmoil.
They both wear white clothes.
Mr. Xiang, how much is the bounty for capturing that man?
I don't know.
That's the Man in White.
I haven't seen them before.
This man and this woman.
That's right.
They should be caught.
Twenty-four years old.
About 88 inches tall.
Fair-skinned, black hair.
Uncle Kang.
I received the co-signed blood letter you left me.
I've memorized
all the names on it.
Unfortunately,
I failed to kill the Man in White to avenge you.
Now that the Man in White and The Faceless have left Changle,
they won't be a threat to me anymore.
You can rest in peace now.
Send Uncle Kang on his way.
Uncle Kang.
I'm a lonely person.
You gave me my first home in my memory.
When I was little,
my happiest moments
were when you visited me in Huangsha Village.
Now I've grown up
and become the princess,
but we can never see each other again.
I swear
I will take you home.
I'm tired.
I want to go to bed early.
You don't need to keep me company.
Your Highness.
Yuan Mo...
has been waiting for you.
When did you get here?
I've been here for a while.
Do you need to talk to me?
Can't I come to see you without a reason?
That's not what I mean.
You wouldn't
ask this in the past.
What's wrong?
Is there something on your mind?
Yes.
It's been three days, Ah Shu.
When are you going to tell me
why you went to see the Man in White alone?
I...
That day, you ordered lots of dishes.
You were wolfing them down.
Did you think it was your last meal?
When you said those words when we were drinking,
were you saying goodbye to me?
If I hadn't found your handkerchief,
you would be dead now.
Do you know what that means?
Why?
What do you take me for?
You weren't like this before.
I'm sorry, Yuan Mo.
I had no choice.
My loved ones died in front of me one by one.
When I had a chance to take revenge,
I couldn't miss it.
But I didn't want to get you in trouble.
Nor did I want to drag Wang
and Yuchi into this.
I couldn't make them take the risk with me.
I couldn't bear
to lose any one of you.
So, you wanted us to bear
the pain of losing you?
Have you ever thought
about how sad we'd be
if something had happened to you?
What would I do?
How would I face a life without you?
Yuan Mo.
Ever since you became Princess Yanle,
you've been reassuring me
that nothing would change.
I tried hard to believe you.
I tried hard to deceive myself.
But what happened then?
Reality kept reminding me
that everything had changed.
You've changed, too.
You're no longer the Ah Shu I used to know.
You are Princess Yanle.
You care
about your Uncle Kang,
Ah Shilan,
and all of your subjects.
There's just no room in your heart
for me, who only wishes you
safety and happiness.
That's not true, Yuan Mo.
You've always been in my heart.
I admit
I failed to keep my promise to you.
I've changed.
I've become burdened with worries.
I've become stubborn and willful.
That's because I have too many responsibilities,
and too many people have lost their lives because of me.
I've often wondered
if the villagers of Huangsha Village could have survived
had I not run away.
Had I admitted that I am the princess earlier,
Ah Shilan might not have killed herself,
and Uncle Kang might still be alive.
After all that has happened,
how could I still live a carefree life in Changle
like before?
So, you've made up your mind?
You were serious when you said
you'd take Uncle Kang home?
I see, Your Highness.
[Changle]
Urgent news from Yanle!
Make way!
There's urgent news from Yanle
that the puppet ruler installed by Long Tuqi died of illness.
All Yanle people are in mourning to show their grief.
Isn't this what Long Tuqi has wanted all along?
Perhaps this puppet ruler
was poisoned by him.
That's possible.
But it's no longer important.
What's important is that during the mourning period,
Long Tuqi announced to the people of Yanle
that he will bring Princess Longshuang back
to rule the state with him
for the state's future.
The official document demanding the return of Princess Longshuang from Yong
is already on its way.
We should firmly reject Long Tuqi's request,
expose his crimes of rebellion and usurpation,
and condemn his intention of using the royal family to elevate himself.
Meanwhile, we should warn the people of Yanle and the other states in the desert
not to be deceived by Long Tuqi's words.
Yuan Mo, what do you think?
Although I don't think
Retainer An should always put interests first,
on this particular matter,
on a political level and on a personal level,
I hope Princess Longshuang can stay in Changle.
But...
But what?
But I believe
as a powerful and prosperous state,
Yong should convince a foreign desert state
with righteousness.
We're protecting Princess Longshuang
from Long Tuqi's persecution.
This is a righteous act.
It is for Yong.
But for Yanle,
I'm afraid it's debatable.
Why?
Although Princess Longshuang's title was given by Yong,
she is the princess of Yanle after all.
The blood of the Yanle royal family runs in her veins.
Every citizen of Yanle is her subject.
But now, under Long Tuqi's rule, the people of Yanle
are suffering.
The princess loves her people.
What is righteous
to her?
What should she do
to be considered righteous
by the Yanle people?
I'm not wise enough.
I humbly request guidance from you, my superiors.
That makes sense.
According to what you said,
Princess Longshuang should neither stay
nor leave.
Perhaps we should listen
to what the princess has to say.
Princess Longshuang is here.
Greetings, Your Highness.
Please rise.
Your Highness,
please have a seat.
No, thanks.
Your Highness, did you come here
to discuss something important with us?
I've heard that Long Tuqi wants me back
to Yanle.
Vice Minister An, I'm here to tell you
that I'm willing to return to Yanle.
Your Highness, please think twice.
Long Tuqi has evil intentions.
He doesn't want to rule Yanle together with you.
Mr. Yu, no more words, please.
I've made up my mind.
It's going to be a long journey,
and there will be no turning back.
That's right.
I am a member of the Yanle royal family.
How can I live like a coward
for my own selfish reasons?
I chose this path.
I will never regret it.
Milk ice cream.
Fresh milk ice cream.
Come and take a look.
Milk ice cream.
Young Master.
I'd like a bowl of milk ice cream.
It's just enough.
Take care.
Milk ice cream.
Milk ice cream for sale.
Madam, would you like some milk ice cream?
Your Highness.
Here.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Here, take this.
Thank you.
Here.
Here. Go put it on.
-Thank you.
-Your Highness, this is heavier.
-Here. Go put it on.
-Thank you.
Go get some more.
Your Highness,
there's nothing left.
How's that possible?
There are so many people who haven't received anything.
There was enough for everyone.
However, the number of refugees
has somehow been increasing over the past few days.
It seems something did go wrong in Yanle.
Si Niang,
go make more clothes and quilts.
Yes, Your Highness.
Your Highness,
is there nothing left for us?
Didn't they say we could live a good life
after coming to Yong?
Right.
How can we survive the cold?
Your Highness, please save us!
Your Highness, you can't turn your back on us!
Everyone, please stand up.
Don't worry.
I promise everyone will get clothes.
Go warm yourselves by the fire and get a bowl of porridge first.
Make sure you don't catch a cold.
New winter clothes and quilts will arrive soon.
Go.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Madam.
Here.
Thank you, Your Highness!
Please get up.
Madam,
what exactly happened in Yanle?
Why are there suddenly so many refugees?
In order to get more people on his side, Long Tuqi allowed
nobles and officials to plunder the people's money and food.
We poor people
could barely survive!
Go have a bowl of porridge to warm yourself up first.
Come. I'll take you there.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Come, madam.
Here.
Thank you, Your Highness.