Liu Yu
Yang Yang
I chose you at first
because you are software engineering majors.
Now
it's time for you to use your strengths.
You'll learn from me for a while
and then work with me
to develop a mobile app.
But remember
you must keep this confidential.
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
What are you scheming this time?
You really know me.
That Zhang Liang kid
has moved up the development timeline for the Fruit Phone.
This means
he has changed the times.
Technology
is now entering a period of rapid advancement ahead of schedule.
As soon as this phone hits the market,
customers will love it.
It will become a nationwide sensation.
So
we need to develop
a game software that can be compatible with this phone.
a game software.
You mean
this is the same as when we outsourced Yuanqi
the same kind of situation?
Yeah.
But Zhang Liang has always been against us.
Would he agree to work with us?
We'll have to come up with a way.
President Ye,
long time no see.
Our President Li
has become even more handsome.
President Ye, doing this
aren't you afraid President Zhang will get angry?
You really
know how to kill the mood.
President Ye, you've kept things well hidden.
I only just found out
that you and President Zhang
are married.
You were the one who reached out to me.
You didn't just come to hear gossip, did you?
President Ye is straightforward.
You definitely wouldn't get mad
over a joke.
I came to see you today
because I want to discuss a collaboration with you.
You want to work with me?
Yes.
The Fruit Phone developed by Mr. Zhang
is about to be launched.
As for this phone,
I know a bit about it.
To retain users,
besides the essential software,
lifestyle and entertainment apps are also indispensable.
I have a mobile app
that would be a great fit for your Fruit Phone.
I can't give you an answer on this right now.
However,
I can ask Mr. Zhang for his opinion
and get back to you later.
Alright.
Then,
thank you in advance, Mr. Ye.
Goodbye.
I never thought Li Tian would come to me for help one day.
But his idea is actually pretty good.
Isn't Chen Yang
also competing for the software agency rights?
But Chen Yang's technology isn't very stable yet.
It still needs improvement.
Enough with the nonsense.
The old-timers at the company are watching me closely.
We can't let Li Tian take advantage of this.
Contact the person in charge at Chen Yang
and agree to work with them.
As for Li Tian,
let's keep him waiting for now.
Leave.
Is there anything else?
Tianming Group said
they could consider signing an agency contract.
But they still haven't given us the contract.
Sister Lin, don't worry yet.
Since Brother Tian said this can work out,
there shouldn't be any problem.
Yeah.
Don't worry.
This technology,
if you look across the whole country,
no, actually,
to be precise,
it's the whole world.
Only our Qianxi's technology meets the standard.
They probably
wouldn't risk their own future as a joke.
Let's hope so.
Yeah.
Let's go.
Okay.
Yeah.
Sorry about that.
Thank you all for waiting.
Today, our Tianming Group
is holding the decision meeting for the mobile system software agency.
So,
we've invited two
potential future partner
company representatives
to attend this meeting.
The proposal from Qianxi
in terms of logic and technology
is excellent.
Therefore,
after careful consideration and research,
we have decided to grant the agency rights
to
Chenyang Company as the sole agent.
Congratulations, President Chen.
Mr. Li
Our company, Qianxi,
has only recently switched industries.
So in terms of experience and technology,
we're definitely not as good as Chen Yang.
I'm really sorry about that.
Thank you for your trust.
Looking forward to working together.
Logically, the technology provided by Qianxi Group
should actually be more advanced.
That's right.
I remember Qianxi did really well
in the gaming industry.
What a fool who can't see real talent.
Let's talk about
today's hot topics in technology.
Tianming Group announced today
that their smart Fruit Phone has officially launched.
It has made a strong entry into the domestic market,
with its unprecedented high-performance specs
and revolutionary user experience,
officially opening a new chapter in communication history.
It has sparked a buying frenzy.
Sir,
may I interview you
about your thoughts on the Xiaoyao game?
It's so convenient to play games on this phone.
And this game is really fun.
Ma'am,
may I interview you
about your thoughts on the Xiaoyao game?
Although the price is a bit high,
there are many helpful lifestyle apps included.
There are even makeup tutorials.
Stop watching.
Let's eat.
Alright.
Let's go.
Mr. Li, someone is here to see you.
Mr. Chen.
Long time no see.
Let me introduce you.
This is Mr. Chen,
an old friend.
We still have to thank Mr. Li.
Our Xiaoyao
has not only made huge profits,
but the other lifestyle apps
have also earned quite a lot.
When did you two start working together?
Hello.
Oh, please come in.
Are you Chen Yu?
Yes, I am.
I know you.
You're a top student from the Computer Science Department at Qingbei University.
Currently, you're starting your own business.
You want to create your own internet company.
Oh, let me introduce myself.
I'm the founder of Millennium Investment Company.
Li Tian.
I'm willing to invest in you.
Okay.
Oh.
Thank you.
So you two set this up from the beginning.
That's right.
It's because Mr. Li gave me startup funding.
Otherwise, I wouldn't have achieved what I have today.
Well played, Li Tian.
You even kept it from the two of us.
Exactly.
Isn't it because you and Xia Yu acted so poorly?
I was afraid you two would give it away.
What are you talking about?
You're something else.
And you didn't even say anything.
Yeah.
I did it for the company.
You kept it from us.
You didn't tell us just because it was for the company?
Mr. Chen is still here.
The real boss behind Chenyang Company is actually Li Tian.
We just found out too.
He fooled all of us.
Terminate the contract for me immediately.
I won't let him make another cent off me.
But our contract is for ten years.
If we terminate it now,
we'll have to pay a huge penalty.
If I say terminate, then terminate.
Stop with all the nonsense.
As for the shareholders,
I developed the phone.
They've made so much money.
What right do they have to bargain with me?
When you met Li Tian before,
what did you say to him?
Nothing.
I didn't say anything.
Help!