No.
This is just too infuriating.
They're clearly the ones copying us.
And yet they're the ones playing the victim.
Tian.
We can't just let this go, can we?
A gentleman's revenge is never too late.
Don't be so impulsive.
That's how it is.
Behind Tianming,
there's a powerful programming team.
They stole our ideas
and business secrets.
Then, using their massive user base,
they suppressed us and overtook us.
After that, they refined it further.
They don't copy outright,
they just "draw inspiration."
On top of that,
they have a strong legal team behind them.
It's hard for us to catch them out.
It's tough for us to win.
So how do we turn this situation around?
Let's look at it from another perspective.
If our product can be copied,
it means our product
has gained commercial recognition.
The more our competitors go out of their way to suppress us,
doesn't that just show they're afraid of us?
As long as we keep innovating
and upgrading our products,
maintaining our vitality,
we'll always remain unbeatable.
So what do you plan to do next?
I plan to
develop a brand new product.
I've even thought of the name.
It will be called
Heart Moon Dream Journey.
Brother Tian,
you're still such a romantic.
And this,
is also a gift for my wife.
How do we have the money to develop a new game right now?
Find new investors.
I support you.
You little rascal.
You surprise me every time.
That piece of land you resold to me last time,
has doubled in value again.
So, how about it?
Do you regret it?
Of course I don't regret it.
You deserved it in the first place, Brother Fang.
But,
your investment this time is a bit large.
My personal cash flow
isn't enough.
But I just met a few people
who might
be able to help you.
That would be perfect.
Thank you so much, Brother Fang.
Then I won't stand on ceremony with you.
Thank you for making the introductions.
Fish.
Hurry.
Don't do yours yet.
Shake it, shake it.
You,
don't put too much pressure on yourself.
You need to find a balance.
Right now,
haven't we already taken a step toward success?
Thank you, dear—
Thank you for caring, honey.
Brother Tian,
Xiaoyu is here.
Sister Xinyue,
I heard from Sister Wanqing
that you're starting a new business again.
That's life.
It's about growing through each failure
and becoming stronger.
So inspiring.
Yeah.
Here is ten million.
This is the money you worked hard to earn.
I can't accept it.
This is my investment.
Please take it.
Why are you investing money?
I can't take this money.
Brother Tian,
I want to make money too.
I've thought it over and over.
Your project is the most reliable.
So,
please help me make money.
What,
you don't want to help me make money?
No,
you don't want me to get rich?
Sister-in-law, look at him.
Just accept it.
We're all family.
Let's make money together.
That's right.
I have a share too.
It's not much,
but it's still an investment.
Alright.
Then,
it's settled.
Anyway, I won't let you lose money.
Okay.
Hello, Brother Fang.
My friends from foreign companies
have already set up a meeting for you.
Tomorrow morning at eight.
Come to my company to meet them.
Really?
Thank you, Brother Fang.
Chairman
Sparks received good feedback as soon as it launched.
But it also got a lot of negative reviews.
They say we
have too much overlap with our previous games.
None of these are real problems.
How are things going with Li Tian?
It's said he's developing a new game.
But all his employees have been let go.
How could he have the funds to develop a new game?
How are the talks with Blizzard going?
Sparks
They think it's not influential enough yet.
But they're very interested in our game in development, Defender.
They're still very interested.
Speed up the development.
Make sure we can collaborate with Blizzard.
For us,
this would be a major breakthrough.
Okay.
Li Tian
Will you make a comeback or stay a loser?
Let's see what you're really capable of.
Honey, come out quickly!
Coming, coming!
We're going to be late!
You're going to nag me to death.
Let me see.
Is it okay?
My husband is so handsome.
Let's go.
Wait.
All the clients today are foreigners.
Are you sure you don't need a translator?
No, I don't.
But...
I need
some encouragement.
What?
Let's go.
Go.
Next,
Let's have Mr. Li present the design plan.
What you're seeing here
is our character design sketch.
Dear Mr. Li,
we also hope
to collaborate with Millennium on "Heart Moon Dream Journey."
This would be a win-win situation for both of us.
Your company is famous worldwide.
Let's work together.
Mr. Li,
I believe our company can contribute
to character creation.
As for the investment,
we are also very interested.
Alright.
Wishing us a successful partnership.
We're back again.
Mr. Li, Mr. Lin,
everyone,
you're all back.
Is everyone here?
Everyone's here.
Well then,
Are you ready?
Ready.
This time,
we must succeed.
Failure is not an option.
Let's do our best!
Go, go!
Eat up.
Okay.
Here.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Do you want to eat something first?
This is your favorite.
It's done.
The "Xinyue Dream Journey" game
has been successfully created.
You’re amazing.
That's great, that's great!
Mr. Zhang.
Dinner with the person in charge of Fengxue
is scheduled for 6:30.
You should get going.
Okay.
Got it.
Mr. Zhang, your arrangements are very thoughtful.
This place is pretty good.
Yeah.
Perfect.
Delicious, delicious.
Really good.
Mr. Qin.
Yes?
The next steps
are in your hands.