Let me tell you some good news.
Tianming and Chen Yang forcibly terminated their contracts.
They paid a large amount in penalties.
This battle made Zhang Liang suffer a loss.
He probably won't let this go easily.
What if he tries to get back at us?
Don't worry.
Now, we
are no longer left with nothing.
It's time to have a real showdown with Zhang Liang.
Today is a good day.
Let's give everyone a day off.
Get some rest early.
Let's have dinner together tonight.
To celebrate.
Alright.
But I'll have to go a bit later.
Right now,
I need to help my wife at the restaurant.
Take care.
Okay.
Thanks.
Xinyue.
How about we close the restaurant?
It's too exhausting.
Why?
Isn't this pretty good?
I'm just worried about you every day,
working so hard.
Then you should help out more.
Yes, ma'am.
Mm-hmm.
Go ahead.
I'll put this in.
Okay.
Xinyue.
Coming.
Yeah.
The usual.
Alright.
Take care of him.
Excuse me.
Mr. Li
You always put your hard work into useless things.
What are you guys doing?
I thought he looked too lonely eating by himself.
Keep him company.
Come on, help us get two bottles of beer.
Beer.
Don't drink too much.
Thanks.
Here, Mr. Guo.
Let me toast you.
Thank you every day
for looking after our Xinyue's business.
Xinyue is a great cook.
I can only get used to her cooking.
That's true.
Every day,
I get to eat the late-night snacks Xinyue makes for me with love.
Looks like Xinyue works really hard.
It's not enough to be busy at the shop,
she still has to take care of someone at home.
Someone who can't take care of himself.
Some people want to be taken care of
but don't even get the chance.
You didn't know how to cherish it before.
Why pretend to be so devoted now?
Say that to me again.
I said, why are you pretending to be so devoted?
You...
What are you two doing now?
Cheers.
Everyone, behave yourselves.
Mm.
This is called realizing one's mistakes and changing.
It's not too late.
I hope so.
Come on.
Weren't you going to drink with me?
Let's compete.
Yeah.
Come on.
We won't stop until we're drunk.
You old rascal.
Stop drinking.
It's getting dark.
I made hangover soup for you two.
Hurry up and drink it.
Thank you.
Childish.
Hey.
Don't forget the celebration dinner tonight.
Xinyue.
Yeah.
Our company is having a celebration dinner tonight.
Do you want to come with us?
I can't leave right now.
Why don't you go ahead first?
I'll come find you later.
Okay, finish up early and come find me.
Okay.
Get up.
Let's go back.
Alright.
Um, Xinyue.
I'll come see you again later.
Why come again?
I already drank you all under the table.
Be careful.
Who was the first to pass out?
Great singing.
Come on, come on.
Li Tian.
An incredible man.
Go, go, go.
No, no, no.
Thank you for everything you've done for us.
Let's do it together.
Let's toast to him.
Cheers.
Come on, cheers.
Come on, come on.
Cheers.
Li Tian.
Thank you.
Brother Tian.
Come on.
Thank you all, too.
Cheers, cheers.
Drink up, I'm telling you.
You have to drink well.
Some things,
don't take them to heart, okay?
Brother Tian, why did Brother Tian leave?
Why isn't my wife here yet?
Hmm.
Why isn't she answering the phone?
Could it be that Guo Wenbang is still bothering her?
Li Tian
Why did you come out?
Why are you here?
Qing
Why do you look
a little sad?
I just feel
that starting a business together
has really not been easy.
I really didn't expect
even a strong woman like you would have moments of sadness.
How about this,
if you have any anger
or if you're upset about something,
just hit me.
Hit me a couple of times, it'll help.
Don't move.
Let me lean on you for a while.
It's okay.
Li Tian
Do you know,
Mm.
I once loved a man.
He was just like you,
talented,
smart and wise.
I thought I had found
the most reliable man in the world.
But I never expected
he would use me
and cheat me out of all my family property.
Wanqing
The past
is already behind you.
Besides,
you still have me now.
And Xia Yu,
Jun,
we can all protect you.
Li Tian
Yeah
You're better than him
Tian
Wanqing, you...
Xia Yu
What happened to you guys?
Wanqing
Xia Yu
Tian
How did you all end up drinking this much?
Let me help you back
Okay
A big brother fell from the sky
Look at all of you
Why did you drink so much?
Why did you push me over here?
I don't know either
But
I really like you
What did you say?
She's a real beauty
Who are you?
You're in my way
Let go of me
Come home with me
My cat can do backflips
Wanqing
This is bad
Beautiful lady
Stay here
Don't go anywhere
Let's have some fun together
Yeah, that's right
Come on, come on
Let go of me
Let go of her