I've already got what you wanted.
What about mine?
I've already drafted the contract.
Pleasure working with you.
I hope that when the time comes,
you'll keep your promise.
What's going on here?
The character design concept for Guardian.
Why is it exactly the same as Dream Journey of Heartmoon?
I don't know.
Then last night,
did you see anyone suspicious
come to my office?
I'm not sure.
I'll go check now.
That's right.
I was the one who gave the information to Zhang Liang.
Why?
When you had nothing,
I was the one by your side.
When you had no money,
I gave it to you.
When you had no connections,
I gave them to you.
When you argued with your wife,
I was always the one comforting you.
Now you have everything.
Your relationship is going well too.
And now you just want to kick me aside.
When did I ever want to kick you aside?
Wanqing.
I never thought you would misunderstand me this much.
Misunderstand?
Li Tian.
I do like you.
Even knowing you have a wife,
I still like you.
But I just can't control it.
I'm being pathetic.
I can lose to her in love.
But I just can't understand
why you brought her into the company.
And now you're pushing me out at work too.
What do you take me for?
Wanqing, don't get so worked up.
We've been through so much together.
Is there anything we can't solve together?
Let go of me.
Lin Wanqing.
Li Tian.
I'm officially announcing now
that I'm leaving Qianxi Company.
Come on,
let's welcome our Director Lin
to join Tianming Group.
Hello, everyone.
I'm Lin Wanqing.
From now on, we'll be colleagues.
I look forward to working with you all.
Mr. Li
We can't pay this month's salaries anymore.
Most of last month's salaries are still owed to the staff.
Let's dissolve the company.
Is there really no other way to save us?
At this point, there's nothing else we can do.
We invested all our funds
into Xinyue Dream Journey.
We even signed a partnership agreement with Fengxue.
Now the game data has been leaked.
We can't afford the penalty for breach of contract.
We can only use all our game assets
as collateral to Fengxue.
I'm sorry, Xinyue.
I've let you down.
This isn't your fault.
How could Sister Wanqing betray Qianxi?
Is there some kind of misunderstanding here?
There's no misunderstanding.
She admitted it to me herself.
She even went to work at Tianming.
Honey,
at worst, we can just start over.
Life is full of ups and downs.
But no matter what happens,
I'll always be by your side.
I'll help you make a comeback.
Brother Tian,
I support you too.
Mr. Li,
I support you as well.
Gather everyone
for a meeting.
Our Millennium Company
is very fortunate
to have everyone's companionship and support.
However, our company
due to work-related mistakes
is now unable to operate normally anymore.
But everyone, please rest assured,
I will have the HR department
issue back pay for the past two months' salaries.
Thank you for your hard work.
President Li,
Xin Yue Meng Lv is everyone's hard work.
Are we really going to give up just like this?
We all know very well.
If we keep working on Heart Moon Dream Journey,
it still won't help.
We can still make changes.
We can build on this foundation
and create a version even better than the first Heart Moon Dream Journey.
A better game.
Yes.
That's right.
We can revise it.
Yes, exactly.
But the company
can no longer afford to pay everyone's salaries.
I'm willing to stay and work on Heart Moon Dream Journey.
Millennium Company
has given me so many happy memories.
I don't want to see it just disappear.
I believe
if we hold on for two more months,
the revised Heart Moon Dream Journey
will be even better.
I'm willing too.
I'm willing.
Me too.
The company is truly lucky
to have had you all by its side.
However,
I really won't force anyone.
Those who want to stay can stay.
If you don't want to stay,
I'll have HR
pay you the back wages for the past two months.
Today
It's really lively.
What are you doing here?
Miss Xia Yu, there's no need to be hostile.
I'm not your enemy.
I'm willing to lend you money to help you through this difficult time.
And
I don't need any interest.
Why are you helping me, President Ye?
Because
I'm also one of Qianxi's shareholders.
So
You admit it.
You were the one who provided that ten million.
That's right.
But aren't you Zhang Liang's wife?
What exactly is your goal?
Of course, I have my own plans.
So, what do you think?
This money—
Do you want it or not?
Of course.
Brother Tian
I can also contribute some funds.
If it weren't for Brother Tian's help back then,
I wouldn't be who I am today.
Now that you're facing difficulties,
as a shareholder,
I also have an obligation to share the hardship.
Don't forget,
I'm here too.
I'm also one of the shareholders.
Thank you all.
Let me out!
Let go of me!
Who are you?
Zhang Liang
What are you going to do?
Your value has already been used up.
A discarded item
naturally needs to be disposed of.