The King's Avatar
Episode 16
Uncle Feng!
Uncle Feng, I've been with you for so many years!
How could I do this to you?
Uncle Feng, I wronged you!
Uncle Feng!
Uncle Feng, the man was cheated by the Black Ghost.
The gold was lost by the Black Ghost.
You took the water room back.
I never talked to Wang Jincheng.
How could I be the mole?
Uncle Feng, the 13th Office is always cautious.
He knew I was going to do it.
He deliberately put such important documents
in the office.
He's fishing! He's fishing!
He's fishing me!
Bullshit!
Uncle Feng, I came for the antidote.
I wanted to save my sister.
But you stole it.
You framed me again!
You cheated me again!
I'm telling you.
If anything happens to my sister,
I'll kill you!
Uncle Feng, the 13th Office did ask me
for help because he wanted to save my sister.
I think he's very emotional.
So I agreed to let him try.
I didn't expect Brother Dong...
Uncle Feng! Uncle Feng, listen to me!
I want evidence! I want evidence, Uncle Feng!
Xiong, let him go.
Uncle Feng, I have evidence.
Last time, on the 13th,
my subordinate was found.
Uncle Feng, let me make a call.
I beg you. Let me make a call.
You'll know immediately what kind of person he is!
Give him a call.
Thank you, Uncle Feng.
Thank you, Sister Zha.
He's my subordinate.
He's not investigating at all.
I don't want to be caught easily.
I don't want it to be a misunderstanding.
Do you understand?
If he doesn't want this,
the dog has a good hammer in its back.
He knows it's dangerous.
This is exactly why he decided to use lower power.
There simply can't be Hello.
All right?
Fine.
People who mention the number,
Han Che, you're a crazy man
Just a phone call
I know the enemy is a man and a ghost
I can tell him
I can also say you are a cop
Dongge Dongge
I have a group of photos
I'll send it to you
Send it to me quickly
Han Che
This is your father
This is you
This is Jingfu
Why don't you admit it and still want to hurt me?
Feng Zhong, look
Zhang Xin, look
Look
Look at him
He is a cop
Officer Han
You're hiding it really deep
Lock him in
Uncle Feng, you framed me
Uncle Feng, this photo is a fart
Heiguedong, I can't forgive you
You can't forgive me
Boy, you're crazy
Brother Dongge, is it convenient for you to talk now?
Say it, say it quickly
Captain Dong, Shisan is just a small role
Those photos just now
Can only solve the problem of the original beauty
The police have ordered to kill
The whole station will be bombed
You must not be careless
Hun Cheng
What did you say?
He is a cop
Old man, my brother is on a business trip
When will you come back?
what
My ears are not working
I said my brother is on a business trip
When will you come back?
Yes, yes, yes
My ears can't hear clearly
Young man, sit down first
I'll get you a glass of water
Brother Dongge
This Shisan is a cop
Come, come, come, drink water
Old man, when did this photo come out?
Yes, yes, yes
My ears have been sick for a long time
It's heavy and light at the same time
Uncle, my brother's job is too hard
I have been persuading him not to be a cop
Do business with me and make some money
How good is that?
He just doesn't listen and has ideals
What? You want to eat pears?
No, uncle, I don't want to eat pears
You eat it yourself, I'll go
What are you doing?
No, no, no
How can I eat it myself?
Young man, you are a guest
Sit down first
I'll wash your nose
No, uncle, you can hear me
What? My ears are not good
You speak louder
Coming
Young man, sit down first
Open the door
No, uncle, you can hear me
Uncle
What?
Sit down first, young man, don't rush
He is still here
He has been asking about Han Chuan
I will stabilize him
Although our Lan Ye succeeded this time
But the fraud group may suspect Han Chuan
Master, you mean
They will definitely investigate him in China
You should keep an eye on Han Chuan's family
Captain Dong
We cooperate well with the water room
Sister Zhan
The comrades of the imperial court
have found many useful clues
The provincial court has given new orders
Under the premise of your guarantee of safety
Collect evidence of Yan Xu's brain and iron Buddha
Try to lure him back to the country
and be punished by law
Captain Dong
You should be careful in the fraud group
We will cooperate with you
When you retreat
You...
Uncle
I will actively cooperate with you
It's a good thing for you
It's a good thing
Uncle
I wronged them
I wronged them, uncle
Uncle
Han Chuan
You are so cruel
You are so cruel, Han Chuan
Uncle
Uncle, please believe me
I...
They all did harm to me, uncle
I said you finally told me
Uncle, please believe me
I still can make money with you
Uncle
God, you bastard
My brother is just a low-born
He has no family
Uncle
Look at Shisan
He is not greedy for money and not interested in color
Now that the position of Black Ghost Cave is out
You see
Shisan
Do you think he is greedy or not?
Which one is good?
The person who was cheated is greedy for money
Black Ghost Cave is out of the way to seize power
Si Hai has been unable to be promoted
That's for color
You are different from them
After you came in
I have observed you for a long time
You don't talk about anything
What else is good?
Money, money, woman
I have enjoyed all these in China
In the end, the police did everything
I appreciate your ability
You can start over here
and get back everything you lost
Uncle He, I came here
One is to find my sister
The other is to hide from the police
So I don't ask for much to do under Uncle He
I only ask for uncle He
Your sister will take good care of her
You can stay here and do your work
The rest
You don't have to think about anything
Drink the soup
Okay
Shisan, thank Uncle Buddha
Thank you, Uncle Buddha.
You're kind and thoughtful.
Not bad.
Uncle Buddha,
don't worry.
I'll let Shisan sit in the black hole.
Thank you, Uncle Buddha, for saving me.
I'll be grateful.
But I just arrived here, I'm still a newcomer.
I shouldn't be so hasty.
Don't be so anxious.
I'll give you time.
Think about it.
Yeah.
Thank you, Uncle Buddha.
Thank you, Miss.
With one stone,
with two stones,
we'll send all skills for you,
and your drinking ability.
Hey.
Zhai Shi went into the black hole.
Who would he be
if he misses the spot?
Of course it must be our Hai.
But I heard that
I'm so embarrassed.
Go.
Eat.
Brother.
Tie Fuzhen wants you to replace
Pei Guidong's position.
So you agreed?
No.
That's good.
You don't know
Ba Sihai is now
the top position.
If you agree,
you'll offend him.
Then we'll never
cross the line again.
Sister won't be able to send him out.
Yes.
Think about it.
Brother.
Give me a bowl of mung bean soup.
It's hot.
Uncle.
My name is Sang Tuo.
I'm Brother 13's brother.
Say it.
Uncle.
You can't let Brother 13
replace Pei Guidong's position.
Why?
We have 400 or 500 people.
The most important thing
is balance.
13 is Ba Sihai's man.
If he really
replaced Pei Guidong's position,
it's like Ba Sihai
has the whole second floor.
When he gets more powerful,
it'll be hard
to balance.
Go on.
We have a lot of people.
I just want to make money.
More and more money.
Uncle Buddha gave me the most money.
I only listen to him.
I, Sang Tuo,
beg Uncle Buddha
to give me another chance.
Three months.
In three months,
I'll make Lu Liao Clan
a rich family.
If I can't do it,
Sang Tuo will come to see you
with his head.
You're brave.
Your personality and appearance
remind me of
an old friend.
After me too,
I almost died.
Why?
My heart Stew bag.
I have never had aouchi since I was born.
Life is like a movie.
The balance of the waves, the whirlpool above
The dawn has never fainted