The King's Avatar
Episode legislative
Peishuang
Once we meet,
I'll dive into the sea
to realise my wish
Wait a moment
Captain
Hello
Brother
Where are you going?
That's my professional habit.
You can say that
this is a cookie to a
He's really here.
You can imagine
if he's here
in a second,
I'd get Strategists
to take me
You can cheat 9999 times
What's wrong?
Is this your rule?
Brother Hai
Four nine is my lucky number
Every first day of the month
is this number
It can bring good luck
You can say you are not capable
Lucky number
You know what?
My brother's lucky number
can bring us good luck
Our team is full of good luck
This meat is not enough
Lucky number
What's wrong?
Our team is better than yours
We have opened three or four orders today
Unlike some teams
who didn't make any money
Look, take a good look
Do you know what is a store?
Do you understand?
No matter how many you have
you are just a small family
You are wasting the money
we bought
I will tell you
about this order
It's a daughter
who bought her mother's life
She has 300,000 yuan in her hand
She has made it
She will close the store tomorrow
Hei Guidong
You can make money by saving her life
I didn't know
you are so noble
We all know
money is money
You can kill or save people
You really take yourself as a policeman
It's a pity that you are wearing this
You don't want to do it, do you?
Don't do it
Wait for tomorrow
to prepare for the birthday party
Go
You must win her tomorrow
Otherwise
I will send you to the city
Brother, have you seen только?
Brother, have you seen deja vu?
I have checked it
I think Black Ghost does'nt believe universal
I think that at least we must fight on as long as we have dzisiaj!
Okay
Yang YaQi
Stop
I'm busy
No matter how many of you are, you are still a little kid
Look
Look carefully
It's the money that the filial daughter paid her mother
Mom, don't worry
I have already raised enough money in the emperor
I can get it tomorrow
Lv'er, I'm sorry
Hello
Hello, Miss Hu Pei
Your ID number is
213-327-2006-01234-821
You are studying in the literature department of Donghu University
Your mother is living in the country
You are studying in Donghu University, right?
You are
I am the expert in love and hatred
The number 13102
I called you this time
Mainly to inform you
Because our website is behind the scenes
Repair and upgrade
The number is not available
Because our website is behind the scenes
Repair and upgrade
Your money
It will be paid after three to five days
But I
What's wrong?
It's okay, mom
School matter
You rest here first
I'll call you later
Hello
My mother is going to have surgery the day after tomorrow
I really need this money very much
I'm sorry, Miss Hu
What can I do
Can I make it tomorrow?
Without this money, my mother can't do the surgery
I really need it very much
Your situation is very special
How about this?
I'll help you apply
The green channel that was proposed earlier
If you can apply
The fastest tomorrow noon
Can be proposed
Okay, thank you
You're welcome
We need you to re-publish a document
I will send you the application link of the green channel later
Follow the requirements
Just upload the new materials
it is good
Then you send it to me
After the verification
I will contact you immediately
it is good
It's on the table
The virus has entered her phone
As long as I still have to pay her tomorrow
We can end the network
brother
Today we do one thing
Take a step and forget it
You hit the iron while you are here
brother
What are you doing?
What do you mean
This is the rule of my work
You can also understand
Is a good product for the good
Captain An, have breakfast
And then
He finally said
He told me to remember
He said he was going to do it with his heart
With his heart
Han Chuan
What does it mean
An Fei
The time to test our tacit understanding has come
With heart
Powerful and noble
Heart-wrenching
The evil is a crime
The heart is higher than the sky
The evil name of the red horse
Return to the empty turtle
The world is against the east
The evil is trying to take the enemy
The thunder rages in the dream of the Jin family
The eyes and eyes are blinded by the new alliance
The eyes and eyes are blinded by the old and the new
The world is not as good as the chaos
The lie is very pure
Hu Daxue
Hu Pei
Mom, I just finished class
I'll be right over
Hu Pei
Teacher Zhou
How is your mother recently
The doctor said she can arrange the operation tomorrow
You just went to college
Take care of mom
This is our college
Teachers have to be considerate
I hope you don't work too hard
No need, Teacher Zhou
I don't donate money online
The money can be paid today
You can be heavily favored online
We can't donate
This is your loan
Return it to us in the future
it is good
I will definitely return it
Thank you, Teacher Zhou
Dongge
Hu Pei's new money has arrived
Great
I can't get through
You try
Hello
I can't get through either
Hu Pei's phone
It is likely to be cheated
The signal of the user's means of payment
Can't get in
You are not clean
What are you looking at
Get out
I think Dongge's bill is about to be done
I'll come and learn
Brother, don't look
Let's go back and work
it is good
Kid
Let me show you
How you died
All right
Which hospital?
Donghu Hospital.
Okay, thank you.
Hello?
Hello, Ms. Hu Lian.
I'm the customer service of Aisin Chou.
The number is 13102.
I'll contact you tomorrow.
Hello.
Can I make a reservation now?
The materials you submitted
have been reviewed.
The Aisin credit
has been transferred to your account.
You can use it anytime.
Great, thank you.
You can check the bank card
to make sure it's in the account.
Okay.
I see it.
The money is in the account.
Ms. Hu,
you're a special client.
You'll receive a verification code later.
You need to tell me the verification code.
I'll make a memorandum for you.
Okay.
Ms. Hu,
have you received the verification code?
I have.
Let me check.
It's...
Six...
Three...
Nine...
Two...
Fine, you're until now.
Maybe next time I won't be around.
Well, what do you mean?
Let's keep the world safe for now.
The first thing in my mind
is I want to
leave the world with you.
Then,
why don't we
The whirlpool of love never fades away