The King of Blaze
Episode 16
Brother, you've been here for so long.
Aren't you curious about what the seventh floor is?
I'll show you today.
The King of Blaze
Brother, these gold, the money,
and everything here are ours.
You can take these money as you like.
You don't have to agree with me.
You can spend it however you want.
Just spend it however you want.
You can use it to light a candle.
How about it?
The King of Blaze
We need it.
What do you need?
Don't answer yet.
Let me think.
I know.
You need to be a police.
Right?
You need to uphold justice.
You need to kill all criminals.
Brother, take this money.
What are you doing?
From tomorrow,
I'll let Da'an be a new identity for you.
you'll be a great,
glorious member of the Eastern Police.
You can arrest all criminals in the Eastern State.
You can uphold justice.
Here.
All the money here
is your money.
Of course, brother.
If you don't like the law of the Eastern State,
I can change it for you.
You don't know,
the local officials here
like gold very much.
I can use this gold to bribe them.
I can change all the laws
you don't like
into the way you like.
How about it?
Are you really crazy?
How can I be crazy?
We need to be confident, brother.
These laws
are all made by people.
Those who have power and power can make decisions.
Why can't we make decisions?
You can give up.
I can't be like you.
I...
I believe you'll really become my brother.
Just like I believe you'll really come to save me.
Right?
Why don't you take me to the second floor?
I'll let you live here.
I love you.
Okay.
Go.
Clean up the gold house for me.
My brother lives here in the future.
No problem.
Brother.
You must think for your sister
I tell you
Da'an is on the way back
Don't forget your sister and Li Bailing
Are still in the east
What are you doing?
I don't call Da'an
D punct means aMich
Annoying
D
We respect what you do
Please see my progress
O
You two are here to disturb our work
Go
Go inside first
Stay here
Brother
We were hungry just now
We want to go to the toilet
Okay
I'll take you there
Follow me
What's wrong?
The police have a problem
They want to catch us
There is a back door
Let's get out of here
Go
Stop!
Don't move
Li Bailiang, what are you doing?
Go
Li Bailiang
Li Bailiang, get out of here
I didn't hear you
Li Bailiang
Brother, stop
Stop
Li Bailiang
We didn't hear you
Get out of here
Li Bailiang
mantle
i want to get out
Stop
Li Bailiang
I want to get out
I don't want to hide in the darkness
I just know that I'm lost
and forget my old dreams
I'm looking for the light at the end of the world
I've been in the dream for many times
They all want me to give up
and be stubborn
This is my faith
There is still a song
I won't surrender if I have to
The suspect in the water room
gave us an important clue
There is a black box in the middle server in the water room
Every thousand yuan they fraud
and all the transaction records
will be in this black box
This time, we must protect this important evidence
Without evidence
Even if they are brought back
we can't catch them or betray them
Black box
Where did you come from?
They won't be caught
Don't make fun of me
Did you do this for shit?
No
I came up with it
Couldn't go with someone else
Then stay with your dad
You are h차 drowned
I liked you
Have you been alone for long?
I'd been searching for you
These times
I've left this Self-Gather and bad vibes
х
The only thing I have is my money
What about the rest?
Uncle, don't worry
I can fight here
I can hold on
If he insists on going back to China?
No
I believe I can change him
People must have their own purpose in this world
As long as he has his own purpose
I can open his shoes
President Ji
Department of Treasury
Department of Astronomy
tit wiring
T counselling
Chief Of Political Department
Officer
Ten percent of all flagstading
Was shoveled down from the back
Four thousand是什麼 squared
Chief Tet Are you not prepared to affect?
The characteristics of the grace are perfect
mission of the
Zhen摊不就差不多你吗
Absolutely
Can we do it
Run
I
We kill them
We win
It's been 23 years
impression
Don't worry
It's too hard
You'd better fight
Yes
I have about four people
seven
and one
five
six
seven
No, the prison is gone
Go
Go to call the security guard
Call someone
Third brother
This ventilation tunnel
is not only in the entire building
but in every room
Our security guards are not enough now
Then go and call everyone
Go
Okay, okay
Okay, okay, okay
You go too
I have to protect you
It's okay
He won't hurt me
Go
Anshun
What on earth do you want?
We want to look
everyone
pack up
его
Don't worry. I believe we can find the Chinese police soon.
Han Chuan.
Chinese TV Series Exclusive YouTube