They're gonna kill me.
What?
It's all right.
You can go back now.
All right.
We'll meet again.
I'll go out first.
All right.
I'll wait for you there.
Thank you.
Bye.
After you go out,
contact this number.
Who is this?
His name is Da'an.
He's my hair stylist and a police officer.
After you go out,
he'll arrange a hospital and a place to stay.
Okay.
Remember,
all the phones on the ship have a monitor.
You can only send short messages,
not phone calls.
By then,
just send the codes on it.
What do these codes mean?
Da'an has a code for police communication.
I learned it before.
The codes on it probably mean
you're Sang Tuo's friend,
and you need a hospital and a place to stay.
Once you get the code,
you'll think it's a system error and won't be saved.
Thank you.
Brother.
I don't know how long I can hide this from you.
When Tie Fu finds out that I helped you escape,
he'll kill me.
Brother.
You must come back with the police as soon as possible.
I'll be waiting for you.
But I don't know when.
Where is our stunжmode?
Hey, Uncle Fu is here. What are you doing?
Uncle Fu,
locate the ship. Hurry.
all the mobile phone locations have been lost.
The ship, killing people, taking people away,
in such a short time,
he can't do so many things alone.
He's not a good person.
He's a good person.
In such a short time, he can't do so many things alone.
Someone must be helping him.
Hurry and check all the surveillance cameras in the building.
Yes.
Xiaoxiao, we're here.
Xiaoxiao.
Han Cheon, Xiaoxiao fainted.
Xiaoxiao, wake up.
Don't scare me.
Han Cheon.
Shi Shan.
Officer An, my sister is now...
The hospital has contacted them. Let's go.
The rest is on the way.
Uncle Fu,
the surveillance cameras in the building have been lost.
Shi Shan and Tao Hua's video of that time
has been leaked by the guards.
The Han brothers have informed us.
Shi Shan is now in the Bangli Hospital.
They've already sent someone to look for him.
Han Cheon.
Come here.
I didn't think that the Iron Talisman would be so powerful.
It's a relief that you found them earlier.
Otherwise, it would be a problem.
But don't worry. I've already contacted the police.
None of them can escape.
Thank you.
Doctor, is my sister's surgery successful?
Her surgery was successful. She's fine now.
She'll be fine in a few days.
Thank you.
Since your sister is out of danger,
we should talk about you.
I heard that you were with the Chinese driver
and he's going to the police station with us.
Okay.
Officer Han, I'm sorry.
We just contacted the Chinese police
and verified your identity.
I'm sorry for being a nuisance.
It's okay.
I didn't hide the identity of the police.
We're all police. I understand.
Officer Dan, can I use your phone to make a call?
Of course.
Please come in.
Thank you.
Hello?
It's me.
Han Che.
I'm sorry.
It's really you.
What's wrong?
You sound worried about me.
It's okay.
Hello?
The Chinese police are here.
It's okay.
They found the driver.
You go inside.
Yes.
According to Han Che's lead
from a life-threatening source
we basically know
the location
the location of the bomb and the personnel.
The Ministry of Security has decided to implement
the highest-ranking court, the highest-ranking procuratorate,
and the Ministry of Security's opinion on the use of legal evidence
for the use of telecommunication fraud cases.
The document requirements
will be used to combat the bombings in the telecommunication fraud groups
in the eastern region.
The 118th Special Major Trans-Taiwan Electric Fragment Project
will formally send a request to the eastern police.
Our mission this time is,
first, to safely bring Han Chuan and Han Xiaoxiao back to the country.
Second, we will actively cooperate with the local police
to destroy this fraud group
and bring all the telecommunication fraud personnel
from China back.
I order Comrade An Fei as the leader
to lead Yang Yang and Wang Yaqi,
and go abroad officially three days later.
Yes!
Hello, Chief of the Security Department. Han Chuan.
Han Jin Kong, thank you for your hard work.
We've been trying to destroy this fraud group for a long time.
But we never got a breakthrough.
Thank goodness we have you.
This is what I should do.
I just got the documents.
The joint operation of the eastern and China
against the fraud group
has been approved.
That's great.
I order Chief of the Security Department
to lead this operation
and cooperate with the Chinese police
to completely destroy the fraud group.
Yes!
I order Chief of the Security Department
to lead this operation
and cooperate with the Chinese police
to completely destroy the fraud group.
Yes!
I order Chief of the Security Department
to lead this operation
and cooperate with the Chinese police
to completely destroy the fraud group.
Yes!
I order Chief of the Security Department
to lead this operation
and cooperate with the Chinese police
to completely destroy the fraud group.
Yes!
I order Chief of the Security Department
to lead this operation
and cooperate with the Chinese police
to completely destroy the fraud group.
Yes!
I order Chief of the Security Department
to lead this operation
and cooperate with the Chinese police
to completely destroy the fraud group.
Yes!
I order Chief of the Security Department
to lead this operation
and cooperate with the Chinese police
to completely destroy the fraud group.
Yes!
I order Chief of the Security Department
The suspect in the water house
has a key clue.
There's a middle-end server in the park.
There are six black boxes.
Every coin they fraudulently stole
and all the transactions
will be stored in this black box.
The police told us
to protect this important evidence
during this operation.
Without evidence,
we can't catch them
or get them back.
Okay, I understand.
Officer Han.
There are emergency situations.
Let me pick you up.
Don't worry.
If I hadn't recoveredимость
as we speak,
you would have got
dug pleasant for Sang Tuo
and drawn him out to get revenge.
Why?
You are beyond doubt.
Brother.
I'm not going to let you get away with this.
You're not going to get away with this.
Officer An, what's going on?
Aren't we supposed to be on the day after tomorrow?
There's an emergency on the island.
We have to act early.
Get to work!
Since we knew where the island is,
we've been keeping an eye on the eastern border.
This morning, a message came from the tongue.
Tie Fu is running away.
I think he knows you've escaped.
And he knows your identity as a cop.
I don't know how long I can hide it from him.
Tie Fu will kill me if he finds out I helped you escape.
Officer An,
the situation is sudden.
We've prepared well.
Let's go.
Get on the boat.
It's this Sang Tuo.
He helped Shi San escape.
His loyalty was fake.
He fooled us all.
Today, let's see
how he will end up betraying the Buddhist books and Yuan Qu.
I'm sorry.
When I saw you last time,
I thought you looked like an old friend.
I didn't expect you to be his slave.
Even the back bone of your head
is as high as your father's.
I'll kill you if I have a chance.
Good.
Let's see how long your army can last.
The clouds are entangled in the wind and waves.
They float in the dust.
The waves are in the balance.
The whirlpool is in the sky.
The dawn never falls.