Log Cabinet
Episode 6
Of course you two should have settled the case
Have some more time
The money is transferred
Continue the 2011 joint business
I'll surrender
Oh no
Then three years have passed
доп me
What?
Slowly
Don't worry
The money has been transferred. Continue to clear.
They have transferred the money from the first-level card.
Check to 61 cards and 2-level cards.
I have already transferred the card number to you.
There are 192 cards in the 3-level card.
I have checked 80 cards.
Master, you're still not stopping them?
Wait a bit longer.
I will get all the cards that they have previously transferred.
Okay.
Let the car driver start.
Yes.
Wu Xun, there are no new cards.
I will get all the cards that they have previously transferred.
Okay.
Wu Xun, the blocking is successful.
Did you get the information?
Wu Xun, you are scaring me.
Director Wang, thank you for your cooperation.
You're welcome.
Please be kind to us.
Master.
There are a total of 333 cards.
The other ones were used to block the money from being used for the virtual currency.
They only transferred the 3-level card.
It means that they are still using the car driver.
Since there is a car driver who is taking the money, he will leave a video.
Wei Yang Yang, you two
continue digging along the bank card line.
Try your best to find out all the information about the car driver and the car owner.
See if there are any clues. Check the water source behind them.
Yes.
Director Wang, do you think Director Wang can understand what we are trying to say?
Let Han Chuan cooperate with the gold fraud case?
The gold fraud case has been too rampant lately.
It has had a huge impact.
We have been investigating for a few months and there is no clue.
Now Han Chuan is in the fraud group.
Maybe this is a new breakthrough.
What are you doing?
I will try to send him a message.
I believe he can understand.
He will definitely understand.
I will not be innocent and keep my eyes on the video.
Gold followed the water source.
From the various banks to the fraud center to cooperate with the law enforcement,
we have increased the barrier rate of fraud.
But the frauds have come up with a new type of gold fraud.
They can let the victim buy the gold and then cheat the owner.
This can avoid network supervision and increase the privacy.
But it also increases our difficulty in finding the gold.
The problem we are facing now is that only the frauds
can let the victim use a taxi or a flash drive
to send the gold to the location they have set.
The people who took the gold are also their temporary customers.
So it's hard to find the gold.
The most important thing to fight gold fraud
is the pure presence of their transaction volume.
And the most beneficial thing to us is also this.
Who is in charge of the gold fraud in this circle?
Uncle Fu, I know the speed of the water room.
From the first level to the third level,
there is also virtual currency.
At most five minutes, it's all gone.
In such a short time, unless the police know it first,
otherwise, it's impossible to stop it all.
This kind of situation never happened before.
How can it be so coincidental?
Something happened at the third level.
No, what do you mean?
Uncle Fu, I suspect something is wrong with the third level.
It's connected to the police.
Uncle Fu, Sister Zha, it's nothing.
What are you doing?
If you have the chance, you have to
put the money on my people.
Your people are already in the third level.
Do you really think he's willing to be your little brother?
What's wrong with you?
No matter who's little brother, it's all Uncle Fu's people.
What's wrong with you two?
Do you want to be the boss yourself?
Sister Zha, I didn't mean that.
It's nothing.
Enough.
This time, it's not about the water room.
It's not about the thirteenth level.
If you want to blame it, blame it on the actions of the Chinese police.
It's getting faster and faster.
It's getting harder to deal with.
The water room will also have to be more careful from now on.
Uncle Fu, don't worry.
I've already tried my new method for three months.
I've never failed.
It's about 20 million.
You can't just let it go like this.
No matter what method you use,
you must get back at me.
How's the investigation going?
Brother Dong, I should have found his father.
Brother, are we really going to do this?
We've never touched the gold business before.
We won't just learn.
Learn? Who are we learning from?
The area is so big. No one will mess with us.
Who?
Anyway, as far as I know,
Basi, HaiKan, and HeiRuiDong don't have this business.
They won't sneak up on us?
That's impossible. We can't stop them.
Besides, they have their own business. Where's the time?
Gao Hong Jin, find Nezha.
Nezha is doing this business?
I don't know if what I told you is true.
The area usually has new business. They will give it to Nezha first.
When he's done, they'll give it to Er Lou.
And I heard Si YanZai bragging about the gold business.
But I didn't take it seriously.
You're good, Brother Rui. I didn't see it coming. You know a lot.
Think about it. 90% of people in the whole area eat here.
You think he's a market, but he's actually a small intelligence station.
No matter what people say, do, or want to do,
as long as you're attentive, you can find out.
Okay, okay. Brother, look at him. He's so capable.
I'm just kidding. I'm a high-class student.
I'm in that...
I know, I know.
DongBang WuYanZuMa.
You just need to know.
Let's eat.
Brother, how about we really ask around?
I'll take a bite.
Brother, I heard that Black Ghost is investigating your real identity in China.
You need to be careful.
I know, brother. Thank you.
Actually, I have one more question to ask you.
Go ahead.
This time, 20 million people were intercepted by the police.
You're really unlucky.
You're lucky to have a good life.
Are you really unlucky or did you deliberately call me a liar?
It's okay, brother. I didn't ask.
I didn't ask.
AnRui, you're smart.
Brother, even though I still don't understand what you're trying to do,
I think you're different from them.
If you need anything in the future, just tell me.
Let's eat.
Xiaoxiao, stop taking medicine.
Your foot is too infected.
If you don't take the medicine, you won't be able to...
Stop pretending to be a star, okay?
The doctor said that if I don't take the medicine,
I'll become a disabled person.
You're the one who caused me to be like this.
What are you doing now?
Are you pretending to be a good person?
No, no, Xiaoxiao.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to. They forced me to scold me. If I don't take the medicine...
Then you deserve it.
I deserve it?
Yes, you deserve it.
Yes.
I deserve it.
I deserve to be here. I deserve to be beaten. I deserve to be treated like a bastard!
You think I'm doing well, right?
Ever since I came here, I've never been beaten.
These wounds are all because I was forced to take the medicine on the sixth floor.
I made money and begged for money. What did they do?
They beat me, beat me, and abused me.
They didn't even treat me well.
They didn't even treat me as a human being.
I...
I am the tool they used to bully me.
Do you think I want to be like this?
I want to live. I don't have a good brother who's trying to kill me.
I want to live. Tell me, am I wrong?
Tell me.
Do I want to live? Am I wrong?
I...
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have said that.
I...
I... I...
I actually regret coming here. I regret bringing you into this hell.
Xiao Qiao, beat me.
Beat me!
I don't know why I'm like this.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
The light fades in the night
The fireflies are shining
The light is all over the city
I'm with you in the storm
Think about it.
I owe you this.
Believe me one more time.
Even if I have to risk my life, I will be with you.
I'll take you with me.
The light is all over the city
The fireflies are shining
I'm with you in the storm
Think about it.
I owe you this.
I'm with you in the storm
The fireflies are shining
I owe you this.
Gotta make a decision.
I'm with you in the storm
Let him in.
Okay.
Sister Zha.
Brother Hao, you're here.
I asked Li Bailing to take care of your sister.
They're classmates.
Don't worry.
Thank you, Sister Zha.
But besides seeing Xiaoxiao,
I have one more thing to ask of you.
Ask me?
Brother C3.
Thank you.
I'll go out after I finish.
Okay.
My back hurts lately.
Sister Zha.
I just learned how to massage.
If you don't mind...
Come on.
Sister Zha.
Is this massage okay?
Use more strength.
Okay.
Sister Zha.
What we know about the medical conditions on the island
is that Xiaoxiao is badly injured.
I want to send her to the east gang.
It really hurts.
Don't cry.
rein into the heart
term fired
Silver starry sky
Sp campoloud
The dark clouds rise in the window
The light in my fingertips melts the cold winter
In my palm, my heart holds the fire
In the fog, the unidentified boat
I know where to go and where to go
The light scatters, the night color glows
The light travels around the world
The clouds are in the wind, the waves are in the wind
The waves are floating in the dust
The waves are in the ice, the waves are in the whirlpool
The dawn has never fallen