You're here.
I'm sorry I'm late.
Is everything finished?
You won't leave again, will you?
Why won't you say anything?
Promise me.
I love you.
Lee Yeon-seo.
What? Why isn't he coming?
-Did you sleep well?
-You're late.
I told you to come within a minute
after I ring the bell.
Stand on the right
and give you my left arm.
Right?
Not bad.
I will serve you with my best
as if this is my first time.
-Don't be so cute.
-Fine.
Forget it then.
I never said no.
Do you remember
what happened
last night?
You got your hopes up, didn't you?
Hey, Yeon-seo!
Don't let me catch you.
-No.
-Stop running. You might fall.
If I catch...
If you catch me, then what?
What now? What will you do?
Kim Dan?
Goodness! Ms. Jung!
Have you been well?
What happened?
Are you back for good?
Things must have been tough because of me.
I'm sorry.
You've done well until today.
You can start commuting as of today.
No wonder.
I thought I heard the door open
last night while I was sleeping,
so I called the security company
to see the CCTV footage.
-No!
So it was you, Dan.
Young Lady, your friend
and the guy who wanted some time.
Is he back?
What?
Oh, yes. Probably.
I'm not sure.
Tell her not to trust men so much.
A guy who changes his mind often
will definitely turn out to be a bad guy.
I did my best as I waited for you.
I ate well and practiced hard too.
Good girl, Yeon-seo.
What were you up to?
Aren't you going to tell me?
Go inside.
They say fickle guys are always bad.
No way. I'm going to stay
by your side from now on.
I decided to do that
as soon as I walked in yesterday.
So what if you stay by my side?
Your heart might be with someone else.
It's not a crime to love a lot,
but it's a crime to have too many secrets.
-Who said that?
-Lee Yeon-seo.
She's a great person.
Do a great job,
great person.
Are you going to be her rib?
It's none of your business.
If I turn into dust or dissipate,
that's for me to deal with.
You'll be very lucky
if you just dissipate.
You can't even imagine
what the punishment is like.
Something horrifying
will happen.
How
do you know that?
There was a young angel
who thought he was special
just like you.
Her rib? Love?
You need to give up.
There won't be a happy ending.
One of you
will end up living a dreadful life.
So do not throw a stone
into still water to satisfy your desire.
Pretend you're a human,
then disappear quietly.
Desire?
You might be right.
But
I don't want to be a coward.
I want Yeon-seo to know who I am.
It doesn't matter if I'm a human or not,
or if I'm dead or alive.
I want her to know my present and my past,
and love me for who I am.
Don't you feel the same way?
Don't you wish
to be understood?
No, I don't need that.
The moment you tell her,
everything will be over.
Do as you please.
However,
keep your mouth shut until the audition.
I was going to do that anyway.
You're not the only one
who cares about her.
So don't try to give me
any advice.
By the way, about that young angel...
Why do I feel like it's...
Never mind.
You're nothing but a foolish and weak
human being.
My gosh.
Ask your petty deity why I'm like this.
And whether it's Yeon-seo or Kim Dan,
if He wants to ruin my plans again,
tell Him to wake up as well.
Ruin his plan again?
(Living is already a nightmare,)
so wishing to be born again
is a silly thought.
And wishing for peace in the afterlife
sounds lame, doesn't it?
(Choi Seol-hee)
Lower your shoulders. Okay, that's good.
Welcome.
-Ma'am.
-Yes?
-May I have a bottle of soju?
-Coming up.
-Here.
-Thank you.
(Butler Jung Yu-mi)
(Just give us a little more time.)
You're a dad too.
You know how I feel, don't you?
Mr. Park.
I'm known for my persistence.
Would you like me to leave
80 missed calls?
Hello, Ms. Jung.
Are you sick?
What's wrong with your voice?
Don't tell me you've changed your mind.
(No, that's not it.)
(Tomorrow at 3:00 p.m.)
(If you don't come,
I'll go to Fantasia myself.)
(Do you understand?)
(Don't sound so scary.)
I didn't forget.
Do you know that Kim Dan
is giving up on his mission
and is about to cause trouble?
I don't care if your junior or underling
turns into dust as punishment
after acting recklessly.
But I thought you should
at least know about it.
Do as you please.
Come sit down.
Let's have a drink.
Humans sometimes drink
instead of praying.
I have nothing more to say to you.
I once heard
about an abandoned angel
who had turned into a human.
"They reeled and staggered
like drunkards."
"They were at their wits' end."
You didn't forget it.
I'm tired of those verses,
but they just won't disappear
from my memory.
You must've gone through a lot.
You were left in this barren world,
not being able to live or die.
Are you saying that you're
a merciful angel who understands me?
Then what?
Did you expect me to kneel down
and repent my sins?
Dream on.
Just focus on managing
that junior of yours.
Why are you so hostile towards Dan?
You achieved your goal.
You successfully placed a woman who
looks like your dead lover, Noisy Gong...
No, I mean Yeon-seo on stage in her place.
You did it.
That's what I thought at first.
I thought that she was the key,
and everything would be over
once I put her on stage. However...
It might be an endless tunnel,
but it'll be easier together.
You want to live now.
You used to say
that living was a nightmare.
I want to break free
from that nightmare.
(Lee Yeon-seo, Yoo Seong-woo)
Yeon-seo.
Listen carefully
to what I'm about to tell you.
Do you know
what a guardian angel is?
No.
Don't be surprised. I'll...
Darn it. This is what Ji Kang-woo said.
So
I was Seong-woo.
I was him.
But after I died, I became an angel.
But I just happened to remember--
What am I saying?
It doesn't make sense even to me.
(Lee Yeon-seo, Yoo Seong-woo)
(Lady Yeon-seo)
"Lady Yeon-seo"?
-Hello?
(-Come to the garden right now.)
Sit down. It's chamomile tea.
"Lady Yeon-seo"?
You changed it, didn't you?
You shouldn't use my phone
without my permission.
Why is it yours?
It's the cell phone
I bought with my money.
What's wrong with "Lady Yeon-seo"?
It's much better than Noisy Gong.
"Lady Yeon-seo". Repeat after me.
Lady Yeon-seo.
Why did you call for me?
Are you having trouble sleeping?
Which one is it?
Are you married?
Or do you have a terminal disease?
I've given it some thought.
I tried to figure out
what you're hiding from me
and what you need to take care of.
Why are you in pain because you fell in
love with me when you shouldn't have?
What could it be?
Either you're married or you're ill.
Come on. It's none of the above.
You're the only one for me.
You're my first and last.
And I'm really healthy.
I'm not ill.
Then tell me what you did
while you were away.
Where did you go?
I'll tell you everything
after the audition.
I don't want to bother you
for no good reason before your big day.
Kim Dan, listen up.
If it's about you,
even a strand of hair
is a good reason for me to care.
To me,
you're the most important.
Do you understand that?
Tell me.
I'm okay with whatever it is.
Really?
Actually,
I met
my dad.
Gosh.
I've never said that out loud before.
Your father
who kicked you out?
Did you ask for forgiveness
for your mistake?
Well,
it's a common, boring story.
I've totally forgotten about him
for over a decade of my life.
I barely managed to meet him right
before he died.
I asked him what I wanted to know
and said goodbye.
That's my story.
What did you
want to know from him?
Well,
I wondered why he was so harsh on me.
I was his son, after all.
He should've loved me.
Things like that.
Did he apologize to you?
Fortunately, yes.
All right. Storytime is over.
Wasn't it boring?
Come here.
No, I'm all right.
I let everything go already.
You and I
are both alone in this world.
You've been through so much,
Dan.
I'm all right.
I'm really fine.
When does your rehearsal end today?
Around 6:00 p.m.
Darn it. I was hoping it'd be at 3:00 p.m.
Hey, look at your outfit. Is that new?
What do you think? Isn't this pretty?
-It's pretty.
-What?
Are you teaching more classes?
Do you have time for that?
By the way, did you two
meet with Associate Director Geum?
My gosh.
Did Associate Director Geum
contact you in private?
I don't know.
I only heard about it.
I'll cancel the audition
and publicly announce that
the general director and the associate
director bought votes from the troupe
to ensure their daughter
and sister got the leading role.
I'll announce it to the association
and the media too.
Go ahead.
However, you don't have
witnesses nor evidence,
so be ready to take responsibility
for saying that Fantasia is in ruins.
Regardless of the results,
I'm sure you can't deny
that you tried to buy votes.
I only met with my dancers in private
as an associate director
to ask if they needed help or if there
were suggestions for the ballet theater.
If you're calling that buying votes,
I'll take responsibility
and resign from Fantasia.
Your resignation
won't resolve this matter.
If auditions aren't executed fairly,
don't you know that we can't
prepare for the show properly?
What do you and General Director Choi
want from this ballet theater?
Is it truly about money?
Director Ji.
You keep condemning
General Director Choi and me
as though we're
the most despicable people on Earth.
Let me give you a warning very politely.
Please refrain yourself
before my patience runs out.
We'll proceed
with the audition as planned.
Present the evidence that proves that
we bought votes with money or bribes.
Once I'll confirm it myself,
I'll cancel the audition.
My goodness!
No one followed you here, right?
No.
What about you?
Are you acting naturally,
so they don't suspect you?
Of course. No one knows. No one.
(I've got everyone fooled.)
(Good job.)
(Let's go in.)
Who is this?
Mr. Moon.
(Mr. Park.)
Where and how have you been?
You never called!
After hearing from Ms. Jung,
I knew it would be you.
What do you mean?
You can catch up later.
Let's cut to the chase.
Ji-woong is going to testify for us.
-Testify what?
-The accident
that caused Young Lady to go blind.
That wasn't an accident. It's an incident.
Someone instigated the incident.
It was planned.
What? What did you say? Who?
(Is it ready?)
(I'm doing it
because you're telling me to,)
(but she could really end up dying.)
(Right. That's the whole point.)
(If you fail,)
(you know that you have to give back
all the money we've given you, right?)
(Please.)
(Don't forget.)
(The ending of Act Two.)
(It's when Lee Yeon-seo's solo ends.)
(I knew it was wrong.)
I shouldn't have done it
even if I was about to lose everything.
I think it was a trap.
You said he never played cards,
not even once.
But your father owed thousands of dollars
for gambling within days.
And a stranger gave you 10,000 dollars
and 5,000 dollars for no reason.
I bet it was all part of the plan.
Who? Who planned it?
We should look into that now.
After the audition tomorrow,
I'm going to the police with Young Lady.
(Bring the recording and documents
you mentioned by then, Mr. Park.)
Okay.
(Untitled)
(We should look into that now.)
(After the audition tomorrow,
I'm going to the police with Young Lady.)
(Bring the recording and documents
you mentioned by then, Mr. Park.)
I told you not to do anything.
If you had any conscience,
you wouldn't have done it to begin with.
You're dying anyway.
Are you scared of being condemned?
I told you to stay still.
How can I?
You said you're going to die after this.
-This is his last time.
-He should know better.
He deceived Giselle.
She's going to die
because he deceived her.
How dare he hold her hand?
He didn't know that this would happen.
He feels bad,
so he wants to atone for what he did.
What's the point of that?
Can you just kill everyone
like Director Ji's interpretation?
That's more intense.
You really have to win tomorrow.
And don't forget. At 5:00 p.m. tomorrow--
How many times must you tell me?
A party at the cafe by the police station.
We can celebrate, or you can console me.
Things will get very hectic
after tomorrow.
-Be ready.
-Okay.
Let's try it one more time.
You've been doing this for three hours.
It's because something
is still bothering me.
I'm still in love,
but I know he deceived me.
I don't know what to do.
(Report)
(Are you asleep?)
No. Why?
Do you want to help me practice
a bit more?
What?
Come here.
I told you. I have to practice.
You don't need to do that.
Let's forget everything
and get some fresh air.
What do you want to see?
The river, sea, trees, fields,
tell me anything.
I'll take you there. Okay?
Stars.
I want to see the stars with you.
He must have had a reason.
What?
He truly loved Giselle too, didn't he?
Maybe the first engagement
was made against his will.
That might be
why he ran away to the countryside.
Keep going.
He ended up in a strange place,
met a woman,
and fell in love with her.
He shouldn't have fallen in love with her,
but no matter how hard he tried,
he couldn't help but fall in love.
He probably made a decision
to abandon everything and live there.
Then he should have told her earlier.
He probably wanted to.
But he put it off for a day
and another day.
Probably.
Was he afraid she'd leave
if he told her the truth?
He was probably afraid.
He didn't trust her.
The man
trusted his love, but not Giselle's love.
She's a woman
who loved him
even after she became a ghost.
That's so sad.
Let's go. I need to dance this out.
Right now?
I need to try it out
when I get the feeling. Let's go.
I need to talk to...
Why did you come here?
Where is your handkerchief?
It's mine,
so I'll take care of it.
Stop threatening me.
I already made my decision.
No, you need to turn back.
Ji Kang-woo is...
You know he only wanted her
because she looks like his first love.
He was sincere.
He is sincerely in love with Yeon-seo.
That can't be right.
Your mission was half successful.
You just have to leave now.
If that's what you came to say, leave.
So what if you tell
your story to Noisy Gong?
Then what?
Then
are you going to show her
how you turn into dust?
The best thing you can do for her
at this point is leaving.
Before she falls deeper in love with you.
Before she gets more hurt.
Before something more frightening happens.
Ji Kang-woo will be by Noisy Gong's side.
You and I can return to paradise.
That's a happy ending for everyone.
Isn't that right, Dan?
I'm sure there is a way.
If a human can become an angel,
an angel can become a human too.
Stop talking nonsense!
Think about it.
If you act rashly,
something bad will happen.
Stop trying to scare me!
I'll deal with the bad thing
and get struck by lightning if I must.
Leave.
Dan...
Don't be nervous.
You're the one who'll be dancing,
so why am I nervous?
You can do it, Noisy Gong.
That again.
You're my Noisy Gong,
the prettiest one in this world.
Here.
It proves that you are an angel,
and it connects this land with paradise.
Do not lose it.
Make sure you always carry it around.
May I borrow that until today?
I want it as my good luck charm.
This is yours now.
Are you giving it to me for good?
I don't need this
because I'll be with you.
Your vote today
will determine the future of Fantasia.
I believe that you will vote for a dancer
who touches your heart.
Geum Ni-na didn't come?
Good luck, everyone.
San-ha, control your emotions.
Soo-ji, get bolder.
Jung-eun, maintain your balance.
And Yeon-seo...
Focus on your interpretation.
Whoever it may be,
I'm going to do my best
to use their interpretation.
So do your best to convince them
so that the troupe
and I will be able to follow.
Just give up.
You overworked after giving birth.
I think you have an inflammation
in your pelvis.
Have you gone to the hospital?
What is it?
Are you desperate to gain my vote?
You don't consider me a rival, do you?
You're not going to quit in a year or two.
You didn't work this hard to end to return
to quit so soon.
Give up on this audition
and focus on getting better first.
No. I can't do that.
I will never give up again.
You of all people know
how hard it is to come back
once you've fallen behind.
I may be nothing in your eyes,
but I am still a ballerina.
Do you know that?
We will now begin the audition.
The candidates were allowed to choose
any scene from "Giselle."
The first candidate is Lee San-ha.
(If we have 13 votes of 30,)
(are we in the clear?)
Since the voting will be done in secret,
we won't be able to track them.
We can't be sure.
I don't like this idea.
(If we meet them too often,
it'll leave a trace.)
(I know that.)
But there's no other way.
Yeon-seo is second to none
when it comes to ballet.
She's aware of that, and that is why she
has put everything on the line for ballet.
(The troupe will give back for
what they've received.)
(Ni-na should do well.)
(As an artist,
I'm sure she has her pride.)
(You can't act noble without money.)
(Whether you're an artist or not,)
(nobody can turn away from money.)
Next up is Geum Ni-na.
Geum Ni-na just arrived.
(Wow,
she has a completely different vibe.)
(Stop!)
I told you to stop crying.
What is this disgusting emotion?
I can't stop myself.
What use is all of this?
It has to be Yeon-seo.
As long as I'm not Lee Yeon-so,
nothing I do will be enough.
Did you just realize that?
This was your fate from the beginning.
No matter how pretty you are,
you're just a display that nobody wants.
Unless you're Yeon-seo,
you have no choice
but to be locked up behind glass doors.
Give up! Why do you even bother to try?
1,124. 1,125. 1,120...
She did it.
Bravo!
That was incredible.
You were really good.
Don't evaluate me.
I didn't do that to gain your approval.
Mind your own business.
(Next up is Lee Yeon-seo.)
(She feels resentment.)
(Not towards him, but towards herself.)
(Was my love not enough?)
(It's not like that.)
(He probably couldn't tell me)
(because he couldn't trust me.)
(No, I do want to tell you.)
(I want to tell you the most.)
(I want to tell you who and what I am.)
(But can I do that?)
Well done.
(I will now tally the votes.)
(1: Lee San-ha, 2: Lee Soo-ji,
3: Hwang Jung-eun)
(4: Geum Ni-na, 5: Lee Yeon-seo)
(Ballot Box)
The last vote goes to
Lee Yeon-seo.
(4: Geum Ni-na, 5: Lee Yeon-seo)
Since it's tied,
we can either have a final match
or a head-to-head vote.
But why are there only 29 votes?
Did one of you abstain?
Where did Ms. Hwang Jung-eun go?
She said something urgent came up,
so she left.
It looks like she didn't vote.
Let's call her and ask.
She left in a hurry,
but she saw the performances.
And I bet she has no idea about the tie.
We can just call her
and ask her whom she wants to vote for.
Including the candidates and the voters,
if anyone is against this idea,
we'll push forward
with a head-to-head vote.
Does anyone object?
You know that Korea
is known for its competitiveness.
We can't end the audition
without a clear winner.
Go ahead and call her.
(Director Ji Kang-woo)
Hello?
Jung-eun, you saw the performances, right?
(Hwang Jung-eun, Fantasia)
I won't drag this out.
You'll vote on the phone.
(Among the 5 candidates,
cast your vote for 1 of them.)
Now? On the phone?
Yes.
Everyone is listening to the phone call.
But if you feel uncomfortable,
you don't have to do it.
This is supposed to be anonymous,
but everyone will know whom you voted for.
-If you want to abstain--
(-No, I'll vote.)
If you'll count my vote, I'll vote.
I
(Hwang Jung-eun, Fantasia)
(liked Lee Yeon-seo's performance
the most.)
(Hwang Jung-eun, Fantasia)
(liked Lee Yeon-seo's performance
the most.)
Giselle will be performed by Lee Yeon-seo
in Fantasia's 2019 production
of "Giselle".
Let's accept it.
The dancers who are performing
with them chose her.
Everyone will agree that it was fair.
What have you done for Fantasia?
What have you done for Ni-na's audition?
They're artists?
My foot.
Those two-faced dancers can't be artists.
They took everything we offered.
How dare they stab me in the back?
What do you mean?
Did you bribe them?
Stop, stop!
If she plays the lead,
it's over for us. This is the end.
No. I can't let this be.
What choice do we have?
Should Yeon-seo go blind again
for Ni-na to--
Right.
I just need to make sure
that she never performs at all costs.
Yeong-ja, come to your senses.
We've been
too kind to her since she is our family.
Right?
Ni-na.
Ni-na, where are you?
I wish she would die.
I wish
Yeon-seo was dead.
-Ms. Lee, can you change your pose?
-Okay.
We'd like another shot of your face.
How will your 2016 interpretation of
"Swan Lake" be different from others?
I'll show you a visible difference
between good and evil.
Can we expect to see the best
"Swan Lake" of the year?
Of course. I'll show you 32 perfect turns.
If Yeon-seo weren't here...
If she weren't here,
I would be the lead dancer.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
I convinced you too, right?
Shall we have dinner later?
-Pardon?
-I've thought a lot about this,
but I must tell you
why I chose you
and what happened to me.
I have plans tonight.
I'll wait until you come.
Don't wait.
If it's about work,
we can do it in the studio.
If it's a private matter,
-I won't listen to you.
-You don't know anything
about how I feel as I stand
in front of you.
I respect you, and I am grateful to you.
Working with you is fun,
and I'm excited for it.
Please
don't make me feel more uncomfortable.
Decide after you hear me out.
You know the restaurant out front?
Meet me there after your plans are over.
Yeon-seo. Yeon-seo.
Hey, someone might see us.
Congratulations. You were so good.
You were beautiful.
What about my present?
What?
What's this? You didn't prepare anything?
I don't have a present,
but there's a place we should go to.
I need to go meet Ms. Jung.
It won't take long.
-Where?
-Where we met for the first time.
There's something
I really want to tell you.
I'll tell you who I am
and where I came from.
I'll tell you everything
from the beginning.
I'll have some coffee first.
I'll order food once my party arrives.
Okay.
You still have some time.
No, it's not that.
Director Ji...
What about him?
Did he yell at you for not
following his instructions?
Or did he say something weird?
Did he say something to you?
He said he needs to tell me something
and that he'll wait until I come.
I told him that I wasn't going to come,
but it's bothering me.
That man is unbelievable.
He had his nose in the air, you know.
He said that he'd wait for you?
Neither think about him nor accept him.
Are you jealous?
-What?
-That's what it looks like.
No.
Fine. Yes. I'm jealous.
If this petty, embarrassing,
and nasty feeling is called jealousy,
you got it right. I'm jealous!
I hate Ji Kang-woo.
I hate that he's clinging onto you,
that you connect through ballet
which I'm clueless about,
and that he meets you in private. So...
Don't meet him unless
I'm with you from now on.
Do you like me that much?
Yes.
Let's go.
What's your deal with rain?
-Why do you ask?
-In hindsight,
you always ran away whenever it rained.
Didn't you?
-Well...
-Do you have a trauma about rain?
Or an allergy?
Or do you transform into
the Hulk or something?
How would you feel
if I can really do that?
What if
I become something else
other than what I am now?
I'll pray that you'll return to yourself.
I'll go buy us an umbrella. Wait here.
Let's go together.
I won't run away anymore.
I'll be right back.
Have a nice day!
Excuse me!
(I had a weird feeling.)
(It felt like)
(I will search everywhere for him
in the distant future.)
(It felt like I will be left alone)
(in sadness and despair,
longing and missing him.)
Lee Yeon-seo!
Be careful.
(Maju Police Station)
(Lee Yeon-seo)
(Director Ji, I'm sorry.)
(I feel too burdened,
and I'm not confident.)
(I think this is my limit.)
(I'll end everything
in the ballet theater that I loved.)
(Where am I?)
(I hear cars)
(and a ventilator?)
(Ji Kang-woo)
(Power off)
Yes. Everything is ready.
I sent him an invitation,
so he will be there soon.
We need to let him see the final moment
of the ballerina whom he adored.
A hypersensitive ballerina who was
paranoid and spoke of conspiracies
before her death
kills herself due to the stress
of her comeback.
It's a nice headline.
(Make sure you end this well.)
Is this 911?
There's a person on the rooftop.
I think she's about to fall down.
Hurry up!
Who are you?
Who sent you?
My aunt? Was it my aunt?
Believe in whatever you want.
This is the end anyway.
This is the rooftop
of the ballet theater, isn't it?
You should reconsider.
Do you know how many
CCTV cameras are here?
You'll definitely get caught.
You should just go.
You don't have to take off mt blindfold
or untie my hands.
I'll let it go, and I won't go after you.
You made the right decision.
Go. I didn't see your face.
Thank you for letting me live.
I'm not letting you live.
No one kills themselves
with their eyes covered
and their hands tied.
(Dan.)
(Angel's Last Mission: Love)
(You can't hurt Yeon-seo ever again)
as long as I'm around.
(You lost your consciousness.
You need to rest.)
(Give it back to me.)
(Something is going on. I'm sure of it.)
(I'm going to find the reason.)
(It was you, wasn't it?)
You don't really like me.
You messed with her memory?
Keep your eyes on her
(when I'm not around.)