Are you surprised?
What?
A little.
Sorry.
Oh, no.
That's not it.
Should we... sleep now?
What?
Huh?
Oh, no.
That's not what I meant.
I mean sleep, literally.
I didn't say anything.
I'll sleep here...
BASED ON THE WEBCOMIC
MY ID IS GANGNAM BEAUTY! BY KI MAENG-GI
...and catch the first bus. So, you go.
No, I'll go with you.
It'll be uncomfortable for you.
It's fine. Don't worry.
Maybe you can change.
My dad's clothes won't fit you.
I'm fine. Just go to bed.
You won't sleep much.
Okay.
I'll go to sleep,
so you can sleep, too.
Good night.
Okay. Good night.
This doesn't feel real.
It's not a dream, but it feels like one.
Oh, that was my first kiss.
Oh, right!
Sorry.
It's okay.
Good night.
Okay.
She left her phone here.
FROM: MOM
Is everything really okay?
I'm worried.
INCOMING CALL: MOM
Hello?
Mi-rae, are you there?
Oh, dear. Who are you?
-Don't be scared.
-Who is this?
I am Do Kyung-seok.
CALL ENDED
VIDEO CALL
Hello.
Why did you answer Mi-rae's phone?
She is... sleeping right now.
What? Where?
In her room. I'm in the living room.
But... why are you there?
We came here together,
and I missed the last bus.
Just the two of you?
Yes.
What's your relationship with Mi-rae?
I'm her boyfriend.
-You?
-Yes.
You're going out with Mi-rae?
Yes.
So, you two are dating?
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to surprise you.
What are you doing out here?
Good night, then.
Who was that?
Mi-rae's boyfriend.
-What?
-Do you know who he is?
That super-handsome boy!
FROM: MOM
VIDEO CALL
It's true.
Hi.
-So, you're dating Mi-rae?
-Yes.
I will tell you one thing.
We have CCTV at home.
It records everything.
Good night, then.
What time is it?
Oh, no. I have to wash up
and put on make-up again.
I slept without washing my face.
My skin must look so bad.
I can't show him my bare skin.
Why is he sleeping like that?
It must be uncomfortable.
Where's the CCTV?
You're awake?
CCTV?
What are you talking about?
What kind of home has that?
What's the matter?
Did you have a dream?
I'm gonna sleep ten more minutes.
Drive slow. They left already.
Why did Dad say that?
Kyung-seok couldn't sleep.
Why? Did he do something?
He didn't do anything.
You can't really speak
because he's right next you?
Yeah.
I'll talk to you later, then. Bye.
So, they don't like me?
Weren't you sleeping?
I shouldn't have said hi that way.
They must've not liked me.
That's why your dad mentioned the CCTV.
-I shouldn't have answered the phone.
-Why? Are you worried?
Of course.
I've never seen you care
about someone so much.
Of course. They're not just anyone.
They're your parents.
They're just curious
because I have a boyfriend.
-That's all?
-Yes.
So, don't worry and sleep.
You didn't sleep much, either.
Aren't you tired?
A little bit.
Lean here.
-What?
-Lean on me and get some sleep.
You can lean over, too.
It's obviously a hidden camera.
Why can't it be deleted?
-Are you the one in the picture?
-Well...
If it's a domestic site,
can't it be shut down?
We also consider this a harmful site.
But it's hard to shut it down.
We can block the domain
so no one can access it.
And what if they post the picture
publicly or re-upload it?
We track down and delete the photos.
You can file a complaint as a proxy,
but the victim has to testify anyway.
Hello?
Hi.
It's been a while.
Who said this is me? Jang Won-ho?
-Jo Jung-yeob?
-Does Jung-yeob know about this,?
Won-ho!
Did he spread the rumor?
No. He came to see me
because he was worried about you.
He told me that he would not say
a word to anyone.
How can I trust him?
Sua.
I don't want to make you worry
for no reason.
Wouldn't you be worried
if you just let it be like this?
Don't you want to find who did this
and take them to court?
The police will investigate
if they consider this a crime.
I called, but they said
this is not considered a crime.
So, the victim has to testify.
Victim?
What?
No. I don't want to be
one of those weird girls.
Why is the victim weird?
Whoever filmed you is weird.
They did something wrong. But I'm the one
who has to deal with the rumors.
Don't you know victims get harassed
after talking to the police?
It makes more pictures circulate.
That's why we have to investigate,
so it can stop.
The police can track down
and delete the photos.
They can trace the download
and catch the culprit.
And...
we can ask them not to make big noise
during the investigation.
Once the police finds out who did this,
they'll arrest them. So, no worries.
No.
I don't want to do that.
Just leave me alone, please.
-Bye.
-Sua.
You were asleep when I came back.
I wasn't late.
Let's have dinner after freshening up?
Okay. That sounds good.
-See you later.
-Okay.
-Hello?
-Yes.
You hang up first.
No, you first.
No.
Then, I will hang up first.
See you later.
Okay.
I did not know hanging up the phone
would be this difficult.
HI!
What's up?
My friend said she needs to tell me
something about Sua.
Let's just meet tomorrow.
What's there to talk about Sua?
Sua is not well, you know.
I'll just listen and come home.
Don't go.
Don't worry.
I'll call you when I get back.
Maybe she didn't like you
because of those bad memories.
I know Sua
has done a lot of things to you.
She must have.
It was hard
because I liked her in the beginning.
Even though I am a girl,
I felt nervous in front of Sua
because she's so pretty.
When she told me we were friends,
I was very happy.
I'm ashamed now.
But I felt pretty, too,
because a pretty girl was my friend.
Anyway, there is nothing I can do
for her now.
And I don't want to.
Of course. I understand.
Maybe not now,
but if you could still be her friend...
that would change Sua's life.
If I can't even change my own life,
how could I change someone else's?
The wounds caused by other people
get cured by people.
I don't understand that very well.
However, it's obvious...
that the person who can make
the greatest impact on Sua
is not Kyung-seok,
or anyone else for that matter.
It is you.
Sua is not well, you know.
I'll just listen and come home.
Stop being so nice.
Is something wrong?
No, nothing.
Kyung-seok!
Is anyone at school following Sua?
Jang Won-ho?
No, never mind.
-Hello?
-Where are you?
I'm in Eun's neighborhood.
You don't have to pick me up.
Okay.
I won't forgive you.
Why did you mess with me?
All you have is your face.
I know where you live.
I will do it and prove it tonight.
Next time,
I'll get you cat food, not this.
You like this.
Do you live around here?
You despised me.
What?
Apologize.
Kyung-seok likes you
more than you like him, right?
No, it is not like more or less.
The feelings cannot be equal.
Usually, the person
who has stronger feelings calls,
wants to meet, and gets mad.
Gets mad?
You guys haven't fought yet, right?
I think we did before we dated.
I'm not sure it was exactly a fight.
Yes, Woo-young.
Sua?
Yes, I live close by.
Have you seen Sua today?
-Why do you ask?
-Nothing.
I wanted to ask her something,
but I can't reach her.
I know where she lives.
Should I go there?
No, you don't have to.
Don't go.
Okay.
She could get into trouble, too.
I would like to report.
Was it Woo-young?
Yes. He asked if I had seen Sua today.
He wants to ask her something.
Kyung-seok!
Is anyone at school following Sua?
No, never mind.
Do you know where Sua lives?
I do.
What did I do?
I thought I was the only one
who liked you.
I need a normal weight to look pretty.
I have the body of a little kid.
You must be kidding.
You never had a boyfriend?
Are you okay?
So, I wanted to give up.
But you liked me, too.
You said hi to me first.
You smiled at me!
I did?
Hi, Dong-won!
You two have the same name!
His name is Dong-won, too.
You even named the cat after me.
Who would ever give that name to a cat?
You did that on purpose
to get my attention.
You liked the drink I gave you.
You wanted to take a picture with me, too.
FOR SUA
Thank you for the drink.
Do you want to take a picture like that?
Why me?
Take a picture of Dong-won, too!
And you said you like Kyung-seok
in front of me?
You looked down on me!
You don't really like Kyung-seok, right?
What are you talking about?
What a loser.
It was a misunderstanding!
You had feelings for me!
You can't just change your mind.
Please. Help me!
You?
No.
You know what this is?
What's the matter?
I don't know.
I have a weird feeling about this.
I hear her over there.
Hey, isn't that Dong-won?
Kyung-seok!
What did you do?
She didn't apologize.
What?
Sua!
Are you okay?
He sprayed something on me.
What?
-What did he spray?
-I don't know.
He just sprayed something.
It's nothing. You're okay.
Don't look!
I said don't look.
Please, don't look.
Take it easy.
It's nothing, okay?
It's just water. Look at me, Sua.
I told you not to look!
I'm going to kill myself.
Sua!
Put that down.
Sua, look at me.
Look!
Here, Sua. Look!
You're fine.
Nothing happened.
You are fine.
Everything's okay.
Put that down.
Give that to me.
Did he hurt you?
Let's get up slowly.
Let go!
Why are you here?
Why you?
Why is someone like you helping me?
Who asked you to help me?
Why are you acting
like you're better than me?
like you're happier than me?
You're not even pretty.
Please. Stop now, please!
You...
I really don't like you.
Do you know how much you frustrate me?
I feel like I'm talking to a wall.
Fine. I am not pretty,
so I had plastic surgery.
I was unhappy because I was ugly,
like you said.
What about you?
Are you happy because you're pretty?
Are you happy?
Why does it have to be this way?
Why do we have to be like this?
We are on a diet
even though there's no weight to lose.
We throw up and have surgeries...
as if we'd die if we didn't get pretty.
We judge faces...
and fight with each other.
Why do we have to do that?
I... really don't want to.
I don't want to do that any more.
I...
From now on,
I will concentrate
on what makes me really happy.
That's what I'm gonna do.
Yes, Sua is fine.
She was scared, but didn't get hurt.
Yes, she is sleeping now.
So don't worry.
Of course.
Are you okay?
I am.
Well...
can I stay with Sua for a while?
Don't you hate her?
Hate?
You hate her, too,
and you still helped her.
-That's...
-Is it okay if I stay?
It's your decision. Do what you want.
Thank you.
-I'll call you later.
-Okay.
What a psycho.
What will happen to him?
After the police investigation,
he will be kicked out of school.
The legal process will remain to be seen.
-Are you waiting for Mi-rae?
-No.
I was waiting for you.
I wanted to go home together.
Why are you so friendly
all of sudden?
It's not all of sudden.
When you were drunk last time,
I brushed your teeth.
What?
-Let's go.
-Wait up!
-What are you saying? When?
-When you came home drunk.
You brushed my teeth?
Yes. And I made you breakfast.
Oh, that day!
Now that I think of it,
I did everything...
You didn't brush my teeth!
I did.
You sure are brave.
I thought I was.
Are you still here?
I'll stay here.
Okay, then.
Call me if you need me.
I will.
Silly.
You're even sillier than me.
Let's stop...
living like this.
What picture was posted online?
I didn't see it.
It was just the back of a woman.
You can't even be sure it was Sua.
The face also was online for a short time.
Her phone is off.
And she's not picking up.
I thought we were close,
but she's not calling me.
You were close
and you spoke behind her back?
I'm not the one who spread the rumors.
Everyone knew she was throwing up
and dating all the boys.
Anyway, people have
a bad impression of her now.
-She's not even from a wealthy family.
-Who said that?
Dong-won.
When we were in the lab,
he said everything about Sua is fake.
How would he know?
Isn't he a little strange?
Look! You always say bad things
about people.
-Just eat.
-Why?
He is weird. He never makes eye contact.
I hope he stays in prison forever.
I understand you feel nervous,
but don't worry too much.
He will be issued a restraining order
when he gets out.
And you will be fine
with counseling and treatment.
I don't know
why I have to go through this.
I don't think...
I can go anywhere alone.
Do you have anyone you can count on?
Someone who can be with you for a while.
I thought I had someone.
But I don't have anyone.
COUNSELING ROOM 2
Okay. I got it.
I see. All right.
Sua!
Why, didn't you think I'd be waiting?
I'd like to be with you for a while,
if it's okay with you.
There.
The cakes in that bakery are good.
Let's go and eat some next time.
No one knows what happened.
Really.
Everyone knows how to hold their tongues.
Woo-young, Kyung-seok, Mi-rae.
And you.
I've tried...
but I have to say something.
Mi-rae liked you at first.
You told her you two were friends.
She said that made her happy.
Thank you.
Of course. Don't worry.
The cat knows you.
Yes. Sometimes I feed him.
He likes my food.
You like cats.
Yes, I do.
Kyung-seok and Mi-are are dating.
-Since when?
-Since the break.
-They began dating at Kelun Korea.
-Wow!
I should have applied for Kelun.
If you had,
would you be able to date Kyung-seok?
Mi-rae is so lucky.
She must have saved the country
in her previous life. I am so jealous.
-I should have...
-I know.
Everyone scream!
A campus couple is born.
-What are you two?
-Are you guys really together?
Yes, we are together.
Kyung-seok smiled.
Don't kiss during class.
Okay. Not in class.
After class, then?
You don't have to answer everything.
You said I should be nice to people.
Next year, I'd like to apply
for the exchange student program.
Is your GPA over 3.5?
Do you also have the prejudice
that pretty girls get bad grades?
I thought you were different.
I'm disappointed.
I don't think you're that pretty.
I just asked.
What's for lunch today?
You're curious about that
on the first day of the semester?
You're all curious, right?
You're just not saying it.
Now that I think about it, it's true.
I thought about it, but I didn't say
anything because I knew you would.
I knew it!
Am I the only one who has a problem
understanding this conversation?
Sorry.
About what?
I hurt your feelings.
It's okay. It's all in the past.
You can't make yourself
feel a certain way.
I know.
I can't control how I feel.
I can't stop thinking about you.
Really?
That is so sad.
I don't really think about you.
There are people who are fine as a friend.
But they're just okay as a boyfriend.
You're one of them.
So, I got over it quickly.
Don't feel too bad. I gotta go.
Woo-young!
Do you have a minute?
None of the seniors are available.
So, they want me
to be the president for a while.
Silly Tae-young.
If he doesn't want to do it,
there's nothing we can do.
Behave until the election.
Don't get in trouble.
Okay. By the way...
do you know her? She's the prettiest girl
in the Dance Department.
-No
-Really? She is very famous.
I don't know her. Why?
She asked to be introduced to you.
She saw you in a science class.
You will meet her, right?
-No.
-Why?
-Do you have a girlfriend?
-No, that's not it.
I want love at first sight.
Tell her I am sorry.
She's not a model, but she's very pretty.
Oh, he's the pine tree of the school.
Never changes.
Who is she?
You scared me.
If Woo-young won't meet her, I will.
-Don't talk to me.
-Hey, hey!
Let's get along, huh?
This is not my year.
Hyun-jung!
-Are you going home?
-Hi!
What's wrong?
Will you buy me a drink?
Okay, sure.
He said "friend",
so I expected someone in his 20s.
He was 33! Oh, my God.
If we met and fell in love,
that's a different story.
How can a 33-year-old man
want to meet a college freshman?
Is he some kind of weirdo?
It was wrong.
He should have told you his age
in advance.
I don't expect much.
I just want an ordinary boyfriend
and ordinary love.
How can everything go so wrong?
There is no ordinary love.
Every relationship is special.
I'm curious to see who you will meet.
I also don't know.
How do you change an exponential function
to a log function?
Where did you have the surgery?
This is study hall. Let's focus.
If you change to a log function,
this is how it should be.
Did you do it all at once?
Or one at a time?
Can you not concentrate
because of my face?
No, of all the tutors I had,
you're the best one.
Really? Then let's do it again.
And you switch X and Y here...
and this is how it goes.
-How much did it cost?
-Look here!
I'm explaining an important concept.
Okay.
-Do you remember symmetric transformation?
-By the way...
Now what?
-...can I go to the bathroom?
-What?
Okay. Go ahead.
Be patient.
You need money
to buy Kyung-seok's birthday present.
-Your brother is so handsome.
-Really?
What do you want to eat?
I will pay.
-Order whatever you want.
-Wow!
Is your brother real?
And...
what is that?
My ID.
I HAVE A GIRLFRIEND
-I'm here.
-Just a minute.
Take your time. I will wait.
KYUNG-SEOK
CHEMISTRY DEPARTMENT
-Isn't it inconsiderate?
-Oh, my! You scared me.
-What?
-Am I just your classmate?
I wanted to change it, but I did not know
what I should change it to.
How did you save my name?
I don't know.
What's the matter?
Kang Mi-rae, chemistry department.
Are you upset?
Okay. I will change it.
What should we do Saturday?
Do you have any plans?
If not, do you want to go somewhere?
Okay.
Saturday is your birthday!
-Are you 33 years old?
-No.
You will spend the day with Mi-rae.
Come by for a while.
I'll buy you a drink.
When do girls get tired
of their boyfriends?
What?
What are you talking about?
Are things getting cold with Mi-rae?
No.
I'll call you later.
Okay.
Hey!
-You put on the cologne I gave you.
-Yes.
Just a little.
I don't want to use it all up .
I'll buy you more if you run out.
When is your birthday?
Mine? September 25th.
-I was born in September, too.
-Really?
I was born on the 15th. So, I am older.
Okay. I'll call you big guy.
Maybe she forgot.
You can't just work
part-time jobs forever.
Stop rejecting your dad's business.
You can quit if you don't like it there.
You haven't even given it a try.
Do you want to go
to my dad's business place with me?
Can anyone go there?
Yes, everyone's welcome there.
Why did you want to come to a church?
Dad!
Yoo-jin!
-Who is this?
-She is a junior at my school.
Hello. I am Choi Jung-boon
of the chemistry department.
Chemistry?
Isn't that Kyung-seok's department, too?
-Yes.
You said business.
You must have a lot to think about.
You like drinking so much.
That's just the first problem.
I feel sorry for you and the kids.
There's a lot I regret.
If I said for us to eat together tomorrow
to celebrate Kyung-seok's birthday...
that would be too much to ask, right?
-Is that what you wanted to say?
-No.
I want you to know one thing.
I only loved two women in my life.
Hye-sung at 26 and Hye-sung at 46.
-I am 47.
-What?
Oh.
Just...
-Hey, brother!
-You...
I was fired,
you're not my boss any more.
Yes, you are right.
I'm sorry for blaming you
for Kyung-hee's problem.
Oh, no. It's all good.
I got a better job now.
I will tell my boss Kim,
head of the party,
to take good care of you, brother.
Take care.
It's not her.
Did I sleep through class?
Mi-rae!
Were you asleep?
-I think so.
-You didn't answer the phone.
I think I passed out.
What's this?
What? What is it?
Someone must've put it there
while you were asleep.
-What are you saying? It was you!
-No, it wasn't me.
You're trying to fool me.
It wasn't me.
It really wasn't you?
Someone else must know you well enough
to give you perfume.
I gotta go. I have a class.
-Call me when you're done.
-I have to go to work.
What is this?
Who put it here?
Tomorrow is Kyung-seok's birthday!
It's been a while.
How did you find me here?
Your picture is everywhere on SNS.
You're famous.
Now, I use the internet
and see stuff like that.
Do you feel okay?
It's weird that you worry about me.
I took some time off of school.
I don't know when I'll be back.
And I don't think
we'll see each other again.
Do you have something to say?
Yes.
I need to tell you the truth.
I never liked you,
not even for a second.
I will go now.
Are you wearing perfume?
Yes.
I tried something new.
Everything else became easy.
What can I do
if someone I don't know left it there?
-Is it my fault?
-Did I say anything?
What can I do? My girlfriend is popular!
I changed your name in my contact list.
Look!
♥KYUNG-SEOK♥
Is that good? Do you feel better?
Yes. Okay.
Where are we going?
The weather's nice. Let's go far away!
-Far away?
-Yes.
Two people?
Yes, I made a reservation
under the name Do Kyung-seok.
Yes, please follow me.
Sit down, please.
You...
You thought I forgot?
No! Don't you dare.
Don't.
Yes, I will.
Happy birthday to you!
Happy birthday, Kyung-seok!
Blow.
Happy birthday!
Here's my present.
-So, you pretended you didn't remember?
-I really wanted to surprise you.
You want to do a lot of things.
Thank you.
Open it.
-Do you like it?
-I don't...
I like it.
I have one more thing.
Ta-da!
One, two, three!
Actually, a long time ago,
I used to judge people's faces
when they walked by.
But at some point, I stopped.
I am conscious of other people,
so I figured they would do the same.
But not many people pay attention to me.
This would be a nice place to propose.
What?
Places like cafes go away
as time goes by.
But this place will always be here.
Looking at my parents,
I thought I would never marry.
The hoodie I gave you,
I bought one for myself, too.
Hey, Do-rae couple!
You guys should buy lunch!
Let's leave in matching hoodies
Are you guys on your honeymoon?
Should I not have bought mine?
Who cares? Do whatever you want!