Just do what you want.
Yes, I'm done.
Choi Hyun-joon gets two points on blue.
Eun-yu, my alliance is now over.
I'm going to show my true colors.
He's joined them. Why would he do that?
-I know. He has nothing to gain.
-Exactly.
Are they giving him Pieces?
Hyun-joon is practically
keeping us guarded here.
If not for Hyun-joon,
the game would be over right now.
Hyun-gyu would have taken us
all down. Hyun-joon is keeping us alive.
So we have to protect Hyun-joon.
We just have to.
I told you. I'm okay with that, 100%.
Right.
Eun-yu went up to Hyun-joon
and told him that our ultimate goal
was to eliminate Hyun-gyu.
As a result,
he might lose half of his Pieces.
You're probably aware
that I can't guarantee that
you won't lose half of your Pieces.
-I know.
-Okay? Yeah.
It might come across
as the majority bullying the minority,
but in any case,
I don't feel any guilt about it.
-Hyun-joon is protecting us right now.
-What?
Hyun-joon is protecting us right now.
-Really?
-Yes.
He could have ended the game just now.
Is that how it is?
I'm not happy about this.
This sucks if that's how it is.
It feels lonely.
I bet it is.
I'm just fighting to win.
I felt like, "Am I the bad guy?"
"Should I just give up?"
It is now Kang Ji-yeong's turn.
-There's nothing else I can do. Here I go.
-Yes, go here and get this.
Kang Ji-yeong gets four points on blue.
That concludes Round 9.
Round 10 will now begin.
Jeong Hyun-gyu, please move the counters.
I'm really not feeling it today.
Me neither. I'd rather
have the game just finish here.
But Hyun-joon…
I don't have a move.
Son Eun-yu gets one point on green.
It is now 7high's turn.
What did he do?
-Come here.
-It's a lonely, lonely world.
Look at him.
He's really depressed and gutted now.
It's really difficult playing alone.
-Hyun-joon won't play with you anymore?
-He's going to stick with them.
-No way, really?
-Yeah.
-Weren't you giving him Pieces?
-I said I'd give them to him.
Then why?
He's just betraying me
to team up with them.
They're all banding together?
You made a really tough decision.
I can see through Hyun-gyu.
He showed me the score and
told me I'd end up with the most Pieces.
But to be honest,
I'm not really interested in that.
If Hyun-gyu and I were to
shut down the game and win,
that's also dangerous for me
because I'd have to face him.
-He also has some sort of advantage.
-Exactly.
I didn't team up with him
because I knew that.
Hyun-gyu tried to rile me up by asking
if I was struggling with the math,
and that just made me so annoyed.
Would I really be that clueless?
Now I only have two choices.
Keep getting points or blow it all up.
But I don't think I can blow things up.
-It must be so hard for you.
-Yes.
On your own.
Can't you two betray them
and come back to me?
-Now?
-I think I could.
I'll take all of Hyun-joon's Pieces
and take you two to the living area.
Today, I would like for it
to be just the three of us.
This one. Do this, 7high.
Release this one,
then this will become five.
Then whoever is here can get this next.
Then that makes six.
It's good for us to get blue points.
If we do this--
So make a blue pot? That's not a bad idea.
What is it you want?
From here, it's 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 spaces.
You'll be there on red…
-It doesn't matter.
-Go to red.
We can't get a whole lot of points
evenly all at once anyway.
-Let's stack it up first.
-Okay. Do that.
If you put me in on the red,
I'll get this blue and make it six.
So-hui also needs blue, by the way.
If you give them to So-hui,
Hyun-gyu will try to end the game.
Hyun-gyu is in first place right now.
It's better for us to get them first.
Put So-hui in here.
To keep Hyun-gyu in check.
7high gets one point on red.
It is now Yoon So-hui's turn.
So-hui.
-Here--
-She's on my team.
-What was that?
-Hyun-joon went that way.
What the heck? So-hui, what's going on?
I'm thinking about it.
What are you doing right now?
Hyun-joon betrayed me too.
But we agreed to play together.
What the heck?
Did you talk this over with So-hui?
So-hui.
Put 7high in here and blow it up.
-What?
-Give him four points.
You're going to blow it up, So-hui?
-That was my plan all along.
-I know that.
I was going to do it with Hyun-joon,
but he betrayed me and joined you.
I know that. So-hui
agreed to play with us today but now…
Now she's back. If Hyun-joon
can say the same and switch sides,
then So-hui can play with you
and join me again.
Isn't that the same?
So-hui, are you really going to do this?
I'm going to think about it.
To be honest, when I agreed
not to play with Hyun-gyu,
I didn't feel too bad about it
because Hyun-gyu
still had Hyun-joon on his side.
But Hyun-joon decided
not to side with Hyun-gyu anymore
and made his own moves.
Hyun-gyu complained about
being all alone, and I know how he is.
I really felt like he was feeling lonely,
and I just couldn't get past that.
To be honest, I don't think this is right.
It's so unfair, for sure.
That's what keeps going through my mind.
But then, I keep thinking
that games aren't meant to be fair.
There's so many thoughts
racing through my head.
I don't think it's right
to eliminate Hyun-gyu like this.
I can't do it.
I mean, it was okay to try that
when he had Hyun-joon on his side,
because they were tough opponents.
But if we turn our backs on him like this…
I just can't do that to Hyun-gyu.
I mean, if nothing had happened,
it would've been okay.
Hyun-joon only did that
to try and save himself.
Of course Hyun-gyu
wants to stay in the game too.
So, whatever happens going forward,
I don't want to leave him playing
all by himself like that.
Okay, let's go.
I was so determined not to cry in here.
It's just because we've spent
so much time playing as a team.
But…
there's nothing wrong with that, right?
I mean, let's just look at it logically
with the game in mind.
If you want to win this thing,
shouldn't you want to eliminate Hyun-gyu?
And this is our only chance.
But I don't like how things have soured.
At the beginning, they said they would
applaud betrayal and dirty tricks.
But no one's applauding. They're just…
I see that you're really mad.
I mean, there hasn't been
any theft or violence.
But no one's applauding.
7high, let's talk.
Anyhow, when we first heard
what you were proposing,
we agreed completely
and so we've been playing together.
But with Hyun-joon switching sides,
well, it's not about morality
or elitism or anything like that.
We just don't feel we can play like this.
Your timing really sucks.
Tell us your thoughts.
At first, we heard your proposal
and were completely in agreement with it.
And as a player myself,
I thought it was ridiculous to say,
"I'll go to prison in your stead.
You go and win this thing."
That's why So-hui and I
decided to join your alliance.
But with Hyun-joon switching sides,
that makes it six against one.
There are six of us going,
"Now it's your turn to feel the wrath
just like you've been doing to us
and controlling us. So die."
What if we don't eliminate him?
How will you do it?
We just finish the game like this
without eliminating Hyun-gyu.
We'll just let him lose half his Pieces.
Then who's going to finish last?
We can make Hyun-joon last.
So what are you saying?
We make both Hyun-gyu and Hyun-joon
lose half their Pieces.
-Then, Hyun-joon loses another five?
-Exactly.
Why would he agree to that?
He would've been fine
if he'd stuck with Hyun-gyu.
He only joined us because I was in danger.
He didn't really switch sides.
I was very open and told him
that we wouldn't be able to protect him.
-I understand Hyun-joon's point of view.
-Yes, he's safe.
And he only did it
to try and save himself.
But by doing that,
Hyun-gyu had become all by himself.
Even if I win,
I think I'd be really angry at myself.
I just feel like
this is not the way I want to do it.
But I don't really understand this.
It's been the majority against one
the whole time.
What about when you got rid of Se-dol?
Didn't you feel sorry for Justin
when he had to play by himself?
Why, all of a sudden, are you being
so righteous? Pretending to be peaceful--
No, they wanted to play by themselves.
But does Hyun-gyu want to play by himself?
We made him be by himself.
So-hui.
But if this happens, look.
The person who benefits the most
is Hyun-gyu.
We're all in grave danger,
and he's the only one who's safe.
He doesn't need to do anything right now.
So if you do this,
I'm saying that would be unfair to us.
We also put our lives
on the line for this.
Betraying us
after making our scores into that,
that's giving us the axe.
Why bring feelings into it?
We're all just here to play a game--
Hang on.
Why can't I bring feelings into it?
What?
-It doesn't make sense. We're human.
-Fine, we get that.
But why didn't you talk about emotions
right at the beginning then?
-Why are you bringing them up now?
-It's different.
Because the situation has changed.
I understand
where you're both coming from,
but I want to know how you're
planning to play the game from now on.
We haven't discussed it.
It's just that Hyun-gyu asked us for help.
But the thing is,
if you do it suddenly
in the middle of a turn,
what happens to our moves?
We've been planning various moves.
To be honest, my only goal for that round
was to execute the plan I had
to get blue points on my next turn.
I wanted them to just come out
and tell us that they were on a team.
But for this round, I wanted them
to stick to the original plan.
That's the deal
that I was trying to get out of them.
They're not wrong.
What 7high is saying makes a lot of sense.
But the variable is Hyun-joon.
I'm not saying that Hyun-joon had
done anything wrong. His choice is his.
I know that.
And I only did that
because my emotions took over.
So your emotions are saying
you can't do it.
I don't know. But even if I end up dying,
I'd rather play with Hyun-gyu.
Want to do that?
To be honest,
if both So-hui and Kyuhyun join Hyun-gyu…
Although Hyun-gyu is in first place
at the moment,
we can grab first place
if one of us balances up our scores.
Although I really don't want to do this
to Kyuhyun and So-hui,
but if that's what they want,
we'll have to pile it on Kyuhyun
and make one of us finish first.
And what's lucky is that
you're in a better situation than he is.
You just need some blue points.
-Because of the red?
-Yes.
Have you come to a decision?
What have you decided to do?
I know it's uncalled for,
but that's what we're doing.
You've both decided to
play with Hyun-gyu, right?
Then let us make a proposition.
-Right now, it's So-hui's turn.
-Right.
For this turn, we planned our moves
based on the moves
So-hui was going to make.
So for this round,
let's stick to our original plan
and make the moves
that make the most sense
for our previous alliance.
So don't attack anyone,
and just get what we each want.
Is that okay?
No, you still have to keep Hyun-gyu at bay
for the rest of this round.
-I think we can agree to that.
-As we planned.
Let's do that.
Let's do our best again.
Jeong Hyun-gyu!
-We're going to side with you.
-Okay.
But they want to keep you in check
for the rest of this round
because we had plans in motion
with various people in mind.
-Okay.
-That's it.
I'm sorry, everyone.
-I'm sorry.
Okay.
Let's do this. It's So-hui's turn, right?
Okay, can I make a suggestion?
On the next turn, we were originally
going to have So-hui take these
and move them to the devil space
so that Ji-yeong would
get a point from the devil space.
Okay.
I mean, we should do moves
that benefit ourselves
in this round and in this situation.
Let's not, for example,
give Ji-yeong one red point
and Eun-yu a green point.
Let's just get what we can.
But we're not trying
to get what we can and end the game.
We're trying to do what we planned
when we were on the same side.
-Just until the end of this round.
-Taking points from the next turn is--
Didn't you mean not to attack each other
and just to get whatever points we can?
No. We're saying
for the rest of this round,
we play as we had originally planned.
-Right. That's it.
-Because we played according to that.
To be honest,
even if we do that for this round,
everything's already a complete mess.
Because 12 counters have
already been placed haphazardly.
Then what do you want us to do?
So, So-hui splits these three up
and puts Ji-yeong here.
Then what about you?
Then I go here and get some blue points.
Well, since those guys
already compromised a lot,
I suggested doing this for them,
and everyone agreed.
Okay, what do you want us to do?
I think you just have to
put me on the devil space.
Kang Ji-yeong gets one point on red.
It is now Son Eun-yu's turn.
But these are all…
-That's good for you.
-…enemies here.
Right. Just get them.
-Son Eun-yu gets six points on blue.
-Into the wolf's lair.
I'm there too.
Oh, right.
It is now Kyuhyun's turn.
What happens now?
Originally, you should've split this one.
But if 7high ends up here, he's screwed.
Originally I wouldn't go there
if it was going as planned.
I won't put you there then. Okay.
Let's see.
I want to get that though. The blue.
-Do that then. That's good.
-What do you want to do?
I want to get that blue one.
Anyhow, we can't just benefit you guys
and suffer ourselves.
But we've agreed to
play this round as an alliance--
I know, but I still need to get points.
I mean, do this and…
So you want me to just help?
No, set it up like this
and get the points later.
-How?
-Then what do you want to do?
I want to get that.
Then you should do it.
So you're not going to give us this turn?
I mean, I won't be attacking
7high with points even if I do this.
-Of course not. Not in this round.
-Yes, right.
Or will I just do something safe?
-How?
-Is it better to play it safe?
Isn't it better to empty this green?
Because you can get blue points
with that move? Right, two blue points.
That might be a good compromise.
-Right, because 7high is in danger.
-Okay, that seems better.
-Hyun-joon is in danger, and so am I.
-Yes, let's do that.
-So it's better to clear that green one?
-Yes, is that okay?
Okay, go for it.
It's better for you to get points.
Blue like this? Two blue ones?
Kyuhyun has got two points on blue.
It is now Choi Hyun-joon's turn.
-I need red, you need blue.
-Yes.
Hyun-gyu, if you can get us
some points, please do.
-Or be on the offensive if you want.
-Okay, I will.
-Let's take a look at the odds.
-Okay.
Now this is getting fun.
How can they go back to him?
Maybe we should've brought only him.
That would've been better. From the start.
Why did Hyun-joon switch sides?
That's why I was like,
"Is he bad at math?"
Don't say it like that.
-He got hurt because you said that.
-Yeah.
-That was the reason.
-He said that earlier.
He's totally the emotional type.
He gets hurt easily.
I'd better apologize later.
For saying he can't do math.
This is so difficult.
Still. One, two, three, four, five.
I think Eun-yu really wants to come first.
Yes, she really wants
to go to the living area.
This is dangerous for us too.
Too many counters in here.
Let's split it up.
Are we going to split this one?
As soon as we put anyone in here
to make it seven,
it can reach all the way
to the devil space,
so we have to release it first.
I mean, Ji-yeong should.
So, break it apart first?
The difference between Hyun-gyu's scores
is so low.
So, Ji-yeong has to release it.
No, wait a sec.
I'm sorry, but we shouldn't
target Hyun-gyu anymore.
Think about it.
Will they push for Hyun-gyu?
With his total score right now?
His total score is low.
Hyun-gyu isn't the target.
We're in a fight with all three of them.
Choi Hyun-joon gets one point on red.
It is now Kang Ji-yeong's turn.
Ji-yeong probably
won't see me anymore, right?
-When we get out?
-Yes.
-Well, it's just a game.
-It's just a game.
I think she will call me
"Mr. Cho Kyuhyun."
-No, she won't.
-She'll call me by my full name.
She's not like that.
Hey.
What?
-Let's end it with Kyuhyun.
-What?
If we end it with Kyuhyun,
Hyun-joon will be in first.
-Is Hyun-joon first right now?
-Yes.
Oh, he is. Then who's in last place?
Who's in seventh?
How many Pieces does Kyuhyun have?
-Isn't it eight?
-Eight.
Then he'll be out. Eliminated.
-It's your turn next, isn't it?
-It's my turn.
I think I'll be all right because
there aren't many who are going for red.
But for So-hui,
there are a few that are after blues…
Kyuhyun gets two points on green.
Me? What?
That concludes Round 10.
Did you just attack me right at the end?
Round 11 will now begin.
Jeong Hyun-gyu will go first.
-They attacked me on the last turn?
-But we agreed not to in that round.
Okay.
I think they're trying to get rid of me.
Yes, they're all lumped in with me.
They've set it all up.
That's a good setup.
Yes, they've given it a lot of thought.
There's a possibility that I could
get four green points right now.
That would be the worst.
Who do you think is
most desperate to survive?
Eun-yu.
Okay.
Let's strike Eun-yu down a bit
and get you some points.
Then when it's your turn,
we can send more her way.
Okay.
Jeong Hyun-gyu gets one point on green.
It is now 7high's turn.
-I end up as -5 points if they do this.
-You?
-Then I'll have three…
-I don't think they'll do that.
-I'll have two points left.
-They can't afford to do that.
-I think they will.
-No, they won't.
-Darn, the order of play really sucks.
-Right.
How did it end up like this?
-Tell me about it.
-Two alliances taking it in turns.
Eun-yu will never do that.
Look, this is right.
But the reason that doesn't work is,
Kyuhyun will put me in here
with So-hui on his next turn.
Then, unless I put Kyuhyun in there
on my next turn,
he will send me there.
So we can't put Kyuhyun in here.
-What?
-We can't put Kyuhyun in here,
because it's So-hui's turn next.
Hey, if you put me here,
I'll go straight to green, dummy.
This is driving me crazy.
That's why this one is here.
Is there nothing else you can play?
They're giving us points
without picking up any themselves.
I'm a bit worried about that.
But if they do that, the game's over.
It'll be difficult
to try to put you in there.
The devil space?
After all, Eun-yu wants to finish first.
Okay.
Kyuhyun gets five points on green.
It is now Yoon So-hui's turn.
-Minus 13…
-How about I give you some red points?
Kyuhyun's turn is coming up.
If Kyuhyun is at risk of dying,
they'll have to try to save him,
so they'll waste their turns.
That's why we're laying on the pressure.
-We can't let it end like this.
-Exactly.
So don't I need to
increase Kyuhyun's score?
Do it.
-That's not a bad move, is it?
-No.
Kyuhyun gets one point on red.
It is now Son Eun-yu's turn.
Son Eun-yu gets one point on blue.
One blue point.
It is now Kyuhyun's turn.
-I can get that. Or here I could…
-And put it where?
I mean, if I move this one,
Ji-yeong has a counter here too,
so I'm wondering where I should put her.
-You could put her in the angel space.
-Ji-yeong?
Yes, do that first.
Next is Hyun-joon.
We have to think about him.
What should we do
to make sure he can't do anything?
Isn't this the only place
where he can't really do anything?
Let's go to the living area together.
We can get rid of him
if he plays his counters like that.
-Okay, I think this is our best option.
-Yes.
Okay.
Okay. Whatever. Let's do this.
It's done.
Kyuhyun gets five points on red.
-Look.
-It is now Choi Hyun-joon's turn.
Yes.
-You take this and put it here.
-Okay.
-And then? Which one do I move?
-Anything is fine. Then that makes six.
Yes. Six in here.
It's 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6.
Then Kyuhyun is finished.
But it's Hyun-gyu's turn next.
No, it's Ji-yeong next.
You're right.
-Then it's over, right?
-Yes.
Choi Hyun-joon gets six points on red.
It is now Kang Ji-yeong's turn.
So Hyun-joon isn't in first place.
No, Eun-yu is.
Eun-yu is in first.
-Isn't Eun-yu in first?
-She is.
Wait, they're ending it?
If we don't have 15 points,
we all lose half our Pieces.
Exactly.
But right now…
To be honest, I stand to lose the most.
Despite that, I did it
because it was the right time.
I had to make sure Eun-yu came first
to be able to send Hyun-gyu to prison.
Kyuhyun gets five points on green.
Kyuhyun has accumulated
more than 30 points on green.
This concludes Balance Mancala.
Well played. Yeah.
-We didn't have a choice.
-It was my choice.
It was my choice.
No one forced me to do it.
It was all the result of my own decision.
Our original objective was to get
rid of Hyun-gyu and secure first place.
I won by finishing off Kyuhyun,
who was on our team this morning,
so I consider it a partial victory.
We agreed not to make things difficult
for other players,
but at the end of the Round 10,
they lumbered Kyuhyun with some points.
So…
Well…
This happened because of my choice.
Kyuhyun ended up that way
because I was too greedy…
That's how it ends up
when you team up like that.
Thanks.
Here are the results of the game.
A penalty will be given to any player
who failed to reach 15 points.
All players, please
forfeit half of your Pieces.
Gosh.
The player with the lowest score is
Kyuhyun.
Kyuhyun, you currently have four Pieces.
Please give all your remaining Pieces
to Son Eun-yu.
-I did end up helping you in the end.
-Thank you.
So you did. We have a deep connection.
-I helped you.
-Thank you.
Kyuhyun,
you have now lost all your Pieces.
Kyuhyun has become the eighth player
eliminated from The Devil's Plan.
Wow, eight. Well, I was born in '88.
Kyuhyun, please
leave this place immediately.
Since you dealt the final blow,
that makes us even.
-Okay.
-I said this too.
We've been wanting
to play together as a team,
and when we did, it ended up like this.
Right.
Kyuhyun, we do…
-You and I don't make a good team.
-…not make a good team.
Not at all.
Bye, Kyuhyun.
Still, at least you avoided prison.
-Hey, I'm not cut out for prison.
-Of course not.
I'm SUPER JUNIOR.
I'm sorry.
Don't be.
I think the reason I was eliminated
was my indecisiveness.
The problem was probably the side of me
pretending to be righteous.
I've done a lot of shows
where I'm a judge or a host.
But for the first time in ages,
I felt my blood racing.
Becoming an actual contestant,
I ran around and racked my brain
with sincere heart
for a thrilling experience.
I think I'm most grateful
that I'm leaving this show
without the need to feel ashamed
of any of my actions.
I'm off.
-Have a nice day.
-See you.
Goodbye.
GG.
Jeez.
Since I've been practically starved,
I really want to enjoy a good dinner
in the living area.
Why do I feel so down?
Enjoy the living area, okay?
Ji-yeong, please make it back.
You should eat something quickly
while you two are here.
Don't you see me?
On the fifth day,
you finally get to go to the living area.
Still, we got rid of one of them
and dragged another one down into hell.
I consider it a victory 70 to 80%.
Here is the current Piece count
of each player now.
With the least amount of Pieces,
Kang Ji-yeong,
7high,
and Jeong Hyun-gyu,
it has been decided
that you will be in the prison block.
I…
I would like to use
my reward from the hidden stage.
What now?
I knew he wasn't telling us.
The benefit wasn't for the final?
Your reward from the hidden stage,
ten Pieces,
ten Pieces will now be given to you.
What the hell is this?
THE DEVIL'S PLAN
DEATH ROOM
Jeong Hyun-gyu, here is your reward.
Thank you.
What the heck is this?
The current Piece count has been changed.
This is the mother of all twists.
The players going to the prison block are
Kang Ji-yeong,
7high,
and Son Eun-yu.
Wow, this is doing my head in.
3 DAYS EARLIER
You have succeeded the hidden stage.
As a reward, you will be given ten Pieces.
Whenever you want these Pieces,
simply state
"I'd like to receive my reward,"
and they will be given to you immediately.
You may ask for them
even if you have zero Pieces,
but you may not use the reward
in the death room.
Like situations when someone is
holding a knife to my throat,
or when I can make impossible things
possible with these ten Pieces.
I'll use them only in those situations.
They haven't given me anything.
What? Then what was it for?
Well, they'll give me something
helpful in the final round…
-Then no Pieces at all?
-No.
I don't consider those
to be my ten Pieces for now.
So I have to try to get
as many Pieces as possible.
I don't have these ten.
I don't want to go to prison.
I know. I know your stance.
Only a fool would
go play the prison match.
I have to avoid that.
After all the effort
we put in to set this up.
The living area
and prison block assignments
have been finalized.
Please make your way
to your assigned living spaces.
I knew he was hiding something.
Hyun-joon, you had it rough.
You guys killed Kyuhyun for this.
Don't forget that.
I'll be back tomorrow, so you wait.
Well,
I have to kill all of them.
I don't trust anyone anymore.
I don't care if I get
beaten up tomorrow. It's fine.
Hyun-joon, stay strong.
-Bye.
-Keep up the good fight.
Well played.
Damn it, why did she end up here?
-Eun-yu, what the heck is this?
-It's fine.
Let's pull ourselves together.
I assumed he was lying about it.
-But I never expected that.
-It really got me. Seriously.
Then how many did he have?
-Ten.
-He had ten?
So, he could use ten Pieces
any time he wanted.
At any time.
Since he could have lost his Pieces.
At first, I thought
Hyun-gyu was doing everything
he could to avoid being eliminated,
but he was never in danger.
-Right.
-So he did that to protect his Pieces…
-He did.
-…going to So-hui.
Am I just supposed
to accept that right now?
What's more, Kyuhyun must have left
thinking he died a hero's death.
Don't you think Kyuhyun's aware of it?
Wouldn't he?
-I don't think he knows. Would he?
-How could he?
Would he have knowingly
helped him protect 17 Pieces?
He didn't think we'd attack him.
Here's what I'm saying.
Fine, we couldn't eliminate you. Okay.
Let's have a rematch down here.
-He's scared to go up against us.
-He says no.
You can't force someone to come.
Honestly, I'm so mad right now…
Hyun-joon, I'm sorry for saying
you suck at math earlier.
No, it's fine.
You must have been taken aback.
Still, it's good
that your reward was Pieces.
We tried to send you to prison
because we didn't know.
-Hyun-joon, why did you end the game?
-What?
Did you do it because you thought
you might lose your Pieces?
I didn't know.
We all felt the same,
"That guy has a secret reward
for the final."
"We can't just let him be
when we don't know what it is."
That's why we did that.
So, you were trying to eliminate me?
If you had just done nothing,
you could have gone into
tomorrow's battle in second place.
But now you're in third.
Why am I in third?
Because I'll give So-hui some.
Oh, I don't care.
Don't give me any and keep them.
I mean it.
Then just take two.
-No, you keep them.
-Then just one.
-No.
-You never know what will happen tomorrow.
I know that.
That's why you should keep them.
I really want you to go all the way.
So keep them.
I would feel awful if you gave them to me
and something happened to both of us,
so you keep them.
To be honest, I'm really curious
about the bond between you three.
How did you become so tight
that you always take each others' side?
Just because we've had
a lot of fun playing together.
Don't you feel an affinity
with the guys in prison?
I do, but you guys all claim
to be really practical…
I was in prison with them both.
They both mean a lot to me.
Don't worry about that.
-Don't worry.
-Just be practical?
-For sure.
-Okay.
Everyone's different. It's not
like we have to be practical in here.
So, there's a bond between you.
I was just wondering what it could be.
The person I really wanted
to keep in check
is now in first place,
and I'm at a disadvantage in many ways.
Also, he's a strong player,
but after we failed to send him to prison,
I think I'll be fretting all night.
-Hey.
-Why ain't I surprised?
Eun-yu, give me a Piece.
I'm back to reality.
Give me a Piece now
since you didn't get to leave.
-I got four more Pieces.
-Maybe it shouldn't be me.
No, it's better to divide them up
to play the game.
Because we don't know who'll be gone?
Yes, just give me one.
And give one to Ji-yeong.
You can both have three each.
Three, three, two, is that okay?
-Do you have two?
-I have two.
It's fine.
I'll take responsibility for it.
By the way, wasn't that still
quite a good result today?
After we split up,
to be honest,
our moves were much worse off.
But we turned it around.
In any case, we got the win.
Right, I think that was an achievement
in and of itself. Honestly.
Well, but I'm not sure
who that achievement was for.
If you look at it
from Hyun-gyu's point of view,
he got rid of Kyuhyun,
who had nine Pieces, thanks to us.
It did turn out best for Hyun-gyu,
because he's the only one
who got more Pieces,
and even Hyun-joon
lost half of his Pieces.
So, I feel like
I cleaned everything up for him,
and I'm just trying to think
if there's anything I missed.
The hidden rule ruined
our plan to shake things up a bit.
It's disappointing, and it sucks.
I wonder what we get tonight…
I'm suddenly curious about something.
What is the situation
between Hyun-joon and Hyun-gyu?
Why are you asking me that?
-I have no idea.
-What I mean is,
the way I saw them,
it wasn't like that from the beginning.
How did you see them?
Both were like,
"I'll scratch your back
if you scratch mine" kind of thing.
Okay. Since Hyun-joon
is officially on our side now,
I'll tell you the truth.
Ever since he got out of here,
Hyun-joon has been…
-Talking with you.
-…talking with me.
We've been trying to get rid of Hyun-gyu
every chance we got.
He'd already set his mind to that?
-While we were playing that monster game…
-Okay.
You can use items on people.
I want to try it out
with a sneak attack on someone.
-Oh, he told you?
-He told me back then.
After finding that out,
we originally tried to kill Hyun-gyu.
Then attack just once.
-On Hyun-gyu?
-Yes, attack him just once.
In any case, Hyun-joon has been
sort of on our side all along.
I really want to get changed.
I've been getting changed every day.
Right, you have new clothes.
I wear new clothes every day.
People will probably think you've
been wearing the same clothes all week.
I change every day and even take a shower.
Gosh, my head.
Are you okay with your fever?
Yes, I'm fine.
Then were they trying to get me over there
and then eliminate me
by ganging up on me in the prison match?
Right.
But eliminating me
doesn't mean they'd win.
I guess they felt
they had to eliminate you
because they didn't know
what kind of reward you had.
So, I wasn't really happy
with what they said.
So-hui, you have to aim to win.
The rest of us are just trying to survive.
They were saying
they had no ambition to win,
-but they clearly do.
-Exactly.
They're being like that
because they want to win.
How many Pieces does he have right now?
-He had 13 and lost half, so six?
-He has seven.
-Seven?
-Yes.
No.
You should be in second.
That's better for me.
Then how many do you have?
I have 12. I have plenty.
I gave her two.
Good.
I wonder how long Pieces
will be important.
It ends tomorrow.
Whoever two have
the most Pieces tomorrow are it.
I don't think there'll be prison tomorrow.
Since everyone has their own thoughts,
they're all saying they're fine,
but they're not.
Perk up, you.
If you're like that,
it makes me feel uncomfortable.
-No, I'm not like this because of you two.
-Cheer up.
The three of them went to prison again.
-So you're feeling down?
-Yes, of course.
-Don't cry.
-I have to see them play the death match.
I didn't know you'd feel like that.
I'm sorry.
I wonder what today's game will be.
So do I.
The three of us are sitting here again.
And later,
it will just be two of us sitting here.
But today's prison match
is going to be crazy.
In any case,
let's do our best and play fair.
And please don't die helplessly tomorrow.
Right, whoever survives, do your best.
Wow, it's that time again.
The prison match will begin in 30 minutes.
It doesn't even surprise me anymore.
Here is the fifth prison match,
which will determine
the ninth player to be eliminated.
Today's prison match is
Wall Go.
They're playing Wall Go.
-What the heck?
-The three of us?
Wall Go is a game where
players have to build walls on the board
to make their territories
as large as possible.
Hey, we did this together already.
Before the game starts,
players will draw balls
to determine the order of play.
Each player will be given two counters
with each player having a different color.
Beginning with the player going first,
each player will take turns to place
their first counter
on a square of their choice.
The order will be reversed
when placing the second counter.
When the game starts,
each player in turn will move
one of their counters
one or two spaces.
Counters can be
moved up, down, left or right,
but cannot be moved
to a space that is already occupied.
When moving two spaces,
it is possible to move
your counter one space forward
and then back to
occupy the original space.
I think placement is
about 60% of this game.
After you move your counter,
you must build a wall on one of the sides
of the square occupied by your counter.
It is not possible to
build a wall on a side
where a wall has already been built.
Each player has 90 seconds
to complete their turn,
and if they exceed their time,
a wall will be placed at random.
When moving a counter,
it may not pass through a wall
that is blocking its way.
However, each player
will be given one chance
to knock down
a wall on one of their turns.
A player may only knock down
a wall that is blocking their path.
The game will continue in this fashion
until each player's counters are walled
into their own separate territory,
at which point the game will end.
Players should note that the game will end
even if not all players have taken
the chance to play their wall breaker.
I see.
The number of squares
enclosed in each player's territory
will be added together,
and according to
the size of their territories,
players will be ranked,
with the player finishing first
securing their survival.
If multiple players have
the same number of squares,
their rankings will be decided by
comparing the areas
of their biggest territories.
The player finishing first
will be rewarded with one Piece.
The remaining two players will engage
in another game of Wall Go.
Another game?
That's too harsh.
At this time, the rule about
using a wall breaker will be rescinded.
When the game ends,
the player with the larger territory
will secure their survival.
The last remaining player will
be eliminated from The Devil's Plan.
The game will start in 30 minutes.
I think it's quite fair
when it's three players.
Because when three play,
if one person makes a bad move,
it's so disadvantageous.
One-on-one should be fun.
There are four counters
when it's one-on-one.
But there's no wall breaker.
-Right, so it's a battle of pure skill.
-Right.
We played Wall Go among ourselves
a few times.
We didn't play it that much,
but it was a lot of fun.
You can knock a wall down once,
which can be an unknown variable.
When? Whenever you want?
Yes, on one of your turns.
After knocking it down,
you can rebuild it.
After you go through it. Yes, right.
That's a variable.
Well, it's only once a game. Yes.
Then I'll knock it down.
Wow, then you've used it.
What happens now?
Now he's used it.
You smash it and move?
Yes, then keep on with your turn.
-I can just block it like this.
-Wow.
Crazy. But now you've played your trump.
You've taken your shot.
This is fun. It's simple but a lot of fun.
I'll brick him up.
Although he'll
probably smash right through.
But if there's a counter here,
he can't break through that way, right?
He can only come out this way, right?
That's why blocking is crucial.
-Eun-yu will probably be quite good.
-Right.
Then it'll end up as a fight
between Ji-yeong and 7high.
There's nothing to do in prison
except play Wall Go and Knight's Tour.
The game of Wall Go was in the prison,
and I tried to play it
several times from day two,
but I couldn't finish it,
but then I finally succeeded
on the morning of day four.
At that time,
I played with 7high and Ji-yeong too.
I thought it'd be tough to beat 7high
in a one-on-one match.
Gosh, I had no idea
we'd end up playing this here.
Emotionally, I feel like
we're all on the same team.
But it's clear this is a match
to decide who represents us.
Whoever does well
at this game will survive
to get the opportunity
to face off against them.
Well, I'm ready to fight fairly
and accept the result whoever wins.
I think the other two also feel the same.
So I'm going to take it seriously
and give it my best.
Who do you have the closest bond with?
Eun-yu.
I feel sorry for her.
I have a lot of sympathy for Eun-yu.
Tomorrow is the last day,
if you exclude the final.
Staying in prison the whole time
can't be easy.
I guess the chicken in my porridge
this morning wasn't big enough.
Are you talking about
your "What good luck!" speech?
I had a good feeling about today,
but it didn't end well.
The prison match will begin shortly.
All prison players,
please make your way to the death room.
Let's do this!
Seriously, let's try and make it fun.
Let's do this properly.
-Let's have fun.
-Nice.
If 7high comes back tomorrow,
I think he'll storm in gnashing his teeth.
Personally, I hope he's eliminated.
I find him scary.
Me too.
Wow, I'm back here again.
-Why don't we start with a handshake?
-Shall we?
Let's play fair.
Good luck.
Do your best, everyone.
Wow, Eun-yu.
She just looks so pretty now.
With her hair tied back like that,
everything about her.
The fifth prison match,
Wall Go, will begin now.
First, we will decide the order of play.
I've got number two.
Number three is good.
You will now place your counters.
Kang Ji-yeong,
please place one of your counters.
Well.
It's hard when there are three players.
Is it too far towards the middle?
Next is Son Eun-yu.
Please place a counter.
7high.
You will now place your second counters.
7high, please place your counter.
Son Eun-yu.
The only thing I was worried about
while placing counters was that
I was going second both times.
This was what I was most worried about.
When I put my first one on the left,
I placed it slightly towards the top.
So I thought, "If 7high thinks
it's encroaching on his territory
and puts one on my right,
that'll be a bit of a headache,"
but that's exactly what he did.
You've really put me in a bind.
Kang Ji-yeong,
please place your second counter.
MORNING, DAY 4
Ji-yeong put hers in the middle.
I think it'll most likely be isolated.
So, for example,
if you imagine four of us are playing
and there is a counter here,
like this, then this one is trapped.
But if you start from the center
and play well,
you can actually
secure yourself a lot of territory.
All counters have now been placed.
We will now begin playing Wall Go.
Kang Ji-yeong, you have 90 seconds
to move your counter and place a wall.
Ji-yeong moved her counter
towards me and immediately put up a wall,
which wasn't great for me,
because if she pushes in my direction,
that inevitably means
that my plot will be restricted.
Son Eun-yu.
Okay.
They all look nervous from the start
since it's just the three of them.
Whose turn is it?
7high.
-Oh, red?
-Yes.
It is now 7high's turn.
Of course, the only move I could make
was one to put a border
between Ji-yeong and myself.
It is now Kang Ji-yeong's turn.
It is now Son Eun-yu's turn.
Oops.
It is now 7high's turn.
It must be difficult for you.
You have 30 seconds remaining.
Nine,
eight,
seven,
six…
It is now Kang Ji-yeong's turn.
7high can get nine squares
with that red counter.
But if Ji-yeong plays well,
it could be less than nine.
You have to finish first to get out,
but if he's limited to nine,
it'll be really difficult.
He does have a wall breaker though.
It is now Son Eun-yu's turn.
You have 30 seconds remaining.
Ten,
nine,
eight,
seven,
six…
It is now 7high's turn.
And when four people play,
being hemmed in by two walls
is the absolute worst.
-Exactly.
-You could end up dying in one turn.
Exactly. Right.
We've figured that out now.
Now that we've played it,
if it's three players, you play like this,
and as soon as someone is isolated,
you pounce and lock them in
while remaining wary of the other.
And you make it
into a "1-versus-1" type situation.
Even if you're not in an alliance.
You have 30 seconds remaining.
Then, 7high can't move up there like that,
because the yellow one
will move to block him.
So what happens if he moves to the right?
Ten,
nine,
eight,
seven,
six…
-It is now Kang Ji-yeong's turn.
-I knew it.
-She's taken one out of the equation.
-Right.
It is now Son Eun-yu's turn.
Wow, 7high is…
It is now 7high's turn.
So why did you come this way?
Why did you come?
You have 30 seconds remaining.
It is now Kang Ji-yeong's turn.
It is now Son Eun-yu's turn.
It is now 7high's turn.
You have 30 seconds remaining.
You're practically penning me in
and beating me down.
I'm going nuts here.
Well, it only happened
because you came over here.
However it came about,
I couldn't afford
to waste any more moves on it.
Ten,
nine,
eight,
seven,
six,
five…
I made that move thinking,
"Is this the only move I have?"
I wanted to shut down that fight
and was waiting for the opportunity
to use my wall breaker.
It is now Kang Ji-yeong's turn.
With red and blue facing each other,
it'll take two turns to move
two spaces down and escape,
so they're in deadlock.
She's locking Eun-yu in.
It is now Son Eun-yu's turn.
As 7high and Ji-yeong fought it out,
everyone's territories
kind of became defined.
It is now 7high's turn.
Now 7high has no choice
but to escape to the left to win.
Wouldn't he break through?
I suppose he might. Who knows.
Eun-yu was benefiting
from my battle with Ji-yeong, so…
I was going back up
to challenge Eun-yu for territory.
It is now Kang Ji-yeong's turn.
It is now Son Eun-yu's turn.
That will make it difficult
for Ji-yeong to move.
Yes, they have to block Ji-yeong in.
Why did she go there?
My counter was trapped
as red and blue were battling.
But I was actually really happy with that.
If someone has got a lot,
and they're not going to
knock a wall down just yet.
Then I wonder if this counter should
move around putting up walls.
Because the funny thing is,
the territories must be determined
for it to end,
so even if you've secured land…
Oh, you're right about that. Right.
You would have to keep trapping yourself.
I mean, you end up
reducing your territory yourself.
If you look at the area
where I was trapped,
it was kind of like
one square, two squares, one square.
So, if I left that area and shut it up,
I'd cede it to blue,
but it'd have to keep moving
inside there and reducing its territory.
So I thought
it was better to give it to someone else.
It is now 7high's turn.
It is now Kang Ji-yeong's turn.
It is now Son Eun-yu's turn.
Oh, she closed it.
7high.
It is now Kang Ji-yeong's turn.
I was hoping it'd be
turf battle between those two,
but Eun-yu was coming from the top-left,
and 7high was coming like this,
so I was busy defending myself.
After I blocked this one,
I had to block the other next.
You have 30 seconds left.
Ah, she's blocked him.
Why did she do that?
I think she meant to keep 7high in check.
It is now Son Eun-yu's turn.
It was my objective to get the territory
in my top right, from the start.
I was waiting for a chance to go there
or to smash through the wall
if I was completely blocked in.
But then Ji-yeong moved up,
so I thought it was my chance
and quickly moved up.
And as I did that,
7high also blocked here,
so I was thinking it would be difficult
for Ji-yeong to do anything up here.
It is now 7high's turn.
Oh, goodness.
Ji-yeong had become
marooned between the two of us.
As a result,
two separate walls had been formed
rendering my wall breaker useless.
The most decisive thing in
blocking a player's counter is not a wall
but an opponent's counter.
Even if you knock down a wall,
if your path is blocked
by an opponent's counter,
you cannot gain any territory.
Even if they had used their wall breakers
and moved a space,
I would've blocked all of them,
so I wasn't expecting their wall breakers
would do much to shake things up.
Why are you glaring at me?
It's over. It's finished.
I think we're done.
It is now Kang Ji-yeong's turn.
Damn it.
You have 30 seconds remaining.
Jeez.
I will use my wall breaker.
-Confirm you will use your wall breaker.
-Yes.
Oh, Ji-yeong's using her wall breaker.
But she should break that one up there.
Please remove a wall
and move your counter.
Why? Eun-yu can
just block that straightaway.
Ten,
nine,
eight,
seven,
six,
five,
four,
three,
two, one.
Your time is up.
A wall will be placed at random.
Is that being forced on her?
-Why didn't she move another space?
-Exactly.
I can't think properly
when I'm pressed for time.
But this time, we were told
we had up to 90 seconds to think
and do this and that.
That was a lot of pressure
to know I only had 90 seconds.
So, it was like I could
hear a ticking sound in my ears,
and I could feel
the time limit crushing me.
It is now Son Eun-yu's turn.
It's over.
Eun-yu has won.
Yes, for sure.
Goodness. I hate this.
Do it quickly.
You know you've won. Everyone knows.
It's okay. It's just a game.
Why are you crying?
Eun-yu, why are you crying?
There's no need for that.
It's just a game.
Finish it off quickly.
We all know the score. I knew you knew.
You've won. Well played. Go on.
Do it. Well played. Congratulations.
You have 30 seconds remaining.
All counters are now walled off,
thus ending the game.
Congratulations. It's okay.
Why are you crying? Come on.
Eun-yu, it's just a game.
Oh, poor thing.
You just did well.
As a result of
having secured the largest territory,
Son Eun-yu has secured your survival.
Consequently,
Son Eun-yu will be awarded one Piece.
Son Eun-yu,
please return to the living space.
Finish it well and come back.
Okay.
Personally, I think I played
really hard with the two of them.
So when I thought that I was
condemning one of them to leave,
it was really hard for me.
Eun-yu is really good.
Even when we played before,
she was always the best.
The funny thing is
that it just so happened that
Ji-yeong and I had
played together for five days.
So now, we have a lot of shared feelings,
and in the end,
when it was just the two of us left,
I approached the game thinking,
"The best way to respect
my opponent is to give it my all."
To be honest, in that moment, I felt it.
We already knew that we'd already decided,
"If we have to cross swords,
let's fight with dignity."
Once again.
Having failed to secure your survival,
Kang Ji-yeong
and 7high
must play another game of Wall Go.
You will be given four counters each.
The positioning of two counters
has been determined in advance,
but you may choose
where to place the remaining two.
Also, you may not use
the wall breaker in this game.
The player with the largest territory
when the game ends
will earn their survival.
The other player will
become the latest player
eliminated from The Devil's Plan.
As the player who secured
more territory in the previous round,
7high will go first.
Then, the game will now begin.
You will now place your counters.
As the player going first,
7high, please place your first counter.
Kang Ji-yeong,
please place your first counter.
please place your next counter.
Put it in the middle.
In the middle.
There you go.
-Blocking is going to be important.
-Yes.
7high, please place your final counter.
All counters have now been placed.
7high, you have 90 seconds
to move a counter and build a wall.
It is now Kang Ji-yeong's turn.
It is now 7high's turn.
Ji-yeong needs to move in an L-shape.
Yes, she's bound to.
That's not bad.
In any case,
7high has to get out of there.
It is now 7high's turn.
It is now Kang Ji-yeong's turn.
She's good.
I think she'll win
as long as she remains calm.
It is now 7high's turn.
You have 30 seconds remaining.
Ten, nine, eight, seven…
It is now Kang Ji-yeong's turn.
It is now 7high's turn.
You have 30 seconds remaining.
Putting it like this
will be better for her.
Ji-yeong should go here
and put a wall up here.
Then 7high has to block here,
then she can bring this one down.
Ten,
nine,
eight,
seven,
six,
five…
It is now 7high's turn.
-Oh, what was that?
-What is it?
I guess he's trying to block this.
To try and wall Ji-yeong off completely.
It is now Kang Ji-yeong's turn.
It is now 7high's turn.
But Ji-yeong has got a lot.
She can secure nine spaces in there.
It's nine, and even if she loses two,
it's still seven.
It is now Kang Ji-yeong's turn.
Yes, she could get another one.
Oh, she could?
Yes, one or two more squares,
but that one is dead now.
-That's dead.
-You're right.
Oh, dear.
It is now 7high's turn.
It is now Kang Ji-yeong's turn.
But this is really good.
Ji-yeong has effectively
made 7high abandon these two.
So right now, he doesn't have a move.
So leaving counters in place
makes them like a wall.
So I saw 7high's counters
gathered in the center.
So, I thought I shouldn't yield the center
and that I mustn't move these
no matter what.
You have 30 seconds remaining.
Ten,
nine,
eight,
seven,
six,
five…
It is now Kang Ji-yeong's turn.
Why did he do that?
Has he blocked that because he thinks
all this is his? What's going on?
Ji-yeong has eight, nine, eleven.
She'll win
if she just gets another five or six.
I think she's going to win
unless she makes a mistake.
I was trying to trap
the counters in the center
and made a mistake
by putting one in a bad spot.
You have 30 seconds remaining.
What the heck?
Why? There's no wall breaker this time.
Are they like this
because they're nervous?
Maybe they're just so tired.
Yes, it's difficult to think straight
when you play there.
Why did she do that?
It is now 7high's turn.
Oh, no.
I was determined to stay put
and not give up the center,
and give myself room
to move in any direction as needed.
I was so absorbed in my thoughts
that I pretty much isolated myself.
You have 30 seconds remaining.
Ten, nine…
It is now 7high's turn.
This is the best option for 7high,
because it earns him three more squares.
It is now Kang Ji-yeong's turn.
I hope Ji-yeong notices this.
Exactly, that's her escape route.
Nice!
Yes!
Huh?
-But she could've gone further.
-There was no need for that.
She needed to block it later.
To be honest, I actually thought
about going further up and blocking it,
but thinking I might've gone too far up,
suddenly I got scared.
So I was overthinking things.
You have to move that counter.
The one at the top.
It is now 7high's turn.
It is now Kang Ji-yeong's turn.
Nine, twelve.
Eighteen, nineteen, oh.
You have 30 seconds remaining.
I wanted to play the best possible move.
But time was passing,
and every time he was counting down,
my heart was just…
Don't do it. Don't go there.
Not there.
Why would you go there?
Ten,
nine,
eight,
seven…
It is now 7high's turn.
It is now Kang Ji-yeong's turn.
You have 30 seconds remaining.
Ten,
nine,
eight,
seven,
six,
five,
four,
three…
Put it underneath. Underneath.
Two, one…
Underneath.
No, put it underneath!
Oh, no.
It is now 7high's turn.
GG.
All counters are now walled off,
thus ending the game.
Here are the results of the game.
Having gained the larger area,
7high has secured his survival.
Having failed to secure her survival,
Kang Ji-yeong becomes the ninth player
eliminated from The Devil's Plan.
Kang Ji-yeong,
please leave this place immediately.
I can't believe Ji-yeong is leaving.
It's such a shame.
I feel so sorry for her.
I'm used to this kind of competition,
so I don't feel sad or anything
about eliminations.
I've always just taken it
as part and parcel of the game.
But I've experienced
a lot of things with Ji-yeong.
Like having
that ridiculous bread in prison
and also having a beer
together in the living area.
There was also the sense of helplessness
we felt together in the main game,
and after all that, I ended up
sending her home myself.
So I think it's the first time
I've felt like this.
I really…
I'm so glad we got the chance
to keep playing together. Honestly.
I really hope you know that.
Everything's so vivid.
I keep thinking of
when I said goodbye to Justin
and putting Kyuhyun's counter
in the Devil space at the end.
And of when I first came in here
and saw Kyuhyun and thought,
"Oh, now things are getting real."
And since I was eliminated while
trying my best in my own way at the games,
I don't have any anger or hard feelings.
In fact, I feel relieved.
My biggest regret is stepping aside
when we found the secret wall,
and I think that led me
to this end result.
When it comes to
a contestant for the final…
Well, I definitely have a bias,
so I just hope that
either 7high or Eun-yu goes to the final.
Then I'll be cheering them on
no matter what.
Well played.
See you the day after tomorrow.
That concludes the prison match.
7high, please return to the living space.
You did well.
Honestly, I knew I'd feel like this
after it was over, but it's…
I had no idea.
So, I'm feeling a bit out of it right now.
It wasn't something we planned,
but somehow coincidentally,
Ji-yeong and I kept playing together.
And more than anything,
when the three of us played together,
how do I put it?
Our play was driven
by pent-up anger and grit…
Our play from rock-bottom.
Yes, so I think it felt different
when the three of us played together.
To be honest,
I would've been really sad too
if one of us got eliminated
for a mistake made in the main match.
But it happened while we competed
against each other in a prison match.
It's different from
losing in the main match and leaving.
So I really thought
this situation wouldn't happen today.
But…
Honestly, when Ji-yeong
comes back the day after tomorrow,
I think it will feel like
the opening of a treasure chest.
If one of the two of us is standing there.
When the treasure chest gets opened,
she has someone to cheer on.
Or maybe both of us will be sitting there.
Nobody knows.
When you say things like that,
it makes me feel so sad.
Like I have to live
up to her expectations.
But honestly, you're really amazing.
You've come through this five times now.
Tomorrow, I'd really love
to sleep in the living area.
-Then, you've made it to the final.
-I won't have any opportunity otherwise.
It's ironic. I can't spend a night there
unless I make it to the final?
Oh? Yes.
If you don't make it to the final,
you can't change your clothes,
and you'll end the game with no make-up
and wearing a prison uniform.
Hey, what better motivation
is there than that?
-That's some motivation.
-That's so funny.
If Eun-yu claws her way into the final,
she'll be formidable.
Wow, if she does that,
then she'll be called
"Queen of the Prison."
Eun-yu really is amazing.
Just how scary is Eun-yu?
She's the Queen of the Prison,
but the fact that she's really good
at maintaining her composure
makes me think she's really amazing.
I'm looking forward to going
up against her properly tomorrow.
I'm going to do my utmost to
ensure that we're still in 1st and 2nd.
Only the top two will survive tomorrow.
So you have to protect your position.
Okay.
Still, today might have
turned out well for Hyun-gyu,
but I think it's meaningful
that So-hui lost a lot of her Pieces.
In any case, if it's a solo game,
then Hyun-joon's Pieces…
But I'm not thinking
about things like that anymore.
-Really?
-In any case,
it won't be a fight
to take Pieces from each other.
It'll be more like a system
that weaponizes Pieces.
Right.
That's how games are.
If you manage to get a hit in,
another chance will follow.
And if your opponent makes
a mistake after that,
-you can get another chance.
-That's what we did today.
Then they might go down.
But today, both sides
suffered a lot of damage.
Because of Hyun-gyu.
To be honest,
I've been thinking I was the villain.
I thought, "Oh, why do I keep
doing such bad things?"
for the past five days.
But there was
a real villain hidden in plain sight.
I was nothing but a hoodlum.
A hoodlum? Not a villain but a hoodlum?
I wasn't a villain, I was a hoodlum.
The real villain was someone else.
Well, to be honest, I was impressed
with all the moves
that Hyun-gyu made today.
And after that,
that stunt he pulled at the end
with the Pieces, yes, I was amazed,
but it wasn't because
he made a really great move.
I was just, "Wow, how can he…"
"How can he go that far?"
Yes, but I think in some way,
that's pretty amazing too.
If you look at all this as one long game,
he's made a very good move there.
-It was the right choice. Yes.
-At the end…
He had a golden ticket up his sleeve
and played it at the end.
So he made
the best choice for his survival.
He put that as top priority.
He made the best choice.
Well, his moves were good,
but there are people
who have been hurt and eliminated.
Tomorrow, 7high is probably
going to direct a lot of rage at you.
But what did I even do?
He might attack me by sacrificing himself.
If I were 7high, I'd do that
to back Eun-yu up.
So I'm bearing that in mind.
Anyhow, things are very simple now.
The game has become very simple.
It's kill or be killed.
Have fun tomorrow.
So-hui and I are going to play together.
Without you.
Fine.
I'm telling you in advance.
Even then,
he was so honest and ruthless.
"Hyun-joon, I'm going to play
with So-hui tomorrow, not you."
You do your best, and I'll do mine.
In any case, I need to go
up against Hyun-gyu again,
so I think it'll be fine
if I play with 7high and Eun-yu.
At least,
we'll be able to mount a defense.
Although he has
so many more Pieces than us,
I'll do my best.
You went through a lot today.
You went through more.
We need to be
in tip-top condition tomorrow.
Is that really possible in here?
As best as we can in this situation.
If we get abalone porridge
tomorrow, I'll really enjoy it.
I want to eat samgyetang.
That would be great.
But it will never happen.
I think the best we can
expect in here is abalone porridge.
I just miss meat,
like braised spicy chicken,
braised short ribs, and things like that.
That'd be amazing.
I didn't think I was missing anything.
I thought I'd forgotten all about food,
but braised spicy chicken or short ribs?
Amazing.
Yikes.
Thank you.
What could it be?
I wonder what it is.
Hey.
Is it abalone porridge?
Isn't this beef and mushroom porridge?
Oh, it is. It's mushroom porridge.
Three different types
of mushroom porridge now.
Darn it, I'm so depressed.
I was looking forward to it.
Still, at least
it has a bit of beef in it.
There's hardly any meat.
-Are you going to get up?
-Yes.
Did you sleep well?
How about you?
-I slept well. Yes.
-You did?
I'm full.
No matter how much I eat, I feel empty.
No matter how much I eat,
I feel like I'm getting indigestion.
Wow, it doesn't feel real
that this is a set,
and we have to play a game in a bit.
It's the same every day.
Don't you think people change
the moment they leave this room?
That's what scares me.
The atmosphere here, the warm
atmosphere in prison, it all vanishes…
-Right.
-…and everyone is on their own.
Of course that's how it should be,
but still. Jeez.
-It's not easy.
-No.
That door is the problem.
The moment we leave here
and enter the game area,
people change.
They're not their usual human selves.
Toss Sang-yeon out.
We need to just kill them all.
I think we have no choice
but to go with them.
Do you know how to do arithmetic?
I'll be back tomorrow, so you wait.
It's like they turn into
the most hideous version of themselves.
What exactly was that thing you did then?
When you and Justin
only had a few chips left,
what exactly did you do then?
How did you determine whether
it was the right time to go all-in or not?
To put it simply,
when you judge that it's meaningless
to just raise one or two chips,
and you're better off doubling up,
you can use the strategy.
For example,
if you think that
after seeing two more cards,
there's a 50% chance
you'll have a good hand.
-Okay.
-Imagine a situation like this.
Someone has 150 chips,
another person has 30, you have 20,
and I have 10.
They have 150, 30…
Is that what our situation is now?
That's our situation.
That's why I'm giving this example.
So I go all-in.
But the other two fold.
It's just you left.
Now, you think you have a 50% chance
of developing your hand.
Or you might end up with nothing.
Now, do you think you can call?
-It's not easy.
-Right.
To be honest,
the strategy of going all-in…
You only use it against someone
who'd feel the pressure.
Then how do you go up
against the guy with 150 chips?
It's tough.
It's a long, drawn-out war.
Games like that are really tiring.
You have to consider
how many chips you have
and decide whether to go
for a short, sharp game
or try and drag things out.
I hope today's game will
be a long, drawn-out affair.
After all, aren't we going to be stronger
than the other two in a long fight?
I actually think
it's a miracle we're still alive.
But I'm holding onto the hope
that such a miracle will occur again.
We must do what we can.
Right.
I wonder how fun today's game will be.
That startled me.
THE MAIN MATCH WILL BEGIN SHORTLY
You get startled every time.
The main match will begin shortly.
All players, please make
your way to the game area.
Let's do this!
Yeah!
We got this!
Let's have some fun.
Let's do this!
-Good!
-Something feels different today.
There's, like,
a higher tension in the air.
Great.
-Oh, it's betting.
-Yes.
-Good morning.
-Now this is more like it. Hello!
Hi.
-I'm sorry, Eun-yu.
-Thanks.
What do you mean?
The Queen of the Prison is going to win.
-Cut it out, Hyun-gyu.
-We've been saying that all along.
Fourteen?
I was blown away when you got 14.
I had to solve an 8x8.
There was an 8x8 version
of A Knight's Tour?
6x6, 7x7, and 8x8.
That's amazing. Then you deserve them.
Thanks.
7high.
Hello.
Well played. I watched the Wall Go.
Hey, Hyun-joon.
I can't believe you're wearing denim.
It's hilarious.
I wore it on purpose.
-On purpose?
-Yes.
After all, we'll be playing as a team.
Good morning.
The sixth main match of The Devil's Plan
will now begin.
Kang Ji-yeong was eliminated
during yesterday's prison match,
leaving just five players remaining.
Gosh, that's right.
Before the game begins,
here is the current Piece count
of each player now.
Currently,
Jeong Hyun-gyu has the most Pieces.
Here are the rules
of the sixth main match.
Today's main match is
Doubt and Bet.
Doubt and Bet is a game
where players must predict
the number of cards of a certain color
or doubt your opponent's prediction.
The game is played
with a total of 60 cards;
10 each of red, yellow,
green, blue, purple and rainbow.
Before the game starts,
each player will be given
5 card slots and 4 slot chips.
The slots are the spaces where
players place the cards they are given,
and the slot chips are used
instead of the slots when they bet.
After thoroughly shuffling all 60 cards,
the dealer deals each player in turn
five cards face down.
When all players have
placed their cards in their slots,
the player going first
will make a prediction and a bet.
The player going first has
three minutes to make a prediction
on how many cards in total
of a certain color
are held by all players in their slots.
And rainbow cards
will be counted
as the color that was predicted.
After making their prediction,
the player will consider how much
to wage on it and place their bet.
The player will bet at least one Piece,
or may alternatively bet a slot.
To bet a slot,
the player will use a slot chip.
If the player loses,
that slot will be withdrawn,
and in the next round, they will
only receive the number of cards
equal to the number of
slots they have available.
One slot is reserved
for participating in the game
and may not be wagered.
That is to say,
a maximum of four slot chips can be used.
After the first player has made
their prediction and bet,
the next player uses their turn to declare
that they either "accept"
or "doubt" the prediction.
Accept.
If they judge that the previous
player's prediction is correct,
they will declare "accept."
If they declare acceptance,
the Piece or slot chip
wagered by the previous player
is returned to them,
and the player who declared acceptance,
makes their own prediction and wager
in the same fashion.
At this stage,
the player must make a prediction
that is higher than the prediction
they have just accepted.
For example, if the previous player bet
that there were seven yellow cards,
the current player must bet that
there are at least eight yellow cards.
Because they accepted it.
At this time,
they may bet on the same color
or change to a different color.
Doubt.
If they judge that
the previous player's prediction is wrong,
they will declare that they "doubt" it,
and go up against that player.
Darn, it's a head-to-head duel.
The doubting player can choose
to "raise" or "call" the previous player.
If they choose to raise,
the player being doubted can choose
to raise, call or fold,
and betting will continue
until one of the players calls or folds.
When one of the two players folds,
the Pieces and slot chips wagered
are given to the other player,
and the round ends
without the cards being revealed.
If both players have
wagered the same number of chips,
and one of them calls,
all cards are turned face up.
If this reveals that the previous
player's prediction was wrong,
the doubting player
has made a successful doubt
and receives
all the Pieces or slot chips wagered.
For example,
a player doubts a prediction
when at least five red cards
have been wagered.
If there are only four red cards
when the cards are revealed,
the player that made the bet loses the bet
and loses all the Pieces
and slot chips they wagered.
But if the player
that made the bet is correct,
that is to say there are at least the same
number of cards as was predicted or more,
the doubt fails,
and the player that instituted the bet
gets all the Pieces and slot chips
that were wagered.
At this time, slot chips that were bet
are converted into Pieces.
Oh, you receive Pieces, not slots.
Moreover, at any point during the game,
players may exchange Pieces for slots
and vice versa.
When exchanging slots for Pieces,
you can only receive
as many slot chips as there are slots.
It is not possible
to have more than five slots.
Oh, that's the max.
When the match-up is over, the round ends,
and all players will return their cards.
The cards are then shuffled
and dealt to the players
in as many slots as they have,
and the game continues.
The order of play for Round 1
will be decided by drawing lots,
and from Round 2, the player
that lost the bet will go first.
If someone is eliminated,
the player directly before them
will go first,
and players will swap places
every ten rounds.
Additionally, after the end of round 15,
every five rounds, all players
will relinquish one Piece each.
What the…
Looks like fun.
If a player loses all their Pieces,
they are eliminated,
and the game will continue
until three players remain.
When there's three left?
When the game is over,
each player will be given one Piece
for each slot they still have in play.
At this time,
the player with the most Pieces
will advance to the final match.
The other two players will go to prison.
The prison's still in play today?
Come on, don't be like that.
The game will start in 30 minutes.
That's a bit harsh, Mr. Dealer.
Spend this time as you wish.
I might go back to prison?
If I spend tonight in prison,
I suppose that's a good thing.
"God, there's still prison?"
That's what struck me the most.
But the next thought I had was,
"Wait, it's not so bad."
All I have to do is
finish in the top three,
and after that,
I can just play the prison match.
I thought that was better for me.
I thought this might be a game
which might send me home sooner,
but it also might be
the only game that would give me
a chance of making it to the final.
So it's not that bad.
We need to work together.
Information is king.
-Of course.
-Let's talk with Hyun-joon.
-Let's talk.
-7high, come over here.
It looks like those three
are going to work together.
-What?
-I think those three are working together.
Anyhow, he was very open.
Last night he actually said,
"I'm not going to play with you."
So, the three of us have to play together.
-Of course we will.
-Yes, well, precisely.
In a game of five people,
three people sharing information
is a huge benefit.
It's a great advantage.
So we can use
that information to gain chips.
So ultimately, hopefully
it's them that will be eliminated.
Pro-poker player 7high,
Goddess of the Prison Eun-yu, and me…
What am I?
Just someone that survived the prison.
The three who have been to prison
versus the two who haven't.
Of course, we might
end up being eliminated.
Still, our objective is to show
how desperate we can get.
I think a lot will be
decided by the order of play.
Yes, I thought it'd
be a completely individual game.
It is.
But it ended up like this?
I didn't think
we'd split up to talk like this.
We have a lot of Pieces,
so we can work together,
but those guys can't.
So-hui and I each have a lot of Pieces,
so we're thinking of
applying pressure from Round 15 on.
We tough it out to Round 15,
and they're bound to be divided.
And I'm hoping to see 7high in danger
so that they turn against each other.
If we do this, it's so simple.
We just need to share what we have
-with each other.
-Exactly.
We just have to play
a game of guessing ten.
-That's better than having to guess 15.
-Yes.
But how do we share?
We get them, then write it down,
and then, during those three minutes,
we can gather together and share.
So there are six colors.
Let's assume that the 25 cards
are evenly distributed to some extent.
That means there are
about four of each color, right?
Then eight on average.
Since the rainbow cards
are equivalent to plus four.
It doubles up any color.
So we can calculate to some degree.
This is important.
It’s eight on average?
Because, it's an average of four,
and the rainbow just adds four
to everything.
-Right. So it's an average of 4.33.
-To everything?
Because if I choose blue,
the rainbow cards are blue,
if I choose red, then they're red.
Then, it's better
if we get a lot of rainbow cards.
-For sure. That's the best.
-Right.
And it's good for us to be
at one extreme or the other.
Either absolute none,
or an absolute truckload.
Either a lot or none
of a particular color.
They will go for "true" in the beginning.
-They can't bluff.
-You're probably right.
Since they have to play it safe,
they're just going to go for true.
So, if we're bluffing and they doubt me?
If they doubt, just call.
Yeah, just call it.
If they doubt you on three,
just give it to them.
-Right.
-Right? You only lose one chip.
But once they start leaning,
we just keep raising.
Right, I'm going to raise them every time.
I've just going to go for them.
I think they're mostly just going to call.
I'm just going to go for it all.
I'm going to be eliminated anyway.
I'm mentally prepared.
You're going for it right from Round 1?
I'm a Poker player.
I don't bluff when I'm in a tight spot.
Just don't forget, your slots are
like energy to our alliance.
I'm very aware.
It's my life, so I'll do my best.
Don't worry. I won't do anything stupid.
We can just bluff once in a while.
So, if I bet a slot chip and lose it,
I lose the slot itself, right?
For example, if I lose two slot chips,
then do I lose the slots as well?
Players can use their slot chips
to wager card slots instead of Pieces.
However, if they lose the slot chip,
they also lose the slot itself,
which reduces the information they have
and makes subsequent predictions
more difficult.
When we start taking their slot chips,
we're on the road to victory.
Right.
But I think the order of play
is going to be so important.
If the three of them are
one after the other…
-The worst-case scenario would be this.
-…it's not easy.
Two, one… If we're stuck like this.
Exactly. I'm worried
that's going to happen.
Then someone definitely
has to doubt someone.
-That’s how the game ends.
-Exactly.
If we're in a row,
it won't be bad to shut it down
exchanging a Piece.
You can make strange doubts,
but also accurate doubts.
We can exchange them back and forth.
Right, you can guess it spot on
or incorrectly.
Then I'll raise two and just get it wrong.
Let's hope we're playing in a row
so our strategy works.
Right.
-It's a war of attrition.
-Yes.
We need a bit of luck.
Right.
We need a good place.
This is going to be fun.
Let's make it to the final. Whoever it is.
Your time is up.
Please gather in the hall.
Let's do this!
We can turn things around.
All three of us might make it.
That's really possible.
Goodness.
This is going to be fun.
You will now draw lots
to determine the order of play.
Please.
Oh, nice.
It'll be just a bit hard to communicate,
but we got good positions.
Is Hyun-gyu going first?
Hey, Hyun-gyu, honestly.
Hey, Hyun-joon,
wouldn't you be better off joining us?
-What?
-At least prison would be guaranteed.
He's at it again.
You said you wouldn't play with us.
You can come to us.
No, thanks.
I will now shuffle the cards.
Today, I'm even more certain.
So-hui and I are aiming for the top two.
Having made it this far, I'd better win.
I want to get to the final, at least.
I'm proud of myself
for making it this far from prison.
I just hope Hyun-gyu won't lose.
I want to help him as much as I can.
I'm in a very unfavorable position
right now with just two Pieces.
So I'm going to put my life
on the line and do my best.
Round 1 of Doubt and Bet will now begin.
What's more, Kyuhyun must have left
thinking he died a hero's death.
Don't you think
Kyuhyun's aware of it? Wouldn't he?
-I don't think he knows. Would he?
-How could he?
Did any of the others know about
your reward? That it was ten Pieces?
Can I let you in on a secret?
-A secret? About where you went?
-Yes.
I solved it with just a minute left
and got ten Pieces.
But I get the Pieces
whenever I ask for them.
If I yell out,
they'll give them to me straightaway.
So I've got a reason to never go to jail.
Wow, that's amazing.
I wanted to tell you and So-hui.
Okay.
I'll give you more if I get them.
Don't. Please don't.
I want you to get through.
-Still, I hope you--
-I hope you don't end up in prison.
Still, I hope you do well until the end.
-But you never know.
-That's amazing.
Wow, that's amazing.
That means you're practically immortal.
Then who do you want to end up last?
-Do we have to decide that right now?
-Yes.
I want to get rid of Hyun-joon
because of Hyun-gyu.
But I think Hyun-gyu is going to win.
Hyun-gyu is going to win for sure.
-Because he's just that strong right now.
-Because… Yes, he is.
Then let's target Hyun-gyu.
Then we should do that.
If we don't, I think he'll get through.
If we can send him to prison,
we can eliminate him there, right?
But there's nothing
wrong with that, right?
I don't want to reveal
Hyun-gyu's reward by killing him.
"You practically have one more life,
so you can lose a life
and start over with the ten Pieces."
But is it really right to ask that of him?
And I felt a little sorry for him
battling all alone against six players,
so I wanted to help him.
Subtitle translation by: Paul Carver