Hi!
Hello!
Are you Parin?
This woman…
Her smile seems familiar.
Yes? No?
You are?
Thea.
I'm Thea. Nice to meet you.
I have something to ask you.
Answer me, please.
Are you Parin?
No? Yes?
Oh, what's happening?
Don't follow me.
Hey!
Minutes.
Hours.
Days.
Months.
A year.
These are the markers of our memories.
Waiting…
and waiting.
Why do we always search for answers?
Answers that time may never reveal.
Last year,
I’ve been searching for someone.
But that someone…
chose to become a mystery.
I’d like to warmly
welcome you onboard CX 614,
our oneworld flight to Hong Kong.
Captain Chris Johnson
will take us to Hong Kong
in two hours and 45 minutes.
To our members,
it’s a pleasure to see you all again…
Would you care for a champagne, sir?
What?
You're giving me champagne?
Don't you have something stronger?
Yes, we have stronger drinks.
What would you care for?
Oh my God.
Whiskey,
vodka,
tequila.
Whatever is stronger.
Certainly, sir. I’ll be right back.
Dad,
I'm going to Hong Kong.
I don't know how long I'll be there.
I hope you and Mom…
Forget it.
Just call me if you need anything.
So, what brings you to Hong Kong?
I'm looking for my mom.
Your mom is missing?
She left a message to my dad,
like, last month.
And… I just found out,
like, three days ago.
What did she say?
She left a short note to Dad saying,
"I'm leaving you and everyone else.
Don't look for me."
What?
Did you guys have, like, a family fight
or something?
You know, my dad has been busy
with his business trips.
Actually, everyone is just busy
with the last weeks, months, years.
I don't know, man.
Man, I'm sorry to hear that.
So, how's your business going?
Didn't you say that you were getting
into the car business?
Well,
I thought it would fly.
It was doing so well at first,
and then, it went down, like…
so fast!
Hello, George?
Yes, George. What's up?
I'm sorry for your loss.
Yeah.
Oh yeah, sure.
I will do your shift tonight.
Yes. I can do it.
For the entire week?
You know if I do my shift in the morning
and then your shift at night,
I might be the next one to die.
Don't cry.
Yes. I understand.
Okay.
I can do it.
Yes, sure.
Sure.
I got you.
Okay.
Bye-bye.
Condolence.
Here’s your keycard,
and the instructions for the wi-fi
are written here as well.
-Enjoy your stay!
-Thank you.
Hey, Leo!
Bro!
Dude!
Oh my God!
-Hey!
-Wait. Two more shots.
Two more?
-Two more shots. Wait.
-Alright.
Oh my, please don't approach me.
Oh, here's the bar table.
Two more shots.
Two more.
Good evening, sir.
Do you have a reservation?
-Two more shots.
-Two more shots!
-Two more shots! Hey!
-Hey.
-Hold up.
Please tell your driver
to move the car.
I have to move the car, bro.
Alright, brother!
-I missed you!
-Yeah.
Hang out again. Tomorrow.
Oh, your luggage.
-Don't forget it.
-Thank you.
Thank you.
Sir?
Do you have a reservation?
Hey.
I'm drunk, but I'm not deaf!
Iris.
So, sir…
do you have a reservation?
No.
I don't have.
Okay, sir.
So, upon checking, unfortunately,
we are fully booked,
and we only have one room available.
It is the suite room.
Room 2802.
Here.
Oh.
Sir!
Bhurit…
Bhuritparin?
Dammit!
What does this name even mean?
Bhuritparin. Kieth…
Kieth…
methikul…
Iris, what's the matter?
A guest arrived.
-And?
-And he's drunk.
He left his passport, wallet, and luggage.
He just left everything here.
Okay, make sure you return his stuff,
including his luggage.
Including his luggage?
It's important that you take care
of that guest.
Come on.
-Okay, ma'am.
-I'll handle this.
-Okay.
-Go ahead. Go.
Wait, sir.
Sir!
No, don't!
Wallet, cellphone, and passport.
Blanket.
Hang on.
I must admit. This guy is cute.
Hey!
Drop it, Iris!
What the heck are you doing?
Okay.
I have to go now, sir.
Good night.
It's too early!
Hello?
Yes?
Our boss just called me.
He asked us to take care
of Mr. Bhuritparin.
Come again?
His father called our boss.
We're going to be in trouble
if we don't look after him.
Hey!
I'm looking for the owner of this.
Yes, sir, it's mine.
So, you were in my room?
Yes, Mr. Buniparin.
-It's Bhuritparin.
-Oh!
What's wrong with you?
Bhuritparin.
So, why were you in my room?
You don't remember, sir?
No.
Okay.
So, sir, you were drunk,
and you came with your--
Hello?
Yeah, I'll meet you outside.
Alright.
Sir?
Yes?
Don't you want to hear
the rest of the story?
I'm drunk.
That's the story.
Sir?
Is there anything else I can do for you?
I don't need help with anything.
I am being dragged.
I am being dragged away again
by this woman.
Good Lord, sir!
You didn't make it again!
I have to pick you up
in the hallway again!
-Do you know that?
-Why am I so important for someone
-who doesn't even know me?
-I bought you apples.
An apple a day really does keep
the doctors away.
Mr. Buniparin?
Mr. Buni.
There's something special
about this incredibly strong woman.
Dammit, sir!
You're burning me out!
Next time, don't drink too much
if you can't take care of yourself!
I shouldn't be carrying you!
What are you?
A baby?
She gives me words of wisdom.
And what's truly important
are relationships and good health.
Mr. Buni?
Buniparin!
Hello.
Buniparin?
Never to give up.
Never to give up on life.
Oh, look!
This monkey has even the nerve to smile!
You know, when I'm sad,
I exercise.
You know, it's good
for your mind, body, and soul.
You bike.
It makes you feel calm.
Hi, sir. Good evening, sir.
-Bye, sir.
-Hello.
Excuse me, miss.
I think we lost our keycard.
So, do you think you can make
another one for us, please?
Oh, sure, sir.
I'll be back or I will have
someone to come here.
Wait. Sorry.
I think we found it already.
-No problem, sir.
-We were at the rooftop.
We thought we lost it there.
And there was a guest there.
He was really drunk.
And he wanted us to get away from him.
Yes. And he's flapping
his arms like a bird.
You should take a look at this guy.
Thank you for that information, sir.
I will have everything taken care of.
Thank you.
-Thank you.
-Good evening.
Mr. Buni?
Sir?
What?
-I'm a bird.
-Mr. Buniparin!
Stop.
Mr. Buniparin! Please!
In every problem, there is a solution,
and in every solution,
you will find peace.
Peace?
Sir, please. I'm begging you. Please!
Get down from there! Or else…
Or else what?
-Sir.
-What the fuck are you doing?
Sir, I am saving you.
Saving me from what?
I am saving you, sir, from jumping!
I'm not going to jump.
I'm going to fly because I'm a bird!
Goddammit!
Sir, I like your bird.
I mean, it's good
that you want to be a bird,
but you are not a bird, Mr. Buniparin.
It’s Bhuritparin!
Sorry, Mr. Bhuritparin.
Is there anything else I can do for you?
Doctor!
-I need a doctor now!
-Okay! Okay!
-Okay.
-No, don't leave me.
Just call a doctor.
-Just call a doctor!
-Just stay there, little bird! Okay?
What?
Good day, love.
Hi, Doc.
-Is it serious?
-He'll be fine.
Not serious at all.
You've got nothing to worry about.
A few days rest and he will be back
on his feet in no time.
-Thank you, Doc.
-No problem at all.
-Thank you.
-I'll see you later.
Okay.
Mr. Buni.
Sir?
Hello, sir. Can I enter?
You're already inside.
Sorry.
I brought you food.
Will you prepare it for me?
Yes, sir, sure!
Hello.
Uncle, have you seen my message?
Have you seen Mom?
Or did she get in touch with you recently?
No.
The food is ready, sir!
Knowing that you're Thai,
I bought you this Thai food
from Thai Street
in Little Thailand.
Well, I'd be surprised
if you bought American food
in European Street
for a Thai guest that you have injured.
You're so funny, sir.
You really have a good sense of humor.
Anyway.
I bought you pad thai,
Thai basil chicken, and tom yum.
Oh, sorry, sir.
I forgot, I have to go
to my workstation now.
Enjoy your meal.
Hey.
Do you want to join?
I mean…
If you don't want to, that's fine.
Oh, no, sir.
I mean, yes.
Yes! I'd love to join.
You know, I'm actually
very hungry right now.
Let's eat.
Okay.
Sir, again, I would like to apologize
for what happened.
And now, as a sign of peace,
as you can see,
I bought you Thai food
from the Thai Street in little Thailand.
And now, I accepted your offer
to start dining with you.
Now, we can start eating.
Thank you, sir.
What is wrong with you?
You're like a robot or a talking parrot.
Why, sir?
You're too formal.
But sir, you are my guest.
And I am but a simple receptionist.
Whatever. Let's eat.
Okay.
This is so good.
Like the original tom yum.
It is original, sir,
because I bought that
from the Thai store--
In Thai Street in Little Thailand.
I know.
I can bring you there.
Yeah. If I can go.
It hurts.
It's just a bad sprain, sir.
You know, in a matter
of three to five business days,
you'll be fine.
How long do you intend to stay here, sir?
I don't know.
Weeks.
Months.
Forever.
Oh, then there's plenty more time
to visit the Thai street
in little Thailand,
you know.
You definitely won't miss your Thai food
while you're here, sir.
So,
will you go with me tomorrow?
-Where?
-Thai stores… in Thai Street.
I'm not sure, sir,
because I'm on duty every night.
Then, let's do it in the afternoon.
I'm also on duty, sir.
Do you ever rest?
It's only for this week, sir,
you know, and also… more…
kaching kaching!
What?
Kaching kaching!
It's a slang term for "more money".
And more money means more fai lok.
-Fai what?
-Fai lok.
It’s Cantonese for "happiness".
That's not true.
What's not true, sir?
Money cannot buy happiness.
I'm not saying all the time, sir,
but money can buy certain happiness.
For instance,
are you enjoying your tom yum?
Yes.
Are you happy eating Thai food?
Well, yeah.
Then you are happy!
I bought your happiness!
Whatever.
I rest my case.
Can we just eat in peace?
Ma'am Juday.
-Yes?
-You were looking for me?
Yes, please.
Okay.
So…
He called me up,
requesting that you go with him
if he needs you.
Who called?
Who else could it be?
Of course, our guest, Mr. Bhuritparin.
Well, I said you couldn't.
So, we had a compromise.
Retain your night shift
and then I'll release you
on your day shift.
He said he wouldn't press
any charges against you.
Press charges?
But I stopped him
from jumping off the building!
Also, he said
you always get his name wrong.
What is going on, Iris?
You know that we're very strict
with that policy.
I'm sorry, ma'am,
but it's hard to remember his name.
If only we were not understaffed.
Anyway, I'll let it pass.
You take care of Mr. Bhuritparin, okay?
Iris.
Okay, ma'am.
Can you carry my bag?
Can you walk faster?
I'm the one who got sprained here.
Sir, you know what? I can even run!
I can run. You know, I was part
of a sports event in school.
Track and field!
Wait.
-What?
-Is this a Thai store?
Yes, that's a Thai store.
You can go inside.
Is there more?
This one. This one, over here.
SELLS ALL KINDS OF THAI PRODUCTS
What?
You didn't buy anything?
-No.
-Why?
Is there nothing there that you like?
Where are the other Thai stores?
There. There's another Thai store there.
Alright.
I'm hungry. Let's go!
So…
-Mr. Buni.
-Hey.
It's Bhuritparin.
Not Buniparin.
I'm so sorry.
What? Why are you laughing?
Because…
buni…
buni is a Filipino word.
What does buni mean?
Ringworm.
What?
You've been calling me
"ringworm" all this time?
I'm so sorry.
Your name is so hard to remember.
And, you know,
pa rin is also a Filipino word.
It means "still always".
Buni is "ringworm".
Pa rin is "still always".
So, you've been calling me
"ringworm always"!
Your last name is even harder to remember.
Why do Thais have to have such long names?
It's the law.
What law?
The law requires us to come up
with a unique family name.
Yeah.
So, from now on,
you can call me Parin.
-Parin?
-Yes.
That's my nickname.
So, does that mean… we're close now, sir?
'Cause you're letting me call you
by your nickname.
Of course!
Not.
Because you can't pronounce
my original name,
so Parin is fine.
Plus, I don't want to be called
"ringworm always"!
Eat it.
It's so big!
-Hello?
-Parin?
Hi, Leo.
Yeah, I'm fine.
My foot is back on the dance floor.
Yeah, I was just partying
the past two weeks.
Yeah, the sprain is gone.
Yeah.
Yes.
No.
I didn't get any leads.
I went to Thai Street and I asked around,
but I got nothing.
You found her?
Where?
No one’s home!
I paid my rent already!
Check your records!
Hey! Whoever you are, I'm busy!
I'm busy sleeping!
Iris. It's me.
Buni?
Iris, it's me, Parin!
Oh, I meant Parin.
Iris!
Wait. Wait. You wait.
Hang on!
Wait.
Iris, please open the door!
Okay.
Iris!
I thought you were sleeping.
I was sleeping.
But you look like you're going somewhere.
I was sleeping!
This is how I sleep.
I woke up like this.
I need to use your toilet.
May I?
Yeah?
You came here to use…
Oh, shit.
You're here because
you want to use my toilet?
No, of course not!
How did you even get my address?
I asked around.
Asked around?
They just gave my address?
-What?
-Hey, they just gave my address?
Apparently, money can buy happiness.
Seriously?
Okay.
So, why are you here?
I'm hungry.
You're here because you're hungry?
Well, I mean… Can we eat first?
Oh my gosh.
How can you live in this tiny space?
This is so small.
My hotel toilet is even bigger.
Are you trying to insult me?
No, I'm just being honest.
Oh, I'm sorry.
This is all I have, my king.
I was just stating a fact,
that your apartment is so small.
And I can't imagine anyone
living in this tiny space.
Well… this is not an imagination.
This is the reality, my king.
Fine, then.
So, you have to understand
that your king is very hungry right now.
So, let's stop arguing and let's go eat.
Oh, here.
Best Indian food.
-Is Indian food okay with you?
-Yeah.
Okay.
Kunal!
Kunal?
Hello, Iris.
-Hello.
We're going to order.
We'll have six samosas,
four chapatis, two chana, and one dal.
Okay.
Boyfriend?
No.
No, he's my guest at the hotel.
Also her friend.
-Alright.
-Yeah.
Okay, I'll just heat up your samosas
and… get your change as well.
One moment, please.
Okay. Thank you.
Thank you.
What?
I'm not your friend.
What do you call this, then?
Acquaintance.
Definitely more than "acquaintance".
But less than a friend.
Less than a friend
who pays for my samosas and Indian food.
Hey.
You're my guest at the hotel.
Less than a friend
who drags me into my room
whenever I'm drunk.
Okay.
But not BFF.
What's BFF?
Best friends forever.
Best friends forever?
So good.
Okay.
Look.
I know I've been such an asshole
for the past weeks.
Good thing you know!
Can I ask you a favor?
Are my services not enough
to satisfy your favors?
I need to go to Tai O village.
Tai O?
The fishing village?
Yeah.
I’ve been looking for my mom.
That's why I'm here, in Hong Kong.
Your mom is missing?
Yes, and no.
Yes,
because she left us in Thailand.
And no, she's not really missing
because she knew where she was going.
I…
I don't get it.
My friend got leads to where she is.
That's why I'm here, in Hong Kong.
I really need to find her.
Maybe she doesn't want to be found.
Maybe it's over there?
I think I see someone there!
Mom!
Mrs. Pimchan?
Parin?
Come. Let's go inside first.
Mom, this is Iris.
Hi. I’m Iris.
Hello, Mrs. Pimchan.
Hi.
Mom!
Why do you live here?
You have friends in Hong Kong, right?
Why don't you stay with them?
Parin.
Mom, look around.
-Is it safe here?
-Parin.
There are many good hotels out there.
She also works in a hotel.
Parin.
This is my home now.
Pimchan, my love!
Look at what I got!
Ho Yin?
We have guests.
This is Iris.
Hi, Iris.
-Hello.
-Parin's friend.
And Parin, my youngest son.
Parin, this is Ho Yin,
like what he said…
my love.
Tea is also delicious.
Let's try. It smells so good.
Parin.
Look at me, son.
I'm very happy now.
Don't you want to see me happy?
Weren't you happy when you were with us?
No.
I used to be happy.
But people change. I changed too.
I no longer feel happy in our family.
Why, Mom?
I didn't want to marry your dad.
Ho Yin is my first love.
But he was not good enough for my family.
My parents said…
that I would not be happy with Ho Yin.
I remember a burning passion
Once flourished
Oh, your Cantonese is good.
Not really.
-I just have a technique.
-Oh?
I learn Cantonese songs,
so that I can remember
the Cantonese words easier.
Oh, maybe I should memorize Thai songs.
I only know sawasdee khrap,
khaawp-khun khrap,
and phom rak khun.
That's all I know.
So… Mister Ho Yin.
You were saying that you've known
Miss Pimchan since school?
Oh, yes.
The first time I laid my eyes on her,
I knew she was the one.
She's so beautiful.
But then, her parents
had different plans for her.
They lived here, in Hong Kong,
just for two years.
But those two years
were the most memorable years
of my whole life.
They didn't like you?
I couldn't blame them.
I had no work.
I stopped schooling to help my father
in this small town at his small shop.
I knew
they just wanted Pimchan to be happy.
I wanted her to be happy, too.
Wait a minute.
This one is for you.
Oh, I’m very old school.
I only record all of my favorite songs,
even the modern ones, like this song
in the cassette tape.
It gives a different feel.
Nostalgia, memories.
And also, I'm giving you this one too.
I have memorized it already.
And also, Pimchan is with me now.
I don't need this sad song anymore.
When your grandparents said
that I'd be happier with your father,
I believed them.
So, I chose your father.
I was really happy with our family.
But everyone changed.
I changed too.
I always thought about money.
Now,
no amount of luxury bags
or expensive shoes
can ever replace the happiness
that I desire now.
We love you, Mom.
I never said that you all didn't love me.
Let's begin again.
I will tell Dad and…
Why were you looking for me?
Is there any problem with your business?
You will be successful by yourself,
without any help from me.
Failure always happens,
but what's most important
is you know how to stand up again
after the failure.
But can you come back?
Let's go back to our home.
I left home for almost a month.
No one even noticed it.
I was invisible to our family.
It seemed as if I were a person
who lived in an empty house.
I want to live in a real home.
A real home,
where someone knows that I exist.
Please come back, Mom.
You are old enough to make decisions
and old enough to find
true happiness in life.
When you find it,
never let it go.
Never let it go.
Hey, let's go for…
Let's go for the big fish.
-Iris, take it!
-Okay.
-Yeah.
-I get the first serving.
Careful.
-Just a slice.
-Oh, no!
-Get a big portion. Get some.
-Okay.
-Wow.
-This one is for you.
Oh, that's wonderful.
-Have some vegetables.
-Honey, I'll give you a big one. Yeah.
How about you? Do you have vegetables?
-Get some more.
-What's your favorite fish?
-I don't know.
-That one is your favorite fish.
That is good. That's yours.
You don't…
That's why all the fish is for her.
I have never seen you like this, Mom.
You look so happy.
Full of life.
I don't recognize your laughter anymore.
Yeah. She's getting jealous.
Do you see that?
Do you love it?
I understand you now, Mom.
Who am I to take away the existence
of this happiness from your life?
You know, there is something
like this in Thailand.
But it's bigger.
It is called Chao Phraya River.
You know, in the Philippines,
we also have something like this.
The Pasig River.
It is not as clean as this.
I hope it's better now.
Do you miss Thailand?
Yeah.
But the question is really more for you.
Do you miss the Philippines?
Yeah.
I do miss the Philippines.
You know, you're always
a second-class citizen
when you're in other countries.
But I like this place.
I like Hong Kong.
You know, the weather
is similar to the Philippines,
the crowd, the food.
I guess it's…
it’s more my family that I miss.
But can we not talk about my family?
Fine then.
Let's not force ourselves
talking about our family.
-Okay?
-Alright.
You know, I constantly see this view
at daytime and nighttime.
And this is the first time
that I'll be seeing
the transition from day to night.
Sunrise and sunsets.
Twenty-four hours.
Twenty-three hours of day and night.
Thirty minutes of sunrise.
Thirty minutes of sunset.
But sunrise and sunsets
are the most beautiful times of the day.
And I've always missed it.
You know,
sometimes, these little transitions,
these little changes,
they're only a small fraction
of your life.
But sometimes,
these little fractions,
they define the true meaning of life.
I never thought that you were that smart.
I'm smart, hey!
Will you be my… "drinking buddy" tonight?
Sure!
But I bet you'll be drunk right away.
Yeah.
You'll be like…
Excuse me.
Do not underestimate the Filipina!
And don't underestimate the power of Thai!
So? Tara!
-Tara.
-Tara!
-Pai kan.
-Pai kan!
Yeah.
-You say tagay!
-Mhod Kaew!
-Mhod Kaew.
-Yeah.
-Mhod Kaew!
-Tagay!
Mhod Kaew!
We speak in a language
that only our hearts can understand.
Are you okay?
I fell down so many times.
Hey! Are you okay?
What’s the purpose of standing
when you keep on falling?
-You baby…
-No matter where you come from,
you'll always find ways
to understand me, Iris.
It's not aligned.
She never gave up on me.
You’re okay. That's enough.
Fai lok.
You're so heavy!
So weak! My God!
Happiness.
Hey, I cooked adobo
for our beach picnic, okay?
So, don't get too full.
But do you think that it would taste fine
until we reach Peng Chau?
Don't belittle the power of adobo.
It can last for weeks, days,
maybe even months,
if you refrigerate it.
For real?
Here, I can show you. Putang ina mo!
-What?
-It's a… Filipino bad word.
Putang ina mo.
-Putang ina mo!
-Hey!
-What if there's a Filipino here?
Tada!
Turtles.
-So cute, right?
-Do they have names?
I named this one Win.
This one is Sigrid. Richard. Ian.
I don't know the rest.
There are so many, right?
You know what?
We are like…
toys in Disneyland!
Hi! I'm Parin.
Nice to meet you.
This is a drum set!
Hi! My name is Iris.
Nice to meet you…
my king.
Nice to meet you, my queen.
My clown.
So…
You're calling me your clown, huh?
Go look after yourself!
Hey, Iris!
Hello, Cynthia!
-How are you?
-I'm good.
Let me introduce you. This is Parin.
Wow.
How are you?
Hello. Nice to meet you.
Iris, my cafe is for rent now.
Maybe you want to check it out?
Come!
Here.
Maybe this place is waiting for you, Iris.
I really hope so, Cynthia.
I hope the universe allows me
to rent this place.
Nice meeting you, Parin.
Nice meeting you, Cynthia.
-See you.
It's still for rent.
And here.
Here…
there is a small kitchen.
I can cook here.
And then, over here,
I can put maybe a table here, here, here.
Maybe two or three tables.
So people can eat their snacks.
Here?
Let's go!
-Go where?
-Let's go to the Thai store.
And then, after that,
I will take you to the beach.
Thai shop!
Hi!
I'm Parin, and this is Iris.
Hi! Are you Thai?
It has been a long time
since I've met Thai people.
I'm Noi.
What about you, Iris? Are you Thai too?
No. I'm a Filipino.
Oh, you can look around.
If you like anything, let me know later.
Okay.
Crispy silkworms!
I love these! I will buy all of these.
Have you ever tried these?
-No.
-No?
And I don't want to.
I won't take no for an answer.
You should try.
Okay. Here you are.
I love adobo.
I'm happy that you like it.
I can eat this every day.
You know pork buns?
Maybe I can experiment
and make some adobo pork buns.
That's sounds awesome.
Do you have something
like that in the Philippines?
We have siopao,
which is kind of similar to pork buns.
Siopao?
I really love this place.
If you love this place,
you'll love this even more.
-Crispy silkworms?
-Here.
Don't be such a coward.
I'm not a coward!
It's called preference.
And I prefer not to eat your silkworms.
Come on.
Don't you want to experience
a bit of adventure?
You know, every day is already
an adventure as long as I'm with you.
I feel the same.
I told you that it's delicious.
Krob!
A roi mak!
Your Thai is getting better.
I'm a fast learner.
No. I'm a good teacher.
Hey, you see that thing with the red roof?
That's Disneyland!
The happiest place on earth!
Disneyland is like
a dream come true for kids.
You know, when I first went to Hong Kong,
I went straight to Disneyland.
And you're right.
It really is a dream come true.
Not just for kids,
but also for kids at heart.
I just wish I was there with my sister.
Are you still in touch with your sister?
No.
We're…
kind of avoiding each other.
Is she here?
No.
She's in the Philippines.
Or maybe not.
I don't know.
You know, we're…
We kind of lost of communication.
I really like it here.
You know, there is something in this place
that makes life feel… simple,
no pressure.
Just pure fun.
I agree.
Iris.
What if we stay here?
Like, stay here,
on the beach, for longer?
No.
I mean, live here, in Peng Chau.
Are you serious?
Yeah.
I mean, we can rent a place
that you really want,
and we can start a business!
You mean, we're going to live together?
Well…
You know, it's cheaper
to live in one place, right?
But you know, it's really up to you.
You know…
This place has actually been
on my mind for three years now.
Its just that…
Well, my income cannot support
my cost of living here,
and it's far away from work.
Quit your work.
I mean, we can split the rent.
I have the money. I can loan you some.
So, both of us can start
a business together.
I will learn how to make Thai milk tea,
and you'll learn how to make
adobo pork buns.
Minimal investment, simple living.
And the best part is,
we are happy with our choices.
What's the matter?
I'm scared.
I don't think you are scared.
You're just nervous.
I feel the same.
But isn't it exciting?
Okay.
But you pay for 60% of the rent
because you have more money.
Kuripot!
What is it?
What's mine?
It's not a really good fortune.
Come on.
It's not that bad.
Good business.
Good career.
Questionable love life.
And… poor health.
You know, we can reverse the luck.
We can go to another temple
and do it again.
You make your own luck.
I'm okay.
Hey.
Hey, what's wrong?
Are you okay?
You're burning right now. Let's go.
I'm okay.
Just get a taxi and take me back
to my place, please.
Okay.
Iris, I will give you a sponge bath, okay?
Alright.
You know, my mom used to do this
when I was sick,
and it made me feel better.
I hope it does the same to you.
Okay.
Is there anything that you want?
Please stay.
Yeah. Sure.
I'll stay.
I won't leave you, okay?
On this day, everything changed.
I finally found my life’s purpose.
And that is to stay, to take care of you.
Ma'am, I'm just going to Peng Chau.
I'm not going to disappear!
That's still in Hong Kong.
It's still different if you're here.
But…
I'm proud of you.
It's all willpower, ma'am.
The truth is,
this is Parin's idea.
You're no longer addressing him as "sir"?
Are you dating him?
No. We're just business partners.
Business partner, I see.
Iris, you're not in show business,
so stop playing innocent.
But ma'am,
thank you for everything.
I still don't know why I agreed.
As long as it's a good opportunity,
grab it!
But it feels like
it's all happening so fast.
In this day and age,
everything should move fast.
Look at the locals of Hong Kong.
They move fast, they walk fast,
they eat fast, and they talk fast.
Every minute counts.
Every second means money.
That's why I prefer to live in Peng Chau.
It's more slow-paced.
It seems like you have concerns
other than your business.
It seems like how fast your heart beats
for Mr. Parin is your main concern.
Stop it, ma'am!
Excuse me, Iris!
You're not a teenager anymore,
to play hard to get.
Flirt for as long as you can!
Ma'am!
I'm not sure what's happening to me too.
You don't need to figure everything out.
Love is not measured by how long
or short you know the person.
But I hope he won't hurt you.
If he does, just let me know.
I'll have him run over by a dim sum cart!
Thank you for everything, ma'am.
I'm done!
That's nice! What an art!
Whatever.
Oh, you know what?
I forgot. I have something for you.
Ho Yin gave me this cassette.
"Remember", by Terence Lam.
It's a famous Cantopop song
here in Hong Kong.
Cantopop!
So, I've been trying to learn
this Cantopop song
for three years now.
Do you even know how to sing this song?
Do I know how to sing this song?
I can even dance!
-Dance?
-Yes.
-Show me.
-Okay.
-You press play for me, okay?
You have to press it.
Ready?
Please remember that we were lost
At some point
Please remember the love that still exists
Please remember to hold onto your feelings
As you pass into the crowd
I remember that all will clear up
With the rain
Her laughter.
Her touch.
Her voice.
In a city where everyone’s
racing against time,
you are my unexpected pause.
Iris.
Are you okay with this?
With what?
Living together.
Yes. I'm okay with it.
But I don't know if you're okay with it.
I'm definitely okay with this.
You know, it's just that…
I don't know your culture in your country.
Yeah.
They will gossip.
They will curse me.
They will judge me.
They will stone me to death!
Really?
What the hell?
It's a joke!
So funny.
You…
How about you? How about your country?
You know, it's very hard in my country.
If they see me with someone,
especially a girl that I'm not related to,
they will follow me and kidnap that girl.
And they will throw you
in a deep pit full of live,
big, slimy silkworms.
And you will only have two choices
in your life.
To be eaten
by those silkworms to death or eat them.
Seriously?
It's a joke!
I think you're watching too much drama!
But you know,
you should try those live silkworms.
It tastes good though.
Iris.
What if we fail?
So what?
What do you mean by "so what"?
If we fail, then we fail.
And we just rest,
think, recharge, and then try again.
You are so positive in everything.
And you're so negative in everything.
You know what?
There's another way
not to be fed to the worms.
What?
Like…
Maybe we…
could have… a relationship.
No! I mean…
We can be BFFs!
BFFs?
Yeah.
I don't like BFF.
What do you want, then?
I want BF!
-Good night.
-What? BF?
Best friend? Iris, wake up!
Best friend only?
Iris.
BF.
Best friend only.
No forever?
Just a little more.
And then…
Shucks.
It seems like…
I think this is it.
Milk.
Alright!
Are you ready?
I'm ready.
-We can do this!
-Yes!
-Okay.
-Let's go!
You first.
-Me?
-Yeah.
Okay.
It actually tastes good.
But this one has, like,
a stronger tea flavor.
I like it!
It's actually like my dad's recipe.
Then my mom tweaked it
and made the tea stronger.
That's cute.
Yeah. They were cute…
when they were together.
Hey! It's your turn!
It's your turn to try it!
What?
You fed me the paper!
That's part of it!
You have to eat the paper first.
It's edible?
So, how was it?
Good.
So good!
Are you ready?
Two more days before the show starts.
I have a good feeling
that our Fai Lok is going to be a hit!
You know, my Thai milk tea
and your adobo pork buns,
it's going to be great!
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
Parin.
Is it okay if I go to the city tomorrow?
Yeah, sure. I'll go with you.
No. I…
Is it okay if I go alone?
Yeah.
No problem.
Do you need any help?
No.
Everything's fine.
I just need to go to the doctor.
Oh.
Is that about your allergies and…
Yes.
But I already had it checked,
and I just have to get
the results tomorrow.
Okay.
I hope it's nothing serious.
I really want to go with you.
I'm worried about you.
No.
Everything's fine.
You know, you have to be here
and get ready for showtime!
Right?
Alright.
Now the king follows the clown.
Parin!
Hi!
Gub ma laew ka!
Your Thai is getting better.
Hi. How are you?
What's this?
Birds?
What are we going to name these two?
I know. I know!
We'll name her Sawasdee.
And we'll call him Mabuhay.
Yeah?
It's good?
Mabuhay!
Kumusta kayo?
Baliw!
Sawasdee!
Sawasdee, Mabuhay!
How are you? Are you alright?
Hi.
I don't know what happened.
It must be the love birds.
It must be love.
It must be the birds.
Even though I don’t know
what you’re going through,
I know
I need to be here for you.
Iris.
Huwag malungkot.
Masaya lang.
Iris.
You know, if you're pressured
in opening Fai Lok,
we can delay it.
Just take it easy.
No.
Let's do it now.
Do it now?
No, not now. Can we do it tomorrow?
Because your more than an acquaintance,
less than a friend,
would love to cuddle more.
Kilig ka?
You know,
I think we're on the next level now.
More than a friend but less than a lover.
I think I have a better idea.
What if we speed things up
and we take it
to the next, next level?
Like… BFF.
Best friend forever.
Boyfriend forever.
No.
I mean, not forever.
We can be something else.
Like…
HF.
Or…
husband forever.
Never mind.
But if you don't like it,
you don't want it,
we'll be something else.
PF.
Not professional fee.
But…
partner forever.
It could be in business or, even better,
like, monkey business, you know?
And… we can--
You don't like it?
Ma-sa-rap.
Once the story ends
We must bid farewell in person
Farewell to those inns
We braved storms together
Like migratory birds landing on the lake
Faces leaving
Once they fly away
It's hard to meet again
The August evening breeze
Blows softly, so peaceful
Shaking off those golden fragments
Yellow leaves fill the sky
Leaves flutter, each on its own path
Seen along the way
Hints were hidden from the start
Please remember who was here for a moment
Please remember
The love that once existed…
Parin?
Please remember, hold on to the feeling…
Thank you.
Enjoy.
You can do this.
I believe in you.
Just look straight. Like this, okay?
-Don't look down.
-Are you sure?
Parin!
Yes?
-Go!
-Push!
Go!
Okay--
I fell.
It’s fine.
I fell again.
Excuse me.
I’ve fallen so many times.
Everything is fine.
What happened?
You're almost there. You got it! Come on!
But unexpectedly falling for you
is pure happiness.
They're calling you.
Yeah.
Yes.
How was it?
Was it good?
-Come here!
-Come on!
Finally, I’ve achieved
a sense of balance in my life.
-Look straight! Yes!
-I'm going straight!
-Yes!
We can do this.
We can do this together, Iris.
You know, my favorite part of the song is,
"I am grateful for the fleeting bloom
of the epiphyllum flower.
That memory, in the end, is still love."
And do you know what an epiphyllum is?
No.
It's here.
What?
Open it.
What’s this?
Is this an epiphyllum flower?
Yeah.
So beautiful, but so wilted.
Hey, do you know what?
This is so precious, very expensive,
and very rare.
You know,
epiphyllum flowers are also called
"Queen of the Night".
They bloom only at night.
And you
are also my Queen of the Night.
Every night when I get drunk,
you always come to rescue me.
Hey, I thought I was your clown?
Queen of clowns.
You know, this…
only blooms at night,
but they wilt before dawn.
It's a sign that
good things never last.
And you know what?
What?
Good things may come to an end…
but new good things
will arise from endings.
I didn't know you were that smart.
I'm smart!
Parin?
I…
I need to go back to the Philippines.
Really?
When?
On the 10th.
That's next week, right?
Yeah, sure.
When are you coming back?
On the 10th of next month.
One month?
Yes.
Okay.
Is there anything
that I can help you with?
Or do you want me to go
with you to the Philippines?
No.
I just want to sort things out
with my family.
I understand.
But maybe… you need your BFF?
No.
I…
I… I don't want to be
with my BFF for this one.
I want to do this alone.
Okay.
Don't worry, it's fine. Really.
It's just…
I'm going to miss you so much.
I'll miss you too.
I will always wait for you
at the port area.
It's okay.
That's the last of our adobo buns.
Thank you very much.
Next time, make more.
You should make more adobo buns.
Bye!
Hi, Mr. Bhuritparin. Hi.
Hi.
I'm so sorry for bothering you.
I just…
I just don't know what to do.
I waited at the port area in Peng Chau,
but she never came back.
She was blocking my calls.
She's just leaving me voice messages.
I'm just hoping that
she mentioned something to you
before she left.
I really want to help you, but…
I was also trying to call her,
and I already asked around about her.
But it's so hard to look for her.
Sir?
Sir, are you okay?
I just remembered something.
Maybe…
she doesn't want to be found.
Parin? I’ll take care of them.
Thank you.
Here's the key to your new place.
And here's the key to…
our Fai Lok.
Mabuhay!
Sawasdee?
Mabuhay.
Sawasdee!
Hello?
Thea?
Yes. Who is this?
Thea, it's Iris.
Sister?
Is there really no other way?
I hope you'll fulfill my wish.
Of course, I will.
But…
don't you want to talk to him anymore?
Or even say your goodbyes properly?
It's because…
I don't want…
I don't want him to see me this way.
Weak.
You know, weak-willed.
I understand.
But this hurts for him.
And it hurts me, too.
It pains me a lot.
But it's better for him
to remember me
the way he first met me.
Until the end.
Crazy, right?
Love knows no time.
In that short moment
that we were together,
I loved him.
I love him.
Don't you want to seek
a third medical opinion?
How about that?
Thea.
I just want to spend my remaining days,
weeks,
and months that I still have
with you.
Let's travel together.
Anywhere here in the Philippines.
I don't want us to spend
my remaining days in the hospital.
Hey.
Enough of that.
Thea,
what matters
is you choose.
You choose what makes you happy.
Me?
I became happy.
I'm still happy.
Because I choose to be happy.
Hi, Parin.
I am the sister of Iris.
Where is she?
I'm begging you now.
Tell me now!
Where is she?
Where is she?!
Please.
She's dead.
She's gone.
She was sick for months.
She wanted to do her treatment
in the Philippines,
but it was too late.
She was very hopeful.
She didn't want to give up.
She didn't want to give up because of you.
She didn't want to give up on life.
But life betrayed her.
And now, there's nothing we can do.
Parin.
Iris wanted me to tell you…
she's so sorry.
She didn't want you to see her in pain
or weak.
She wanted you to remember her
as someone who's strong.
She wanted you to remember
all your good memories together.
You know,
she was very thankful
that you came into her life.
You know, you're the…
You're the best thing
that's ever happened to her.
She loves you so much.
You know, I've actually
never seen her that happy.
Except for when she was telling me
about your mini adventures.
Here.
You can reach me here.
I wrote down my number.
I'm going back to the Philippines
within the next two days.
If you're free,
maybe we can, you know,
celebrate her life…
by reminiscing all the good memories
we had with her.
Mabuhay left.
Sawasdee left.
My mom left.
And…
you left me, Iris.
Good things never last.
Happiness never lasts.
Yes, that's a Thai store.
You can go inside.
Parin! Do you need anything?
Hello, Parin.
Hi!
Yes, I got my results now and…
everything's fine.
There's nothing to worry about.
Yeah.
I’m just taking a stroll
around the city, okay?
I'll see you later.
Bye!
Hey there. Check out this nice parrot!
Super nice! Buy it!
This is a really good one!
Lots of Filipinos buy love birds
because it's easy to take care of them.
Hi. How are you?
Please be patient, okay?
I'll be back on the 10th.
I'll see you at the port?
Please don't be mad at me.
I miss you too.
I want to be with you as soon as I can.
We'll eat your grilled fish together.
Okay?
Don't look for me.
Don't call me.
And don't wait for me.
Do it for me.
Please.
I want you to be happy.
Fai Lok. Fai Lok.
Please look for happiness,
even without me.
Please remember
The love that once
Existed
I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry, Parin.
Ruk khun, tee ruk.
It's still broken.
I cannot fix what is broken.
But you taught me that happiness
is not the absence of brokenness.
True happiness lies
in creating joy in the present moment.
Thank you for the memories, Iris.
My fai lok.
Hi, Thea.
Hi!
Thank you.
Your sister once bought me this.
She actually bought me a lot.
Thai food from Thai Street.
Samosas from Mirador Mansion.
Dim sum.
She taught me how to ride a bike.
Adobo.
Mabuhay.
Fai Lok. Fai Lok.
Happiness.
She made me smile.
She made me cry.
Cing gei dak
Waan yau yat fan oi
Cyun joi
"Please remember
our love still exist."
I miss her.
I miss her, too.
Good things in life
never last.
But great memories…
they remain forever.
Look.
They're starting to turn on
the lights now!
Wow.
Beautiful sunset.
Sunrise and sunsets.
Twenty-four hours.
Twenty-three hours of day and night.
And 30 minutes of sunrise.
Thirty minutes of sunsets.
But sunrise and sunsets
are the most beautiful time of the day.
I never thought of it that way.
Sometimes, these little transitions,
little changes,
may only be a small fraction of your life.
But these little fractions
can define the true meaning of life.
Will you be my drinking buddy tonight?
Yeah. Yeah. Sure!
Well, just a few drinks,
you'll be drunk right away.
Never underestimate
the power of the Filipina.
the power of the Thai too.
Tara!
Pai kan!
What's pai kan?
Let's go!
-Pai kan!
Pai kan!
-Cheers!
Mhod kaew!
-What?
-Mhod kaew.
-Yeah.
Tagay!
-Tagay!
-Later, you say "tagay"!
Tagay!