- Welcome.
- Hi.
The sensation locked within me
was unleashed
the day I first got my ears pierced.
Are you worried it will hurt?
It gave me...
sexual arousal.
- Is your neck okay?
- Yes.
I couldn't hold back the feeling
no matter how hard I tried.
I even love the sound of the razor
grazing my chin.
I feel aroused
whenever my ears are stimulated.
Am I abnormal?
You're all done.
PLAY BOOKS
Our listener says he is aroused
whenever his ears are touched.
He's worried that he may be abnormal.
Being aroused easily
should be considered a blessing,
but it could be a problem
if you're too sensitive.
Right.
Many people are concerned about
not being easily turned on,
but there are those who find sex difficult
because it tickles.
Mr. Kang, then could there be a way
to lower one's sensitivity?
I'm not a doctor...
but there isn't a way
to do that artificially.
But in one case, it can be done.
How?
By getting older.
As you age, your sense of touch dulls.
So it happens naturally with age.
That's right.
There's also a thing called
the spotlight effect.
It refers to how some people
can be more self-conscious than others.
Rather than their erogenous zones,
they might be more concerned
with how others think of them.
What you're suggesting is
that they change the way they think.
They should be more brazen.
I guess you're right.
Erogenous zones can be vague
since they differ from person to person.
But since we all at least have one,
there's no need for you
to feel singled out because of it.
You can be aroused
by touching any part of your body.
What's your erogenous zone, then?
Mine?
My lips.
I see.
What's yours?
Mine is...
HIT THE SPOT
EPISODE 6. THE MOOD THAT DAY
Mr. Kang filled in
as our special guest today.
What was it like to join us?
Most of my readers are women,
so it was a pleasure
to hear their stories somewhat up close.
When will we do it again?
Sorry?
The podcast.
When will we get to do it again?
I had a blast.
The podcast?
Have me over again sometime soon.
Is that a promise?
Sure.
That'll be all for today's Hit the Spot.
Next week, DJ Min will be back.
Thank you.
My gosh.
Mr. Kang, you should quit being an advisor
and host the show instead.
That was some sound advice.
Tell me about it.
No wonder he's an expert.
Mr. Kang, you're the best.
Thanks.
What do you say
to a permanent spot on the show?
I'm not interested.
This one time was enough.
It was fun.
What a bummer.
Do you have any plans today?
How about some tea?
Sounds good.
Enjoy your conversation, then.
I have some stuff to go over.
I see.
Yi-kyung, shall we?
- Me too?
- That's right.
I wanted to join them for tea.
Beat it.
- Just five minutes.
- It's fine. Go.
- It'll be my treat.
- Leave.
She just can't take a hint.
Mr. Kang, a signing event
for your book is coming up.
Would you be up for a brief AMA session?
- What do you say?
- At the signing?
Yes.
I really hope you'll agree to it.
PLAY BOOKS
How did the meeting go?
Were you waiting for me?
Of course.
Why? Did you need something?
It's because we're special friends.
That being said,
when will we do it again?
The podcast?
No, not that.
You never gave me an answer.
Do I look that easy?
I never said that.
You're the one
who first said that we're friends.
I take it that you want
a different kind of friendship.
Anyway, call me once you have your answer.
Have a pleasant night, then.
How are you feeling?
Can't you tell?
You seem good.
Have your incision disinfected
before you go.
You want me to show you my butt again?
No, not to me.
To the doctor you first consulted.
Why are you angry with me?
Did I do something wrong?
I honestly don't know
why I'm mad at you either.
What's this?
Seaweed soup. It's good for your bowels.
Eating is key to a speedy recovery.
Recovery will take about two weeks.
So lay off the sex and alcohol until then
and call me in two weeks' time.
I'll get you my documents again.
SEAWEED SOUP
Unbelievable.
Kang In-chan has
250,000 followers on social media.
He's pretty much a celebrity.
And you asked him to be your sex partner?
Yes.
Why? Don't celebrities have sex?
They do, and they should.
You're all grown up now.
So? What did he say?
He asked if he looked easy.
Is that his way of saying that
no one has suggested that to him before?
But that wasn't why I asked him.
Wait. Maybe it is.
He doesn't seem easy to me.
But maybe he seemed that way to you.
It's ready. Let's eat.
What if you end up dating him?
Come on. Are you nuts?
I won't ever date him.
It'll be strictly sex.
Right. Well, I'm proud of you,
but let's not talk about sex
while I practice abstinence for two weeks.
Hey, dig in while it's hot.
And no leftovers.
But I don't want to overeat.
If a lot goes in, a lot must come out.
But you have to eat to recover.
Seaweed soup. It's good for your bowels.
Eating is key to a speedy recovery.
That's what he said.
Who?
It's nothing.
Do you know how much it hurts to poop
after a hemorrhoidectomy?
I looked it up online.
They say pooping on an empty stomach
hurts even more.
Here.
My heart skipped a beat just now.
- Out of the blue?
- Yes.
You know I'm a sucker for people
who care for me when I'm sick.
I do.
Now, eat up.
Good girl.
Tell me.
Do doctors normally wipe the sweat
off their patients?
I'm not sure.
It'd make sense
if you were sweating like a pig.
Do they tuck you in as well?
What's with your doctor?
I quite like this clinic.
He also dozed off beside me
while I was asleep.
Could he have fallen for you?
Does it hurt a lot?
I'll give you an epidural.
I'm sorry I keep leaving you
on your own.
Have you had an epidural injection before?
It makes you feel funny.
Something happened
at the clinic, didn't it?
No.
I'm just saying.
PSYCHOLOGY FOR HER, A TALK ABOUT SEX
KANG IN-CHAN'S BOOK SIGNING EVENT
- What's your name?
- It's Kim Young-ju.
Ms. Kim Young-ju.
TO. MS. KIM YOUNG-JU
I have a job interview lined up.
Could you wish me luck?
Sure.
Ms. Kim, everything will work out.
Even if it doesn't work out this time,
it eventually will.
Good luck.
- Thank you.
- The pleasure's mine.
- Good luck, Mr. Kang.
- Good luck.
May I have your name?
It's Son Hee-jae.
Are you stalking me now?
Does it look that way?
TO. SON HEE-JAE
A little, I guess.
I never thought you were easy.
I know that I'm acting like a lunatic.
But...
there's something
I'm desperately looking for.
Can't you help me just this once?
Next.
Hello, thank you for coming.
THEN BUY ME A DRINK
- What's your name?
- It's Im Soo-yeon.
- Ms. Im Soo-yeon?
- Yes.
88 BIG GULPS
- Over here.
- It's been so long!
What do you think about this place?
I like the atmosphere.
I told you this place was great.
The whelk soup here is to die for.
How does soju sound?
I'm in.
Ma'am, one whelk soup
and a bottle of soju, please.
- They will be right out.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
- Enjoy.
- Sure.
I thought you didn't drink
with people you weren't comfortable with?
So? What is it that you're looking for?
An orgasm.
I want to experience it
with another person.
Why me, though?
That's...
Well...
Because I'm easy?
Come on. That's not it.
For some reason,
it feels like I could tell you anything.
I feel somewhat safe.
Maybe it's because you're a psychologist.
A psychologist?
Then promise me one thing.
What is it?
You have to be honest with yourself.
And also with me.
Then it's a yes, right?
You can't take it back.
On one condition, though.
Fire away.
I'm looking for something as well.
And what's that?
I'll tell you later.
Fine.
Whatever it is, I'll help you find it.
Let's start by being friends first.
When are we going to do it, then?
Hold your horses.
There's an order to these things.
Drink to it?
- Let's.
- Cheers.
JAE-WOOK
No.
LEE HAE-JUN
LEE JUN-YOUNG
No way.
I'm sorry I keep leaving you
on your own.
CHA WOO-JAE
I must be out of my mind.
Recovery will take about two weeks.
So lay off the sex and alcohol until then
and call me in two weeks' time.
I'll get you my documents again.
I'm so bored.
Cheers.
What should I do now?
What should we try first?
HOW ABOUT WE GO STEADY?
You said your erogenous zone
was your lips, right?
You'll rip the book!
Nice!
Hold on.
Mr. Kang.
We're having sex if I beat you, okay?
Why are you so good at this?
Why can't I hit anything?
Seriously?
Lights on or off?
One, two, three.
On.
Off!
Deeper or faster? One, two, three.
- Deeper!
Cheers.
What is it that you're looking for?
Ancient treasure?
There's nothing here.
Have faith in me, will you?
What are you even looking for?
My legs are killing me.
Maybe I should run away from home.
You brat. You shouldn't say
such things so lightly.
THE 12 FELINE TROUBLEMAKERS
Do you even know what that means?
Dad, you're always on my case.
Do you want one?
SEAWEED SOUP WITH BEEF
PUMPKIN PORRIDGE
Seaweed soup. It's good for your bowels.
Eating is key to a speedy recovery.
Oh, hot! Darn it.
Have you completely lost it?
CHA WOO-JAE
How's your recovery coming along?
Why did you come here at this hour?
Are you not feeling well?
I hurt myself.
You did well coming here.
Come in. I'll patch you up.
You asked me how I was doing.
Why would you text me that?
Because I was curious.
Do you do this to all your patients?
Give them seaweed soup,
wipe away their sweat,
and nurse them all night?
Is that what you normally do?
Why are you so upset?
Why are you doing this to me
when I'm so vulnerable?
You can't do that. It's not fair.
Let me treat this burn first.
I wanted to find out...
why I kept imagining kissing him...
and not having sex with him.
I get it now.
I now know...
that I've...
fallen for him.
Luckily, the burn isn't severe.
You asked me if I was this nice
to all my patients.
I'm rather well known
for being considerate,
but I don't treat just anyone
free of charge like now.
All done.
You weren't kidding about us
being friends.
I can't stand
not getting a bang for my buck.
So?
Did you find what you were looking for?
I think I did.
Thanks to you.
What was it?
Do you want to know?
You don't have to tell me
if you don't want to.
It's my turn, then.
Do you like music?
It's been a while
since my heart raced like this.
A song that I hadn't heard before
tickled my ears.
The smell of winter, sweet wine...
and this man who said his heart raced
as he sat next to me.
Just as all these sensations
began to feel so alien...
my body began to react.
What I was aroused by...
was the mood.
I...
want to kiss you.
EPILOGUE
Are we still not there yet?
We're almost there.
It's so pretty!
It was worth the hike.
I found it.
The reason for me to fall in love again.