Is Mr. Ye...
going to announce his relationship with Han Hui?
Mr. Ye has never held a press conference...
because of personal matters.
Those who came are all entertainment reporters.
I'm sure it's not about work.
- Looks like there's a big scoop. - Yes.
Mr. Ye is here.
- Mr. Ye. - Mr. Ye.
Mr. Ye, are you in a relationship with Han Hui?
Mr. Ye, what's your relationship with Han Hui?
- Please tell us, Mr. Ye.
- This press conference...
is called on to clarify one thing.
So far,
all the rumors about my relationship...
are false.
So please stop spreading false rumors.
I'd also like the rumor-monger to stop.
Stop speculating.
Else,
Anning Culture...
will send a lawyer's letter.
If one day, I, Ye Fei Mo, am in a relationship,
I will announce it to everyone.
Thank you.
- Mr. Ye! - Wait, Mr. Ye!
Come and see.
Look, it's Han Hui.
- Come and see. - Will they fight?
Come and see. What do you think?
Mr. Ye has clarified.
What is going on?
What is happening?
It's your first time playing the female lead.
You must be excited.
Han Hui.
It's Mr. Ye.
So please stop spreading false rumors.
I'd also like the rumor-monger to stop.
Mr. Ye never cared about scandals before.
So many people have taken advantage of his fame,
but he never clarified anything.
What's going on?
Han Hui.
Calm down.
You're in public.
Give them two more racks later.
And reinforce the fence for safety.
- Okay. - Go.
Buddy.
I have a question.
- Who is Wen Xiao Nuan? - Wen Xiao Nuan?
Up there.
She's Wen Xiao Nuan.
So this is my cousin-in-law.
Beautiful.
- Aren't you... - No, I'm not.
Xiao Nuan, I'll get you some water.
So please stop spreading false rumors.
If one day, I, Ye Fei Mo, am in a relationship,
I will announce it to everyone.
- Thank you. - Mr. Ye.
- Mr. Ye! - Wait, Mr. Ye!
What's up? I'm on set.
You're on set?
Don't speak without thinking.
Do you hear me?
You mean, I can't call her my cousin-in-law?
Go home.
I'm filming with my cousin-in-law.
Her acting is good.
I'm looking forward to acting with her.
I'm warning you.
Don't cause trouble.
Okay.
Mr. Ye, it's time for the meeting.
I am alone and have no one to rely on.
I wonder what year it is.
When I...
When I look at the clouds, I don't see you.
Who can I tell my troubles to?
Who should I tell my troubles to?
Xiao Nuan.
I was just listening.
There's a line of yours that needs a little more meaning.
Why is she here?
This is it.
I wonder...
what year it is.
- Han Hui! - What happened?
Call an ambulance!
- Go! Call an ambulance! - Xiao Nuan!
I'm sorry. I didn't do it on purpose.
- What happened? - I'm sorry.
Get out of the way.
Who is this?
Who are you?
It's me.
Xiao Bai?
Xiao Bai!
- Get out of the way! - Han Hui.
Xiao Nuan.
Be careful.
Xiao Bai.
Here, Xiao Bai.
- Xiao Bai. - Xiao Bai.
Mr. Ye.
(Wen Xiao Nuan gets injured on set)
(Mo Xiao Bai shows up at "Blue Galaxy")
(Emergency)
Mr. Ye.
What's the situation?
The doctor is examining her.
Zhou Xiao Jing.
What are you doing?
Did you hire the assistant for nothing?
Sorry, Mr. Ye.
- It's my fault. - Why are you yelling?
It's not something in her control.
There were too many people at the scene.
It's inevitable that she'd lose focus.
No one wanted any accidents.
(Mr. Gao)
- Hello, Mr. Gao. - Xiao Jing.
News about Mo Xiao Bai taking Wen Xiao Nuan to the hospital...
on the headlines.
It's all over the Internet.
Mr. Gao, please give me a minute.
Mr. Ye, Mr. Gao is on the phone.
Rumors about Xiao Nuan are spreading.
I suggest the PR Department to issue a press release...
stating that Xiao Nuan was injured while filming...
and announce that Mo Xiao Bai is the male lead of "Blue Galaxy".
He was just kind enough to take Xiao Nuan to the hospital.
We can prevent the netizens from making assumptions...
or creating a bigger issue.
Mr. Ye, what do you think?
Go take care of it.
- Okay. - Xiao Jing.
Wen Xiao Nuan is an S-class artist.
To me...
To Anning,
she's an important talent resource.
She's very important.
Mr. Gao.
Issue a press release right away.
Fei Mo.
I'll get going too to avoid suspicion.
I'll come back to see Xiao Nuan after things have calmed down.
Don't go out without my permission.
Okay.
At least I can have tea with Aunt.
Don't be photographed by reporters.
Okay.
Han Hui, will they find out that it was us?
What are you afraid of?
Everyone knows...
that it was just an accident.
What should we do now?
The lead actress is injured.
We can't let the crew to wait for her and burn the money.
It's fate that let Han Hui get this role.
Get in.
Let's go to the hospital and see our poor heroine.
Luckily, we were cautious...
and came straight from the parking lot.
I didn't expect so many reporters to be here.
They're all here for Mo Xiao Bai.
Wen Xiao Nuan is just a rookie.
She doesn't have that much influence.
What's wrong, Han Hui?
Mr. Ye, Xiao Jing.
Director.
The reporters are outside the hospital.
They're waiting for an interview.
I've sent people to disperse them.
But they said they're waiting to write the news.
Mr. Ye, I'll handle it.
It's better for me to handle it.
Okay, please wait.
Please wait. Director Li will come out...
and give everyone an explanation.
Director Li will be here soon.
Step back.
Is Wen Xiao Nuan seriously injured?
Will it affect the filming of "Blue Galaxy"?
Is it true that Mo Xiao Bai is the male lead of "Blue Galaxy"?
Will "Blue Galaxy" change its female lead?
During the casting process, Han Hui was a popular choice.
Will you consider Han Hui?
As the director of "Blue Galaxy",
I've never received any notification about the casting change.
Director Li, why was Mo Xiao Bai on set?
What's his relationship with Wen Xiao Nuan?
- Director Li. - They're just co-workers.
They must be in a relationship.
This isn't the right place for this makeup.
The color of the lips is too strong.
Why didn't you remind me?
How about this?
Get me some gauze.
Okay.
Fei Mo.
How's Wen Xiao Nuan?
Is she badly hurt?
She's still in the emergency room.
There were too many people on set.
It was so chaotic.
Everyone rushed up to me.
I was so scared.
If it weren't for Linda,
I too would've...
No wonder you were in such a hurry.
If you didn't show up,
your wound would've already healed.
Ms. Han.
You're a good actress.
So...
you've already decided that I did it.
How did Wen Xiao Nuan get hurt?
You know it best.
I'm warning you.
Stay away from her.
Don't use your tricks on her.
You've already decided that it was me.
There's nothing I can say.
But Fei Mo...
Fei Mo.
Do you remember how much you trusted me back then?
But now, we...
Are you Wen Xiao Nuan's family?
Please pay the bill.
From now on,
I don't want to hear any more of the past.
You...
don't want to know what I'm capable of.
Whether you believe me or not,
it's up to you.
I really didn't do it on purpose.
Han Hui.
No one...
can take away what's mine from me.
Director Li, why was Mo Xiao Bai on set?
What's his relationship with Wen Xiao Nuan?
They're just co-workers.
How can they just be co-workers?
That's right. They were so intimate.
Are they in a relationship?
Xiao Tian, have the flowers arrived?
Almost, Mr. Jiang.
Free up your afternoon.
Okay.
(Jiang Hao)
Mr. Jiang.
I was just on my way to see you to report to you in person...
about the situation of "Blue Galaxy".
You let Ye Fei Mo lead you by the nose.
Aurora Film couldn't even get a finger in the door.
And you want to report to me in person?
Report what?
Report how incompetent you are?
Li Can publicly admitted...
that Mo Xiao Bai is the male lead.
Why didn't you get any advance information?
Also, have you signed Han Hui?
I'm preparing the documents.
Jiang Fang.
I made you Aurora Film's vice president...
for Ling Er's sake.
I'm only giving you this chance...
because I heard you're a capable person.
I can give you this position,
but I can also give it to someone else.
Mr. Jiang, the flowers are here.
Forget the flowers.
Take the script to Linda.
Ask her what Han Hui thinks.
Okay.
Mr. Jiang, what about this afternoon?
- Proceed as usual. - Okay.
Con Panna plus two shots of espresso.
You still remember.
Xiao Jing.
Are you worried...
that Wen Xiao Nuan will get involved with Fei Mo?
No.
We've known each other for so long.
When have you ever been able to fool me?
If you're really worried about this,
why did you send Wen Xiao Nuan...
to Fei Mo back then?
Just because she looked like Han Hui back then?
I admit.
When I signed Wen Xiao Nuan,
it was because she looks like Han Hui back then.
But now, whatever happens between Wen Xiao Nuan and Mr. Ye...
is beyond my control.
Don't you think it's like drinking poison to quench your thirst?
So until I'm sure...
that Mr. Ye isn't using Wen Xiao Nuan...
as a substitute for Han Hui,
I don't dare to bet on anything.
What about you?
You're the one who trained Han Hui.
Now you're going to train Wen Xiao Nuan...
to be the next Han Hui.
To you,
isn't she also a substitute for Han Hui?
Wen Xiao Nuan and Han Hui are different.
You also know they're different.
So how can you be so sure...
that this medicine called Wen Xiao Nuan...
can't cure Fei Mo's mental illness?
Perhaps Fei Mo won't change...
for Wen Xiao Nuan.
Just like...
how you refuse to believe...
that I'd change for you.
The patient is awake.
Please take a look at her.
Okay.
Xiao Jing!
Where's my sister? How is she?
She's awake. Go see her.
How's my sister?
- Nuan Nuan. - Xiao Nuan.
- You're awake, Xiao Nuan.
- You're awake.
Who are you looking for?
I'm not looking for anyone.
Xiao Nuan, are you looking for your husband?
Is it that handsome guy?
Where's my handsome brother-in-law?
Xiao Kai, stop talking nonsense.
He's in the doctor's office.
He'll be here soon.
Do you want to sit up?
Slowly.
Can you do it?
Is this okay?
Xiao Jing.
When can I be discharged?
I'm afraid...
I'll delay the filming.
Xiao Jing, you're injured.
Why are you worried about other things?
Your health is the most important.
It's okay.
I can do it.
You can't.
My handsome brother-in-law.
Fei Mo, do you still remember me?
I'm her younger brother, Wen Kai.
Do you remember me?
Xiao Kai, stop it.
Fei Mo.
Go.
All the best.
Xiao Kai.
I'll get his autograph for you when he comes back.
Sure.
Handsome, right?
- Aunt. - Handsome guy.
You're back.
- You look good. - Aunt.
Just half a year and you've gotten prettier.
- Have I? - You look younger.
Really?
If we go out for a walk,
everyone will think we're dating.
All right.
You're such a sweet talker.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
Let's go inside.
So I rejected the other jobs...
and came back.
That's how he coaxed you to come back to ac?
Tell me about it.
For his little girlfriend, Wen Xiao Nuan,
I came back from abroad to act.
And this is how he treats me.
He won't let me go out...
or get photographed by the reporters.
I really don't know how she puts up with him.
Wen Xiao Nuan?
I wonder when Fei Mo will pursue her successfully.
They're not official?
You know his temper.
Making him say nice things...
is harder than climbing to the sky.
However,
I quite like Wen Xiao Nuan.
If things work out between them,
I'd be happy to see it happen.
You're praising her.
She must be nice.
A hero rescuing a damsel in distress.
What a great opportunity.
He didn't make it in time.
Fei Mo? Forget it.
It's good enough that he didn't make her angry.
That reminds me.
Listen.
You have to help him.
No problem. Leave it to me.
- Okay. - Aunt, have some tea.
It's a deal then.
- It's a deal. - Okay.
You're not going anywhere until the splint is removed.
Mr. Ye, are you here to see me?
I'm here to see an uncle.
I'm only seeing you in passing.
I want some of Jia Yi's soup.
It's hot. So hot.
Blow on it.
I'm talking about the soup.
It's hot.
Then...
are you still going to drink it?
I want to go back to the set soon.
No.
The doctor said you can't go anywhere.
You have to stay here and recuperate.
How do you know what the doctor said?
Aren't you only seeing me in passing?
In short, you're not going anywhere.
You can only stay here and recuperate.
Don't think too much.
What are you so happy about?
Nothing.
Nothing?
Come on, slowly.
Jia Yi.
Say.
Does he like me...
a little bit?
You like him.
I don't like him.
Why would I like him?
He's sharp-tongued and picky.
He's a monster and a pervert.
No, he's not that kind of person.
He's not?
Jia Yi, you've gone bad.
Okay. Easy now.
Don't hurt yourself.
Silly girl.
Nuan Nuan, take care.
I'm leaving.
Xiao Nuan.
Why are you here?
Jia Yi just left.
I'm just here to visit you.
Just to visit me?
Yes.
But since Jia Yi just left,
I can only talk to these fruits.
No, Xiao Nuan.
I'm sorry.
Xiao Nuan.
I really don't know what to do.
I went to see Jia Yi.
She's been cold to me.
I didn't want to upset her,
so I stopped bothering her.
She's really mad this time.
But I swear. I'm serious about her.
Can you help me?
Jia Yi is a kind girl.
She trusts people easily.
She's also very smart.
She knew everything about you, but she didn't expose you...
and waited for you to confess.
I helped you hide it from her...
because I thought...
she was happy during that time.
I also hoped that someone...
could take her out of the past...
and start over.
We all saw...
what you've done for her.
I believe that you truly love her.
Actually, that day,
what you said at the cafe...
might have just been for fun.
You might think it's a bit silly...
that things turned out this way.
But I know her too well.
Because of what she's been through,
she has become less confident.
She's afraid she's not that important to you.
She's afraid she'll get hurt again.
So if you really love her,
when she takes a step back,
you have to take one more step forward.
You have to show her that you love her with your actions.
Give her the courage and confidence...
to open her heart again.
Are you even listening to me?
Can you...
get me Jia Yi's...
recent schedule?
Now we're talking.
Don't worry. Leave it to me.
But I'm telling you.
If you...
Be careful.
If you make her sad again,
you're done for.
Don't worry.
I'll make her happy.
I believe you.
Come in.
Mr. Jiang.
You got rejected again?
Ms. Linda said it's not a good time.
That's just an excuse.
What did Han Hui say?
Are there any other projects recently?
A few good ones are here.
What's all this?
("Magpie Bridge")
This script is also about Cowherd and Weaver Girl.
And it's of good quality.
I suppose there's always a way out.