(How could you let Wen Xiao Nuan and Han Hui meet?)
Ms. Cheng, since you brought it up,
I need to vent to you.
Because of Xiao Nuan,
Mr. Ye is too strict with the management department.
He nags us every day and keeps an eye on us...
in case Xiao Nuan gets bullied and suffers.
The room can't be too hot or too cold.
We have to pick the best co-stars to work with.
You know, we're only employees.
At this rate,
even ten Zhou Xiao Jing won't be able to handle him.
Ms. Cheng.
You have to say something on behalf of the management department.
All right, I got it.
It's the hardest on you.
I know.
Ms. Han.
Why did you want to see me today?
Ms. Wen.
Ms. Zhou.
I have something...
to discuss with Ms. Cheng in private.
Please excuse us for a moment.
- Okay. - Ms. Han, you might have forgotten.
I was the one who managed you back then.
I know your matters like the back of my hand.
I don't think I need to leave.
I'll get going then.
Wait.
You're the daughter-in-law of the Ye family.
Why do you need to leave?
Sit down.
Sit.
Ms. Cheng.
I'm the only person Fei Mo has ever loved.
My goodness.
So Han Hui and Ye Fei Mo...
Wen Xiao Nuan, why are you upset?
Remember. Don't get too immersed in your role.
Ye Fei Mo is nothing but your employer.
(How could you let Wen Xiao Nuan and Han Hui meet?)
How's the situation?
I know Fei Mo's temper best.
When he found out it was you who saved his life,
he insisted on being with you...
to repay your kindness.
But how could the Fei Mo back then...
understand what love is?
He's different now.
Fei Mo is all grown up.
He knows what he wants...
and what kind of person he wants to love.
Look at Nuan Nuan.
She just made her debut,
and Fei Mo has been protecting her all this time.
So...
I want to make one thing clear.
I don't want any nonsense gossip...
to affect Nuan Nuan, my son,
and Anning Culture.
Ms. Han, for old times' sake,
I hope you know when to stop.
Don't embarrass everyone.
I must be out of my mind.
How could we talk about your past relationship...
with Fei Mo in front of Nuan Nuan?
It's too disrespectful to Nuan Nuan.
Sorry, Nuan Nuan.
Okay, let's drop that.
Let's talk about what you truly came here for.
If you had known about Fei Mo's background back then,
you would have brought this up way earlier.
It'd be too long...
to wait until today.
Ms. Cheng, I've never taken advantage of you.
Of course.
Ms. Han, back then,
even without Mr. Ye,
you'd still be successful.
But now,
Anning Culture is finally...
in your good graces.
Naturally, you won't belittle Mr. Ye's resources.
Ms. Cheng, don't worry.
Ms. Han will get to the point soon.
Ms. Cheng.
I know you're prejudiced against me.
But this is business.
I hope...
you have the future of Anning Culture in mind.
To be blunt,
with my current status in the local film industry...
and box office appeal,
if I join "Blue Galaxy",
I'll be of great help to it.
Be it for Anning Culture...
or "Blue Galaxy",
I'm the best candidate for the female lead.
Speaking of which,
when was the last time I cared about our company's business?
Who's the director of this movie?
Ms. Cheng.
The director of this movie is Li Can.
But you know Li Can's temper.
He's used to doing the casting himself.
He never listens...
to anyone's opinion.
How could it be him?
He's notorious for being a pain in the butt.
He won't even give in for a so-called boss like me.
This is not going to be easy.
These two are too good.
Even I can tell they're passing the buck.
Han Hui is smart. How could she fall for it?
What's wrong, Nuan Nuan?
Do you have something to say?
Why are you always choking today?
The coffee has milk in it.
I'm not used to it either.
It's still too bitter.
Fei Mo likes bitter coffee the most.
Really?
Maybe Mr. Ye has been influenced by me.
When I'm with him,
we both like having mocha.
Is that so, Nuan Nuan?
Fei Mo changed for you.
Really? When did he change?
Ms. Cheng, you're not aware.
Lately, Mr. Ye has started to smile more.
Really?
That's great.
Nuan Nuan, you're amazing.
Thank you, Ms. Cheng.
Ms. Cheng, I'm a bit hungry.
May I have something to eat?
Of course.
Of course you can eat.
Waiter, serve the food.
We can't let Nuan Nuan starve.
(How's the situation?)
(Big Princess)
Hello.
The subscriber you have dialed is unavailable.
Ms. Cheng.
About what I just mentioned,
I hope you'll think about it.
Ms. Han, aren't we done with our business?
Can you let me have a meal with my daughter-in-law in peace?
Enjoy.
Ms. Cheng.
Do you think Han Hui would believe us?
Why should I care?
I'm full.
You're full?
Won't you have some more?
No, it's okay.
Okay then. You can go ahead.
I need to talk to Xiao Jing.
Okay.
Wait for me in the parking lot.
Thank you for the meal, Ms. Cheng.
Xiao Jing, I'll get going first.
Ms. Han.
You're still here.
Ms. Wen.
I underestimated you.
I didn't expect you to fit in with the Ye family so quickly.
Don't think you can fool me with just a couple of acts.
Fei Mo won't like you.
The title of daughter-in-law...
is just Cheng An Ya's wishful thinking.
Don't you get carried away.
Ms. Han.
I'm not getting carried away.
But you,
what are you so nervous about?
I...
Let me remind you.
You're an international star.
Arguing with a rookie like me...
is beneath you.
I see.
So this is what's going on.
Ms. Wen.
You're really something.
In front of Cheng An Ya and Zhou Xiao Jing,
you pretend to be all innocent.
It turns out...
you're not as innocent and kind as you look.
You're smart...
for knowing how to get on their good side.
You want fame...
yet you suck up to them.
Ms. Han.
Actually, there was a time...
when I thought of you as my goal.
If I could be one-tenth of what you are,
I'd be satisfied.
But I realized today...
that making you my goal...
was truly a shallow choice.
- You... - Don't get mad.
I'm only telling the truth.
Whether I suck up to Ms. Cheng or not,
that's my business.
There are so many people who want to please her.
If I can truly make her happy,
that's my ability.
Unlike some people.
She tries to please them,
but they don't accept it.
Wen Xiao Nuan.
You'll pay for what you said today.
Thank you for your kind advice.
Fei Mo.
You've got a good eye.
I like Wen Xiao Nuan.
She's soft yet strong.
She's resilient and has a bright future.
I can give her full marks right now.
Listen.
I've accepted Wen Xiao Nuan as my daughter-in-law.
If you dare to play games with me,
I won't go easy on you.
I'll teach you a lesson.
- Go. - Okay.
Get in.
Bye.
Why were you there?
Why can't I be there?
Yes.
Everything you do is a matter of course.
I heard you had dinner with my mom...
and Han Hui today.
You were in a relationship with Han Hui before?
Actually, we...
Why didn't you tell me this gossip?
I really thought you were a monk.
Your mom... No.
It was the first time I've seen Ms. Cheng...
so domineering.
Xiao Jing too.
She was so calm at passing the knife around.
They were so in sync.
What about you?
Were you just listening like a fool?
No.
Xiao Jing's instruction for me today...
was to just sit there quietly.
A supporting actor who steals the scene is not a good actor.
Is this what you've learned after the meal?
Of course not.
I really get it this time.
The female lead role in "Blue Galaxy"...
is a very rare opportunity.
I'll make the most of it.
I'll give Anning Culture a satisfactory answer.
I won't let Ms. Cheng down.
Only Ms. Cheng?
And Xiao Jing and Director Li.
And you.
Don't be petty.
Ms. Han.
Well?
How did it go with Cheng An Ya?
Your ex-girlfriend is quite something.
Cheng An Ya...
already sees her as her future daughter-in-law.
Ms. Han.
Has Ye Fei Mo's heart...
ever truly belonged to you?
What do you mean?
I think maybe we're going in the wrong direction.
You should learn from Wen Xiao Nuan.
As long as you can get into Ye Fei Mo's house,
I can block Wen Xiao Nuan's path forward...
and cut off Ye Fei Mo's escape route.
(One hour later)
Excuse me.
Alcohol, please. The strongest one.
Okay.
Mr. Ye, thank you for sending me home.
Nuan Nuan, were you training again?
You're home so late.
Jia Yi, let me tell you.
What happened today was amazing.
What happened?
Look how excited you are.
Hello, I'm calling from Junxin Bar.
Ms. Han Hui is drunk here.
What does that have to do with me?
Ms. Han has been recognized by the customers at the bar.
It's easy for a top star like her to cause a commotion.
Can you come and pick her up?
You should call her manager.
Don't call me again.
Wait.
Her manager said she's out of town.
Ms. Han is drunk.
She's been crying for Fei Mo.
I saw that she talked to you on the phone just now.
I had no choice but to bother you.
Fine.
More alcohol.
Miss, you're drunk. You should stop drinking.
I'm not drunk.
Fill it up.
Fei Mo.
You're here.
You're finally here.
You're here for me.
Look, everything is still the same.
Except for that annoying waiter,
nothing has changed here.
Have you changed?
You shouldn't be here.
I'll send you back. Come on.
I'm not drunk.
Who says I'm drunk?
Be careful.
Do you know?
I've always loved you.
What about you?
What are you doing?
Let's go back. Be careful.
Careful.
Stand still.
Come on.
Fei Mo.
I dreamt of you again.
Tell me.
What happened back then between Ye Fei Mo and Han Hui?
It's a sad story.
Back then,
when Han Hui and Ye Fei Mo first met,
Han Hui was just an unknown actress.
But she wasn't satisfied with her then status.
She worked hard to climb up the ladder.
She wanted to reach the top.
Thank you, everyone.
Thank you.
But Ye Fei Mo...
never revealed his background.
So Han Hui thought Ye Fei Mo...
was just a poor kid who hadn't graduated yet.
But Cheng An Ya kept an eye on Han Hui.
So she arranged an American director for Han Hui...
to invite her to the US to develop her career.
Actually, at that time,
Ye Fei Mo was already preparing...
to reveal his identity to Han Hui.
And through Zhou Xiao Jing,
he arranged for her...
to be the female lead in an S-class project.
That's "Blue Galaxy".
Unfortunately,
it's obvious that the olive branch Cheng An Ya offered...
was more tempting.
In the end, Han Hui chose to go to Hollywood.
Was Cheng An Ya testing Han Hui?
No one knows what Cheng An Ya thinks.
At most, she just kicked out a daughter-in-law she didn't like.
Say, Fei Mo.
Why doesn't Ms. Cheng like me?
She doesn't want me to be with you.
But she doesn't want you to hate her either.
So she tricked me into going to the US.
When I was in the US and found out that it was all a lie,
I was so devastated.
Let me get you some water.
Han Hui must have regretted it.
There was no turning back for her then.
She had no choice but to hang on.
But it's true that she was talented.
That's how she got to where she is today.
But Ye Fei Mo became her only regret in life.
Fei Mo.
I didn't have a choice back then.
We were together for so long.
But...
you kept it from me.
I didn't even know your true identity.
Suddenly, such a good opportunity was thrown at me.
Say.
If you were me,
what would you choose?
Get some rest.
Fei Mo.
We're just going to film a movie.
We'll be back soon.
Must you go?
You know me.
Ever since I joined this industry,
I've been through so much.
I've suffered so much...
just to wait for this opportunity.
So I won't give it up.
Please stay.
We can work hard together.
I'll help you get everything you ever wanted.
Don't be like this.
Let's be realistic.
Have you ever thought about this?
If you go to the US,
our relationship might be over.
(Fei Mo)