What are you doing?
Gu Yun Zhou, why did you bring me here?
I've never brought anyone here before.
You're the first.
This is my secret garden.
Jia Yi.
I admit.
I'm not a poor guy who's working part-time.
I've lived a privileged life since I was young.
But...
the responsibilities I have and the pressure I face...
are not what ordinary people can imagine.
So...
I'd come here on my own...
to clear my mind.
I don't have to think about anything.
Just like when I was a kid.
Jia Yi.
The reason I brought you here...
is because I wanted to show you...
the most real, direct, and pure side of my heart...
without anything holding me back.
Why didn't you tell me before?
Before this,
I've always wanted to be honest with you.
But I was afraid you wouldn't accept me.
So...
Jia Yi.
Be with me.
From the moment I first saw you,
I couldn't get you out of my head.
I'm always laughing and joking around.
But since I met you,
you made me understand...
what it means to be serious...
and what it means to care.
And I'm even more certain...
that you're the one I've been waiting for.
Let's be together.
Okay?
Gu Yun Zhou, I...
Stop being willful.
I mean...
we're not kids anymore.
We have to be responsible for our own actions.
I know.
We may not be the best match.
But compared to the arguments in the future,
what I care about more now...
is to be happy every day.
So...
are you saying yes?
I guess so.
Really?
Yes.
You fainted due to low blood sugar.
Your body is too weak.
Drink it.
Why did you stop?
I'm sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
Because of me,
the male lead of "Blue Galaxy" quit.
Such a big investment...
might go down the drain just like that.
So that's why you're training so hard...
and torturing yourself.
Turns out you're so vulnerable.
Wen Xiao Nuan.
I overestimated you.
You were the one who swore to me...
that you'd do your best with your first female lead role...
and not let down those who have expectations of you...
nor your passion and effort.
I didn't expect you to break down...
over such a trivial matter.
I didn't.
Don't deny it.
You fainted in front of me.
I was the one who brought you back.
Do you know how scary that was?
Are you angry?
It's not like what you think.
It's because...
I didn't want to embarrass myself...
And I don't want to embarrass you.
That matter with the male lead...
has been resolved.
An international movie star...
has agreed to play the male lead.
International movie star? Who is it?
You don't need to know for now.
What you should do is leave all your worries behind...
and focus on taking care of yourself.
The male lead going on strike...
was not your fault.
They just chose the wrong person.
You told such a white lie for me...
and took on all the pressure on your own.
Rest assured.
I won't make you worry anymore.
Thank you.
You're an S-class artist of Anning.
You're an important asset to the company.
No matter what happens,
you can't hurt yourself.
Do you understand?
All right, I have something to attend to.
Zhou Xiao Jing is downstairs.
She'll come up and take care of you.
Are you leaving?
I mean...
do you want to eat something before you go?
No.
Let's meet up.
I knew Mr. Ye still had you in his heart.
See? He took the initiative to ask you out.
Fei Mo.
Sit.
The salad here is not bad.
I'll tell them to serve it.
I'll let you two talk.
Linda, order an Americano with an extra shot for Mr. Ye.
You used to only drink this.
People change.
I drink mocha now.
You called me.
I was really happy.
You've been back for so long.
It's about time we sat down and talked.
So many things happened abroad.
I want to tell you all about them.
Even three days and nights won't be enough.
Thank you.
In Hollywood, I honed my acting skills...
and expanded my network.
I also got up close with professional teams.
I could choose the opportunities that suit me better too.
I'm different now.
The person I am now...
don't leave a place...
just because someone tells me to.
Your acting has indeed gotten better.
And...
it's different.
Then...
Can we...
start over this time?
The one who needs to start over...
is you.
The male lead of "Blue Galaxy" is on strike.
You know about that, right?
I heard.
You asked me to come...
because of this?
I want to hear your opinion.
The male lead is on strike.
You're in a passive position now.
Wen Xiao Nuan is just a rookie.
She can't handle such a big role.
But don't worry.
If you need help,
I'm always available.
You're very good at accusing others...
when you're the wrongdoer yourself.
This is Jiang Ling Er.
I heard she's Jiang Fang's current girlfriend.
And Jiang Fang is Wen Xiao Nuan's ex-boyfriend.
So...
Keep scrolling.
Aurora Film is investing in a new movie...
with Wen Xiao Nuan as the female lead?
Who told you that?
Everyone knows.
Director Li Can kicked Bai Xiu Wen...
out of the set in front of everyone.
Are you talking about "Blue Galaxy"?
I thought you would become the female lead instead.
After all, in terms of looks and family background,
in every aspect,
you and her are worlds apart.
Why are you looking at me like that?
It's just girl gossip.
It doesn't mean anything.
Fei Mo.
I know you're anxious and angry right now.
So you're suspicious of this and that.
But of all, you shouldn't be suspicious of me.
I'll say it again.
I'm here if you need help.
You don't have to pay me.
I'm just here to give you a friendly warning.
You know the whole story best.
As for "Blue Galaxy",
I'm just a producer in name.
The actual project...
is under the sole responsibility of Ms. Cheng.
If you want to play the female lead,
you can talk to my mom directly.
That might work better.
Well? Any breakthroughs?
He knows Cheng An Ya has a problem with me,
but he still pushed me to her.
He's so cruel.
Okay.
Not bad.
It's quite comfortable.
Okay, I'll take this pair.
Let's see.
Any new arrivals?
This dress is this year's latest.
It'll look good on you.
It does look good.
But it's too girly.
It doesn't suit me.
(Cheng An Ya)
Ms. Cheng, your phone is ringing.
Okay, thank you.
Who's calling me at this time?
They're distracting me from shopping.
(Han Hui)
Hello, Ms. Cheng. This is Han Hui.
I'd like to talk to you about "Blue Galaxy".
Are you interested in it?
When is a good time for you?
Let's meet and talk.
When is a good time?
Tomorrow night then.
The restaurant at GK Hotel.
Okay. See you there.
I'll take the dress.
I'll buy it for my daughter-in-law.
Okay, I'll wrap it up for you.
Okay, thank you.
Contact the stylist for me.
Tomorrow night,
I must win.
You're done?
Yes.
Do you still feel unwell?
Xiao Jing, I think I've almost recovered now.
I was too weak before this.
When anything happens in the future,
I'll get through it.
These few days have been tough on you.
Not at all.
As long as I can play my role in "Blue Galaxy" well.
Then rest well tonight.
Hello, Ms. Cheng.
Okay, I understand.
Good night, Ms. Cheng.
Xiao Nuan.
Tomorrow, come to the office early.
Continue your training.
At night,
you have a big battle to face.
Okay, Xiao Jing.
No matter what it is, I'll make it through.
Relax.
Pay attention to your facial expression.
Open your shoulders.
Relax your arms.
Tuck in your chin.
Xiao Jing, what big battle am I going to take part in tonight?
Isn't this basic training?
It's a banquet.
Ms. Han.
This dress is our newest design.
It's a dress fit for a queen. Noble and elegant.
Not many people can pull off this style...
apart from you.
You're right.
This dress suits you so well.
- This one. - Okay.
Why? It's nowhere near as good as this one.
Of course I know this dress suits me better.
But I'm going to see Cheng An Ya.
That woman has always been tough.
I have to be weak at times like this...
to get what I want.
Dear.
Give her a good fix...
from head to toe, inside and out.
Understood.
Looks like our body training...
wasn't in vain.
Look at yourself.
Wasn't all that hard work worth it?
Ms. Han, you're absolutely beautiful.
So when doing my makeup,
tone down my beauty.
I'd like some softer charm.
Even better if you make me look pitiful.
Ms. Han, your features and skin are perfect for makeup.
You can pull off any look.
You're born to look like an international star.
Why should I tone down your beauty?
I want to keep a low profile.
I don't want to intimidate others.
Okay, I got it.
Xiao Jing, where are we going?
GK Hotel's rooftop restaurant.
What kind of banquet is this? It's so formal.
Ms. Cheng is treating you to a meal.
Really? Ms. Cheng is treating me to a meal?
There's a lot of good food at GK Hotel.
You didn't let me eat all day.
If Ms. Cheng tells me to eat,
but I don't eat,
that would be disrespectful to my boss.
That's right.
There's penalty if you exceed the body fat limit.
I won't eat then.
When you see Han Hui later,
you've got to behave like a female lead.
Xiao Jing, aren't we meeting Ms. Cheng?
And Han Hui.
She's here for the female lead role of "Blue Galaxy".
I want you to prove...
that you're the best candidate for the female lead of "Blue Galaxy".
Xiao Jing, Han Hui is an international star.
I'm but an ugly duckling in front of her.
Besides,
she's definitely the right choice for the female lead.
How can I compete with her?
Let's go back now.
Wen Xiao Nuan.
Look at how unconfident you are.
In this aspect,
you're really no match for Han Hui.
She has such a high status in the industry now.
But she still works hard for the female lead role.
You're not doing your best at all.
That's how realistic this industry is.
Countless actresses out there want to take your place.
Can you avoid them all?
No one can easily take down the female lead.
There will be more difficulties and challenges in the future.
You can't avoid them all.
If you can't even take this step,
then I advise you...
to give up on your so-called dream.
You always ask me...
what else you can do...
when you're not training.
Right now, everyone in the company...
is paving the way for you.
What do you think is the right attitude you should give me?
Xiao Nuan.
I know you're a woman of honor.
A girl who won't admit defeat.
This battle...
isn't just for you.
It's also for everyone who has devoted themselves to you.
That includes Mr. Ye and me.
I'll go.
I'll go see Han Hui...
and those who don't believe in me.
I'll prove it to them.
Xiao Jing, I won't let you down.
Not even Ms. Cheng, Director Li,
and those who support me.
We all know you're the best.
You have to believe in yourself.
Prove to everyone...
that you deserve everything you have.
Go for it.
Fei Mo, have you heard?
Han Hui is going to meet Ms. Cheng.
There's going to be a bloodbath.
So what?
I'm not worried about my mom's combat strength at all.
Attack me all you want.
I have love to heal me anyway.
Ever since you fell in love,
you've become much more nosy.
You're no better than me.
Be honest with me.
You weren't at work all day.
What did you do with your little nurse?
I'm not as free as you. Get out.
I'm busy.
Hello, Mr. Ye.
How's Wen Xiao Nuan doing?
Xiao Nuan is much better.
She's with me and Ms. Cheng now.
My mom?
Isn't she with Han Hui?
She is.
Why did you bring Wen Xiao Nuan?
She's still sick.
Ms. Cheng arranged this.
What is my mom trying to do?
She wants Wen Xiao Nuan to compete with Han Hui?
Why didn't you stop her?
Mr. Ye, I'm just an employee.
I do as the boss says.
Zhou Xiao Jing.
Wen Xiao Nuan is just a rookie.
My mom...
She's putting her out there too soon.
It'll backfire.
Mr. Ye.
Don't underestimate Nuan.
- She can do it. - But...
You should trust Ms. Cheng's arrangement.
She admires Xiao Nuan.
Mr. Ye, I'm hanging up.
Ms. Cheng is waiting for us.
Nuan Nuan, you're here.
Come, have a seat.
Sorry for keeping you waiting, Ms. Cheng.
It's all right. Have a seat.
Ms. Han.
What are you waiting for?
Come in.
Ms. Cheng.
It's been a while.
I brought you a souvenir from the US.
I hope you like it.
Thank you, Han Hui.
It's a diamond brooch.
What a pity.
I'm not young anymore.
I think...
pearls are more suitable for me.
Diamonds...
make me look frivolous.
But I think it looks good...
on Nuan Nuan.
She looks so lively and cute.
Don't you think so, Ms. Han?
I'll gift it to you, Nuan Nuan.
Put it on.
It's okay, Ms. Cheng.
Xiao Nuan.
It's from Ms. Cheng. Put it on.
Come on, put it on.
Thank Ms. Han.
Thank you, Ms. Cheng.
Thank you, Ms. Han.
Sit.
Put it on.
Wonderful.
It's pretty.
Nuan Nuan.
That day, Fei Mo insisted that you wear Rose's Tear to the banquet.
He even announced you as his girlfriend.
What's going on?
What's wrong?
The coffee is too bitter.
I'm not used to it.
Waiter.
Add some milk to my daughter-in-law's coffee.
No, Ms. Cheng. You've misunderstood.
There's nothing between Mr. Ye and me.
He said that the other day...
just to help me out of a situation.
And he only lent me the necklace...
to match my dress.
I returned it the next day.
So please don't get the wrong idea, Ms. Cheng.
Don't be nervous, Nuan Nuan.
I'm not against you two dating.
Since Fei Mo has announced...
that you're his girlfriend in front of everyone,
From now on, just go ahead and act like...
the daughter-in-law of the Ye family.
Don't worry.
I won't give you a hard time.
Do I look like I want to be...
Ye Fei Mo's fiancée that much?
I hope Ms. Cheng doesn't have a misunderstanding about me.
Xiao Jing too.
She didn't tell me anything and dressed me up so formally.
What's the reason for all this?