Mr. Ye, come down for breakfast.
Are you having breakfast?
There you are.
Let's have the meeting first.
The nurse.
We've met before.
Stop chatting. Come down.
Have we?
What's wrong with Ye Fei Mo today?
Do I not look good?
I look good.
What do you think?
Are you getting along with 5203?
Cut the crap.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
Go away.
Get out.
I'm going to get changed.
It looks like having a nurse...
has made your life more colorful.
Cut the crap.
Is there anything going on in the company lately?
Not really.
Then bear in mind...
our current relationship.
When I'm not in the office,
they'll keep an eye on you.
You have to be careful.
Don't let them find out.
Don't worry. I know what I'm doing.
Remember.
Don't let them find out...
about our relationship.
I know.
- Bye. - Bye.
This nurse has been staying here for a long time.
She's a pain.
Don't you know that girls nowadays...
have a rebellious mentality?
The more you reject her,
the more she'll think you're interested in her.
If you really want to reject her,
just give her a scare.
Let me tell you.
No wonder he doesn't feel a thing...
when a fairy is in front of him.
I'll leave the sweeping to you today.
I have more important things to think about.
(On standby)
Let's get to work.
(Cleaning mode)
There's not much time left.
What should I do, then?
(2019 Fall and Winter Style, Men's Suit)
Hello, your parcel.
Okay, thank you.
Thank you.
Sir.
Say it again.
Gentler.
Sir.
Softer.
Say, "Sir."
Sir.
Lower.
Are you scared?
Since you're scared,
get lost.
Okay.
After the market closes tomorrow morning,
let's have a video conference.
I have to have a big project.
That way, I'll have a firm foothold in Aurora.
But Mr. Jiang...
won't allow me to work on any core projects.
It looks like I have to take the initiative.
(Film Project Proposal, "Blue Galaxy")
(Anning Culture Media Group)
Fei Mo, the market closed this morning...
with our stock down by 2.5 points.
I think someone is deliberately driving down...
Anning's stock price.
But don't worry.
I'll bring it back up during the noon market.
It shouldn't be a problem.
If they are driving down the stock price,
that means they took the bait.
Should I spread the good news?
No.
Let's wait and see.
By the way, there's one more thing.
Aurora's new production director...
suddenly came to see me.
He wants to talk about "Blue Galaxy".
The new production director?
We've only worked with Aurora...
on theater chains in the past.
His name is Jiang Fang. He's quite young.
He doesn't have much experience.
I think he's not familiar...
with Aurora and Anning's past.
He wants to achieve something on his own.
That's why he suddenly came to us.
Young and inexperienced?
How did he become the production director?
Don't judge him by his age.
He's Ms. Jiang's fiancé.
The future son-in-law of Aurora.
Why did you lie to me?
Why are you going out...
with Jiang Ling Er from Aurora?
Why, Jiang Fang?
Say whatever you want.
I've got everything I want now.
So it's him.
What? Do you know him?
Let him talk to me directly.
Do you want to let Aurora in?
"Blue Galaxy" is our key project.
Why should we share it with him?
I want to meet him.
Tell him to call me in 10 minutes.
I won't answer if he's late.
Okay, got it.
Hello, Mr. Ye.
I'm Jiang Fang, Aurora's new production director.
I didn't expect to be able to talk to you directly.
I'm honored.
You want to join "Blue Galaxy".
I'll give you two minutes...
to impress me.
Mr. Ye, two minutes might be a bit rushed.
Regarding this project,
I have a lot of ideas and thoughts.
I think we can...
Thirty seconds have passed.
Mr. Ye, I think you know...
Aurora's capabilities.
We have our own theater chain.
If we work together...
We've worked together on
theater chains over the years.
You don't have to tell me that.
You just need to tell me...
what your core competence is...
in production.
That will determine whether I work with you or not.
Mr. Ye, should we...
meet up in person?
Let's sit down and talk.
(Wen Xiao Nuan. Come to the entertainment room.)
I don't think so.
(Ye Fei Mo)
(Come to the entertainment room.)
Here's the thing.
In terms of production resources,
you can't help me in any way.
But if you really want to join,
I'll welcome you.
I can give you five percent of the shares.
at a 200 percent premium.
If you accept it, we'll work together.
Mr. Ye,
you're belittling me.
Come here.
Mr. Ye, why did you want to see me?
Wen Xiao Nuan.
Come here.
Sit closer.
Wen Xiao Nuan!
I just want to tell you.
You've been so tired lately.
Remember to rest.
Wen Xiao Nuan!
Mr. Ye, what's wrong?
There's sand in my eyes.
Let me blow it out for you.
Wen Xiao Nuan!
Wen...
This Wen Xiao Nuan.
What does she want to do?
Okay, you can go now. You can stop blowing.
Go.
Mr. Ye, what's wrong?
There's sand in my eyes.
Let me blow it out for you.
Mr. Lin, there you are.
Vice president of Aurora, Jiang Fang.
Yes, Ms. Ling Er's fiancé.
Nice to meet you.
I didn't expect Mr. Jiang...
to have such a major figure...
in Anning.
I really admire him.
Mr. Jiang asked me to see you.
That means you already have his trust.
I still have a lot to learn from you.
I hope you will teach me.
You're too kind.
You're young and talented with a bright future ahead of you.
Anning is the top film company in China.
It has always been Aurora's rival.
If we don't get rid of Anning,
Aurora will always be in second place.
Mr. Lin, I will be needing your help a lot...
in the future.
Mr. Jiang, if you need anything,
just let me know.
I heard that there was recently a girl...
at Ye Fei Mo's house.
Do you know anything about that?
A girl?
Yes.
Ye Fei Mo never lets girls into his house.
So...
I would like you to investigate this for me.
Don't worry, Mr. Jiang.
Leave it to me.
- Here's to our collaboration.
Mr. Gu.
Does this need Fei Mo's signature?
Then leave this document here.
I'll bring it to him when I'm free.
Mr. Gu, this is urgent.
If you're busy,
why don't I go there?
Okay.
Then I'll have to trouble you.
Hi, Fei Mo.
Lin Zheng is on his way to you.
He hasn't heard from me for so long.
He can't wait anymore.
That's why it's showtime.
Fei Mo, I have a call.
I have to go.
Hello. Did you find out?
Wang Jia Yi?
Aurora's artist?
She even won the Gold Medal Award for Best Newcomer?
How come I've never heard of her?
Well, if she makes any moves,
report it to me immediately.
Hello.
Hello. Who are you?
I'm Mr. Ye's assistant.
And you are?
I'm his personal nurse.
Personal nurse?
Do you have an appointment with him?
- Then come with me. - Okay.
Mr. Ye.
Why did you come back together?
We met at the door.
You two can talk. I'll go wash the vegetables.
Mr. Ye.
Mr. Ye, are you feeling better?
Nuan Nuan.
Come here.
Come.
- What's wrong?
- Come here.
Come on.
Don't move. I'm ticklish.
Look at you. You're sweating.
Are you exhausted?
I feel so bad for you.
Mr. Ye, do you need anything else?
If there's nothing else,
I'll go back to the office to return the documents.
It's so hot today. Have some water before you go.
It's okay. Thank you.
Go and cook.
Hello.
Ye Fei Mo and Wen Xiao Nuan are very flirty with each other.
I saw them hugging just now.
Ye Fei Mo and Wen Xiao Nuan are flirting?
Yes.
Now Ye Fei Mo has a 24-hour companion.
This is quite disadvantageous to us.
It'll be hard for us...
to get close to Ye Fei Mo.
Not necessarily.
Perhaps she can be our way in.
Do you mean...
Don't worry about Wen Xiao Nuan. I'll handle it.
Hi. Look into someone for me.
Wen Xiao Nuan.
What's going on with her lately?
Mr. Ye, dinner is ready.
Try it.
This is my specialty.
My dad taught me everything.
It should taste better than the flashy dishes you ordered.
Try it.
How is it?
It's bad.
Make something else.
Where's my food?
I tossed it.
You tossed it?
It tastes so bad.
Why keep it?
I can eat it if you won't.
It's such a waste if you throw it away.
(Big Princess)
Ye Fei Mo?
He's clearly a three-year-old.
(Big Princess)
Hello?
Sorry, I dialed the wrong number.
Sorry, I didn't dial the wrong number.
I'm looking for Fei Mo.
He's not here.
He's here. He's taking a shower.
Did you two have a fight?
That's how our Fei Mo is.
Please understand.
Your Fei Mo?
Which girlfriend of his are you?
The first one.
The first one?
First love, miss?
But I think...
you were blinded by first love.
He's rude and uncultured.
He's sharp-tongued, narcissistic, and twisted.
Why would you fall for him?
Let me tell you.
When you're looking for a partner,
you should be wiser, really.
I'm sorry. Am I talking too much?
No.
I totally agree with you.
Thank you.
I had a great time chatting with you.
I really look forward to seeing you.
I'm hanging up.
Weren't you looking for Ye Fei Mo?
Why did you hang up just like that?
I'm rude and uncultured.
I'm sharp-tongued, narcissistic, and twisted.
What did you say about me?
Say it again.
Are you stupid?
Why would you want to hear criticisms about you again?
Wen Xiao Nuan.
Don't come near me.
If you do, I'll throw an apple at you.
You answered the phone
when you didn't know who it was.
Isn't she your first ex-girlfriend?
I think she's quite nice.
She's nicer than you.
I saw that you were sick,
so I kindly took you in.
You're not only interfering with my life,
you're even invading my privacy.
You have to leave.
You have to leave now!
I'm sorry, Mr. Ye.
Please forgive me. I won't do this again.
I won't answer your calls again.
You have to leave.
You...
I'm not leaving.
The door is right there.
Leave right now!
I'm not leaving!
What's wrong with you?