Let's just say that Ake
wants to fire him quietly.
Nobody can blame Ake for that.
The pride that burdens your soul.
Isn't it heavy?
No matter how heavy it is,
at the end of the day,
I want the person I love
to be proud of me.
PREVIOUSLY
Bank has evidence to make Petch leave.
I hope tomorrow is Petch's last day here.
How could they arrest
the person who saved your son's life?
What?
Check on Shogun.
I'm sorry, Petch.
I have to do what you never expected.
I'm happy for you.
You and Bank finally cleared the air.
I'm happier for them.
Finally, Bank understands Shogun.
You're quite empathetic.
What do you mean?
I mean, you seem to understand
people so well,
but you don't seem
to understand Mr. Nop at all.
You believe that Bank loves Shogun,
and I believe that Mr. Nop loves you too.
As for my family matters,
I know how to handle them.
Petch.
Then you should let your father know.
Do you have any idea how much
the person left waiting misses you?
Dao.
I know you mean well.
But could you please give me some slack
so that I could make my own decision?
I'm not controlling you.
I just want you to think about it.
In juvie,
I spent countless hours thinking about it.
So please.
Don't make me hurt my dad again.
Why are you so stubborn?
I haven't been
on this live stream for days.
Do all my fans miss me?
Spam the heart button if you've missed me.
Oh, hey.
Nick said, "Do you have a boyfriend, Sai?"
You make me blush.
What should I answer? Should I--
Oh, I don't have a boyfriend.
That's correct.
But I have a husband.
What? Dam!
What the hell did you just say?
Everyone, listen up.
Let me tell you,
if you date a clingy girl like her,
you're doomed.
You're full of it!
- Take this!
- Sai!
- What's going on?
- Stop!
- Sai. Dam.
- No!
- Quit it. Sai, quit it.
- You!
No!
You've ruined my live stream!
Dam!
Why are you making me look bad?
Sai.
You said your heart
only belongs to Petch, didn't you?
So?
What's with those men online, huh?
You're right.
My heart belongs to Petch.
But my charm belongs to them.
- I just need to have fun with my charm.
- Right. Hold on a second.
Do you want to throw up for real?
- Stop it!
- Hey, Sai, quit it.
That's enough, Sai.
Sai.
I'm…
I'm thirsty.
Can you fix me honey and limeade?
My voice is cracking.
Sure.
I'll take care of it.
I'll fix you honey and limeade right away.
You'll be dead meat, Dam.
This woman.
That's a double standard, obviously.
So, you…
Where have you been?
You mentioned the new song, didn't you?
Sudden change of subject.
Did you see Natedao?
She's the boss.
You shouldn't make fun of her.
So, was I right or wrong?
Do you want to practice?
If not, I'll leave.
All right. We will practice, sir.
Sit down, sir.
Come on, I'm just teasing you.
Let's start.
Did you make an appointment
with a guy who will expose Petch?
The appointment is confirmed, sir.
I've made an appointment as you requested.
Don't disappoint me.
I think you should arrange
a party to celebrate.
Because once the clock strikes 3:00 p.m.,
Petch will be gone.
That's not good.
Bank.
Natedao.
How could you do this?
Is there any humanity left in you?
What are you saying?
I know why you're here.
Then you should step away.
I have an appointment.
- Wait.
- Natedao.
Stop getting in my way.
You said Petch was your friend,
didn't you?
How could you
stab him in the back like this?
What?
What are you talking about?
Petch was sent to juvie, wasn't he?
See?
I'm not going to frame him.
I'll tell the truth.
Bank.
I'm begging you.
Natedao.
You should stay out of this.
I can't wait to receive
the prize from Ake.
He's quite the big spender.
Leave.
I'll pay you double.
You're willing
to spend money for Petch too.
Such a shame.
I've already made a deal with Ake.
Stay out of this.
So selfish.
Petch shouldn't have helped you.
There you are.
I'm here.
Good.
Ake will see you upstairs.
All right.
Here you are, tasty honey and limeade.
What?
Where are they?
Dam must be the one who plotted this.
He probably took Petch somewhere else.
He'll see!
Watch where you're walking.
Sorry, I'm looking for Petch.
He's not here.
Where is he?
I don't know either.
Wait.
Why are you looking for him?
What's the matter?
Step away.
Give me the reason first.
Fine. I'll tell you then.
Someone was about to tell Ake
about Petch being in juvie.
- What?
- Why are you being so loud?
Do you want everyone here to know?
I'm about to have a heart attack.
Are you just going to let your fiancé
ruin Petch's life?
I'm not the one to blame.
Then what else can I do?
If the truth comes out
and Petch finds out we lied,
wouldn't that make things worse?
Right now,
we must delay Petch
so he doesn't face Ake.
I'll take care of the rest.
Petch and Dam must be backstage.
We should hurry.
Stop!
Move! What do you want, Joke?
No need to be in a rush.
You're already in my heart.
- That was smooth. Hey!
- You!
- Easy!
- Take this!
How dare you use a pick-up line with me?
I've been planning this for so long.
You're so aggressive.
Was that a woman's fist or a man's?
That hurt so much!
Enough, both of you.
We should find Petch.
What was that, ma'am?
Petch?
You don't have to look for him.
Why?
Do you know where he is?
Enough already.
- Just spill it!
- I'm going to!
I will. Back off.
I will have to choose violence again.
Look. It's like this.
I was about to collect a debt from Petch
because he owes me money.
But before I could even get to him,
Ake ordered someone to drag Petch
and Damrong off to that room.
- Right over there.
- Petch.
Dao, let's hurry.
Hold on.
Where's the fire, sweetie?
I've already told you where Petch is.
Pay up. Twenty baht.
- Joke, you little…
- No!
Let's go, Dao.
My family jewels.
I didn't even get a chance to flirt,
and I'm already in agony. What?
Why are they in such a hurry?
Are you sure, Bank,
that your evidence is solid?
Of course.
I guarantee today will be a day
you'll never forget.
I can vouch for that too, sir.
Bank is an old rival of Petch.
Bank.
Bring out the evidence.
I already told you.
I'll only reveal it in front of Petch.
Then I'll be waiting to see.
If your evidence
isn't actually that great,
you won't get a single baht from me.
Come in.
I'm expecting to see you.
Bank.
Nice to see you again, buddy.
Hurry up, Dao.
What are you doing here?
I don't know what this is about,
but something in this room…
smells fishy.
I bet it's nothing good.
Your best friend here is a good guesser.
Save the chatter.
Bank, you can go ahead
and show us your evidence now.
What evidence?
- The evidence that you used to--
- Wait!
Dao.
Why did you come in?
Sorry.
It's just…
I have an urgent matter
I need to discuss with you.
What's the urgent matter?
Well…
Oh, right.
The client's private party tomorrow,
right, ma'am?
Yes! There are a lot of details
that I want to consult you about.
Should we go talk in my office?
All right, Dao.
Great.
In that case,
excuse us for a moment, everyone.
I'll follow you in a bit.
Let me clear up
an important matter here first.
I think it's better
if you stay here with us, ma'am.
We can all look
at this important evidence together.
That's a good idea.
Stay here and see
the important evidence with us.
What is it?
What evidence?
Bank.
Show us.
Sir, I don't think
this man is trustworthy.
Whoever interrupts me again
is getting thrown out of this room.
All right.
I'm here to tell everyone the truth.
This is my phone
from when I was in vocational college.
I have an important audio clip saved here.
I'm going to play it for everyone to hear,
so we can decide whether Petch
actually deserves to keep working here.
Do whatever it takes
to kick Petch
out of school.
You want me to get him expelled?
Yes.
Make it happen
and you will owe me nothing.
Do you really mean that?
Enough!
What?
Why?
I was just enjoying the radio show.
Shut up!
Bank, why the hell
did you play that crazy clip?
It's not crazy at all.
It's the truth
about how you ordered us to frame Petch
so he would get expelled from school.
- Shut your damn mouth!
- No, sir!
Mud, this is your fault!
Why did you bring this loser here?
Wow, what a sore loser.
Shut it!
Dao.
It's not true. It's a fake clip.
Then why are you acting so defensive?
I never thought
you would be this kind of person.
You used dirty tricks
to force Petch out of school.
Dao.
Why are you overthinking this?
Back then,
Petch and I were still fighting.
But we're good now.
We've cleared things up, right?
Yes.
I don't hold a grudge.
The past is the past. It can't be changed.
See, Dao?
We've already cleared things up.
I wasn't finished.
The past can't be changed,
but behavior can.
If you know the difference
between right and wrong.
Bank.
Thank you so much
for helping keep Petch's secret.
Besides, you totally humiliated Ake.
I'm just lucky
I held onto that clip Joe secretly
recorded of Ake and shared with me.
But you're such a great actor.
I've got to hand it to you.
I had to.
I didn't want Ake and his men
to catch on too early.
Hey.
What made you change your mind
and expose Ake instead of Petch?
Ake was going to pay you too, wasn't he?
The money…
Everyone wants it, of course.
But Petch's goodness
is worth way more than that money.
So, I've decided that
I won't let myself be a tool
for bad people to hurt Petch anymore.
That's wonderful.
So you're both here.
I was just looking for you.
You're totally awesome for exposing
that arrogant jerk's true colors.
I'm not awesome at all, man.
I just wanted to make it up to Petch.
I want you to know
that I'm sorry for the terrible things
I did to you.
Please forgive me, Petch.
Friends don't hold grudges
against each other.
We can forgive each other.
Thanks, man.
Come on.
That's what friends do.
I'm happy for both of my friends.
Bank, Petch, you guys
finally worked things out. Awesome!
Seeing you smile makes me happy too.
Sweet dreams, Petch.
YOU RECEIVED A NEW MESSAGE
Did you really just send me a message?
PETCH UNSENT A MESSAGE
You unsent it.
You're really crazy.
But I'm even crazier for waiting for you.
I will wait until the day
you open your heart.
That's great. Come on.
Yes.
Right?
Follow me, son. Come on.
Yes.
- Right.
- Like this?
Cheers.
Today, Petch and I
are hosting a celebration for you,
father and son,
who finally worked things out.
It's a shame Sai Kaew
couldn't come with us.
But she sent some snacks for Shogun too.
Bank, Shogun,
we're really happy for you guys.
Thanks.
Shogun, say thank you to Mr. Petch.
Thank you, Petch--
- I mean Mr. Petch.
- Hey.
Thank you for helping me with everything.
And for buying me new shoes.
I love them!
I love them so much!
As long as you like them, I'm happy.
I'm planning to wear them
to the dance competition in Phuket.
What? Why are you going there, Shogun?
I'm thinking of moving us down there.
What? You and Shogun are moving to Phuket?
Yes.
My cousin works
at a yacht management company.
They're looking for more mechanics,
so he asked me to work with him.
The pay is pretty good.
I figured that if I moved down there,
I'd have enough money to send Shogun
to the dance classes he wants.
Thank you, Dad.
- I love you the most.
- I know.
Save the sweet talk.
I've invested this much,
so you better be the star
of the dance floor, you hear?
I promise.
If there's a competition anywhere,
I'll wear the shoes Mr. Petch bought me,
dance my heart out,
and bring home a trophy for you.
Right. Make sure you actually do it.
Don't just brag about it, okay?
You have to make it happen.
If Dao heard that, she would be thrilled.
She split the cost of the shoes with me,
half and half.
Why didn't Natedao come with you?
She told me this morning
she was stuck in a meeting
at the head office,
so she asked me to pass along
her congratulations.
Hey.
That sounds so lovey-dovey.
Totally gives off couple vibes.
Don't ruin her reputation, Dam.
She already has a fiancé.
Oh, Bank.
What's up?
Tell Natedao goodbye for me.
Why me?
You can ask Dam.
Oh, come on.
You have someone
so wonderful right beside you,
but you keep running away.
That's enough.
If you're going to talk nonsense,
let's not talk at all.
Hey, hold on.
Natedao is a good person.
Don't let a good woman like her
fall into the hands of a scumbag like Ake.
Bank.
I know you mean well.
But there are still many factors
that keep her out of my reach.
Stop it.
You told me to change my mindset
for the people I love, right?
I would do anything.
But if it means dragging a star like Dao
down to my level,
I can't do that.
Let me make this clear.
I'm not backing down or giving up.
I just can't move forward right now.
Let's just say,
if Ake ever breaks Dao's heart,
I won't let him get away with it.
Okay.
True worth shines through anywhere.
I'll be waiting to see the day
you overcome your obstacles.
And I'll wait to see the day
you'll be happy with the woman you love.
Okay?
All right.
No one is happy about everything,
and no one is sad about everything.
The same goes for me.
Recently,
I was glad to reunite with an old friend.
But now, he has to go on a long journey.
I wish you a safe trip
and good luck.
Until…
we meet again.
Don't be afraid of goodbyes
Don't be afraid of time passing by
That is real love
Don't be afraid of going alone
You'll never be alone
Just want you to know
Out of this endless yearning
Hold on, the wait won't be too long
At the edge of the horizon
Where the fading light remains
- We will meet again
- Hey.
- I'm his fan.
- Sir.
I'll drink for him.
- Hey, stay out of this!
- Let your heart be your guide
- Sir--
- Screw you!
Oh, no!
Drink!
I'm a fan, man!
- No, sir. Thank you.
- Don't be arrogant!
The customer is god!
Hurry, that way.
Hurry.
This singer sucks.
Damn you!
- What the--
- Take him down now.
Get down here.
Hey! What the hell?
Throw him out.
Go home. You're too drunk.
Petch, let's leave.
Why the hell was he acting
like such a scumbag?
Petch, wipe your face first.
Too bad the guards dragged him away first.
I would have torn him apart.
Exactly. Who does he think he is,
the master of the universe?
Musicians have dignity too, man.
He should show some respect.
Yeah.
Forget it.
I'm going to the restroom.
- I'm coming with you, Petch.
- Hey.
Stay here.
What now, Dam?
Petch is going to the men's restroom.
Stay here.
Again! You're so annoying!
Take your eyes off her for a second,
and she's ready to harass a guy.
How's it going, Petch?
How does it feel
to be looked down on?
What now?
I just wanted to know
if it hurt a lot.
Turns out my guy
played his role a little too well.
It really was your doing.
I don't get it.
Why are you doing this?
You still have the nerve to ask?
It's because
I want you to realize
just how low-class
someone like you is.
You completely lost face
when you got exposed in front of Dao.
There's something seriously wrong
with the way your brain works.
Because a guy who uses dirty tricks
to attack other people
is truly low-class.
A lowlife like you…
shouldn't bring Dao down to his level.
You'd better watch your back.
I'll make sure
you're out of her life forever.
A lowlife like you…
shouldn't bring Dao down to his level.
INCOMING CALL: NATEDAO
What is it?
Wait. Why are you snapping at me?
I'm not.
If you have something to say, just say it.
I went straight home
after my meeting today.
I didn't go to the pub.
So, I wanted to ask about Shogun and Bank.
They both wanted to thank you
for buying shoes for Shogun.
And they're moving to Phuket
at the end of this month.
What? They're moving already?
Are they still short on--
You dare hang up on me, Petch?
You think you can just do that?
SO YOU'RE GIVING ME
THE SILENT TREATMENT NOW?
YES.
You jerk.
Fine. I won't care about you
anymore either.
There you are!
You broke singer.
You're right here.
I've been looking for you for ages.
Hey, hold on!
Let's talk first.
Where are you rushing off to? Let's talk.
Sorry, man.
I'm not in the mood to talk to anyone.
Not in the mood to talk?
Feeling lonely? Sad?
Or is it about love?
Wait. Are you heartbroken?
Don't tell me your girlfriend dumped you.
No! Don't hurt me.
I haven't done anything wrong.
I'm looking away now. See?
Just don't punch me.
I won't stand the fight.
Please go easy on me, please.
Why is he so quiet?
Wait. What?
Hey!
Heck!
Such a coward!
I thought you were so tough.
I was acting scared to test you.
Wow!
That's great, Uncle.
Thanks a lot, Ake, for keeping me company.
Let's call it a day.
All right.
In that case,
may I treat you to some coffee?
- Okay.
- Consider it…
a celebration of your top form today.
Sure. Thanks.
Let's head out then.
Uncle.
What are you looking at?
Your coffee is getting cold.
Oh, hold on.
Here, Ake. Take a look.
This guy is going to be our new artist.
I wish I knew if I ever crossed your mind
- I wish I knew if you heard the whisper
- How is he? Are you speechless?
This guy sings really well.
- For my heart is crying out my love
- Uncle.
I don't think he has much of an aura.
And besides…
- This style of music probably won't sell.
- I know that it simply cannot be
Look at the view count.
There's barely any.
But I think he has the potential
to be a superstar.
Just add some production value
and a little bit of marketing strategy,
and he'll be a massive hit.
I love watching these cover songs,
and this suddenly popped up.
Must be destiny.
- Ake.
- Yes?
Track this guy down immediately.
I want him to release a single
under our label.
Uncle.
Well, let's play another round soon.
Okay, sure. Don't forget what I asked you.
I won't.
I'll get this sorted out for you
as fast as possible.
Thanks a lot.
Goodbye.
Petch.
Mud.
Find a highly skilled hacker
to take down Petch's channel right now.
Don't ever let him shine.
I wish I knew if you heard the whisper
Wow, Mr. Subpar-star!
I mean, Superstar. There you are.
People are trying to practice here.
Can you not bother us, Joke?
No can do.
You asshole.
Dam, let's not start a fight.
Just look at how he treats us.
I'll knee him!
Don't do that.
Don't do this to your creditor.
What do you mean by that?
Well,
ask your friend then.
Petch, you still owe me
for the suit rental.
Pay up. Hurry.
Two hundred, right?
No.
It's 1,000.
Stop messing around.
You said it was 200 that day.
How did it magically grow to 1,000?
Hey.
Ever heard of interest?
Overdue payments go up, obviously.
Hurry up. Pay it.
What's your problem?
- Want to take this outside?
- He's not worth it.
All right?
I only have 200 for you.
Take it or leave it
because I'm not paying any more.
Holding onto cash
is better than holding on to grudges
against pathetic debtors like you guys.
You just won't shut up.
If we ever get famous,
don't you dare claim you know us.
You guys? Famous?
Are you dreaming?
No way. You're completely delusional.
At the very least, Petch's song
already has hundreds of views.
Look.
What…
What kind of joke is this, huh?
What's with the buffalo?
It's nothing but buffalo.
Wait.
Petch.
Our clip is covered with buffalo faces.
I can't log into my account either.
Petch!
This is bad!
I don't know what's wrong
with your channel.
I can't watch anything!
I think I know why.
Our channel probably got hacked.
- Hacked?
I can't believe this.
Hey.
Who would bother hacking
neighborhood nobodies like you?
Aren't you imagining things?
Job done. Petch's channel
is out of commission now.
All the data on the channel
will vanish too.
Very good.
You live up to the rumors.
Here.
Your payment.
Oh, wow.
This pays so well.
Whenever you have another job like this,
you can call me.
Keep monitoring Petch.
If his channel ever opens back up,
take it down.
I promise you'll be paid handsomely.
You got it.
Hello, sir?
Any updates?
All done, sir.
I guarantee that from now on,
Mr. Sompob will never find
Petch's channel again.
Good. But that's not enough.
I want him to suffer more.
- What else do you want me to do, sir?
- Mud.
Send some guys to beat him to a pulp.
I want to see him bleed.
Here you are.
Honey and limeade soothe the vocal cords.
But if you want someone
to soothe your heart,
it has to be me.
What? What is this, Petch?
I created one pick-up line for you,
but you didn't even get it.
Petch!
What is it, Sai?
Just because the channel got hacked,
you can't eat
and won't even answer when spoken to?
No.
I'm not giving up that easily, Sai.
I was just thinking,
if we start a new channel,
what should we improve?
Man! This sucks!
What are you yelling about now?
What's gotten into you?
Annoying.
I'm done. Whatever!
- Whatever!
- Hey.
Hey, Dam. Calm down, man.
Listen, Petch.
Rerecording, reshooting,
and reediting everything isn't easy.
And what if we rerecord it
and the vibe just isn't the same?
You can be discouraged,
but don't back down.
Even if we get hacked
a hundred more times,
I'll rebuild it a hundred more times.
I just feel like it's such a waste.
Don't cry over spilled milk.
Dam.
Let's rethink and rebuild this.
Let's make it better than before.
So true.
How can someone be so sharp and handsome?
You've completely won my heart.
- Get over here.
- Ouch!
I can't leave you alone for a second.
Dam! What is wrong with you?
You're always blocking my moments!
All right, you two keep arguing.
I'm going to practice guitar.
You go on ahead, Petch.
I'm going to teach this one a lesson
and straighten her out myself!
- Go on then.
- You're so stubborn.
Hey, Dam.
Sorry, man.
Let's do it tomorrow.
I've got some errands to run.
Where are you going?
Don't worry about it.
I'll meet you at the pub.
And grab my guitar for me, will you?
Petch, I'm coming with you!
- Hey!
- What?
Don't be so nosy.
You're just going to end up getting hurt.
I'm going to get hurt because I have
an ungrateful brother like you.
You never support your sister.
You always crush my dreams.
I'm afraid you're going to get
your heart broken.
Understand, you stupid kid?
I'm not a kid anymore!
How do you know I'll get my heart broken?
You piss me off.
Petch's heart is already taken,
you stupid kid!
Dam, don't even try to scare me.
If he doesn't have anyone,
and I don't have a boyfriend,
that means I still have a chance!
GRANDMA LOT'S GRILLED PORK SKEWERS
Dad.
I bought your favorite
grilled pork skewers.
Oh, my son.
You really know me so well.
This is my absolute favorite.
You have to eat it all then.
Thank you very much, son.
Sir.
How many grilled pork skewers do you need?
I'd like ten grilled pork skewers
and two sticky rice, please.
If you miss your dad,
why don't you live with him?
Wait. Don't go just yet.
It's my family's issue.
Can you just stay out of it?
I'm sorry that I can't stand
watching you act out like this.
You don't know the whole story.
You should be quiet.
Petch.
Please.
This is my business.
I can handle it myself.
Behind you.
Dao, run!
- Dao!
- Follow him!
Where is he?
You go that way!
I'll go this way!
You!
Hey!
Dao, step back.
Watch out! Petch!
Who sent you?
Will you answer or not?
No?
Petch!
- Ouch!
- Dao!
Are you okay?
Let's run!
- I was clumsy.
- Hurry!
Are you all right?
Worry about yourself first.
Let me see.
Hey.
Did you sprain your ankle?
Okay.
It's just a scrape and a little blood.
I'll patch it up for you.
- Are you ready?
- Yes.
Ouch!
Are you hurt?
A little.
Pain, pain…
go away!
Get better soon.
All done.
Now, don't let the wound get wet,
or it might get infected.
Thanks a lot, Petch.
- Ouch!
- Hey!
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
I can walk.
I don't want to be a burden to anyone.
Are you being sarcastic?
Who would dare?
Stop being stubborn.
Let's just say
I'm more than happy to help you out.
What the hell are you doing? Put me down!
- Put me down!
- Keep moving, and I'll do worse.
Where did you park your car?
At the entrance of the alley.
Okay.
I'll offer you a free chauffeur service
straight to your house.
You're only tough in a pack!
Hit him!
Natedao is my fiancée.
You have no right to take her anywhere!
NEXT EPISODE
When you're with Petch,
do you act innocent like this?
Hey.
It's completely ruined.
Which bastard broke Petch's guitar?
How could you do that to Dao?
I wish I knew if I ever crossed your mind
I wish I knew if you heard the whisper
For my heart is crying out my love
It's deep and true
But never reaching you
I know that it simply cannot be
And I never want to cause you misery
I'm just an ordinary man
Worth nothing at all
And I never want to make
Your teardrops fall
You are out of reach
Is it a crime that I need you?
Please let me know for sure
That you're the one I've been waiting for
How much longer can I bear this pain?
How much longer must I wait in vain?
I really don't know what move to make
To end this heartache
And say that I love you
Subtitle translation by: Sarunpon T.