[English subtitles are available]
[Forever and Ever]
[Episode 1]
With long eyebrows
and beautiful, striking eyes,
the man was charming
and irresistible.
Zhousheng Chen,
the Junior Prince of Nanchen,
fought bravely for his country.
Loyal as he was,
he became obsessed with fame
and wealth in his prime,
thus the seed of rebellion began to grow in him.
Fortunately, the prestigious family in Qinghe saw through his plot.
As a result, the Junior Prince of Nanchen got arrested.
The crown prince was furious with him,
and sentenced him to death by dismemberment.
The execution lasted for six hours,
but the Junior Prince of Nanchen never let out a cry of pain once.
He regretted nothing even till his last breath.
You need to hurry,
or you'll miss the flight.
Was it okay?
Your work
has always been perfect!
Then I'm leaving.
I'll finish the rest in Shanghai.
Okay! Have a nice trip!
I've asked them to take your luggage down
to save some time.
Thank you! Bye-bye!
-Bye-bye!
No one can top
Miss Shi's voice.
Of course!
The producer pleaded with her four times.
His persistence finally got her here.
[Guangzhou]
He's a loyal official
who protected his country and had no wife or children.
But in the end
he was framed.
Zhousheng Chen...
The Junior Prince of Nanchen.
[Liede Bridge]
[Check-in Desk]
Hi. I'm here for the 3 pm flight to Shanghai.
Hi.
Please put your luggage on the conveyor belt.
[Out of service]
Hi.
I'm here for the 3 pm flight to Xi'an.
-Hi. -Thanks!
-Sure!
[Out of service]
Here's your boarding pass.
Thank you!
Mr. Zhousheng!
Sorry! I'm late!
Give me your ID card.
Hi. We're on same flight.
To Xi'an.
Okay.
Sir, your ID card.
Here you go.
Let me help you with that.
Please go through the metal detector again.
Did you take your cellphone out?
I did.
I don't have anything on me.
Please take off your high heels.
Okay.
Turn around, please.
Please go through it again.
Thank you!
Mr. Zhousheng Chen!
You forgot your ID card!
Thank you!
Mr. Zhousheng,
I'm so sorry.
I was going
to carry your stuff for you,
but I almost left
your ID card there.
Sir! Sir!
Wait a moment!
May I borrow a few seconds of your time?
It may sound a little abrupt,
but is your name Zhousheng Chen?
I heard they call you that
at the security check.
Yes.
I'm Zhousheng Chen.
Here's the thing.
I've seen your name
a lot recently during work.
Zhousheng Chen.
It's a character's name in a story.
A movie, to be exact.
I've been dubbing for the movie.
So I just had to talk to you
when I heard the name Zhousheng Chen.
Sorry! I've made it even more confusing.
You may not know this,
but I...
The story about the Junior Prince of Nanchen?
Yes! You know that story?
I do.
Nice to meet you! My name is Shi Yi.
Nice to meet you!
I'll be boarding soon,
and I don't have much time.
May I have your WeChat contact
or phone number?
I hope we can be friends.
Just friends!
I'm sorry.
I've just come back from abroad
and I don't have
a local number yet.
I see.
That's all right.
If you don't mind
contacting via email,
we can exchange
our E-mail addresses.
Sure!
I give you mine, or you give me yours?
I'll give you mine.
Pen and paper, please.
Final call for flight CA 1866.
Would Miss Shi Yi
please go to the boarding gate as soon as possible.
The flight will take off soon.
Here.
Thank you!
I'll be going then.
Goodbye!
Final call for flight CA 1866.
Would Miss Shi Yi
please go to the boarding gate as soon as possible.
The flight will take off soon.
[Air China Inner Mongolia]
Miss, let me help you.
Thank you!
[ID Card]
[Bones of a Great Man]
[Six months later]
[Shanghai]
[I love Shanghai]
Your mom asked me yesterday
if you have a boyfriend.
I felt too embarrassed to tell her
that you've wasted half a year
dating a chemistry professor
who's in Germany online!
We're not dating online.
Oh, sure it's not!
Then why does it take you so long
to reply to his emails?
Why is that?
The format and contents
of his emails
are always so formal.
You'll understand when you see them.
I have no choice but to reply carefully.
A friend of mine wants to read them.
A friend of mine
thinks they are too boring to share with others.
How old is he exactly?
I've never asked.
How old did he look?
Late 20s?
That's a dangerous age.
It's hard to say whether he's married or not.
In that case,
everybody who's over 18 is dangerous.
But
the two of you are in different countries.
How are you supposed to develop your relationship?
I say, you should give up.
Am I wrong?
Don't tell me you'll want to be in a platonic love for the rest of your life!
Actually, he's in Xi'an right now.
He came back?
For you?
I told you he's on a
business trip.
I'm not finished yet!
What else?
I'll go on a business trip
to Xi'an this weekend!
And that relates to me how?
Of course it does!
Don't you think it's too coincidental?
Isn't it destiny?
Would you like to go with me?
Let me break it down for you.
You only need to buy a flight ticket.
You don't need to pay for the hotel,
since you'll be staying with me.
Take it as a trip with me!
At the same time,
you can go see that "online friend"
you've been communicating with via email!
I may not have time.
I need to check my work schedule.
I'm leaving next Monday morning.
You still have time to book a ticket.
[Mail   To: Zhousheng Chen   From: Shi Yi]
I happen to be going on a business trip
to Xi'an next week.
If you like,
we can meet.
Shi Yi.
[Xi'an]
I came unannounced.
Surprised?
I invited you to come back.
Why would I be surprised?
They invited you to a seminar
but placed you in such a small place?
Is this place small?
I requested this room.
It's only five-minute walk
to the lab.
It's a big timesaver.
I know you don't care
about these things,
but as an associate professor,
you should have some standards.
The wealth we own is intangible.
Don't lecture me
about how the wealth of knowledge is above all.
Every equipment in the lab
costs at least 10 million Yuan.
The reagent we've been using lately
is hundreds of times the price of gold.
Since you are that rich,
you should prepare a big red envelope
for the groom then.
Here.
What's this?
Are you getting married?
[Bridegroom: Zhou Wenchuan   Bride: Tong Jiaren]
Your brother is.
Surprised?
Nope.
Nothing is impossible.
What about you?
What do you mean?
When will you meet with the fiancee
your mom arranged for you?
I don't have time.
Do you lack time
or do you lack courage?
I really don't have the time.
Let's talk when we get back.
Suit yourself.
[Lay a foundation for the sustainable development of students]
It's such a strange year.
Three years' worth of rain
all came this year.
It doesn't rain much in Shanghai, though.
The rain all goes from the south to the north.
Are you from Shanghai?
Yes.
Have you come to Xi'an for a business trip?
They are on a business trip.
I just took this chance to visit home.
That's the ancient city wall over there.
You know,
there are many
famous attractions in Xi'an.
You girls can go for a tour
after the interview.
Young man,
you should be a good host
and bring them around!
Yes! You are right!
Has the chemistry professor
replied to your email?
What a pity!
I'm not here to meet him anyway.
I came to work.
I've made an itinerary.
I'll visit the Azure Dragon Temple, the Terracotta Warriors, and the museums.
If I have more time,
I'll go visit
the Epang Palace.
Okay. You have me convinced.
It looks like the two of you
are not very well off.
So what made you
decide to contribute to
your hometown education?
It's because...
we are...
we are poor since childhood
and had a hard life growing up,
we want to make a change to our hometown, right?
I...I'm not good at explaining things.
Dear,
why don't you explain it to them?
They are interviewing you.
Why are you asking me to talk?
Please don't be nervous.
We are just having a chat.
Since you two have donated all your savings,
have you ever argued with each other
because of this?
Never.
I've always supported
whatever he does.
And...
I always listen to him.
What are you talking about?
You are the boss.
Try some of the chili oil.
It's tasty.
Here's your Paomo. Please enjoy!
Thanks!
What did you think about
the interview just now?
Most people are shallow,
for they only see the beautiful facial features, but not good bone structure.
The wife is very special.
She's able to see through the superficial
and appreciate the good qualities of her husband.
Most people are shallow,
for they only see the beautiful facial features, but not good bone structure.
Well said!
What a coincidence!
May I sit here?
Sure!
Is he your friend?
He's Zhousheng Chen.
This is my friend Hong Xiaoyu.
And this is her coworker, Shuai.
Nice to meet you!
Nice to meet you, too!
Are you here in Xi'an for a trip?
Yes.
Xiaoyu came here for an interview
and we wanted to take this opportunity
to take a tour.
In one of the emails I sent you
I've mentioned her.
I'm sorry!
I haven't checked my mailbox for a while,
so I didn't see your email.
It's okay.
This is my business card.
Liu Shuai.
Yes. My name is Liu Shuai.
Pardon me,
I don't usually
carry my business card with me.
My name is Zhousheng Chen.
I'm an associate professor at Berkeley College of Chemistry.
I've been staying
at the Research Institute of Xi'an
for an exchange program.
Good! Good!
Shengchen!
It's a nice name.
You can just call me Shuai.
I'm Xiaoyu's coworker.
My family name is Zhousheng and my given name is Chen.
Mr. Zhou...Zhousheng!
It's a family name, huh?
Shi Yi,
what was it you said
just now?
It sounded quite nice.
Do you understand it?
Of course I do!
Why can't I?
But I'm telling you,
a sentence like that,
you have to
use your heart to understand it, you know?
Cut it out!
Go read the book "Stories to Awaken the World",
where there's a similar saying.
Listen,
the sentence means
people nowadays
only pay attention
to materialistic things.
Such as money,
car, house,
and appearance.
Seldom do they care about a person's inner beauty.
I got it! Got it!
Shi Yi forced me to read when we were little.
She's always been a bookworm.
She reads all kinds of books.
Mr. Zhousheng!
I must buy you a cell phone
when I get my salary next month.
I'll even pay the phone bills for you.
I went everywhere looking for you!
If it wasn't for the car of our institute parking outside,
I wouldn't have found you!
Shi Yi!
Hi!
Were you two going to meet with each other here?
No. We bumped into each other!
What's up?
We have a seminar later.
Did you forget?
Of course not.
I just came out for lunch.
I'll be going then.
I'll contact you later.
Bye.
Mr. Zhousheng.
I heard that the cherry blossoms
are blooming in the Azure Dragon Temple.
We are all not local people
and may not get the chance again.
Would you like to go there with us?
It's been raining these past two days.
If the rain stops
and you guys are still here,
then maybe we could set a date to go. Is that okay?
Sounds good!
It's a deal then.
Shi Yi will contact you by email.
See you!
Yes!
Look at you!
You make a living with your voice,
but you act like a mute
at the most critical moment!
Through today's
simple meal,
I found two good qualities
about him.
He's manly
and straightforward.
Actually that doesn't sound right either.
Ever since we were little,
I could always use you as an excuse
to ask someone out successfully.
In this way,
he isn't that special after all.
A pretty face
can only be maintained
from 16 to 36.
I like looking at pretty things.
It's even better when it comes in a pair.
Plus the good genes would be
passed down to the next generation.
You are way
above his league.
I think he's not bad.
He's
only got a special name.
Your name is good, too.
"A reputation that's well-known."
That's too obvious.
Boring!
Then let me come up with
a more romantic explanation.
Go ahead.
Let me think.
It's a little far-fetched,
but I'm sure you'll like it.
"I'd take the Yuhong Herb
and live in my dreamland forever."
Have you heard of that?
No.
What's that about?
Legend has it that in the Kunlun Mountains
exists a plant named Yuhong Herb.
If one accidentally takes it,
they would fall asleep for 300 years.
Hong Xiaoyu.
Hong Yu, Yuhong.
Don't you think your name
could actually mean
the Yuhong Herb?
I like this explanation!
That's what I'll tell people in the future!
The rain seems to be getting heavier.
Our Shi Yi is 26 years old.
Though she's stunning,
she's never been in love.
May Buddha bless her!
If she and the chemistry professor
are meant to be together,
then please stop the rain!
Buddha said yes!
I dreamt of Chang'an a lot when I was little.
I loved reading
stories about this place.
That's why I've always wanted to visit here.
You told me that before.
Go to sleep.
I don't think the rain will stop.
[Meilin]
Hello?
Hello.
You are getting famous now!
Producers are lining up to have you dub their shows.
A producer contacted me
and wanted you to be a supporting actress in his movie.
He said your look and temperament
are perfect for the role.
I told him
to drop that thought
and that you've turned down
quite a few auditions.
You only want to be a good dubber,
not an actress.
You won't even go on TV programs.
Xiaoyu is still asleep.
It's not convenient to talk.
I'll call you back later.
No need.
I've sent your schedule to your mailbox.
Send me a message
if you have any questions.
Okay.
[Shi Yi  One or two days off in the weekend, snatch a little leisure from a busy life]
[Unread]
[An E-mail from Zhousheng Chen   Recording Assistant-Zhang Mengmeng]
[Zhousheng Chen]
[An E-mail from Zhousheng Chen]
When I walked out
of the lab at 4:36 am,
the rain has stopped.
If it isn't raining at 11:30,
then let's meet at the Azure Dragon Temple at 12:00.
Xiaoyu!
Get up! Come on!
The rain has stopped!
What?
It stopped raining!
Shi Yi, let me pick an outfit for you!
I already have something in mind!
You'll look good in that dress!
Yeah, make close up shots.
Focus on my face.
Look at me!
Shi Yi!
You are so smitten
that you are blushing!
Don't tell me you're sunburnt.
You are here early, Mr. Zhousheng!
But of course, we are even earlier.
Shi Yi insisted on coming here
20 minutes early so that we wouldn't be late.
I was worried about the traffic.
Sure.
Usually I'd be 15 minutes early
when I'm meeting up with my friends.
I spent five minutes
just now looking for the ticket office,
but I was told that it's actually
free of charge.
Let's go then.
Okay.
Let's walk the other way.
Has anyone visited the Azure Dragon Temple before?
No.
Okay.
Now that you are here,
you first need to know about its history.
In 1996,
the State Council declared
the Azure Dragon Temple
to be a critical national relic.
In 1986,
the temple brought in over 1,000
cherry blossom trees
and planted them here.
There are altogether 12
rare species of cherry blossom here.
Speaking of enjoying cherry blossoms,
one must come to the Azure Dragon Temple.
Why you may ask.
Because the temple has
[No sound recordings]
all the cherry blossom varieties,
[Expected to record over 10 hours]
the oldest cherry blossom planting history,
the most precious cherry blossom culture,
and the most beautiful cherry blossom scenery
that's worth appreciating.
All right.
Would everyone please follow me?
Let's go inside
and take a look.
Please keep up!
Would everyone please follow me? Let's go inside
and take a look.
Is the recording bad?
There's too much noise.
Let's go over there.
You seem to like Xi'an a lot.
When I first came here,
a friend of mine at the institute
gave me
a guide book to Xi'an.
If you like it,
I could give it to you.
This city
is full of stories.
True.
It was the capital of several dynasties.
Do you like reading?
Yes.
I set aside
a certain amount of time every day for reading.
What kind of books do you like?
As long as it's interesting,
I'd read it.
Have you visited
old-fashioned libraries,
where numerous books
are put on the wooden shelves?
Old-fashioned libraries?
Yes.
There are some in Jiangsu and Zhejiang.
My parents took me there when I was little.
The place I often go to
also has wooden shelves,
but they are all occupied
by bottles and containers
and all kinds of dangerous instruments.
Most of the things are
off limits.
It sounds interesting.
You think so?
Any incorrect operation
could lead to burns
or even explosions.
It's a high-risk profession!
If it's really like what you said,
who would want to work in a lab?
Well, it's not that scary.
But your operations must be correct.
When I first started uni,
there was one night
where I suddenly remembered
that I left something
in the lab.
I thought
I could go fetch it at six the next morning.
But at the next morning,
the empty lab somehow
had an explosion.
Half of the lab was blown up.
Luckily,
I got up five or six minutes late that morning.
Otherwise,
I don't know
what would have happened to me.
And then what happened?
And then...
Things didn't turn out too bad.
The dozen of samples I made
were still there.
And I moved them
to the lab next door
that afternoon
and continued the tolerance test.
Thank you!
What's the matter?
My legs look short.
Make them look longer!
Even longer?
Yea! Come on!
Fine!
Hurry up! One more!
Like this...
Hong Xiaoyu suggested we come
to the Azure Dragon Temple because of me.
I've heard of this place before.
There's also an Azure Dragon Temple
in that movie.
But the two temples are different.
This temple was built in the Sui Dynasty,
later than the one in the movie.
I don't mean
to disturb you guys.
But this place is too small.
[Do good and receive good karma]
We should've gone to see the terracotta warriors.
At least the place is bigger there.
Where shall we go next?
I have a student,
whose family opened
a tea house in the neighborhood.
If you guys don't mind,
he'd like to invite you guys for some sea.
He's the guy you met
yesterday, by the way.
Do you have time?
Yes. I do.
She's free all day!
The tea house is nearby.
I'll bring you guys there.
I've been observing you two
from behind!
You are reserved, and he's polite.
You guys look like you are on a blind date!
Keep your voice down!
You are really...
Is something wrong?
Would you guys like to take a picture?
No. It's okay.
All right!
Take one! With him!
Let's go!
Gosh!
Miss Shi Yi, are you here for work?
Xiaoyu is. I'm here to keep her company.
I've never been to Xi'an,
so I wanted to come
and have a look around.
Xi'an has
many interesting places.
It'd take a while for you to visit them all.
Please take a seat, everybody.
Thank you!
Would you guys like to play some games?
Aeroplane chess, checkers,
or poker?
I'm okay with anything.
Aeroplane chess and checkers
are a little boring.
But you don't know how to play poker.
It's okay. I'll watch you guys play.
All right, then.
Mr. Zhousheng, do you play poker?
Yes.
Then I'll go get the cards.
Do you wanna check out
your pictures?
Let me see.
Are you sure?
I may as well show you after photographing.
Let me see that one first.
I haven't photoshopped it yet.
Come on.
Here we go!
The last one.
This one.
Look good?
This...This one is nice!
Have you visited the Giant Wild Goose Pagoda
and the Ancient City Wall?
We are going to visit the Ancient City Wall
but we won't go to the Giant Wild Goose Pagoda.
Why is that?
The Giant Wild Goose Pagoda is very beautiful.
You should go check it out.
Our hotel is right
across the street
from the pagoda.
Then the place you guys are staying is very nice!
That hotel is nice for sure.
It was still under construction
when I graduated from the college there.
Mr. Zhousheng,
do you have
any hobbies?
I have quite a few.
I like watching TV dramas.
What's your favorite
TV drama?
"A Step into the Past".
"A Step into the Past"?
Even a chemistry professor likes time-travel dramas!
It's even "A Step into the Past"!
Do you remember
my ex during college?
He also loved that show.
He watched it four times.
I watched it
over 70 times.
To be specific, it'd be
79 times.
79 times?
Wouldn't you get bored?
I think it's quite interesting.
And now I can remember every scene
and every line in that show.
Good for you!
Come on, "Landlord."
You go first.
Do I go first?
Yes.
This one. You can put it here.
Not bad.
You've got a good hand, I think.
If I go first,
I think I've won.
[Leyouyuan]
We'll take a bus to go back.
We'll take a taxi.
See you!
I think he is
into you.
But why did he leave
without even asking for your phone number?
Let's go.
Let's wait for a while.
It's hard to get a taxi here.
Take a look at this.
Are we here?
The Azure Dragon Temple.
I give up!
How long will it take to walk back?
How about we walk back?
No way. It's too far.
Are you going to the Giant Wild Goose Pagoda?
We are going to the hotel across
from the Giant Wild Goose Pagoda.
Here's the thing.
Someone called me
to give you a ride.
Who?
He Shan. Do you know him?
Yes. He's my friend.
One of you has the last name Shi,
and the other Hong.
This gentleman is a photographer.
Right?
Yes. You are right.
Please get in the car.
-Thank you, sir!
-Thank you!
Here.
Watch your head.
Professor.
Come in.
A lady named Tong is here to see you.
She's my friend.
Let her in.
Then I'll go help her fill out her particulars at the gate.
Okay.
[Wedding Invitation]
I'm having a meeting in Xi'an,
so I dropped by to bring you this.
Congratulations!
That's it?
I hope you two have a happy life.
I'm here
to tell you
that you are the only one
whom I've ever
wanted to marry.
Even now I'm still torn.
If you are hesitant
or confused about
your upcoming marriage,
you should talk
to Zhou Wenchuan, your fiance,
not me.
If you are here to bring me the invitation,
it's well received.
Thank you.
Maybe I'm not hesitant.
I'm just thinking about the past.
My wedding is scheduled early next month.
You will be there, right?
I should be back
at that time.
I'll see you then.
My colleague is still waiting for me downstairs.
I'm leaving.
Okay.
Professor.
What's the relationship
between you and Miss Tong?
There's nothing
between her and I.
That's good to know.
Why are you so happy?
Well, she came with a smile
and left in tears.
I thought she was your...
And I was worried about Shi Yi...
Why would you
think of Shi Yi at this moment?
Professor, stop playing dumb.
Shi Yi likes you.
It's very obvious.
I think she fell in love with you
when she first met you at the airport.
You treat her differently too.
Not only did you visit the Azure Dragon Temple with her,
you even called a taxi for her.
If you don't have feelings for her,
then what's all this?
Is that all you think about
when you're here?
I...I've been thinking about the experiments.
I'll do the experiment.
Close the door.