[English subtitles are available]
[Forever and Ever]
[Episode 26]
Professor Zhousheng.
Thank goodness for your attorney friend,
or else
our efforts would have been in vain.
Yeah.
These are some dishes we ordered for you.
Thank you.
We should be the ones to say that.
Yeah.
We have ordered afternoon tea as well.
It's our treat.
There's no need for that.
It's okay, we have already placed the order.
We will leave you to it.
Take your time. See you.
-We have to go now.
Bye, Professor.
Bye.
The lab in Xi'an
is almost done.
You two have no problem
going there first, right?
No problem at all.
Same here.
I'll be fine as long as I visit my parents
on Mid-Autumn Festival and have dinner with them.
Okay.
By the way, Professor.
Your wife works in Shanghai
while you'll work in Xi'an.
How are you going to maintain your relationship?
Our relationship
does not require deliberate maintenance.
That may be the now.
What about in the future?
Living apart for long periods
would definitely cause problems.
What if...
I'm just saying, what if
a very attractive admirer shows up?
What would you do?
Yeah, what would you do?
Her admirers
seem to have never stopped appearing.
Are you not jealous?
It's doesn't feel good,
but it's not a big problem.
You should at least
try to solve the problem.
She never gave
any of them a chance.
To be honest, Professor.
This is my very first time
seeing someone being jealous
and calm at the same time.
Respect.
My wife
is flawless in every aspect.
So it's natural
she has numerous admirers.
For something that's natural,
it is best
to cope with shifting events by sticking to a fundamental principle.
That makes sense.
Miss Shi Yi,
may I know what is
your criteria of spouse selection?
I love scientists.
Especially someone who studies Venus.
Why does it have to be
someone who studies Venus?
Because
they are special.
In what way?
[Entertainment News: Young Dubbing Voice Actor Shi Yi's Criteria of Spouse Selection]
In our neighboring planets,
only on Venus,
will you be able to see the sun rise from the west
and set in the east.
The fact that it is so special
makes the person who studies it even more special.
[Entertainment News: Young Dubbing Voice Actor Shi Yi's Criteria of Spouse Selection]
Miss Shi Yi.
I am sorry, I need to go backstage.
Thank you all.
Chen, she's your wife, right?
I think I've seen her at the gate.
That's right, she's our professor's wife.
Oh yeah?
Our professor's wife is pretty outstanding as well.
You are young and promising
while your wife is multi-talented.
What a perfect match!
Enjoy your lunch.
Okay.
[Shi Yi]
Hello?
Miss Shi.
Are you here for Professor Zhousheng?
He's having lunch
and will be here soon.
Professor Zhousheng.
I'll head in.
Is he your colleague?
Yeah.
How did he know me?
He probably saw you
on TV just now.
On TV?
I don't go on shows
or give interviews.
A playback of the award ceremony?
A backstage interview.
I thought you wouldn't be able to see that.
Why did you come here?
I'm here to ask you for a favor.
Your father-in-law
asked me to ask you for help.
A guest speaker for the lecture
won't make it.
He is an astrophysicist.
So it occurred to my father
that you are an astrochemist.
He doesn't want to let his students down.
So he asked me to ask you
if you can fill the role.
That's it?
Why didn't you just tell me over the phone?
I will go to
the recording studio this afternoon.
And I happen to pass by
your institute,
so I thought I could come see you.
What, are you not happy to see me?
Of course I am happy.
Hi, Miss Shi.
-Hello, Miss Shi.
-Miss Shi.
You guys continue.
We will head in first.
Are you going or not?
Sure.
Okay. It's either
today, tomorrow, or the day after.
Let's make it happen today.
I am only available today.
Today?
Do you have time to get ready?
No need to get ready.
I can still remember the
content of my lecture.
The materials are all
in my computer as well.
Wait for me then.
I will go get ready.
I'll head up then.
You go park the car.
Okay.
Wait.
You can lecture,
but don't smile too many times.
Why?
You smile is
too lovable.
No smiling.
I usually don't smile
when I'm with strangers.
Go on then.
See you.
What do you want for dinner?
I don't know, what do you want to eat?
The class today was so interesting,
-right?
-Yeah.
Miss Shi.
Is that you?
I am from the winter vacation class.
Last year's winter vacation class.
Lin Jia?
Yeah, that's me.
You still remember me?
Shi Yi, are you Shi Yi?
I watched your drama.
You are even involved in plays now?
I am about to graduate,
so I am too busy
to follow you.
That was a rare occasion. I was doing my friend a favor.
Miss Shi.
Can I get your autograph?
Sure.
Thank you.
Can I write the name of the drama?
Absolutely.
There is no notice about a big shot coming.
Is it over already?
It shouldn't be.
At least let us hear the end.
Miss Shi, you are so talented.
Miss Shi, please sign your name here.
Okay.
Miss Shi, you are amazing.
-Miss Shi, please give me your autograph.
-Thank you.
Miss Shi, me too.
Okay.
Miss Shi, me as well.
Miss Shi, can I have your autograph?
That's it, everybody.
That's the end of today's lecture.
Thank you.
Professor.
Is there no Q&A session
for today?
I am sorry.
Because this is a last-minute lecture.
So there is
no time reserved for questions.
Besides,
my wife has been waiting for me downstairs
for a long time.
Your wife?
You're a married man, sir?
Getting married at such a young age.
What if you regret it one day?
Yeah.
You should ask
my wife that question
instead of me.
Because she is way more talented than I am.
I am only an ordinary guy
that happens to meet a woman
exceeding my expectation
at the right age.
If I didn't marry her,
I would have regretted it for the rest of my life.
That's so admirable.
Yeah.
Professor, there's no need to answer questions.
Why don't you talk about your love story?
Exactly, exactly.
Let's talk about that.
All right, from now on,
everyone
may ask one question
relevant to today's lecture.
You may start now.
Professor, I have a question.
Professor, you said
Venus was rather unpopular
in terms of planetary research.
Then why
did you choose it?
Venus to me,
is the future of earth.
I want to see the future.
What turned a planet
that was once livable,
with all kinds of species,
into this planet
that has an uncontrolled greenhouse effect.
In fact, by studying Venus,
we better understand
how to protect our own planet.
Of course.
I also wish that human beings, in the future,
could transform Venus
into our second home.
Professor,
the surface temperature of Venus
can reach up to 500 degrees.
Wouldn't it be too difficult to live there?
Yeah.
Yeah, it is indeed very hard.
High levels of radiation and corrosive acid rain
are no doubt
great challenges.
But our scientists
have never given up.
Since last century,
they have proposed
all kinds of solutions.
Such as building a sun shield
above its atmosphere
to improve its environment.
Or, to build a city above the clouds.
It's just that
implementing these ideas
would be really hard.
But anything is possible.
As long as we persist
long enough,
every impossibility
will become something possible.
Like what our ancestors
believed in.
They held the belief
that the sun would never rise from the west
and set in the east.
But if in the future,
our offspring
make it to Venus,
then they will see,
with their own eyes,
that the sun can come up from the west
and set in the east.
You know what?
You looked pretty cool
just now on the podium.
What?
Am I usually not?
Today you are exceptionally cool.
So,
I want to give you something as a reward.
What is it?
Pro...
-Hello, Professor.
Goodbye, Professor.
Let's go to the bigger house
to get two boxes of stuff first.
Let's go.
Go.
How long are we staying at home during the Mid-Autumn Festival?
Three days, I guess.
Then I will pack for four days.
In case you want to live at Grandma's place,
you can have extra clothes for change.
What are you writing?
Our wedding invitation.
I want to practice a little
before
writing the formal invitations.
Why do you write it yourself?
Do you have enough time?
100 pieces a day.
3000 pieces a month.
I should be able to complete it.
This is something that happens once in a lifetime.
I want to do everything myself.
Then go ahead.
I will go pack.
Last night,
I think I heard you coughing.
I will make a
stewed pear for you later.
Okay.
After we come back,
how about going to that house
and staying there for a couple of days?
Sure.
How about you wearing this tomorrow?
I will iron it for you.
Have some juice. I will iron it myself.
Thank you, Professor Zhousheng.
Let me give you a massage.
Dear customer,
how does it feel?
Pretty good.
Just the right amount of strength.
Please give me a five-star review if you like it.
Oh, right.
My mother asked me when will we arrive tomorrow?
Five o'clock sharp.
Okay.
My wife is beautiful, huh?
She used to be the beauty queen of her school.
I still think
my wife is more beautiful.
But no matter how beautiful your wife is,
my wife gave birth to her.
She can't beat my wife.
Isn't there a saying that goes like this,
the student surpasses the master?
You two college professors
are talking about
such pointless things.
Aren't you afraid that your students might laugh at you?
You see.
When a man compliments his partner,
there is nothing wrong about it.
It's usually the opposite that's bad.
Isn't it?
Yes.
The crabs in the two tanks
love to eat the same food,
but like different fruits.
I'll leave a note here.
All right, I got it.
You have been fiddling with these crabs
the whole night tonight.
[Longevity]
This is a birthday gift we prepared
for Chen's grandmother.
Thank you, Mom.
I'll go to bed.
By the way,
what do you want for breakfast tomorrow?
I will have rice balls and soy bean milk.
He wakes up at 5 am
and eats by himself.
You don't have to prepare anything for him.
Is that appropriate?
It's his first time staying here
and we don't make him breakfast?
It's okay, he won't mind.
Good night.
Look at the current me.
I'm prettier now.
[Eleven]
Why did you
use Eleven
as a pet name?
My grandmother gave me the name.
She thought the name my father gave me
was too literary.
Aren't all seniors like this?
They all believe that it's
easier to raise a child with a simple name.
Seeing you here
in the room where I grew up
feels kind of surreal.
Why?
I don't know.
Last time at your grandmother's place,
I slept with you in the bedroom where you used to live when you were a student.
How did you like it?
That night...
I believe that night,
you were more nervous than me.
As if you weren't nervous.
I was pretty calm.
It's just that...
What?
It's just on that night,
I couldn't sleep.
Because you smelled amazing.
I have never had
perfume
in the room where I sleep.
That's why I couldn't sleep.
Is it?
Yeah.
Your hair smells great,
also your pajamas.
You rascal.
How about smelling the perfume
once again tonight?
We are at your parent's place.
It's okay,
as long as I get back before daybreak.
Sure.
Mother, is he not home yet?
I think he went out for breakfast
and hadn't come home yet.
Why don't you go check on him?
Okay, I will check on him.
Checkmate.
Qin.
You lost again?
What a young man!
Mr. Qin
used to be the best player
in our community.
How about playing another round?
Okay.
Here.
You are pretty talented,
young man.
Making such a special visit to our staff community,
did you fancy some professor
and hope to learn from him?
Mr. Shi, it must be Mr. Shi.
This kid's been talking about economies
since he sat down.
Mrs. Liu.
Mr. Qin and Mr. Li.
Here you are, Shi Yi.
You are back, Shi Yi.
My mother thought you had lost your way,
so she sent me downstairs to look for you.
This is?
Zhousheng Chen, my fiance.
We are about to hold our wedding ceremony.
Where do you work?
Judging from your age,
you must have just graduated with a PhD.
I graduated very early on.
I work in a research institute now.
Sounds good.
We're leaving.
Go ahead.
Go, go.
I'm leaving.
Okay.
Bye.
Okay, here.
Here, here, here, let me challenge you.
Have you had your breakfast?
Yeah.
What did you eat?
McDonalds.
Be specific.
I ate two burgers.
Did you drink milk?
Yeah.
Good.
So, you have been sitting there
since you finished your breakfast?
On my way back,
I heard them talking about economies.
So I sat down and had a chat with them.
They were having fun
and said, how about playing Chinese chess?
So I joined them.
You should go to my father if it's about economies.
That's his profession.
Isn't that so?
You're right.
I thought
if I intentionally guide the conversation,
they should switch the topic
to your family
or your father.
They watched you grow up
and told me a lot of
interesting stories about you.
Seriously, you and your witty tricks.
Let's take the stairs.
When I was a student,
I used to take the stairs.
You should experience it.
Why did you take the stairs?
I didn't like socializing I think.
The elevator is full of our neighbors
every time I go in there.
What I fear the most
was to say hello
to each and every one of them.
So I had to be mentally prepared
from the moment I went into the community,
all the way till I made it to my own home.
Are there no surveillance cameras here?
Nope.
Then it's very dangerous
for you to do this.
What if the light
goes out one day?
Are you not scared?
I think it did go out in the past.
You always look at things
differently.
I just imagined
what you said just now
and I felt a bit concerned.
Then let me feel touched
for the past me.
I have a secret to tell you.
What is it?
I used to have a crush on a senior schoolmate.
He was 2 years older than me.
He was also a straight-A student.
Was he a better student than me?
Not really.
One day, I brought him here
and wanted to make things clear.
You took the initiative?
Yeah, you know me.
I am pretty straightforward.
I usually speak my mind.
True. It's also one of your strong points.
Are you jealous?
Why should I be jealous?
I mean, it's too late to be, isn't it?
Don't you want to know
what I told him?
Were you two a couple?
Didn't you say
I was your first boyfriend?
I am kidding.
You are the first
and only boyfriend I have.
Senior Zhousheng,
will you please help me
with my math homework?
No problem.
How about biology and geography?
Sure.
♫Time can't steal memories♫
Chinese and English?
Fine.
I was good at every subject.
♫With all my strength♫
In that case, you are fully responsible for
♫To find traces of you♫
tutoring our kids in the future.
And I won't take care of it, not even a minute.
Well, everyone has their own ambition.
Let them develop on their own.
♫Spring flowers and autumn moon♫
♫Hidden in my heart♫
Okay, I will be responsible
♫Write words for you♫
until they get their PhD.
That sounds more like it.
♫Tenderly and carefully♫
♫Rewrite the end of the past♫
After you, Senior Zhousheng.
♫Let the story continue♫
♫You're in my dreams♫
♫It's getting clearer and clearer♫
Mr. Chen, you are hanging the lantern?
Lin.
Could you check
if it's tilted or not?
Okay.
That will do.
[Lotus Fragrance Pavilion]
Okay.
That's still tilted.
That's close, right?
It's the old madam's 90th birthday.
Everything must be perfect.
Only if the job is done right,
will I rest easy.
All right.
Come eat when you're done.
I will be waiting for you.
All right, you go ahead.
Okay.
Good for you.
This little yard is gonna be full of people.
I don't care so much about other people.
As for the other great-uncles and grandparents,
they'd better come here less.
I just want to watch my own great-uncle and his wife
live a happy life
behind the closed door.
Every time when I see them
sitting on the couch without saying a word,
all I can feel
is a sense of joy.
The mere thought of someone coming inside
makes me want to
kick them out.
Why are you sitting here alone?
Isn't it cold?
It's okay, I got the cushion.
Brother, come sit.
This is the mooncake I made.
Have a try.
Is it good?
Yeah.
Not good enough.
I will make some more tomorrow.
It's not the Mid-Autumn Festival yet.
Why didn't you tell us
that you were coming?
I could have worn something more formal.
Do you know who she is?
Of course, I do.
From now on,
when I see Mr. Zhousheng,
I don't have to be that overcautious.
The biggest shareholder has been replaced.
Yes, from now on, I am the guest
and she is the hostess.
Here, here, here.
Let me show you around.
Everything here is yours.
You can come here as often as you want.
No need to ask anyone for permission.
Come, come.
This way, please.
The business here
has been doing pretty well over the years.
Do you know
the name of this room?
It's called a drying room.
When I was a kid,
my grandfather gave me one Guqin,
which was said to be from someone famous.
The manufacturing process takes two years,
one of which
is spent to dry in a room.
Like these ones here,
waiting to see the outside world.
Now that I think about it,
our ancestors
have left us many things
and it seems that all of them
went through such a process.
Not just for the people, but the stuff as well.
We have to endure loneliness
and hardship
until we finally achieve greatness.
Miss Shi sure can
give good lessons.
Come on.
They were joking around just now,
or were they serious?
What do you mean?
How many shares did you actually give me?
I have given you
all my shares.
All of them?
This is my parents' wish.
My father said that my mother passed away early
and she wouldn't see her future daughter-in-law.
So they specifically left this
as a gift.
So just take it as
a welcome gift
for their future daughter-in-law.
Thank you, my parents-in-law
for granting me great fortunes.
Your parents gave it to me,
so this is my asset now?
Yeah, yours.
What about the house in Shanghai?
The house in Shanghai
is also something my father
left for his future daughter-in-law.
They all belong to me?
They all belong to you.
Here is the tricky part.
What if one day, I don't want to be with you anymore
and drive you out of my house and deprive you of everything you once owned?
What will you do?
Oh, yeah.
Good news is I have a skill to depend on
and make myself a living.
As for accommodation,
I can only go live
at the institute's dormitory.
You little poor thing.
Then you must listen to me.
Mr. Zhousheng, how are you?
I heard from Mr. Zhao
that your wife is here,
so I came here to say hello to her.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too.
Are we back in production?
Yeah.
From now on,
we will be the pioneers among the environment friendly companies.
I have learnt my lesson now.
This is the boss from the dying factory.
This is my wife, Shi Yi.
All the shares my father used to own
are now under her name.
Our biggest shareholder.
How are you?
Today, the three of us
came here to see our biggest shareholder.
I am afraid someone might
gossip behind our backs,
saying we are meeting the biggest shareholder in private
without taking them with us.
How happy would your parents be
if they saw
how you are right now.
His parents
were really kind-hearted.
Chen's mother
received compliments from almost everyone.
And Chen's father
was polite to almost everyone.
He is a real gentleman.
I had never seen him get mad at anyone.
Like last time,
in that ancestral hall, right?
No need to bring that up.
It's all in the past.
He's like his father since he was a kid.
They're very alike.
Yeah.
You have an eye for men.
Yeah, that's right.
Yeah, I have a special eye for men.
You really do.
The workshops and factories
are in different places.
I will show them to you
when I am available.
Why did we suddenly come here today?
It's like
completing the last step of the ritual.
I had to personally hand down to you
the wedding gifts
my parents prepared for you.
The man just now said that
your father got angry in the ancestral hall.
Why is that?
They didn't agree to move
my mother's spirit tablet into the hall.
So my father
had a big fight with them
and swore from then on,
he would never kneel down before the ancestors.
So he never did it ever since?
What about you?
Same.
They are all my
uncles and aunties.
Nice to meet you all.
You go upstairs first,
I need to talk to them about something.
You asked for me?
Will you go to the ancestral hall of Zhou family with me?
To have a meal?
By now,
they should have finished their lunch.
How about having it at home
and then go over there?
We haven't seen each other for a long time,
even if he had finished his meal,
he would love to have another one with me.
Please have some tea, Great-uncle's wife.
You don't have to call me that.
Mrs. Zhou told me
that seniority in the family can't be confused.
She also told us to take good care of you.
I was afraid
you wouldn't come back.
Why?
Because last time...
Never mind, forget it.
I've prepared for you
new bed sheet, new bed cover.
Everything is brand new.
Are you happy with that?
Yeah.
Chen's uncles and aunties
came to visit Mrs. Zhou before.
But judging from today's situation,
soon, everything concerning Zhou family,
like the clan, the ancestral hall
and everything
she's responsible for
will be handed over to you.
Really?
That's for sure.
There's no hiding from it.
Oh, yeah.
What is that?
Before you came,
Great-uncle specially asked me to prepare this.
It's Qielan incense.
Enjoy your break, Great-uncle's wife.
Call me if you need anything.
They are all gone?
Yeah.
I never knew you were interested in that.
Why are you suddenly interested in that?
I asked some TCM doctors and
they said this fragrance
has the function of refreshing one's mind.
If you are available,
will you come with me
to visit Grandmother?
My mother said,
Grandmother kept herself in the yard
and wouldn't come out.
Other people couldn't do anything about it.
If we both went there,
the problem might be solved.
Okay.
Let me reapply my makeup.
How long will you need?
15 minutes?
15 minutes.
All right, I will go write the wedding invitation.
Go take a break.
Apart from eating, sleeping
and going to the laboratory,
you have been writing them in your spare time these days.
I've been busy lately,
which disrupted my schedule.
I can only do this
whenever I have some free time.
How about I help you?
My handwriting is not bad.
Let me deal with it.
All right, I'll leave it to you.
Why are you being so petty?
It's the invitation for my own wedding,
why can't I have a look?
It's not time yet.
You still have 13 minutes.
In fact,
I wrote you something as well.
What is it?
It's not time yet for you to see it.
You have only 12 minutes left.
Try to persuade her.
She is like a child. I am helpless.
I will go pack up
the clothes she will be wearing these two days.
Grandmother.
Chen.
You're here.
She forgot about me again.
Shi Yi.
Grandmother.
Where's the kid?
My great-grandson. Did you not bring him with you?
Your great-grandson.
He's doing homework right now.
He's only three years old, what kind of homework is he doing?
He loves to do homework.
If he likes it...
Having interest is the most important thing.
Good, good, good.
Come over here.
Do you want to have another kid?
Do we want to have another kid?
Yeah.
It's up to her.
Do you want to have another kid?
Yeah, of course.
Did you hear that?
Yes, I did.
You gotta work hard.
Work harder.
Yeah, I will.
Grandmother.
How about going back to the house tonight
and have dinner with us?
No.
That's troublesome.
There are too many people there.
I get annoyed just looking at them.
But I miss you.
We finally
came back home.
Partly for the Mid-Autumn Festival,
partly for you.
Will you please
go there for our sake?
Okay, okay.
Let's get ready then.
All right.
Is your kid in kindergarten?
Yes, he is.
Watch your step.