My Girlfriend is an Alien
Episode 16
I woke up so early to exercise.
I haven't slept enough and I haven't eaten breakfast.
What's wrong, Song Da?
You still have to get up early?
Why don't you run for a while and get some fresh air?
Please don't affect my work.
I'll go take a shower first. I'll treat you to breakfast later.
You're a bit heartless.
I hope that I can be with you forever
You're like a flame in the air
Is that so?
My unease is scattered
You appear in the vast world, grasping my light
You're covered in light
Melt me once
This is better.
Hey, Song.
Team leader, why are you here?
Ouyang Zuo values you a lot.
He said that you're a newbie and asked me to teach you.
This artiste is late.
She didn't follow the notice and left.
Forget it. I'll wait for her.
No, team leader.
I just took a picture.
Look.
Your chance is wrong.
Come on.
If you want to make a man look good,
you have to lower your body.
Like this, team leader?
Knock it up.
Like this?
Come on. I'll help you.
This way.
Team leader, is that okay?
Team leader. Team leader, what are you doing?
Look.
This...
Who? What are you doing?
Misunderstanding.
I'm the chief editor of the Tang's Club, Cui Yongzhi.
I'm helping him adjust the position.
It's all a misunderstanding.
Song, explain it to me.
It's our chief editor, Cui Yongzhi.
Chief editor Cui.
I thought you were a hooligan.
You're doing this in the daytime.
I'm doing this for the documentary.
I'm teaching him how to adjust the position more professionally.
More professional?
Isn't this my documentary?
I should be the one to adjust the position.
Besides, the contract emphasizes that
in order to protect my privacy,
only one cameraman is allowed to follow up.
Yes. Yes.
I'll leave then.
I won't bother you.
Song, good luck.
I'm leaving.
Good luck?
Do I need to worry about it?
How is it?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Don't just stand there. Have breakfast.
Why is this girl so generous?
How did I know she's that kind of person?
I'm just here to work.
No matter what you do in the future,
you have to protect yourself first.
You have to resist the front-runners of this kind of workplace.
The main thing is that I didn't see it before.
What didn't you see?
I think you're very cruel to me.
You're so soft to others.
This kind of person is a stubborn person.
He's a stubborn person.
If you put up with him once,
he will challenge your bottom line endlessly.
I know.
Next time, I'll...
Next time? There's still next time?
I just said it.
Forget it. It's no use telling you.
You're so skinny.
You should work out your body first.
I'll teach you some defense techniques.
Okay.
You have to calm down when you encounter something.
Especially someone like you,
who has a weak body and physical condition,
you can't compare yourself to others.
What should I compare myself to?
What do you think?
How would I know?
Of course, you have to compare yourself to skills.
Skills?
Come on, Awu.
Give me your fist.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Today, I'll teach you a shoulder drop.
Let's do some exercises.
A fist fight.
If the opponent reveals a hand,
hit me.
First, do a shoulder drop.
Grab his arm with your other hand.
You have to stick your upper body to his body.
Put your hand in his wrist.
This will be easier to use.
Okay.
Turn around and close your legs.
Use your hip to touch his abdomen.
Then,
pull your right arm towards your waist.
Okay.
Come on, let's try it.
Here we go.
Yes, the upper body is too far from me.
You have to put your foot closer to me.
This will make it easier for you to lift your hips.
Turn around.
Come on, three, two, one.
Let's go.
Are you okay?
Use your power of the red square.
What red square?
I'm not okay.
I'm fine.
Use your power of the red square.
What power of the red square?
It's the power of your ancestral 18 times.
Your ancestral 18 times?
Three, two, one.
Go.
Think about the safety distance.
Lie in your arms.
Give me all your courage.
Tell me,
is he taking advantage of me?
What advantage?
Are you listening to me?
I'm being serious.
What's wrong with him?
He took me to practice defense today.
I'm about to fall apart.
He made you fall apart?
It's not what you think.
He's taking me to the edge.
Like the cannon ball against Luo Jin.
Think about it. He's going to fall apart.
He just wants to play with you.
See if he's interested in you.
Stop.
Acting is acting.
I'll help you.
The front is the peach blossom.
The back is the peach blossom.
Look, the peach blossom.
Chu Xingyan and me.
He's such a big star.
Who am I?
You don't lack legs.
And he's acting like that
because he likes you.
I don't want to be a fish in his fish pond.
There can be many fish ponds.
He has his own sea.
You have your own waves.
I just heard you say that
he's gentle, considerate, and caring.
Except for missing occasionally
and not knowing how to make public relations.
He's not lacking at all.
Imagine falling in love with a handsome guy.
How interesting.
Remember,
more friends, more ways,
more partners, more families.
I don't want to fall in love now.
I just want to finish my job.
It's not a conflict with love.
You can pay the public expenses
while you're in love.
Such a good thing.
I can't go.
No.
I can't make the same mistake
for the second time.
He doesn't suit me.
Remember,
he doesn't suit me.
It's so troublesome.
Don't be nervous.
I'm looking out the door.
He's not hiding from you.
So many reporters.
I guess he's a star.
Let's go back.
Lin Hao, come and look.
Look over there.
Lin Hao, come.
Come and look.
Look at the camera.
Lin Hao, look at the camera.
Look here.
Look at the camera.
Okay, okay.
You're so annoying.
Are you here to shoot a new drama?
Hao Hao, you are the best female lead in this season.
Do you have anything to say?
Sorry, sorry.
We don't accept any interviews.
Please continue to follow the official news.
Thank you.
Please forgive us.
Okay, okay.
Chu Xinran, you're so nice.
Chu Xinran.
They haven't been on the same stage for three years.
Is there a new drama to cooperate with?
Say something.
Chu Xinran.
Please give us some news.
You and Mr. Lin are going to break up.
Chu Xinran.
Chu Xinran, you're so nice.
Is there a new drama?