The Long Ballad
Episode 1
According to the date of the photo of the INS,
I found the two models.
Then I entered the hotel corridor surveillance of the suite.
I clearly photographed their entry and exit time.
They were deliberately disguised
as leaving the new room.
And they performed repeatedly at the door of the room.
I took three shots.
I finally chose the first version
and cut it into the video of the three-person video of the victim.
Now, with this surveillance,
it proves that you were maliciously harmed.
I have called the police.
I can soon catch the person who framed you.
That's great.
Then, we will send the surveillance video to the PR company.
Soon, everyone will know that you are innocent.
Sister Na has already informed me
that the movie will start normally according to the original plan.
Congratulations, Xing Yan.
Thank you.
From now on,
no one can call my boyfriend
a thug.
When I was young, my family was very strict.
Everything was arranged by my mother.
The only happy thing was that
my father brought me here to ride a horse.
Your mother is too strict.
She thinks riding a horse is a waste of time.
But I am very envious of those
who are free on the horse farm.
So I will never forget one day
when my father secretly stole my father's car.
I was so happy.
That day, my father secretly brought me here to ride a horse.
It was like how I am bringing you here now.
But not long after,
when I just learned how to ride a horse,
my mother found out.
She had a big fight with my father.
She said that she shouldn't have brought me here.
But when I was young,
I was envious of children like you.
You can get anything you want.
Unlike me,
I have a toy.
I have to beg my mother.
That's nothing.
When I was young, I went to my neighbor's house to steal fruit.
I was caught by a police officer.
I was acting like a ghost at night.
Later, my father found out.
He broke several of my chains.
That's great.
When I was young, I even ran away from home.
But the farthest place I went
was the door of the community.
Running away from home is also like running away from home.
Why not?
That's the only good thing.
The shop is about to reopen.
The time I spend with you
won't be long.
Miss Song.
Hello?
I'm Chu Xing Yan's mother.
I want to buy you a meal tonight.
Is that all right?
I'm fine, Auntie.
Okay. I'll send you the address.
She's a young lady who just came into my apartment.
There's a small hotel in our house
with the best restaurants in the city
and the world's best chefs.
I hope Miss Song will like it.
Thank you, Mrs. Chu.
You're too kind.
Hello, Chef.
Miss Song, this way, please.
Here, see what you want to eat.
Thank you.
This is Evan, a chef who came back from France to study.
He's good at cooking all kinds of top-notch Western dishes.
We brought these ingredients from France.
The cooking method is very complicated and the texture is very delicate.
Miss Song, you can try it.
There are foreign words on it.
I don't know them.
It's Spanish.
Miss Song, take a look.
If you don't like it,
I'll ask them to change a Chinese-style menu.
No need, Mrs. Chu.
I can do it.
In that case, I'll choose for you.
Okay.
I'll have the one I usually eat.
Here, Miss Song.
You're welcome.
Please.
Okay.
By the way, Miss Song,
I heard that your family also owns a restaurant.
Whenever you have a chance,
bring me to try it.
I usually like to try snacks from all over the world.
Our family is an outdoor farm.
Snacks are like fried skewers and spicy hot pot.
The price is relatively cheap.
That should be very beautiful.
Here, start.
Okay.
Miss Song,
if you have something to say, I'll just say it.
Okay.
I'll treat you as my goddaughter.
You don't have to work so hard anymore.
You can choose from many positions in our company.
Also, give your parents a shop.
Then your parents won't have to work so hard anymore.
What do you think?
Thank you, Mrs. Chu.
But...
By the way, Miss Song,
what kind of boy do you like?
I have many friends who are good-looking.
Mrs. Chu,
I appreciate your kindness.
But...
As long as you give up Chu Xing Yan.
Why?
Because...
you don't deserve it.
Okay.
Let's start.
Enjoy.
I'll treat you as my goddaughter.
You can choose from many positions in our company.
Also, give your parents a shop.
Then your parents won't have to work so hard anymore.
What kind of boy do you like?
I have many friends who are good-looking.
I appreciate your kindness.
But...
As long as you give up Chu Xing Yan.
Why?
Because...
you don't deserve it.
If I can't even get my graduation certificate,
and I have to part with the Chu family,
can I really deserve it?
Thank you, friends in the media,
and friends who care about movies all over the world.
Next, let's welcome the director, Lin Sen,
to tell us about the new journey of his movie.
Thank you.
First of all, I'm honored to be the director.
After three months of preparation,
I finally meet you.
Thank you for your support.
Now let me introduce our leading actor,
Chu Xing Yan.
Now, let Chu Xing Yan say a few words.
Thank you.
The first time I came to this city,
I felt her enthusiasm.
It's very suitable for our movie theme,
Back to the past, say I love you.
I believe if it can really go back to the past,
this city must be full of beautiful memories.
I hope that when the movie is released,
it can meet everyone's expectations.
Our beautiful heroine is so good.
What do you want to say to your fans,
and our lead actors?
Hello, everyone.
I'm actress Lin Hao Hao.
I'm very happy and honored to be in this movie.
Thank you very much to the director and the actors
for giving me this opportunity.
The closer we get, the farther we get.
In this long night full of sleep,
I'm left alone with you.
When the sun and the moon are at the bottom of the sky,
the more I think about it, the more I miss you.
I'm glad that I can't find my way home.
It's been a long time.
I'm left alone with you.
Why are you so quiet?
I might not sleep well last night.
I want to ask you a question.
Hello, I want to see what you two are going to order.
She is waiting for me.
I've already ordered it.
You can start now.
The starry sky with the starry sky in my eyes.
It's the wish in your heart.
A part of the past that can't be erased.
It's usually a star.
At the moment when I'm trying to leave and go home,
is it happiness?
I want to be forgotten.
If I'm left alone with you,
I'm left alone with you.
The night that is so dark and foggy.
At least I want to be alone with you.
The sun behind the moonlight.
It's the answer in your heart.
A big and heavy dream.