(Kim Soo Hyun)
(Cha Seoung Won)
(One Ordinary Day)
(Bring the Murderer to Justice)
It's okay. Don't be afraid.
Let's go in.
Goodness, look at these hyenas.
It's okay. It's all right.
Hey, Hyun Soo. It's okay.
Look at me, Hyun Soo.
Hey, Hyun Soo.
This walk-through isn't about winning or losing.
It's like a stage play, okay?
They'll do whatever it takes to provoke you...
to shake you all up.
Do not react to the things they say or show you.
Just think of it as a stage play and watch them.
Okay?
Yes?
Okay.
Prosecutor, please proceed.
This walk-through of the scene...
will be conducted...
by Chief Park Sang Bum from Chungang Police Station.
Let's begin.
The accused and the victim...
drank together right here.
As you can see,
they almost finished an entire bottle of tequila.
LSD and ketamine...
are the two drugs that they took.
- Chief Park, look here! - Look at the camera.
Over here!
Hey, boyfriend.
Around midnight,
the accused, who was drunk,
started sexually assaulting the victim.
He undressed the victim.
Be more brutal.
The victim strongly resisted.
So in the end,
he began to threaten her with this knife.
The victim got these cuts on her palm...
while tussling with the accused.
And these are the traces that he left...
while attempting to destroy evidence immediately after the incident.
They started...
right here,
and through this staircase,
they went upstairs.
Let's go upstairs now.
After taking down the victim,
the accused pushed her onto the bed and tried to rape her.
In this process,
this lamp here was knocked to the floor.
The victim continued to resist.
So the accused, who was furious, stabbed her...
on the right side of the neck and the left side of the chest.
He stabbed her twice.
Then he flipped the victim, who had no strength left to fight back,
and stabbed her ten times in the back.
As you can see, the stab wounds in this horrible photo...
are the result of this.
Hyun Soo. Hey, what's wrong?
The nebulizer!
Does anyone have a nebulizer?
- The nebulizer! - Call an ambulance!
Get me a nebulizer.
What are you doing? Get lost, jerk!
Hey, breathe!
Breathe! Hey!
Hyun Soo! Darn it.
Before the walk-through of the crime scene, which began...
- at 9am this morning... - Reporter Kang.
Drinking, smoking, stress, and dealing with trashy reporters.
Guess what's the worst for the skin out of the four things.
Gosh, watch what you say.
I'm no trashy reporter.
He was on the verge of death,
yet you were busy getting that all on camera.
That's pure trash.
I call that a strong work ethic.
Despite the weather, dozens of civilians came...
and watched the police...
conduct a walk-through of the scene.
Ms. Seo, I'll see you tomorrow.
Pay for your drinks!
Darn it.
You didn't suffer a cardiac arrest,
so don't worry about the complications.
If everything's okay tonight, you can be discharged tomorrow.
Don't forget to take the nebulizer.
I think you're putting on an act.
That was the best choice you could make at that moment.
I've met so many guys like you,
who hide their true colours with their innocent façade.
I've been dealing with the likes of you for the past 30 years.
You are the last one, Hyun Soo.
The last one in my career as a police officer.
(Shin Joong Han Law Firm)
(Episode 6: Double Face)
What is this?
Gosh.
Darn it.
- Bring the murderer to justice! - Bring the murderer to justice!
(Ministry of Justice)
(Urgent Transportation)
Hyun Soo, I'm terribly sorry about this,
but as you can see,
I look terrible.
Darn, this is upsetting.
So that's why...
- Ms. Seo, go ahead. - Right.
Hyun Soo, I'll be first chair in your trial today.
- Right. - Well...
To be honest, this is my first trial as a lawyer,
so I'm actually a nervous wreck.
I'll do my best though.
Can you put your faith in me?
(Supreme Court of Korea)
(DUI Checkpoint)
What did you do next?
I confirmed that he wasn't the taxi owner...
and ordered a breathalyzer test after smelling alcohol on him.
However, I couldn't because the battery in it died.
You weren't able to administer the test,
so how did you know that he was drunk?
He had lost focus in his eyes,
and he reeked of alcohol.
That must be why you took him to the station.
Yes, driving under the influence is against the law.
That will be all.
You may cross-examine the witness.
Go and get them.
It'll be all right. I wish you luck.
(Defence)
(Prosecution)
Officer.
(Defence)
(Judge)
(Defendant)
Sorry about that. I apologize.
(Supreme Court of Korea)
Officer.
(Witness)
If I'm correct,
you must offer water during a breathalyzer test.
Did you?
What? No.
We were just clearing the DUI checkpoint.
I see.
And due to the battery dying,
you weren't able to administer a breathalyzer test.
That's right.
Did you have an arrest warrant?
- No. - Was an urgent arrest ordered?
(Prosecution)
What? No, ma'am.
There wasn't a warrant out for his arrest...
or an urgent arrest order,
and a breathalyzer test wasn't administered,
but you still took him to the station.
- The circumstances at that time... - On top of that,
on your way to the station,
you took a detour to the crime scene.
- Yes. - So answer me.
How many unlawful acts...
did you commit that night?
- What? - Unlawful acts?
Is the woman...
dead?
"Is the woman dead?"
What went through your mind...
when you heard that question?
At the time, I didn't think too much of it.
But when we found the knife in his jacket,
I realized what he meant.
Which was what?
I believed he was seeking confirmation.
So you're saying that he checked...
to see if the victim had died.
That's right.
That will be all.
"Is the woman dead?"
This was before he was arrested as a suspect,
so why would he have asked you this?
Well...
Because the victim being alive...
would only cause more trouble for him.
Could he have asked you this...
because he was worried about her?
Well...
He didn't sound worried if you ask me.
What about you then?
Did you feel bad for the victim?
Sorry?
Oh, yes. Of course, I...
Let's watch the dashcam footage together.
The call came in at 4am.
It was 4am, right?
The victim was 25 years of age.
Hold on a second. How many times was she stabbed?
I'm not sure. Probably 12 or 13.
Is that your lottery ticket?
(Jury)
- What on earth? - Seriously?
Officer,
were you so sad and upset for the victim...
that you matched the numbers on your lottery ticket?
Well...
But I...
(Judge)
That will be all.
(Prosecution)
The defendant's high school homeroom teacher...
will be summoned as the next witness.
In high school,
the defendant...
was advised to transfer schools.
Could you elaborate on that?
Hyun Soo...
(Witness)
Well, he fought with a classmate...
which led to a severe injury.
Two of his classmate's teeth got broken.
Physical altercation can happen between friends,
so a transfer of schools seems like cruel punishment.
Because it wasn't just a tussle.
Hyun Soo...
pushed him down the stairs.
(Jury)
During a physical altercation,
he pushed his classmate down the stairs.
One can say that both parties are responsible.
So why did the defendant have to transfer schools?
The friend's teeth didn't break...
before he tripped down the stairs.
It was the other way around.
What do you mean?
He was pushed off the stairs first.
And then Hyun Soo assaulted him...
while he lay unconscious.
(Jury)
Defendant.
(Defendant)
This is important,
so think long and hard...
before you tell us what really happened.
Well...
(Defendant)
My father partook in a strike...
to increase the base taxi fare by 30 cents.
The friend made snarky comments...
about the fact that it was only 30 cents.
From then on,
everyone teased me endlessly by calling me 30 Cents.
Why didn't you alert the school of the bullying?
Well...
I...
couldn't.
It would kill my father...
to have known.
Mr. Kim,
do you regret...
what happened in high school, and have you shown remorse?
Yes.
It was a lapse in judgement.
I apologized...
and also asked the friend for forgiveness.
That's right.
A lapse in judgement.
Today...
is my first day being first chair in a trial.
And I also slipped up.
Four years in college,
three years in law school,
and eight months of on-the-job training.
Despite the dozens of mock trials I participated in,
I made a mistake.
However,
isn't that the same for all of us?
The police officer who didn't provide water at the DUI checkpoint.
The officer who played his lottery ticket...
with numbers from the crime scene.
A son who physically assaulted another...
outraged by the insults made toward his father.
How can we say they are at fault?
Today in court, the prosecution failed...
to provide direct evidence linking my client to the murder.
All she did was blindly question his moral conduct.
"Is the woman dead?"
Is it logical and reasonable to assume that this one question...
is an admission of guilt?
That I can answer with certainty.
And my answer would be "no."
I rest my case.
Hyun Soo, do you remember this?
It looked like you had eaten fruit in her bedroom.
No, I don't recall eating the fruit.
There must've been a knife here.
Could it have been the knife you had?
That knife was in the kitchen.
What about the drugs?
The drugs that Hong Guk Hwa gave you that night.
Do you know where she got them?
Here, look.
This girl's name is Yoon Hyo Jung.
She and Hong Guk Hwa lived together.
Did she say anything about her?
The house is big enough,
so I let a friend stay with me.
But I had her leave after a big falling-out last week.
She did say she had a falling-out...
with a friend who was staying with her.
A falling-out?
Yes. They had a falling-out, and she had cut all ties with her.
I see.
They had a falling-out.
I'd say it's going very well so far.
The jurors are starting to listen to you.
I know this isn't easy, but try to stay strong.
I'll do my best too.
- Okay. - Good.
(Prosecution Fails to Present Conclusive Evidence)
(Chrysanthemum Murder Case, Was Prosecution Overly Ambitious?)
Give me a moment. I'll go get ready to wash your hair.
Okay.
Kim Hyun Soo is probably not the killer, right?
Ms. Yoon Hyo Jung.
I heard you and Hong Guk Hwa had a big falling-out.
And that's why you cut all ties with her, right?
Right?
(True Corrections for a Better Future)
(Korea Government, For Official Use Only)
Let's go, sir.
(Self-Reflection for Self-Reform)
We need a full list of your inmates who were taken to outside clinics...
in the past month.
To outside clinics?
Stop.
(Korea Correctional Service)
Is that Kim Hyun Soo?
Lower Cells 2, 4, and 6.
Upper Cells 5 and 7.
And...
Lower Cell Eight.
Mr. Kim Hyun Soo.
Please come with us.
(There Can Be a New Beginning)
Why did you and Hong Guk Hwa have a falling-out?
She had cut all ties with you, so you two must've had a big fight.
I don't know why I have to answer this question.
It's none of your business.
The drugs that she took.
Did you get her the drugs?
What are you talking about? It wasn't me.
Then who was it?
Who?
I bet you either got her the drugs or did it with her.
But even if you get waxed...
and dye or bleach all your hair,
you'll get busted with the advanced technology...
we have now.
Hyo Jung, what about here?
Did you shave the hair inside your ears?
What about your toenails and fingernails?
You see, I really don't care whether you do drugs or not.
As long as you're not the killer.
I swear. It really doesn't matter to me at all.
I'm done talking to you.
Did you kill Hong Guk Hwa?
I told you. It wasn't me.
Then you'd need an alibi.
Why do I need an alibi when I'm not the killer?
You lived together for two years...
but had a falling-out and cut all ties just before the incident.
Even if you weren't the person who got her the drugs,
you used them with her.
Look, Hyo Jung.
If the police investigated this case properly,
you'd be the prime suspect now. Do you realize that?
You don't want the police to come after you, do you?
You may get arrested.
I moved out a week before Guk Hwa died.
After that, I didn't call or visit her once...
because I was so angry.
Right. I find that very strange.
I understand that you two had a falling-out,
but your friend who you had lived with for two years died.
Plus, your stuff is still there.
And you haven't visited once? Why is that?
If I were you, I would've visited at least once out of curiosity.
I bet you intentionally...
avoided visiting her because you felt guilty about something.
It's got to be one of these two.
Either you killed her,
or you know who the killer is.
Ace Orthopaedics Clinic.
This therapist known as Bandage. You know him well, don't you?
He was your minion.
The Drug Squad caught him.
And that has led me here.
Kim Hyun Soo.
You know him, right?
I saw that he went to Ace Clinic for his dislocated shoulder...
a few days ago.
Tell me everything you know.
About what?
Oh.
Do you not know that you smuggled a drug into this place?
You dislocated your shoulder, went to the clinic,
and delivered the drug.
Don't you remember?
You went to Ace Clinic for your dislocated shoulder.
And this man treated you.
(Kim Jae Hoon)
As you can see, this guy is the pitcher.
And you caught the ball.
I just...
went there to get my shoulder fixed. That's all.
Tell me how you dislocated your shoulder.
I'm really sorry,
but how did I...
deliver the drug?
You're confusing me here.
Are you totally clueless? Or are you just a good actor?
The bandages that you had on your arm...
had been soaked with a narcotized solution.
You see, this isn't something we can just let go of.
Gosh.
Civil servants get paid peanuts and are always on the chopping block.
I have to deal with this because the higher-ups want me to.
But you know me. I hate dealing with a nuisance.
So let's not make things difficult for both our sakes...
and deal with this quietly.
You know, give and take.
I'm not here to get you, Hyun Soo.
I'm here to catch the one who put you up to it,
Do Ji Tae.
With everything that's going on,
there is no way you did it knowingly.
But think about it.
Let's say Do Ji Tae tells us everything.
But if you keep your mouth shut,
what do you think will happen?
You'll take the fall for it.
He'll stab you in the back.
Your case is on trial at the moment.
Giving the prosecution yet another thing to use against you...
won't do you any good. Am I wrong?
Those in prison are one of two kinds.
Backstabbers or those who get back-stabbed.
Being the former makes me invincible.
My secret is to not trust people.
You know that...
I can have you transferred.
Then you'll have to work your way to the top again.
Are you good with that?
Did you report to your superiors before bringing the party here?
How many correctional officers do you think have been in this place?
There have been seven wardens.
Deputy chiefs, chiefs,
and all those that rank higher than you.
Do you think their hands are clean?
Are you sure you can handle this?
You piece of...
You should get that.
Yes, sir.
Right.
Sorry?
But...
I see.
Yes, sir.
It stinks from miles away.
How high does the rotten food chain go up?
I hate to tell you this,
but I can't return without anything to show for myself.
Let me at least have something.
(Korean beef sirloin)
That will be 113 dollars.
You must pay extra if you wish to grill it here.
I thought your specialty was drugs,
but I see you're good with knives too, Mr. Um.
Do I know you?
What I want to know is this.
Here.
Why did Hong Guk Hwa call you that night,
and where were you when the incident took place?
Are you the police?
When was the last time she bought from you?
Buy what from me?
I don't appreciate you jumping to conclusions.
Right here.
I bet you took her on as a client around the time...
she was denied treatment for her alcoholism.
I don't know what you're talking about.
You met her that night,
but you didn't sell her drugs.
Are you accusing me of killing her?
You've got to be kidding me.
Who was it though? Who gave up my name?
You probably know who it was.
Whatever. I'm hanging up.
Goodness.
(Interview)
I forgot my phone.
Good day then.
Good luck with your business too.
In here or out there,
- it's the same old story. - Darn it.
Money can buy you anything.
You can buy anything you want...
whether it's food or clothes.
Correctional officers and inspectors alike.
To earn a living is why they work.
(Korea Post Bank Account, 100 dollars)
You're more tight-lipped than I expected.
What's this for?
Call your father.
I had his taxi delivered.
Hello?
Dad, it's me, Hyun Soo.
Hyun Soo?
How are you calling me?
Isn't this a cell phone number?
I happened to get my hands on one.
Dad, did you perhaps get your taxi back?
I just got it back, so how did you know that?
Really? Did you really get it back?
Yes, that's what I said.
The call came out of nowhere...
which was odd since they wouldn't listen when I begged.
I see. Well, I'll call you again when I can.
Hyun Soo?
Thank you.
It's yours now.
You've got to be kidding me.
Did you think I would let this slide?
Darn wench.
You were also going to see Guk Hwa that night, right?
Don't you know that I can also go to the cops about you?
Not this again. It's getting old.
Like I said, I didn't sleep with her.
- You darn cow. - Careful. It's hot.
Whatever. I'm hanging up.
It's too bad...
since only a consented recording is admissible.
From here, we'll find something we can use.
Guk Hwa had a falling-out with her roommate...
a week before the incident and had cut all ties,
and Um Ki Jong was her drug dealer.
The three were in a love triangle,
and the two of them have no alibi.
Anyone can tell that this is fishy.
I'll have them requested as witnesses...
and see to it that the subpoenas are delivered.
Do you have the CCTV footage from the day of the crime?
Oh, yes.
I secured all the CCTV footage...
that was on Hyun Soo's route that night.
However, there are a lot.
Are you going to watch them all?
I have to.
What?
I see.
(Gas Station, LPG)
Oh, Lee Chul Ho?
I'm afraid he quit last month though.
Why? Is there an issue?
Yes, with the delivery of ours.
I'd like for him to confirm something.
Can I have the name and address?
The name is Hong Guk Hwa.
The address is 68 Chusa-ro, Chungang-Gu.
Let's see if I can find 68 Chusa-ro.
Ms. Hong Guk Hwa. Just a second.
Let's see.
A package was delivered last month.
Is there an issue with it?
A few disappeared en route.
Darn.
That jerk...
By the way, why did he quit?
Well...
Actually, he didn't quit. He was let go...
because he hid the fact that he was wearing an electronic anklet.
It's illegal for a delivery business to hire sex offenders.
Oh, he had an ankle monitor?
(Yumin Ironworks)
- Thank you! - Thank you.
Darn, you stupid dog.
Gosh.
Goodness.
Hello?
Anybody here?
- Who are you? - My gosh!
Evidence 109.
As soon as the defendant got into the stolen taxi...
Darn it.
He turned off the dashcam,
which was intentional.
Evidence 113.
CCTV footage from the scene, at 8:41pm.
He chose his victim.
He was hunting for his victim.
Is there another reason...
why you believe that the murder was deliberate and premeditated?
What he did after the incident...
matches the patterns that sly, manipulative murderers exhibit.
He did not report the incident.
(Defendant)
He did not call the police...
and didn't even tell his parents or friends about it.
He didn't tell anyone until the moment he was arrested.
And that day,
he had at least three opportunities to turn himself in.
As soon as he found the body,
when he was stopped at the DUI checkpoint,
and when he came to the police station.
However, he did not say anything...
about the incident.
He attempted to destroy evidence at the scene and fled.
And he had the murder weapon on him until the moment he was arrested...
but showed no remorse whatsoever.
No.
Mr. Kim.
That is not true.
I did not kill her,
so why should I feel remorse?
The prosecutor is examining the witness.
Doing this can put you at a disadvantage.
No one believes me!
I've been telling the truth all along.
Why won't you listen to me?
If I don't speak out like this,
everyone will believe what the detective is saying.
What I'm telling you is the truth,
whereas that's just what he is claiming.
Are you insisting that the witness is lying now?
I did not kill her. It really wasn't me.
I did not kill Hong Guk Hwa.
I'm not a murderer.
Mr. Kim, please calm down.
That's the kind of behaviour I'm talking about.
A murderer's violent nature.
Mr. Kim.
If you'd like,
you can give evidence now.
It's simple.
All you have to do is be on the witness stand.
Mr. Kim, you're very upset right now.
If you get up on the witness stand now,
and if something unexpected happens...
I'll do it.
I will get up on the witness stand.
You made a wise decision.
Your Honour. Ladies and gentlemen of the jury.
As per Mr. Kim's request,
I would like to bring him in as a witness.
- Shall I pour you a glass too? - I'm good. I gave up drinking.
Not much happened that day.
Although that rude girl threw her cigarette butt at me.
Other than that, nothing happened.
You started chasing the taxi as soon as it drove off.
No, I wasn't chasing it.
I had to take off too because I had somewhere to go.
Where did you have to go?
Why do you want to know that?
Well...
I noticed...
that you have been to Hong Guk Hwa's place in the past.
That's nothing odd because I used to work as a courier.
What's the problem?
You knew Hong Guk Hwa,
and you followed her that night.
Anyone would think that it's suspicious.
Let me just say this one thing to you.
I had nothing to do with it.
If I had anything to do with it,
the police would be here,
not a lawyer.
Breaking and entering and rape.
An ex-con with the exact same priors...
followed the victim...
all the way to the Han River on the day of the incident.
Do you not think it's suspicious?
By the way,
did you come here alone?
What if I did?
Do you want to fight me?
Mr. Kim.
Would you say you're honest?
Pardon?
Do you think you're an honest person?
I think I am.
Shall I give you a chance to change your answer?
No.
Okay.
You said you were honest,
so I expect you to answer my questions honestly.
On the day of the incident,
did you get your father's permission...
before leaving home in his taxi?
No.
You don't have a license to drive a taxi, do you?
- I don't. - So that's illegal.
Right.
Why did you tilt your head like that just now?
I'm just not sure...
if this is an important matter in this situation.
Because of your illegal act,
your father may lose his taxi license.
Is that not important to you?
I didn't think of that.
Do you enjoy endangering the lives of others?
No, I do not.
If that is the case, then why...
(Evidence 1)
Then why did you take illegal drugs...
and drive the taxi when your blood alcohol level was 0.12,
which is enough to get your license revoked?
Why did you pick her up?
(Jury)
She just got in the car.
I said the taxi was off duty and told her to get out but...
If you pull over with your for-hire light on,
the passenger would get in the car, of course.
Let's say the passenger was someone else.
If it was a guy,
would you still have gone to the park by the river with him?
- No. - In other words,
you went there with her because it was her.
Hoping to get her into bed.
No, I never thought that.
You say that, but your actions say otherwise.
You did sleep with her a few hours later.
The thought of...
sleeping with an attractive woman whom you had just met...
must've gotten you very excited.
You had been drinking on top of the drugs,
so you couldn't think straight.
She said she didn't want it,
but you just went ahead and did it.
No, that is not what happened.
- We were attracted to each other... - No.
A woman who lived alone invited you over to her place...
and even gave you drugs, so I bet you thought she was easy.
You had been drinking, so you couldn't resist the urge.
Mr. Kim.
Can you deny that?
(Judge)
(Supreme Court of Korea)
Ms. Hong trusted you.
It is why she went out with you,
invited you into her home,
and had drinks with you.
However, you had other ideas.
You...
only saw her as someone who could satisfy your sexual needs.
This difference in thought.
This one lapse of judgement on Ms. Hong's part...
led to her death.
Hong Guk Hwa. You killed her, didn't you?
It wasn't me.
Whatever. It doesn't change the fact...
that you'll have to sit in court...
and provide an alibi for the time of death.
Hey.
I said it wasn't me.
How did you feel after you slept with her?
I don't know.
How do you feel after such activities?
Defendant!
Please refrain yourself.
Then put yourself in my shoes.
I'm here speaking the truth,
but instead of listening, she's asking useless questions.
Why didn't you speak the truth at the police station?
During your interrogation,
you repeated "I don't know" 157 times.
Well, that...
That's what my attorney advised me to do.
No, you yelled that you couldn't remember,
but to questions that weren't in your favour,
you said that you didn't know.
You don't speak about Ms. Hong's death either.
Why is that? Well, it's simple.
It's because...
you...
killed her.
No. How many times must I say that it wasn't me!
After you found her body,
you stated...
that you fled the scene because you were flustered.
The horrific scene that you saw made you panic.
Is that right?
- Yes. - But actually, you went back there.
You returned to her house,
grabbed your jacket with your car key inside,
got rid of the evidence,
took the knife which is the murder weapon,
and fled the scene for the second time.
Come on.
How can someone in a panic accomplish such activities?
I know... I know how this may look.
That's right.
It looks like...
a cold-blooded killer tried to clean up after him.
In the squad car that night,
why did you ask if the woman was dead?
That's...
That was because I wanted...
to be wrong about her being dead.
Didn't it occur to you that you should call an ambulance?
No.
Why not?
Because... Because I was scared.
What were you scared of?
The police thinking that I did this to her.
So rather than trying to help a bleeding woman,
you were more worried...
about being mistaken as the killer.
Even when it's the woman...
you made love to that night.
- I guess it can seem that way. - It does.
You fled the scene without trying to help her.
How did you feel when you first...
found her?
I don't know.
How did you feel when you ran away?
Just like now,
you choose not to answer questions that aren't in your favour.
Was this also your counsel's advice?
Do you know what I can't understand about you?
From the very beginning,
you've been claiming your innocence,
but that night,
you fled the scene for selfish reasons.
But then you returned...
to eliminate and contaminate incriminating evidence...
and drove under the influence...
just to flee the scene once again.
What if you called for an ambulance...
and the victim...
received medical treatment?
She might still be alive right now.
(Supreme Court of Korea)
That night,
there was a sliver of hope.
There was a tiny window of opportunity,
but you wasted it by trying to only save yourself.
You turned a blind eye to Ms. Hong who was bleeding out.
So considering all that,
can it be said...
that you are innocent?
Mr. Kim, you believe yourself to be honest,
so I'll ask you one last time.
Mr. Kim.
That night.
Did you...
kill...
Ms. Hong Guk Hwa?
Mr. Kim?
I...
I don't know.
I don't know anymore.