(Kim Soo Hyun)
(Cha Seoung Won)
(One Ordinary Day)
(Northern Prison)
Mr. Kim.
That night.
Did you...
kill...
Ms. Hong Guk Hwa?
(Building a Law-abiding Society Through Genuine Reform)
I don't know.
I don't know anymore.
What does that mean?
Does it mean there's a chance that you killed Ms. Hong?
Mr. Kim, please answer the prosecutor's question.
(Episode 7: Transformation)
Hong Guk Hwa. You killed her, didn't you?
It wasn't me.
Whatever. It doesn't change the fact...
that you'll have to sit in court...
and provide an alibi for the time of death.
Hey. I said it wasn't me.
- Scumbag! - Scumbag!
- Darn it! - Darn it!
I guess you're trying to drag me into it,
but I'm not an idiot.
I won't fall for your tricks.
Hey!
Hey, arrest this jerk for attempted murder.
- Now! - Gosh, that scared me.
Put that down, and we'll talk. Come on. Put it down.
I'm a police officer.
- Hey. - Darn it.
If you arrived even just a minute late,
you'd be holding a funeral for me right now.
Speeding in the rain nearly cost me my life.
What is that?
What do you think? Did you think I'd come here unarmed?
How dare he throw an axe?
Does he think he's an Apache or what?
You're such a handful, seriously.
Yes, Mr. Shin.
Hi, Ms. Seo. How did it go?
Did you manage to teach Prosecutor An a thing or two again?
What about you? Is everything okay on your end?
Ms. Seo.
You sound upset. What happened?
I think I ruined everything.
I should have stopped him at all costs.
What do you mean?
What happened?
I'm sorry.
You see,
even if you'd had me in the courtroom,
the results would've been the same.
Both you and Ms. Seo did your best.
Don't worry too much, okay?
It's not like they obtained new evidence by examining you.
Nothing has changed.
I think I saw her finger move.
What?
Guk Hwa.
Initially, I had no recollection of seeing it.
But I've thought about it,
and I think I remember seeing her finger move.
You're mistaken.
The knife pierced her neck...
and through her heart and lungs. She died on the spot.
Even if her fingers did move,
that's called "rigor mortis."
It's commonly seen in violent deaths.
I should get back to my cell.
(Order)
Hey, just shake it off.
It's okay. You have me, you know.
Goodness.
Darn it.
Have some manners, seriously.
(Hire Lawyer Shin Joong Han for Just 300 Dollars)
Who drew all over my face?
It won't even come off.
(Divorce, Child Custody, Division of Assets, Inheritance)
(Yoon Hyo Jung)
The victim's...
roommate. And...
Um Ki Jong.
Sexually involved...
with the victim.
No.
Lee Chul Ho.
Previously convicted of the same type of crime.
Hold on.
Darn it.
(Lee Chul Ho, previously convicted of the same type of crime)
Darn...
I heard you said in the courtroom that you don't know.
At first, you insisted that you didn't remember anything.
And now, you don't know whether or not you killed her?
What is the truth?
Here's what I'm wondering.
Maybe you do remember what happened, but you just want...
to believe that you didn't kill her.
Wake up!
Attention!
Straighten your uniform.
Hey, you.
So Kim Hyun Soo, that twerp, killed her after all.
That scumbag.
After acting innocent and all.
Recover position!
He said, "I don't know."
Do you think it could be interpreted as an admission of guilt?
He could insist that he did not want to give false testimony...
when he really wasn't sure.
However, it's true that most judges would shyly interpret it...
as an admission of guilt.
Many are speculating that the prosecution...
- will ask for the death penalty. - Hey, kid.
- You're done for. - As for Kim Hyun Soo,
- the suspect in this case... - So what now?
His crimes are quite heinous.
That means the prosecution could ask for the death penalty.
Throughout the case, the prosecution...
has been taking an unyielding stance.
Talk about a two-faced brat. Right?
For sure.
(Cultivate Morality for a Healthier Life)
(Keep order)
Got it. I'll be in touch.
("Kim Hyun Soo Confesses? Death Penalty Could Be Served")
Don't be too worried.
Thirty years will go by before you know it.
By the way,
who uses shabby flip phones like this these days?
Don't you agree?
(Restricted Area)
(Rehabilitation)
Should the game be this tricky?
- Darn it. - I want my phone back.
Darn, I lost.
You brat.
How can you prove that this is yours?
I know you stole it, you scumbag.
What?
Scumbag?
Give it back!
Give it back?
Why you...
You punk.
I dare you to talk back again.
I've suddenly lost my appetite.
- Let's go. - This stinks.
Darn it.
Block him, darn it.
(Keep Order)
Okay, good.
Go on. Show him how it's done.
Put some power to it. Shake like you mean it.
Thrust like so.
Is it that hard? Give it a try.
Nice!
Nicely done.
Good one.
- Over here. - Nice!
(There Can Be a New Beginning)
I need your help.
Have a seat.
"In dubio pro reo."
"Nemo praesumitur malus."
(When in doubt, in favour of the defendant.)
(No one is presumed to be guilty.)
This was the first tattoo I got when I was 20.
Back then, I was a nerd who had his nose in books.
I got caught up in an assault case and was falsely accused.
No one believed me.
Like you, I tried everything I could.
I even tried to commit suicide.
At the brink of death, I had a revelation.
That I hold the key to my freedom.
To survive,
I must be the one to change.
The choice is yours, Hyun Soo.
(When in doubt, in favour of the defendant.)
(No one is presumed to be guilty.)
(The woman I used to love)
(You have 18 missed calls.)
What is with this mess?
You know that this is exactly why I divorced you.
What brings you by unannounced?
I called and texted you over ten times.
"Unannounced"?
I didn't come here because I was worried about you.
I wanted to talk to you before the witness examination.
Take a look.
Sure, thanks.
You know, about Kim Hyun Soo...
I know he's got asthma, but does he have anything else?
I'm not sure.
Have you seen a doctor yet?
A doctor? Come on.
I've still got it.
You know that.
No, I'm talking about...
your atopic dermatitis.
Oh, that.
Lawyer Shin Joong Han.
Don't rely on an unscientific folk remedy like this.
You need to see a dermatologist.
If dermatologists could cure it, I wouldn't still be dealing with it.
It's not like I wanted to resort to a home remedy like this.
Lawyer Shin Joong Han.
I don't want to see you give up.
Whether it's your atopic dermatitis, the trial,
or your family.
Just leave it. I'll clean up.
(An exchange of kind words stirs companionship.)
(Accused: Kim Hyun Soo)
(List of Witnesses, Ha No Seok)
(Yoo Seung Hoon, First Witness)
(List of Suspects)
(Yoon Hyo Jung, had a falling out with Hong Guk Hwa)
(Um Ki Jong, provided drugs to Hong Guk Hwa)
(Lee Chul Ho, courier who served the vicinity of Hong Guk Hwa's home)
- Nice, yes! - Over here.
That's it!
(Law and Order)
Nice.
Yes, that was good.
Hey!
Witness, please come forward.
Take an oath.
Oath.
"I solemnly affirm that I will tell the truth, the whole truth..."
- "and nothing but the truth." - Hey, Hyun Soo.
"I understand that I would be committing perjury..."
There are some things...
the accused should never do in the courtroom.
For example, yawning like you did just now...
or leaning back in your chair with your legs crossed.
It's awfully rude, okay?
Such an attitude won't help you at all.
(Defendant)
What prompted you to start supplying the victim with drugs?
Guk Hwa was my girlfriend's roommate.
That's how I got to know her, and it happened very naturally.
But the thing is,
Guk Hwa said she used drugs when she was studying in the US.
Did you...
have sex with Ms. Hong?
(Defendant)
Do I have to answer this question?
The victim was stabbed 13 times by an unidentified male,
which was the direct cause of her death.
In such a case,
it's normal to suspect that it may have been a crime of passion.
Yes. Once, just because we were drunk.
I did sleep with her once.
You spoke with Ms. Hong on the phone on the day of the incident.
Did you have plans to see her that day?
Look. That crazy girl threatened me.
We slept together just because we were drunk.
When my girlfriend found out, she lied to her that I raped her.
Gosh, it still makes me so angry.
Then you probably wanted to kill her, right?
Objection, Your Honour.
Mr. Um is here as a witness,
but the counsel is treating him...
like a suspect.
Objection sustained.
Counsel, please be careful.
It is true that I was fuming mad,
but I wasn't angry enough to kill her. I'm not like that jerk.
Mr. Um.
Did the police interview you at all with regard to this case?
Either about the drugs...
or your relationship with the victim.
No.
When you found out that Ms. Hong, your roommate,
had sexual intercourse with Mr. Um who was your boyfriend,
how did you feel?
I was freaking miserable, obviously.
Witness, you're in a courtroom now.
Please watch what you say.
A week before Ms. Hong's death,
the two of you had a big fight because of that,
and you were hurt pretty badly.
We did fight,
but you know what happens in a cat fight.
Just pulling each other's hair, that's all.
(Defence)
Then how come...
the doctor thought your injury required three weeks of treatment?
After the fight, you packed up and moved out. Then a week later,
on the day of the incident,
you called Ms. Hong.
Correct. Let's be honest. I was wronged,
so I thought she owed me an apology,
and I had to pick up my belongings that I had left at her place.
That's why I called her.
But she didn't pick up, and she ignored my texts too.
That must've made you angry.
No, not at all.
I had already made up my mind to break up with Ki Jong,
and I was hoping Guk Hwa and I could put it behind us...
and patch things up.
Ms. Yoon, then did the police ever ask you...
to come in for an interview regarding this case?
No.
You had a big falling-out with the victim,
and your boyfriend cheated on you with her.
I'd say you definitely had a motive for killing her.
But they never even asked you to come in for an interview?
Why should I be questioned? I didn't kill her.
That guy is the killer.
(Prosecution)
(Yoon Hyo Jung)
(Um Ki Jong)
These two here clearly didn't do it.
Why? We haven't confirmed whether their alibis check out.
When they were testifying in court,
they didn't get defensive at all.
They said everything without a second's hesitation.
That can only be done...
when people know for a fact that they're telling the truth.
But the thing is, they were in a relationship.
Maybe they talked to get their story straight.
No.
Even if they did, it doesn't matter.
Even people who lie all the time...
can't lie easily...
when they take the witness stand.
Look them in the eyes,
and you can tell whether they're telling the truth.
Look them in the eyes...
Speaking of which,
don't you think Mr. Kim was acting a bit strange today?
(Accused: Kim Hyun Soo)
- Hyun Soo? - Yes.
Well...
Maybe he's found a way to cope with his situation,
to survive.
Get up.
Come on.
(A Healthy Mind and Body for a Better Tomorrow)
(Kim Ji Soo)
Hyun Soo, is that you?
Hey, Ji Soo.
Did you really not kill her?
If you didn't, then tell me.
Why won't you say anything?
How idiotic are you?
I wasn't going to say anything,
but we put the house on the market.
We're too ashamed to live in this neighbourhood anymore.
I was nearly forced to transfer schools...
and Mom was let go from her job.
Do you even know what's happening?
Our lives are ruined because of you.
You pushed us down a hell hole!
Are you still there? Hyun Soo!
(Live a Healthier Life)
The person you have reached is unavailable.
Please leave a message after the tone.
(Northern Prison: Purchasable Item Prices)
Moving on.
Kim Hyun Soo's lawyers...
have introduced the idea of a new suspect.
We'll hear from our reporter at the court.
Ms. Lee?
This is Lee Ki Hyun at the court.
Kim's lawyers introduced a man who had an affair with the victim...
- What? - Hey.
(Be your best at what you can do today.)
- Seriously? - He must be out of his mind.
Darn brat. Have you lost your mind?
- Whatever. - Darn it.
Unbelievable.
(Painting Studio)
(Calligraphy Studio)
Did you just glare at me?
Look at that glare.
What then? Is it a duel you want?
I'll rip your eyes out.
Bring it on.
You must be insane.
Okay.
If you're that confident, be at the boiler room in an hour.
Whether you lose or win, see the end of it.
It's cleaner that way.
I've been looking for a way to put an end to you.
And here we are.
Don't just stand there and come closer.
Goodness. Now I'm trembling.
I see you gave yourself a nice haircut.
By the way,
I won't bat an eye if you die.
What game are you trying to play?
Turn on the lights.
Fine. Hide if you want.
But once I spot you,
you'll be dead meat.
(No inmates allowed in this area.)
You...
Darn punk.
Whether you lose or win, see the end of it.
It's cleaner that way.
Scared, are you? Darn punk.
It's not over yet...
(Chungang Police Station)
Chief Park.
He was arrested at the scene...
for the attempted murder of lawyer Shin Joong Han.
He hasn't said anything regarding Hong Guk Hwa's murder.
Breaking and entering, attempted rape,
and attempted murder are his priors.
What do you mean?
Lee Chul Ho has been released? Why?
Well, he's still on probation,
so we have all the GPS tracking data from his ankle monitor.
I've been busy, so I haven't checked it yet myself,
but I heard he didn't go anywhere near Hong Guk Hwa's home.
Well, maybe he had disabled the ankle monitor somehow...
before heading over to her place.
He's not an idiot.
I don't know. Chief Park let him go, so you can take it up with him.
What happened?
Lee Chul Ho...
has been released.
What?
What about the investigation? Is it already done?
What about his alibi?
Well...
I underestimated this case.
For Chief Park Sang Bum,
Hyun Soo has to be the only suspect. He won't accept another one.
- Darn it. - Gosh.
Then he won't even appear in court as a witness tomorrow.
He will.
That punk will probably...
attend the trial tomorrow.
(Defendant)
You clean up nice.
(Supreme Court of Korea)
Mr. Kim.
Do you recognize the witness, Mr. Lee Chul Ho?
(Defendant)
Yes. I saw him at the gas station that night.
(Prosecution)
Mr. Lee, did you recognize Ms. Hong when you saw her there?
No, I don't even recall seeing her there.
You delivered a package to the victim's home address,
and she filed a complaint against you. Correct?
I guess you don't know the industry well at all.
I receive 12 complaints a day... It happens all the time.
You were previously convicted of the same types of crimes.
Would you tell us what they were?
That has nothing to do with this case.
I do not feel the need to answer this question.
In August of 2017,
you were sentenced to three years in prison...
for breaking and entering and attempted rape and murder.
You threatened the victim with a weapon, which you obtained...
in the victim's home.
Like I said,
that has nothing to do with this case.
You followed Ms. Hong all the way to the park by the Han River.
That was just a coincidence.
She had filed a complaint against you.
You ran into her at the gas station by chance...
and just happened to run into her again at the park.
Then, she happened to die that very night.
Now, can that be called a coincidence?
Then maybe...
it was fate.
On the day of the incident,
your ankle monitor...
was turned off for about an hour.
The battery died.
Well, it happens from time to time.
When did the police interview you?
They never did.
You have priors and were holding a grudge against the victim.
On top of that, you ran into her that night.
Then you disabled your ankle monitor...
and followed her all the way to the park,
yet the police never bothered to interview you?
Correct.
My gosh.
Mr. Lee, why do you think the police didn't ask you to come in?
I guess they know...
that I didn't kill her.
Can you provide an alibi for the time of the incident?
(Witness)
An alibi?
Honestly,
I really can't wrap my head around this.
The man who slept with her...
and was found with the murder weapon...
is right there.
Why must I provide an alibi?
(Judge)
(Criminal Procedure Act)
My phone.
Did you give it to Park Doo Sik?
Why?
Why did you do that?
I had no choice.
I need to survive in this place too.
Thanks for everything anyway.
(Keyless Door Lock at Victim's Residence)
Ms. Hong had a keyless electronic door lock system installed.
As you know, anyone who knows the door code can get in.
And it was an older model, which can be disabled...
with a stun gun or the master code.
(Rear Door to Terrace Left Open Due to Broken Doorknob)
What about these photos?
The door to the terrace was unlocked as the doorknob was broken,
so anyone could've come into the house.
Are you saying...
it is possible that there was an intruder that night?
I will just say that the possibility cannot be totally ruled out.
Objection, Your Honour.
The possibility that there might have been an unknown intruder...
has nothing to do with the defendant's charges...
and why the prosecution decided to indict him.
It is completely irrelevant.
You also pointed out...
that there may have been another weapon.
Correct. A knife, which could have been used in the murder,
is unaccounted for.
- Is this it? - Yes.
(8-Piece Knife Set, 2 Missing Knives)
This is an eight-piece kitchen knife set.
They all look slightly different,
but the set is missing two knives.
One of them...
is the knife, which the prosecution insists was used in the murder.
But...
where is the other one, then?
(Missing Knife)
This photo was taken at the scene shortly after the incident.
As you can see, there was leftover fruit,
but the knife that was used to peel the fruit is missing.
Objection, Your Honour.
(Judge)
All right.
By saying there might be another possible murder weapon...
fully knowing Mr. Kim was found with the murder weapon on him,
the counsel is trying to distort such clear evidence.
It's nothing more than the counsel's subjective speculation.
And therefore, it is inadmissible.
Objection sustained.
What you're looking at is the photo of the victim's right hand.
Could you elaborate on this?
Her hand was probably penetrated due to a knife game.
Your findings don't match that of the medical examiner...
who conducted the autopsy.
Could you explain why?
Traces of a fluorescence brightening agent...
and formaldehyde were found in the wound.
The combination of those chemicals is found mostly in toilet paper.
It indicates that someone tried to stop the bleeding.
Oh, no. My gosh!
Evidence which points to a knife game...
can be found on her dining table.
As you can see, this proves that the victim...
often engaged in the dangerous knife game.
The prosecution claims that the wound was inflicted on her...
when the knife slipped...
from hitting her spine.
Do you agree?
I don't see how that can be true.
Could you elaborate?
If you look at her wounds,
you will see that the blade was facing up.
Like this?
Yes, according to those wounds,
the killer held the knife...
with the blade facing up when stabbing her.
So what would happen...
if the knife slipped from one's grip?
If the killer was wounded from such an event,
the wound should be found on the inside of his hand.
As the report states,
on the broken glass of the front door,
the defendant's blood, epithelial tissue,
and DNA were found.
So he suffered the wound...
in the way he testified to.
From cutting himself on the broken glass.
My witness' findings...
go directly against those of the medical examiner...
who conducted the autopsy.
Does the prosecution have an objection?
How the wound was inflicted could be debatable...
which is why it will heavily rely...
on the judgement of the jury and judges.
(Judge)
Mr. Kim, could you write your name on that piece of paper?
(Kim Hyun Soo)
Dr. Hong, what is shown on the screen?
It's the analysis report of the 13 wounds on the victim's body.
The analysis...
helps us identify the suspect's traits.
And what would that be?
Eight out of the thirteen wounds were inflicted...
from the 1 o'clock position to the 7 o'clock position.
One can presume that the killer is right-handed.
I see. But as you just saw,
the defendant...
is left-handed.
The fact that he is left-handed...
can be proved through multiple evidence.
He writes with his left hand,
plays table tennis with his left arm,
and plays badminton with his left arm too.
I object!
- Counsel is displaying... - This...
is the report written by the NFS medical examiner...
who conducted the autopsy.
Let's see. "The probability..."
"of the killer being right-handed..."
"is high."
High.
High!
That'll be all.
You may cross-examine.
Dr. Hong,
you are a senior researcher at the NFS...
and teach forensic medicine at a college.
- That's right. - Right.
Were you assigned to this case?
No.
Then why are you here today?
Could there be a particular reason?
My presence was requested by Lawyer Shin Joong Han.
Do you have a close relationship with him?
We used to be married.
I'm sure that's what you were fishing for.
I see.
So you must have taken on this case for Mr. Shin's sake.
This I can say with certainty.
Not at all.
I can't really stand the man...
which is why I divorced him.
Then why are you here testifying?
I believe that...
the medical examiner's report is biased.
Despite there being other possibilities,
he presumed that the defendant was guilty.
The issue is that...
the jury believed his testimony to be the only truth.
I am here today to inform everyone...
that certain evidence can be interpreted differently.
After all, the jury has a right to hear from various experts.
You too, Ms. An.
Thank you for pointing out the basics.
That'll be all.
(Defendant)
(When in doubt, in favour of the defendant.)
(No one is presumed to be guilty.)
So what should I call you?
Anything you want.
(When in doubt, in favour of the defendant.)
(No one is presumed to be guilty.)
Ji Tae.
I'm curious though.
Do you really believe that I didn't kill her?
Hong Guk Hwa, I mean.
What if I did though?