[English subtitles are available]
[Advance Bravely]
[Episode 19]
Yao,
go and take a look.
A gorgeous girl is here.
[Copyrights + Co-innovation Space]
What is it?
It's about that incident...
If you're here about that,
you can leave.
I know I was rather cruel that day,
but you're so easily embarrassed.
I can't just accommodate you all the time.
If I beat around the bush,
you might be even more hurt.
I'll make things clear.
Sexual dysfunction is just an excuse I made up.
I told you that
because I wanted to get rid of you.
Are you...
telling the truth?
Yes.
She can flare up at me.
I'll bear with anything she does
as long as it's not too outrageous.
I need a clean break.
Oh my gosh.
You aren't sick?
Hello?
Wang Shuang?
What?
A television station is there?
What about you?
What else can I do?
This is so embarrassing.
What's so embarrassing about that?
I've done far more
embarrassing things.
Listen up.
Your mind
has to be strong if you want to woo a man.
Well,
let's not talk about that for now.
I have amazing news
to share with you.
What amazing news?
I can't talk about it now.
Let's go shopping later.
Okay,
it's settled then.
I'm busy. I'll get going.
Bye bye.
My luck sucks.
I went to such lengths to catch that jerk.
Two hours haven't even passed.
I wasn't even done venting my anger,
but that call summoned me all the way to Macau.
Yes,
you were gone for a whole week.
How's everything?
Has he
stirred up any trouble?
No,
he's unbelievably
obedient.
Maybe he has something up his sleeve.
I don't get it, either.
If an ordinary person was locked up there
without any phones,
without anyone to talk to,
and without any free time to wander,
they would have gone insane.
He's pretty relaxed.
A dung beetle can keep him entertained the whole afternoon.
You can't view him
as an ordinary person.
No,
I bet he isn't even human.
You gained weight while I was away.
What a strong mind you have.
Bro,
what's the cologne you're using?
It smells great.
Does it?
How about
I spray it on these guys' fists?
I'll make sure this fragrance sticks in your mind forever.
What's wrong?
Are you scared now?
I'm not scared.
I'm just heartbroken.
What did you say?
Did you guys hear him?
Does he have a heart?
I stole your money
only to get close to you.
I know that money
isn't much to you.
I'm just scared that you'll forget about me.
I want to stay on your mind.
Knock it off.
I stole your money
just to make you look for me.
You're just too stupid
and failed to find me.
That's why I came up with those idiotic tactics.
I used the same trick near the place you were playing cards.
Think about this.
How can there be such a coincidence?
You even caught me
while I was getting onto someone else's back.
I weaved these lies
and then stole your watch
so that you would be driven to look for me.
After that, I stole liquor
just to get caught.
Which idiot
would drink stolen liquor
on the spot instead of fleeing?
I can't trust him.
Everything he says is nonsense.
It's my loss if I take his words seriously.
Now that
I've caught you and brought you here,
your wishes must be fulfilled.
I guess so,
if these guys weren't around.
Good Lord,
Wang Zhishui.
What other ridiculous lies
can you come up with to dupe me?
I'm telling the truth.
I'm not lying.
What's going on?
I got some guys to beat him up yesterday.
In the end, those guys pulled some dirty tricks.
They covered Wang Zhishui's face with underwear
and provoked him.
He smashed his head onto the ground.
Didn't I tell you to go easy on him?
Why is his life at risk now?
How would I know that he valued his pride more than his life?
How is he now?
We brought him here yesterday,
but his safety was only confirmed today.
He's been transferred
from the ICU to a regular ward.
Take me to him right away.
What?
Where is Wang Zhishui?
He left.
He left?
Doesn't he
have to be hospitalized for some time?
We told him the same thing,
but he insisted on leaving.
We have to respect the patient's wishes.
Come on,
let's go downstairs to take a look.
He's over there.
[Emergency]
He escaped again.
I bet he's scared that I'll beat him up again.
That's not it.
He's really broke.
If he really wanted to flee,
why didn't he take a taxi?
Why did he wait for the bus?
What is your plan?
I'll keep looking for him.
You will?
He's already in such misery.
Forgive and forget.
What do you want from him?
Why can't you get over this grudge?
I...
I'm used to being like this.
Get two guys to join you.
After that,
come over here.
Lift this twice.
Okay.
Then showcase their muscles.
You two,
come over here.
You can stand over there.
You, come over here.
Okay.
Just repeat our usual training.
Keep your back straight.
Use your arms.
Okay,
one more time.
Slow down
and do it properly.
One, two, three.
Okay.
Look up.
Nice.
Lower your buttocks.
Back straight.
Look up.
Okay,
lift them back.
One, two, three.
Everyone, take a break.
Director, how was it?
Pretty good.
Everything went well.
You can take a break, too.
We have to set up the cameras.
We'll call you over later.
Okay.
Hey, Tao.
What's wrong?
I'm tired.
If you're tired, rest in the car.
I'll take you home after everything wraps up.
You don't have to join the afternoon session.
I'm not physically tired.
My heart feels worn out.
Do you even have a heart?
Why wouldn't I have one?
There's so much on my mind every day.
What are you doing?
Give me an allowance.
Are you going to buy junk food again?
I won't buy junk food.
I'll buy yummy food.
Lies.
You took some money
from my drawer and bought trash.
I took a bite
and threw the rest away.
Are such things that delicious?
Yes, they are.
The only thing
that tastes good to you is green onion dipped in sauce.
Do you know what?
I grew up in a very strict household.
I never got to eat such things.
That's why I'm hooked on them now.
If you're so insistent on stopping me,
you'll only spur a greater desire for it.
Only by showering me with such food,
you will make me sick of them.
¥2.
Do you have loose change?
No.
If you don't, pay with your phone.
I want to get loose change.
Here you go.
¥98.
How are you spending the new year?
I'm going to my hometown.
Your hometown?
Hei Longjiang?
Umm-humm.
When will you go back?
Once this batch of trainees completes their final examination.
How long will you be there?
A month.
I haven't been back for three years.
My relatives miss me.
I need to visit my parents' grave too.
Sure, go back.
Everyone goes home during the new year.
Why are you back so early?
What's wrong with coming home early?
Are you keeping secrets from me?
What secrets can I have?
Your dad's superior is coming over for a meal.
Be quiet.
My dad isn't home.
Why is his superior coming here?
Don't jump to conclusions.
His superior is a woman.
What...
What is all this?
Snacks and local delicacies.
Local delicacies?
From Beijing?
Yes.
Why did you buy Beijing delicacies?
For my colleagues.
You've never been so nice.
I'm craving food.
Eating a little wouldn't matter, right?
I bought so much anyway.
I can play games for a bit.
No, I can't.
I have to hand them over tomorrow.
If I don't, I'll finish everything.
Eat these on the road.
It's only a two-hour flight.
Why did you buy so much for me?
You can take them home.
Isn't your hometown a poor mountain village?
You'll have to travel far to buy things.
The general store only has cooking necessities.
They don't have any snacks.
I told you about my childhood.
My family has long since moved away.
I could have eaten more if I knew that.
But...
I really haven't tried any of these.
They might not be sold over there either.
Right?
There are two more boxes here.
Take them back with you.
How did you get those here?
I carried them up.
By yourself?
Yes,
they aren't heavy.
Why are you so silly?
You can check them in.
If you can't,
you can mail them back.
They won't expire so quickly.
There are piles of New Year goodies in my house every year.
It's a waste if we can't finish them.
Take some home.
You can enjoy them
or give them to your relatives.
It's a token from me.
I'll see you off for your flight.
I can help you carry some.
It's fine.
I can manage.
Son.
Why are you back so early?
My company let us leave early.
Why didn't your company
send any gifts this year?
They did.
Isn't everything here?
I'm not talking about these.
Doesn't your company give you
something extra every year?
The smoked meat.
The stuff I said was delicious last year.