[English subtitles are available]
[Advance Bravely]
[Episode 1]
[Kickboxing Tournament]
Ladies and Gentlemen!
Welcome
to China-U.S. Kickboxing Tournament!
We have
16 contestants tonight.
[China-U.S. Kickboxing Tournament]
They will be the stars of tonight's exciting matches!
I believe
we will witness more than a show of fists and strength.
This is also
a competition of endurance and wits!
Let's get ready
and give our most passionate cheers
for the 16 valiant warriors!
Let's welcome them to the arena!
That was an impressive hook.
That was extremely...
That was definitely a fierce move.
A very fierce move.
That American is quite aggressive.
Yeah.
Our guys are like little chicks
next to him.
The ones who entered the arena
were severely beaten up by that American.
I bet the remaining three
won't stand a chance.
Damn!
Oh, man.
Another one down.
Wow...
G-Get up.
Come on.
Get up.
Let's give it up for our Chinese contestant.
Xia Yao
and the American contestant Brown!
Xia Yao. Xia Yao. Xia Yao.
Ladies and Gentlemen,
here comes the most exciting
moment of tonight.
After three intense rounds,
Xia Yao from China
and Brown from America
are eagerly awaiting to throw their fists!
Who is the strongest?
Who will clinch the golden belt of victory?
Only the brave will triumph in this treacherous arena.
Let us shine the spotlight on the contestants in the arena.
Applaud
and cheer for them!
Xia Yao. Xia Yao. Xia Yao.
[Round 1]
Understood?
Are you ready?
Ready?
Fight!
Xia Yao. Xia Yao. Xia Yao.
Xia Yao. Xia Yao.
He delivers a sweep kick!
Amazing!
Nicely done!
A great move!
That was a sweet move!
Yes. Yes.
A clean strike!
The champion of China-U.S. Kickboxing Tournament is...
Xia Yao.
What are you doing here?
You didn't pick up my calls
or reply to my Wechat messages.
What else can I do but come look for you?
There's a cocktail party tonight,
organized just for you.
You must go.
I won't.
Don't be like this.
Dou has booked the hotel.
Beautiful girls have been invited.
You must go.
Well, I just don't get it.
It's just a cocktail party.
Do you feel particularly embarrassed to meet people?
I would do more than attend a cocktail party
if I had your looks.
I would gladly invite myself
to a red carpet event.
I'm not interested.
Who is talking?
Xia Yao,
did you hear a strange noise?
I didn't hear anything.
Who is talking?
Are you trying to scare me with ventriloquism?
Hello.
Over here.
Xia Yao,
it's mimicking my speech.
It's mimicking my speech.
Bark like a dog.
Woof!
Say Peng Ze.
Now.
Repeat after me.
Adding red beans into a dice of bone.
Xia Yao,
it's so clever.
So clever.
I'm going buy a few when I get home.
It's so cute.
It even mimics what I say.
Xia Yao,
I'm begging you.
I already promised Dou
I would get you to go.
If you don't show up,
I'll be humiliated.
Yuan Ru is attending as well.
All the more reason for me not to go.
Why?
That beauty from Northeast China is wonderful.
She has big boobs
and long legs.
Why aren't you the slightest bit interested?
This meal is on me.
You guys can have fun.
Thank Dou for me.
Tell him that I'm tired after the match.
We can
have a gathering
another time.
Xia Yao.
Please, I'm begging you!
What if I respect you like my grandpa?
Yes?
Mr. Wang.
Are you taking a walk?
Yes, I'm taking a walk
to help my digestion.
Great.
See you.
Take care.
Yao.
Auntie Li.
Where did you get this bird?
I've never seen it before.
I bought it recently.
These days, few youngsters
have elegant hobbies
like you do.
But you shouldn't be so preoccupied with walking your bird.
It's about time you got married.
You're such a great catch.
It doesn't seem right
for you to be single.
Lower your standards.
If someone suitable comes along, give it a shot.
I'm not in a rush.
Why aren't you in a rush?
How old are you?
At least twenty-six, right?
Umm,
Auntie Li,
my friend is waiting for me.
Let's chat some other time. Bye.
My goodness.
Youngsters these days
are just unbelievable.
Why?
That beauty from Northeast China is wonderful.
She has big boobs
and long legs.
Why aren't you the slightest bit interested?
Xia Yao!
Open the door.
Why did you lock the door?
Mom,
don't come in!
I'm not dressed!
Open up!
What are you doing?
Open the door!
Hey,
Mr. Xia.
Why didn't you come to the cocktail party
that was threw for you?
I didn't want to go.
Are you avoiding me?
No, I'm not.
Hey,
I'm talking to you!
Don't walk away.
The slit on your dress
reaches all the way up to your hip.
How is it?
Sexy, right?
Hey,
don't go.
Brother,
another guy has caught my eye.
But he's not interested in me.
Can you help me, please?
You're probably the only one
in the world who can deal with him.
He's the prince of Imperial City.
He was brought up well
and is insanely handsome.
His fighting skills are outstanding,
and he doesn't have any scandals or a bad history.
Here's the most astonishing part.
He's a virgin.
Think about it.
Where else can I find a man like that?
I'm the only one
who can handle him.
Brother,
I'm talking to you!
The problem is that this man
is a real immovable brick.
He doesn't waver no matter what I do.
Look at my legs.
They're so sexy and tantalizing.
Every man who sees them falls at my feet.
I let him feast his eyes every time we meet
but he doesn't show the slightest interest.
What does this mean?
It means this man is dependable.
Brother,
help me.
I promise
that you'll be charmed by him
at first sight.
Deal with him yourself.
Madam,
chewing gum, please.
That'll be ¥3.
Wh-What would you like?
The same as him.