[English subtitles are available]
[Advance Bravely]
[Episode 24]
I want to eat those meatballs, too.
Sure.
If you can catch it,
I'll toss it to you.
Okay.
Ready?
Yeah.
Three.
Two.
One.
You're so mean!
Xia Yao!
You did that on purpose!
You didn't look where you were tossing it!
One more time.
Nah! No more.
Where the heck are you?
In the Northeast.
It's so cold out there!
Why are you in Northeast?
Hey,
I mean,
dd you really fall in love with that northeastern chick?
No way.
Call him back here.
Okay.
Xia Yao.
What are you doing here?
-Is that girl looking for you? -If you don't get in, the food will be cold.
I'm hanging up.
I gotta go to eat.
Bye bye.
What are you doing?
Get in the house.
Can't you see that I'm heading out?
Go on.
I'll be fine even if I'm alone.
Don't worry about me.
I mean.
Who's worrying about you?
Who do you think you are?
Is this your house?
Do you think you can come and go as you please?
I'm here to spend the holidays with you.
What holidays?
The Lantern Festival!
Have you forgotten
that it's the fifteenth of the first lunar month?
No, I haven't.
but I don't remember agreeing to spend it with you.
Hey.
Have you forgotten?
It was the fifth or the sixth of the New Year.
And you said you wanted to spend the holidays with me.
I was talking about that one particular day,
not today.
We already spent that day together.
Why not today?
We already spent that day together then.
Why must we be together today?
That's because we spent that day together.
Don't quarrel with me.
Just get out of here.
How can you do this to me?
I even canceled my gig at the temple fair for this.
The wage today is supposed to be doubled!
I made sacrifice for you!
So you're saying I have something to do with you quitting your job?
Did I force you to quit?
I mean,
I bought glutinous balls here to celebrate.
It's gonna be a waste if we don't eat them together.
Where are you planing to go during the New Year?
-Hey. -Come on.
Hurry and cook those glutinous rice balls.
Leave once you're done eating.
Roger.
Is it that delicious?
It's so sweet.
Don't you think it's too sweet?
Not at all.
When I was a child, I loved eating glutinous rice balls.
Back then, my grandmother used to make handmade glutinous rice balls,
and they tasted much better than the ones available elsewhere.
Let's hang out in the afternoon.
Nope.
Fine.
I'll entertain myself.
What's so fun about being alone?
Why can't I have fun alone?
I've always played by myself from childhood.
I don't believe it.
There are so many people on the street,
and they're all in pairs.
That's true.
I also went to the temple fair alone.
Everyone has their odd moments.
Fine.
I'll hang out with you.
Joyrides, hitting on girls,
or clubs.
Pick whatever you want.
I'll pay.
Wow, there are so many people here.
Please make way. Make way.
Hey!
I don't get it.
You're here all the time.
How come you still came here when you're off work?
Indeed, I'm here all the time.
But I never truly spent my time here.
When I was dancing and performing on stage,
my biggest wish was
joining the crowd down there
enjoying the show,
and buying some stuff.
It would be so much fun.
Come here.
Such a loser.
It's so fun!
Hit it.
This is for you.
Wow.
I bought it for 47,000 yuan.
If you want to sell it,
you can raise the price.
What does your family do for a living?
Why are you so rich?
It's not your business.
Who's richer?
You or Xia Yao?
My family can't be compared to his.
What?
Then,
why does Xia Yao
look so poor?
Some things can't be measured by money.
I'd rather
grovel and lick someone else's boots
just to drive a fancy car.
You're helpless.
It's so beautiful.
Is this really gold?
Hey, Wang Zhishui,
why are you so lame?
Give it to me.
My gosh, it really is gold!
I'm taking it back.
I won't give it to you.
Hey, you said it's a gift for me.
How can you take it back?
Because I've never seen someone looks so jobless as you do.
Have a look.
Cheap prices!
How much is it?
Five.
What is this?
Come and take a look.
Five yuan for each.
Hey, how about 10 yuan for three of this?
Take one.
I'll give you a discount, don't go.
Do you wanna play this?
Roller coaster.
I'm not playing that.
It's no fun.
It's thrilling!
Come on! Take a look over here.
Five yuan for each. Five yuan for each!
Here! Take a look.
Cheap prices!
Let's go.
Take a look at this one.
How much is this?
Six yuan.
Six yuan?
Let's buy one.
Take a look.
Take a look over here.
Five yuan for each. Five yuan for each.
Childish.
Ten yuan for three of this.
Wow, let's get one.
I'll give you a discount. Don't go.
Hey, take a look. It's cheap here.
Hey.
Come and have a look.
Do you want some cotton candy?
Yeah! Sure!
I want some!
Stickers! All kinds of stickers!
10 yuan for 3 pieces!
I want to have this mushroom plushie!
Come and have a look.
Sir,
how much is it?
Ten yuan
for 10 bullets.
And if you can hit the target five times,
you can pick whatever you want.
Take it!
You're awesome!
Hey, sir!
You haven't paid for the game!
Well, then.
You can go home now.
I'll walk you home.
No!
You should leave.
I don't need you to walk me in.
Go home.
Just go.
Go.
I really don't need you to walk me in.
I can go by myself. You should leave now.
Come on.
Hey.
-It's fine. -You should go back now.
Go.
Darn it!
How dare you come back?
Come.
Come on in!
Get in.
Mom!
It hurts!
Mom.
My friend is still here.
Will you stop embarrassing me?
Am I embarrassing you?
Look at what you have done.
Do I need to think about how you feel right now?
Auntie.
I asked Xia Yao come over.
I had a family emergency and needed his help.
It's my fault that
I didn't inform you in the beginning.
Couldn't he tell me first?
A call wouldn't take up much of your time!
He's intentionally trying to annoy us,
-refusing to go to the blind date! I'll give you a lesson! -Blind date?
I'll hit...
Auntie.
I made him come over.
At the time,
he called me to request a few extra days off,
and coincidentally I needed someone to help out urgently,
so I called him over temporarily.
It was my fault that
he didn't inform you about this.
Mom.
Look,
I brought you some Harbin sausages.
His family made these themselves.
And this,
smoked meat.
Weren't you complaining that we didn't receive any this year?
He made these for you.
Smell it.
It's definitely as good as the stuff we received.
Yuan Zong,
did you really make these yourself?
Mom.
I even brought this back to you.
The most authentic mountain delicacies from the northeast.
They're great for making soup and braising meat.
I even brought back ginseng
and antlers.
All the best stuff from the northeast
are here.
All right, all right.
Tell me
before you leave next time.
If you pull this nonsense again,
I'll twist your ears off,
understand?
Yuan Zong.
Come here.
Have a seat.
Come and have a seat.
Does your ear still hurt?
It doesn't,
but it's burning.
You're a grown man.
Why does your mom still punish you?
Alas,
an old woman
like her is probably lonely.
What's up with that blind date thing?
During the New Year festival,
my dad set up a blind date for me.
He wanted me to meet her.
Then?
Nothing happened.
Is it good?
Hey,
did that guy
really make these smoked meat?
Wow,
he doesn't seem like
he can cook.
Then, you're totally wrong.
Not only can he cook,
but he's also quite the chef.
That sticky rice lotus root dish you often praise,
well, it wasn't something I bought
He actually made it himself.
Really?
That's impressive, isn't it?
Yeah, duh!
What a good boy.
If any girl can marry him,
she must be very lucky.
What are you laughing at?
You should learn from him.
The number you dialed is busy now.
[Xuan Dayu]
The number you have called is busy now.
Weird.
Why can't I get through to his phone?
Where is this guy?
[Peng Ze]
What's up, Yao?
Hey,
do you know where Dayu is?
I don't know.
I haven't been in touch with him for a long time.
What's the matter?
I can ask around
if you're looking for him.
It's fine.
I'll do it myself.
Okay.
What brings you here?
I've been looking for you for quite a few days.
Why didn't you pick up my calls?
I also spent days looking for you.
Did you pick up my calls?
I was in the northeast back then.
Don't even mention about that.
I don't want to hear it.
You're mad now, huh?
You broke my heart.
So I have erased all my longing.
Do you have to be that dramatic?
It's just that I didn't pick up
your calls or chat with you.
Xia Yao, listen up.
It's not just about the phone calls.
What place do I hold in your heart?
And how much significance do you have in mine?
You should think about it.
You've been hiding all kinds of secrets.
You should be well aware of that.
Rich Xuan!
Mr. Xuan!
Xuan, the rich guy!
Sir!
What are you doing here?
I went to look for a famous store selling sour and spicy noodles.
The two bowls I ate yesterday weren't enough,
so I went to buy more today.
I brought them here for you to try.
Try it.
I guarantee that it's spicy, sour, and flavorful.
If you like rich tastes,
I have two extra packets of vinegar.
Piss off!