[English subtitles are available]
[TharnType 2 : 7 Years of Love]
What are you doing?
Oh, you wanted to be romantic,
but you ruined it, right?
Don't be upset.
I'm on my holiday, but I still have to get up early for you.
I wanted to do something for you
because you aren't working today.
And blow up the house?
I won't. I was baking a cake.
Oh, never know you'll make me a cake.
Yes, as you can see.
But what I saw was you trying to blow up the house.
-And...
-And what?
I think
you'd better do something else that you're good at.
It's your precious holiday.
I was going to let you take a good rest at first.
I didn't ask you to do that.
You eat like a child, it's all over your mouth.
Wipe it properly.
Can you stop nagging?
That's how I always eat.
And you always ask me to wipe your mouth.
Then clean it for me.
By the way, have you finished talking with your mom?
That's why you have time to talk to me?
Yes.
I told her.
I came back because of your knee.
What?
Then she'll blame me for your return.
My reputation as a "good son" has been ruined.
No.
I should call your mom
and tell her it was your own decision to come back.
You don't have to call her.
Your position as the "good son" is still there.
I told her
that I came back because I found out from my teammates.
If she blames you,
it's because you didn't tell her when you were in the hospital, okay?
She almost booked the earliest flight back
when she knew that you were in the hospital.
But I told her that you're much better now.
Oh.
Looks like
I have to call her tonight and say I love her.
Whatever.
At this point, I don't know whose mother she is.
Oh, I almost forgot.
This is from my teammate.
Hey, aren't these the shoes I wanted?
They're on sale, and they're just around here.
Can you take me there, please?
Your knee hasn't recovered yet.
Do you want to make it worse?
Choose the one you want.
I'll look for it.
No, I want to choose it myself.
You're injured. You should more careful.
What if I don't like what you pick?
Please, Leo, let me go.
Please? Please?
Alright.
Don't complain to me later.
I promise I won't.
Look into my eyes.
Okay, Leo?
Please take me with you, please.
Don't you feel bad for me?
I'll get the car, come out after you finish it.
I love you the most in the world.
You love whoever can satisfy you.
I'm hungry.
Well,
I'll cook something for you.
What do you want to eat?
I said I'm hungry.
I wanted to invite you to eat out with me.
Do you want to go on a date?
It's rare for you to invite me on a date.
Of course I have to go.
Go take a shower first.
I'll take a shower there.
Okay.
Hurry up.
Or do you want to shower with me?
Stop seducing me, Type.
I'm really hungry.
Go take a shower quickly.
I'm going to take a shower.
Okay.
-Tharn.
-Yes.
Is this where Thorn proposed to Ahn?
Yes.
That's why I brought you here.
Tharn.
My staff texted me. You can read it.
A teacher asked for a discount on the guitar string and bass string.
That's why my employee texted me and asked me how much of a discount should be given.
I didn't say anything.
But I want to tell you,
so that you can be at ease.
Do whatever you want.
Tell me about your website. How's it going?
My website?
It's been quite good recently.
Many people like shopping online nowadays.
So I got more orders.
I just hired a new admin to monitor the website.
And I plan to open a physical store soon.
I'm looking at the location now.
Isn't it a bit rushed?
Don't forget that you just started your online business.
What should you do
if it only does well for a while?
Are you worried about me?
I've studied the market.
If the sales are bad,
I'll use the physical store to store the goods.
In this way, I don't need to put it in my dad's warehouse.
I don't want to bother him.
Even so,
you think too far ahead.
Think about it.
Take your time. Don't rush.
I'm not.
I'm just anxious.
I hope to provide you with a stable and secure life.
Besides,
I want to take care of you as much as I can.
I can work. I can take care of myself.
And I can take care of you too.
To be honest, maybe you're not sure about it now.
But in the future,
can you put on our wedding ring?
Dream on.
Finish your meal and pay the bill.
We have to buy some household stuff later.
Eat. It tastes good.
Okay.
Shopping together like this
reminds me of our first year.
Why are you recalling the past now?
I begged you for a long time
to ask you out at that time.
Look at you now.
You've become the financial director of our family.
If I'm not in charge,
you would simply spend without a second thought.
I haven't counted
the money you spent treating your colleagues to dinner yet.
I know you're rich,
but you need to learn to save money, too.
That's why I can't live without you.
Screw you. Stop flirting.
I've lost count of how many times you've succeeded.
I'm tired, Type.
I'll put the stuff in the car first.
And I'll come back to flirt with you later, okay?
Okay. Come back soon.
Damn it, when are you going to get over the love-sick phase?
We've been together for years.
I'll leave this with you.
I need to use the toilet.
Come back here after you're done.
Hurry up, Leo.
It's going to sell out.
Slow down. Mind your knee.
I told you, I'm afraid that it'll sell out.
Didn't you say today was the last day of the promotion?
But I told you
that I can help you buy it.
Why do you still insist on coming together?
I'm afraid that you would pick the wrong one.
So troublesome.
So what?
Don't you love me anymore?
-Brother Type. Brother Type.
-It's you.
Are you shopping?
I'm here to buy something.
How's your knee? Are you okay to be here?
Oh, I feel much better.
Thank you for your advice.
I've reflected on myself.
I have to at least heal my knee for myself.
I'm glad you think that way.
Don't forget to come for rehabilitation practices at the time we agreed on.
Okay.
Well, Brother Type, this is Leo.
My friend.
Leo, this is Brother Type.
I told you. He's in charge of my rehabilitation.
Hello.
Take care of your friend.
Don't let him walk too far.
I just walked a bit, brother.
I have to go. Goodbye.
Brother Type, I'll text you later.
Text me when you have something important.
Okay.
Brother Type is cute, right?
But he's too cold.
I'm so handsome, but he shows no interest in me.
What do you think?
Leo, where are you going?
You said you were worried about my knee.
Who were those two guys?
A patient from the hospital.
I ran into him, so I asked him about his injury.
Really?
So stop looking at them.
If not, your eyes are going to meet.
And they'll fall for your charm again.
I'm sick of being jealous.
Who is the charming one,  actually?
Have you realized?
You're the only one who likes me because you're out of your mind.
How I wish I were the only one.
Who else could it be?
Let's go. Aren't you going to buy books?
-Let's go.
-Okay.
Who was that?
-Which one?
-The guy you just saw.
Are you deaf or forgetful?
I told you.
He's in charge of my rehabilitation at the hospital.
I know that.
But your gaze tells that he's more than that.
Why? What's with my gaze?
I can tell what you're thinking, okay?
Take it easy.
Look at your friend's face.
People like me
never fail to get what I want,
except for one thing.
That you'll never stop whining at me.
Oh, right.
Hurry up and pick one for me. My knees are starting to hurt.
Didn't I tell you not to complain?
Alright.
Which pair do you want?
I want this.
-This pair?
-No, lower.
This one?
No, that one.
-This?
-Yes. Yes.
What do you think? Do you like it?
It's light. It'll be comfortable.
-Can you wear this size?
-I can.
Try it.
How is it?
Pretty good.
Is it comfortable?
Do I look good?
You're really...
[Restaurant No. 5]
-What are you doing here, doctor?
-Well...
Well, I...
How did you get here? Are you alone?
I...
I didn't come here for you.
I... I just got lost.
Yes, I got lost.
Oh, I didn't say anything.
Did something happen?
No, I'm fine.
I really got lost.
Yeah, I know.
If you don't believe me, I can explain.
I took the wrong turn and...
I remember... I remember...
Your shop happens to be nearby.
So I...
I...
I just remembered that your shop was nearby.
Then when I realized it...
When I realized it,
I was already in front of your shop.
Oh, I see.
Look.
Hey, it really worked, doctor.
Are other staff coming?
Did you invite anyone else?
Well...
You...
You're too close to me, Champ.
Really?
I'm sorry.
This is how I get along with my friends.
It's okay.
Why? Are you shy?
You're still so shy.
You're so cute.
-Since you're here, let's get inside.
-Hey.
I... I told you I took the wrong turn.
Since you came to my shop by mistake,
I'll take you to something delicious. Let's go.
Here, my signature dish.
Chicken Breast with Super Herbal Sauce.
Do you know how many herbs
I've studied for this dish?
If I didn't come up with this dish,
I would sell herbs instead.
That's funny.
Who would have thought someone like me
would open a restaurant.? Not even I.
Doctor.
Are you okay? Are you sleep deprived?
I'm sure you stayed up all night reading again.
Speaking of this,
I suddenly remembered when we were in our first year.
You always read at night.
And I can't sleep because of you.
Do you know that
I almost changed rooms with Type that time?
Thankfully, there's Tharn.
I found someone to switch rooms with you.
Who?
Hey, Champ! This way! Come here!
What's wrong, No?
This is the guy who wants to change rooms with you.
He's the only one who's willing to change rooms with you.
Yes, I was looking for someone to change rooms too.
It's not because my roommate is not good,
but because he studies medicine.
I couldn't sleep because he was up studying all night.
So I want to change rooms with someone.
You can discuss it yourselves.
Go to the Student Dormitory Service Centre later.
I won't change.
Thank you for offering to change rooms with me.
But my roommate and I still have things to do.
Sorry for wasting your time.
It's okay. Tell me if you want to change later.
Bye.
Guess who's the reason I can't focus on reading?
Who are you referring to?
Nothing.
Kun, what are you doing?
Why do you look so serious?
I'm preparing for the lab test this afternoon.
I'm not very confident.
You're kidding. How are you not confident?
Because I'm not.
Papeng, I think Champ has been trolling on me lately.
Champ? Your roommate?
Why? Did he do something to you?
He didn't do anything.
-Oh.
-Actually,
It's not entirely his fault.
It's mostly my fault.
Recently,
Champ likes to walk naked without his top in the room.
I can't focus on reading.
I have to wait until Champ falls asleep,
then only I can focus on reading.
And then?
I mean, it's summer time.
So Champ always walks in the room in his underwear.
And I feel so awkward.
I don't know what to do.
Not to mention reading,
forcing myself to not look at Champ
is way harder than focusing on reading.
Did he make you shy?
I'm not.
My cutie pie.
What should I do, Papeng?
I can't focus on reading at all.
It's okay.
Why are you laughing, doctor?
Nothing. I'm just
thinking about something.
Okay, then.
Try it and see if it tastes good.
I've been thinking about this recipe for a long time.
Then it must be delicious.
You...
You said it was delicious before you took a bite.
Try it first.
Okay.
I'll eat it then.
Hey.
It tastes good, Champ.
You seem to be in a good mood recently.
Maybe it's because Ahn agreed to my proposal.
I envy you.
Does that make you think about you and Type?
Yes, a little.
I don't know when he'll say yes.
Just like what Type said,
marriage is not a child's play.
Give him some time.
Brother, I've always been serious about Type.
I know.
But don't forget, Tharn.
Even though we can ignore what others think,
But Type is right.
Our society hasn't really accepted it yet.
Type must be worried about this.
And he's afraid that it'll affect dad and mom's reputation.
But I don't care.
No one in our family cares about this.
But he does.
He cares about you and our family.
Give him some time.
It's like I don't know him at all,
even though I know what he's thinking.
Okay, I can wait until he's ready.
Hang in there.
Excuse me, Mr. Thorn.
Mr Tharn.
I'm bringing you coffee and dessert.
Thank you.
I haven't asked you to come in yet. Get out.
Don't come in unless I tell you to.
Sorry, Mr. Thorn.
It's almost noon,
and I thought Mr. Tharn might be hungry.
So I brought some snacks here.
If there's nothing else, I'll get going.
But if you need anything, Mr. Tharn,
you can call me anytime.
Okay.
I told you to leave. Please.
What made our Mr. Thorn Thara
so annoyed?
Anyone can tell that she's here to seduce you.
But I already have Type.
Don't forget that I don't like women.
I know, but I don't really like her.
She came in to seduce me before
until she found out that Ahn and I were getting married.
She probably thinks that you're still single.
So you're her new target.
If you don't like her,
why do you keep her here?
Speaking of work, she's actually a skilled worker.
Isn't it inappropriate to just fire her?
Are you done signing it?
Yes.
I'll go back now.
I'm going to buy dinner for Type tonight.
You've taken good care of him.
I hope he will be softhearted
and marry you soon.
I hope so too.
-I'll get going.
-Okay.
Call me if anything happens.
-Champ
-Yes?
I'll get going.
Thank you for being my guest today.
When I develop new menus later,
I'll let you try it.
Okay.
I'll come to you when I'm free.
But if you find a nice restaurant,
let me know.
So that I can try it,
and come back to improve my recipe.
Okay.
Well...
Can I ask you out?
Of course. Why not?
Look, you're getting cute again.
Are you going back to the hospital now?
Yes, I'm on duty.
Okay, go ahead, or you'll be late.
Hey.
Sorry, I forgot again.
-I'll get going.
-Okay.
Take care. Don't get lost this time.
But it would be nice to see you here often.
Okay, see you next time.
Okay.
[Get some rest. I'm worried about you.]
What are you filming?
I'm swearing my sovereignty over you.
Ridiculous.
Type.
Yes?
Well...
I'm
worried about you.
You always say you could hang on when you can't.
Because you want to work for a full year.
You know it.
So don't worry about me.
Anyway, if I really can't hold on,
I'll resign and let you support me.
Well,
resign now, then.
I have no problem supporting you.
You crazy.
Anyway, I still can handle it. Trust me.
If you want me to trust you,
stop your work,
and have dinner.
As for
the coffee,
I'll pour it out.
[Techno: Tharn, my man is a perfect husband material.]
[Thanya: Who's your man, Techno? He is Brother Type's man.]
[PuGan: LOL, Thanya.]
[Nana: I also want to be cared for. What should I do?]
[The photo wall of Tharn]
[Nana liked this.]
Who is it this time?
Here it comes. Thank you.
Excuse me, can I get 10% off?
Well, he just left.
He's smiling. That means...
We need to register as a member first.
Is this enough? I don't think so.
-Excuse me. Excuse me.
-No.
Five minutes ago, you said
that you're full with your mom's cooking.
You're still the same after so many years.
You're still a big eater.
None of your business. Tell me about you.
Isn't your husband going to perform today?
Why are you here? You're not going to guard him?
-You jerk!
-You jerk.
Speaking of Tharn,
I think the older he gets, the more attractive he is.
Do you think so?
The older he gets, the sexier he is. Like a daddy.
Especially when he was on the sofa that day.
I remember it very clearly.
That moan was amazing.
-Damn it, I get hit on my right face.
-You talk too much.
I was just kidding, screw you.
Do you want me to order some dessert?
It can relieve stress, right?
You deserve a beating.
Even if he's charming like you said,
I can't stay by his side every day.
Why?
Last time,
I ran into Jeed when I went there.
She kept boozing me
until I was so dizzy that I almost got late for work the next day.
Did you say that you were dizzy because you were drunk?
-Of course.
-Oh.
I thought you had drunk...
Oops, I thought it was something else.
You're dirty-minded.
I can hear you even on the sofa, you jerk.
Okay, I'll stop.
Speaking of Tharn,
he's indeed charming.
A few days ago, when I went shopping,
I saw him walking with a woman.
-Oh, my...
-What?
Is he with a woman?
Did I spill the beans again?
I had it slip out again. What should I do?
Type.
Tell me everything.
No, I really can't tell you.
I really can't.
But if you takeaway 2 Brownies...
-I'll buy you five.
-Deal.
-Here's the thing. Listen carefully.
-You really only care about food.
You jerk, food is always number one.
Especially when it's free.
Here's the thing.
I planned to watch a movie a few days ago.
But it's not time yet.
So I went downstairs for dinner.
Then I suddenly wanted to use the toilet,
so I was walking to the toilet.
Then I glanced at the right,
I saw Tharn.
I thought it was Tharn.
Was it him? I'm not sure.
It must be Tharn. Okay, let's eat first.
Let's eat first.
-Tell me first.
-You messed up my hair, jerk.
Okay, leave it here. I can tell you first.
Well...
Every time I see Tharn, I see you, right?
You two come in set, you're always together.
Right, so I looked around when I saw him,
and didn't see you.
I was going to say hello to him,
and ask him if he saw you, or where you were.
It's like we were in a drama, you know?
The first step, we got nothing. And the second step,
the director said "stop".
It was stopped without any obstacles.
Then a woman just walked over.
I was shocked.
That woman was coming for Tharn.
She said hi, and talked to him, like they were close to each other.
And I thought it must be. Yes, it is.
But I can't hold on to my poop anymore,
so I went to the toilet in the end.
Otherwise, I would've followed them. I missed the chance.
What a pity.
Don't worry. I understand.
Five Brownie, takeaway.
-Go and order.
-Okay.
Excuse me, I want to order.
I'd like five Brownie, takeaway please.
It's on him. Thanks.
Eat up. Worrying won't help.
Have some tea. Don't think too much.
[Nana liked this.]
So you are here.
Dr. Thiti wants you at his office.
Okay, thank you.
[I've been working hard on rehabilitation lately, Brother Type.]
[I want to get better soon, so I can play basketball with my friends again.]
Are you serious about him?
Yes.
♫I want you to know everything hidden in my heart♫
♫If you try to become me♫
♫You'll understand♫
Type.
Didn't you say you wanted to watch this movie?
You're just playing with your phone.
Fine. I'll watch it with you.
So you really can't come over?
I was going to ask you here to meet Mr. Tharn.
[If I hadn't been called to work at the last minute,]
[I would've gone.]
[I'm curious to see how handsome is the man that you fall for.]
He's handsome and smart.
His personality, appearance, and behavior are perfect.
If I can get him,
everyone would envy me.
Most importantly, I've checked.
He is definitely single.
I've already missed Mr. Thorn.
I'll get him no matter what.
[You should've had some background check on him.]
[See? That's why you failed.]
I know, right?
After I've set my eyes on Mr. Tharn,
I'm thrilled to think
that I was able to get away from Mr. Thorn in time.
The younger brother is even better.
He's the youngest son, but he owns the same amount of assets.
[Fine. You've said it more than 10 times.]
[Then what are you going to do?]
Since I'm going to seduce him,
I'll take a leave, and ask him out for dinner.
[Good luck, then.]
[I'm going to work. My boss is going to scold me.]
Okay, let's talk next time.
[Current Location]
[I was just passing by your house. Do you want to have dinner together?]
[Okay, see you later.]
[Plan for Type's Husband]
[Techno invites Thorn and Thanya to the group chat]
[Thorn joins the group chat]
[Thanya joins the group chat]
[Champ: Wow. You even brought Brother Thorn and Thanya in.]
[Techno: Stay still.]
[Techno: It's just a few more helpers.]
[Thorn: That's it? I'm just a helper?]
[Techno: Of course not. You're the leader of the group.]
[Techno: Hey, did you see the photos on Tharn's photo wall?]
[Techno: It's so sweet.]
[Thanya: I think you just want to gossip.]
[Thorn: Tut, tut, tut. Your Highness, you shouldn't say that.]
[Champ: So... Did he really betray Type?]
[Techno: Type already knows. Just wait and see.]