(Lee Je Hoon)
(Lee Dong Hwi)
(Kwak Dong Yeon)
(Cha Eun Woo)
(Rented In Finland)
(The Renters visit a husky house.)
(They will be taking care of huskies for a day.)
(I've never seen anything like that.)
(The huskies that pull sleds...)
(are essential in Lapland.)
(After receiving help in the winter, )
(taking care of huskies is part of their life during the summer.)
Doesn't that feel good?
(The Renters fall in love with the huskies.)
(Or it seemed that way.)
(Not only do they try to escape, )
(but they also push you with their bodies.)
(It's impossible to match their energy.)
(An essential part of the husky house schedule)
(We're going hiking.)
(Hiking with them?)
(They go crazy even before they leave.)
(Hurry! Let's go for a walk!)
(They are soon left dazed.)
(Getting dragged away)
(An uncomfortable journey begins.)
Skeef.
- Yelka. - Skeef.
- Skeef. - Miyu.
Sakha.
- Yelka. - Miyu.
(They try Lapland-style husky hiking.)
- Wait, Yelka. - Skeef.
They're all barking because they want to go fast.
Yes?
(Hurry.)
(A barking surround sound system)
(Feeling dazed)
(Going crazy)
You can see she's strong.
Yes.
(Huskies get physically and mentally stressed when they hold energy in.)
(During the summer when they can't pull sleds, )
(hikes are essential for them to let out their energy.)
Look at Miyuki.
(She was so calm before.)
She wants to follow the dog in front.
(They go wild as they go for a walk.)
(Miyuki)
- Miyuki. - You have veered off route.
- Finding a new route. - Miyuki.
This is unbelievable.
(Even Dongdong's owner, who has experience, is confused.)
(Sakha)
Sakha.
(Another dog veers off route.)
When we arrive...
- Sakha. - Sakha, this way.
(It's impossible to hold a conversation.)
(Sakha)
No.
(Sakha loves to stray off course.)
Wait.
Stop.
(He's being dragged around.)
- Super. - Sakha.
It looks like you're being dragged around.
(We'll walk you.)
Gosh, it must be challenging for her to walk all of them.
I know.
(Not even taking a walk is easy in Lapland.)
- Skeef calmed down. - I see.
Now it's quieter.
(The huskies have calmed down after 10 minutes.)
Skeef doesn't go off course at all.
It's like autonomous cruising.
Skeef, autopilot.
(Skeef's autopilot mode is on.)
Skeef.
(Input, Output)
Good dog, Skeef.
Turn left, Skeef.
He's good at taking instructions.
He doesn't go off course.
(He passes the lane-changing test.)
(It's a calm drive with autopilot Skeef.)
He's so cute.
All right.
(There is a couple that is enjoying their date.)
Does that make you happy?
Let's go slowly.
(I love taking walks.)
Is that so?
Okay.
No.
Stop.
- She's so nice. - Yes.
Je Hoon's dog is the nicest.
Yes, she is.
She probably doesn't walk them by herself, right?
- I'm sure she has employees. - Right?
I walk all the dogs..
And do their training.
- What? - All of them?
- Alone? - Yes.
So it's nice to have help.
That's a relief.
Much better.
We're going to arrive at a lake soon.
- Yes. - Okay.
(Where is the destination of their husky hike?)
Look at that lake.
It's a huge lake.
(The lake is part of the hiking course?)
They know where we are going and are so happy.
Yes, she's so happy.
(They get happier as they approach the lake.)
- Just stop here. - Okay.
Sakha.
Miyu.
(The huskies see the lake.)
I'm going to check.
What?
- Gosh. - Gosh.
(Jumping in boldly)
He looks so excited.
(Swimming in the lake?)
Miyuki.
(I can't stand this.)
Miyuki, stop.
Okay. 1, 2, 3, let's go.
(Miyuki...)
(jumps in too.)
Come on, Mimi.
(Miyuki boldly swims forward.)
(This is why I enjoy swimming.)
(Proud)
Gosh.
- Okay. - Go on.
They're excited.
Look at how excited they are.
- They want to play. - Gosh.
(The huskies give off happy energy in the lake instead of the snow.)
It's okay. Come.
I didn't know dogs loved water this much.
- Gosh. - They look so happy.
They look really happy.
(They look so happy.)
(Lapland is the happiest country for both people and animals.)
We go along this.
- This is a big island. - Okay.
We'll go behind it, around it, and everywhere.
- Really? That island? - Yes.
How? By boat?
No, during wintertime, we sled.
- I see. It's ice during wintertime. - Ice.
(On the vast snow-covered lake, )
- That would be awesome. - On the ice.
(the huskies run fiercely.)
(Proud)
It must be beautiful.
(Visit again in winter.)
You can catch the dogs.
Take your own dogs.
(Now it's time to go home.)
- Let's go. - Yelka likes swimming.
(Yelka looks comfortable.)
You have to come back, Yelka.
- Yelka. - Let's go home.
- Here, Yelka. - Yelka.
She even refuses a snack.
Yelka, it's a snack.
(She prefers swimming over snacks.)
What are you going to do?
Yelka.
- Good job. - Yelka.
(She finally comes out after Je Hoon desperately calls her.)
Stop it.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
(Barking)
They're at it again. They are full of energy.
- Yes. - Skeef.
Skeef.
They'll have a good nap when they go home.
(Passing out after letting out their energy)
(The Renters are about to pass out too.)
- Je Hoon. - Yes?
I'm suddenly exhausted.
Dogs are different here.
Wait. Since you're tired...
(I brought this knowing we'd need it.)
- I brought this. - What is it?
What is that?
It's Kopiko.
You'll feel less tired if you have it.
That's interesting.
I eat it when I'm tired.
Do I just leave it in my mouth?
Yes, you let it melt.
- It's energizing. - Yes, it is.
After having this...
You can leave first. I think I can walk more dogs.
(The Renters get another taste of Lapland life through the huskies.)
- That was nice. - It was nice.
- I loved it. - I feel good.
(Let's meet again.)
Let's go.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
Walking the dogs is a lot of work.
(How does she walk 30 dogs daily?)
(The Renters are overwhelmed by the energy of the huskies.)
(Wait a second.)
(If they continue driving down this road...)
It's deep in the forest.
Yes, it is. We've been driving down this path for ten minutes.
Was it this far?
(They drive down the rough unpaved road for 1 hour.)
- This road seems endless. - I know.
- We have to go even further? - Gosh.
It feels like we're entering...
a part of the world nature is trying to keep us out of.
My phone has no reception.
I lost signal.
(No reception, no neighbors)
There must be bears here.
(Rented room in the woods)
(They can't even imagine going out.)
We'll have to scream for help.
(They will be secluded deep in the forest until they move out.)
We're in trouble.
We don't have anything to eat at home.
Should we stop by a supermarket to buy a few things?
Yes, we should do that.
(We'll starve if we go home like this.)
What should we eat today?
(The city boys always ordered food when in the city.)
For dinner...
(They worry about every meal in the countryside of Lapland.)
Dinner? There is a food that's recently become my favorite.
I like kimchi, but we didn't have it at all.
- That's right. - Yes.
I thought everyone would ask for kimchi.
- So I brought plenty of it. - That's right.
I have kimchi too.
You do?
- Did you bring it? - Yes, I did.
(He leans forward when he hears about kimchi.)
I feel like kimchi and pork belly.
(I want kimchi and pork belly.)
(Pork belly and kimchi, Koreans' soul food)
Kimchi and pork belly.
My mouth is watering.
Should we have a barbecue today?
(Say no more.)
Let's do it.
Sounds good.
(He applauds the decision.)
As we have plenty of kimchi,
- we can also make stew. - Sounds good.
That's more than enough.
(Kimchi stew, the life of Koreans)
Master Kwak.
I've suddenly been promoted to master.
(Congratulations on being promoted from Mr. Kwak to Master Kwak.)
You went from Mr. Kwak to Master Kwak.
(He boosts the energy of the chef before he starts cooking.)
Master Kwak.
This will be the best feast ever.
(Look forward to it.)
But will they have...
pork belly at the supermarket?
They should have it, right?
(Will they have pork belly in the countryside?)
I was talking to Mailys earlier.
- We're staying in Posio, right? - Yes.
She said it was a city.
- It is? - It's the busiest area?
It's practically considered a city.
- Downtown? - Yes, it's downtown.
That's right.
It's downtown Posio.
- Yes. - That's right.
(This small area with a radius of 50km is the busiest area.)
(The city boys head downtown as a group for the first time.)
(They start seeing it.)
This is downtown.
It's downtown.
I feel energized.
It's like my HP is being charged.
(Welcome to downtown Posio.)
Look at that couple walking hand in hand.
- Yes. - It's so sweet.
(They feel jealous of the people in town for some reason.)
It seems busy today.
(They are surprised to see a crowd for a change.)
We're here.
(The city boys have arrived in town.)
I hope we're allowed to park here. Let's park here.
(They park as soon as they see a parking lot.)
- Thanks for driving. - Don't worry about it.
Goodness.
(What is in the countryside town of Finland?)
Isn't that building pretty?
Yes, it is.
It has a pharmacy and police station.
(It's a public building with a pharmacy and police station.)
The police station opens only three days a week.
Really? Not every day?
No.
- How is that possible? - That's amazing.
I like the size of this town.
I see a cafe. Why don't we have coffee...
before we go home?
We have nothing at home.
- You're right. Should we buy some? - Yes.
Let's stop by the cafe before going to the supermarket?
- Should we have something to drink? - Let's have coffee.
- Should we have some coffee? - Sounds good.
- Why don't we cross here? - Okay.
- Let's use the crosswalk. - Okay.
It'd be great if they had donuts.
Yes, that'd be great.
They wouldn't have iced Americano, would they?
I don't think they have it.
(They lose their minds at the first sighting of a cafe.)
- Iced Americano. - You're right.
I'm sure they have ice.
You can add it.
(What do they have at a cafe in the European countryside?)
I cross like the Beatles.
One at a time?
(The Renters)
(They're so excited.)
You know what?
I prefer places with stores...
(Laughing)
than the countryside...
with nothing but nature.
Je Hoon, that's what I mean.
I wish we could stay longer.
Let's enjoy downtown while we're here.
Enjoy civilization.
Cafe Sorrento.
(Happy to find a cafe in the countryside)
Dong Hwi looks ecstatic.
Look at this.
(Skipping)
(The youngest skips out of excitement.)
Ice cream?
They have ice cream?
(The ice cream sign triggers a dopamine explosion.)
- They have ice cream. - We chose the right place.
(What is the only cafe downtown that excited the Renters like?)
- It's nice. - I like the cafe's vibe.
(It has a vintage vibe.)
(It's where people from all over town gather.)
Good morning.
(They are surprised to see the splendid civilization.)
(There is so much to see.)
- It looks like a Western movie. - It's American-style.
- It looks like a movie set. - Chevrolet.
(They haven't been at a place with electricity for a long time.)
The bread looks tasty.
They seem to bake it here.
Here?
(Really?)
(He approaches the baked goods.)
They also have cookies.
(Homemade cookies and bread)
Have one.
They have a set menu.
Over here.
This is insane.
(They marvel at the ice cream and coffee set.)
How did they come up with that set?
(Even small things seem interesting after time in the countryside.)
- I need to have that ice cream. - Me too.
- Me too. - Nice.
(Even frugal Dong Yeon can't think straight right now.)
I want this.
(Swallowing hard)
(Are they from the forest?)
Three of this combination,
and 1 coffee, 2 vanillas,
- and one of these. - Okay.
(I'm excited.)
(Here comes the ice cream.)
They have an ice cream machine.
- They use a machine. - It's an ice cream dispenser.
I'll have vanilla too.
Dong Yeon, can you pay?
(Did something urgent come up?)
(While they're in town, )
I need to use the restroom.
(he uses the restroom.)
I need to pee but don't want to go to the bathroom.
(The sawdust bathroom makes them hold it in.)
(How long has it been since they had a flushing toilet?)
(He looks much brighter.)
Is our order ready?
I need to use the restroom too.
(They take turns using the flushing toilet.)
- I'll use the restroom. - Okay.
Me too.
(The atmosphere has gotten lighter.)
(They now fully enjoy civilization.)
Who wants this?
Isn't this Eric Clapton, one of Dong Yeon's favorite singers?
(That's right.)
(While the duet...)
(is busy singing)
I want either one of these.
- This one? - No, this.
(The snack-loving duo are in their element.)
- What about this? - No. Maybe a muffin?
Do you feel like a muffin?
(They carefully pile the plate up with baked goods.)
Let's have one of each.
(What?)
Wait a second.
- Do you take 1 of each? - Yes, just 1.
We didn't choose that much.
One vanilla.
Thank you.
- The coffee is here. - Okay.
This is how it works.
You can just pour the coffee.
(Coffee made with an electrical device)
(At their rented room, he had to grind the beans...)
(and start a fire.)
(It took 1 hour to make coffee.)
(All it takes is 10 seconds here.)
It's the technology of modern civilization.
(He feels sad and disappointed at the same time.)
(They also pay at an electronic cash register.)
Let's go.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(They spend 45 dollars at the cafe detour.)
- This is so tasty. - I'm so happy right now.
It's so nice.
This is nice.
(They sit at the terrace of the cafe.)
The weather is really nice.
This is the Finland I imagined before coming here.
- Me too. - Right?
(The city duo misses the city after visiting a cafe.)
Dong Hwi really does look happy.
(Same coffee, different face)
This is what I wanted.
A cup of coffee in the city.
(He didn't expect to be 100 percent in nature.)
(Counting their money in the midst of this joyous event)
(The Renters' mom suddenly starts counting their money.)
Dong Yeon is checking our expenses again.
(Dong Hwi is flustered.)
Do you have a ledger?
(Audit: Do you have a ledger?)
(The air suddenly turns cold.)
(Answer wisely.)
(Glancing at him)
(They're like an angry mom...)
It's in my head.
(and anxious dad.)
We have 460 dollars left.
(They spent over half the money in less than half their stay.)
Isn't that fine?
(How dare you!)
(Trying to read Dong Yeon's face)
- Did you donate the money? - No.
Did you toss it in the lake to make a wish?
I know you don't have it. I'm just asking.
(The youngest son is uncomfortable while his parents argue.)
- Actually, - Yes.
- I gave Frida... - Frida?
Some money to buy herself snacks.
(The youngest son comes up with an idea.)
Do we get free refills?
I think the cafe owner...
(That's a good idea, Eun Woo.)
will be generous about refills.
Let's play rock, paper, scissors to see who will go and ask.
- Yes, let's ask. - That's embarrassing.
Rock, paper, scissors.
- Rock, paper, scissors. - Please let me win.
Goodness.
Goodness, please.
(The youngest one who brought up about it got picked!)
- The one who wanted it got picked. - That's true.
- I'll go and ask. - Okay.
- If they do, we'll get it refilled. - Yes.
Am I really going?
(Am I really going?)
What should I say?
"Refill" is an English word, right?
(Laughing)
- It's re-fill. - Right?
Do not use the word "refill," just in case.
- Don't say "refill." - Right. Refill...
- Get a lot of coffee. - This is a little...
(Will he be able to refill it without saying the word?)
Is there a path over there?
Isn't that the way to the kitchen?
- This is the kitchen. - Come this way.
Eun Woo is uncomfortable at doing something like this.
Will you just...
(Reaching)
- Hey! - You can't do that.
(How dare you have your eye on the money?)
It's for a refill.
- This is fun. - Yes.
Is "refill" an English word?
This is going to be fun.
He got really embarrassed at the restaurant yesterday too.
- That's right. - Well.
Refill...
(He is still thinking.)
(Completely nervous)
Can I have a little more coffee?
(He did it without saying the word refill!)
(Can he?)
Yes.
(Fortunately, it's possible to get a free refill.)
They are generous, indeed.
I'll fill it up.
(He fills it up, so he won't have to come back for it.)
Thanks.
It tastes good.
(He suddenly compliments it out of embarrassment.)
(Compressing his lips)
Eun Woo might say,
"Can we just eat what we have?"
Dong Hwi.
- He did it. - What?
What did you say to get it?
You got it secretly without asking him.
- You didn't tell him, did you? - He got it without telling him?
Did you not ask for it?
- Dong Hwi, I'm not like that. - Is that so?
- It's really hot. Let it cool down. - You filled up the cup.
Yes. To share with you.
- Good. - Thank you.
I didn't use the word, "refill."
- You didn't. - No.
- Let's get going now. - Let's go.
- It'll get cold soon. Let's go. - Right.
- Dong Yeon, - Yes?
- do we really have to go? - We do, Dong Hwi.
I love it here, though.
Honestly,
I love this place the most.
Dong Hwi and Eun Woo, you two stay and live here, then.
We're leaving.
I love it here. I want to stay and listen to music.
You can live here, but we're going to leave.
- Let's go. - I'm recharged.
Yes. Very much so.
(A dreamy moment comes to an end! It's time to go back!)
Gosh. When I think about going back, it feels...
(When I think about going back, it feels...)
(The man of nature hums as they return to the cottage.)
- Dong Yeon, are you happy? - Yes?
(Dong Yeon, are you happy?)
(The man of nature is feeling good!)
I can really live here...
(I can really live here.)
if there's a water supply.
(If there's a water supply)
I washed my hands and face back there.
I thought they had water supply because they had a faucet.
But that wasn't true.
They filled up the container and attached a faucet.
- But the water from the river... - It's so clean.
Is unbelievably clean here.
(The lake's water is clean, so it's okay without the waterworks!)
(After talking for a while, )
This is the place where we lose our signals.
(they are at the entrance of the no-signal zone.)
Are we already here?
(Laughing)
(They face the off-road forest again.)
(They confine themselves in the deep forest again.)
We're almost there.
- We're here. - We're here.
But we still have to walk quite a bit.
My goodness.
I feel like I got a little used to this lifestyle.
(I feel like I got a little used to this lifestyle.)
It's really pretty, though.
- That's right. - Yes.
Should I go for a boat ride?
(They are amazed by the unreal view of the front yard...)
(whenever they see it.)
(In this uninhabited place...)
(exists only nature and the renters.)
We came back.
I love it.
Now that it's our second day here,
- it feels like home. - Right.
- It feels familiar. - Right.
(It's really cozy like home.)
Should we get some rest...
- before getting ready to cook? - Yes.
I'll zone out a bit.
(Current time: 4pm)
(What can the city boys do to have fun in the no-signal zone?)
(Shaking)
(The oldest brother shakes off the dust in the pastoral scenery.)
Hey. It'd feel great...
to wash clothes and shake them off in this view.
(Meanwhile, Eun Woo, who said he'd zone out, )
(sits at the edge of the dock, the 1st row to the lake view.)
(It's his first time to relax since he arrived in Finland.)
(He indulges the panoramic view of the lake in front of the house.)
(He takes off his socks!)
(Then he rolls up his pants.)
(A foot bath in the cold lake)
It's so cold.
(He's more used to the lake than a shower head.)
(It's peaceful and quiet in front of the lake.)
Did my phone lose signal again?
(He turns on his phone again.)
It doesn't have a signal.
I used up the portable charger I brought with me.
(I used up the portable charger.)
(City Dong Hwi is going crazy because he wants to know...)
(what's going on around the world.)
(He whistles to relieve the boredom.)
(Zoning out)
Gosh. At this place,
no one will hear me even if I scream.
(There are only 4 of us within 20km radius.)
(No-signal zone)
(What will they do now in the vast wilderness?)
(Meanwhile, the man of nature wanders toward the forest.)
(He lets his feet lead him...)
(to a lonesome place.)
(He must have found a spot that suits him.)
(Cracking)
(He enjoys the taste of the civilization in nature.)
(The man of nature is following the stream of consciousness again.)
(Meanwhile, the city boys in front of the lake...)
(The city boy plays the cassette as he couldn't take it anymore.)
(This song is...)
(A K-ballad song spreads...)
(across the cottage at the end of the world.)
(Gazing gently)
Dong Hwi, what was this song?
"Fool" by Park Hyo Shin.
"Pool?"
(Laughing)
Hey.
- "Pool?" - Come on.
Hold on.
Time out.
- Eun Woo. - Yes?
You're just like the title of the song.
It's such a heartrending ballad.
It can't be a "Pool."
"Fool."
(Come on.)
(The fool gets a small revenge.)
(This is crazy. He's just pure and happy.)
You're doing it again.
- You might break it. - Okay.
I'll break too.
(Looking around)
Dong Yeon is really by himself, right?
Where did he go?
I think he went in somewhere like there.
(Dong Yeon is Missing 2)
Where is he?
(Did the man of nature find something?)
(It was wild berries!)
(He enjoys the salty-and-sweet combination...)
(with the wild berries and chips!)
(The man of nature seeks a higher ground.)
(This is it!)
(He takes out the knife that is part of his body now.)
(Is he checking the quality of the rock?)
(Where he lies his body is a bed for him.)
(Deep inside the backyard of the cottage, )
(Mr. Kwak becomes one...)
(with the forest.)
It's important that I believe in it.
It doesn't matter what it is. A true actor...
(Practicing his lines for a play)
(Actor Kwak is professional at what he does.)
(Right?)
We'll use the firewood...
again in the evening.
(We'll use the firewood again in the evening.)
(Turning on the guardian mode)
(He splits firewood while the younger brothers have fun.)
(Should I show them what I can do?)
(Slamming)
Gosh.
(Running hurriedly)
(But he gradually gets the hang of it.)
Gosh. I'm so tough.
(Gosh. I'm so tough.)
(I need to split more firewood for dinner!)
But if you go that far...
(The problematic man of nature appears.)
- Dong Yeon. Come here. - Yes?
Why are you wearing the vest?
(Laughing uncontrollably)
- Dong Yeon. - I have to set out on a voyage.
But...
(He's getting beyond interesting.)
(He doesn't care.)
(I'm going my way.)
What? Are you going to ride the boat?
Why can't I pull it?
(Oiva did it in one go.)
(Groaning)
(His friend comes to help...)
(as he keeps making an old man's groaning sound.)
(Groaning)
Give it a little push.
- Do you want a push? - Yes.
(Spreading his legs wide open)
(Goodness)
Be careful. Hey.
(Be careful with your crotch.)
- Be careful. Hey. - Be careful, Eun Woo.
(A painstakingly beautiful friendship)
- Eun Woo. - Hey.
(The man of nature leaves on a voyage alone again.)
Dong Yeon, how far are you going to go?
Don't go too far.
(In the midst of the chaos, )
(Je Hoon, the guardian, piles up the firewood.)
(The scenery of the rented cottage in the no-signal zone)
(The oldest brother is proud after piling up the firewood for dinner.)
(The second oldest brother sings while playing his favorite tape.)
(The youngest takes a nap while dipping his feet in the lake.)
(The man of nature goes on a picnic on a small boat.)
(The city boys are getting quite used to the life of Lapland.)
(Enjoying the relaxing time they earned from adapting to nature)
(He's lying down for the 2nd time today.)
(He found a broom mic.)
(The sound of his singing wakes the man of nature up.)
(With 1 hand in his pocket and 1 hand around the broom, )
(he sings while looking at the lake.)
(Like a flame)
(He casually joins for a duet.)
(The song picks up momentum as Dong Brother joins him.)
(A fierce serenade by the two men)
(He has never seen anything like it before.)
(A master singer...)
(and a handsome fool next to him)
(The harmony at its peak)
(Screaming)
(Still feeling it)
For goodness sake.
I can sing better here.
Is it because the air is clear?
- Did you have fun? - Yes.
(After a fierce duet, the man of nature comes back to the dock.)
(Soldierly)
(Will he be able to park the boat inside the narrow space?)
He looks serious.
It seems it's not going as he planned.
(How do I put this in there?)
I'll turn it and...
(As they see Planner Kwak on a weak mode, )
Dong Hwi, should I make him never be able to park?
(he wants to tease him.)
(Go back.)
(Enduring)
- Good. - I'm fine yet.
Dong Yeon.
(You're not fine.)
It's hilarious, but...
Gosh. He's even strong.
(Mischievous Eun Woo is even strong.)
(I'll get going.)
- Bye, Dong Yeon. - This is funny.
- I'm going in. - Okay.
- Yes. - Come back
(A confrontation)
(Pleading for clemency)
- Dong Yeon. - Yes.
Cook us a delicious dinner.
I said I'd make an incredible kimchi stew.
- Thank you. - It's hard to park the boat alone.
It won't be easy.
Oiva is truly amazing.
Watch your feet.
(Struggling)
That's it.
(They join forces to barely pull it up.)
Gosh. I need to wash my feet again.
(They look peaceful in a flash.)
(But...)
(Sighing)
(There's an elephant in the room.)
(Cutting quietly)
(2 of them have to sleep here.)
Dong Hwi.
(The ones who slept hanging on the trees last night...)
(In the icy-cold weather, )
(they had an icy-cold battle.)
(A dizzying night on the tree tents)
Are you alive?
(It's a pain they never want to experience again.)
(No matter what, we will sleep inside tonight.)
A game...
(Dong Brothers are clenching their teeth.)
What can we play?
(They are more serious than ever to choose a game.)
In fact, with the photos, I wanted to guess who they were.
But we can't download the photos without the internet.
(In order to play the game of Guess Who, )
(they have to travel 2 hours back and forth.)
What can we do?
(The witnesses are careful about it too.)
Okay. Then...
(A silent tension fills up the front yard.)
Hey. How about Word Chain?
Okay.
Should we play Word Chain?
Yes. Word Chain is nice and classic.
- Let's try it. - Let's do it.
- Are we trying it? - Yes.
(A classic game, World Chain, that suits the classic place.)
(The last match with the night in the air at stake)
(Will they struggle in discomfort?)
(Or will they greet a cozy morning?)
Let's try it first. For now...
Okay. For now...
(The 4th lumbar vertebra remembers...)
(the night in the private room.)
(He has been prepared sharply...)
(for this match!)
Are we doing it for real?
(A kind brother in town)
Should we change to find who endures a bug the longest?
(An eccentric brother who is addicted to jokes)
(Fierce)
(An unpredictable, freestyle brother)
(Everyone's type)
The bottom one, the first to get eliminated,
will lay in the first coffin.
- Okay. - No. It's not a coffin.
- The last one will have Tent One? - Yes.
(Tent One is...)
(Last night)
(Tent 1, Tent 2)
(Of the two tents, )
(Surprised)
(it's even hard to go up into the Tent 1.)
(On top of that, )
(the wind blows straight to it.)
(Dizzy)
(I'll run away if I get picked again)
We'll go in this order, starting from Dong Yeon.
- Okay. - Dong Yeon, Je Hoon, me, and you.
It has to be three syllables.
(Three syllable rule)
- Let's go. - Let's go.
A three-syllable word.
- Kungkung-dda. - Kungkung-dda.
Husky. Kungkung-dda.
(Ki...)
- What? - This is...
(Is he stuck on his first try?)
You can't do that.
But this is so...
- Just say it. - It's okay.
(What is the word that he's reluctant to say it?)
(Hesitant)
Is it okay to say it?
Will you do it again?
- Husky. Kungkung-dda. - Kungkung-dda.
(He begins to speak with determination.)
Kiss me. Kungkung-dda.
(The tension strips off from the beginning.)
(Unpleasant)
(Serious)
It does work, though.
Okay. Let's do it again.
- Je Hoon, we'll let that pass. - Okay.
You know how to do it now, right, Je Hoon?
Okay. Let's go.
(Now, if one gets it wrong, he'll get eliminated!)
Bl-berry.
(Bl-berry?)
(He shortens blueberries...)
(to bl-berry to play the game.)
(Confident)
Hurry up. Kungkung-dda.
- Rivera, kungkung-dda. - Kungkung-dda.
Lilac, kungkung-dda.
Rock star, kungkung-dda.
- Oh-strich, kungkung-dda. - Kungkung-dda.
(This time, he extended the word "ostrich.")
Oh-strich? Okay. Kungkung-dda.
Kungkung-dda.
- Continue. - Continue.
Joe Black, kungkung-dda.
Tow-truck service, kungkung-dda.
- Kungkung-dda. - Hold on.
(Making silent syllables urgently?)
- Hold on. - Let it pass.
(Laughing silently)
(Laughing)
- Tow-truck service, kungkung-dda. - It's crazy.
Tow-truck service, kungkung-dda.
Service is one syllable.
Gosh. This is...
We'll let it pass if one persuades us with his charm.
- Since it's an individual match. - Yes.
(Suddenly, he tries to bring out their charms.)
I was going to let everything pass and keep playing.
I've never felt...
this energetic ever since I came here.
I'm so excited.
All right. Let's focus now.
- Okay. - Okay.
From Dong Yeon, let's do it for real now.
- Again. - Again.
- For real. - Right.
(They begin the game again.)
- Kungkung-dda. - Kungkung-dda.
- Kettle, kungkung-dda. - Kungkung-dda.
- Bicycle, kungkung-dda. - Kungkung-dda.
Well...
- Five, four, - Five, four...
- three... - Cobweb, kungkung-dda.
Wife, kungkung-dda.
(His future wife must be so happy.)
- Amsa-dong, kungkung-dda. - Okay, good.
- Club, kungkung-dda. - Kungkung-dda.
(What's next?)
Well...
- Five, four, three, - Five, four, three,
- two... - two...
Handcart, kungkung-dda.
Cassette, kungkung-dda.
Trend, kungkung-dda.
Drama, kungkung-dda.
Mario, kungkung-dda.
Audio, kungkung-dda.
(To avoid sleeping in the air, )
(they compete fiercely.)
NewJeans.
(This messy game continues...)
(for 30 minutes.)
(Tired)
(Drained)
- Yogurt, kungkung-dda. - Good.
- That again? - Yes.
(It came out quite often.)
Let's end it this time.
(Well, then...)
Twist, kungkung-dda.
(It's a four-syllable word, but they let this much slide now.)
He's good.
- It's that again? - Yes.
Je Hoon.
(His roommate from yesterday is up to help him.)
(Twerking)
Oh, I get it.
(A sexy hint...)
(gets him to twist his body.)
- Come on. - Are you that shocked?
- How mean. - Are you that shocked?
- Hey. - Je Hoon, this.
Can this be aired?
- Of course, it's just dancing. - It's just a dance move.
- Okay. - Kungkung-dda.
(They pull themselves together and resume the game.)
T...
(He just can't say the word out loud.)
(He's too innocent and shy.)
- You've got to do the dance too. - Do it.
- Do it as you say the word. - Right.
What? No.
Then, are you okay with losing?
No, I can do it.
You can do it, but you won't?
- Well... - I can easily do it.
- I can keep doing it. - Me too.
I can do it if I have to.
(He's torn...)
(between mid-air sleeping in the cold...)
(and losing his dignity.)
(Take this.)
Twerking.
(Becoming serious)
(Screaming)
(To avoid sleeping in the mid-air tent, )
(he takes every resort.)
(It's shocking...)
(even for the one who caused this.)
Goodness, I watched "Architecture 101."
(The memories have been restructured.)
(His face blushes more than a monkey's buttocks.)
Let's not do this.
Gosh, this is too...
(His agency's actor is feeling so embarrassed.)
Let's do it for real.
Let's do what's needed for real now.
We've played this game for more than an hour.
Right,
so let's flick a bottle cap...
to have it reach as close to the finishing line as possible.
- But if it falls, you're out. - Okay.
That person will sleep in the tent.
- Okay. - Let's do it without practice.
- Of course. - Okay.
- But... - Even if something unlucky happens,
- let's just go on. - Okay.
No playing easy.
No exceptions.
- Right away. - Right away.
- I'll go. - Let's go.
(Twerking Je Hoon is up first.)
(Carefully getting ready)
(He can't afford to lose after all that twerking.)
(He's all spiteful and focused.)
- Let's go. - I'll go.
A little more.
Flick it sideways.
Hey, stop giving me instructions.
(Playing innocent)
There's an obstacle on the way.
(The patronizer backs down, )
(and the prankster comes.)
Gosh.
(The youngest members attack together.)
This is...
- like war. - I'll go.
A little to the right.
There...
(Flicking through the disturbance)
(Super focused)
- Well done. - Not bad.
Gosh, it's too short.
If it falls, does it count?
- Yes. - I see.
If it falls, you'll enter...
the tent right away.
(There will be no second chance.)
(Next up is Dong Yeon.)
- Dong Yeon. - There's a fruit fly here.
(Shaking a bug swatter)
Dong Yeon.
There are too many winged insects.
(Yesterday's loser...)
(wouldn't be disturbed.)
That's not it.
Come on.
Dong Yeon.
It's not that finger.
(Fierce)
Gosh, the fruit fly.
No, Dong Yeon.
(He must really hate to sleep outdoors.)
Take it easy.
(He flicks...)
(with an incredible sense of focus.)
Take it easy.
(Surprised)
(Je Hoon)
(Dong Yeon wouldn't take it easy.)
- He's good. - Nice.
(He's not the bottom-place player of this round.)
This is...
(He just has to win one more time.)
(Meanwhile...)
I want to play safely.
Oh, you'll go that way?
(Je Hoon, Dong Yeon)
(Maybe he feels burdened.)
(He chooses to take a safe way.)
It's quite bumpy there.
(Compared to the right side, )
(it's bumpy on the left side.)
- Player Eun Woo... - I'm ready.
- is off to make an attempt. - It's going to fall.
- Three, two, one. - He's quite strained.
Bungee!
He's too strained.
(Flicking)
- It fell. - Oh, dear.
Game over.
Oh, dear.
(The twerker is all excited.)
That's an unexpected variable.
Eun Woo will sleep in the tent.
Gosh, I didn't...
see it coming at all.
It's really not easy to make it roll like that.
How did he get it up?
- Eun Woo. - Oh, gosh.
(Eun Woo managed to do something that tricky.)
(Welcome. Isn't it your first time sleeping in the mid-air tent?)
Still, you should try it.
- Okay. - Come on.
- Give it a try. - Okay, I will.
It should at least go farther than this.
- I... - Not this area.
(If it doesn't pass the base line, they will go again.)
I...
You know me so well.
You really... I mean...
- You know, 1cm is not allowed. - Right.
- Right, it must at least pass here. - Right.
- Make a line. - Or you'll be out.
Right.
I can do this much.
(Meanwhile, he's overly relaxed.)
Let's make it fun.
- What's fun? - Dong Hwi.
It's not fun for me.
- There has to be a twist. - A twist?
(You want a twist?)
(I don't.)
It's Eun Woo.
(Eun Woo was a promising candidate.)
(And now, he's confirmed to sleep in the tree tent.)
Gosh.
(Laughing out loud)
(How sweet.)
Let's do it for the last time.
No, we've got to eat now.
But we need one more person to sleep outdoors anyway.
We can decide by firewood-laying.
Fine.
Eun Woo, search for ways...
to raise your body temperature...
while the three of us do the firewood-laying.
He's so desperate.
He uses his handsome looks on us.
Look at the lake at a time like this.
(He understands Dong Yeon.)
Anyway, it's just the four of us.
Not a dozen people.
- It's just us four. - Right.
Dong Yeon.
(Swinging)
All right. Whatever.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
- To where the firewood is. - Let's go and see.
See what? There's no way for you, Eun Woo.
(There's no need to see because...)
- Come on. - Let's go.
(Stunned)
(Dong Yeon is out.)
(Dong Yeon is confirmed to sleep in the tree tent again.)
Good game.
So my friend is my sleeping mate.
(He's given up.)
Goodness. Have a good night.
(He's devastated just like this fallen firewood tower.)
I've already done it once. I can do it again.
(The rest is omitted.)
I'll be going. It feels a little uneasy here.
Gosh, Dong Hwi.
(The games are over with the youngest as losers.)
(Sleeping is one thing.)
- You'll steam rice? Okay. - Yes.
(Let's get the food ready first.)
(Going to their positions)
Meat.
Should I cut and grill the meat?
Can you grill it well?
Yes, I'm good at it.
(Stir-fried shredded potatoes, stir-fried spicy pork)
(He learned how to cook in Lapland.)
(Chef Cha Eun Woo for Korean barbecue)
(Rye sujebi, cabbage doenjang soup)
(He's like a food bending machine.)
(Chef Kwak Dong Yeon for kimchi stew and pot steamed rice)
I'll grill the meat...
when you start making kimchi stew.
- Okay. - That will do, right?
(But the problem is...)
We'll steam rice.
- The problem is... - Yes?
That we have to grill the meat here.
(How are they supposed to grill meat at this fireplace?)
(There's nowhere to place a grill.)
(They've waited so long...)
(for kimchi barbecue.)
(Korean barbecue...)
(in the countryside of Finland)
(Was it too much to ask for?)
(They dreamed of Korean soul food in the dense forest.)
(How will their fate turn out to be?)
We have to grill the meat here.
I have an idea.
What is it?
I'm going to stack up some bricks.
(He'll try to remodel their outdoor kitchen.)
- You'll place a grill there? - Yes.
- Like this? - I think it's better.
- I'll move these away then. - Yes, those two stones.
(Will they pull off remodeling the fireplace?)
To the side.
(Securing enough space to put up a brazier)
- Thanks. - No problem.
(Moving bricks)
(Stacking them up one after another)
- The rest... Okay. - All the rest on that side.
(The city boys couldn't even light a fire, )
(but now, they're trying to remodel the fireplace.)
(Checking level)
- Kind of. - Kind of.
(It's a little higher on this side.)
I can just lower this part.
(He tends to handle everything with power.)
Je Hoon, this is a nice way to work out.
(It's a nice way to work out.)
(Suddenly doing push-ups in the middle of remodeling)
(Joining in)
- Don't lower that side. - Not here?
It has to be higher there.
(While they're adjusting the level with power, )
(the firewood servant, Dong Hwi, gets into his position.)
(The work is divided naturally.)
We need more firewood to make the fire stronger.
(Inexorable steps)
(Placing it indifferently)
(His confidence comes...)
(from the firewood-chopping skills he earned during the first stay.)
(The firewood servant is back.)
Gosh.
I've lost my touch after not doing it for a few days.
(He's become rusty.)
(Failing)
(Flustered)
(Failing again)
(And again)
(A single day is enough to make you rusty at chopping firewood.)
(His touch is finally back.)
(Firepower is important for grilling barbecue.)
(He chops firewood nonstop.)
(He returns with an armful of firewood.)
What's with this new construction?
What do you say?
It looks perfect.
- It looks high enough. - You think?
But when should we make a fire?
Should we do it along with cooking?
- I'm going to do it now. - I see.
It's okay to do it in advance.
Okay.
(It's become a daily routine. They begin making a fire.)
(The eldest member...)
(Scratching)
(He'd seen it only in movies.)
(But now, he makes kindling on his own.)
(The second-eldest member...)
How kind of you to help me out.
(He couldn't do anything without Dong Yeon.)
(Right in one go)
(Now, he's good at lighting a fire even without Dong Yeon.)
Put it down there like this.
(Carefully moving the fire to the fireplace)
It's not catching fire.
It's spreading now.
- Let's wait now. - Okay.
(They manage to light a fire at the new fireplace.)
- Nice. - All I did was throw one match.
- Good job. - Good.
(They've leveled up to be country boys.)
(Will they see it through with the kimchi barbecue?)
(And how will Dong Yeon's kimchi stew turn out?)
(Homemaker Kwak begins cooking.)
(Going outside with the chopping board)
(It's brighter outside due to no electricity.)
(From one point, he's used to cooking under the bright sun.)
(Chopping stably even on the handrail)
(This homemaker in Lapland creates an outdoor kitchen himself.)
(The sunshine aids him to speed up with preparing ingredients.)
(Dropping)
No.
(Dashing to save the onion)
(Going straight to the lake)
(It's become natural for them to wash stuff in the lake.)
(He's back to the kitchen.)
I feel like my knife skills have improved in days.
Awesome.
I've gotten better at cutting.
I mean, who would practice cutting in Finland?
(With faster cutting skills, )
(he's done preparing the cooking ingredients.)
- Should I put... - What?
Ham or meat in the stew?
- Can't it be both? - Both.
- I can't do that. - No?
Then, why don't you put ham in since we'll grill some meat?
Ham?
(Okay, got it.)
(He has his own way of cutting ham.)
(A plastic bag?)
(Putting a chunk of ham into the plastic bag)
(Rubbing)
(Crushed ham melts into the broth much faster.)
(Chopping the other chunk into pieces)
(It's got to have something to chew on.)
(Isn't it such an easy way?)
Can one of you come over to help me?
- Okay. - Got it.
I need some minced garlic.
- Sure. - Okay.
- I'll do it. - Garlic?
- Okay. - I'll do it.
(Dong Hwi volunteers with a sense of confidence.)
Dong Yeon.
- You'll do it? - Yes, of course.
- For real? - Yes.
(Full of suspicion)
All right, okay.
(He's like a husband willing to help his unsure wife.)
(Leaving the garlic to him)
(Taking the kimchi they brought from Korea)
A plate there...
(His cheeks shake too.)
(Shaking all in)
(Shaking the crushed ham...)
(in as well)
(He's got to light a fire now.)
(Striking a light in one go)
(Lighting the gas stove skillfully)
(He's used to the manual ignition system now.)
(Stir-fry the kimchi and crushed ham together.)
I hope
(Suddenly singing passionately)
(This is how the housework stress is affecting Dong Yeon.)
(Sorrowful)
(Venting all his pent-up emotions)
Make sure to be happier than me
(Turning)
(Returning to the kitchen after relieving all his stress)
(Focusing again)
- Je Hoon. - What?
- I looked around and found this. - Found what?
(To test the new fireplace)
- What do you say to fried eggs? - Why not?
For an appetizer.
That'd be a nice appetizer.
Why just the two of you?
What?
- Did you hear us? - Yes.
You have such a nice hearing.
I have...
such a sensitive hearing right now.
I can hear even better since I came to Finland.
(His ears have recovered from all that city noises.)
(Making fried eggs for the member with a sharp hearing)
(Sliding)
I messed up.
- No. - Gosh, my eyes sting.
It's not flat.
(The fireplace isn't even.)
It's slanted a little because it's not flat.
(They notice a problem thanks to making fried eggs.)
The eggs slide because it's slanted.
(Still, the eggs are being cooked nicely.)
(Trying to flip the eggs once)
(Trying for the second time)
The oil... Oh, no.
(He messes up.)
(Still, they're happy.)
The yolks popped.
It'll be the same once it goes into our stomachs.
I'll come back.
- You'll feed them directly? - Yes, this way...
- Really? It's okay. - Gosh!
(Off to deliver it right away with the frying pan)
It's okay. I'll take care of it.
(He's off to protect the youngest member's mentality.)
Nothing is a problem. It's all right.
- Gosh, the eggs didn't break. - They're safe.
Thanks.
(If Homemaker Kwak was here, he'd slap him in the back.)
- Dong Hwi. - What?
(Is he releasing his stress again?)
It looks really hot.
Gosh, you're cooling it down for me?
(In this case, he's willing to have it.)
Dong Hwi.
Darn, it's hot.
Darn it.
(Troubled, Laughing)
(The older one is troubled while the younger one cracks up.)
- Eun Woo. - Gosh.
What's the problem with you?
Okay.
(Struggling)
(He tries to endure the heat, )
(but he fails.)
It's hot.
But it's really good.
It's really good, but it's too hot.
(He burned the roof of his mouth, though.)
- Dong Yeon. - What?
- Dong Yeon. - Yes.
- It's an appetizer. - What is it?
Fried eggs.
(He's sweet enough to blow air to it again.)
It's really good.
- It's hot. - Okay.
- Are you okay? - Yes.
(And it's hot again.)
Gosh, my teeth ache.
What do I do?
(He decides to put it down for a moment.)
Gosh, it's hot.
It's good. That's for sure.
(He stops eating...)
(and starts ransacking the seasoning storage.)
(After going through it for a while, )
(he takes out ketchup.)
(He makes sure to enjoy even a single fried egg thoroughly.)
Painful love
It's hot.
(He throws it in his mouth all at once.)
(And he goes back to cooking.)
(He's boiling the stir-fried kimchi and ham with water.)
(The alarm Planner Kwak set earlier goes off.)
(Dong Yeon takes a look at his collection of seasonings.)
(Without any hesitation, he picks up the anchovy extract.)
(To make something umami, add a spoonful of anchovy extract.)
(Relaxing...)
(is not an option right now.)
(The alarms are never-ending.)
(This is why Homemaker Kwak brought portable chargers.)
(At the alarm, he adds chili powder for spiciness.)
Chili powder.
(Now he adds chili flakes.)
And then chili flakes.
(He's so meticulous that he's using different types of chili powder.)
I have to let it boil.
(Bringing his seasonings to Finland was worth it!)
Did you mince the garlic yet?
(It's time to put in the garlic.)
- What? - You have to hurry.
All right. I just have to mince these now.
You didn't do it yet?
- No. - I see.
(Wordlessly nagging)
(Timing is key.)
(Dong Hwi is hurrying because of Dong Yeon's silent nagging.)
I feel like I'm the one being minced.
(If you don't want to be minced, )
(mince the garlic...)
(before Chef Kwak gets angry.)
(He kept...)
(mincing the garlic nonstop...)
(until he was done!)
(Complete!)
(During that short time, Dong Hwi became exhausted.)
- Dong Yeon. - Yes.
I minced the garlic.
All right.
(He safely brought Dong Yeon the minced garlic on time.)
- Thank you. - Sure.
(Thankfully, Dong Yeon is pleased.)
(He throws in the minced garlic that Dong Hwi put a lot of effort into.)
(What does the mashed ham kimchi stew taste like?)
(Very pleased)
Nice.
(The onion he cut earlier...)
(is thrown into the pot as soon as the alarm goes off.)
(Dong Yeon throws in the rest of the ingredients on time.)
This has that Korean flavor.
(He made a dish full of Korean flavor all the way in Lapland.)
Ten minutes on high heat, ten minutes on medium heat.
(Dong Yeon is addicted to being precisely on time until the end.)
Ten minutes each.
- There's a griddle. - Gosh, we have a griddle here.
We can use this.
- Gosh. - The griddle.
- We had this here? - The griddle's here.
Be careful.
(They found a griddle to use as an alternative to a cauldron lid!)
What do you think?
(But...)
(it's severely crooked.)
(Emergency)
We need to find a way.
(At this rate, they won't be able to grill properly.)
We're going to have to do repairs...
if we want to grill the meat well.
- Because of how it's crooked? - Yes.
(Is it that important?)
(At Eun Woo's words, Je Hoon takes the issue seriously.)
(What will Eun Woo decide to do?)
(Put out the fire and do repairs? Or just do repairs as is?)
(The fire pit is in flames.)
What can we do to fix this?
(With no time to put the fire out, Eun Woo rushes at the fire pit.)
What do you need?
I was thinking of raising the part below the brick, but it's not easy.
(He has to protect...)
(both the fire pit and the fire.)
(Eun Woo is attempting to prop up the lower side with some wood.)
(Watching attentively)
If you're going to grab it like that,
I'll bring you a pair of fireproof gloves.
(Outdoor kitchen? He's used to it enough!)
(Doing repairs on the fire pit?)
(It can't be impossible.)
Here, put this on your right hand.
(Je Hoon brought fireproof gloves.)
Gosh.
(Startled)
- It's all right. - Gosh.
(A disaster)
(Dong Hwi is startled too because he has good hearing.)
(My fire pit fell apart today.)
(It turned on me in an instant.)
(Sad)
It's all right.
It's all right. First, put the fireproof glove on.
- This is why I wanted to fix it. - I see.
(He tried to repair the fire pit, but it ended up collapsing.)
Gosh, Je Hoon.
(Having a barbecue party)
Having a campfire isn't easy.
What do you think we can do?
First, we should remove all these bricks.
Then, we'll stack them up again evenly.
This is why repairs are important.
We should have done a better job when we first built it.
Let's put out this fire first...
and move the bricks over here.
- All right. - Okay.
(The eldest takes the lead in the face of a crisis.)
(Je Hoon is no longer merely naive.)
Gosh, I wanted this to be easy.
(I should do what Je Hoon is doing.)
(He carries sand in both hands after pulling himself together.)
(Under the eldest's leadership, )
(Eun Woo puts out the fire with the sand.)
(Let's do this again safely.)
- Dong Hwi. - Yes?
We're going to rebuild the fire.
That's all right.
Things happen.
(Dong Hwi cheers Eun Woo up.)
(Pouring sand)
Do we have to put out the fire completely?
It's too hot.
All done.
(After a lot of ups and downs, they finished putting out the fire.)
- We'll need more firewood. - Yes.
Gosh, Dong Hwi.
That was nice.
I'll go chop some.
(The two older renters remain calm even during a crisis.)
(The eldest starts actively rebuilding the fire pit.)
(Enduring the burning sensation in his eyes, )
All right.
(he finished making the surface of the ground flat.)
That seems nice.
(He stacks up the bricks by himself too.)
(Eun Woo feels relieved with Je Hoon helping him.)
It looks flat.
(The brick pillar is more stable than it was earlier.)
(Please don't collapse this time.)
It looks flat.
Can you press down on it?
(The Renters learned something new again today.)
(Again)
- What do you think? - It's nice.
(We begin)
(The path to having kimchi barbecue is long and rough.)
(Meanwhile, it's peaceful in the indoor kitchen...)
(when Dong Yeon's alarm rings.)
(As the sound of the alarm fills the small kitchen, )
(the kimchi stew is complete.)
Gosh, this is insane.
It's great.
(Homemaker Kwak is on his way.)
- It's okay. - Is it?
Well, the left side is slightly lower but...
- The kimchi stew is complete. - I see.
I just have to wait for the rice to cook.
- Really? - It's time to grill the meat then.
(Homemaker Kwak's appearance got all of them rushing.)
All right.
Let's hurry.
(Let's hurry.)
Is it break time?
- No. - No.
The fire pit was crooked and collapsed.
- I see. - There's a reason.
Ten minutes.
Okay.
All right, let's do this.
(Mission: Finish grilling the meat within ten minutes!)
What do you think?
Let me see.
(Je Hoon seems reliable for the first time.)
- It looks all right. - It's much better.
- It's flat enough. - Okay.
All right. Let's start the fire again.
Yes.
(He's making kindling again.)
Dong Hwi, here's the mingling... The kindling.
(They're stuck in an endless cycle of starting a fire.)
It's on fire.
- It's on fire. - Yes, it is.
Nice.
Let's go.
(The new fire pit is stable on the ground and burning fast.)
Gosh.
Gosh, the meat is really thin.
It's cooking right away.
Wait.
(The meat is sticking to the griddle because they didn't use any oil.)
Gosh, it's sticking to the griddle.
- Right. - The grill is...
(After overcoming the fire pit crisis, )
(the three brothers are now faced with a new difficulty.)
Have you heard of scrambled meat?
- You're a scrambled-dish expert. - Yes.
Meat too.
Should we just add some oil?
No?
I honestly don't know.
Should we try it?
Let's just add oil on the griddle.
I think you should use a lot of oil and then coat the griddle.
Yes, that's right. I think I've seen it somewhere.
That's enough.
I'll coat it.
(The second oldest confidently tries to coat the griddle with oil.)
- Gosh. - You want me to do it?
I have a glove on.
(Trying to remember what he saw at a barbecue restaurant)
Nice.
(Struggling)
- You're doing great. - Is that enough? It's hot.
Gosh.
- Goodness. - Dong Hwi.
(Their path to Korean barbecue is long and rough.)
Be careful.
(Getting used to the fire pit isn't easy at all.)
- You all right? - Yes, I'm all right.
Dong Yeon really is...
(Dong Yeon really is feeding the three of us.)
(Dong Hwi feels ashamed.)
I feel so bad.
(The white rice is done.)
How do I keep doing a good job?
(Dong Yeon succeeded again in cooking rice in a pot.)
(He's the only one in Lapland who can make rice in a pot.)
(Mixing the nicely cooked rice)
Gosh.
I can't make ssamjang.
That's a problem.
(There's no doenjang left to make ssamjang with.)
Did I not bring the spicy chicken sauce?
(Barbecue without ssamjang would be devastating.)
(The once peaceful indoor kitchen is now in crisis.)
(Empty)
(What on earth can he use as an alternative to ssamjang?)
(After much thought, )
(Dong Yeon takes out the seasoned soy sauce, his secret weapon.)
(He's taking on the challenge of creating a new sauce.)
(Tasting)
(He decides to use the seasoned soy sauce.)
(What else?)
(Dong Yeon adds sugar for sweetness.)
(He also puts in Dong Hwi's minced garlic.)
(To make it look aesthetically pleasing, )
(Dong Yeon chops some green onion.)
(What will Dong Yeon's special sauce taste like?)
Can I come outside now?
(It's been a lot more than ten minutes.)
("Can I come outside now?")
(Of course...)
(not.)
(Dong Yeon is shooting lasers with his eyes.)
Can I bring out the rice and the kimchi stew?
I guess,
judging by the speed the meat is cooking at.
(In a rush)
The meat strips are thin, so let's keep flipping them.
Gosh, the meat is...
It's going to be good.
The smell is insane.
(The smell of pork is spreading all over the property.)
Hurry. Tell Dong Yeon to come out.
Let's just grill everything at once.
(They have to finish cooking before Dong Yeon gets here.)
That looks nice. Let's put some salt in now.
(No matter how much of a hurry they're in, they can't forget salt.)
Nice.
(The pork is being grilled very quickly.)
Dong Hwi, nice timing.
Nice.
(Dong Hwi quickly adds black pepper too so he doesn't get in trouble.)
I'll add the kimchi now.
(He puts the kimchi on the griddle to make it even better.)
(They don't even miss the barbecue places back in Korea...)
Nice.
(because they have Korean barbecue here in Lapland.)
(It looks and smells perfect.)
The smell is insane. This is amazing.
- Okay. - We're done.
(Current time: 9pm)
Dong Yeon, we're ready.
(Thankfully, they finished cooking before Dong Yeon lost his temper.)
This is great.
Let's eat.
- Yes. - Let's eat.
(The Renters are now used to eating dinner so late.)
(Dong Yeon's ham kimchi stew is finally revealed.)
- This is insane. - This is amazing.
You even added chopped chili pepper to decorate.
Your cooking skills keep getting better.
Dong Yeon, this is amazing.
(Spicy stew is perfect with white rice.)
This pot-cooked rice looks great too.
This is incredible.
(They also have the Korean barbecue they struggled to complete.)
- It feels like we're in Korea. - It really does.
Let's dig in. Thank you for the food.
- Thank you for the food. - Thank you for the food.
(The table full of Korean food feels like home.)
(Dong Hwi tries the kimchi stew.)
- What do you think? - Gosh. Wait.
(Do you like it?)
Gosh, you make me laugh.
What do you mean?
This is beyond good.
(That bite of kimchi stew was so good.)
You really make me laugh.
I didn't realize food could make me laugh.
(Dong Yeon has kept Dong Hwi laughing in Lapland.)
You really made this?
(Dong Hwi praised Dong Yeon 10 times with that 1 bite.)
This is really...
This is the real deal.
(What on earth does it taste like?)
- This is insane. - Gosh.
Goodness, the stew...
The cabbage doenjang soup...
- we had before. - Yes.
(Dong Yeon made cabbage doenjang soup for dinner on Day Two.)
This is even better than that.
- Right, it's so good. - This is really...
(The kimchi stew looks and tastes even better.)
(Eun Woo takes a sip of the soup.)
(And then he takes another sip right away.)
Gosh, this is unbelievable.
Gosh. This is so good, Dong Yeon.
(They keep admiring Dong Yeon's stew each time they have a bite.)
- This is great. - It's so good.
(It tastes great.)
This really is incredible.
(Dong Yeon takes a bite while listening to their praises.)
- It is. Gosh, it's so good. - This really is...
It's unbelievable.
It's so good.
It's my specialty.
(Dong Yeon is proud that they're enjoying the food.)
(Yum)
(Gosh)
Gosh, this is insane.
(Dong Hwi is still admiring the kimchi stew.)
(Yum)
(Dong Hwi's reaction is worth the effort Dong Yeon put in.)
If this kimchi stew was a person,
I would have proposed to it.
(Dong Hwi's unexpected proposal made Dong Yeon happy.)
For real.
I would have brought out a ring.
- A ring? It's that good? - Yes.
Gosh, this is...
(Proud)
This kimchi stew really makes me laugh.
(He's praising Dong Yeon nonstop.)
This combination is extraordinary.
(The praises are making Dong Yeon happy about feeding the Renters.)
- The combination? - Yes.
(After finishing up the stew, his attention is on the meat.)
What kind of meat is this?
- Pork shoulder - Pork shoulder.
(They went through so much...)
Let's try the Finnish pork shoulder.
(to grill the Finnish pork shoulder and kimchi!)
(This is it!)
(The firewood chopper eats two pieces at once.)
(I'm going to have two pieces too!)
This is way too good.
Seriously.
It's so good.
Do you like it?
We did a good job at grilling it.
I'm not sure who added the salt and pepper,
but it's seasoned perfectly.
It was you, Dong Hwi.
- Try it with some kimchi. - Okay.
- Grilled kimchi? - Yes.
(Dong Hwi wraps the kimchi with a piece of pork.)
This tastes like stir-fried pork.
Yes, kind of.
Stir-fried pork with kimchi.
This stir-fried pork is great.
(Eun Woo eats pork, kimchi and rice...)
It's pork wrap.
(all in one bite.)
(His mouth is full.)
(The sauce Dong Yeon made)
(The creator is pleased.)
It tastes amazing with the sauce.
- The pork shoulder? - Yes.
Hey, what kind of soy sauce did you use?
It's so good.
Gosh.
The sauce is making me laugh.
How did you make this sauce?
(Dong Yeon's improvised alternative to ssamjang is also a huge success.)
- This is great with rice. - Totally.
(Its flavor is the perfect blend of savory and sweet.)
Even the rice...
tastes better than last time.
- Yes. - Right.
(Dong Yeon's pot-cooked rice keeps improving.)
The rice is amazing.
How did you make rice in a pot?
Gosh.
I feel like I'm being taken care of by my child on this trip right now.
Goodness.
Father, do you like the food?
Son.
You should never get married.
You should stay home and cook for me instead.
(Don't get married and stay with me forever.)
This is so good.
I didn't think I would need Korean food,
- but I did. - Of course.
Eating Korean food is great.
It's making me feel...
- much more emotionally stable. - That's right.
I'm in trouble now.
I've never craved Korean food while I was...
- traveling abroad before. - Same.
- But this is going to make me... - You're now going to...
- want only Korean food from now on. - Right.
(Dong Yeon's cooking even changed Je Hoon's eating habit.)
It feels like I'm at a Korean restaurant near my house.
It really does.
A Korean restaurant...
with this vast lake behind it.
It looks like computer generated imagery.
(They can never get tired of looking at their marvelous front yard.)
This is what happiness feels like.
Gosh, this is so good.
(They get to enjoy food that reminds them of home in Lapland!)
This is insane.
(The Renters are full.)
The food was so good.
Dong Yeon, you really are amazing.
(The second oldest Renter knows how to make someone feel good.)
Gosh.
I stuffed my face with food.
- I stuffed my face with food. - Seriously.
I feel like I can easily stay in Finland for a year.
(As long as he has the Korean food Dong Yeon made)
I can make it here for a year with this meal.
Seriously, though. Watching you...
inspired me to start cooking myself...
(Will Dong Hwi, who is obsessed with delivery food, cook?)
- just a little. - I see.
You really moved me.
Gosh, should we really make them sleep in the tent?
(That's right. The tent at this rented house...)
(is practically wildlife, with the sound of the wind and...)
(the cold air being the only things they could sense in the dark.)
(The sleepless tree tent of horror...)
(is where the two chefs will be sleeping tonight.)
(The two youngest Renters cooked a warm meal for them, )
(but a cold night in the wild is what awaits them.)
Gosh, should we really make them sleep in the tent?
(Is the eldest offering them a hand of mercy?)
(Is he?)
(Is this a spark of hope?)
(Those two did work really hard.)
(Should they make them sleep in this tent, or not?)
(Thinking hard)
Or there's another way.
- You know the table there? - Yes.
We can push it aside...
and create space between the two beds.
(We'll gladly sleep on the floor.)
(Good thinking!)
Take out the table for a while.
Oh, take it out?
(Being convinced)
Most of all, in our previous stay,
I liked it when we all slept and woke up together...
- in the same room. - I know.
(They even bring up their memories from spending the nights together.)
Okay, got it. Let's do that, then.
- Let's move the table over. - Yes.
And let's all sleep next to each other.
- Okay. - Nice.
Before we sleep in the same room,
shall we have some local beer that I bought?
I'd love that.
- Oh, okay. - That was the best.
(To celebrate sleeping as a group, they end the day with a local beer.)
Gosh, it's nice and cozy with everyone in here.
- Oh, goodness. - It was perfect.
Anyway, things are going well.
Thank you, guys.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(A cool can of beer...)
(to finish the day)
(Glancing)
But...
it's almost 10pm right now.
- The sun won't set. - It still feels like daytime.
But even when the sun sets, it's still bright out.
It's so fascinating.
(Even after some time, they still find the midnight sun fascinating.)
(The sun must not want to go to bed yet either.)
(It's still holding on tight.)
Honestly, I think today was...
the day I felt most adjusted.
Since things were a little bit uncomfortable...
- as we were used to... - Right.
- Korean culture and lifestyle, - Yes.
But I think I've adjusted to the standards here now.
- Today was so nice. - Right.
Not that the other days weren't nice.
(Even the most steadfast city boy was truly adjusted.)
Earlier, while we were resting before cooking and eating,
I was just walking down to see what was there,
and I felt kind of sleepy.
I just lied down on a rock there and took a ten-minute nap.
Oh, really?
- That's why you weren't around. - Yes.
While the three of us were skipping stones.
Then, when I saw a boat,
I wanted to go rowing a bit.
(If you want to row, you can go on the boat in front of the house.)
I thought, "Living like this must bring you such joy."
(The way I lived my life wasn't the only correct answer.)
Dong Yeon, you're a true man of nature.
Dong Yeon really seems to like that kind of stuff.
And more than anything else...
- Maybe it's the great air quality, - Yes?
But I can sing so well.
"Love of a Thousand Years."
I can't sing the high notes for "Love of a Thousand Years" in Seoul.
But it was so fascinating that I could reach them so easily here.
(One person on the river, another person on land)
(The natural echo makes singing a duet fun.)
- From land to water... - We sang back and forth.
- It was good, right? - Yes.
- It was our own karaoke. - Yes.
And today,
things felt really Finnish.
- Today? - Right.
- Eun Woo. - Yes?
You didn't sleep in the tent last night.
(The guy with that experience keeps his mouth shut.)
That's enough.
Dong Hwi, I'll just...
- sleep in the tent tonight. - No.
I can't let you sleep out there.
Maybe Dong Yeon, but not you.
Why do you keep doing that to Dong Yeon?
Stop saying that stuff.
(Seriously, stop saying that to me.)
- You're scary. - Watch out for your carotid artery.
(It hasn't even been 10 seconds since they were in sync.)
You brought a taser gun.
(The funny Dong Brothers have a unique way of showing love.)
Seriously...
But honestly,
seeing a bear is also...
- We really have to see a bear. - Yes.
I always think about this kind of stuff.
First of all,
- I'd block the window with the bed. - Right.
We just have to block the window.
And then, the lower cabinets there...
Lift that up.
(Pretending to fall asleep)
(Also pretending to sleep)
Eun Woo, are you sleeping?
Dong Hwi, are you sleeping?
(Why, you people...)
I'm not going to cook anymore.
No.
- Oh, I... - I won't cook anymore.
(The news of Chef Kwak's strike strikes down like lightning.)
I was listening to you so well.
Yes, I related to what you were saying.
I'm only going to cook for Je Hoon now.
(From now on, he's Lee Je Hoon's personal chef.)
- Why did you tell me to do it? - You were copying me.
I won't give you any food. You should just starve now.
I'm really sorry.
(An apology that's faster than the speed of light)
I have so much respect for people who can cook.
- I know. - Dong Yeon did a great job.
I know.
(That's not enough.)
- Dong Yeon deserves our respect. - Of course.
Gosh, seriously.
(Smirking)
You're like our savior.
(The final bit of praise)
(Savior Kwak's anger melts away after three rounds of praise.)
Should I post an apology on social media too?
(Should I post an apology on social media too?)
Shall we go to bed now? Shall we get ready for bed?
(I'll cook for you, so let's stop this and go to bed.)
(It's still bright at 11pm. They wash up early to get ready for bed.)
Gosh, that's refreshing.
(They move the table and set up the two sleeping bags.)
(While organizing the bed...)
I'll just sleep on the floor.
(I'll just sleep on the floor.)
(The eldest will sleep on the floor instead of the two youngest guys.)
Je Hoon, will you sleep there?
Gosh, yesterday, we still...
Shall we sleep down here, Je Hoon?
- I wanted to try the sleeping bag. - Oh, really?
I've never slept in one before.
(Positive Eun Woo thinks the sleeping bag is actually nice.)
- Okay. Let's become caterpillars. - All right.
Orange caterpillars.
(The two orange caterpillars look rather cute.)
Goodness.
(Squirming around)
(Squirming)
Hey, why do you look so cute?
- Dong Yeon and I... - Yes?
Sorry, but we simply... What?
(Why are you down there, Je Hoon?)
But why are you...
Last night, you guys...
slept in the sleeping bags, so we were very grateful.
You guys should sleep in the beds tonight.
- Oh, really? - Thank you so much.
Thank you so much.
I was expecting it.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
We won't refuse.
All right. Good night.
- Let's go to bed now. - Yes, turn off the lights.
Dong Hwi, we can't get out.
- I'll get the lights. - Because of the sleeping bags.
(In the no-electricity rental room, they turn out...)
(all of the lanterns and the candles.)
But we really are tired.
We've had a full day.
(Current time: 11:30pm)
- Good night. - Gosh, seriously.
I'm so tired.
- Dong Hwi. - Yes?
Can I go like this in my sleep?
Can I go like this too?
That looks like it'll be harder for you guys.
- I'll work out my abs. - Leg raises?
- Goodness. - Oh, you're right.
(A sudden show of super strength by the caterpillars)
- These sleeping bags are nice. - They are nice.
- You guys have so much energy. - Hang on.
Why are you waking yourselves up when it's time to go to bed?
- Je Hoon. - This is driving me crazy.
- I'm wide awake now. What do I do? - Yes, I know.
Please stop talking.
(Stop talking.)
We can't sleep.
(We won't be able to sleep tonight.)
Good night, guys.
(The Renters went to bed before midnight for the first time?)
Dong Hwi, what do you think happiness is?
I think he's crazy.
No questions allowed.
(Please go to sleep.)
Dong Hwi, how do you grow out your mustache like that?
Not like now... But...
(Not like now, but when you looked cool.)
- When... - But...
can't you ask me this in a private message?
(Can't we sleep now and talk about this in Korea?)
Why? I could ask.
You sure have a lot of questions.
Dong Hwi, why did you name your company, "Company On?"
Eun Woo, please stop asking questions!
(Can't we just go to bed early today?)
My gosh, seriously.
Dong Yeon must be sleeping. He's so...
- Dong Yeon, are you sleeping? - He's seriously...
Why did he come here if he's going to do that?
He should've just stayed at home alone.
I have no clue.
(Laughing)
(Dong Hwi couldn't be woken up alone and decides to wake everyone else.)
Stop it.
Oh, that was good.
All right.
That was great.
I feel like we're shooting a sitcom.
Dong Yeon.
I put my foot on Eun Woo's leg.
Okay.
(Laughing)
(The fantastic chemistry between the Dong Brothers)
Gosh, darn it, Dong Yeon.
(Our dear Dong Yeon)
Gosh, I ought to kill you.
(What use is it to go to bed early?)
That was great timing.
I love that timing right there.
Being brave and wise.
Giving laughs and touching hearts. We did it all.
(Dong Hwi is proud after waking everyone back up.)
At what point were we supposed to feel touched?
- First of all... - Your twerking.
(The most touching moment of today was Je Hoon's twerking.)
Gosh, seriously. That was shocking.
Caterpillar twerking.
(Then I'll show it to you again. Caterpillar twerking!)
Here they go again.
Why aren't you guys sleeping?
Encore!
You guys seem crazy.
I mean...
I think it's right to sleep apart.
We shouldn't sleep together.
(The rented room was filled with the sound of laughter.)
(They ended up falling asleep past 2am.)
You're right.
(After the darkness passes...)
(that fell after everyone became quiet, )
(the bright sunlight of Lapland...)
(comes up without fail.)
(They greet their own morning, apart from the world.)
(Current time: 8am)
(Rustling)
(Click)
(Waking up and coming outside barefoot)
(Je Hoon woke up first today as well.)
Goodness.
(A quiet privilege...)
(that only those who wake up early can enjoy)
My gosh.
(He can't go without his pajamas today either.)
(At this rate, Je Hoon's personal color is his sky blue pajamas.)
This is incredible.
(As long as he has the deck and his pajamas, )
(this is his runway.)
(Maintaining his dignity with his pajamas...)
(as they're the city boy's last bit of pride)
(He can't give up his pajamas even while washing up with lake water.)
How can it be so clear?
(Perfect to the final turn)
(Meanwhile, the younger guys in the room...)
(The sunlight at 8am, not in the middle of the day)
(They're used to the midnight sun now.)
(They sleep well even when it's bright.)
(Woken up by the sound of the door)
- Je Hoon. - Are you awake?
(When did you get up, Je Hoon?)
(The other two are still deep asleep.)
- Get some more sleep. - Okay.
(He heads to the kitchen on his tiptoes.)
(But then...)
(Ringing)
(Frozen)
(Eun Woo is startled awake.)
(A sudden game of wits)
(What is he trying to do that he's making such a ruckus?)
(He takes out a bag of apples?)
For over 30 years,
I always have an apple in the morning.
That's my routine.
(Je Hoon's morning routine for staying young)
(Let's all grow younger together.)
(He prepares breakfast with the apples and blueberry juice...)
(they bought from the supermarket.)
(What are you doing, Je Hoon?)
Are you up?
(Nodding)
(He nodded, )
(but he's still squirming around.)
Guys, it's time to get up now.
Okay, Je Hoon.
(The youngest members listen to the oldest so well.)
(Eun Woo gets up right away too.)
Why was it so cold?
It kept turning off.
- Did you sleep in your jacket? - Yes.
For breakfast, let's have a simple meal...
with apples and blueberry juice.
- Sounds good. - And let's clean up...
and get going.
Bye!
(The second oldest can't get up after talking late into the night.)
Later...
(In their wide open sink, )
(he washes the apples like he's so used to it.)
(Squeaky clean)
(His behind as he washes apples)
(His behind as he stretches)
(Outside, the guys with handsome behinds have a busy morning.)
(Inside, Dong Min and Dong Hwi are still rolling around in bed.)
I miss my mom.
I miss Dongdong.
I miss my cats too.
I miss Dong Hwi too.
Dong Hwi is right here.
The real Dong Hwi.
Then am I a fake Dong Hwi?
Not the fake Dong Hwi, but the real Dong Hwi.
(It sure is fun to tease Dong Hwi the moment they wake up.)
Still, it's our last day.
Let's sit over there and eat comfortably by the river.
- Sounds good. - Looking out at the river?
- Yes, let's relax. - Okay.
Do you want a red or yellow one?
- I want a red one. - Here.
Thank you.
(Dong Hwi takes a red apple as he only eats familiar foods.)
(Positive Eun Woo obviously takes the unfamiliar yellow apple.)
Dong Hwi, try the yellow one too.
No.
Because the yellow one was a little more expensive.
Oh, really?
Then I should have a taste.
(Then let me see that.)
How is it?
Isn't it tasty?
- It's tasty. - Isn't it?
(Thanks to the rental brothers, )
(he's trying lots of unfamiliar things too.)
(They're enjoying Je Hoon's morning routine for staying young.)
This is nice.
Apples are the best in the morning.
(A hot spot for good apples and good views)
(This is the last day they'll get to see this view.)
Usually, when I go abroad, I look up gyms and stuff.
Gyms?
But here, all I care about is...
the bathroom and whether there's a sink in the kitchen.
You don't need a gym. You can just chop firewood.
- And row the boat. - Yes, row the boat.
- You're right. - That's the rowing machine here.
We do have a rowing machine.
It's actual rowing.
- The time... - Yes?
Just flies by.
(It's already time to go to their third rental room.)
Right, and I am looking forward to the vibe of the third house.
I know.
(The third rental room they'll get to meet today...)
(What kind of place will it be?)
Oh, here it is.
It's here.
(Ta-da!)
- The next house? - The next house?
What's this? Where is it?
I'll read it out for you.
I'm so curious about what the landlord looks like.
Their faces...
- Oh, they're a couple. - Yes, they're a couple.
- Yuri and Anne. - Yuri and Anne.
"Hello, we're a newlywed couple in our first year of marriage."
- My goodness. - "We fell in love with..."
"the friendly and peaceful vibe of Kemijarvi village."
"That was why we built our own home here."
"We're living with our animal family now."
Please.
- Let there be a cat... - A bear.
I miss cats so much.
"PS, the villagers are all waiting for you guys to visit."
(The villagers?)
It's Yuri and Anne's home.
Hey, then...
(Does this mean...)
(we will finally have neighbors too?)
But since they said the villagers were waiting for us,
it must be a village where people live close by.
- I see. - Billie Jean
Is not my lover
Eun Woo.
- Yes, that's it. - Nice.
I'm sorry,
- but that's enough pelvic movement. - Hey, so...
after the twerking...
(So hot)
He sure is different.
I have to hold onto something, though.
I can't do it.
- Darn it. - So early in the morning...
(Since they danced from the early morning...)
It never ends.
- Shall we get ready now? - Shall we get ready?
- Let's go. - Okay.
We need to get moving soon to...
It feels sad to leave.
Shall I organize my stuff?
Oh, dear.
(The fly swatter goes back into Je Hoon's bag.)
But now that we're about to leave,
it feels sad.
I think I've become attached to this place.
Is it because it's cozy here?
I'm sure the third house will have its own charms, right?
Of course. I'm sure it will.
We have to leave.
(They're sadly preparing to move houses.)
(Knocking)
(Knocking? An unfamiliar sound they've never heard here before)
(We're the only people around...)
(in this dense forest.)
(And someone has paid them a visit?)
(What is the final incident at the second rental room...)
(that fell upon the Renters?)
(Leaving the second rental room, )
(they arrive at the new rental room!)
(They come out of the forest and start village life.)
(For the first time since living in rented rooms, )
(they have neighbors!)
(And more neighbors)
(And it's full of other animal neighbors.)
(Seeing a crowd after a long while)
(Village life sounds fun.)
(Village life is so busy.)
(Let's hurry up and get going!)
(The village life with so much work starts!)
(Pull!)
(They pull, )
(hammer, )
(and get kicked.)
(With more neighbors...)
(comes more tasks to do.)
(And with more eyes on them, )
(they must dress up.)
(Let's wash up and get clean to live in the village.)
Gosh, my sleeves keep falling down.
Dong Hwi, I'll roll up my sleeves, at least.
(Chuckling)
(Eun Woo.)
(Let's give it a rest.)
(I can't give it a rest during our first village experience!)
(Using all kinds of tricks and schemes, )
(they adjust to village life.)
(This village really suits me.)
(The rental life begins in a strange rural village.)
(Lee Je Hoon)
(Lee Dong Hwi)
(Kwak Dong Yeon)
(Cha Eun Woo)
(Rented In Finland)