Please do NOT hardsub and/or stream this
episode using our English subtitles.
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
I like you, Jo Jae Hee.
that I just fall down awkwardly, and only make people hurt.
I've been grazed and getting weary of love.
Those lonely days.
Love was hard.
Even with practice, it wasn't working.
Even awkward me, even late me, will you love me?
It must be love.
It's love. Look at me.
Even if I close my eyes,
I can see you.
Because inside me, you're there,
because I can love you
because you stayed in my heart,
I'm not lonely anymore.
My heart, that once was so dark,
has a candle lit in your direction.
That clumsy heart
flew up to the sky that miraculous day.
It must be love.
It's love. Look at me.
Even if I close my eyes,
I can see you.
Because inside me, you're there,
because I can love you
because you stayed in my heart,
I'm not lonely anymore.
You are amazing,
more than anyone in the world.
Your loving and caring heart
has taught me too.
Episode 12
"Is okay to be troubled?"
Please have a sit.
You don't look too good.
I worked on the design late into the night.
Is that so?
I was picturing the house that..
I will live in with a certain someone.
With a certain someone?
Until now I've been designing
other people's houses.
I really want to design a house that...
I will live in together with
the people I love.
It's really... a little difficult.
That... isn't really good to work on.
It's still very frustrating,
and there's nothing good about it.
It's more comfortable to live alone.
Marrying, is like that.
But then, I met you.
Seeing to talking to people,
hanging out with the
people who understand me,
I feel it isn't bad either.
So...
I, too...
like you Dr. Jang.
I think...
I've liked you from the start.
Maybe... marriage isn't too possible,
but after meeting you...
Wait a second.
Yes?
Wh.. what did you just say?
After meeting you...
Before that.
I can't marry.
Right now I can't understand
what you're saying.
Didn’t you say you thought
about marriage after meeting me?
Yes, I thought so before.
But if I were to really design a
house to live in with you...
it won't go too well.
Haven't I made myself clear just now?
I'm lost for words.
Huh?
Who said they wanted to marry?
Why are you drawing a house
to live in with me all of a sudden?
No... but Dr. Jang wants to get married,
and if I also like Dr. Jang...
then we have to carefully
consider every aspect.
So then, you do like me...
but we just can't marry?
Just because...
you can't draw up a house we will live in?
Yes.
The house, I don't need it.
Huh?
Houses and all those, what does
it matter if it's paid annually or monthly?
That can't be done.
If I can't draw up or picture in
my mind a world with just the two of us,
then I can't marry!
This is a problem.
Huh? This person is seriously...
someone who only understands himself.
No... until now...
I don't need that anymore now.
Never again...
never again show your face in front of me.
Huh?
Houses and those things?
Pretending to understand me...
Oh! Doctor! What's wrong?
Can you let be alone for a while?
You've lived your entire
life like that haven't you?
Such a weird woman.
Don't walk so fast!
What are you doing?!
Huh?
Ahjussi are you crazy?!
Didn't you just poke my butt!
That probably... was done by that kid.
Oh my ahjussi is really funny hey!
Why are you falsely accusing my child?
I'm also a victim.
Hey, aren't you owning up?
You brat... you brat!
What are you doing ahjussi?
No... you've got it wrong...
This kid... butt...
Ahjussi! You're really...!
Ahjussi?
It's not me.
Yes, yes... We'll know after
we've done our investigations,
so let's go.
Hey hey look here,
please let me explain myself...
Ahjussi, what's wrong?
What's happening?
Thank god you're here. Let it to them.
Am I the kind of person who
will poke people's butts on the streets?
Huh?
Hurry tell them!
Hurry hurry!
Aish this ahjussi is really insistent hey?
Hand me your identification card please?
I can't give you my identification card.
There's no reason to.
We have to investigate before
knowing whether you're innocent.
I've already said that
it was that child who did it,
why was he let go just like that?
This student is accusing you ahjussi.
Student! Ahjussi isn't that sort of person.
This ahjussi is a very famous architect.
Just because you're a famous
architect then everything's alright?
Do you know how unhappy
and embarrassed I was back then?
I'm being dragged here,
do you think I don't have any unhappiness?!
Ahjussi, we'll see when
my parents are here!
Let's write up a investigation
report first. Name?
It's Jo Jae Hee.
Age?
40 years old.
Stop talking!
Marital status?
Single. This ahjussi lives alone.
Really...
That work... is one which received
a Gold Award from the Royal Family.
Ahjussi, let me see your
identity card please.
I'm not saying you're that sort of person.
Sometimes a person can be strongly denying,
but after that he's revealed
to not be a first-time offender.
You're already 40, have no dependents,
and there's your appreciation
for adult entertainment.
We should do our job shouldn't we?
Being 40, single, without dependents,
if I walk on the streets,
then I'll poke a high school girl's butt?
I'm not saying that.
You're really weird!
You're speaking as though
he is some offender!
I've already said this
ahjussi isn't someone like that!
Just treat it like you've
simply stepped on dung.
Woa... I helped so much
and he doesn't even say thank you.
I discovered a room that's better
than I thought I would find.
Really? Look around for more.
After tomorrow there's no
more overtime so I'll accompany you.
Am I bothering you too much?
At first I said I'll go with Hyun Kyu,
because my job requires me to travel.
Not a bother at all.
Look for places near my small district.
When Yu Jin moves out, I'll be lonely.
Me too.
Mun Jung, over here!
Here.
Father.
Hello!
Why are you suddenly picking
up a musical instrument?
Because I see dad's learning very well.
I also want to find some zest in my life.
Go learn together with Mr. Jo.
Please give up your hope on Jo Jae Hee.
I've decided not to see him again.
Don't ask me anything.
Dad don't raise the topic
on Jo Jae Hee anymore.
No... wh... what...
Which should I learn?
Oh...! Jo Jae Hee,
Yun Ki Ran Architecture Firm.
So, then this was the condition
for your return?
Because of the strong emphasis...
about us being the perfect partner,
so they requested.
Then we should openly admit being partners.
If he doesn't change his legal
name then he won't come back, right?
Regardless, from today onwards
I've decided to be reborn.
40 years old,
what can you do even if you're reborn?
Let's begin the Sam Choon Dong meeting.
Tonight Hyun Kyu and I have to go to
down to Wando for a while.
I worried leaving him here alone.
What on earth did Jae Hee tell
that couple that they haven't even called?
I didn't do anything wrong alright.
No matter what I don't feel at peace.
Mum had your surgery,
so now I feel less worried.
Yea... I came back to life without any pain.
See I told you.
We can run with all our hearts now!
Yes.
- Omo...
- Hello!
Dr. Jung, I'm being discharged already.
It's been hard on you.
Take care of yourself.
All the time I've been in the hospital,
you've put in much effort., thank you.
I didn't do anything special either...
Because of us, you've also had a tough time.
You have to come visit
our home alright? Hmm?
Then, please go well.
What's wrong?
What's with the atmosphere?
For this house,
the price is well worth it right?
That's true, but the alley
is a little scary.
Yu Jin, don't be like this, stay in with me.
My house has so many rooms.
I shouldn't trouble you.
I'll just have to look for more houses.
One more to view then come over to my house.
Come for a meal how about that?
Let's just eat out.
You're weird...
Why aren't you coming to my house recently?
I've been watching you.
Doctor...
Omo who is it?
Yu Jin, Yu Jin.
Come here.
Here, here.
Ahjussi...
the guy who stalked me on the public bus,
do you remember him?
Does it look like him?
Back then you saw him,
did you see him again after that?
I never saw him again, but I can't
think of anyone else other than that person.
How would that person know
your handphone number?
If he set his mind to it,
why couldn't he find out?
To look for a house,
she posted her number on the web.
I have to look for a house, what can I do?
Hyun Kyu isn't here either,
what should you do after work?
Ahjussi, can you leave work
together with me these few days?
Huh?
The high school girl incident,
I helped you quite a bit.
This ahjussi, on the streets...
was accused to have poked a
high school girl's butt.
I helped him when he was
taken to the police station.
703!
It wasn't me.
You owe Yu Jin, so you should help her once.
While Hyun Kyu is away, if Jo Jae Hee,
at least, went around with her...
don't you think it would be a
little less scary for her?
Even Mr. Jo Jae Hee?
The office is nearby too.
It's troublesome.
It can't be more troublesome
than marriage right?
It's such a troublesome matter,
how can you breathe?
Just for a few days,
before Hyun Kyu returns.
It was the same with Sanggu.
Have you already forgotten
that kind of hardship?
With a few experiences of being exhausted,
Mr. Jo Jae Hee will also
become a real person.
Did you two quarrel again?
I'll leave it in your hands.
Yu Jin, sleep well, don't worry alright?
Get home safely.
Dr. jang...
You were also in the sent picture.
Why aren't you thinking it could be you?
Maybe Dr. Jang is the target.
The picture wasn't sent to me,
it was sent to Yu Jin's handphone.
What's with him....
saying weird things to make me afraid.
What are you doing?
Just walk.
Huh?
It's not a time for me to be in a daze.
What exactly is that man trying to do?
What did you say?
Can't build a house so he'll not marry?
Hey! Just buy a house!
Don't you guys have a lot of money?
It's not that.
You have so many things really.
He's not a normal guy
that you imagine in your mind.
During that time he kept advocating
to me his thoughts...
that he is this sort or that sort of person.
I disregarded everything he said.
Did he say he likes you?
Does he want to date you?
If it were that, then I think he might.
No, I don't even know what
will happen then...
he's doesn't even know where to jump.
He isn't even a grasshopper,
how can there be such a person?
Even if he's willing to go ahead...
at my age do you think I'll enter a
relationship with no future?
Unni you're really...
Yes,
there isn't much time left
for you to give birth.
Just give birth!
Not bearing a child,
do you know how regretful that is?
A man whom I confessed my feelings to...
but concludes he can't get married,
can't make it right?
You first confessed and
now you're having this attitude?
My gosh! You're so disappointing!
Hey! Forget about it! Forget it!
Getting all agitated again.
Instead of saying it's a disappointment,
see it as sincerity.
That person seem to like living alone.
Hey! Forget it forget it!
Hey, could it be that guy?
That one from the meeting,
he keeps in touch with you, right?
That guy?
See.
Oh, what's this?
My boss is dead.
When I played dodge ball at lunchtime,
I stepped on “gold*”. (*dog poo?)
How could this kind of guy
do such scary things?
And he doesn't call me anymore.
I called him and scolded him upside down.
Hey, can it be he can't get
over it and ended up doing this to you?
Maybe he's so busy crafting humor
that he has no time to bother with this.
It's all your fault I'm can't live properly.
I shouldn't have gone to that meeting.
That Ahjussi....
That ahjussi can't be the criminal, can he?
Ahjussi,
I'm very thankful that you're
sending me home.
This is so embarrassing,
can't we talk as we walk?
You want me to send you home...
now you want me to provide
conversation service too?
What's that?
This?
A 1945 Baton Rachir.
It's one of the limited
15 bottles imported into Korea.
Ahjussi, it seems a part of your
life has stopped in the growing up stages.
What?
How is it you display such
child-like expressions?
After all, you're already a
man in his forties.
What expression?
When you speak with those expressions,
it's really sickening, you know.
What? What? Why? Why?
I'm sure it was this kid.
What?
The kid who wedged my butt.
What was that all about, ahjussi?
There'll come a day we'll meet again.
What were you thinking?
Putting up your contact number on the web?
The root cause is that you're
too lacking in caution towards others.
If you treat others with
caution all the time,
then I'll become just like you,
isn't that right?
You!
Ahjussi, you get along so well with Sanggu,
why do you always quarrel with other people?
Dogs don't talk, right?
They can communicate, you know.
I'll show you.
Sanggu, down! Down!
You call that communication?
I'm sure you haven't seen this one yet.
Sanggu, down, bang!
Bang!
Bang! Bang!
Kiddo!
Ahjussi, you and Sanggu seem
to have telepathy.
Cute lady!
Such a cute lady!
Ahgassi, how old are you?
What do you think you're doing?
I say, you....make.....way.
- Ahgassi.
- Stop that.
- You hit me?
- So what if I did?
Jerk, how dare you hit me?
Anyhow, you always bring trouble to others.
I'm sorry.
I've lived for 40 years,
but it's my first time
facing a situation like this.
Ahjussi, it's because you've
never dated before, that's why.
Alright, you may go.
Ah!
This lady here is being stalked.
Please activate phone-tracking on her.
What kind of harassment are you facing?
I receive this kind of messages.
Is that all?
You're asking if that's all?
Then what other harassment is necessary?
Please go ahead to file a suit.
What is that?
So you mean we'll have
to wait for court proceedings?
Once the court rules that
this is a crime of stalking,
then we can start phone-tracking.
But what if something
happens before that, then what?
That is the regulation.
Does that regulation make any sense?
I can't do anything....
But if the regulation is not
sensible then it's got to be changed.
The people's police force
should protect the people, right?
Oh, sorry.
Oh, Yu Jin.
Ahjussi sent me home safely.
You didn't get any of those
harassing messages again, did you?
Yes, we made a report at the
police station too.
Really?
Doctor, about the ahjussi,
it's so surprising.
What is?
Just now I saw him reasoning
out with the policeman,
I suddenly found him so dependable.
Is that so?
Yes.
Lock up properly before you sleep.
Yes, good night.
Sleep well, Yu Jin.
Hey, Yu Jin.
Yes, where are you?
I'm still at Wando.
But I can only work if my heart's at ease.
Why must such things happen
exactly when I'm away?
You must keep the alarm
with you at all times,
and you must contact me as soon
as you receive those message again.
Hyun Kyu, when will you be back?
I think I have to stay for another two days.
I'm really sorry, Yu Jin.
Yu Jin....
It's because of work, it can't be helped.
Once I get back,
I will surely stay by your side.
Just let my boss protect you
for the time being.
Alright.
Yes, sleep well.
703?
You got off work already?
Yes, ahjussi.
But I'm working overtime today.
Today, I've contacted my boss already.
You don't have to come over.
But you still have to walk the dog, right?
Ah, Sanggu.
Alright, I'll call you when I get back.
Bye.
You...that sounded like setting up a date.
It does sound like creating
a misunderstanding.
Is that Dr. jang?
You're so lacking in discernment,
he didn't use polite terms just now.
You two are close enough
not to use polite terms already?
No, it's not Dr. jang.
Then is it that colleague we saw?
Don't bother.
It's a dog owner.
He mentioned about walking
the dog, didn't he?
So it's because of this girl,
you quarreled with Dr. jang?
Uncle,
are you going on a date?
No.
Hey, who is it?
For me, it's alright even
if it's not Dr. jang.
Mum!
Yes, yes, of course.
Let's arrange a meeting soon.
Have a good trip. You're welcome.
Bye!
The Samshin-dong client...resolved.
The one who got mad at Director?
How did you do it?
I gave away Jae Hee's Jeju island
travel voucher to the lady.
Maybe it's because the husband
forgot about the wedding anniversary,
that's why the wife became extra-sensitive.
The husband then annoyed
the wife unknowingly.
But it didn't sound like
they were fighting about that.
The wife.....
you guys really don't know women.
Jae Hee has the instincts to design
the best architecture with the best style,
and you're still far off from him,
but you should research on people first.
Only then can you build
houses that people live in.
Why are you lecturing me so bluntly?
These are the inspection results.
Manager,
did you really dump Mun Seok Hwan?
With your instincts,
you can't even build a small dog house.
Too much.
I really like Jae Hee.
What? What!
Oh, I feel relieved.
How is it you guys have no sense?
Manager, you said you like Director?
Why did you say such a ridiculous thing?
When we're done with work,
how about we go for a drink?
Seems like it's for real.
Well, drinks....but make sure you don't cry.
What should I do? My tears are falling.
Hey...
do you think I should just
give it a good cry before we go?
You stay here with me.
You can't do that.
Don't cry, please.
Got it.
Really.
Thank you.
This man doesn't fit you.
I'm the only one who fits you.
What's this?
We will be meeting real soon.
Have you found out who it is?
2 days ago, he sent some photos.
When I was looking at them,
I remembered something.
What did you remember?
What's this?
2 weeks ago, I went to Family World
with Soo Young.
Family World?!
Ah That's right.
You lost your handphone then, right?
Yes, you remember that too?
Hey, my handphone is gone!
Where did it go?
Thank you.
That's great.
Shall we take a photo together?
1....2.....3.
That day, I dropped my
handphone in the Haunted House.
I went back there and looked for hours,
then I found the Mummy holding my handphone.
What did he look like?
The bandages were all around him,
I couldn't see his face.
Should we report to the police?
If it's only our suspicion,
the police won't act on it.
We have to get proof.
How about I make a trip there?
You, Doctor?
Since I'm free anyway, I'll go.
Not by yourself.
When I finish work, we'll go together.
It's still day time, it's alright.
I'll take a look and be right back.
I'll check if that guy was at the
Haunted House yesterday and the day before,
whether he reported for
work or not, that's all.
Right? Right?
It's not time for you to get
off work yet, is it?
Ahjussi, Dr. jang went on her
own to check out that harassment suspect.
Suspect?
She went by herself to
Family World to see the suspect,
I keep worrying that she might be in danger.
Maybe, ahjussi, if you have the time,
This woman is really....
Mr. Jo Jae Hee, why are you here?
Why are you messing with
other people's business?
It concerns Yu Jin, you know.
You two should just get married.
Why did you come all the way
here to make trouble?
I got a shock.
Welcome all passengers,
to the Haunted House.
You will see all kinds of evil
spirits from hell,
we hope you will have an...
unforgettable time here with us.
- Does it always shake like this?
- If any of you have done wrong things.....
you will face the judgment of hell in here.
You go first.
You go first, please.
- But...
- Please.
- Come nearer.
- Oh really.
You jerk.
Go! We got frightened twice already.
Who are we looking for again?
The Mummy.
Mummy.
We're here in hell.
Earlier, those were yama* ghosts.
(*sent to bring the one who just died to hell)
What?
Those without children, when they die,
they can't bear the loneliness
and the grievances,
so they come to haunt others
with their loneliness and resentment.
Just like someone I know.
Ghost stories like this,
were crafted to get people married.
Bachelor ghosts, virgin ghosts,
hanging ghosts,
those who aren't married
will suffer and be ill-at-ease,
do you know why that happens?
Ah!
That....
That's the one,
I think it's him, let's get him, quick.
Mr. Mummy!
Telephone number?
I just handed back the handphone
to the owner, that's all.
Have we met somewhere before?
What?
You...
Ahjussi, ahjussi, ahjussi.
Behind, there's a weird fella behind me.
Bus.
Bus?
The guy who stalked Yu Jin?
What are you saying?
Remove those bandages.
I won't.
You!
Check it out, quick.
What are you doing?
You were on that bus!
Hey, I don't know what you're talking about.
Is it him?
Come with me to the police station.
If it's him, let's call the
police now, quick.
If the police finds that
I'm not the culprit...
how will you be responsible?
But you guys are too ridiculous.
Just because I do this kind of work here,
you look down on me?
What's up? Why? Did something happened?
- What is it?
- What's wrong?
Where were you last night?
Of course, I was working here.
Yes, he was here yesterday.
Let me see your job time card.
Time card? What a joke! Are you joking?
Why do you have to see the job time card?
I'm sure that's the guy.
Many people saw him at work
there last night.
So he has an alibi then?
What alibi?
What a coincidence!
If he's not the one then who else?
Is there anyone else suspicious?
He's the one. That's it,
that's it, that's it..
that policeman!
Every time 703's in trouble,
she goes to the police station, right?
How can it be the policeman?
That's ridiculous.
When ahjussi's butt was wedged,
he was grilled by that policeman.
So I think he's been bearing the grudge.
In movies and dramas...
the most improbable person
is always the culprit.
Security guard, police, friend...
people who seemed trustworthy
turns out to do bad things.
Is this the time for jokes?
Jokes?
But who am I doing all this for?
From Sanggu to 703,
Dr. Jang, I'm not like you...
butting into other's affairs just
because you're lonely.
I am a man with a busy work schedule.
- Ahjussi!
- What?
Yes...
I'm so bored that I'm
butting into other's affairs.
If you're not happy, you should have
said you didn't want to do it.
Then, Dr. Jang...
Forget it...
today I'll send Yu Jin home.
We will never trouble you again,
Mr. Jo Jae Hee.
Alright?
Since we're done talking, you may go.
I'm telling you to leave it and go.
Do you have a discount card?
Do you have a member card?
It's 12, 000 won.
[Today] [Closed]
[Apologies]
Is this place safe to rent?
Yes, since you said a
rooftop place is too dangerous,
this time round,
I chose a half-basement place.
Whether it's rooftop or half-basement,
it's still dangerous.
Excuse me....
Let's go, Yu Jin.
What?
I found a decent place
so we're taking another look.
You don't have to explain these
things in detail to Mr. Jo Jae Hee.
Two feeble ladies,
who's going to protect who?
Could it be a place with some problems?
I was told the owner had to go
overseas urgently hence he's renting it out.
And the facilities nearby
are all affordable,
and no property fee too.
To me, this is like striking lottery.
Even so we must ensure there's
no problem with the place.
Let's have a look, if there's a problem,
you shouldn't rent it, understand?
Hey, what problem can there be?
Who is it?
Is this the place for rent?
Please come in.
Isn't it too quiet?
It's alright.
Here.
It's cleaner than I imagined.
Where is the owner?
This guy... the Mummy?
Where did they go?
You're here to look at the place,
right? Go ahead.
Stay there.
What's wrong?
I haven't done anything.
Don't come over.
Ahjussi!
You... you!
What?
You stinking Mummy.
703, are you alright?
Jerk, you jerk!
If you dare harass 703 again,
I will... I will...
Ah, ahjussi, are you alright?
Manager, please send me to Yu Jin's house.
You're going to your girlfriend's house?
Of course, I have to see
her to set my heart at ease.
Ahjussi, ahjussi!
Ahjussi, are you alright?
Jo Jae Hee, Jo Jae Hee....
Ahjussi.
Ahjussi, are you alright?
Is it over?
From her photo messages,
we can nail the culprit.
Investigation shows there are evidence.
I think he will be charged with harassment.
I need someone to go make a statement,
these two probably can't.
Can you come with me?
Yes.
About that Ahjussi...
What?
Doctor...
I feel weird.
What?
My heart... my heart's jumping up and down.
Don't tell me I....
I like the ahjussi?
What should I do?
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
Main Translators: krayfi, ai*
Spot Translator: meju
Timer: julier
Editor/QC: NikieNana
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
Please do NOT hardsub and/or stream this
episode using our English subtitles.
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!!!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com