Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
Please do NOT hardsub and/or stream this
episode using our English subtitles.
Episode 3
Why did you come here? Did you follow us?
I'm only here because I followed
the Director.
That... That...
What I said just now... was actually
a joke.
I can't hear you!
Actually... It was a joke.
What did you say?
You still refuse to admit you're
wrong, right?
No.
Didn't you come to apologize?
Eh... Yes.
Then try saying it.
If it's so hard to say,
then this should be of some help
to you. Drink it.
Drink it all.
It's that not enough?
Should I give you more?
Oh my!
- They hugged!
What are you doing?! Oh my, oh my!
You don't have to be this way!
He knelt!
It doesn't seem like it!
What? Oh my, Jo Jae Hee!
Oh my!
He's down.
Jo Jae Hee sshi.
Jo Jae Hee!
Jo Jae Hee! Wake up!
Yes?
Pea...nut.
Are you allergic to peanuts?!
Yu Jin, were there peanuts in the cocktail?
I'm don't know.
Jo Jae Hee!
Ambulance, quick, call an ambulance.
Wake up! It's fine, everything's fine,
wake up.
Is he better now?
Yes.
I heard that the cocktail only had the
slightest amount of peanut butter in it.
Some people react a little more
severely.
He's alright now, you guys can stop
worrying and go home.
Yes, then we'll leave first.
- It's been hard on you.
- Go.
Why are you pulling that out?!
Wait till the treatment is over
before leaving.
Why are you so insensible, you can't even
bear with this?
The medicine is finished.
Oh yes, it is.
Just sit for a while, let me give you
a check up.
I'll lift up your shirt for a while.
Take a deep breath.
Let it out.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know you were allergic,
and I made you drink something
that had peanut butter in it.
I too...
Am sorry.
It is so difficult to apologize?
It's really been hard on you for
40 over years.
Crying so hard because of a joke,
Doctor Jang, you must be tired out too.
I've also seen times when
Mr. Jo was in tears.
There's absolutely no more problems
with your breathing, right?
Yes.
Let me look at your throat.
Ah, say ah.
Ah.
The Man Who Can't Get Married
[The Lonely Financial Road]
Excuse me, I'll... I'll help you.
The best and first-rate speaker system!
No. 800, 200 power amp double-bass system!
It's finally being sold in the country!
How can it be so expensive?!
That's only the price for one speaker,
not the whole system.
But you said he bought it?
That's the point.
That ahjusshi is really a money-earner.
He doesn't have a family to feed,
nor a woman to please,
neither does he have friends to drink with.
If he doesn't spend any of it, he just
saves more and more of it.
How can there be such lonely thoughts?
His concept of spending is very different
from normal people.
How is it different?
What I'm saying is that, this isn't even
enough for one year of a child's education.
Are school fees that expensive?!
Let's say we're not looking at
public education,
he alone is freely enjoying a rich,
plentiful single life.
You've completely been brainwashed.
Even finding pleasure in the single life.
It's worth thinking about. Men basically
love the single life.
When God created Eve, he took a rib
from Adam,
saying that he had given him wings.
That's why I say, the more we want to fly,
the more people tie us down.
Yet our wings grow with leaps and bounds.
I'm sorry, our hours of business are over.
Ah, yes.
Forget it, let's just split the bill.
What's wrong?
Whenever we looked at the menu to order,
you have no idea how worried
you looked, even I get frightened.
When did I?
I said I would treat you to a big meal
today, that's why I asked you out.
Give it to me, quick.
I'm not innocent enough to pretend
I don't know
what financial situation you're in,
yet still ask for a treat.
Let me remind you. Don't remain single.
There's nothing more pitiful than a
penniless single.
Even though your heart has wings,
it needs money before it can take off.
Here.
Do you want me to organize this?
There's no need, right?
Oh, hold on.
Are you planning on buying an apartment?
I'm just taking a look. It happens that
the lease of my house is coming up.
Even you don't buy, you should move.
That neighborhood has too many
homeless people around.
He said he wouldn't let me be independent
if I were more than 5 kms away...
I didn't think that little neighborhood
would be like that.
Are you so eager to be independent?
Wait till you're over 30 and still living
with your parents.
Living with each other is like hell.
We'll leave first. You've worked hard.
You too.
Bye.
Hello.
Your hobbies are really...
Do you know him?
Is he a regular here too?
But... What kind of job does he have?
He comes everyday without fail.
You've worked hard.
Be safe.
32 square meters, $640,000.
You scared me! Why didn't you make
any noise?!
32 square meters... It's quite good
if you live alone.
Even if you get married, both of you
can still live in it.
What do you mean 'if'?
What do you mean by that?
$640,000. You live up to your reputation
of being a doctor.
Isn't your income from construction
quite good too?
Not long ago, their was a piece on an
architect, what was his name?
You look at his houses,
that are luxurious mansions,
just their art collection is...
No matter how you put it, they must be
special cases to get on television, right?
Have you seen this film?
This DVD is pretty good.
It's dual sound, high definition.
Look at you being all happy.
Then... I've still got something on.
Yu Jin, it's me.
The medical report is out.
There's nothing wrong at all.
Really? There're no problem?
Doctor, that's really a relief.
Should we have dinner tonight?
I'll treat you to a big meal.
Yu Jin, could you make a copy for me?
We've recently released a new product,
and have to do marketing surveys.
I've been working overtime recently.
That's right, your internship review
is coming up soon, right?
Yes. If I want to survive and stay,
I have to perform a little better.
Okay, work hard.
Yes!
Yu Jin, the patissier said we could use
the kitchen now, let's go give it a try!
Really?!
Ah, copy! Hey, wait for me,
I'm going to make a copy of this!
The design is already ready, what do you
mean by they're backing out?
They said no matter what they couldn't
get $10,000.
There's nowhere we can cut costs.
Don't say that, let's try and think
of an idea.
Should we cut out the bathroom?
You should try and consider the
customers' position too.
Even though it's a waste, how would it be
if we changed the kitchen?
Let's not use this overhead component,
and nail it to the wall...
This hanging component is the main focus.
You can see the garden through it.
If we changed it, isn't that all destroyed?
If we have to do that, there's no
reason I should design this.
Just compromise a little.
Introduce them to a different architect.
Director,
after Sangye-dong, we have no other
jobs on our hands.
Changing the kitchen around a little
is not a bad idea either.
Are you a designer or a businessman?
I understand.
Is Mr Jo Jae Hee around?
Ah, just sit there, I'll go.
Do we have to give another job away again?
Are we going to give it to
Mun Seok Hwan again?
That person is really making it rich
because of us.
It's all a strategy.
Are you...
You're transferring all the jobs there, Manager,
you won't transfer over there either, will you?
If Manager leaves, how can that person
handle everything by himself?
The company will collapse.
Do you want to leave with me?
I want to stay by Director's side.
Aigoo, how obedient.
What did you buy that's making
you so happy?
The Roulette of Life.
The remake of the 1968 limited edition.
Isn't that the game where you throw
dice and buy land?
You aren't a child anymore.
You can't play that game alone, can you?
That's why?
Why can't I play it by myself?
All these weird people.
There aren't any patients, are there?
Yes. Doctor, I've paid the medical
insurance, and this as well.
Ah, that... Someone called.
Matchmaker?
Yes, not yet... Doctor is back,
please hold on.
He's called many times already,
when you weren't here.
Yes.
Yes, Dad.
How come you're the only person that's busy?
How can I be free all the time?
Really, you've embarrassed me in front
of the nurses,
why do you do this all the time?
Didn't I say you could leave a message
and I would call you back?
Is not knowing what to do and
not doing it wrong?
Because I couldn't contact you,
I'm starting to get a headache.
Ah, just change that habit of yours.
How can everything you want go your way?
Tomorrow at 3, make a trip to a
matchmaker's office in Seocho-dong.
Just go look for someone called
Choi Eun Seo.
Dad.
Didn't I tell you not to make
anymore applications?
It's an interview.
I'm definitely not going, and not going
for a matchmaking session.
Dad, I'm worried about your blood
pressure so...
Your qualifications didn't pass their
standards, so they want an interview.
Inter... Eh?
Out of 100 points, you only got 52 points,
just like your weight.
You really thought you were quite good,
that's such a pity.
So what is the reason that I can't
get married?
So I'm only worth 52 points, is that it?
Thank goodness, from now on you
will always be 52 points.
From 36 years old onwards, you get 0 points.
If other conditions don't change, no matter
if you're 40 or 50, you'll always fail.
On the marriage market you are
already helpless. I'm hanging up.
Ah, really.
[Oh Cha Gyo Matchmaking Agency]
Doctor! There's a patient.
Invite him in.
Please come in.
Where are you feeling uncomfortable?
I am Jo Jae Hee's mother.
Ah, is that so?
Jae Hee hasn't been bothering you, has he?
No, he hasn't.
Even though it's not much...
Oh, you don't have to do this,
I haven't done anything special.
Just accept it. It's just something polite.
Then... I'll eat it well.
Is there anywhere... you're feeling
uncomfortable?
Yes?
I've been feeling weak recently.
Have you been running a fever,
or had any other symptoms?
I don't think I've been having a fever.
Then, let me take a look at your throat.
Please say 'Ah'.
Ah.
Your throat seems fine.
There doesn't seem to be any especially
significant symptoms.
Maybe I'm stressed?
I have a son, who is not anxious at all
about getting married.
That child is just like me, an introvert.
That's why he acts that way, what can I do.
If he meets someone suitable, he doesn't know
how to hold on to her, isn't that right?
Yes.
But he's really successful in his career.
Getting the Architectural Culture Award,
and the Korean Design Award.
Is that so?
Oh my, you didn't know.
That child, has been serious about his work
and ambitious since he was young.
This, this...
The design that won the award.
This is the Seoul Architecture Award in 2005,
this is the 2008 Korea Design Award.
This is the 2008 Architectural Culture Award.
Ah, yes.
Jae Hee is quite a catch, isn't he?
You must be very proud.
I'll give you these.
Yes?
I still have the originals, it's okay.
You... You said something about
feeling weak, we could wait and see.
Watch your diet and nutrition intake, and...
pay attention to how many hours you rest.
What?
Lend me some money.
I borrowed some money from outside,
if Yun Hee's mother finds out, I'm dead.
You've given it to the women at the
Wild Horse club again, haven't you?
Her, let me tell you again,
I'm not having an affair.
If it were really the case, I wouldn't be
ableto ask you for a loan.
What's different about this?
It's pure.
Pure...
But you... How do you solve that?
What?
Ah, talking about purity,
I got reminded of it.
From what I know, you've never
even been in a relationship...
Do you have a obsession with cleanliness
that keeps you from going to those places?
You can't be...
Still a virgin, right?
I'm not lending you the money.
My whole life, I don't lend people money,
neither do I borrow money.
Ah, ah, save me.
How can the person who's maligning me,
have no drinking money?
All my pay is with Yun Hee's mother.
I'm only getting an allowance,
my position is about the same as Yun Hee's.
You can't even spend your own money
as you wish.
This is the result of getting married.
Time to eat!
Oh, oh.
What's wrong, you're acting strange.
Even though you earn much,
I don't see you as a millionaire.
Money you can spend freely...
How much money can you spend of
your own free will?
Have you spent all your allowance again?
Were the two of you scolding me
behind my back?
If you are single, you have your own money.
Once you're married, all your money goes
to your wife and children.
We're not here to listen to your thesis
on the single life.
Let's eat.
Yes.
Oppa, honestly, your inability to get
married is your fatal flaw, isn't it?
What?
Talking about some single life thesis
every opportunity you get,
that should be some kind of flaw, right?
It's not that I can't get married,
I don't want to.
Is there a difference between not being able
to get married and not getting married?
He just hasn't met the right person.
Once Jae Hee meets his other half,
it'll be alright. Right?
I said I'm not getting married.
She's better than I thought.
What is?
She doesn't look that old either.
Who?
Doctor Jang Mun Jung.
She's very presentable, and pretty.
Mom's very satisfied.
Mom!
Aigoo, spring's trash is really formidable.
What's good about getting married for you?
You don't know how good Yun Hee
is to my parents.
Just because of that, I benefit.
Hey, let's go together. After I take the
trash out, I have to go buy bread.
Hello?
I can't watch a movie today.
I have an exam, I have to practice.
What exam is it?
It's an activity where we make bread
with the customers.
Hold on, let me park.
Park? Do you have a car?
No, I'm helping the director run some
errands, so I drove the company car.
What should I do, what should I do?
What?
I hit something!
What should I do, what should I do?!
Is it a big scratch?
Yes, and it's obvious! There's even a dent.
Knock at it first.
Around the dent, make a fist, pound pound.
Hey, it's not at that extent.
Ah, this is a foreign branded car.
What?
Ah, this repair will definitely cost me
a bomb.
Hey, quickly run!
It's right outside my apartment,
where can I run to?
Did you get paint on your car?
Oh, of course!
Ah, just clean the paint off first. Your
carpark doesn't have a CCTV camera, does it?
Camera?
Camera, camera, camera.
Ah, this is really heartbreaking. It's not
even been a long while since I bought it.
I'm sorry, I'll pay you back.
It's really a heartache.
I can go now, can't I?
I never said I wouldn't let you leave.
Being overly nice and your on-scene
analysis, is really touching.
I helped you hide it a little,
I've tried my best.
You helped me a little?
The part where you wanted to run away,
didn't I omit that for you?
That's basic loyalty.
Yes, yes. What touching neighborly feelings.
I'm leaving.
There's really nowhere I could get
the money from.
Ah, I'm going crazy.
Looks like I have to get married.
In this game,
the only important point, is this part.
Okay, I've finished taking your photos.
It's been hard on you.
- Thank you for your hard work.
- It's all down to you.
They say I'm the featured perso
in The K magazine.
What's with the poses?
Actually the more shots I've taken, the less
I know what poses are more photogenic.
See it on next month's The K.
This is the information on one
of my juniors.
Once I mentioned the salary that you offer,
he said he'd fly over immediately tomorrow.
As Director Mun instructed,
he's very inspirational.
He doesn't have many flaws, and he has a
way with people. And pretty.
Manager Yun is a little disappointing.
Inspirational, with little flaws, good
with people, and pretty too.
Wasn't these the words I told you
when I made my confession?
Ah, disgusting.
Look at all the girls who like you,
Director Mun.
Now I really understand how varied
people's opinions are.
That's what I said too.
The salary that can entice someone from
abroad to take a plane back for an interview,
Why aren't you moved at all?
Because I would like to work with
the architect that I like.
Are you chasing me away like that?
With the confidence that
'My architect is the best'.
That is our business strategy.
Manager Yun.
Let's get married.
Sometimes you really make blind
confessions for no reason.
How could you look at it that way?
What if I were sincere?
From the start of the meeting till now,
there's been a woman propping up her chin,
waiting for Director to get off work.
Have you forgotten?
That's right.
Excuse me,
I hear that from the island models, there's
one with the sink separate from the island.
Ah, that type is over here.
Yes.
If I can use this, I can reduce
about 6 million.
Yes?
It's Jang Mun Jung.
Your mother left her scarf when she
was here for her check-up.
When I called her, she told me to
give it to you.
You can throw it out.
No, I can't.
From the dye that is high end,
it's expensive.
Old woman, she left it on purpose.
4.5 million.
It was dark last night so I didn't notice,
but now that I see you, you're very charming.
What?
Why is 4.5 million making you cry?
My youngests can make that in just 2 weeks.
When the money is ready, put it
in here, please.
Yes.
[Room Business Wild Stallion Manager
Lee Hwa Ran]
I could tell by her ambiance.
The car was in a man's name also.
I heard that those women's cars and houses
are provided by sponsors.
I guess it was true.
4.5 millions.
Because it's so ridiculous, I'm speechless.
The company car was in the accident,
so can't we use insurance?
I'm not even a regular employee.
Do you think they will?
If I bring it up for no reason and
get fired, that's worse.
Hey, try asking your parents for help.
I thought maybe I'll give them a call,
but it's not the right time.
They're worse off than I am.
My mom has no money for this.
With the deposit from my attic room,
I barely paid off my credit card bill...
It starts again.
If you get a loan, do you think you can
pay it off?
What can I do?
I have to use my cards to pay off
and work part-time.
Part-time...
Oh! Part-time job!
Do you have a good part-time job?
Yeah.
What?
This.
Get the money you lent to Tae Hyul.
You said it's about 5 millions.
Even if you're separated, you should
clear up debts.
He said he will when he gets the money.
Sorry, I'm late.
I'm sorry for bothering you on a holiday.
Now you know how to say sorry.
Are you happy?
I feel like I made a man more mature,
so I am happy.
Don't feel sorry.
I had some shopping to do, so I was
going to come out.
It's the same as me.
What would you like?
I'll have the ice coffee.
You're going to drink?
Am I not supposed to?
I just need to get the scarf.
I'm thirsty, that's why.
Before the coffee is served,
I'll give you the scarf first.
Where did it go?
That's strange. I brought it out with me.
I'm sorry.
Well, then.
A.. are you going to go like this?
If I drink tea with you, I would be
falling into a certain someone's scheme.
Excuse me?
Why are you carrying this around?
This is a misunderstanding.
Your mother gave that to me.
So that old woman, I can't stop her.
What do you mean cherish?
- Am I some...
- From now on, please don't see my mother.
I'm not the one who went to see her.
Even if she comes as a patient,
don't meet her.
She has her son-in-law at that hospital,
so tell her to go to him.
That's something you should take care of...
Then, what about you?
Why don't you go to the assistant director
instead of me?
You came twice last week.
I was there as a patient.
This!
The person who goes there to give you
this has a different purpose from me.
Then, do you think for another reason?
I will give the scarf to the
assistant director.
Then...
I will pay the bill.
I have no reason to let you pay
for my drink.
Does saying that you will pay the bill
politely make your mouth twist?
Why you!
Why are you giving this back to me?
Yes, Yu Jin.
What are you doing?
While feeling victimized and hollow,
I'm waiting for my ice coffee.
Doctor, why do you think that when you
don't have money, you want to shop more?
Isn't there some kind of study on this
in psychology?
Is that why you called?
I don't have any money, but I want
to buy clothes.
I just came to do some window shopping just
to let my eyes feel luxury, when I found it.
What?
Your clothes!
The way I can see you wearing this dress
100%, it was made for you.
The fabric they use is good and
it's comfortable.
I want to buy it.
Ah, this feeling of happiness.
So this is what people call vicarious
happiness.
Doctor, you're wearing makeup.
You had a date, right?
What do you mean date?
Please give me this in black.
Are you going to buy 2?
Wow, two times this!
If you're going to buy 2, choose one
in another design.
It's a waste.
Rather than disliking another style,
buying 2 of the same style that suits me
is unregretful.
I think as you get older, your shopping
habits change.
The same with cosmetics.
Rather than color, you look at the substance
and you spend more money on underwear.
You're saying that rather than looking
pretty for others,
what's better for your body becomes
the priority.
You can say that.
In my 20s, my youth added to my
fashion style,
but somehow supportive underwear becomes
more important at my age.
An apartment purchase?
Yeah.
I don't have any stocks or bonds.
With my money and my name,
I never imagined that I would consider home
ownership and still not be married.
There's nothing to laugh about.
If you don't pay attention, time passes
by in an instant.
Still, how nice is it to have money
to buy a house.
I'm grateful I can pay my credit cards off.
What?
It's just a situation I'm in.
Isn't your apartment really expensive?
On a young person's salary, it's impossible.
I thought your parents were supporting you.
A relative went abroad for 6 months for
business, so I'm living there for that time.
Oh, is that so?
Jeez, he's so despicable.
Yesterday, in the apartment parking lot,
I scratched someone's car door.
That tattletale enthusiastically
told on me.
Even though I didn't see it, I can imagine.
Ewww.
What's that?
What are you going to do about that color?
That's not for your age!
If he wore that and went in front of kids,
they'll call the police.
I put 10,000 won on it.
I bet that he'll get body searched at
an overseas airport. 30,000 won.
He's not going to buy that, is he?
Whew! Good decision.
That's right.
He's buying it!
What's he going to do about all the
chicken feathers?
You're here?
Boss.
What?
Did you wear that hat from your house
all the way here?
Why?
Nothing.
If you have something to say about
the hat, go ahead.
I think it'll be better if you don't
wear it.
Don't people look at you weird?
Mun Seok Hwan updated.
You really made a hobby of looking
at his homepage.
At his age to take self-pictures and
updating is pitiful, that's why.
What about you going to check everyday?
He's certainly a bum with time on his hands.
That's what I'm saying.
What is this?
Oh. Bring that here.
Yeah?
We'll be able to reduce 10 millions won.
Really?
I found a different model for the sink
and island.
The concept won't change and the cost
will go down.
If we make a few minor changes,
and make the entrance design a little
simpler, it'll be possible.
You didn't already pass the
project on, right?
I never even looked into it.
I felt like you would make it possible.
When should I schedule the client meeting?
Anytime.
Okay.
Make the design modifications with this.
Yes.
Hello.
Oh! Hello.
How did you... here?
No.
It's my day off, so I came to take a look.
That hurts.
I saw you to be a meticulous person.
When I'm wearing a gown, I seem
like that, right?
You're here to buy property?
I just came to look.
What's your expert opinion on this
apartment?
It's pretty nice.
Subdivided apartments are nice,
but if you're buying it as an investment,
apartments that aren't are better.
I don't know much about investments
and such.
Now that I'm here,
to be honest, I'm really confused.
When I look at the people getting
consultations,
all are either couples or with parents.
If I live alone among all those families,
I think I might be more lonely.
You don't plan on marrying?
No, that's not it.
Since I'm at this age, planning all the
possibilities would lessen the shock.
I learned.
You must be thinking "if there's no right
person, I just won't get married".
Single people our age usually
think that, right?
Since you say you're in the market for
real estate, I should make business of it.
After you see a well-built house, you'll
probably wonder why anyone would buy a house.
This is our Director Jo's work.
Oh, really?
The houses are really bright and have
an open feel, so they're unique.
If you look at his personality, you imagine a
windowless, door-less concrete house, right?
He has very good penmanship.
All these houses were built by you two?
Jae Hee does the creating, and I do
the homemaking.
What?
So he can do as much as he can,
I set the dinner table,
and when he causes trouble,
I wash the dishes.
Oh, I heard from Hyun Kyu.
Jo Jae Hee causes the trouble, and
apologizing is always your duty.
You even know Hyun Kyu?
Yes, it just happened.
What can I do, but apologize?
He seems determined to go to his grave
without saying "thank you" or "sorry".
Welcome.
You're by yourself, right?
I can't be alone?
No, not at all.
What will you have?
Give me a macara. Single.
Yes, I understand.
I have a gift for you.
A g ift?
I'll put it on for you.
It's so pretty.
Is it okay for me to accept this?
The jewel definitely has a owner.
I'll go look in the mirror.
By any chance, do you know me?
Yes.
No.
Hey, you're probably mocking me now for
trying to seduce a woman with money, right?
Why would you say something like that?
If you think about it, buying a woman's
affection with money
isn't it the best way to spend that money?
It's really pretty.
Soo Yeon, should we go to the suburbs
next time?
I'll give you a tour of the house I built.
Really?
Give me another Macara.
Double.
Yes, I understand.
"Wild Stallion"
So this is the place.
The entrance is strange.
What the?
That little...
The next patient.
Welcome.
Have a seat.
Where are you unwell?
My stomach...
Your stomach is?
It's different than usual.
Did you drink yesterday?
How much did you have to drink?
A bit.
You only had a bit, but you still smell
like it in the morning?
I had whiskey on the rocks,
about 4-5 glasses.
I drank doubles.
It's a hangover.
I guess that's a possibility.
I'll give you a prescription.
What if it's something else?
I think there are many sides to people.
I don't know much about architecture,
but I think you're a very good architect.
Your works were really warm.
You draw well and have nice penmanship.
I saw Yun Ki Ran yesterday.
Why are the two of you meeting?
I also heard that you redid a design
to save on the budget.
Why is she talking about that for no reason.
She said that with the money you saved,
you were putting in a special bed for
a patient, so I gave her a referral.
I heard that that family has a mother who's
paralyzed from a brain condition.
You really did a good job.
The way you smile is...
What?
Did you...
ever work in a charity group or in
some weird religious group?
Like grabbing people on the street preaching
or going to the mountaintop to
meditate and sing.
You can go now.
You are here? I finished the model,
take a look.
About Yu Jin
Yu Jin?
Your neighbor
I feel really sorry for her.
She's working an extra part-time job to pay for the car repair fees.
She says she only sleeps 3 hours a day.
Because she's dozing off and making
mistakes at work,
she's terrified she's going to get fired.
What kind of part-time job is it?
She won't tell me.
Director,
don't you think you're being too mean?
W... why is it my fault?
The reason you can drink, smoke, and drive
when you come to age
is to take responsibility for your
own actions.
But for 4.5 millions won,
there was no reason to tell on her
so enthusiastically.
How much?
For you that may only be the price
of an audio amp,
but to us poor young people, that money
can ruin our lives, you know.
One room was an office.
Another was a meeting room.
And another was a hospital.
They had it set up by different concepts.
Are all 'room salons' set up like that
these days?
Hey, you should have taken me too.
Hey, what's good that I take you along?
Hey, did men do weird things?
According to that woman,
if a man makes unwanted advances,
he gets kicked out and can't return.
And they still make that much?
She says they actually make more money
that way.
She said that a man's wallet is open
the widest
when he hasn't been fulfilled yet or
something like that.
That's perfect for women in need of money.
All you have to do is sit there with
them for a few days.
She tried to talk me into it.
She did, right? I thought it was weird
to bring the repair fees to her store.
Crazy! What does she take me for?
Let's just suffer for 3 months!
Can you ask your sister if I'm amazing
at sales, if she can give me a bonus?
Understood. I'll make sure to put in a
good word for you about the bonus.
Okay.
Hello.
I'm late again.
I think there's something wrong with
my stomach.
It's definitely a hangover again.
Do you have a problem?
We have to
satisfy all of them with 5 senses.
Smell,
touch,
and please look at this.
Yu Jin...
Yu Jin, wake up.
Wake up, Yu Jin.
Yu Jin...
Why are you like this lately?
You doze off in front of an important buyer
I tell you to put up the meeting agenda,
but you put up a customer complaint.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Call Tae Hyul.
Get your money from him right now!
His situation is obvious.
This isn't the time to consider other
people's situations.
Our evaluations are coming up soon.
Do you want to get fired.
No need for long conversation.
Just give him the account number and say
"give me the money". Coldly, okay?
Hurry.
Are you living well?
Yeah.
Why did you want to see me?
Oppa,
give me back my money.
I really need the money right now.
That's why you wanted to see me?
I didn't call you for a good reason, so
why did you wash your hair before coming?
Why did you put on cologne?
What were you expecting, you dummy?
Doctor.
Yu Jin, your number was on my phone.
I had it on vibrate, so I didn't see it.
I just called.
I was upset about something and
you came to mind.
What is it? I'll listen.
Tomorrow's an off day.
What are you doing?
Do you want to come over?
At my house, let's eat dinner and play
until we drop.
That sounds like a great offer.
Doctor!
Ah, I couldn't even wash up!
You live over there.
I know.
Come out.
What is it?
I heard the repair bill is a lot.
What are you going to do?
What does that have anything to do with you?
I guess I'll need to take care of it
somehow with a part-time job.
You came to ask me about that?
What is this?
Why should I accept this?!
It's not being used anyway,
so you can use it.
It's fine. I'll take care of it myself.
It's because I'm uncomfortable.
I hate making others uncomfortable and
I hate that others are inconvenienced by me.
If it's something that can be solved
with money, it's very easy.
It's simple.
But this is...
I saw you going to your part-time job.
You shouldn't do things like that.
There's nothing I can do.
Though it's a bit hard on my body.
If you were so tight on cash, shouldn't
you have sold the dog first?
He looks expensive.
What did you say?!
It's common sense.
Sanggu is family.
How can you sell family?
Is that common sense to you?
Then,
doing that kind of business with male
clients is common sense?
What's wrong with doing business with
male customers?
That's enough? Just use that for now.
I don't think I deserve to be sneered
at like that.
I don't want this.
It's better than working at a place
like that.
What's wrong with selling clothes?
You sell clothes too?
What else do I sell?
You sell alcohol also.
What did you say?!
I heard it was a secret part-time job.
Seriously!
You're really a ridiculous person!
Ahjusshi!
Do I look that pathetic to you?
Money doesn't seem like anything to you,
but I'm scared to death because of it!
The company is always threatening to
fire me, but I can't get a loan.
When I see girls having fun buying clothes,
I get angry, wondering why I'm like this.
I want to rob others.
I really need money right now.
But,
what did you say?
You're asking if I work at a bar?
Who are you to look down on me?
Do I look easy to you?
You don't even know how well I'm living.
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
Main Translators: wildblooms, ahsieee
Spot Translator: meju
Timer: jann
Editor/QC: snoopyvkd
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
Why is it that when you're around,
it's always like this?
Why are you bothering me on my day off?
I should have gone to the hospital to work.
I'm crazy. Why did I get on that bus?
Dog-napper!
He's your ex, right?
That's embarrassing.
Why are you running with a dog?
Leave.
Are you playing with me right now?
Jae Hee, do you want to watch a
play with me?
It took 8 years to get this close to you.
The client I talked to just now is sending us
tickets to watch the fireworks festival.
Boss, you're really not going?
You know there's a fireworks
festival, right?
Are you by any chance
asking me to go watch it with you?
Please do NOT hardsub and/or stream this
episode using our English subtitle
This is a FREE fansubs. Not for sale!
Get it for free @ withs2.com