[English subtitles are available]
[K💖I💖S💖S💖K💖H]
[Love Between Fairy and Devil]
[Episode 27]
[K💖I💖S💖S💖K💖H]
Just leave.
If you break into Cangyan Sea again,
I will not forgive you.
You too.
If you show up again in Shuiyuntian,
I won't go easy on you.
If we meet on the battlefield someday...
We will eventually have a winner.
Yes.
You and I have to settle the score.
I wish
we could go back to the days in Lucheng City.
Orchid,
can I have a word with you?
♫ Fall in love with your clear eyes ♫
♫ It's the most unforgettable scenery along the way ♫
♫ No one can ever replace what we've been through ♫
Do you like Yunmeng Lake?
♫ It's as bright as the stars ♫
Of course.
♫ Every decision I make for you ♫
The days we spent together in Lucheng City
are so happy.
♫ The story goes on and on ♫
It's like a dream.
♫ Stories in the past play in my head ♫
Me too.
♫ I will remember it to the end of my life ♫
When I was Xiao Run in Lucheng City,
♫ Don't think, don't miss, don't listen to it ♫
I had friends and brothers.
I dared to love and hate. I could follow my heart.
♫ No more ripples in my heart ♫
Compared with being Changheng,
♫ The sky lights up, be together and apart ♫
being Xiao Run is much better.
♫ People come and go, it always changes ♫
♫ Tramp over hill and dale to search for you ♫
♫ Act worthily of this life and our encounter ♫
In Shuiyuntian,
due to the responsibility of the God of War,
♫ Act worthily of my trip to a sea of woes ♫
and also because of my mother's sin of running away，
♫ Only in order to save you ♫
during all those years,
I've been abiding by Heaven's rules.
I dare not take a wrong step.
♫ Blaze a way through brambles and thorns to search for you ♫
I couldn’t even protect the one I love.
I could only keep her in my heart.
♫ Make light of traveling from afar for days with you ♫
When I was in Lucheng City,
I finally realized
♫ I will never betray you even if I betray the world ♫
what I want.
Orchid,
when I was Xiao Run,
I made many vows to you.
All my words are sincere.
Even if I'm Changheng now,
they still count.
♫ Don't think, don't miss, don't listen to it ♫
Before I transformed,
♫ No more ripples in my heart ♫
my immortal root was ruined by my master.
♫ The sky lights up, be together and apart ♫
It was you who pleaded for me.
So Master kept me.
♫ People come and go, it always changes ♫
You saved my life.
But...
♫ Tramp over hill and dale to search for you ♫
I was ignorant
and knew nothing of the world.
♫ Act worthily of this life and our encounter ♫
I didn't know there were various feelings in this world.
♫ Act worthily of my trip to a sea of woes ♫
My affection for you...
♫ Only in order to save you ♫
is gratitude and appreciation.
♫ Blaze a way through brambles and thorns to search for you ♫
It's not the affection that
♫ Make light of traveling from afar for days with you ♫
can make my heart sour and painful.
It's not the affection that even though it's crushed and buried in the soil,
♫ I will never betray you even if I betray the world ♫
it can still survive and blossom.
Lord Changheng.
Please take this back.
♫ Every decision I make for you ♫
♫ The story goes on and on ♫
♫ Stories in the past play in my head ♫
♫ I will remember it to the end of my life ♫
♫ Don't think, don't miss, don't listen to it ♫
♫ No more ripples in my heart ♫
You don't even want to
♫ The sky lights up, be together and apart ♫
keep it as a souvenir?
♫ People come and go, it always changes ♫
Please give it to your fated one.
♫ Tramp over hill and dale to search for you ♫
♫ Act worthily of this life and our encounter ♫
♫ Act worthily of my trip to a sea of woes ♫
♫ Only in order to save you ♫
♫ Blaze a way through brambles and thorns to search for you ♫
♫ Make light of traveling from afar for days with you ♫
♫ I will never betray you even if I betray the world ♫
What did you just say?
He's gone. Stop staring.
Let's go.
I've been standing for too long.
My legs are sore. I can't walk anymore.
♫ Tramp over hill and dale to search for you ♫
♫ Act worthily of this life and our encounter ♫
Can't walk?
♫ Act worthily of my trip to a sea of woes ♫
♫ Only in order to save you ♫
♫ Blaze a way through brambles and thorns to search for you ♫
♫ Make light of traveling from afar for days with you ♫
Put me down!
No.
♫ I will never betray you even if I betray the world ♫
What did you just say?
I'm not telling you.
Your Highness.
Shangque.
What's the matter, Your Highness?
After I went back,
I was worried every night.
Is there a way that
can lift my brother's Heart Curse?
If I knew it, would I hurt my brother?
Of course you won't.
Then why are you hesitating?
Actually,
the only way to break the curse
is to kill Orchid
with the ancient sword of Chengying.
But as you know,
I've been searching for it in the three realms under the order of the Lord.
But I still couldn't find the last fragment.
Even if we know how to lift the curse,
it's useless.
So that's why
you went to search for the fragments of Chengying sword.
Yes.
Your Highness,
have you found the last fragment?
No.
Pretty love locks.
Take a look.
Love locks.
Hi, have a look at the love locks please.
Very nice.
Look at them.
Are they good?
Have a look.
Pretty love locks.
Take a look.
Love locks.
Look at them.
Why are there so many love lock sellers suddenly?
The streets are lively too.
Yes.
Seven days later
is the Mountain and Moon Festival once in a thousand years.
Mountain and Moon Festival?
Do you see the moon-shaped mountain?
Every 1,000 years,
the full moon in Cangyan Sea
will meet it.
By then,
the full moon will be fully inserted
in the mountain.
If they meet,
will it be a bigger full moon?
This is the origin of the Mountain and Moon Festival.
What does it have to do with buying the love locks?
Why does everyone buy the locks?
I don't know.
Maybe it's a new custom
in the past 30,000 years here.
Jieli.
Orchid.
My lord.
Good.
No wonder I haven't seen you all day.
So you went on a date with the Lord?
Jieli.
My lord.
What are these?
You bought two locks?
Why did you buy them?
You have no idea, my lord.
It is said that
if couples who are in love
carve each other's name
on the love lock,
and hang them on the bridge of love
on the night of the Mountain and Moon Festival
when the Mountain and Moon meet,
then they will be...
What will they be?
They will be together forever and ever.
Really?
It's just nonsense.
It's just some groundless saying
without evidence.
It's not strained at all.
How wonderful it is.
I won't be interested in those activities
to cheat kids.
Neither am I.
So the Mountain and Moon Festival
is the lovers' festival
in Cangyan Sea every 1,000 years.
I grew up in the Haishi City.
I didn't even know
there was such a festival in our Moon Tribe.
I almost missed it.
Brother Shangque.
Are you available at the Mountain and Moon Festival?
I wonder if you have any instructions that day, my lord?
My lord,
please lend me Shangque
at the Mountain and Moon Festival.
Approved.
Thank you, Lord.
Great.
Just leave.
Go.
I'll look around.
Look at those merchants.
They are not good at doing business at all.
They're all selling locks.
How much can they earn though?
Let's set up a stall
to sell sharp gravers.
What?
Think about it.
On the day of the Mountain and Moon Festival,
almost all lovers in the Cangyan Sea will come.
So all of them will be
our potential buyers.
By then,
we can also sell some rouge, cosmetics and ornaments
with high price.
In such a romantic atmosphere,
men will not hesitate to spend money for women.
You'll be in charge of purchasing and running errands.
I'll be responsible for attracting customers.
We'll make a fortune.
I'm going to be rich.
So you're not going to
admire the moon with me?
Are you crazy?
How can you miss the chance to earn money
but to admire the moon?
Don't worry.
Your benefit is guaranteed.
If you come to help me,
I'll give you 10% of the profit.
What? Is it too little?
Then 15% of the profit.
That's not what I mean.
20%.
You're still not satisfied?
Black Dragon!
Boss.
You wanna buy the lock, Miss?
Show me your most beautiful locks please.
They are all here.
Pick one.
So beautiful.
Sir, do you want a lock?
What kind of locks do you want?
Lower your voice.
The style doesn't matter.
I want the hardest and strongest one.
Okay, I got it.
The stronger the better.
Okay.
I'll take this.
No. No.
I'll take these two.
Okay.
They cost one stone.
See you.
Please take a look.
[Little]
[Orchid]
Brother,
What is it?
Since the fairy is related to your life,
she should be strictly guarded.
Nothing must go wrong.
Why did you still
take her around?
Why do you indulge her so much?
As long as I am with her,
how can things be wrong?
Brother,
you can't use Hellfire now.
You're not like before.
I will recover in a few days.
And my Hellfire will be recovered soon.
Brother,
that fairy will be a disaster sooner or later.
Since you know how to break the curse,
why don't you reforge the Chengying sword and kill her
to prevent any trouble?
Not to mention the last piece of Chengying sword couldn't be found,
even it's successfully reforged,
I won't kill my beloved one.
Beloved one?
You keep saying
you're ashamed of the 100,000 soldiers in Xuanxu realm.
But now you're turning the culprit
as the one you love!
She is not the culprit,
but me.
The primordial spirit of the Chidi woman has been destroyed.
I will find another way to unseal them.
At this point,
I will do my best to help you find another way.
But no matter what,
the people of Moon Tribe and I
will never agree our Moon Supreme to be with
a fairy who brought disaster.
[Yunmeng Lake Lucheng City]
On the day you and the Chidi woman completed your hardships,
Rong Hao used the evil spirit to trap me.
Rong Hao?
You mean
the evil spirit that hurt you was from Rong Hao?
Yes.
Are you sure?
Of course.
Rong Hao must be closely related with that Lord of Haishi City.
Yes.
The Lord of Haishi City captured me in the Thousand Dreamland
and transformed out of the Arbiter Hall.
He even imitated Lord Changheng
and asked me to fix the Destiny Book.
He must have been to Shuiyuntian.
Otherwise, how could he be so familiar with the Arbiter Hall?
And he was so good at imitating Lord Changheng.
It was so alike.
Could it be that Lord Rong Hao told him?
[Crane Pavilion]
You're here.
I've been waiting for you for three days.
I knew you would find me.
I wonder
who is the one waiting for me?
Is it that carefree
and open-minded Lord Rong Hao,
or the Lord of Haishi City,
who is cunning
and plays tricks
in order to manipulate the fairy realm and the Moon Tribe?
[Crane Pavilion]
When did you start suspecting me?
I never suspected you.
But I don't know
how do you get the evil spirit to trap Dongfang Qingcang.
And why did the Lord of Haishi City, who has never been to Shuiyuntian
turn into me,
and created a fake Arbiter Hall
to cheat Orchid.
How do you explain
all these things?
Why?
That day,
when you insisted to save Orchid in Cangyan Sea,
you should have already known the answer.
If I could save my master,
what do you think I would do?
You will definitely fight to death.
Even if you will be betrayed by all the people,
or go against the law of heaven,
You'll do anything you can.
Do you know where this place is?
Once,
there was a mortal child.
He was born blind.
He had no parents.
He could only make a living
by playing the flute.
That year,
the winter in Yunmeng Lake
was freezing cold.
That blind child
hadn't found food for three days.
His body was freezing.
Only his fingers could move.
He sat there,
kept blowing the flute.
Gradually,
he lost consciousness.
He thought
he might be frozen to death.
But when he woke up,
he saw a person.
Yes.
He could see the world.
The first thing he saw
was a very dazzling
and beautiful lady.
But she looked so sad.
That blind child
is you.
Before I met my master,
I lived in endless darkness.
After my master died,
she took away all the brightness in my heart.
There's only
a hollow skin left.
To revive her, I became hollow-minded
who only knows killing and fighting.
And the Lord Rong Hao you know,
who is easy-going
and carefree
is just a mirage
outside this body.
Did you really kill
the 3,000 soldiers?
That day,
although I could save half of the primordial spirits of my master,
the 30,000 years of hardship experience
made her fragile primordial spirit
weaker.
Only the evil spirit
can stabilize her primordial spirit.
So I set up the Haishi City,
and instigated the internal strife of the Moon Tribe
to absorb plenty of spirits of the Moon Tribe
and refine the evil spirit.
But after Dongfang Qingcang returned to the Cangyan Sea,
I couldn't do anything to the Moon Tribe.
I could only...
The late God of War was upright
and tried her best to protect the people.
If she knew
you kept killing your fellows to make her resurrection
how would she feel?
People?
How can the people compare to her?
I just want my master to come back to life.
As long as I can see her again,
even if I will be killed by her,
I still feel no regrets.
We've known each other for ten thousand years.
You were my best friend.
But now I realize
I know nothing about you.
How foolish I am.
For the past 30,000 years,
on each anniversary of my master's death,
I would go to the monument to condole with her.
And the only person I met there
was you.
Changheng.
For the past 30,000 years,
I've been disguising
and lying.
But being friends with you is something I did
from the bottom of my heart.
I trust you.
I know you trust me too.
In order to save Orchid,
you are isolated and betrayed by others.
You and I are the same.
Otherwise,
how could we be friends?
But you've committed a crime.
Your sin is unforgivable.
Let's go.
I'll go back with you.
Li Yuan.
Yes, Your Majesty.
The matter of the sinner Rong Hao
is related to the three realms.
Each of his sin is horrifying.
He needs to be interrogated carefully.
Put him in the karma jail for now.
You are asked to strictly guard him.
Don't let anything go wrong.
Yes.
Although you committed a serious crime for the sake of a traitor,
you did a great job catching the criminal, Rong Hao.
She is not a traitor.
At this point, you are still stubborn
and disregarding the overall situation.
The overall situation
is just your big picture.
In your eyes,
our mother and I,
and your closest relatives
are all chess pieces on your overall situation.
You...
Why are you still pretending?
The power of Heaven is like millions of soldiers.
At the Memory Loss River,
I have openly defied you.
If you didn't kill me,
how will you rule the fairy realm in the future?
Besides,
if I die,
you can completely get rid of
the shame of our mother's sin of running away.
Isn't that a win-win situation?
Changheng,
do you really think I won't kill you?
Since I'm back,
I am ready to be killed.
Just for a traitor who colluded with the Moon Tribe,
you truly desire to die?
She's not a traitor!
I have been obeying the rules since childhood.
My long life
is like the frozen Northernmost Ocean
doesn't have any waves.
Until I met Orchid,
my world has colors.
Now she has someone in her heart,
and is willing to stay at Cangyan Sea.
The rest of my life is too long.
I really don't know how to spend my days.
Only after I die,
you can defend your authority.
In the three realms,
only you
can compete with that Dongfang Qingcang.
You are the God of War of Shuiyuntian.
How can you abandon your duties?
Changheng,
as long as you admit your mistake to me,
and be punished in front of everybody...
No need.
I'm tired of war.
From now on,
I won't fight for you anymore.
Fine.
I...
grant your wish.
Before I came here,
I've seen the fate of Changheng in this life.
The hardship he is supposed to experience
is not to kill Xie Wanqing.
In this life,
he should die for the one he cares.
Lord Changheng has successfully experienced hardships.
It meant I was the one he cared about.
But
the one he cared about was Cricket,
not Danyin.
Besides,
Lord Changheng loves Orchid.
One of the two weddings Tianji Mirror predicted
has come true.
Will the second wedding come true as well?
If he knows that Orchid
might be the Goddess of Xishan
who is his fiancée.
If I tell him,
there will be no turning back.
They will definitely get married.
But if I don't tell him,
no one will know that Orchid is a goddess.
Will Lord Yunzhong punish Lord Changheng
for committing a crime of collusion?
He'll has to be sent to the fairy guillotine.
Not necessarily.
After all, they are siblings.
No matter what, Lord Yunzhong will care about his sibling.
Fairy Danyin, bad news!
Fairy Danyin!
Lord Changheng offended His Majesty.
He...
What's wrong with him?
Tell me.
He's sentenced to a crime of committing a crime of collusion.
Seven days later,
he will be executed at the fairy guillotine.
Wooden Head, time to take the medicine.
You haven't recovered yet.
Why are you using your power again?
I've recovered 60%. I'm fine.
You start to act tough since you only recovered 60%.
Take the medicine.
Are you still worried
about your Hellfire?
In order to purify the primordial spirit,
you've wasted much of your energy and power.
You need to recuperate first.
We still don't know how to unseal the soldiers.
If my Hellfire can't be restored,
how can I protect the people of Cangyan Sea?
I'm afraid that I'm going to give birth the baby.
I'll get someone to deliver the baby for you.
You can't go.
I'm a woman from the Moon Tribe.
Our child
can't be found.
I'm fine.
Xing Luo.
But...
What should we do with our child?
Neither the Moon Tribe nor the fairies will accept her.
I'm afraid
she'll need to hide all her life.
No, she won't.
Xing Luo.
I'm here. Don't be afraid.
There's a trace of the Moon Tribe nearby.
Search!
Xing Luo.
Star Luo, are you alright?
Lord Rong Hao.
She is a member of the Moon Tribe?
have you seen a woman of the Moon Tribe
who is about to give birth?
A woman of the Moon Tribe?
I think I saw a pregnant woman
went that way.
Thank you.
Let's go.
Thank you for saving our lives.
You should leave now.
Go.
I didn't expect that Rong Hao is the Lord of Haishi City.
He's about to be interrogated.
What if he leaks the identity of Danyin?
Father, please save Changheng.
Danyin.
This is...
Father, why do you have something from the Moon Tribe?
Don't make a fuss.
This is just something I got
when I was on patrol.
Why didn't you submit it after it was confiscated?
It's a complicated matter. I forgot.
Father, tell me.
Lord Changheng will be executed in seven days
for committing a crime of collusion,
is it true?
Yes.
Lord Yunzhong
doesn't even show mercy to the Lord Changheng.
If he knows
you've been keeping the stuff from the Moon Tribe with you,
you'll get in big trouble.
Father.
You must be careful.
My dear daughter.
Don't worry.
I will be fine.
I won't let anything happen to you, too.
Father.
What's wrong?
I'm fine.
Xing Luo.
I'm sorry.
Not only did I fail to protect you,
but also your only belongings.
But I have no choice.
For the safety of our daughter,
I can't let her identity
be exposed.
Xing Luo.
I'm sorry.
Why is this black dragon's name
so hard to curve.
It's eight times harder than
the work Orchid does for the Lord.
Pavilion Master.
Greetings, Pavilion Master.
Lord,
I just received a report
there was a suspicious movement.
I'm afraid someone has sneaked into the palace.
Go.
Find a chance
to drop this blood
on the Bone Orchid worn by Orchid.
Whose blood is this?
Will this hurt Orchid?
[Love Between Fairy and Devil]