[English subtitles are available]
[K💖I💖S💖S💖K💖H]
[Love Between Fairy and Devil]
[Episode 36]
[K💖I💖S💖S💖K💖H]
Tai Sui.
I know you're here.
Come out.
Dongfang Qingcang.
I've been waiting for you for a long time.
I told you long ago
you'd lose her forever.
Give me your immortal body and spirit.
Only I can help you get what you want.
I've been waiting for you for a long time too.
Good.
Then give me your immortal body.
You want it?
Take it.
You! What are you doing?
What are you doing?
This is the sea of your heart.
This is
where you and I will be buried.
Do you think
you can trap me here with your power?
I myself
may not be enough.
But
with the power she planted in my heart,
it'll be enough.
This…
This is…
This is the power of the Goddess.
You can't get away from it.
Because she has left traces
all over the sea of my heart.
How dare you lie to me?
I only played a small trick
and you swallowed the bait.
Tai Sui.
Your delusions of grandeur
have fooled yourself after all.
Dongfang Qingcang.
I don't believe you!
I don't believe you have no delusions at all.
Dongfang Qingcang.
Are you crazy?
We could have lived the same life as heaven and earth
and become the heartless lord of the three realms.
But now you want to burn your spirit
for Xi Yun
and die with me?
Was it worth it?
The immortals will gloat at
our death.
You are the supreme being of the three realms.
Are you willing to
sacrifice yourself to save a bunch of nobodies?
Why would I not
die for her?
What about the wishes of your father and brother?
What about the revival of the Moon Tribe?
Are you going to give up all these?
They already have their own destinations.
Can you even give up Xi Yun?
Don't forget,
if we die,
Changheng will get Xi Yun
and they can be together forever and ever.
Dongfang Qingcang.
You can't fool me,
because I am you.
I know how much you hate
and how grudging you are in your heart.
If you didn't have delusions,
I wouldn't be here.
Our death
can bring her eternal peace.
I have no regrets.
Lord Changheng
guards Yujing and protects the living.
Goddess Xi Yun
cultivates all creatures with grace.
The two of them are a match made in heaven
who are bound for a marriage that lasts forever.
Heaven and Earth are the witnesses
of their vows.
All the gods felicitate them upon
the completed ceremony.
No, no.
You must still have a weakness.
It is a delusion to change the fate.
Dongfang Qingcang.
Do you really understand?
Do you really know
what price you have to pay?
I am an ancient evil god who is immortal and indestructible.
If you want to completely destroy me,
it's not enough to burn my primordial spirit.
I'm afraid of nothing.
Is that so?
Then your existence will be completely erased by the heaven's rules,
just like
you've never existed in the three realms.
Tai Sui.
These are
your fears,
not mine.
I have let go of everything.
There is nothing in this world
that can shake me.
But Xi Yun wouldn't remember
all that you've given to her.
All the happiness
and pain you have experienced.
Even the fight against fate.
However strong the love is,
she will forget it.
She will truly forget you forever.
Aren't you afraid of
all this?
I see.
So what?
Dongfang Qingcang.
This moment of your wavering
it'll be enough.
Tai Sui has regained the immortal body.
He is in Spirit-Shattering Abyss.
Why would this happen?
Yeah, what's going on?
Dongfang Qingcang.
He is not Dongfang Qingcang.
He is Evil God Tai Sui.
No way.
He has a strong mind.
How could he possibly be controlled by Tai Sui?
That's impossible.
What Chidi said
is true.
When the ancient gods and Goddesses Wu Qi
joined forces to seal Tai Sui, the evil and killing,
violent and evil spirits in the ancient barbaric era
were also suppressed under Xishan.
If he lifts the seal
and releases them all,
the people of the three realms
will be flooded with calamities,
and back to the barbaric wilderness
All immortals,
let's work together to suppress it.
Let me go.
Orchid.
Come back.
Orchid, come back!
The Evil God Tai Sui has taken over Dongfang Qingcang's immortal body
and is soon going to restore the power.
Orchid has just transformed into a human.
She hasn't fully recovered the power of the Goddess.
There is no chance of victory for her.
It's too dangerous.
Goddess.
Come back now!
Now that this has happened,
we can only try our best
to hold down the seal
and buy her time.
We Moon Tribe soldiers
come to help Shuiyuntian
to kill the Evil God Tai Sui
by the order of the Moon Supreme Dongfang Qingcang.
Your Highness Xunfeng.
Do we really have to fight against My Lord
My Lord
for Shuiyuntian?
Surely not.
This is not for the sake of someone.
This is for the three realms.
I will never
make past mistakes ever.
Orchid, stop!
It's useless for you to go there now.
You are no match for Tai Sui.
Dongfang Qingcang…
He is no longer in this world.
Orchid
has awakened the supreme divine power in her bloodline.
This is Hellfire.
Brother has regained consciousness
and his Hellfire too.
No.
This is not Hellfire.
This is glazed fire.
Glazed Fire?
It is the fire of compassion that has been lost since ancient times.
The person needs to be tempered by emotions and sufferings
and still keep the original heart.
Only those who have great love and compassion
can harness it.
I never thought
people from Moon Tribe can master the glazed fire.
Dongfang Qingcang.
Orchid.
Kill me.
Now that I am one with the primordial spirit of Tai Sui,
you can kill Tai Sui if you kill me.
Hurry!
I can't hold out much longer.
No way.
I can't do it.
That's right.
You can't do it.
You can't do it,
Xi Yun.
I know
you love him
more than your own life.
Tai Sui.
Your enemy is me.
Let him go!
Orchid.
Look at me.
Kill me.
No!
I don't want to!
If I don't die,
Tai Sui will continue to plague the three realms.
Then everything you've done will go in vain.
It's my destiny to save the world,
not yours.
But it's my mission
to save you.
Hurry!
I can't hold on anymore.
Xi Yun.
How can you kill Dongfang Qingcang with your own hands?
You can't do it.
Orchid.
I can't hold on anymore.
I beg you.
Hurry!
♫ Who exchanged the rest of their life for tonight's infatuation dream? ♫
♫ Only kept the emotion from the first encounter ♫
♫ Humans, one glance, one word, everything goes with the wind ♫
♫ Want to ask why do you still feel so heartbroken ♫
♫ Sing the lovers' song quietly ♫
♫ Brewing orchid fragrance ♫
♫ Who will cross the Memory Loss River to engrave love in their heart? ♫
♫ How unforgettable a lovers' dream is ♫
♫ Will ultimately get hurt when one wakes up from the dream ♫
Little flower spirit.
♫ This love is marked as a crazy love ♫
I said I would change your fate for you.
♫ Why is it hard for us to escape these changes? ♫
I did it.
♫ Let's embrace each other, even if we are destined to be separated by one's death ♫
♫ Your soul flows with my tears ♫
Wooden Head.
No.
♫ Reflecting the appearance of a deep love ♫
Wooden Head.
♫ Several times of obsessive entanglement and then forgetting them ♫
No.
♫ May the palm lines be entangled with the rest of your life ♫
♫ Sing the lovers' song quietly ♫
♫ Brewing orchid fragrance ♫
♫ Who will cross the Memory Loss River to engrave love in their heart? ♫
Don't go.
No.
♫ How unforgettable a lovers' dream is ♫
Dongfang Qingcang.
♫ Will ultimately get hurt when one wakes up from the dream ♫
♫ This love is marked as a crazy love ♫
♫ Why is it hard for us to escape these changes? ♫
♫ Let's embrace each other, even if we are destined to be separated by one's death ♫
♫ Ha ah. Ah ♫
♫ Unknowingly, silently ♫
♫ I know you are still in my heart ♫
Come and take a look.
[Wedding Dress made by Yang]
Will my brother
come back?
He took everything on
for me
and his life can't be brought back.
Xunfeng.
Do you believe in a wonder?
I don't know.
Everything in this world
happens so fast
except for love.
[500 years later]
The hatred and war between immortals and the Moon Tribe
have lasted for tens of thousands of years,
causing many deaths.
But
one of the most magical and power forces
in the three realms
finally changed all this.
That is love.
It makes everyone
a better version of himself.
For the most cautious and restrained people,
love can set them free
and help them find the true desire.
My name is
Xiao Run.
You can call me Mr. Xiao.
Mr. Xiao.
Yesterday, you said
the bad Evil God Tai Sui had come.
What happened after that?
Yeah, what happened after that?
After that…
Run.
For the most unruly and capricious people,
Love
can make them strong, open-minded
and broad-minded.
Join the army for training?
Have you really thought about it?
I've always admired the late God of War.
When I was young, I always thought
I would become the God of War in Shuiyuntian
and protect the lives in three realms too.
But later
I indulged in selfish delusions for a while.
Not only did it cause you trouble,
I also forgot my original intention.
No.
You're a good person.
I just can't respond to you.
It's all in the past.
You treat me like a good friend.
I also consider you my buddy in life.
Your buddy in life?
Let me ask you.
Are Xiao Run and Qu Shui
buddies?
Of course they are.
Are Lord Changheng and the Moon Supreme Dongfang Qingcang
confidants?
Of course they are.
Since this kind of affection
can go beyond status,
and racial difference,
why can't it
break gender gap?
Fairy Danyin is right.
What about you?
You really
will no longer be the God of War?
Now that the three realms are at peace,
I just want to travel around the world
as a loose immortal.
The position of God of War is now vacant.
I'm expecting you to
come and get it.
Don't worry.
It won't take long.
For the most narrow-minded and jealous people,
love makes them grow
to be tolerant
and responsible.
I see.
Do it this way.
Thank you for your hard work.
Yes, my lord.
Your Highness Xunfeng has become more and more sophisticated.
You look quite like the previous Moon Supreme.
I've been holding the position
for my brother for 500 years.
I wonder
when he'll come back.
If he really can't come back,
you and I will have to
take on the responsibility
to protect all of this,
so that the Moon Tribe
can remain peaceful
and prosperous.
For the most deceitful person,
Love
makes her sincere and reliable.
Have you learnt the lesson?
I see.
I'll never lie again.
Be careful.
Good girl.
You're not orphans anymore.
From now on,
I'll take care of you.
So don't lie and cheat anymore.
You have to be a decent person from now on.
Got it?
Aunt Jieli.
Were you also an honest child when you were a child?
When I was a child…
I used to misbehave
and make mistakes too.
But now I'm all right.
I'm honest and upright.
And I don't lie.
Aunt Jieli is right.
You should
listen to her from now on.
Where did you go?
Bad Black Dragon.
Did you go drinking again?
I didn't.
You didn't?
You've been drinking.
You must have been drinking.
-I didn't. -You must have been drinking.
You did.
You just don't admit it.
Bad Black Dragon.
For someone who makes a momentary mistake
and goes astray,
love can hold him
before he finally falls into the abyss
and make him come to his senses.
Look. It's a cloud whale.
Love
can make a heartless person
understand compassion and love
♫ Fall in love with your clear eyes ♫
and even give up everything for the one he loves,
♫ It's the most unforgettable scenery along the way ♫
including his own
his life.
♫ No one can ever replace what we've been through ♫
♫ It's as bright as the stars ♫
♫ Every decision I make for you ♫
♫ The story goes on and on ♫
♫ Stories in the past play in my head ♫
♫ I will remember it to the end of my life ♫
♫ Don't think, don't miss, don't listen to it ♫
♫ No more ripples in my heart ♫
♫ The sky lights up, be together and apart ♫
♫ People come and go, it always changes ♫
♫ Tramp over hill and dale to search for you ♫
♫ Act worthily of this life and our encounter ♫
♫ Act worthily of my trip to a sea of woes ♫
♫ Only in order to save you ♫
♫ Blaze a way through brambles and thorns to search for you ♫
♫ Make light of traveling from afar for days with you ♫
♫ People come and go, it always changes ♫
I'm back.
♫ Tramp over hill and dale to search for you ♫
♫ Act worthily of this life and our encounter ♫
♫ Act worthily of my trip to a sea of woes ♫
♫ Only in order to save you ♫
♫ Blaze a way through brambles and thorns to search for you ♫
♫ Make light of traveling from afar for days with you ♫
♫ I will never betray you even if I betray the world ♫
[Love Between Fairy and Devil]