[English subtitles are available]
[Love Between Fairy and Devil]
[Episode 18]
Qingcang.
You've always used me as a tool
to revive the Moon Tribe!
You made me suffer the lost of my emotions and my ability to love!
You made me bear the name of killing my own father!
You made me a monster that everyone avoids!
Have you ever felt heartbroken for me?
Or have you ever found it unbearable to see me suffer?
Qingcang,
you were young, strong,
and talented.
I believed
you can master the Hellfire.
You
are the hope
of the survival of the Moon Tribe.
This again.
I'm sick of it.
Let me ask you now.
If you could turn back time,
would you make a different choice?
Say something!
If I could turn back time,
I would make the same decision.
I knew it.
No matter what,
it's my duty to revive the Moon Tribe.
But you are...
a father who is worse than a beast.
That's why you have a son
who is worse than a beast.
Son.
At that time,
I had no choice.
I really had no choice.
You don't have to look so hypocritical!
Aren't you always fierce, strict,
and firm?
Why are you saying this now?
My Lord,
Chidi Woman led the immortal army and attacked us.
We lost the south of
Silver Lake.
My Lord,
the north has fallen.
Eight thousand soldiers
were wiped out.
Father,
you promised me
that you'll play football with me.
After all,
you still treated me as a sharp blade without emotions.
You used me as a tool to resist the Fairy Realm.
I couldn't bear to see you suffer.
How dare you say that!
You're even cruel now!
You couldn't bear to see me suffer?
You should have killed me.
Back then,
you should have killed me!
But what did you do?
You made me suffer a lot.
I'd rather die.
I couldn't bear to see you suffer.
That's why I chose for you to kill me.
Have you considered my feelings?
I don't have time to listen
to a dying soul now.
Wait.
The First Moon Supreme,
what do you mean by letting him kill you?
I read the secret book.
It didn't state
that only by killing your loved one
can you completely destroy the seven emotions.
That's because
emotions are hard to destroy.
Every time he comes back to life,
it takes a thousand years to remove them completely again.
Besides the secret technique,
if you can kill your loved one,
your emotions can be completely destroyed
in that moment.
So,
you chose to let him
kill you.
It's worth sacrificing my life.
Qingcang,
your emotional root has recovered.
That's why you're in so much pain.
Let me ask you.
Are you going to be
the invincible Moon Supreme
and bring the Moon Tribe back to glory?
Or
you want all of your previous sufferings
to be in vain?
If you continue to indulge in your emotions and love,
you will be in pain.
You can't escape from it.
Qingcang,
pull out your Hellfire sword
and shatter my soul!
Then you can get rid of your emotional root.
Hurry up!
I can't do it.
You can do it.
Qingcang, have you forgotten?
You did it once before.
You can do it again.
My boy.
If you don't get rid of your emotional root,
you will be trapped in pain forever.
Do you understand?
Are you willing to bear
the pain of killing your own father?
Come!
Recently,
I kept thinking during the day and
dreaming at night.
They were the happy moments of us
practicing sword fighting and playing football.
So this time, I have to make my own decision.
I'd rather bear the pain of killing my own father
and bear the pain caused by emotions and love.
I don't want to forget these feelings.
Come.
Qingcang.
Wooden Head,
what are you thinking?
Kick it.
Wooden Head,
if you miss this chance,
you won't have another one.
Kick it.
Father.
How many lightning strikes are left?
My Lord,
30 lightnings were struck just now for the
punishment of 81 lightning strikes.
There are 51 strikes left.
I'll take
the rest for him.
My Lord,
this...
My Lord, your body is precious.
How can you take the punishment?
Dongfang Qingcang,
what tricks are you playing?
Execute it.
♫ Waiting for the moment when the sky collapses and the ground cracks ♫
♫ When it collapses and shatters, open eyes ♫
Do you want me to say it again?
♫ There is nowhere to put the soul but only to land ♫
Execute it.
♫ If our souls get to know each other in the world ♫
♫ Watching the vows come and go ♫
♫ I can't bear the world without you ♫
♫ The last of love ♫
♫ The tenderness of fingers tangled ♫
♫ Turned into a sharp sword and stabbed at me ♫
♫ Farewell Love ♫
♫ Blurs time and distance ♫
♫ Even time is suspended ♫
♫ All because of you ♫
♫ Make sure you are the only one in my heart ♫
♫ It's too late to say goodbye ♫
♫ I can't speak the regret ♫
♫ Too late ♫
The punishment of 81 lightning strikes is completed.
Dongfang Qingcang!
My Lord!
Wooden Head, are you alright?
♫ If our souls get to know each other in the world ♫
Dongfang Qingcang.
♫ Watching the vows come and go ♫
Don't think I'll thank you
♫ I can't bear the world without you ♫
for your pretentious act.
Even in death, I will get my
♫ The last of love ♫
revenge for father.
Your Highness Xunfeng.
♫ The tenderness of fingers tangled ♫
As his brother,
♫ Turned into a sharp sword and stabbed at me ♫
do you really know his pain?
Do you know the truth between them?
♫ Farewell Love ♫
You only cared about yourself.
♫ Blurs time and distance ♫
You know nothing.
♫ Even time is suspended ♫
♫ All because of you ♫
See for yourself.
♫ Make sure you are the only one in my heart ♫
♫ It's too late to say goodbye ♫
♫ I can't speak the regret ♫
♫ Too late ♫
It has been so long.
Why is he not up yet?
♫ Too late ♫
Lightning strikes are strong.
Even the Lord can't take it.
Although his life is not in danger,
it will take some time
to recuperate.
♫ Farewell Love ♫
You're awake.
Where are you going?
I'm not going anywhere.
Your medicine is almost ready.
I need to keep an eye on the fire.
The medicine is...
Moon Supreme Lord?
Are you
willing to bear the pain of killing your own father?
Recently,
I kept thinking during the day and
dreaming at night.
They were the happy moments of us
practicing sword fighting and playing football.
So this time, I have to make my own decision.
I'd rather bear the pain of killing my own father
and bear the pain caused by emotions and love.
I don't want to forget these feelings.
In the past, when it's my father's death anniversary,
I don't feel anything.
Now
when I think that today is his death anniversary...
When I think that...
I'll never see him again...
If I destroy the Love Tree,
would the suffering end?
Would the suffering end?
I don't blame him.
I don't blame him anymore.
Time to take your medicine.
Why do I have to take the medicine again?
It's bitter.
How can I take it?
How can you recover without taking medicine?
Because you didn't want to take the medicine,
you haven't recovered for days.
The wounds are getting more and more painful.
I have to hold you for you to walk.
Take it.
Take it in one go. You won't taste the bitterness.
If you take it,
I can make your favorite fresh flower cakes for you.
Assorted flavors
with honey.
What do you mean by letting him kill you?
I read the secret book.
It didn't state
that only by killing your loved one
can you completely destroy the seven emotions.
If you can kill your loved one,
your emotions can be completely destroyed
in that moment.
Once you're done,
get up and walk more.
The doctor said
you have to be able to walk freely
for your wounds to be
considered better.
No.
It still hurts.
I need your help.
My Lord, His Highness Xunfeng wants to see you.
What is he doing here?
Forget it. Let him in.
Brother.
How is your injury?
It's just the punishment of lightning strikes.
I'm fine after some sleep.
What about you?
What brings you here?
It's to
tell you the truth about Haishi City.
30,000 years ago,
the news of you being killed by the Fairy Realm
spread to Cangyan Sea.
Southern and Northern Youxian County had a mutiny one after the other.
They intended to take over the Ninth Youxian County.
When I was extremely anxious,
a mysterious man came to me.
The Lord of Haishi City?
I don't know who he is and
where is he from.
But he told me,
as long as I can help him build Haishi City,
he can help me control the Kings of Southern and Northern Youxian County.
He never takes off his mask
and shows his real face.
So at first, I didn't trust him.
But...
But both kings were pressing.
So you accepted any help that came your way.
You even put the fate of the Ninth Youxian County
in the hands of an unknown person.
Go on.
Did you see his face after that?
No.
Not asking for his identity was
one of his conditions for helping me.
30,000 years ago,
at this timing.
Is the Lord of Haishi City
also involved in the Great War?
Since you told me previously that
the Lord of Haishi City secretly used the primordial spirit of the dead of the Moon Tribe
to make evil spirits,
I recalled
what happened in the past 30,000 years carefully and
noticed something.
Every time when I'm close to losing the war,
he always helped me to turn the tide.
Every time I had the upper hand,
the Southern and Northern Youxian County
always got away safely.
The Lord of Haishi City's planning
is like...
Always letting you fight against each other
without getting a definite result.
The three kings of Cangyan Sea engaged in
civil unrest that lasted for tens of thousands of years.
This caused the power of the Moon Tribe to perish for no reason.
I'm so stupid.
I feel guilty towards my people.
I deserve to die.
You shouldn't have pardoned me the day before yesterday.
I didn't pardon you.
From now on,
you have to win on the battlefield
to correct your mistake.
Yes.
You may leave.
What?
Are there any details missing?
No.
In that case,
you may leave now.
Yes.
Wooden Head,
are you still holding a grudge against His Highness Xunfeng
for wanting
to kill you?
There are tens of thousands of people in the three realms
who want to kill me.
He's not even on the list.
It's such a trivial matter.
Since he has admitted his mistake,
I don't blame him.
Why do you ask?
Just now,
didn't you see
his desire to speak?
He wanted to tell you something,
but he's afraid to bring up what happened in the past
and upset you.
Did he really misunderstand?
You finally made up after so long.
I think
next time you see him,
don't always
act like the almighty Moon Supreme
and scold him.
If it was me,
I would be scared too.
You need to do something intimate.
This way, he will know
that you've forgiven him.
Something intimate?
You don't want to?
I don't know how.
People only taught me how to become stronger,
how to kill,
and how to conquer the world.
But no one has ever taught me
how to get close to others.
This is very simple.
Let me teach you.
Next time you see him,
don't pull a long face.
You need to smile.
Come on, smile for me.
Can you smile more naturally?
Look.
This is a good angle.
Is this enough?
No.
You are brothers.
Next time you see him,
you need to be more friendly.
How?
Let me think.
I got it.
Next time you see him,
you can hug him.
How?
Like this....
Hug him like this
or pat his shoulder.
Next time you see him,
you'll do it, right?
No.
Why?
It's cheesy.
How is this cheesy?
What are you thinking?
Why are you smiling so happily?
Jieli,
have you ever noticed that
sometimes
the Moon Supreme Lord is quite cute?
Cute?
Are you alright?
How can the Moon Supreme be linked to cuteness?
You didn't see it.
When he was learning how to smile at people,
he was silly and cute.
He'll do whatever you tell him to do.
He is very serious.
Orchid, Orchid.
You're really something.
I thought I was a good liar.
You don't show it normally.
But I didn't expect you
to be so good
at acting.
First, you risked your life
to find the first Moon Supreme's primordial spirit at the bottom of Memory Loss River.
Then, you even boiled medicine and made pastries for him every day.
Whenever you talk about him,
you smile and glow.
If I hadn't known you were acting,
I would have been like the Moon Supreme
and think you've
betrayed Shuiyuntian for him.
Are you
not acting?
You mean it?
No way.
Of course I was acting.
Good acting, right?
My Lord, Lord Xunfeng wants to see you.
Is what you said
true?
The seal that holds 100,000 soldiers
at Xuanxu Realm for 30,000 years
can be broken?
Yes.
The next reincarnation of Chidi Woman who'll be experiencing hardships
is called Xie Wanqing.
When she is born,
I want you to go to Yunmeng Lake immediately
and take her to Xuanxu Realm.
Place her primordial spirit into Shuofeng sword.
It can break the seal,
and you can bring back 100,000 soldiers.
I'll set out immediately.
Wait!
What else can I do for you?
You're still injured.
You must be careful.
Yes.
So he didn't hug him.
He was shy.
For him,
it's a massive improvement.
Shangque,
your Lord has feelings now.
He knows forgiveness, kindness, and mercy.
That's great.
What's wrong with you two?
Are you unhappy?
Not really.
The Lord and His Highness Xunfeng made up.
They are working together.
Of course I'm happy.
But,
if the Lord really changed
as you said,
is he still the Moon Supreme?
Why not?
Since ancient times,
the Fairies and the Moon Tribe have been enemies.
Yannv, our first ancestor, once passed an ancestral teaching.
Only a tough general who
never gives up on hatred
is the key of the survival of the Moon Tribe.
Why must there be hatred?
Whether it's the Moon Tribe or the Fairies,
there are good people.
Let's not talk about Shuiyuntian.
Anyway,
the Lord will destroy the Fairy Realm
to avenge the Moon Tribe.
I believe he won't give up.
That's because you didn't see how
he was with the first Moon Supreme.
He's different now.
He's no longer the Dongfang Qingcang we know.
Jieli,
what's with that look?
My Lord.
Are my fresh flower cakes ready?
Have you taken your medicine?
The medicine is too bitter.
But I've finished it.
Not a drop left.
The fresh flower cakes are almost ready.
I'll get them.
Wait.
What is this?
According to the Moon Tribe's rules,
if you want to thank someone,
you have to use your blood
and apply it on that person's face.
Thank you very much.
No, this is your blood.
I guessed you may not like blood,
so I changed it to cinnabar.
Can I not apply it?
No.
This is the first time I've ever thanked a person.
Don't refuse me.
[Love Between Fairy and Devil]