- She gave it to us just now.
- That's not it.
Are you serious?
Don't flip the meat here. I'll do it.
If she was alive, would she be about that age?
Hye Ri, I mean.
My younger sister, Hye Ri.
You know...
family members with adult missing persons
often get ignored even though they report them.
Because they're adults,
they get reported as runaways at times.
But you know...
even if they're adults, they might not have run away.
They could have been kidnapped
or gotten into an accident.
But if there's no clear indication,
they first assume they ran away.
Do you know how that feels for the people left behind?
You fret in torment,
a little every day.
It becomes agonizing.
So my heart...
broods so much that it's agonizing.
I fear...
that she might be dead.
Welcome.
What? "Dead"?
What are you saying?
I'm not drunk.
Hey, Ju Eun Ho.
Hye...
Hey, Jung Hyun Oh!
- Hi.
- What?
What? What are you doing here?
I'm here for the triple-broadcast integration campaign meeting.
That campaign? Our team planned that.
Sunbae, is Ju Eun Ho there?
She's an announcer from our Group 28.
No, it's just you so far.
Hey, you're going to Culture and Education, right? This way.
Okay.
You're not Hye Ri. You're Eun Ho.
Why did you kiss me?
An announcer who has my exact face...
I keep thinking of Ju Hye Ri.
Are you happier now?
Doctor.
Isn't it strange?
Now that I'm in love, everything looks shiny.
Are you awake?
Where is...
The nurse's office.
Why am I here?
- Do you not know?
- No.
I definitely went home last night.
And now I'm here.
You saw me earlier.
No way. I don't even remember coming to work.
Then you ran away.
No way!
Why would I run away from you, Ju Yeon?
Then you went to the restroom and broke a mirror.
Who did? I did?
Then you passed out.
But why?
I don't know. Don't you recall?
No, I don't.
I see that losing your memory
is quite convenient.
Then...
will I get arrested now?
The mirror cost 302,000 won (226 USD).
Are restroom mirrors that expensive?
That's what I asked.
One above-the-sink mirror costs 50,000 won, and 100,000 won with installation.
But there are two sinks. They need to custom order matching mirrors.
The total is 302,000 won.
Then why did I...
break the mirror?
I don't know.
Why didn't you ask yourself in the broken mirror?
I paid for it.
I'll repay you
tomorrow.
But...
why did you do it?
Why did you run away when you saw me?
I told you I want to know, too.
Are you hurt?
It's about time you asked. Are you a "T"?
What's a "T"?
In MBTI (Myers–Briggs Type Indicator), a "T" (Thinking)!
Are you a "T"? You're a "T"?
Why can't you empathize?
How can I empathize with someone who broke a restroom mirror for no reason?
Well...
I've never seen happiness with my own eyes...
Are you really not hurt anywhere?
however, if I could see it,
if I could touch it,
maybe it feels like this.
Ju Yeon.
Yes?
I think I wrecked my knee.
I don't think so.
The restroom mirror is wrecked.
- What?
- Doctor, now that I'm in love, everything looks shiny.
I've never seen happiness with my own eyes;
however, if I could see it,
- if I could touch it—
- No.
Before that, you broke a mirror.
Yes, Doctor. Why did I do that? I don't understand.
Do you remember breaking it?
For example, what were you feeling?
No, I don't remember anything like that.
Then, Hye Ri...
Yes, Doctor. I'm Hye Ri.
Yes, Hye Ri.
As I said, we must first figure out the connection between Eun Ho and Hye Ri.
But, Doctor.
Yes, go ahead.
After we figure it out,
what happens after that?
These symptoms will improve.
"These symptoms will improve"?
Then...
what happens to me, Ju Hye Ri?
- As for that...
- Do I disappear?
Do I go away?
It might be hard to understand for the present Hye Ri,
but Hye Ri and Eun Ho are the same person.
So when your symptoms improve, you will be one again.
You will be both Hye Ri and Eun Ho.
No, Doctor. I'm Hye Ri.
I'm not Eun Ho; I'm Hye Ri.
No matter how much I think about it, I've always been Hye Ri.
When I open my eyes, I've always been Hye Ri.
I see Eun Ho only when I close my eyes.
Eun Ho has existed only in my dreams.
But I don't even have those dreams anymore.
Now...
I dream about myself.
My days aren't boring anymore.
I look forward to the next day.
Not Eun Ho from my dreams,
but who I am in the present,
I'm curious about what tomorrow will bring.
I have hope
because...
I'm in love.
Doctor, I'm happy now.
But you want me to abandon myself when I'm happy?
No.
I don't want to abandon Hye Ri.
At least, in the present, I'm much happier
than Eun Ho from my dreams.
I'm so, so much happier than anyone else.
I'm happy. I'm happy, because I'm Ju Hye Ri.
I'm happy. I said I'm happy, so happy; I can't even explain.
So, so, so happy.
I'm happy, happy, happier than anyone else.
I said I'm happy. I'm happy.
Happy, happy, happy.
I'm happy. Happy, happy, I'm happy.
I'm so happy.
I can't let Ju Eun Ho take this body.
Hey.
Why aren't you picking up your phone? Kim Mi Yeon called multiple times.
I lost it.
- If you lost your phone–
- I'll go get a new one today.
Are you going to the workshop or not?
"Workshop"? I haven't heard of it.
I'm telling you now. It's Saturday. Will you go?
What? I'm not going. It's Saturday.
Also, you...
Hey.
Why are you looking at me like that? You're ruining my mood.
You were at Media N Seoul a few days ago, right? I think I saw you.
What are you talking about? I'm a PPS announcer.
Don't just say no. You've done this before.
- You saw me and said you didn't–
- I really don't know or I wouldn't say that.
Are you sick?
Yes. I'm sick.
Because of this company, world, and unfair system
that doesn't recognize a talent like me, I'm very sick!
So you're not going, right? Bye.
Great work!
- Announcer Ju Eun Ho, you aren't going to the workshop, right?
- No, I'm not going.
Then, Sunbae, let's get your lines before we leave.
I'll do it there.
No, I'm not going to work there. I'm going to drink.
You got drunk and had to write an incident report.
Do you still want to drink there?
It's a workshop. What's a workshop? It's a bonding session.
You're the only person who works there. So let's split up the lines then go.
- Could you get the script from the writer?
- Yes.
It's okay, it's okay.
Mi Yeon. I'll do it there. Bye.
Sunbae!
That little... Geez!
Excuse me.
Does Jung Hyun Oh split our lines?
It's always been that way.
You know how fussy he gets.
He throws a fit if he has too many lines or if he has too few.
So we air our show only after checking everything in the script with him.
So by chance, if you think your lines are few, don't look for me.
Look for that guy...
My bruised ego.
Here you go. You can use it right away.
Thank you.
The call is not going through. You'll be connected to the voicemail after the beep.
That's the end of today's news. Thank you for watching.
Great work. Thank you. Thank you.
The call is not going through. After the beep...
Sunbae!
Hey, Baek Hye Yeon.
How many times have I asked you out to dinner?
Are you finally gracing us with your presence?
I don't know about that.
Baek Hye Yeon, it's time for you to be a main announcer.
Don't you think?
That sounds good to me.
Maybe it's because you're from a rich family.
You have such a straightforward personality.
Regardless of her family wealth, she was born with a frank personality.
What about you, Kang Ju Yeon?
Are you doing okay with the news?
Yes, it's doable.
Even though you're a replacement, you're so good.
So I've been wanting to buy you dinner.
He's good, right?
Exactly.
I said you could permanently be 8 o'clock news anchor. Why did you turn it down?
I don't think I have the capacity or experience to take that on.
Well, that's something you can continue to consider.
Baek Hye Yeon.
Are you seeing anyone?
No, not yet.
Why not? I'm sure many people are pursuing you.
Why aren't you hooking up?
We all rot when we die!
- Enjoy yourself when you're young.
- That's enough.
Press Director.
What did you say, Scoundrel?
Wow, is he out of his mind?
For real? Why bring you two out and start cussing?
And why did he throw water on you?
I know. I'm really fine.
Ju Yeon, are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
Sunbae, I'm really sorry. Because of me...
Hye Yeon, why are you sorry?
What did that crazy guy say to you?
Wh-What did he say?
I'm so furious I can't even remember.
I'm really fine, Department Head.
He's like that. He's infamous for it!
But, Sunbae, all due to me...
- It's okay.
- Wait.
- Don't we need to report this?
- I really don't care! Really!
Hye Yeon, how many times has this happened to you?
Gosh, come on, chill out, Department Head.
Sunbae, I'm sorry.
Hye Yeon.
Go!
Don't think about me!
Hye Yeon, are you sure you're okay?
I'm fine! Bye!
Darn it.
Is it good?
Yes, it's good.
The name of the udon is so funny.
"Tight Tight, Chewy Chewy Udon."
Wow. They even have "Sticky Sticky Conch."
Let's try that next time.
Sure.
Ju Yeon, didn't you eat already?
Are you just sitting here for me?
It makes me happy just to see you eat.
I don't think so. You look like you're in a bad mood.
Me?
No, I'm not angry.
No?
Your eyes look angry. They're fired up.
Do my eyes look different when I'm angry?
Yes, they do.
When you get angry, your eyes
are so calm
and gently twisted.
What?
So why are you angry, Ju Yeon?
Did something happen?
Is your mother sick?
Did someone cry in front of you?
Well...
I mean...
Hey, this is Yoon Jong Hyun.
No, I just heard this morning.
He's sick!
How could he be sick suddenly?
He just has to drive.
I had to drive myself.
I'm the newsroom press director.
How could I drive my own car?
Then attendants told me to park my car.
How dare they?
I'll tell the facilities department to fire them all!
Darn it. What?
So many fools are acting up these days.
My company doesn't own the parking lot.
I know. That's why.
Really?
Got it. See you later.
What? Ring my amount.
­
What is this?
Why do you stare at me like that?
Hurry up! Ring this up.
What the...
Why are you screaming?
Poke what? I didn't poke you.
I just handed you the parking validation ticket.
Is that so?
No, he poked her chest with the parking validation ticket. Like this.
I know. I didn't even have pockets.
I held it out, and you didn't take it! I gave it to you so you could take it!
You should have just handed it to me. Why poke my chest?
I feel so violated.
Poking her chest is clearly sexual harassment.
What? She didn't take my ticket! How was I supposed to hand it to her?
Tie it to a string? Put it in a pigeon's mouth?
You could have just handed it to her. Just like this.
I just don't remember! I...
- didn't poke her!
- Criminals always say they don't remember.
What? "Criminal"?
Hey, who are you to make me into a criminal?
She's saying it's possible.
If she didn't give consent, and you made her feel violated or sexually humiliated,
that constitutes sexual harassment.
- Are you serious?
- And I'm sorry, but we are not Media N Seoul.
You might run the newsroom over there, but you're just an ahjussi passing by here.
Please speak formally to us.
- What did you say, Bastard?
- That word, "Bastard,"
refers to the offspring of an animal.
So save it for your children.
What!
I didn't do it!
So dirty,
terribly loud.
I'm sorry.
I was wrong.
I said, "I'm sorry"!
Excuse me.
Yes?
I have a question.
Did Press Director Yoon Jong Hyun truly sexually harass you?
He poked my chest with a parking validation ticket, twice.
It was so degrading.
Wow, why did he do that?
What?
Isn't he usually like that?
That guy never messes with people who might talk later.
I see. Does he harass only people who keep their mouths shut?
Yes.
- Because in this field–
- Whistle blowing is worse than sexual harassment?
What?
You seem to know something. You're too smart.
Well, these are just basics.
But no matter how careful those people are,
their true colors come out someday.
But...  I have one more question.
Anything.
- Are you dating Kang Ju Yeon?
- Oh...
How did you know?
Wow!
Must be nice.
Right. It is nice.
It's so nice.
Then can I ask one last question before I go?
- Go ahead.
- When are you off work?
There's a place I know.
Their conch is the stickiest.
I can't tell if it's gum or conch.
Wow, this conch is crazy. So sticky!
I've been craving it since the last time I was here.
It tastes perfect.
It's like a piece of gum, right?
Sunbae, over here!
Over here!
Here, here!
­
How come you two are together?
I asked Hye Ri out on a date.
She seems an intriguing person.
Sunbae, do you want anything to eat?
No, I'm fine.
Sunbae, did you hear?
Yoon Jong Hyun apologized to Hye Ri.
He said he would do anything she asked.
So Hye Ri asked him to make her look younger.
- What?
- He said he'd do anything if I didn't tell the police.
I kept thinking of you telling me I look old.
So I asked him to make me look younger, and he sighed.
That made me feel worse.
So how...
Oh, hello.
Yes.
I'll be right there.
Okay.
Sorry. I have to go.
I have to head out. I'm sorry.
- What?
- Where?
He's like that.
Don't worry about it.
Excuse me.
Hye Ri.
Yes?
Could you...
Could you go somewhere with me?
Where?
Where did you—
Give me back my wallet!
"Give me back my wallet," I said!
Give it to me!
- Give it! Give it!
- I'll find it for you!
I said to give it!
Give it to me! My wallet!
My wallet...
- Give me back my wallet!
- Ahjumma, stop!
- Okay, okay.
- You arrived.
My wallet!
Se Yeon, you arrived.
Mom.
It's Ju Yeon.
Ju Yeon...
You can go. I'll stay.
Okay.
Ju Yeon.
Want to come here?
Come over here, my Se Yeon.
Can I come in?
Hye Ri.
- Who...
- Hello. I'm Ju Yeon's...
girlfriend.
You look like a cute rabbit.
I've never heard that before.
When did you get a girlfriend, Se Yeon?
Ahjumma, can I hold your hand?
You're already holding it.
Your hands are so thin.
Are you eating?
You're so thin.
I... can't really swallow.
But Koreans live on rice.
Ahjumma, you need to make sure to eat.
Then will I become pretty like you?
No.
You'll stay alive.
Staying alive is a good thing, Ahjumma.
Is it?
Of course.
It's a really, really good thing.
So be thankful
that you're alive
and that Ju Yeon is alive.
Does my Ju Yeon
treat you well?
Yes.
Ju Yeon is so warmhearted,
as warm as your hands.
Is that so?
It's a good thing to be warm because that means...
That means you're alive?
That's right.
You're smart.
I thought life was so boring.
But in my tedious days,
you arrived, Hye Ri.
Is that why you fell for me?
Thank you for the ring.
I think it's so pretty.
I didn't give it to you, though.
Your mom did. That's why I'm even more thankful.
Did you push back my hair since I look so pretty right now?
No. I thought you might have a hard time seeing.
Wow.
The sky is so clear tonight.
Yes.
It's clear.
What does that mean?
Everyone's here, right? Let's leave now! Yes?
- I thought she wasn't coming.
- What?
I said, "I thought she wasn't coming."
But she did.
Right. I ended up coming.
I'm so sorry.
No need to be sorry.
There are many lines after this news item.
This is the main item of the day.
But, Deputy, if you take this one, you already–
In my opinion, I think I should do it
because you said the line is long.
I'm good at memorizing. I should do it, no?
Let's keep going.
I'll do it up to here.
From here to here...
- Oh, my gosh!
- Shouldn't I take over from here?
Why are you in this car? I thought you were in the other car.
I just wanted to lie down. I didn't realize it was this car.
Excuse me, where are we going?
I just came along without even knowing that.
I'm so busy. There's so much on my mind.
This is...
Up to here.
Wow!
It's so pretty here.
We should go for a walk later.
We can get footage if we see anything.
Sounds good.
A walk at night? No way.
Hello.
Why can't we take a walk at night?
So many people have died in the forest at night.
No way.
Why would they die on a walk?
Are there animals?
No.
The forest is so dense that they get lost and die.
- "Lost"?
- Lose the way.
The way.
Why would we get lost? The map apps work so well these days. That's nonsense.
You're just trying to scare us.
You won't get a phone signal in there.
So if you get lost, you're in trouble.
You'll wander all night and freeze to death.
In this weather? It's so warm these days.
The woods are cold, even in summer.
How will you survive the cold night?
I'm sure some people still go in.
That's for sure.
Too many ignored my warning and went in.
Then they never return from that forest.
Did that...
happen to many people?
Well, one or two people.
College students, especially.
When they get drunk and go in there, they can't come out.
The woods are just like the ocean.
If you go in the middle of the night, you can never leave.
If you're going in, go now.
Darn it.
After hearing that, I can't go even in the day.
So good!
Drink! Drink! Alcohol is going down!
Chug, chug, chug!
I finished it.
Unnie, you're leaving already?
I think we're done discussing work. It's finished, right?
We have one more item.
But Su Jeong hasn't finished it yet.
That's nothing. I'll head out.
U-Unnie!
Travel safe!
Come on! Hurry! Drink it up!
Mi Yeon is here!
Do it again.
- Hurry!
- Do it again!
A graduation trip?
You have to go.
You should definitely go.
Go on the graduation trip.
You have no friends because you don't go to things like that.
I don't want to go.
I really don't.
But I really don't want to go, Unnie.
What do I even do there?
I don't want to.
Can I just stay home?
Unnie.
I'm not going.
I don't need friends!
Unnie.
I'm not going.
All I need is you, Unnie.
The daily temperature range is wide this spring.
Your immunity might get weaker.
There's been an increase in patients visiting hospitals with the flu.
But there have been issues of hygiene at some hospitals.
The repeated problem of hospital hygiene,
"Issue-In" is reporting on it now.
VCR start.
Three, two, one...
Cue.
"A child who can't take a step forward,"
"a child who can't have a spoonful of food,"
"if her older sister doesn't say to go outside,"
"or if she doesn't tell her to eat,"
"14-year-old Chae Hyeon stays home all day"
"and does not eat anything."
"Since her older sister left home, Chae Hyeon has not eaten anything until now."
"She is currently in the hospital for extreme malnutrition."
Chae Hyeon, who lost her parents young,
depended on her sister as if she was her mother.
When her sister, six years older than her, went to school,
Chae Hyeon was like a puppy, waiting for her sister all day.
This is how she spent her time.
Only when her sister came home,
that's when Chae Hyeon would eat anything. That was her day.
To Chae Hyeon, with a mental health disability, her sister was her everything.
After the VCR, it's Ju Eun Ho's line, right?
Yes, Announcer Ju Eun Ho can pick it up.
Producer.
What?
Did you hear that? After the VCR...
What's wrong with Ju Eun Ho?
Announcer Ju Eun Ho, what's wrong?
What's going on?
Who else does she have? All she has is her sister.
She would always follow her around.
Her sister thought it was annoying.
She ran away in the middle of the night with a boy.
That's why she stopped eating.
- She eats only if her sister is around.
- Hey.
My goodness. Oh, no...
Sadly, the older sister always found Chae Hyeon bothersome.
- Unnie.
- I'm busy. Let's talk later.
- Hey.
Can you just stay still? Be quiet and wait.
All I need is you, Unnie.
Ju Hye Ri!
What?
Ju Eun Ho.
I like you, Unnie.
I like only you.
I'm good at waiting.
Hey.
Wait over there.
Mi Yeon, how many more minutes in the VCR?
"VCR"? How many more minutes in the VCR?
- Eight minutes.
- Call an ambulance.
When the VCR is done, give me the lines. I'll figure it out.
No, Sunbae. You have so many lines after the VCR.
If you do it alone, it'll look odd.
What about the finish?
You can figure out the lines, but you two need to finish together.
Call the ambulance right now.
Hey, Ju Eun Ho.
I'll do the lines.
Then I'll see how she's doing and hand her the mic.
Mi Yeon, turn off our mics.
Turn off their mics, please.
Hey.
Ju Eun Ho?
Eun Ho...
Look at me.
Who did this to Chae Hyeon?
Was it her sister?
It... it wasn't me.
Right.
It wasn't you.
It wasn't you, Eun Ho.
Even today, Chae Hyeon is still waiting for her sister in her dreams.
She dreams of her sister coming to save her.
No... no...
It's okay.
I'm here.
You're fine.
It's okay.
You can do it, right?
Let's get up.
Sit.
I'll take the line right after the VCR.
Announcer Ju Eun Ho, take it from the next section. From "At 'Issue-In,' we are..."
Really? Is she okay?
Eun Ho, are you really okay?
Yes.
Here.
At "Issue-In," we are looking for Chae Hyeon's sister.
Her name is Kim So Hyeon, and she is currently 20 years old.
Her round eyes and face are so pretty.
That's all the news we have today.
Have a good day.
Please, please, please...
Thank goodness.
Yes, yes. She got better.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
- Chan Woo, do it fast.
- Got it.
Are you done?
- Yes, they're off, Deputy.
- Good work.
Good work.
Eun Ho, are you okay? Are you sick?
Do you need to go to the hospital? Should I call an ambulance?
Are you really okay?
Hey, how can she answer all those questions at once?
We're headed out. See you after the holiday.
What? Answer me before you go.
Call me.
- Sunbae.
- Hello.
Hey.
Let go.
You can go now.
Should I go?
What should I do, Ju Eun Ho? Should I get out?
Doctor.
I've never seen happiness with my own eyes;
however, if I could see it,
if I could touch it,
maybe it feels like this.
Eun Ho.
Look at me.
♫  Those dazzling moments and shining dreams  ♫
♫  The warmth of that day and your breath  ♫
♫  I won't forget when you smiled at me  ♫
♫  All those moments are so precious  ♫
♫  Your voice drifts farther away  ♫
♫  Even if it feels far, please don't let me go  ♫
♫  Our times are not over  ♫
♫  Remember, I'm waiting for you every day  ♫
♫  I love you, I love you  ♫
♫  I always want to be by your side  ♫
♫  I love you so much, every moment  ♫
♫  The sad air, your cold tone  ♫
♫  I miss you and your smile  ♫
♫  Our times are not over  ♫
♫  I love you, I love you  ♫
♫  I always want to be by your side  ♫
♫  I love you so much, every moment  ♫
♫  I love you  ♫