Would you save me?
Ju Eun Ho, do you know that you're dirty?
How many days did you leave these dishes piled?
Answer me! If I were drowning, would you save me?
Find your own way out.
Dude.
Are you crazy?
- Does it hurt?
- Did you just bite me?
- You're really insane.
- I bit you!
I bit you like you were a chicken leg!
I'll get you once I'm done with the dishes.
With extreme heat, this will be the hottest day of the year...
- Hyun Oh.
- What?
With the heat wave warnings around the country, as of 10 a.m. this morning—
Is it I or the nine o'clock news?
You seem crazy.
Me or the nine o'clock news? Answer me.
Excuse me.
Hurry up and answer me!
Listen. I won't tell you twice!
The nine o'clock news for sure.
Recorded 150 mm (6 inches) of rain in Jeju...
Oh, hey!
You seem like a crazy person.
Me or the nine o'clock news?
Please! Seriously!
- Hyun Oh.
- What?
Me or the vacuum cleaner?
Ask a real question.
It was a question with a question mark at the end.
Answer me. Is it I or the vacuum?
What is wrong with you?
Me or the vacuum?
- Answer me now!
- You really kicked me!
Answer me! Is it I or the vacuum?
The issue of granting privileges in the legal field has resurfaced.
Recently, major law firms have been
- Hyun Oh.
- actively recruiting former judges and prosecutors.
What?
- Is it I or the nine o'clock news?
- Concerns about their influence and access to information
- You, of course.
- used in the judicial system have been raised.
- The former position holder can
- I like you better than the vacuum
- and the news.
- use his influence to gain
- Are you satisfied?
- information advantageous to his case.
No.
I want more.
Well, what else?
I like you better than doing the dishes.
I like you better than the current issues, and I like you better than a news scoop.
Then...
can you sit right there?
Why are you so nice suddenly?
Because...
I love you.
Me, too.
I love you and support you.
No.
Why not?
Seriously, why not?
Team Leader, I do the early morning radio.
I get to work at 5 a.m. and work like a dog until 2 p.m.
How can I do the 4 p.m. live on top of that?
Make someone on the afternoon team do it.
Exactly.
You can leave the morning team and join the afternoon team.
Then I would have to quit my radio program, and I don't want to.
Darn it. Why not?
Team Leader, my program is number one in the ratings.
Not second, but first.
That didn't happen overnight.
I worked hard for three years to get to number one.
Who would easily give up what they have worked so hard for?
"A radio show is a long-term commitment."
It should continue for 10-20 years.
"Loyalty with your listeners is built over time."
Did I first say that? Did he say it?
Did he say it?
No, you said it, Team Leader.
How about you change your mind?
Why do I need to take on the 4 p.m. live?
Several announcers are right here.
We need a woman to announce,
a woman.
Eun Ho, the host is Sunbae Han Seok Jin.
Think about it.
Should a woman or a man stand beside him?
A man.
- What?
- Why can't a man do it?
We have so many men here.
Team Leader, "Boy Love" is all the rage these days.
- What love?
- Team Leader, if two men stand next to each other,
you'll defy outdated gender roles and become a global pioneer.
- You must be crazy.
- Team Leader, don't do this to me.
Just pick one of them. Keep pace with trends.
You told me that I'm awful,
that even after 14 years, I'm not a national announcer whom people recognize,
and if I'm not even a deputy general manager at the company, I'm doomed, totally doomed.
And even if I freelanced, I wouldn't earn a won.
Did I say that?
Did he say that? Did he?
Team Leader, you said that!
So don't do this to me—
I'll do it, Team Leader.
What?
The 4 p.m. live "Issue-In." I'll do it, Team Leader.
Instead of that.
What? "That"?
Hey. What did you just call me? "That"?
No, no.
No, Hyun Oh.
What are you talking about?
You know the 4 p.m. live.
It might get ratings, but the announcer has to be off-site.
It's nice to be off-site and deliver information dynamically.
You get recognition and become friendly with the viewers. It's good.
You can catch all kinds of fish: shark minnow, mandarin fish and mackerels.
It's good. Good!
But you're going to anchor the news
so you can't go there.
Not in ten years, not in five, but very soon.
As soon as possible, you'll be doing the news. So no.
What are you saying?
So I'm supposed to do all the fishing and make him look good?
Isn't this gender discrimination?
No. This isn't gender discrimination.
This is human discrimination!
More specifically, I'm discriminating between you and him.
Hyun Oh, you can't go there. Got it?
You just can't convince...
that.
"That" again...
Hey!
Still no, Hyun Oh.
I'll handle her.
Don't worry about that.
You can't worry about that right now.
Got it, Hyun Oh?
No, Team Leader.
I'll do the 4 p.m. live.
- Well then.
- No.
No, Hyun Oh. Hyun Oh?
Jung Hyun Oh! Hyun Oh?
Hey, you!
What are you going to do?
Sunbae, he must be out of his mind.
- He called me "that."
- Hey!
You must take care of this.
He can't do this! You know that!
He absolutely cannot!
You take responsibility and talk him out of it.
If you can't, you'll surely be on the 4 p.m. live. Got it?
- Sunbae, he said he'd do it. Just let him—
- Hey!
I wouldn't say this in front of those guys, but do you know how hard this was for me to get?
Those producers don't even know you!
They wanted Jung Hyun Oh!
Exactly. The producers want him, and he wants to do it.
I pushed and pushed to recommend you!
I pushed and pushed like plugging you into an outlet!
Why? So you could do something real for once!
You should be thanking me and accepting it!
But what?
"Boy Love"?
Got it, Team Leader.
What's up?
What?
You know, I thought you despised me.
You're not completely wrong.
But even those feelings stem from affection.
I was wrong.
Now that I think about it,
you still love me.
What are you talking about?
Were you daytime drinking?
The 4 p.m. live show,
you volunteered in my place so I wouldn't have to do it.
You were so stubborn, making everybody uncomfortable.
Has it occurred to you I sacrificed for the team?
Not at all. I think you did it for me and only me.
Don't be delusional.
Excuse me. I wish I were being delusional, too.
But how could it be?
Aloof people could separate work from personal life,
but I'm a hot-blooded 37-year-old spinster.
If you take a hit for the team to prevent others from hating me,
since I'm a pain in the neck,
there are only limited reasons I can imagine.
"Omo, maybe he loves me."
"Oh my, maybe he's still not over me."
Of course, I already have my reply.
No, thanks. Bye. You keep your love and regrets to yourself.
I would rather bear everyone's hate, you know.
Are you done?
No. You know, don't you?
That affection you speak of? It's all fluff. It's actually crap.
So you can keep the crap.
I'll talk to Team Leader and have someone else—
I'm curious about something.
I'd rather you didn't ask, but go ahead.
Do you really like the morning team that much?
Yes, I do. I told you.
I need to stay on the morning team if I want to keep my beloved radio program.
How about this? I'll move the 4 p.m. live to a morning slot.
- What?
- The morning works. Right?
Then you can stay on the morning team.
What?
Moving programs isn't like moving a vase between tables.
Hey, no matter how beloved you are in this industry,
even if you're the next nine o'clock news anchor, you can't do that.
Do you think you're some all-powerful video game cheat character?
I've always thought this, but you're so full of yourself. Are you aware?
No, I think I'm actually all-powerful.
I think I can get it done.
The heck you can.
Hey, do you own our company? Do you?
Not even the CEO of PPS can—
Hello.
Starting today, "Issue-In" will be brought to you a little earlier.
I'm Announcer Jung Hyun Oh, one of the new hosts.
We will cover the issues on your morning commute.
I'm Announcer Ju Eun Ho.
My goodness.
Sunbae.
Wh-Wh-What?
I experienced something so mysterious.
Jung Hyun Oh said, "If you really want to stay on the morning team,"
"I'll move the program to the morning."
I told him, "Not even the CEO of PPS can do that."
But the next thing I know, I'm hosting "Issue-In" at 9:05 a.m., Sunbae.
My goodness.
A program can easily move to the morning
with just one word from Jung Hyun Oh.
But you know what's even more fascinating, Sunbae?
I heard that Sunbae Han Seok Jin would be my co-host.
But when I came to my senses, it was Jung Hyun Oh next to me instead. Why?
Oh, as for that...
Sunbae Han Seok Jin had a scheduling conflict in the morning.
Then Hyun Oh said he would take responsibility so...
Then that jerk can do it alone. Why include me?
Eun Ho, I'll say this again.
A woman needs to stand next to a man.
I'm sorry.
I haven't escaped from my old-fashioned ideas yet.
I see.
But Sunbae, do you know?
I used to date Jung Hyun Oh.
Of course. You dated him for eight years.
So what is this?
Why are ex-lovers made to be co-emcees?
Hey. This is sincere advice.
You should be thankful you were assigned a program.
It's next to Jung Hyun Oh. Jung Hyun Oh.
Why would I be thankful?
Why not? That Hyung is great.
You should absorb some of his energy.
Hey, Ji On.
Jung Hyun Oh and I are the same age.
Why is he your "hyung" while I'm just "you"?
Address me like you do for Jung Hyun Oh:
"Noona. Sunbae."
Or be like him and say, "Hey, you. Over here."
As I consider you a woman, I won't call you "Noona."
Oh, really?
You're nice to everybody. What's with the mutiny?
Ju Eun Ho, Hyung is nice to everybody, too.
But he dated you.
Then why can't you date me? I'm nice to everybody, too.
Yes, I dislike that the most.
Then why did you date him?
Do you think I knew before dating him? I didn't.
I like someone who's rude to everyone except me.
Then I'll do my best, Ju Eun Ho.
No need. And I...
will get my revenge.
What revenge?
You know, some people were saying this on the Internet.
Saying what?
"The best revenge at your ex-boyfriend is to become hot,"
"so tremendously hot that he can't even approach you."
Excuse me, Writer. I'm so curious.
What's going on with Ju Eun Ho's hair and makeup?
Is there a war? Where?
What is wrong with her outfit? Is she Francesca (former first lady)?
I don't know. Will it change the trends, Producer?
No. It won't affect the trends.
Next news.
While we transition from winter to spring, the wide daily temperature range might make you catch a cold.
Right. That's why immunity is so important to prevent colds.
-  At "Issue-In" today, we seek foods to help immunity.
- Oh, what is that?
We visited the vendors ourselves.
VCR start.
What do we do in the closing two-shot (of both people)?
Can we do a chest-up on Deputy Jung to finish?
Sunbae, we will do a chest-up shot on you to finish. Close it out, please.
Three, two, one, cue.
That's it for today's news.
- The wind is still—
- Chilly and cold.
Please watch out for your health, everyone.
- Have a—
- Have a good day.
Good, good. Display energy, Sunbae.
Director, keep Camera 2 chest-up.
We're not doing a two-shot. We will close here.
We're going to cut it here. Start the title sequence.
I'm sorry, Hyun Oh.
Are you not feeling well?
Excuse me, Jung Hyun Oh. Are you not feeling well?
- I'm okay.
- I don't think so.
You don't look fine. You look really sick.
Get off me.
Oh, no, this was still here.
What did you just say, Jung Hyun Oh?
Get off? Get off me? No?
Get out of here right now?
Just go now.
Excuse me, Jung Hyun Oh.
If you're in pain, don't hold back. Get angry.
You want to curse me out, don't you?
Then just—
- Go.
- So why did you steal my line?
Did you want those few lines so badly that you stole them?
Hey.
Why? What's up?
You must not have a grasp on reality.
Hey. Few people have a tighter grasp on reality than I do.
You've done this for 14 years.
Where's your professionalism?
Your actions could ruin the broadcast. Do you ever consider that?
So why did you steal my line?
Hey. Stealing my line would ruin the broadcast, not my stepping on your foot.
I'm not so sure.
Accidents never happen the way you expect.
Excuse me. Are you trying to give me advice now?
No.
A warning.
That's just...
Are you okay? Put this around your waist.
Why, Chan Woo?
Your skirt ripped.
What? Where?
Oh, no, how did this happen?
If Deputy Jung hadn't stolen your line, it would be a serious accident.
Don't ruin your career just to get revenge on Hyun Oh.
What?
You just said the same thing as Jung Hyun Oh.
He said that, too?
Yes. He asked me where my professionalism went.
Honestly, I felt super guilty.
Then I thought,
"Oh. I've lived a pathetic life because I am this pathetic."
"That's why Jung Hyun Oh treated me like I was so pathetic."
- Ju Eun Ho.
- Ji On.
It's "Noona" or "Sunbae."
Can you try not to hate Jung Hyun Oh?
What do you mean?
You hate him so much that it seems you like him.
What are you saying?
Then don't hate him.
It bothers me.
- Moon Ji On.
- What?
Want to go on a date with me?
What?
Would you go on a date with me?
I mean...
I have time only this week.
I have filming on the weekends starting next week.
Then we can go out this weekend.
No canceling.
Fine, no canceling.
Hey! What do you want to do? What do you want to eat?
Is there a gift you want? Tell me everything.
One date and you're asking what gift I want?
In that case, I want pork belly.
I can't have pork belly alone.
Hey, let's go get pork belly.
Not that! Something more date-like!
Fine dining, sushi, or what else?
Oh, teppanyaki (fry on iron slab).
Sushi, gross. Fine dining, gross.
- What else did you say?
- Hey.
If you keep this up, I'll take you on vacation.
Pork belly on vacation? Let's go.
Seriously.
Not pork belly. How about beef?
But I like pork belly.
Okay. Beef is fine.
Okay, beef, okay!
Hey. Why are you so pretty today?
Right? So pretty, right?
But everyone else seemed frightened.
Really? Why would they be like that? I don't understand.
Right? Say I'm pretty a few more times.
I can feel my confidence growing.
What's on the filming agenda this weekend?
W-W-Wait one second. Let me check.
Reporting on the ocean waste in Yangwan.
It's two days on the weekend. Why?
Send Ju Eun Ho.
What? That business trip pays dirt-poor.
We can barely get people to do it even if it's a special.
Ju Eun Ho likes that kind of thing.
Send Ju Eun Ho.
Stop talking nonsense!
Sunbae, no one's into that kind of thing. Do you get that?
Sure, I'm into it.
Wh-What?
The ocean waste filming, I'll go.
What's the schedule like?
Oh, well...
it's this weekend.
Oh, the weekend.
Right? You can't, right?
It's the weekend, overnight and everything.
How many minutes on the VCR?
Oh, that's...
Thirteen, oh, fourteen minutes.
Fourteen minutes.
Yes. I know, it's not great.
Fourteen minutes for an overnight schedule, not great.
I just figured I would ask.
I'll do it.
You'd be leaving at 5 a.m. on Saturday.
Sounds good, I'm a morning person.
Oh, you're a morning person.
I'll see you on the day then.
Thank you!
- What?
- Our date.
Can we go out next weekend?
Next weekend, this noona will—
I told you I can't. I'll be filming.
Right. You did.
Then why don't we... hop on the phone like it's a date?
A quick call?
Or let's imagine that we're on a date right now and go down to the cafeteria to eat, and—
You got something scheduled, didn't you?
How did you know?
You're trying to dominate the VCR.
Were you there just now?
Did you hear everything?
You're choosing screen time over me.
I mean...
"Issue-In" is going off-site to film on the weekend.
But do you know how long the segment is?
Fourteen whole minutes, fourteen minutes!
In my fourteen long years of being an announcer,
I have never once been on TV alone for fourteen minutes!
And they're giving it to me.
I need to take it. Don't you think?
Fine. I'll accept it.
What?
Is your heart like Lake Titicaca?
A lake 4,000 meters above sea level, serving vast highlands?
Is it open, wide and very vast?
No. I'm coming with you.
What do you mean? It's an overnight shoot.
Even better.
I'll ask to share a room with you.
Okay! See you on Saturday, Ju Eun Ho.
What did you say, Ji On?
Moon Ji On?
Moon Ji—
- Hello?
-  Sunbae!
I'm at the shoot. Guess who Ju Eun Ho brought.
She brought Moon Ji On. Moon Ji On!
She brought a guy to an overnight shoot.
Are they dating or something?
How can she do that on an overnight shoot?
Mi Yeon.
Let me ask you a favor.
What? What favor?
Can you wrap up the shoot within the day?
Why?
It'll be tricky here due to the high tides and stuff.
Still. You can squeeze it all in.
If it were that easy, I would have scheduled it that way.
I can try, but it won't be easy.
But why? Why do I need to do that?
This is a beach in Yangwan.
Do you see the garbage here?
Where did this garbage come from?
Butane gas, tin foil...
It appears that someone grilled meat out here.
But humans are not the ones who clean up this kind of trash.
It's the animals that live here.
The trash is not just limited to the beach.
Here—
Cut! Eun Ho, what's wrong? Do you not want to go in the water?
Then you don't have to.
No, I can go in.
Oh, then just dip your foot. Let's go again.
Hi. Cue!
You can also easily see garbage in the ocean water.
Ji On.
I-It's a seaweed!
I'm sorry I misunderstood you two.
As you can see, the issue of ocean waste is quite serious.
Oppa, I think you should stop laughing.
Right, Unnie?
Oppa, do you know that word has spread?
- What word?
- They say you hate her so much
that you came all the way here to watch her struggle.
Unnie, I can't find spare clothes anywhere.
Everything you brought is wet from the rain.
What if you catch a cold?
I'm okay, Yu Yeon.
I'll be loading our stuff.
See you two later.
Take some.
Come on.
You were laughing at me.
Now this?
Of course.
If I came all the way here and obviously showed I like you,
it'd hurt your career that's already not going well.
Take them before you really catch a cold.
You'll return in my car, won't you?
I don't know.
What do you mean, you don't know?
- Nice work.
- Yes, great work.
Travel safely!
Okay, Yu Yeon! See you at work!
Okay!
Here. Put this on.
This?
Yes. It's too cold.
Get changed. I'll go get some stuff.
The call is not going through. You'll be connected to voicemail.
After the beep, a fee will be charged.
What?
Do I look more attractive to you now that you think of it?
No.
On second thought,
I think you're a really serious person,
yet people treat you like you're not.
You know that I'm a serious person.
That's why I like you.
Thanks for the ride.
I'll wash your sweater and return it.
Aren't you tired? I told you to sleep as I drove.
I can sleep at home.
Bye.
But…
why did you want to see me?
You didn't want to be with me anyway.
There must have been a different reason.
You said you wanted to say something.
What is it?
Later.
Can I tell you later?
Do you want to go on another date?
Ji On, I…
hate…
Hyun Oh.
Still?
Yes.
Why do you hate him?
Marriage? No way, Eun Ho.
I won't do that.
I don't do such a thing, Eun Ho.
Because he's not mine.
No matter how much I want it,
no matter how hard or desperately I try,
he will never be mine.
To give up what you want so badly,
do you know how much you must…
hate it?
Is that why you…
Yes, I hate him.
I hate him to pieces.
I'm sorry.
No.
There is no need to be sorry.
What?
You just have to choose.
- What?
- I'll be with you, no matter what.
Ji On. Moon Ji On, I—
If you say no, I'll never make a move on you again.
But if you stay where you are without saying anything,
I'll try harder to make you stop hating Hyun Oh.
What do you think?
Have you decided?
No, I… I…
I have.
I really don't know.
What do you like about me?
I'm 37 years old.
Why do you always mention your age? I don't care at all.
- Here you go. Bye now.
- Thank you.
Ju Hye Ri, what's happening?
Were you dreaming again?
What was your dream?
I was an announcer.
That's the dream I had.
Could you be more specific?
An announcer who looks just like me.
In my dream, she was running around the broadcast station.
In this one, she was at the beach for a shoot.
After there,
she even kissed a much younger guy.
Doctor, why are my dreams so vivid and realistic?
Is it because I sleep 16 hours a day?
Instead, does something make you feel exhausted?
"Exhausted"? Doctor…
I'm bored to death daily.
Is this because I've lost most of my memories?
When you lose your memories, instead of feeling bored,
you're more likely to feel uneasy and anxious.
When your days feel tedious, you could try to make exciting things happen.
"Exciting things"? By chance…
like falling in love?
That could be one.
Why? Are you in love?
I have someone I like.
Excuse me, is this a parking spot?
No, it's under construction.
Go away.
I don't think so. There's a spot right here.
Darn.
Who is the person?
Hello, everyone.
It's Monday, March 18. This is Media N Seoul's 8 p.m. news.
After the salmonella-contaminated onion scandal, we are now under a food safety alert.
After salmonella was found in some onions grown and distributed by Daeju,
the Ministry of Health is holding an investigation.
A good person.
And…
a good-looking person.
Is that why you like him?
No. Because he is rude.
You said he was a good person.
He is good…
but also rude.
What?
W-W-Wait!
Why would you be drawn to that?
I read in a web novel once
that a guy like that is totally devoted to his girlfriend.
Have you ever actually seen that?
Yes.
Hey, if you do this, you'll be late. Just go.
I won't be.
Do they all need pushing?
Doesn't that mean he likes men?
No. He's just nice to those close to him.
Still, I don't know if you'll be that one special girl.
Min Yeong, I lost most of my memories, didn't I?
That means I don't have much data on failure.
So all I have is overflowing confidence.
Is that right?
Ju Hye Ri.
Yes?
I see Kang Ju Yeon.
Just joking!
I have a question.
What is it?
What does a guy like that think of when he's alone?
Se Yeon.
I'm so happy Se Yeon became an announcer.
My son is so handsome.
I wish Ju Yeon was as handsome as you and became an announcer, too,
but he wanted to be a soldier like his dad, right?
Se Yeon, I saw your dad in my dreams last night.
In my dream, your dad…
Se Yeon.
Mom.
It's Ju Yeon.
Sunbae!
Sunbae, are you going to work now?
Yes, Hye Yeon.
Sunbae, do you have time this evening?
No, Hye Yeon.
There's a new udon food truck in the area.
Do you know what they call udon?
"Tight Tight, Chewy Chewy."
How good are noodles named "Tight Tight, Chewy Chewy"?
It makes no sense. Is that right, Sunbae?
It does make sense, Hye Yeon.
-  See?
- Excuse me.
Kang Ju Yeon and Baek Hye Yeon are dating.
Wait a minute.
No.
She's the only girl Kang Ju Yeon has to deal with.
That's right.
Then what else would they be?
Sunbae, where are you going? Home? Are you going home now?
Yes, Hye Yeon.
Sunbae, I actually have a wish.
Can you make my wish come true?
No. I can't.
It's a challenging task to fulfill a wish, Hye Yeon.
No. Fulfilling a wish is really easy.
You can just have dinner with me.
All right. What's your wish?
If I fulfill it, will you make mine come true?
What is your wish?
My wish is for the world to end.
- What did you say?
- That all trees outside my house get pulled out.
Or all the paper cups at work hang from the ceiling.
Or my news desk flies into a sudden gust of wind.
- Bye.
- It's one-sided.
Why does he have such a wish?
Now I have to be brave.
You? You live with a curtain over your face in case Kang Ju Yeon sees you.
You claim self-confidence, yet still live with a face curtain.
Now you say you want to be brave?
- Min Yeong.
- What?
That's because if he sees me, he will fall in love with me.
I'm too pretty.
Hey.
Has anyone in your life ever told you that's not true?
No. Even if they did, I don't recall.
I've lost all my memories.
Wow. Your life is so easy.
I'd love to lose my memories like you.
Until now, the time just wasn't right.
Because even in unrequited love, I loved myself.
Daebak.
So?
What will you do?
Prepare my heart.
Prepare to meet the version of myself in requited love.
I am preparing my heart.
Make sure you go to the hospital.
I already take time off and go every Wednesday at 5:30 p.m.
You know that.
That's true.
That's why I work more.
I feel very bad about that.
I just want to pay for this.
Oh, sure.
Let me total your bill.
You're all set.
I thought you were ready.
So why did you hide?
I meant I would do it from now on.
From now on.
That's right, from now on.
Kang Ju Yeon, step down! You misreported the onion scandal!
Step down! Step down!
We demand a true report!
We demand! We demand!
Get Kang Ju Yeon out here!
Please leave.
- Step down!
- I need to see Kang Ju Yeon before I go!
What are you talking about?
You can't stay here.
Let go!
Stop it!
Stop It!
Kang Ju Yeon!
This is done.
But this is not the last one.
We're all going to work late for it.
I hear the basement printer is ready. Go check it out.
Okay.
Let go!
Hey! You… you!
Die! Die! I said die!
Do you know what you've done?
No…
You've killed all of us!
Kang Ju Yeon! Stop right there!
Kang Ju Yeon!
Excuse me.
Get out here! Where are you hiding?
Kang Ju Yeon!
I'm going to kill you!
Calm down! Put that down.
Let's go.
How did you find me here?
Well…
That's…
They are…
all gone.
So…
she just showed up in front of the elevator.
She threatened me with the pickax so I tried to stop her...
because I thought I could.
Didn't you think you might get hurt running at her like that?
Oh…
Are you hurt anywhere?
Hey, Ju Eun Ho.
Have you met someone from your dream…
in real life?
Yes, Doctor.
I met this person.
This person appeared before me in real life.
How is that possible?
How could someone in a dream exist for real?
Do you know what he called me?
The name of the woman in my dream.
How is that possible, Doctor?
What is the name of the woman in your dream, Eun Ho?
The woman in my dream…
What did you say, Doctor?
What is the name of the woman in your dream?
No, after that.
Eun Ho.
Doctor, am I…
Eun Ho?
Yes, Eun Ho.
You've been seeing me for the past two months, Eun Ho.
Why, Eun Ho?
Doctor, I'm Hye Ri.
No.
Eun Ho, you're not Hye Ri.
You are Eun Ho.
I-I...
I am…
the same person…
as her?
What are you doing over there?
Why are you walking like that?
Are you trying to make me laugh?
How is this possible?
How can someone from my dream…
How can this be real?
What are you saying, Ju Eun Ho?
What is this? Did he just call me "Ju Eun Ho"?
Wow!
Is this your new method of ignoring me?
I-I'm really not Ju Eun Ho…
Oh, really?
Then who are you?