It's so pretty here, right?
Yes, it's nice.
Aren't the pinwheels pretty? Don't they look like spinning rainbows?
Right. How pretty.
Everything here looks like a painting, right?
Exactly.
But...
are you a Twizzler (candy)?
Why do you keep twisting yourself?
Oh, so...
You keep inviting me to such places
and you phone me every night.
So I asked people; everyone said...
you must be interested in me.
What did you say?
By any chance, are you
interested in me?
- I mean–
- Don't answer that.
There's no way you're interested in me. You have it all.
Right. Darn it. So funny.
What's so funny?
I mean, there's no way you'd be interested in me.
Hey, I'm hungry. What should we eat after our walk?
Pork belly? Intestines? Oxtail stew? Seonji (ox blood) hotpot?
Hey, do you know garitguk (Beef bone soup)?
I'm very interested in you.
Wh-What?
Isn't it obvious?
Why would I call or ask you to meet if I wasn't interested?
I think it's weirder that you didn't know.
I know garitguk. It's really good.
Let's go eat it later.
It's really nice here.
Wh-What? Wh-What did you say?
- Hey, Ju Eun Ho.
- What?
I don't like you anymore.
- I mean...
I said I was interested in you weeks ago, yet you never gave me an answer.
A month passed.
You haven't responded.
Are you meaning me?
Whom else would I mean?
So...
Wait, that was...
It's fine. I'm leaving. Don't follow me.
Hey!
Wow!
Wow, wh-what was that?
D-Did he just...
He said he was interested. He didn't ask me to be his girlfriend.
Did he say we should date?
He didn't say anything!
How can I answer if he doesn't ask?
"I'm very interested in you." So what did he want me to do?
Did he want me to say, "Hey, Jung Hyun Oh, who is very interested,"
"I'm also very interested in you. Should we start dating?"
Wow! Darn! What a passive jerk!
Hey. Where are you going?
Can I go with you?
Who are you?
I'm Jung Hyun Oh.
What are you saying?
What?
You just do whatever you want, don't you?
One day, you're very interested in me.
A month later, you don't like me and say to avoid you.
Excuse me, it was over six months since we've spoken.
Then you just show up and say,
"Where are you going? Can I go with you?"
Hey, am I a joke to you?
Eun Ho.
Can you stop using my name? We aren't friends.
So you thought of me a lot, right?
So annoying.
Can you please not talk to me?
Do you want to go to Namsan Tower like this?
I...
like cable cars.
Really? Let's go ride one.
Don't do that from now on.
Do what?
Not talk to me.
Ignore me for six months.
I'm not sure.
What did you say?
You never know with people.
Just joking.
Jung Hyun Oh.
What should I do?
I like you so much.
From the top of your head to the bottom of your feet.
Fold your laundry.
Why?
Are you the lazy grasshopper?
Hyun Oh, you fold laundry so well!
Attention!
Welcome to the... what group are you?
Yes!
I'm in Group 34.
It's an honor to join PPS. I anticipate working with you!
All right, everyone.
Congratulations on landing a hard-to-get job at PPS through nepotism.
Should we do some introductions?
Who here is in the oldest group?
Group 28, right? Stand up. Say hello.
Sit, sit. I'll be the representative.
Hello, I'm Announcer Ju Eun Ho. I will work with you.
Applause!
Sit. Let's fill our glasses for a toast.
Here. Fill it up.
Welcome.
Welcome!
Hey, Moon Ji On. How can you not know how to do this?
I know. Why am I so bad at it?
Hey, is it because you majored in Physical Education?
Yes, I'm a PE major, right?
Maybe that's why.
Whoa, you don't even have pride.
Geez...
Hey. Do you know what?
- He majored in Economics...
- Pardon?
with Applied Statistics.
So if Kwon Gyeong Jin messes up numbers, say this.
"Sunbae, you majored in Economics. Why don't you know that?"
Sunbaenim, I'm not upset at all.
Really.
You don't look upset.
But you seem to be struggling.
Do you want some coffee?
You scared me.
What? How did you know I was here?
I heard you and Hyung broke up.
It was two days. How did you find out?
Ju Eun Ho.
Why are you using my name?
I thought I was your sunbae.
Are you okay?
Hello.
Aigoo, how can we help you?
I have a question.
I heard there was an accident nearby.
In front of Ttaenggang Supermarket. A woman got hurt...
Oh, that young lady?
Yes, yes. I heard she ran off.
If so...
Are you okay?
Aren't you hungry?
Are you hurt?
Should we go to the hospital?
Eun Ho.
Do you want to change?
I'll bring you some clothes to change into.
Don't go anywhere. Stay here.
All my passwords are your birthday.
I'm just curious.
What should I call you?
Anyway,
you aren't Eun Ho, are you?
Should I call you Hye Ri?
Okay.
Change your clothes first, please, Hye Ri.
Come out after. I'll make you something delicious.
Sunbae, you know what?
I can drink.
So I will drink for you.
Do you know what else? I've been acting like I don't know,
but I think I already know.
I guess you and Hye Ri broke up.
Right?
­
You know... how can I not know?
Because all I do is stare at your face.
As for the exact timing, I'm not sure.
Maybe a month ago?
Your face was gloomy since then.
Considering all you've said so far,
I think Hye Ri broke up with you.
Because she was two-timing you.
Right? One heart, two loves...
You were blindsided by her two-timing and learned of your breakup.
I'm right, aren't I?
Hye Yeon.
What, Sunbae?
Each person...
has one heart only.
It's true.
Each person...
truly has only one heart.
By any chance...
do you recognize me?
We've met before.
I-I'm really not Ju Eun Ho...
Oh, really? Then who are you?
Of course. You might not remember.
Eat slowly. I'll go upstairs for a second.
Jung Hyun Oh.
Hello?
Kang Ju Yeon.
This is Hye Ri's...
I mean, this is Announcer Ju Eun Ho's...
- No, Hye Ri–
- I'm Jung Hyun Oh.
Sunbaenim, why are you picking up her phone?
Because Eun Ho
is back.
Where is she right now?
Is Hye Ri okay? Where was she?
What is she doing right now? Can I talk to her?
S-Sunbaenim.
Hey, Sunbaenim!
She is healthy and safe.
Bye.
Thank you.
She's asleep.
- Then–
-  I see...
She's asleep?
Who's asleep?
I want to know.
Is Hye Ri...
Hye Ri right now...
or Announcer Ju Eun Ho?
He doesn't know. Hyung, you don't know, right?
But...
who are you?
I'm Moon Ji On. Who are you?
I'm Kang Ju Yeon.
I'm an announcer with Media N Seoul.
I didn't get in there.
Which cohort? I'm in Group 34 at PPS.
"Group 34"?
When did you start?
March 2019?
Then we started the same year.
I started in 2019, too.
But I'm 35.
I see.
I'm 32.
You look young.
Since we started the same year, I can talk informally, right?
No, you can't.
So, Hyung.
Can I ask what's going on?
I already explained it to you earlier.
Yes, I understand that much.
Ju Eun Ho has Dissociative Identity Disorder
and worked in the Media N Seoul parking lot under the name "Ju Hye Ri."
That's where she met me.
She was seeing me.
- For how long?
- A month.
"A month"? Wow.
A month.
You might as well not have been together.
What do you mean by "you might as well not have been together"?
A totally blank white canvas is better than
one drop of paint on it.
So?
Is Hye Ri okay?
As I've said, she's healthy and safe–
No.
Which personality is she right now?
If it's Hye Ri, I think I should be her guardian.
No, no, no.
How can you trust someone she dated for only a month?
I never dated Eun Ho, but I've known her for five years.
I think I should be her guardian.
Even if we dated only a month,
I have the right to be her guardian since we loved each other.
Excuse me!
A guardian shouldn't have personal feelings but just be a guardian.
- So I–
- No way.
I think a guardian should have personal feelings.
So do you hire caretakers based on love?
Yes, I hired my mother's caretaker based on love.
Don't talk of your mom. That's cheating. Should I talk about my mom?
- My mom left–
- Do we need to mention this?
Why must we pick a guardian?
Ju Eun Ho is an adult.
- But you said she isn't well–
- Yes, you said she's sick.
Yes. In that case, I dated her for eight years. I loved her.
And now I have no personal feelings so I should be her guardian.
Right? Right?
So... you can go.
Go, please.
I'm 37 years old. I'll guard her.
By the way, where did Hyun Oh go?
He didn't come home last night.
What? What's wrong?
Give him a call.
I already called him to take you to the hospital, but he didn't pick up.
What are you saying?
I think Jung Hyun Oh's gone crazy.
What's wrong, Producer?
He just called me...
to say he won't be at meetings for a while.
What? Is that really that strange, Producer?
It is. For the Deputy, it's strange.
Wow! This has never happened to me before.
What is this? Writer.
Why is he doing this?
Why are you asking me?
I thought you were like family. You must know what's going on,
why he's acting like this suddenly.
Don't you know family members always keep things from each other?
Oh, is that so?
Shall we go?
Wait here for a second.
Let me go talk to him.
- I said I'll call you—
- Hye Ri.
Wait.
Talk to me first.
Is that Hye Ri or Eun Ho?
We're headed to the doctor. I'll tell you when we're back.
But actually...
it doesn't matter to me.
It really doesn't matter to me,
no matter who Hye Ri is.
It doesn't matter to me, Hye Ri!
Because...
all I need is for you to be fine.
- Excuse me, Kang Ju Yeon—
- Even if it's not by my side,
if you're alive and well, it's enough for me.
You don't have to love me.
Even if you return to the woods, I'm okay with your choice.
If you want, I will come with you.
I can leave everything behind and come with you.
I'm not afraid to do that, Hye Ri.
Hey, Ju Yeon.
Hye Ri can't have this conversation right now—
Because, Hye Ri,
I didn't fall for you because you were somebody.
Just because...
you came to me as I am.
That's why, Hye Ri.
I like you for you.
So...
♫  My heart changes according to your gaze  ♫
♫  If I could feel every moment  ♫
♫  That's enough  ♫
♫  I'll be with you, always there but barely noticeable  ♫
♫  I'll be in your background  ♫
♫  I'll protect you forever  ♫
♫  I'll be the affection for another side of you  ♫
♫  So you won't get hurt in this harsh world  ♫
I missed you, Hye Ri.
♫  I'll be in your background  ♫
♫  I'll protect you forever  ♫
♫  I will be for only you  ♫
♫  I'll be by your side  ♫
♫  We will be happy  ♫
This is the item I brought up last time.
We shelved it because it was too heavy for "Issue-In."
To celebrate your comeback, why don't we...
put it out there. Yes.
It seems a good idea.
Sunbae?
Excuse me, Sunbaenim?
One second.
Jung Hyun Oh.
I want to speak with Kang Ju Yeon.
Excuse me, Sunbaenim!
Oppa!
What? What is it? What's up?
Get it together. What's wrong with you?
Right.
How have you been?
Just... so-so.
Are you hurt?
Are you feeling okay?
Yes, I'm okay.
So right now...
are you Hye Ri?
Or Eun Ho?
I'm...
What? Hey, Jung Hyun Oh.
I thought you were taking today off.
I'll make it a half-day.
Geez, I guess everyone's just doing whatever they want to do.
Why are you showing up on a day off, saying it's a half-day?
What's wrong with you? What?
Did you eat something bad?
Hey, hey! Stop!
It wasn't even two months!
Are you crazy?
Hyung.
Hyung!
Can we talk?
Say it.
I went to Giyidong, too.
What did you say?
Shim Jin Hwa said she saw Ju Eun Ho there while filming.
So?
What do you mean "So"?
You had already taken Eun Ho home when I got there.
Then?
Then... I went to the forest.
"The forest"?
That forest where Ju Eun Ho was apparently living.
Do you know why Ju Eun Ho went into that forest?
No.
She wanted to get rid of herself.
She even hurt her own arm, and she wanted to...
get rid of herself.
If it were me, I would have hated being here.
I would have especially hated my name, "Ju Eun Ho."
I think that's why she hurt her arm to look like Ju Hye Ri
and was staying there.
You know, Ju Hye Ri was like that.
She didn't care about anything else except being loved by Kang Ju Yeon,
rather than where nothing worked out for her, no matter how hard she tried.
Here she was always heartbroken due to you.
The other side is much better.
I think Eun Ho...
wanted to be fully Hye Ri.
That's why she left everything behind and ran away.
But Hyung,
do you know...
what I found...
in that cabin?
She wanted to leave everything behind,
but she took that with her.
Hyung.
I'm... so jealous of you,
but I also don't like you.
I've always thought you don't deserve her
and that I'd get a chance at some point.
Someday, if I kept waiting,
but Ju Eun Ho couldn't leave you behind even if she left all else.
Even when she gave it all up,
she couldn't give you up.
You don't deserve her, but Ju Eun Ho...
Eun Ho...
For her, it's only you.
Hyung...
It must be so nice, really...
to be loved like that.
Here.
Geez.
You must get it for me, okay?
Are you crazy?
I'm not crazy!
I drew it since you said you'd buy it for me.
You should keep your promise.
Fine, fine.
I'll get it! I'm going to.
I'm...
I am Eun Ho, Kang Ju Yeon.
However,
I wanted very much to be Hye Ri.
So...
have you been trying to be Hye Ri?
Yes.
I wanted to know why she was happy.
I've always...
wanted to ask Hye Ri.
Ju Hye Ri.
Are you happy?
If you're happy,
I will try
living as you.
If I try,
it could happen, right?
I've always tried to be her.
But Ju Hye Ri,
I really want to know.
You have nothing.
But why...
Why...
are you happy?
Hey! What's wrong?
What's going on?
But...
in the end, I returned unable to become Hye Ri.
Hye Ri.
I...
Eun Ho, I'll be back.
Okay. Make sure you take an umbrella.
I've never been happy.
Eun Ho.
Not one second.
I love that. Can you do it again?
Eun Ho, you don't know how to say no.
Do it again. Do it again.
Should I leave a little later?
Yes. Just one second.
Okay. Move over.
Just a little longer.
Okay.
Hyun Oh, today...
is special.
What? What's special about it?
So today...
Today...
I really didn't want to be alone.
I...
don't think...
I could become Hye Ri, Ju Yeon.
It really doesn't matter to me.
Whoever Hye Ri really is—
Maybe today...
is the end for us.
No.
- No—
- I wanted to say thank you.
I needed love more than anyone,
and you liked me.
Thank you for taking care of me.
What you said to me earlier
is what I wanted to say to you.
You're right.
I didn't fall for you because you were somebody.
But you came to me
as I am. Thank you, Ju Yeon.
I hope you never leave.
Who?
Me?
Yes.
I want...
you to always be by my side.
Can you do that, Hyun Oh?
Yes.
Of course.
How long will you love me?
I'll date you my whole life.
No, not dating.
Loving me.
How long will you do that for?
Forever.
Hey. So the potted plant next to that,
trim it once a month or two? How could it—
♫  I love you, I love you  ♫
♫  I always want to be by your side  ♫
♫  I love you so much, every moment  ♫
♫  The sad air, your cold tone  ♫
♫  I miss you and your smile  ♫
I'm going to get out here, Sir.
♫  Our times are not over  ♫
♫  I promise I'll be by your side always  ♫
♫  I love you, I love you  ♫
♫  I always want to be by your side  ♫
♫  I love you so much, every moment  ♫
♫  I love you  ♫
I thought...
I've never been happy, not even for a second.
But?
But no.
I was so happy today.
Oh...
Because I'm by your side?
What?
Why are you smiling?
Because I...
Because you like me so much?
If he comes back to me,
I'll tell him.
I'll have to tell him.
♫  All the seasons we spent together  ♫
♫  In calm anticipation, time passes  ♫
♫  The moment I thought would never come  ♫
♫  Came to us silently  ♫
♫  Every second of the day, inside my quiet heart  ♫
♫  Waves rise slowly  ♫
♫  In the gentle sunlight season  ♫
♫  We stood on that road  ♫
♫  Holding on to words we couldn't say  ♫
♫  Our today, soaked in sunlight  ♫
♫  Will remain for a long time, deep inside me  ♫
♫  Every moment, I long for "us"  ♫
♫  I thought it would be only natural  ♫
♫  Like falling leaves, I turned away  ♫
♫  With an unfamiliar expression and tone  ♫
♫  I spoke words I didn't mean the moment I let you go  ♫
♫  In the gentle sunlight season  ♫
♫  I stayed there for an eternity  ♫
♫  Holding on to words I couldn't say  ♫
♫  Our today, soaked in sunlight  ♫
♫  Will remain for a long time, deep inside me  ♫
♫  Every moment, I long for "us"  ♫
♫  How can I say it all?  ♫
♫  You turned on the lights during dark nights  ♫
♫  You held my hand tightly  ♫
♫  To that day when gentle sunlight shone  ♫
I will tell him.
♫  I want to go back and tell you  ♫
Thank you, my love.
Thank you for coming to me
as I am.
♫  Can be completed with you  ♫
♫  In all of time  ♫
♫  It's "us"  ♫
I missed you.
Even though you saw me every day?
Yes.
Although I've seen you at work daily.
Me, too.
I did miss you every day.