Lyrics: Soya la
happy life
is like Mount Namcha Barwa.
What's your name, miss?
My name is Ding Nian.
Ding Nian.
This is our inn's
cleaning lady.
Her name is Baima,
you can call her Ajia La.
Ajia La.
Ajia La in Tibetan
means something like 'big sister.'
Are you here in Nyingchi to see the peach blossoms?
We've got a flat tire,
can't drive anymore.
The inn isn't far anyway,
let's walk back.
Here.
Baima, help her carry this.
Thank you.
Let's go.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Coming!
Could it be
she went to Tibet?
We're here.
What's going on with you guys?
Where's the car?
The car got a flat tire
on the road.
You had to take a shortcut
instead of staying on the main road.
Where are my things?
In the trunk,
you can get them yourself later.
So you're Ding Nian?
Yes, this is Ding Nian,
Ding Nian.
This is our chef, Sun Qianqian.
From now on, you two
will be roommates.
Hello, just call me Qianqian.
You can call me Nian Nian.
Can you take me to the car?
Let's take the first step toward our dessert freedom.
Let's go.
Ask Ajiala to take you there,
I need to show Ding Nian around.
Alright then.
Ajiala,
let's go.
During the online interview,
do you remember the things
I told you about?
Yes, I do.
This is your work phone.
Our inn's WeChat account
has quite a few regular customers
and new guests referred by them.
You need to provide good service.
Also, familiarize yourself with those booking platforms
as soon as possible.
Make sure you understand
the check-in, check-out, and room change procedures.
We only have eight rooms in total,
so it's not difficult to manage.
If you have any questions, just ask me.
Here's the key to your room.
Okay.
Hey, Lao Lei,
what's wrong with Jianguo?
My daughter might have gone to Tibet.
I'm so busy with work
and can't get away right now.
Ding Nian has come to Tibet.
She had an argument with me
and ran away from home.
I'm guessing she might have gone to Tibet.
Alright, I'll help you look into it right away
and get back to you.
Okay.
Thank you so much.
Let's welcome our new team member
Ding Nian.
Welcome.
Though I don't know how long you'll be staying with us,
but
I still hope that here with us
you'll find the answers you're looking for.
Come.
Welcome.
Come try our chef Qianqian's cooking.
Go ahead, eat up.
These are all my specialties.
I used Sister Ping's new oven
to try making these madeleines.
Try some too.
Thanks.
This is delicious!
You're so talented.
Can you even get dessert ingredients here?
Let me tell you,
we have the freshest yak milk here,
which is an excellent ingredient.
For everything else, I asked Sister Ping
to order them online for me.
You know,
it's hard to find madeleines,
Basque cheesecake and Opera cake here,
so I decided to make them myself.
I see.
When someone is doing
what they love,
they really do shine.
Eat up, have some food.
You look like you could be from around here.
Actually,
my mother was a local from Nyingchi.
Well then.
Why aren't you staying with your grandmother?
Why come work at my shop instead?
I've never met my grandmother.
This is my first time in Nyingchi.
First time in Nyingchi?
I...
my father never brought me to Tibet.
He never told me anything
about my mother.
All I know is
that my mother was from Nyingchi.
Does your father have some dark secret?
Kids, don't make wild guesses.
I don't know either.
He's always so secretive about it.
Whenever I ask him
about my mother and grandmother,
he gets angry.
I've always been confused.
I can't understand
why he reacts so strongly.
So.
Have you ever seen your mother?
No.
My father said
that my mother
died from complications during my birth.
She only left one photo for me.
Whenever I see girls
being close with their mothers,
I wonder...
If my mother were still alive today,
she would be
53 years old now.
What would she look like?
So I decided
to visit my mother's hometown
and search for traces of her past.
I know this place very well.
I'll get the whole village to help you find information.
For a little brat, you've got quite an attitude.
Sit down.
You think you know better than me?
No.
Ding Nian, don't worry,
Sister Ping will take care of it.
Thank you.
Eat up.
What made you
decide to run away from home?
My daughter is home.
Look, I've made a table full of dishes for you.
Come, let's eat.
Come, sweetheart.
Dad needs to talk to you about something.
Look, it's been two years since you graduated.
You said you wanted to take the graduate entrance exam,
and I supported you,
but you didn't get in, did you?
It doesn't matter.
But with your major,
you shouldn't let it go to waste,
you should put it to good use.
As it happens, there's a public institution exam
for the Teachers' College Elementary School,
and Dad has already registered you for it.
What?
Isn't that great?
You're a proper graduate
from the Teachers' College Art Department,
so becoming an elementary school teacher there makes perfect sense.
Didn't I tell you I want to be an illustrator?
It won't affect anything,
you can teach and paint at the same time,
isn't that the best of both worlds?
Look, at this Normal University Elementary School,
being an elementary school teacher
is both stable and relaxing.
And in the future when you get married.
Who are you throwing that at?
You're so disrespectful.
Why are you always like this
since I was little?
You arrange everything in my life.
When I was young,
I liked sports,
but you insisted I learn dancing.
I preferred short hair,
but you made me keep it long.
When I grew up,
I wanted to apply to a university in Beijing,
but you wouldn't let me, saying it was too far.
I wanted to study art design,
but you said it's hard to find a job with that.
You found me
some teaching-oriented art major instead.
I'm already 24 years old,
yet you still control how long my skirts are
and what time I come home at night.
I'm only doing what's best for you, aren't I?
Mom is watching from heaven,
is this really for my own good?
Does your father know you came to Linzhi?
I can't tell him.
My father explicitly forbade me from coming to Tibet.
If he finds out,
he'll definitely drag me back home.
Qianqian.
I've already said no raising chickens,
no chickens allowed.
Why doesn't anyone listen to me?
I saw it could lay eggs,
so I kept it.
Wouldn't it be nice to have fresh eggs every day?
Quick, quick,
get it out of here.
I'll...
I'll do it.
Chicken!
Open the door!
Call Suolang tomorrow
to slaughter it for me.