[English subtitles are available]
[Skip a Beat]
[Episode 15]
Excuse me.
Gu Yi.
Please make way for us.
You can't go in.
Please wait outside.
[Under rescue]
What happened exactly?
I went there after I got a call from Gu Yi.
You need to ask the police about the details.
Mrs. Gu,
Gu Yi got hurt because he wanted to save me.
I'm sorry.
What on earth did my son do wrong
to meet a jinx like you?
Son, you're finally awake.
Qiao...
Qiao Jing.
Where is she?
I want to see her.
Don't worry.
She's fine.
Thanks to her, you've become like this.
Yet you still think about her.
Glad to hear that she's fine.
That's good to hear.
I've always let her down all this time.
No matter what it takes
and to what extent,
I'm willing to pay for it.
Fool.
You're awake.
Why are you sleeping here?
How's the wound on your hand?
It's fine.
How did you find me?
Our phones have turned on
the function of sharing locations with each other.
That day, I saw
you stay in a remote factory.
Moreover, you were in deep water because of Bai Yun.
I felt something was wrong.
So I went there.
I called the police on my way.
Luckily, you're fine.
Lie down. Don't move.
The doctor said you hadn't hurt the vital part.
The wound is not too deep.
But you need to rest more during this period.
This time,
thank you.
I don't want your gratitude.
If possible,
I want a chance to explain.
I was really unaware of
what Bai Yun did before this.
The Gu family has never
despised the child.
When I came to the hospital after knowing you had a miscarriage,
I saw you and Su Juan...
I was too childish and impulsive.
I said those words without further thinking
because I thought you didn't care about our child.
Qiao Jing,
I'm sorry.
I should have known that
you are the one who suffers the most
from losing a child.
That day,
why did you
ask me out?
That day,
I was going to propose to you.
This ring
should be on your finger.
I'm not forcing you to say yes.
If you give me another chance,
it will be good enough.
I'm back.
How did it go?
-Yes. How did it go?
-Yes.
Ms. Qiao was fine.
Mr. Gu would be hospitalized for a few days.
Poor Mr. Gu.
Mr. Gu said
the person in charge of the Great Project had arrived in Nancheng.
We must finalize the proposal within a week.
Work hard, everyone,
so that Mr. Gu can have a good rest.
Okay.
Come on. Keep it up.
OK. Come on. Keep it up.
The incident
must have something to do with the Bai family.
Bai Yun is already jailed.
Why is she still trying to look for trouble?
We can't let her go easily.
The police are still investigating
who the mastermind is.
It's just speculation for the time being.
How is Gu Yi?
I heard his waist had been stabbed.
The doctor said he was fine
but needed some rest.
This time, he really threw caution to the wind
for the sake of you.
It seems that
he's not on the same side as Bai Yun.
I misunderstood him.
Are you now pitying him?
If you still like each other so much,
why don't you take the opportunity to make up?
But many problems between us
haven't been solved yet.
But now,
I want to give each of us another possibility.
No one knows well about love.
But if you follow your heart,
nothing will go wrong.
We've got news from the police.
The Bai family didn't force Qiao Jing
to declare the letter of understanding.
Those thugs didn't know anything either.
If not the Bai family,
who could it be?
How are you? Are you feeling better now?
No big deal. I'll be fine after a while.
Aunt Fang.
You two talk.
I'll get the medicine for you.
Okay.
Be careful, Aunt Fang.
Tell me, what is it?
Nothing.
I'm here to check if your waist can function normally.
It's better than yours.
You were really heroic.
You won a big victory even in the face of a large number of enemies.
Are you really not afraid of death?
No, I'm afraid.
But I had only one thought in my mind at that moment.
It was to protect her.
Awesome.
I'm so impressed.
Are you here to plead for Bai Yun again?
No one can influence your decision, can they?
Besides,
Yun is willing to bear
all the consequences.
What else can others do?
Am I right?
I'm here to tell you
that Chairman Gu
has fully handed over the Great Project to Su Juan.
How could that be possible?
I've worked hard on the project for a year.
How could my dad give it to him?
You're now injured and hospitalized.
Su Juan will certainly not let go of this project.
[Anxia Group]
How is Mr. Gu?
It's a pity
for him to quit this time.
Mr. Gu needs to take some rest.
Before he recovers,
I'll be totally in charge of the project.
Okay.
Please.
Mr. Ren.
Mr. Gu.
The proposal of Anxia
is the best proposal I've ever seen.
We won't disappoint your company.
The bidding this time will be a cutthroat one.
Those who will attend the bidding are all the tycoons of the industry.
Don't underestimate them.
Trust our strength.
I'm full of confidence.
[Anxia Group]
Your ability is obvious to all.
I trust you.
Wish you success in the bidding.
Sure.
Goodbye.
How is it?
The wound was torn.
I've taken care of it.
I'll leave first then.
Thank you.
You were too reckless.
If I hadn't been there,
what would have happened to the project?
It's everyone's hard work.
I can't disappoint them.
If you're worried,
you can stay here
and take care of me personally.
You don't even listen to me.
What's the use of staying here?
I listen. I don't dare to not.
I'll listen to every one of your words.
Have a good rest at home.
I'll go to the company to keep an eye on the project.
Okay.
He still minds what happened to Bai Yun.
Don't take it to heart.
What about you? What do you think?
Bai Yun did something wrong,
so she has to bear the consequences.
But there's one thing
I feel fishy about.
Bai Yun told the police that
she found out about your pregnancy
from Su Juan.
How could that be possible?
I never told him I was pregnant.
But Su Juan had been around you these days.
Maybe he got some inklings.
But why did he do that?
First, he made use of Bai Yun
to sow discord between us.
After I was hospitalized,
he then took away the Great Project.
So far,
he's the biggest beneficiary
of everything.
H-He's not that kind of person.
Qiao Jing.
People change.
If you look at him objectively,
you'll find
he's not that simple.
Gu Yi is indeed reluctant to give up on this project.
The Bai family is no more useful either.
If we want to dominate him,
we have to put more effort.
Don't worry, Uncle Jiang.
Everything is going as planned.
[Su Juan]
Are you free tomorrow?
What happened?
I wanted to get off the bed and put on my pyjamas,
but I fell.
Can you help me?
M-My wound hurts.
Come on. Let me help you.
What are you doing?
Don't be so petty.
Let me hold you for a while.
This ring
was designed for you.
I know you're not ready yet.
Whether you accept me or not,
it belongs to you.
It only belongs to you.
Let me put it on you.
You're here.
I have something to ask you.
Can we talk later?
I want you to come somewhere with me.
Where?
Today is my mother's death anniversary.
Mr. Gu, that's all for the proposal.
What else do you think needs to amend?
Well done.
We've worked hard for a year.
Tomorrow is the time to hand in the paper.
I believe Anxia will gain the final victory.
[Thank you for watching]
Declare your bidding document for the Great Project
to the public,
or you'll suffer the consequences.
Who are you?
Mr. Gu.
I'll only give you 30 minutes.
[Sorry, the subscriber you dialled is not in the service area.]
She's not home either.
What happened?
Has she been kidnapped again?
Inform the police to track the anonymous call immediately
and investigate the competitors of the bidding first.
Yes.
Could they have taken this in advance
to trick us?
I put this necklace on her last night.
What should we do?
I can't risk her life.
Let's declare the document like what they requested.
No way.
We've been preparing for the Great Project for so long.
If we declare the document, we are considered to have given up the bidding.
All of our efforts will be in vain.
Of course, I won't give up the project in vain.
I have a plan.
Let's have a meeting.
It's an emergency.
We need to combine the eliminated versions and turn them
into a new proposal
in the shortest time.
Hide all the questionable points and highlights
and make it half-genuine and half-sham.
Don't let them discover any loose ends.
Mr. Gu, it is too urgent.
We can't complete it in time.
You have to.
Tang Ping, put your work aside
and give the Design Department full support.
Okay.
Mr. Gu, we'll finish the task as soon as possible.
Xiang Sese.
Draft a few PR plans immediately.
Once we locate Qiao Jing,
distribute the news immediately
and minimize the negative impact.
Okay.
Time is running out.
Move. Hurry.
[The Grave of the Loving Mother, Su Nian
Su Juan, the Son]
Aunt Su.
I'm sorry.
I didn't come to see you until now.
My mum liked you very much.
Unfortunately,
she didn't get to see you before her last breath.
The Gu family
was a drag on her whole life.
Mr. Gu.
Have you checked?
We did it according to your instruction.
It has no problem at all.
Send it now.
Okay.
Have you been with Gu Yi these days?
He got hurt because of me.
I should take care of him.
Just take care of him?
What are you trying to say?
Gratitude isn't love.
I'm afraid you might get confused.
I'm grateful to him.
But actually,
before you came back,
I had already been into him.
So,
that's why you never responded to me.
We've known each other for so long.
Isn't it worth more than these three years?
Love can't be measured by time.
You and I
have missed too many things.
Why would we miss them?
It was all because of the Gu family, because of Gu Yi.
How could you fall in love with him?
So,
I'm also a pawn for you to take revenge on Gu Yi,
right?
I never wanted to make use of you.
Were you aware of
my pregnancy long ago?
Yes.
You didn't tell me,
so I didn't expose you.
What about Bai Yun?
You abetted her, didn't you?
No.
Yes.
I admit I let it slip.
I really didn't expect her to do that.
Such a lame excuse.
Do you believe it yourself?
You'd rather trust Gu Yi
than me?
The Su Juan I liked
will never come back anymore.
Gosh.
Tang Ping, come here.
Ru, Yang Yang, look!
[The Great AI + Future Amusement Park]
Oh no.
Go in!
He is the one
who took the wrong USB flash drive
and sent out our real proposal.
What's going on?
Mr. Gu,
there were too many versions.
I sent it wrong by mistake.
Have you taken it back?
Yes, I am doing it.
But I guess it won't help much.
I've been emphasizing the checking.
Why would you still make a mistake?
I'm sorry, Mr. Gu.
Dad.
Stop it!
He's still injured.
The leak of the proposal was an accident.
I'll take full responsibility.
But dad,
Qiao Jing is still missing.
I need to ensure her safety.
Qiao Jing is important.
Yet thousands of employees in the company
are nothing to you.
Because of your mistake,
all their efforts have gone in vain.
On what basis can you bear the consequences?
Yi,
you were indeed too impulsive this time.
No matter what,
you couldn't sell the company
for the sake of a woman.
Yes.
You don't own Anxia.
Do you have any respect for us?
Dad.
You were not in the company all day.
Where have you been?
Today is my mother's death anniversary.
I went to visit her.
Gu Yi,
what happened with the leak of the proposal?
Mr. Gu heard that Qiao Jing was kidnapped.
So he sold the project to save her.
That couldn't be.
Qiao Jing went to visit the grave with me.
She should be at home now.
She was with you?
Why couldn't I reach out to her by phone?
The graveyard is on the mountain.
Maybe the signal was bad.
Yi, you are such a fool.
Wait. Why didn't you discuss it with me
when such a big event occurred?
You just couldn't get in touch with Qiao Jing for a while,
yet you already sold a big project of the company.
If anything happens to her,
you'll surely implicate the whole Gu family for her.
From tomorrow onwards,
you don't have to go to the company anymore.
I'm glad that you're fine.
Sorry.
I wanted to talk to Su Juan today.
I didn't expect...
Let's go home first.
Let's go.
Su Juan took me to the graveyard today
on the spur of the moment.
No one else knew about it.
And the shooting distance and angle
show that this photo couldn't be taken far away.
You said you had called me many times
during that period.
But my phone didn't ring at all.
He must have blocked the signal.
Su Juan is indeed mean.
He even made use of his mother's death anniversary.
I guess Chen Lan who sent out the real proposal
is also his man.
I'm sorry.
I should have told you my whereabouts.
We didn't do anything wrong.
If it started over again,
I would still make the same choice.
As long as you are fine.
Tomorrow is the bidding.
Are we really giving up
the bidding for the Great Project?
Wasn't there an older version?
Why don't we ask the employees
to work overtime and amend it?
Or we can contact the Great
and ask them to spare us a few more days.
Then we...
Enough.
Juan.
What do you think?
I think at this point,
we can't turn the table anymore.
But we can consider
collaborating with the company that wins the bid in the end.
The Great Land is not a small project.
Besides us,
it's most likely to fall into Jiahe's hands.
This is feasible.
Our proposal was leaked,
but
we have more experience than Jiahe.
I'm sure they won't refuse us.
Right.
Young people are indeed quick-witted.
In this way, we can get a share
and minimize the company's losses.
How about this?
Juan, you replace Gu Yi
and carry on with the project.
Dad...
[Anxia Group]
After working hard for half a year,
we're now back to square one.
Do you think Jiahe did what happened yesterday
for a destructive competition?
They knew Ms. Qiao's whereabouts in advance
and took photos to deceive us.
I don't think so.
I think
it might not be done by outsiders.
It depends on who got more benefits in the end.
Mr. Gu.
Notify the Design Department and Project Department for a meeting.
We can't give up the Great Project yet.
Mr. Gu.
Are you sure about the meeting?
What do you mean?
Su Juan, why are you sitting here?
You came at the right time.
The transfer order for you has been issued.
The properties in Wanyuan District are almost done.
Dad asked you to keep an eye on them.
I tried to persuade him.
But he's on the warpath lately.
So for the time being,
you have to suffer a bit.
The Great Project hasn't been solved yet.
I can't leave.
The project has been handed over to me.
Don't worry.
I won't let your efforts go to waste.
Also,
take your photo with you.
Since I was hospitalized,
you have been setting me up.
I underestimated you.
I don't understand what you're talking about.
Since you like this position so much,
I'll give it to you.
But I hope you can sit tight.
Don't fall from the position too fast.
Su Juan.
I'm now asking you.
Did you feel any remorse
in front of Aunt Su's grave yesterday?
Why should I?
I just took the girl she used to like
to visit her.
You used her to lie to me.
I did not lie.
Yesterday was her death anniversary.
Then you shouldn't have done that.
No matter how you take revenge on the Gu family,
you shouldn't use Aunt Su as your pawn.