[English subtitles are available]
[Skip a Beat]
[Episode 19]
This ungrateful bastard.
You treated him so well.
How dare he do such a thing?
No, I have to ask him now.
What did the Gu family do to him?
Mother.
People change.
We can’t understand nor stop them.
Zhou Rui and I
are no longer on the same path.
But we can't just let it go.
With Chen Lan's testimony,
we've found a breakthrough.
Anxia withdrew the lawsuit.
How come?
Yang Yang said the president just received a reply from the lawyer.
Su Juan and the others wanted Chen Lan
to take the rap.
But Chen Lan told the truth,
so Zhou Rui must also be held accountable.
Anxia is withdrawing the lawsuit now
to save Zhou Rui
and remove him from the matter.
Su Juan's reach in the company is outrageous.
Let's go to your dad now.
I want to see
if there's really no one who can deal with him.
Mom, take a seat.
Dad needs to rest now.
We'd better leave him alone.
I'll settle this myself.
Why did you withdraw the lawsuit?
I didn't want to deal with
the mess my predecessor left me anymore.
Plus, Anxia's reputation couldn't take the hit.
You wanted to stop
because your true colors were showing, right?
Let me tell you.
This concerns the company's interests.
You can't do this.
Su Juan!
I can't do this?
How are you talking to me like this?
As Mr. Gu or as my brother?
Before you withdrew the lawsuit,
did you ask Dad?
Did he agree?
He's already halfway inside his coffin.
He doesn't have time for this.
He's your dad too.
I'm just stating the facts.
If there's nothing else, I'll get going,
my little brother.
What are you doing?
I can't stop you if you want to drink.
But I can drink with you.
If you drink one bottle, I'll drink two bottles.
If you keep drinking,
your health will suffer.
What about you?
What about your health?
Don't hurt yourself when you're in a bad mood.
Okay.
Tomorrow, I'll go to the company's other shareholders.
I don't believe everyone will just sit and watch.
Hello, Mom.
Gu Yi, your dad is dying.
[Emergency Operation In-progress
How is my dad?
We've tried our best.
My condolences.
Brother.
My Dad raised me
to be the successor of Anxia.
He wanted to have a say in everything I did.
I didn't want to listen,
so I always quarreled with him.
When I grew up,
I found that he always made my mom angry.
So I grew more and more
resentful towards him.
Even when he fell sick,
I didn't visit him.
If I didn't see him,
I could see him another time.
If we couldn't reach an agreement,
we could talk another time.
But now,
he's gone.
There's no other time anymore.
Qiao Jing,
I don't have a father anymore.
I wish I had gone to see him that day.
Although he was mad at me,
I could at least have seen him again.
You still have me.
Everyone,
this is the will
President Gu made before he died.
Next, I will read it for you.
I, Gu Nan,
am making this will
to prevent conflicts regarding the inheritance.
First, all my property and savings
are joint owned property between my wife and I.
From the part that belongs to me,
one million shall be set aside
as a startup fund for Gu Yi.
The rest
will be used to form a Gu Family trust fund.
Each member of the Gu family can receive
100,000 RMB per month.
Second, I own
80% of the shares
of Anxia Holdings,
of which 10% will go to my brother, Gu Yu,
10% to my sister, Gu Ying,
and 10% to Gu Yi.
The remaining 50%
will be inherited by my eldest son, Su Juan.
Third, Su Juan will take over
as the President of Anxia Group.
That's all for the will.
Impossible.
Gu Nan wouldn't leave the company to him.
Why not?
Your son has been kicked out of the company.
Would he leave it to him?
There must be something wrong with the will.
[Will]
Impossible.
This will has definitely been forged.
This is the original will
President Gu gave me before he died.
When your husband passed away,
you didn't shed a single tear.
Now, the original will is right in front of you.
You still want to question its authenticity?
My brother is so unlucky
to have married a woman like you.
Enough!
I'm telling the truth.
It's fake.
Su Juan must have forged it.
It's fake!
Mom, I respect Dad's decisions.
Let's go.
It's impossible.
Let go!
Su Juan must have forged that will.
He's long prepared
to steal what belongs to you.
Lawyer Zhao has been working diligently
for Dad for over 20 years.
How could he help Su Juan fabricate it?
But I don’t understand.
How could your dad leave the company to him?
The company must be yours.
Dad must be disappointed in me.
Son, don't think like that.
Your dad just...
It's okay, Mom.
No matter what decision he made,
I'll accept it.
Madam, Mr. Gu.
President Gu left some belongings in his study.
What should we do?
Look at your dad.
He didn't like me.
Why did he bring this photo around with him in his wallet
everywhere he went?
When I first met your dad,
he was a boss of a small company.
He had no money
and no backers.
He wooed me
just with his mouth.
I must have lost my mind
when I insisted on marrying him.
In the end,
the business became bigger and bigger.
Our relationship
got worse and worse.
I fought and quarreled with him
for a whole lifetime.
How could he leave just like that?
Mom.
You still have me.
Are you hungry? I'll cook some noodles for you.
I'm not hungry.
Don't bother. Have a rest.
What is this?
It's a birthday gift from my dad.
It's the first time we played with legos together.
I didn't expect
that to be the last time.
Later, there was once I quarreled with him.
I was so angry that I broke it.
I didn't expect my dad
to gather all the pieces back.
He's kept them until now.
President Gu has always loved you.
Qiao Jing, let's put it back together.
OK.
Lawyer Zhao, we're not suspecting you.
It's just that
I thought about the will all night.
I still don't understand
President Gu's arrangements.
I didn't know beforehand
that his physical condition was not very good.
When I arrived,
he handed me
a sealed document,
saying the will was inside.
He told me to keep it safe
and not to open it until he passed away.
Was Su Juan there?
Only President Gu and I were there.
This will
should have come from himself.
I know you have doubts about Su Juan.
But the fact is that
President Gu died of an illness.
It has nothing to do with anyone.
To be honest,
I also think President Gu’s arrangements are weird.
But who knows
what President Gu was thinking?
What are you doing here?
I just went to see Yun.
This is from her.
Qiao Jing,
there's something I should have told you a long time ago.
But I was too weak back then.
This is the only way
I can apologize to you.
I know
this cannot make up for the hurt I caused you.
I don't expect you to forgive me.
But I still want to apologize to you.
I didn't understand this before.
You were inferior to me in every aspect,
so how did you get Gu Yi's love?
Now I understand
I was the one
who was inferior in every aspect.
So,
I sincerely wish the best for the two of you.
Yun was sentenced to two years for assault.
She really let it go.
You must be happy
to see her like this.
Even she has come to terms with things.
How long more are you going to wallow in self-pity?
Gu Yi really thinks of you like a brother.
He is the last person you should hurt.
What do you know about us?
I don't know anything.
But I still want to tell you
to stop hurting the people who love you
in the name of love.
The handover ceremony is about to begin.
We can't let down our guard.
Is there any news from Gu Yi?
They went to see Zhao Ming.
What's the use of seeing Zhao Ming?
When Gu Nan was alive,
there was someone with him at all times.
Even if I had contact with him,
there's only one will.
The division of the inheritance
is final.
What tricks can he play?
He's here.
Mr. Su.
President Gu's important documents,
certificates, and safe
are here.
Thank you, Assistant Lü.
Where does this go?
I didn't find it on the diagram
I remember when I did this with my dad,
there were just enough pieces.
Plus, the color scheme of this castle
is grey and beige.
This extra red piece
doesn't seem to be part of the original.
This is the only one.
It's normal to have extra pieces
in this kind of toy, right?
Are you thinking too much?
Mom, after Dad passed away,
did anyone touch his things?
Since he fell ill,
I've been the one tidying up his room.
No one else has been inside.
Your dad was the only one who has opened that cabinet.
Right, the housekeeper told me
that half a month ago,
your dad opened the cabinet
and rummaged through the things inside.
My dad never does things without a reason.
There must be important information
in this extra piece.
President Gu always has his reasons for doing things.
This piece is number 0407.
Do you know what it means?
0407.
This is our wedding anniversary.
That means
it's not a coincidence
that this is the only extra piece.
Your dad
has always liked riddles.
Let's go back now.
Take these numbers
and find your dad's safe
to see if it's the password.
Okay.
Assistant Lü.
Who gave you the right
to send all the documents and the safe
to Su Juan?
Madam,
Mr. Su has taken over Anxia.
It’s reasonable to hand them to him.
You...
Mom.
Assistant Lü, you can go now.
Thank you.
Mom.
No, I have to get everything back
from Su Juan.
Mom, it won't be easy
to get them back from Su Juan.
If we pay extra attention
to the safe,
he will get suspicious.
It's our honor
to work with Anxia.
I’m also looking forward to this collaboration.
Mrs. Gu, you can’t go in.
Mr. Su is in a meeting.
Mr. Su.
Sorry, I couldn’t stop her.
Su Juan.
Gu Nan and I bought a villa
in Mingyuehu Resort ten years ago.
Doesn't it count as a joint owned property?
He promised me
the three rows in front are mine.
Where is the property title deed?
Mom, why are you making a fuss here?
It's embarrassing.
We don't want that anymore.
We don't?
Do you like getting the shorter end of the stick?
You don't want anythng.
You weren't worried even though you lost the company.
Now, you don’t even want the house.
Aunt Fang, I’m in a meeting.
Can we talk about this later?
When?
When you've transferred the house under your name?
I'm telling you.
If you don't give me the property title deed,
I'll sue you for theft.
Mom, let's go first.
Go where?
I'm not going anywhere
if I don't get that title deed.
Mr. Su,
I think you have something to deal with.
Let's talk next time.
Take care.
Su Juan, the title deed.
Aunt Fang,
I will give you what you want.
But I hope
this is the last time.
If this happens again,
don't make a scene at the company.
Dad's stuff is all here.
Do you remember which cabinet it was in?
It's been too long.
I don't remember.
I only remember
it was in an old
and big safe.
This is it.
There are many confidential documents in it.
My time is limited.
And I have a lot of things to deal with in the company.
These are Anxia's accounts from the past ten years.
I've taken inventory.
There's nothing else.
It must be this one then.
These are the official seals.
Aunt Fang, you’d better figure out
where the thing you want is.
Mom, is it that cabinet, 0407?
I remember Dad said
the things in the cabinet
are all gifts for you.
Yes, it must be that.
Are you sure?
Yes.
It seems that I don't have
what you want.
Please go back.
Let's go.
Don't forget your bag.
At first, I thought 0407 was the password.
But then I realized
it wasn't the password.
It's the serial number of the safe.
Yes.
We saw that safe
when your dad and I
went on a trip together.
The number was the same as our wedding anniversary.
I thought it was fate,
so I bought it.
I didn't expect
the clue your dad put in so much effort to leave
to be an empty safe.
My dad would never
do anything without a reason.
Maybe the things inside
had been taken away.
Damn it.
Lawyer Zhao.
Mr. Gu, is Mrs. Gu here?
Yes.
Mrs. Gu.
Lawyer Zhao.
After you left that day,
I checked President Gu's will again,
carefully.
I found something.
Lawyer Zhao.
Everything is inside.
Before I pass away,
no one is to open it.
When President Gu gave me the will,
the seal was yellow.
But the seal on the current copy
is new.
I didn't realize it then.
The more I think about it, the weirder it is.
I suspect the will had been swapped.
The only one who could do this
is Su Juan.
But these are just speculations.
We don't have solid evidence
that he forged the will.
The clue my dad left is a dead end, too.
Lawyer Zhao,
haven't you been taking care
of Gu Nan's safe and documents?
Not entirely.
I'm just in charge of
his art and collections.
There's a safe number 0407.
Do you remember it?
The last time President Gu stored things
was in that safe.
He stored a painting.
Painting?
I work overtime and stay up late every day.
When will this end?
Stop skiving off.
Mr. Su’s inauguration ceremony is coming.
We still have a lot to do.
Poor Mr. Gu.
He lost completely this time.
Isn't Mr. Gu starting a business?
Why don't we join his company?
Yes.
Maybe we can even
get a bonus
as his first batch of employees.
Yes.
Ms. Qiao.
Why are you here?
I was just passing by
so I came up to chat with you
and treat you to afternoon tea.
Thank you, Ms. Qiao.
Share it.
Ms. Qiao, we were just talking about you.
We heard that you and Mr. Gu
are starting a business.
Are you still short of people?
Definitely,
if you're willing to come.
What did I say? Thank you again.
Hello?
We'll be there in five minutes.
Another project meeting?
Ms. Qiao, we have to go.
How long will you be gone for?
I'll wait for you.
It'll be half an hour.
Wait for us.
Alright.
Okay, let's go.
Let's go.
Go on.
See you.