[Eternal Rebirths]
[Episode 13]
[Playing the Game]
After all that,
I still have to take the bus back.
Who are you guys?
You're Brother Fan, right?
We're Brother Fei's men.
Brother Fei's boss
wants to invite you for a drink.
Your boss?
What if I don't want to go?
If you don't want to go,
we can't guarantee
anything will happen
to your girlfriend, Yun Mo.
I haven't seen Brother Fei
for a couple of days,
and he's really surprised me.
Please don't make it hard for us.
We're just the messengers.
Alright.
If you want to play,
I'll play along.
Just don't regret it later.
Brother Fan, please go in.
Brother Fei and the others are waiting.
This is it?
This bar's nice.
Handsome guy, we meet again!
Looks like we're really fated.
Come on, sit with me.
Oh, it's the sexy motorcycle lady.
Go ahead.
You're so young,
but you're bold.
Fan, am I beautiful?
If you keep this up,
I might be out of control.
Out of control?
What are you going to do to me?
Boss Dong!
I told you
this guy's not
just an ordinary schooler!
Not ordinary?
But he's still just a high school kid.
Now that he's on my turf,
I'll see
what he can stir up.
That's true.
He's weird,
still, he's just a student.
Once you step in this time,
he will suffer the consequences!
Handsome guy, you're quite bold.
I like that.
If you like it,
I can be bolder.
Alright then,
I'll give you a chance.
Gladly.
Just say it.
Let's play a game.
If you win, I'll go with you.
But if you lose,
we'll make you pay
for hurting Fei
and hitting on me.
Deal.
Here we go.
Don't hurt yourself.
Your turn.
Impressive.
What?
Scared?
Handsome guy,
don't end up
hurting your hands.
Don't worry.
I've got plans for this hand later.
Alright.
You're a real man.
I'm going to enjoy this.
So, Miss,
who's winning here?
Alright,
I'll keep my word.
You win, and I'll go with you.
Then let's go.
Be gentle with me later.
Don't worry.
I'll be gentle.
Boss Dong.
How's the setup over there?
Everything's set.
Don't worry.
To ensure nothing goes wrong,
take them all there.
Yes, Boss.
Have some water first.
Or maybe take a shower?
Wait a second.
What are you doing?
What are you up to?
What am I up to? We're already here,
and you're still pretending?
If I'm not mistaken,
you're waiting for Brother Fei, right?
What are you talking about?
I don't understand.
Don't understand?
That's just my personal hobby.
Why?
Don't you like it?
Keep going then.
What are you doing?
This is your last chance to come clean.
What? You gonna kill me?
You can try it.
Where is he?
Fei,
untie me. He ran away.
You!
It's you who tried to mess with me, huh?
Get him!
Hold on.
Wait a second.
What are you doing?
Come on…
♪In my heart♪
♪A brilliant light♪
♪Shines on me♪
♪On the journey home I'm looking for♪
♪Youth♪
♪The undergrowth of the forest♪
♪Flourishing along the long journey♪
♪I can't lose to promises made to myself♪
♪Every sincere embrace must be counted♪
♪Protecting every bit of my purity♪
♪Pushing open the doors that hold me back♪
♪Let youth photosynthesize my life♪
♪Smoothing every scar from a wound♪
♪Let my heart warm♪
♪A soul chilled by the cold♪
♪Vows sink into my heart♪
♪Germinating♪
♪then taking root♪
♪I can't lose to promises made to myself♪
♪Every sincere embrace must be counted♪
♪Protecting every bit of my purity♪
♪Pushing open the doors that hold me back♪
♪Let youth photosynthesize my life♪
♪Smoothing every scar from a wound♪
♪Let my heart warm♪
♪A soul chilled by the cold♪
[Exclusive right of communication through information]
[Belongs to Youku Information Technology (Beijing) Co., Ltd.]