(Blackstone Hotel VIP room card)
(10th floor)
Why don't you hold an umbrella?
I thought the rain was about to stop
Don't catch a cold!
come over
is this new
Didn't you want me to wear black?
Like it?
uh...i like it
Are you worried about getting pregnant?
that's too heavy for us
Then we should get married!
you know i don't like formality
i like you cool
but you're too cool
Do you think it's not good for us now?
you know we're just bored
i want to marry you
Who in this world would
Married to a friend with benefits? Ok?
I like it now!
Doctor Kim is full on Friday
I need a chart of Patient Ting Hee
OK
I am sorry…
he can at 2 o'clock on friday
see you then
Did you meet Dr. Kim yesterday?
yeah...how?
no wonder oh... you look so good in the morning
what's the secret?
You know…
I'm good in bed
You are taking advantage of it!
I am you and I will marry him
You will be able to avoid that demon head "Aunt" far away
You can also fulfill your dream of learning
No! I don't want to be an accessory
i will pay off my debt soon
Then I'm leaving the country
Sorry…
I shouldn't have introduced you to Big Mom
don't say that
if not you
My father didn't have the money for the surgery...he died
Forget about it, I'm happy with my life now
You always have to think of a way!
Oh, look at that hunk
Is he electric discharge with you?
What a turnoff!
keep eating
do you like this
A little more! Don't rub your breasts!
Like this?
Pinch yourself to the point of bulging!
Have! I'm touching it...
Brother is hard!
Is it hard enough? People are excited...
God!
Can you put your finger in it?
Can I have a look at the video footage?
Sorry, the lens is fixed!
How dare you fucking slut steal my guest
- you bitch - what the fuck are you doing?
What? you are fucked
let me go!
Both bitches stop me
Oh shit!
Are the two sluts crazy?
Call me halfway through work?
I answer the phone halfway
She rushed in and pulled my hair!
my beautiful hair
This bitch stole my client again
I must kill her today!
stop!
I didn't steal your customers, they ordered me
Why don't you show off your figure too?
Do you think I don't want to?
That's enough for the two of you. It's our prime time.
Get back to work!
I have to kill you!
God! so comfortable
oh bro...
put it in now
You are a big GG! people will hurt
Oh...it's awesome, it's so cool...
Fuck bitch, what time is it?
I just stopped by...
Why do you treat me like this?
Don't go back to work yet!
my measurements
34 24 26
The breasts are not big but very straight, so I put silicone pads in my underwear
Uh-huh…
College students can also have... plastic surgery
I'm a water snake with a big ass
No
You have to be a little fleshy so you can hug and touch it.
If I'm too skinny, won't it hurt when our fried rice hits a bone?
Cherry, I heard you have two jobs
certainly!
I'm so good I can work three jobs
Hello!
look what this slut is saying
How fucking rude!
stop talking
Let's keep drinking the bar
your life is better than mine
Look at me, I'm getting old!
let's go together...
Hurrah
Stop talking about that, I have other things to do
You are enough
1 , 2 , 3
Fuck it!
I don't know it's so late, I have to go
Are you leaving already?
Enjoy the food ~ see you tomorrow...
- be careful on the road - bye..
The wine is good to drink! a little more
good enough wine
don't eat that
please i'm starving
- mine's gone - why don't you eat more?
I have something to do
i go with you
goodbye
- Don't be clingy - let others follow...
Good night
The needle will sting a little
what the hell!
I'm sorry you must be in pain...
Hello
There is an appointment at two o'clock
No way! It is not allowed
Appointment times can't be changed, it's not fair to other people
Hey?
Oh...yes!
Is it four o'clock in the afternoon?
Please wait
OK!
I've changed it for you to Friday at four o'clock in the afternoon
see you then!
What are you doing?
You seem to be in a bad mood today, very sensitive
so i want to help you
If patients are allowed to ask for anything
The hospital will be in chaos
I know
But it's 4:00 p.m. on a Friday.
Ok
Why put it here?
please put it on the counter
you and him must be fine
you guys look very close
I can't keep a straight face in front of him
he is our boss
Makes sense!
We have no special relationship, don't think about it!
I didn't think about it even though he was rich
He is divorced with two children
Nurse Yun
can you be quiet
i don't mean to make you sad
Are you kidding me?
This month's performance is only half of last month's
We can't even pay the electricity bill! Die thirty-eight!
It's not our fault!
It's been a bad time
- the guest doesn't want more than 10 minutes - how dare you talk back
you are the worst
Your guests certainly won't come back...
Because you keep repeating, the same words suck
oh... i'm coming...
like a chicken
stop cliche
Don't be stupid! do it with heart
Caidie, you need to show more
How many times do I have to say that?
you owe the most
so that the debt can be paid off
No matter how long it takes, I will pay it off
so don't tell me that anymore
i know some of you
Sleeping with clients behind my back
If I catch you, you will die!
Understand?
hi... i'm here
Dear
you fucking bitches
Why make my baby angry?
Do it right!
How is it going?
What do you think?
I'm rich so it's not a problem at all
- bring it in - yes!
get ready soon
If performance declines further
I want to get back the money I borrowed from you
you know what i mean
Hello?
Seung Sik?
What do you want me to do today to make you happy?
clear
do you like this
Do you want me to suck my dick like this?
Brother can't come out like this!
damn it!
Hello...Zhu Hao?
oh...i see
I'll start first
I mean, I can't I might get caught
Like you said
I meet other girls and don't want phone sex anymore
and then?
boring
They are too childish and immature
Let's meet!
I have to pay first, right?
how much is it? 20 dollars?
no? That $30?
Well, Zheng Gu
oh oh i shouldn't have said my real name
It's okay, no one knows anyway
Eunmi...
Only I know your real name is Eunmi, right?
certainly!
look! You are different to me!
something i have to tell you
What's up?
I…
I'm shy when I see strangers
So you dare not do video?
It's Luo
I will transfer the money to you now, please check
Let's discuss how to meet tomorrow
Okay, bye
Please use
thanks
Why only order one?
It tastes delicious when shared by two people
for you
We haven't dated outside in a long time
what's wrong with you it doesn't feel like you
What should I do normally?
Am I the sweetest man in the world?
Oh really?
If you marry me, you will win the lottery!
I don't want to win the lottery!
All right…
I have to go
Why do you have to work part-time at night?
you have been busy during the day
Just tell me if you need money
here we go again
We agreed to respect our respective space
Ah... You said you have something for me?
At this
These…
i think you may need lo
thank you very much
try this baby
I think you must be very handsome in clothes
Why are you buying these?
Wouldn't it be better to plant cash directly?
I'm going to travel to Japan next week
don’t worry
i will work hard to make money
i will give you cash
How nice! You can just wear it for a trip to Japan
You are in great shape! Looks good on anything!
seriously…
you know how to make me happy
come here i'll make you happy
Do you want to ride a motorcycle?
- what? - let's take the car out and play
how? Isn't it cool?
Mmmmm... that's awesome!
- come on, baby - hurry up?
Oh my God
cool
if you touch another woman i will kill you
baby i only have you
you sure?
certainly! go make money
I am Nabi
How old are you？
20 years old
to be honest
I'm 30
so
What exactly do you want sir?
show off what you're good at
I'm wearing a red thong now
The front is mesh...
Do you usually dress like this?
Sometimes I wear more lewd ones
for example?
i have a pair of panties
There are holes in the "vital parts"
you are so funny...
what! Have a little imagination
There is a hole in the panties, it's at the...little sister
You don't need to take it off at all, you can go straight to Huanglong...
For example, in places like subway toilets
You push my legs and put my cock in it
What a lewd nympho!
Isn't that what you're calling for?
not every man is the same
Yeah? Want me to be your psychologist?
Are you kidding me?
- I said that's not what I want - so what do you want?
I think you have dialed the wrong number
This is not a normal phone number. It may not be what you are looking for
You can just hang up without wasting money
Why don't you talk about who you're actually dating right now
And there are people in bed?
what are you talking about?
Forget it, Nabi
hello...
Hey…
(How long are you going? I'm waiting for you)
understood
Are you alright?
Can't you have a drink with me tonight?
please?
Well... since you have a date, so be it
you are hot
you have a dirty ass
oh! I'm freezing Hojo!
sugar, give it to me
Take it all!
Fuck bitch!
leave!
I made soup for you
Do not be like that
I have no mouth
What about your hospital work?
I leave early today
Dr. Jin didn't ask?
i made up excuses
What the hell happened?
Didn't I say yesterday, I don't know those people at all
Didn't I also advise you, don't invite guests to meet outside
I can only be unlucky!
i should have guessed
He has no reason to give me so much money
Don't you call the police?
How can I call the police!
Did you see their faces clearly?
do you know?
they took me to a room
and make me drink something
Then I'm at a loss
I got dizzy and took a shower
then unconscious
what happened?
etc.
Hello! where have you been
groan...it hurts
What are you doing here?
did you do it
what are you saying?
Did you ask someone to beat Tangtang?
You are such a coward
Don't you know what that bitch is doing out there?
You shouldn't have done that, make her face
It's that bitch who stole my guests
Where did you learn it, are you pulling people's legs like this?
You are the smelly old crow!
What quail? Want to rebel?
you're just a rotten chicken
Pay back the money you owe and leave your grandma!
When you use the money, you never think about paying it back? right?
You are cornered!
That shouldn't hurt her face, she still has to work during the day
She's trying her best to find a way to pay you back
Hold! so i just want to warn you
so funny! i want you to give me my money back
goodbye
oh...bye...
I'm so sorry, sir
cheer up at work
- do you know? - I'm very sorry
Haven't had lunch yet?
I eat when I'm hungry because I eat alone
Do you want to eat with me next time?
really?
Is it seaweed rice rolls? looks delicious
Do you want it? i have another
Really can? How much do I eat?
certainly
I'm surprised...
What's up?
You work hard!
When you are admitted to be a doctor, you will hire me as a nurse
maybe a lifetime
don't talk stupid
I will wait no matter how long you take
to hire me...
Somewhat off topic but…
Doctor Kim is very lonely
What did you say?
He's been depressed ever since his wife committed suicide
Is it suicide?
i thought they were divorced
do not you know?
i shouldn't have said
They...are not divorced
she actually committed suicide
Looks like Dr Kim loves his wife very much and is obsessed with her
The story goes like this...
Hmm... please just pretend you don't know
After all, it's his painful past. I may be talking too much.
I just came
Where are you?
Are you kidding?
cut!
Hey…
do i look ok Ugly?
How did you get out of the hospital?
you know i can't afford the hospital
But still have to...
Are you really okay?
It's fake!
ha?
make mom feel guilty
You are too ridiculous!
It hurts me so cheap!
take a break you look tired
to you
Why are you so emotional recently?
don't do that at work
Who cares? We are in love!
in love?
What happened this time?
Do you feel good talking like that?
I'm leaving!
I'm not finished yet!
it's hot outside
What holiday is it today? so early?
Did coming early annoy you again?
By the way, why haven't I talked to Cherry yet?
How would I know
Every time she makes money, she loses contact
Die thirty-eight!
I say let's talk!
sit down
you're right
I should pay attention to my words and deeds in the workplace
Also, can you stop talking about marriage?
it is good!
Let's live together, if having in-laws and children bothers you
I'll help you get a suite and give you living expenses!
What nonsense are you talking about?
-  what? - do you want to punish me?
Because I love you!
i don't want to lie to you
i hope your life is better
stop making those sex calls
who are you?
are you spying on me
You have sex with clients, like Nurse Li, don't you?
Ok?
i knew you would
I can't believe you're digging my privacy
We're fucked!
Ah, where are you going?
Does anyone know where Cherry lives?
did you call her
result?
her phone is off
Do you know where Cherry lives?
have no idea
i heard she lives in a prefab
maybe she doesn't want to connect with people
Look at Luo again
If I find her, I'll break her legs
Hello
- Oh, it's too hot! - oh my god
I shouldn't bother you like this
do you have burns
no i'm fine
How clumsy!
i took off your pants
Your big GG is right in front of me
i start licking it
you're right
You really want to know my story?
i really don't want to
we are done tonight
sorry last time
i dirty your clothes
please don't get me wrong i am happy to be with you
you don't have to be so polite
And~
I know no one in the company likes me
Not at all! Who said this?
It has been a long time
I'm used to it too
I'm very sorry
don't say that i'm fine
do you know?
I really like you
you are pretty
me?
Thank you
what happened?
What's wrong?
you look sad and gloomy
will i?
I'm going to the bathroom
Eun Joo, be careful
it's ok i can go by myself
Eun Joo...
Eun Joo
so i don't know what to do
Eun Joo?
Eun Joo, don't you need to go home?
(Today is Sunday, hope you rest more)
What are you doing?
You like playing tricks!
Are you crazy? What if someone sees it?
look at us
Anyway, everyone should know about us
Do you think I don't know?
I know you well even if you don't tell me
Think I'll be here at the beck and call?
Dare to play me?
Nurse Li has a call for you
Find me?
It's the patient who had the nose surgery that day.
Oh
thanks
where were you last night
talk!
Are you cool?
I just asked you a question!
I said your body is getting more and more flirtatious
Because you're a real whore!
He rudely pushed me against the wall
take off my pants
start raping me
I'm totally insensitive, I'm not mentally prepared
he is rough and hurts me
I have goosebumps all over
I keep shaking
i'm going to kill him
after he raped me
stare at me coldly
like watching a dirty whore
i guess he is angry
i know...but not because of him
i'm going to call him
Is this the only reason?
i didn't go home but nothing happened
Then why didn't you tell him?
He doesn't trust me anymore anyway
Why do you think so?
men are always subjective
to come like this
I don't think it's easy to leave him
Do you want to break up with him?
I have no idea
Break up if you're not sure!
who are you?
Why are you interested in my private life?
stop calling me
I won't take it
if you want it like this
It's me Junhe
what! impossible!
maybe i'm not
talk next time
goodbye
Must ×, Hey Hey Erf you,
What service do you want sir?
Is sir there?
Then let me make a sound?
wife
it's you right?
wife...
husband?
How can you trick me into doing this behind my back!
i didn't sell myself
just sex calls
I do this...
can pay your hospital bills
I'll wait and come back
Wow! Butterfly
Call me again if you want someone like Nabi to serve you
Shut up!
Screw you!
Thank you so much!
There is no need to collect money, right?
the bastard
How much money do you have?
Nurse Li can't work because of a car accident
Post a job ad for me
yes! Physician Kim
take this
I'm too small for you to wear
Don't keep wearing the same old T-shirts!
You are a nurse working in an aesthetic clinic
Dress decently!
Is this okay? Will I look good in it?
Of course it looks good
Would you like to have lunch with me?
wow! thank you for the night
My pleasure
Where did you sleep last night?
I ran to a nearby bathhouse
Sorry! Thank you!
You're welcome! let's go to lunch
- thanks - take it easy
Hope you like it
I can't remember the last time I ate here
shall we start lo?
funny to say
but my dream is to have lunch with you
it feels so good to eat together
outside of work
yes…
We've been together for a long time but this is the first time
the two of us eat alone
yes! What a first!
I've thought about it many times!
- what ? - Oh! nothing
Please use
oh! It was so delicious!
look
Didn't you say you won't answer my calls?
The visitor is a guest!
Am I just a guest? Is it that simple?
who are you?
Who am I?
you must be curious
yes i am curious
stop now! If you are trying to trick me!
Whether it is Junhe or not
I don't want to do that either
Then why don't you just quit?
You are…
Junhe, is that you?
I told you I don't know who I am
then let's talk about something else
talk about yourself
if i were junhe
I want you to break up with him?
- hey - hi
Have a drink with me if you're free tonight
no, he's waiting for me
who?
My new guy, I guess he looks like a lot of gold
I see...then be careful
Is there a problem?
nothing, you go
Sure! I'll call you again!
(Suspected of murder, under investigation)
I am home
I shake it casually
Why?
i came to you
don't turn on the light
yes?
ok, i'll take a shower first
please... take it easy
Please
please
i beg you
you hurt me
it hurts... lighten
answer me
answer what?
Where did you... go that night?
please tell me
I sleep out
but did nothing
Why are you hitting someone?
Shameless bitch!
say it one more time
tell me again
You do the same to your wife, don't you?
What?
you do
I want to commit suicide too!
Hit me!
hit me!
Rather than seeing other men having sex with you
i would rather kill you
die! You die!
i stayed up late last night
A conspiracy j , t ?
Another murder?
Let's just resign
Is that exaggerated?
How can it be possible to sleep until dawn after lurking and monitoring all day long?
You bastard, you're so unprofessional
should i ask for a replacement
sir
it's really hot
- so is it true? - No
3 months ago...
How long have you known Cherry?
About two years?
two years...
thanks you can go
yes?
do you know?
If anyone thinks of anything suspicious
Call me
hey, bring that woman in
aunt?
hey mom
Please wait
something?
Do you have anything to add?
i have doubts about a person
hope you like this
I know you don't like spicy
so i make spicy
I try my best but I like spicy food very much
please try
How about it? Is it better than the restaurant outside?
oh! It is too sweet?
It's okay, I'll eat then
Really tasty!
what happened?
That bastard found the police coming
Watch him make a mess on purpose
really useless
Hello! don't touch that, come here
(Nurse Kim Eun-joo)
(a week ago)
go out!
No! Let's go out and talk!
i know you can fuck anyone
But I didn't know you went to that bastard's house
cut!
I gotta go! I don't want to talk to you anymore!
Hey
Where are you going?
we'll talk inside
let me go
I think I'm going crazy, if I keep seeing you
you…
you have no idea how much i love you
you and that bastard
Are you crazy?
we go inside
come with me
go in
let's talk
follow me
Eun Joo don't be afraid
I promise he won't bother you anymore
Nurse Yun
Don't be afraid I'll fix it soon!
After that, we hid where no one knew
live together
Don't touch Eun Joo
Oh, no!
This dress is very expensive!
Blood can't wash away
This is the clothes my boss gave me
I will wear it for a long time
I've warned you enough
Why don't you know when enough is enough?
Why are you still pestering Eun Joo?
Ok!
Let me do it!
Junhe...
Sorry
Don't talk. The ambulance is coming soon.
Junhe!
i love you so much
You love that bastard over me
you crazy
i never liked you
why do you say that
how happy we are together
Have lunch and drinks
Now the maniac who followed you is gone
we can be happy
Yeah? Eun Joo!
don't come near me anymore
Let's just go with him!
yes
Good idea!
Ok
we go to heaven together
Restart
Is that so, Nabi?
(a few months later)
Can you be a little imaginative?
I have a hole in my panties, it's where my little sister is
no need to take off
You can go straight to Huanglong
For example, in places like subway toilets
you just push my legs
and put the little brother in
Imagine your fingers running between my thighs on the bus
bus in motion
passengers are asleep
i'm soaked
and i have dewaxing
So no fluff...in "there"
my skin is smooth
Come on, want to lick me?
Guests, please wash your hands and come quickly...
I'm your friend with benefits "Nai Die", thank you for calling!
You are so flirtatious!
Thank you!
How rude!
you are great
You paid off such a huge debt!
Congratulations, Nabi
thank you all…
What are your plans now?
I'm going to travel for a while
I'll call you after get off work
drink together
your treat!
Ziyu...I'm waiting for the phone call at home, you call me
What the hell are you waiting for? Not going to work yet?
What a bitch she is!
Let's get to work!
Goodbye, Butterfly...