The Untamed
Episode 45
If you don't believe it,
you're welcome to ask old Master Lan
if there is such book in the Forbidden Chamber
of Cloud Recesses.
Granted that there is,
when I was apprenticing in Lan clan of Gusu,
I was never allowed to enter there.
Who said you have to get in there yourself?
As long as the man behind you
could get in without limitation it'll do.
I suppose your way of altering the music
was taught by him too, right?
A man of high position who could access
Cloud Recesses freely.
I believe it won't need more hints
before everybody can get it.
According to his word,
can it be...!
You guys really made a genius decision.
Gathered so many disciples of various clans,
and brought a big bunch of people here in Burial Mounds.
The mantis is catching the cicada, not aware of a bird behind.
Under an excuse of injury, he didn't come here
in order to avoiding suspicion
and collaborating with your from outside.
In the end, hundreds of people all fall in my den.
Nobody would believe it's not
my work at that time.
And you guys are not afraid of running into me.
As notorious as I am,
with old scores and new hatred welling up,
all of you
would be too indignant to listen to my explanation.
Ridiculous!
Lianfang Zun, His Excellency, commands all clans now.
He doesn't need to strive for throne.
What benefit could he get for
letting so many people die here?
I can take it when you slander me.
How could you even slander His Excellency?
Since you're confident that I'm slandering you,
then can you play the battle music you just played
for driving those puppets
once again.
Yeah, play it again.
- Yeah. Again. - Once again.
- Play it. - Play it now.
- Once again.
- Come on. - One more time.
Unwilling to?
Alright. It's OK.
How about tell me
what are these?
You really think we left Jinlintai
without anything found?
In the hidden chamber behind the bronze mirror in Fragrance Hall,
Jin Guangyao got two torn pieces
of the Soul-chaos Script.
We found them.
We can just show them to old Master Lan,
and let him to tell,
whether there is the melody you just played.
The truth will be clear then.
Watch out!
Did my eyes go wrong?
You still got some spiritual power in you.
Congratulations.
But
if there's no malicious intention
why did you conceal the truth
that you still got spiritual power?
Damn. He's going to ruin the magic circle!
He is the Ghostface Man!
He's got Stygian Tiger Amulet.
It won't work.
Don't try.
Wei Wuxian.
You haven't tell everybody
why Su She could have Stygian Tiger Amulet?
This Stygian Tiger Amulet was forged by Xue Yang.
We met Xue Yang in Coffin Town.
A Ghostface Man showed up when we're fighting him
and tried to save him
but failed.
However he took Xue Yang's Stygian Tiger Amulet away.
And the Ghostface Man is Su She.
- This is... - How...
Wh... Which means
all puppets here are controlled by Clan Leader Su?
Childe Wei! I can't hold back them all!
What should we do?
What should we do now?
Ghost General! Let me help!
Wait.
Uncle.
Don't lose the Purple Lightening!
Do remember!
Jin Ling!
You little fool!
Come back?
Do you hear me?
You should go back.
I won't!
We're done. We're done. We're done.
What can we do?
What can be done?
Dad, what shall we do?
What is he going to do?
When the second wave rush in,
I'll draw them to the blood pool.
Hanguang Jun do the killing.
Here. I'm the bait.
Don't be bellicose then.
Just run to the outside.
They won't attack you.
Let me draw a Lure Flag on my body too.
Don't be fool, OK?
One bait is far enough.
And I only need Hanguang Jun to do the killing.
Rest of you don't make trouble for me.
Listen to him.
Wen Ning. Get them out of here.
We finally made it.
- Yeah. - Finally.
My spiritual power has recovered to twenty percent.
I just got ten percent. So slow.
Everyone.
As far as I'm concerned,
while our power hasn't fully recovered,
we should find a safe place and
rest there till we got eighty percent.
Then we can go home
in case of other incidents
or danger.
- Agreed. - Good.
How about we go to Lotus Cove?
It's the nearest.
- OK. - Agreed.
Clan Leader Yao.
We just leave... like this?
Or what?
Stay here?
What if those puppets come at us again?
They haven't got back!
They won't be back!
I think so.
Nonsense!
Sizhui. What are you doing?
You're out of your mind?
- Come back! - What is he doing?
Senior Wei.
Sizhui.
Senior Wei. Senior Wei.
Are you OK?
Sizhui.
We are OK.
Don't be afraid.
I'm not.
I... I'm just...
I don't know why either.
I just...
Did this boy
become numb?
Senior Wei!
Senior Wei. Wake up.
Senior Wei. Senior Wei.
Yuan.
Yuan?
I couldn't imagine
Su She
is that kind of people.
Yeah.
I could never imagine that.
However,
it doesn't make sense.
Why did he do that?
Just for framing Wei Wuxian up?
Consider
what Wei Wuxian had said in Jinlintai
at that time?
Can it be...
Lianfang Zun?
This Wei Wuxian.
Bad as he is,
he can't always tell lies.
I just heard that...
Is it real?
I also heard...
Yeah. I heard the same.
No wonder. No wonder now.
Sizhui.
There's still a while before departure.
If you worry about seasickness,
we can stay on the pier a while longer.
OK.
Brother Sizhui.
You're seasick too?
Aren't you from Gusu?
How can you be seasick since you're not a northerner?
I have no idea.
I've been like this since I was about four or five years old.
I might have been born like this.
Let's go.
Gho... Ghost General.
What does he want?
Why is Ghost General here?
Can it be that he's going to share the boat with us?
Who knows.
Shouldn't he be with senior Wei?
He's coming.
Wha... What's your name?
I'm a disciple of Lan clan of Gusu.
My name is Lan Yuan.
Lan Yuan...("Yuan" of "Wen Yuan")
Do you know
who gave you
your name?
Naturally, it's from my parents.
What is he doing?
Are your parents still alive?
My parents
passed away when I was little.
Bro Sizhui, don't say too much
in case it's a trap.
How is it going?
Sizhui.
Sizhui is your courtesy name?
Correct.
Who gave you that?
Hanguang Jun.
Gho...
Mr. Wen.
Anything wrong with my name?
No.
Not at all.
You just look
very similar to one of my
distant relatives.
I didn't know Ghost General can naturally engage with others.
Yeah.
Where have I met
this face before?
Childe Lan.
Childe?
Can I call you Yuan?("Yuan" of "Wen Yuan")
Of course.
Yuan.
How have you been these years?
I've been living well.
Hanguang Jun must be very nice to you.
He's like a brother and father to me.
He taught me how to play Qin.
How old was you
when Hanguang Jun started to
take care of you?
I can't remember.
About four or five maybe.
But when I was even younger,
he couldn't have taken care of me then,
because he seemed to be isolating himself
for that few years.
What is he gonna do?
I bought it when I was passing by the wharf.
I thought you'd like it.
Please take it.
Yuan.
Childe Jin Rulan.
What did you call?
Young Childe Jin Ling.
Childe Jin.
Step aside.
None of your business.
Jin Ling.
Put your sword away first.
Get out of my way!
Sizhui.
Childe Jin.
If you are angry
come at me and I won't protest.
But Yuan,
Childe Lan is inn...
Jin Ling, how could you act like this?
Has Sizhui done anything to piss you off?
Yeah.
He was caring for you.
How could you push him
ignoring his kindness?
How undisciplined.
Ill-bred.
Right!
I'm just that awful!
So what?
Why abruptly burst out?
Unreasonable.
What a temper of young mistress.
Erupt without notice.
Ill-bred.
Who did you take us as?
Yeah.
Jin Ling.
Wei Ying.
Lan Zhan.
What happened?
You passed out.
Not me.
I mean Jin Ling.
What happened to them?
It was you who started this.
Why you act like a furious victim?
Stop it.
I'm indeed ill-bred.
But you're not the one who can discipline me!
What's going on?
What happened, Wen Ning?
Childe, I'm sorry.
It's all my fault.
I couldn't control myself.
I just wanted to see him...
Don't put up a play like this!
Jin Ling.
Put your sword down.
I won't!
Jin Ling!
No!
Quit it!
Well. All because I'm misbehaving!
Because I'm so childish! Satisfied?!
This is my dad's sword.
I won't put it down.
Ling!
Why are you crying?
Come here now!
What's wrong?
Who made you cry?
Wei Wuxian!
What's your intention standing on the shore?
Clan Leader Yao,
why do you have to speak in that tone?
If senior Wei had any intention,
I'm afraid we couldn't have made this far, right?
You!
Zizhen is right.
Clan Leader Ouyang.
If I remember it right,
that talking kid is your son, right?
He's so good at talking.
Zizhen.
Come to father!
Now!
Dad,
you said don't disturb you guys there.
Enough.
Haven't you pushed yourself forward far enough?
Come over!
I won't.
You. You...
You disobey me more when you grow up, huh?
I'll go there for you if you don't come over now!
Dad!
Just have some rest there!
Your spiritual power hasn't recovered yet!
Just get inside!
Clan Leader,
we're leaving.
Back to Lotus Cove?
You're barefaced enough to go back there?
Shove off!
Back to Lotus Cove!
Childe,
I'll wait outside.
Sizhui.
Mr. Wen.
Let me keep you company.
Keeping me company?
Right.
Those seniors are going to have
an important meeting there.
I'm not needed anyway.
Let's continue our chatting.
Where did we stop the chat?
Did Childe Wei really put a five-year-old child
in the soil like a turnip?
Just like this.
Let him be.
= Lotus Cove =
That kid was poor.
But
I actually remember when I was little,
Hanguang Jun also
had raised me among a bunch of rabbits.
Really?
And I ate the same as those rabbits.
Therefore
I'm fond of carrots since I was little.
Clan Leader.
Not now.
I can meet them at another day.
Don't you see what's going on here?
I've said that to them.
But those two girls said
they came just for today's event.
And they also had
brought some rare medical herbs.
They seem to have known several clan leaders were wounded.
Everyone, please suit yourself.
And excuse my temporary absence.
I'll be back soon.
So humble of you, Clan Leader Jiang.
Lan Zhan.
Sit please.
No misbehavior.
Jiang Cheng has been gone for so long.
Why he is still not back?
Come on in.
You shall tell that here and now.
Once again.
Clan Leader Jiang.
What's going...
This is an appalling case.
I didn't dare to be reckless.
So I took a while
to interrogate them.
Everyone, please stay quiet.
Listen to their words.
Which of you two want to talk first?
I...
= Sisi = = Bicao =
I'll talk first.
I'm going to tell
an old incident about eleven years ago.
My name is Sisi.
I used to be a prostitute.
I was kind of popular for a while.
About dozen years ago,
I wanted to find a rich merchant to marry.
But I didn't expect that merchant's wife
was such a vicious snake.
She hired a group of thugs
to have cut my face with knife.
Then my face
became like this.
With my face ruined
no one would pay a visit to me.
So the old business couldn't last.
And the brothel kicked me out.
I didn't have any other skill.
So I grouped up with those sisters who
got too old.
Their clients didn't ask for much.
They would take me in whenever there's a deal.
And I coped with that with my face veiled.
One day,
a sister of my place
suddenly got a deal.
She ordered many of us.
And we were shipped to a place by wagon.
Ordered so many of us for a time.
He must be a rich client.
He just is!
Payment's been given.
Look at how happy you are.
I got my gold ingot,
but felt something wrong.
Why would they come to us since they're so rich?
More frankly,
how could it be so convenient to earn that fortune?
- Are we there? - Are we?
I think so.
We're there.
Let's go. Come on.
Move.
Hurry up.
Really ugly enough.
Bring them in.
Let's entertain that old bastard.
Move.
Get in.
Where are we?
What should we do?
- I don't know. - You be the first.
Why are you still standing there?
I think it's no need
to teach you what to do, right?
No.
Father,
I've got you your favorite women.
Many of them.
Are you pleased?
It's Jin Guangyao.
Well... You mean...
The lying man was...
He was...
Continue.
Then... What else could we do?
That middle-aged man was struggling and yelling.
But his body lacked in strength.
We hadn't even finished the first course.
He... He just seemed dead.
He...
He just died like that?
Exactly.
We had never been in that kind of situation.
All extremely terrified.
We sought to
call that deal off.
However,
the man behind the curtain said...
He said...
- Said... - What?
Don't stop even if he's dead.
You tell me.
What, what, what...
What kind of thing is that?
After all Jin Guangshan
was his own father.
If this is true,
it's so...
so...
- Yeah. - Excessive.
We knew we were done for
when that man died.
Not surprisingly,
when it's done
those about twenty sisters of mine were
all killed.
None survived.
Why did they leave only you alive?
I don't know.
I implored them that
I wouldn't take the money
and I would never speak that to anyone.
Then they really didn't kill me.
They confined me in a residence
for eleven years.
I just got rescued by someone recently.
So I escaped.
Who rescued you?
I don't know.
I have never met the savior directly.
But after hearing my story,
he decided to stop this sanctimonious
degenerate from fooling everyone any longer.
Even if Jin Guangyao's power is beyond our imagination now,
what he had done must be exposed.
It's for the justice of those who got killed by him,
and it also will bring peace to my deceased sisters.
Is there any proof
of what you've said?
No.
She filled his speech with many details.
It can't be a lie.
- Yeah. - I agree.
Miss,
I seem to have seen you somewhere.
You should have...
You should have seen me.
I accompanied my madam
when our Qin clan of Yueling held the Cultivation Conference.
Qin clan of Yueling. (Different from the instrument "Qin")
Are you
Mrs. Jin's maid?
Yes.
Master Lan is right.
I'm the close maid of Mrs. Jin.
My humble name is Bicao.
What I'm going to say
happened even earlier.
About twelve or thirteen years ago,
I watched my young lady grow up.
Our madam always favored our young lady very much.
But when our lady was going to marry,
madam was always depressed those days,
wearing long face all day.
She'd even break down in tears suddenly in the day
and have nightmares every night.
I thought it was because our lady was going to marry
and she's unwilling to let her go.
So I kept comforting her
that our lady was going to marry
that successful and young Lianfang Zun
who was a gentle
and loyal man.
Our lady would definitely be happy after marrying him.
But our madam got even more upset
having heard that.
A few days later,
the date of wedding was decided.
Our madam fainted out at the sight of the invitation.
After the wedding,
our madam's condition got even worse.
She fell sick from constant depression.
It got worse and worse.
Before her demise,
madam finally couldn't hold it back any longer.
She told me everything.
Jin Guangyao, Lianfang Zun, and Qin Su, our lady,
are not a couple.
They are a pair of siblings.
Our madam was
so unfortunate.
That bastard, old Clan Leader Jin, was inhuman.
He craved for our madam's pretty look
and raped her after he was drunk at a dinner outside.
No way could our madam resist him.
She didn't even dare expose that after.
Jin Guangshan might be unable to remember
who was his daughter.
But how could our madam forget that?
She didn't dare to find Jin Guangshan,
and knew our lady was attached to Jin Guangyao.
She struggled for a long time
and finally went to find Jin Guangyao
before the wedding
for avoiding the tragedy.
She told him the secret
and besought him to call the marriage off.
The tragedy must be avoided.
Nonetheless,
Jin Guangyao knew our lady was
his own younger sister
but still married her.
What a beast.
Outrageous!
- Yeah! - I can't bear hearing it.
Old Clan Leader Qin
had been following Jin Guangshan so many years.
How could that old bastard lay his hands
on the wife of his subordinate?
This Jin Guangshan
was worse than a beast.
- Agreed. - Right.
Worse than a beast.