The Untamed
Episode 36
Lan Zhan, sit.
and drink the liquor.
Second Childe Lan,
call me Brother Wei.
Brother Wei.
What's wrong?
Your headband is tilted.
Tilted!
It's been 16 years.
Lan Zhan's capacity for liquor didn't change.
Small capacity still.
Lan Zhan.
Wen Ning, it's really you.
Why don't you recognize me?
What the hell are you wearing?
Stand straight.
Hand.
Wen Ning can twist the steel with bare hands,
he will not let the chain wrap on him.
The chain,
is used by someone to trap him.
Whoever keeps Wen Ning alive,
won't allow him to think himself.
To make him obey the orders,
one must destroy him mind first.
If so,
Then...
That day,
my sister and I went to Jinlintai together
and were locked up by Clan Leader Jin.
Then my memory blurred.
It was just like
that I was locked at a dark place.
Someone came to check occasionally.
Until,
I heard your flute.
Who locked you up?
When did you controlled by the skull-piercing nail?
Do you remember any of these?
Wen Ning.
What are you doing?
Childe.
Sorry.
For all these years,
do you insist doing so?
Fine.
Childe.
Look at you.
Isn't it good to stand straight and talk
like this?
But,
all chaos were started by me.
If not for me,
Childe and sister won't suffer.
All chaos were started by you,
You are so 'great'.
If that is true,
It's not enough to burn you
thousands of times.
How can you be alive till today?
I... I...
Wen Qing was right.
You are a blade,
a precious one.
Who isn't interested in such a treasure?
Back then, Jin clan of Lanling announced
that they had burnt down you and your sister.
Now, you, the ghost general
are still alive anyway.
It's strange to keep the chains on you
which jingle all the time.
I should find a sword to cut it off.
Well,
wait me here.
I go back to inn first.
If Lan Zhan is awake,
then forget it.
If he falls asleep,
I'm going to borrow his Dirt-eschewing (sword name).
Lan Zhan.
You wake up.
I am saying to borrow your Dirt-eschewing.
definitely not steal.
Lan Zhan. You...
Lan Zhan.
Lan Zhan, look at yourself.
You shouldn't go out when you are drunk!
Go back to sleep.
Don't move.
Lan Zhan,
I'm sorry.
It seems that I can't find our way back...
Lan Zhan, what are you doing?
Lan Zhan, what do you want?
Lan Zhan.
Lan Zhan, you...
Take it.
Why do you give a rooster?
What are you doing?
These roosters were others'.
Do you know you are stealing?
Are they good or not?
Yes, really good.
You are really good.
For you, it's all for you.
Poor Lan Zhan, born in a gentry family
and was regulated strictly by three thousand clan regulations.
Now he's drunk and becomes even crazier than me.
Lan Zhan.
Now what?
= Lan Wangji visited here. =
Lan Wangji
visited here.
Lan Zhan,
let's stop making a mess,
go back and sleep.
Good boy.
Go, let's go.
Move, now.
Lan Zhan
Wait for me.
Don't move.
Lan Zhan, all settled, let's go.
Come on.
= Lan Wangji visited here. =
=Wei Wuxian also visited here=
Lan Zhan, have you put out the light?
So familiar with Lan Zhan's swordmanship...
Does it mean...
He's one of Lan clan?
Thanks.
Portal Talisman.
Lan Zhan.
Lan Zhan, he's gone.
Lan Zhan, calm down, he's gone.
Let me tell you,
you really exhausted me.
I dare not to let you drink again.
Thirsty.
Water.
OK. I will serve you.
Hold it.
What?
I want you to drink the water.
Ok, enough.
Look at you,
Lan Zhan.
I think when you are sober,
you'd better forget all these.
Otherwise, I'm afraid you'll feel too ashamed.
Lan Zhan,
what's this figure?
Two.
So now it's Q&A time.
Have you ever taste
Emperor's Smile at Cloud Recesses
No.
Have you ever broken any regulation?
Yes.
Do you like rabbits?
Lan Zhan, you admit it finally.
Why do you help me?
I have my regret.
What regret?
At Nevernight,
I wasn't by your side.
So these years,
You've been looking for me?
Lan Zhan,
Remember this.
The whole thing has nothing to do with you.
Defecting
and studying crafty tricks
are my own choices.
Do you understand?
Lan Zhan, what are you doing?
Lan Zhan, do you understand or not?
It's 9 PM, rest.
Stop, you stop.
Stop running, stop!
Stop.
The 'Sun' falls down.
We are not start to shoot it yet, it falls.
Now who's the leader?
Of course it should be me, I'm Jin Guangyao.
I killed the devil of clan Wen.
I'm Nie Mingjue.
I won most battles
and subdued most prisoners.
That makes me the boss.
But I play his Excellency.
So what? You're still my third junior brother.
You're afraid of me when seeing me.
You're a short-lived guy.
Jin Zixuan, you died before me and lived shorter than me.
Short-lived, yes, but I ranked the third.
Ranked third in terms of face.
OK, let's stop arguing.
I'm Thrice Bane Master (Jiang Cheng). I'm the best.
Let me be the leader.
What do you say, Hanguang Jun?
Pooh!
Gentries,
can I ask you a question?
What?
I wonder,
Why there's no Yiling Patriarch?
Er Wa and San Pang, do you want a sound beat?
Playing instead of going home for meal?
Come back, make good speed!
Run! Yiling Patriarch is coming!
Come back! Stop running!
let's run.
Lan Zhan, you wake up.
Last night, I...
You, you didn't do anything last night
You just talked much.
What did I say?
Actually, there's nothing about it.
Actually, you were saying...
For example,
I like...
I like rabbits.
What's wrong with liking rabbits?
Rabbits are so cute, and everyone loves them.
I like them, too
I like to eat them.
What exactly did I do last night?
No, nothing.
Really, you didn't do anything last night.
I was just teasing you.
Lan Zhan.
I'm going to talk about real business.
Say it.
Do you remember the Ghostface Man last night?
His cultivation is really good.
Good enough to support him
to use a Portal Talisman.
He cast spells on his sword and face.
I can understand why he cast a spell on face.
Cause he's afraid of being recognized.
But cast a spell on sword?
Usually the unknown cultivators
won't cast spells on their swords.
Because it's not necessary.
Unless his sword,
is really famous in cultivation world.
So once somebody recognized his sword glare,
his identity is exposed.
Therefore he had to cover it up.
And I saw your fight yesterday.
He seems to know well of swordmanship of clan Lan.
Lan Zhan.
Think carefully,
is he someone you are familiar with?
Moreover,
can he be one of your clan?
No.
Trust me.
You always disdain to lie,
so I believe the answer given by you.
It's just getting more and more complicated.
No matter how,
this man must be related to
the death of Red Blade Master.
Otherwise,
he won't go after your evil-subdue Qiankun pouch.
We must hurry up.
in case he forestalls.
But where are we going?
East of Shu.
Lan Zhan.
Are you sure our good brother pointing at this direction?
So strange.
This road doesn't look like frequently used.
Lan Zhan.
How about asking the villagers?
Excuse me, I would like to ask
where does the road lead to?
To Coffin Town.
It's a doomed place.
Whoever lives in this town,
lives a short life or dies an unnatural death.
As time passes,
it is called Coffin Town.
Thank you.
Be careful on the road.
Lan Zhan, let's go.
What did he say?
That road leads to Coffin Town.
The Chinese character on the stone is Yi.
Yi that means chivalrous?
Right, but also wrong.
Why?
The character is Yi.
But not the one that means chivalrous.
but the one means Yi Home(Coffin Home), an ominous place.
He said,
for a long time,
Whoever lives in the town,
most of them lives shortly.
they either died young or died in unnatural ways.
So there are many coffins in the town.
Furthermore,
this place abounds with coffins and joss paper for funerals.
Local people have excellent skills on
making coffins and paper doll
So they took this name.
He also said,
fewer people went to Coffin town recently.
Except for those who deliver goods, nearly nobody comes out.
There's almost nobody around.
This road was discarded for years.
Really a poor one.
Be careful.
Bad geomantic omen.
A dire place.
Lan Zhan.
If someone sneaks between us
now in the fog,
we might not
discover him.
Shh, be careful.
It's a paper head.
Looks like a stygian malla.
Heed, be cautious.
Who?
Jin Ling. Sizhui.
It's you again.
I also wonder why it's you again.
Childe Mo, you're here too.
Does it mean Hanguang Jun is here as well?
It must be him, that's his sword Dirt-eschewing.
Yes, he's here. He's here.
But tell me
why you are here first.
Don't tell me
that you company each other
here for night hunting.
It's so strange here.
No residents around.
In broad daylight, but was teemed with pathogenic mist.
And none of the shops opens.
That's not the point.
Tell me why you're here first.
That's a long story.
After we entering the town,
we worried about getting lost,
so we gathered together.
Suddenly, we heard this sound.
At that time, it's not that quick.
One by one, slowly.
We seemed to see a small figure
in the fog, walking slowly.
It disappeared once we run to it.
The sound followed us all along since then.
We went on this road after entering the town,
and never changed our direction.
But we still couldn't get out of here.
Have you tried maneuvering the sword?
We tried.
I felt I've flew upwards for a long distance.
But actually it's not very high.
There are some shadows
flying hither and thither in the sky.
Since I don't know what that is,
worrying about being unable to cope with it,
I came to the ground.
Is the fog toxic?
It's not.
We did not die yet as we stayed here for so long.
I should have bring my Fairy.
It's all because of your dumb donkey.
We haven't put blame on your dog Fairy.
It bit Lil' Apple first
and got kicked by Lil' Apple.
Whose fault?
Now neither of them can move.
Wait.
My Lil' Apple was bitten?
Can that donkey be compared with my Fairy?
My uncle gave me Fairy as a gift.
If something happens to it,
It's worth more than ten thousand donkeys.
OK, tell you what.
Don't use the name of Lianfang Zun to frighten me.
My Lil' Apple is the gift
from Hanguang Jun.
How could you take Lil' Apple out of Cloud Recesses?
and even get it injured?
You lie!
Hanguang Jun won't give out such a gift.
Sorry, Childe Mo.
Your Lil' Apple
made noises at Cloud Recesses everyday.
Predecessors have complained it for long
and asked us to sent it away,
while we are having night hunting.
So we...
I dislike that donkey at first sight.
And named it Lil' Apple?
So dumb.
What's wrong with Lil' Apple?
It likes eating apples so it was named Lil' Apple.
Not pretending at all!
It is a name way better than Fairy,
which refers to your fat dog.
Fairy is not fat at all.
Can you find a wonder dog more robust than her?
Why don't you speak?
The silencing charm.
Stygian Tiger Amulet.
How come?
It's not my Stygian Tiger Amulet.
My puppets
won't be cut into pieces so easily.
I think my guess is right before.
Somebody recovered Stygian Tiger Amulet.
But just a half of it.
So it's not that powerful.
What happened to you?
These powder mixed in the fog
are bitter and sweet with fishy smell, disgusting.
We should leave here first.
But we can't see anything.
Which direction then?
Wanna take my Qiankun pouch?
Unfortunately your eyesight is bad.
Why do you take my Spirit-capture pouch?
Lan Zhan.
Here comes the ghost pretender.
Lan Zhan, you are hurt.
Impossible.
Right.
Let's go this way.
How are the people who inhaled the powder?
They can barely stand straight.
Show me your tongues.
Those puppets are poisoned.
Congratulations, you got poisoned.
Congratulate for what?
Regard it as something
you can boast about later.
Childe Mo,
Will they be OK?
They are good for now,
however,
after poison flows into blood,
and all over the body into the heart
then no one can save them.
What will happen?
What happens to the dead, then what happens to them.
Well, what should we do?
What should we do?
Want to get treatments?
OK.
Then listen to me.
From now on,
everyone must listen to me.
Each one of you.
OK.
Good, stand straight.
Those who are not poisoned carries the poisoned.
While lifting
remember to keep head and heart upturned.
I can walk, why lift me up?
Dude,
if you walk around,
the faster your blood flows,
the faster poison flows into your heart.
Therefore, you must be motionless, understand?
Understand.
Go.
This way.
Senior Mo, where are we going?
Since we can't get out of the town, knock some doors.
You want us to get into the house?
It's quite dangerous outside.
What if there are something hidden
in the house to ambush us?
True.
It's hard to say it's more dangerous
outside or inside.
But the outside is already dangerous enough,
the inside can't be worse.
Let's go. They need to be detoxicated in time.
Go.
This house is empty, come.
Who ask you to find an empty one?
Find one with people in it.
Keep searching.
Can't you say it earlier?
Anyone?
Is anybody there?
Madam.
Are you the shopkeeper?
Yes.
Madam.
It's the first time we visited here.
We lost our direction because of the thick fog,
and we are all tired .
Would you mind allowing us to be here
to rest for a while?
My shop
is not a place for resting .
But Madam,
the rest shops of this place
are all empty.
Would you please be so kind?
She really would let us in?
Of couse, my feet stuck here.
Even she want to close the door, she can't.
If you refuse to let us in,
I will kick the door.
Madam.
Why don't you light up the candle?
Candle is on the desk.
Help yourself.
Are these all your works?
Brilliant skills.
This old women is of quirkiness.
You...
You are not a madman indeed.
Who said I'm a madman?
Then why you wear mask?
I like.
The shape of mask is so unique.
Why don't you light up the candle while threading the needle?
Allow me.
Madam,
can we borrow your kitchen for the moment?
Kitchen is in the rear.
Help yourself.
Thanks a lot.
Don't go there.
Though there's no danger in it,
the place is full of weirdness.
We'd better behave ourselves
when we're in other people's domain.
I need someone to help me,
Any volunteers?