The Untamed
Episode 37
Don't go there.
Though there's no danger in it,
the place is full of weirdness.
We'd better behave ourselves
when we're in other people's domain.
I need someone to help me,
Any volunteers?
Senior Mo. I can.
Then what do I do?
You...
Don't move
until I tell you to.
Got it?
OK.
Let's go.
What's the smell!
What are you doing here instead of
thinking up ways to detoxify?!
How did you know that I was going to call you over?
I'm not here to help!
Did somebody kill someone but forgot to bury?!
Why is here so stinky?
Young Mistress Jin,
if you're coming with me, please lend me a hand.
If you're not, then please go back, sit down
and tell someone else to come over.
You're calling who Young Mistress Jin?
Be careful what you say!
Well, I want to see
what on earth you're trying to do.
OK, then.
Sizhui, go fetch me a bucket of water.
To clean the kitchen hearth.
Okay.
What's the use of cleaning the hearth?
You're not going to cook or anything.
I am exactly going to cook.
You, go to sweep the dust.
Get rid of
the straw and other rubbish here.
Get yourself moving!
Making congee?
Why do you make congee?
It's so watery and tasteless!
It's not for you anyways.
What did you say?
I worked for so long, and I can't even have any?!
Senior Mo,
is it that congee can cure poisoning?
Yeah. Sizhui is clever.
But it's not the congee that can cure poisoning.
it's the glutinous rice.
This is a folk method.
So that's why you intended to
enter a house with someone inside.
Only a house with someone living inside could have a kitchen.
Only a kitchen could have glutinous rice.
Am I right?
Yes.
Okay, stand away.
You haven't explained
why you came to Coffin Town together?
It wasn't just by chance that
you ran into each other and then us, was it?
I, the Lan clan's people,
and the ones from other clans
were all chasing after something.
I came from the Qinghe area.
We came from Langya.
What was it?
I don't know.
It never showed its face.
We don't even know what or who
or which organization
it was, exactly.
Who is it?
Who?
Such situation
still continued after I changed the inn a few times,
so I went on the offensive.
If I heard that a cat's corpse
happened to appear anywhere,
I would go and check,
determined to find out who was messing around.
You guys the same?
Yes.
We chased after it to Yueyang,
and came across Chlide Jin.
We found out that we were searching for the same thing,
so we decided to work together,
and only arrived at this area today.
We asked a hunter in the village
in front of a stone tablet,
and we were shown the path to Coffin Town.
A hunter?
When I came here with Lan Zhan this morning,
there was an ordinary farmer at the entrance of the village.
Where did the hunter come from?
Though killing cats and dumping the corpses
both sounded and looked terrifying,
they weren't actually harmed.
On the contrary, these events stirred up
their curiosity to search for the truth.
Also, these juniors met one another
in Yueyang where I and Lan Zhan have stopped off.
It seems as if somebody was purposely leading them
to meet up with the me and Lan Zhan.
And, this isn't the most knotty part of it.
The person who restored Stygian Tiger Amulet
might be within the Coffin Town at this very moment.
Senior Mo. I think that the congee is ready?
It's ready? Take it out if then.
One bowl for one person. Feed those
who had been poisoned.
Jin Ling.
What?
Be careful.
What is this? It's poison?
Poison? It's the cure! Glutinous rice congee.
First, I don't know why glutinous rice can be the cure.
= Ouyang Zizhen =
Second, I've never had
such spicy glutinous congee before!
Did I accidentally sprinkle
the paprika in it?
The taste... is so terrible
that it almost brings about a sense of deja vu.
All medicine is poisonous to some degree.
The spicy taste will make you sweat
so that you get better sooner.
Seriously? Come on.
What are you seeing?
What's outside the door?
Shh. Don't talk.
I'm looking at it.
Amazing.
Move!
What did you mean?
How is it? Doesn't it look pretty?
Yeah,
it's so-so at best.
Only barely worthy of a look!
Se... Se... Senior Mo! There...
Don't say it out,
or else it wouldn't be a surprise.
Let everyone check for himself.
- No, thanks. - No, thanks.
In this situation you're still in the vein for mischief?
Just what in the world were you thinking?
You joined me as well, didn't you?
Don't imitate your uncle's tone.
Sizhui, was that thing scary?
Yes.
Then take another look.
This is an excellent opportunity for your cultivation.
It's scary. That's why you need to see it.
Look carefully
and tell me what exactly it is.
How did it go?
What have you seen?
White pupils.
Female.
Short and skinny.
Fine looks.
Holding a bamboo pole.
The girl is only around fifteen or sixteen.
She has an oval face,
with a lively air
mixed with her comely nature.
Her wooden hairpin has a small
fox head carved onto the end.
She's not only small but her figure is also slender.
Although she's not that tidy,
she's not grimy either.
After some grooming,
she's bound to be a lovely girl.
Well done, well done.
The observations are both
detailed and unique.
Kid, you'll definitely
be the sentimental type after you grow up.
The girl's height reaches my chest.
She is only wearing rags and doesn't look too clean,
dressing like a beggar roaming the streets.
The bamboo pole appears to be a white cane.
She has white pupils.
It's not because she's a monster,
but she's blind.
And she keeps knocking on the ground with a bamboo pole,
as if to express something that she is unable to say.
And
there's some black marks on her neck.
Right. Right. Right.
Jin Ling could see much,
while Sizhui could see the details.
Miss,
you've been following us,
what can we help?
So that's why she could not speak.
Both blind and mute. How unfortunate.
Is it the Ghostface Man?
Probably not.
The Ghostface Man had entirely
different moves from this person.
How could it be him?
Senior Mo,
this man got poisoned.
We need to help him!
How?
The poisoning powder is everywhere.
You're gonna be poisoned if you go out.
Flirty eyes behind thy long lashes,
red lips parted, smiling in tease.
Mind not the good or evil,
with smeared eyes I summon thee.
It's the Summoning of Painted Eyes!
Take the living person back inside.
Other than him,
eliminate everything.
Don't come near.
Be careful not to touch the powder.
Even physical contact would poison you.
Who are you?
Senior uncle.
I'm your acquaintance.
Sizhui.
Go and get a bowl of glutinous rice congee. Go!
We still don't know who he is,
whether he's friend or foe.
Why should we save him
without a second thought?
If he were a bad guy,
wouldn't we be letting a snake in?
But it is also possible that he's a good person.
Didn't you see him outside surrounded by puppets?
He's definitely not a bad guy.
No matter what,
not helping a dying person is against our clan's rules.
Fine.
You're the good guys.
If someone dies, it's not my fault.
Senior Mo.
The Frostwork?
Is he...
Xiao Xingchen.
Oh, no. There are so many puppets out there!
How many is "so many"?
I do not know!
They fill the entire street. Probably hundreds!
I don't think the door can hold them off any longer!
Senior Mo,
are you going to use the Summoning again?
If you dot twice in each one's eyes,
how much blood will you lose?
How about using my blood?
- I can also spare some.  -Me too.  -Me too.
You've only been cultivating for a few years.
Are there any blank talismans?
Written ones are fine as well.
Disperse!
Song Lan?
Tie him up.
Bro Song.
Song Lan.
Detached tongue.
My God?
Who could be so vicious?
Have any of you
studied "association with spirits"?
Me. I have.
Have you brought your Qin?
Yes.
How is your Qin language?
Any practical experience?
Will the spirit that you summon be able to lie?
Hanguang Jun said that Sizhui's Qin language is fine.
Hanguang Jun told me
to focus on quality instead of quantity.
The spirit that I summon will be able to
avoid answering, but won't be able to lie.
So, if it is willing to answer,
then it will definitely speak the truth.
Then, let's start.
The first question.
Who is he?
What did he say?
Song Lan.
Good.
Looks like your Qin language is not bad.
The answer is correct.
Then ask the second question.
Who killed him?
That is impossible!
What did he say?
He said...
Xiao Xingchen.
You played it wrong, right?
No.
"Who are you" and "who killed you" are the two
easiest and most common questions
in association with spirits.
When someone first starts to learn association with spirits,
these are the first and second sentences that he learns.
I've practiced them no less than ten thousand times.
And I checked them before I played.
I definitely didn't play them wrong.
Either you played it wrong,
or you interpreted the Qin language wrong.
Impossible.
If playing them wrong is impossible,
then interpreting them wrong is even more impossible.
The name and the three characters of "Xiao Xingchen"
are not at all common in the spirits' answers.
If he answered a different name
and I interpreted it wrong,
it would not have just happened to be this three characters.
It's said Song Lan went to find the missing Xiao Xingchen,
But he just said Xiao Xingchen killed him.
Why would Xiao kill his own good friend?
He doesn't seem like this sort of person.
Sizhui,
ask the third question.
Who is controlling him?
The. One. Behind. You.
Don't move!
Stay back!
In terms of swordsmanship,
even everybody here added up
wouldn't be a worthy opponent to this Song Lan.
Adults are going to talk to adults.
The children can wait outside.
Go outside for now.
You won't be much help here, anyways.
The poisoning powder should have settled.
When you go outside, don't run around and stir up the dust again.
Breathe slowly.
Sizhui,
you're the most sensible here.
Guide them a bit.
Can you do that?
Don't be scared.
I am not.
Really?
Senior Mo, you are so much like Hanguang Jun.
Us? How are we alike?
We are obviously like fire and ice.
I do not know, either.
But it just feel fimiliar.
It is as though if either one of the two seniors is present,
I will not need to be scared or worried about anything.
Cure of the poisoning powder?
Correct.
Much more effective than your terrible congee,
right?
And it tastes sweet.
Your performance was wonderful.
From courageously killing puppets, tiring out,
to getting poisoned
and losing consciousness.
You have worked so hard
for our entertainment, huh?
Not for you all,
but for you alone.
I'm guessing that
you haven't yet told anyone who you really are, have you?
So, I didn't expose your secret either
and let them go outside
for we could shut the doors and talk in privacy.
How's that?
Am I thoughtful?
All puppets in Coffin Town
were made by your Stygian Tiger Amulet?
Just as you guys came in
and your fluting started,
I began to see who you are.
But the fog is so heavy
and we haven't seen each other for years.
So I had to sound out you.
Though Hanguang Jun is a little troublesome.
But it was not difficult for my friend
to keep him occupied in Coffin Town for a short time.
All right.
I don't have time chatting with you.
Get to the point.
So, taking the group of children as hostage,
what do you want me to do?
Senior, I want you to do me a favor.
A tiny favor.
Whose spiritual cognition is this?
It's already in shambles.
Even glue won't be able to stick it together.
If this person's spiritual cognition
was that easy to stick together,
why would I need your help?
You want me to fix this spiritual cognition?
No offense,
but there really isn't much left of it in here.
If a spiritual cognition itself
doesn't have any desire to live,
then it'll most likely be impossible to save.
If I'm not wrong,
this person is dead already.
Now that he's dead
how can I save him?
Don't you understand this more than anyone?
I don't understand and I don't care!
Wasn't Win Ning dead?
Now that you could have revived him,
there must be a way...
Who told you Win Ning was dead?
He didn't die at all, okay?
Since you call me Senior,
I'll tell you a truth.
Most of the rumors on the world are not to be trusted.
You have to do it even if you don't want to.
Senior, don't you forget
those kids you brought
are still staring at you from outside,
waiting for you to help them out of the danger.
Haven't seen you for years.
You haven't changed a bit, have you?
Xue Yang,
why are you pretending to be a cultivator
when you actually are a delinquent?
Uh-oh. You found out.
Purposely pretended to be poisoned
so that our consciences would urge us to save you.
purposely showing us the upper part of Frostwork.
You know not only how to pretend to be injured and defenseless,
but also how to gain the sympathy of others.
You truly brought out a genuine, virtuous Xiao Xingchen just now.
If we hadn't fought before
I really would have believed
that you were Xiao Xingchen.
Well, it's true that his reputation is better than mine.
Of course I pretended to be him.
It's easier to gain the trust of others this way.
That was some
excellent acting right there.
Now you're just flattering me.
I have a friend.
His acting is what I'd call excellent.
I still have a long way to go.
Anyways,
enough for the chit-chat.
You are Yiling Patriarch, the founder of crafty tricks.
I deem you as my senior,
so you really have to do me this favor.
You're the one who made the long nails that controlled
Song Lan and Wen Ning, aren't you?
You can even restore half of Stygian Tiger Amulet,
so why would you need my help to
restore a spiritual cognition?
They're not the same.
You're the founder.
If you never made Stygian Tiger Amulet,
I wouldn't have been able to
make Yin Iron as effective as half the Amulet.
When we parted,
I didn't expect
that you could have used Yin Iron
to invent Stygian Tiger Amulet, such a treasure.
I misjudged you at that time.
So you did hide
the Chang clan's Yin Iron back then.
Wrong.
I did hide a shard of Yin Iron,
but it's not Chang clan's.
How could Chang clan of Yueyang have Yin Iron?
They were too weak.
You guys are so gullible!
I did hide one shard of Yin Iron privately.
But
I hid it before I went to the Nevernight.
No wonder
we turned Chang clan inside out
with no Yin Iron to be found.
"Yin Iron is intelligent,
suppressed in four directions."
People only know this sentence,
but doesn't know there's another sentence after it.
"All the energy of the four directions belong to Xuanwu."
The Slaughter Xuanwu?
So Senior Wei,
you were so lucky to have found
the last shard of Yin Iron
sealed in the sword
by accident.
So
you already knew there are five shards of Yin Iron.
You are so good.
You could have hidden Yin Iron for so many years
without leaking out any info.
Hence everyone thinks that
I took away your Yin Iron
and made the Amulet.
I feel I'm not your equal.
No, no, no.
You are better than me.
I just happened to discover
some secrets of Yin Iron,
but you're self-taught
when making the Amulet.
You're being too humble.
It's not being humble.
It's the truth.
I never like to exaggerate when I'm talking.
If I say I'm gonna kill someone's entire clan,
I'll actually kill their entire clan.
I won't even leave a dog behind.
Like Chang clan of Yueyang and Snow White Pavilion?
Fight outside, Wen Ning.
Guess who's gonna win?
Would I need to guess? Wen Ning, of course.
It's such a shame that
even though I had put so many nails in his head,
he is still unwilling to obey.
Things that are too loyal
are also quite troublesome.
Wen Ning is not a thing.
Don't you see that
what you said could be interpreted in a different way?
Yeah.
Do you often sneak up on people in the middle of a conversation?
Of course. I'm a delinquent, aren't I?
It's not like you know me for the first day.
Anyway, it's not the first day that I want to kill you.
I just want to make you unable to move. Then I can take you back
and you can take your time repairing the cognition.
I've already said that I can't do anything about it.
Don't be so eager to refuse me.
If you don't know what to do about it,
the both of us can discuss the matter together.
Are you really taking advantage
of my body's low spiritual power?
That's right!
Well, there's an old saying.
"Better upset a decent man than a rogue",
which is you, in this case.
I'm not dealing with you any longer. I'll get you someone else.
Who else?
That Hanguang Jun?
My friend is keeping him occupied.
Should I call this "to come in time
is better than to come early"?
Hanguang Jun, we meet again!
Give me the sword back.
You do not deserve this sword.
The Looming Disaster?
The name of this sword matches you perfectly.
Step back. You are not needed here.
Senior Mo! Senior Mo!
I don't think I'm needed here, either.
Let's go.
Aha. I'll definitely be needed there.
Everyone alright?
Yes!
We all listened to you and held our breaths.
Good.
If anyone doesn't listen to me,
I'll feed him that congee again.
No. No more please.
He's so good!
Well, obviously. Of course Hanguang Jun is good.
He just never likes to show it off. He is very low-key,
right?
Are you asking me?
So you think that Hanguang Jun is not good?!
He's good.
Of course. He's really good. He's the best.
Not good.
With so many people,
if we are surrounded by a large group of puppets,
escape will be impossible.
Go!
Where to?
Follow the sound of the bamboo pole.
You want us to
follow an unidentified person?
Who knows where she'll lead us to!
That's precisely what you're going to do.
The sound has been following you guys
ever since you entered the town, correct?
You were trying to go into the town,
but she was leading you toward the town gate, where you ran into us.
She actually was chasing you out.
She was trying to save you!
Hanguang Jun,
it's up to you now.
We're gonna go ahead!
Let's go.
Last night, she clearly wanted to tell us
something really urgent,
but couldn't express it.
However, she disappeared as soon as Xue Yang came.
She was most likely trying to avoid Xue Yang.
Anyways, she definitely isn't on the same side as him.
Xue Yang?!
The Xue Yang who massacred Chang clan?
He's not dead?
Why is Xue Yang here as well?
Wasn't it Xiao Xingchen and Song Lan?
Uhh. I'll explain that later.
Anyways, the one fighting with Hanguang Jun
isn't Xiao Xingchen, but Xue Yang,
who pretended to be him.
We've already come this far. Let's go in.
This is the so-called Coffin Home?
Where dead people are temporarily put?
That's right.
Corpses that aren't claimed by anyone,
are often put into here.
Why did she bring us to the Coffin House?
It can't be because we
won't be surrounded by puppets here, can it?
Where did she go herself?
It's likely that we really won't be surrounded.
We've been standing still for so long already.
Has anyone heard any puppets?
- No. - No.
Senior Mo.
She wants us to open this coffin for her?
Would it be that her family's body is inside?
Stay back!
Stand further back.
In case it is not a corpse inside and spurts out
some more poisoning powder at you.
Xiao...
= Jing =
Senior Mo.
Don't worry.
Since this girl can't talk
should I associate with spirit again?
There's no need.
We may not be able to
ask the question she wants us to ask.
And I think that her reply will be quite complex, quite difficult
to interpret.
Then what should we do?
How about Empathy?
No way!
Too dangerous!
Using such a wicked trick,
a little carelessness will get you destroyed.
You may never return.
Unless there is a...
Enough! We're running out of time.
Form up now.
Let's begin.
We still need to go back for Hanguang Jun when it's done.