Why won't this open?
Who is this?
You were home.
I'm the realtor. Please open the door.
What do you think you're doing now?
-Why would you try to unlock--
-I didn't know you were home.
I thought the house was empty,
so I tried the old passcode.
Are you kidding me now?
You popped up in the middle of the night
and tried to unlock my door.
This is just ludicrous.
Come on. I said it was just a mistake.
Don't be like that.
I talked to the landlord, and I heard
you needed to move out urgently.
I don't care. I can't open the door
to random visits like this.
Come during the day and call in advance.
People these days
only have time after work,
and that's when they check out apartments.
If you don't cooperate,
it will only delay your moving day.
I have plenty of other apartments
to show him.
I can't just wait like this
with a customer.
So what do you say? Should I just go?
A newlywed couple used to live here.
Then they bought a house with the savings
and moved out.
It's built with good materials,
so there are no defects.
-The master bedroom is here.
-Okay.
Wait.
The young lady lives alone, so it's clean.
There's nothing to fix up.
-Is that so?
-Yes.
That's not true!
-I don't live here alone!
-Okay.
Thanks. We will call you.
Let's go.
I'm going to run away
before I get caught.
I don't get it.
She said she didn't want to run away.
EPISODE 7
THE BOLT OPENS
HONGJIK
Let's take this…
The young lady lives alone, so it's clean.
Is she taking the trash now?
I think so.
Hi, Ms. Kim.
-Hi.
Right. Today is trash day.
-Gosh. You're right.
-Gosh, I must take out the trash again.
Goodness. Why don't you just open a bar?
My husband always has a drink
during dinner.
Gosh, that can't be good for him.
You'll have your second child soon enough.
No way. I just got out of that nightmare.
-It would be a disaster.
-Goodness.
Are you still on a diet these days?
I'm trying to lose some belly fat,
but it's not easy.
Well, it's because
you're so nice and easygoing.
You need to be grumpy and sensitive
to lose weight.
Look at the lady in Unit 506.
She's skinny like a twig.
I guess you're right.
How diligent of you.
Hey.
You know us now, right?
We're the members
of the Women's Association.
Yes.
Right.
You know, the Women's Association has
so much to do.
If we don't keep a close eye
on the recycling station,
people just dump anything everywhere.
We also care about the security
within the apartment.
On rainy days,
we clean the cigarette butts
so the water doesn't flood.
We watch the parking lot too.
-And we hold the market as well.
-We hold the meetings too.
Right.
So what?
You see, I don't ask just anyone
to work with me.
But yesterday at the meeting,
I saw you were
greatly interested
in the future of our apartment.
And to my surprise,
you were very proactive.
And I
was convinced that it won't hurt us
to have you in the Women's Association.
I'm afraid I can't do that.
What?
Why's that?
I'm moving out soon.
Oh, my.
She's moving…
-Hi.
-Hey.
Wait. Are you sure that's all plastic?
-My goodness.
-Oh, no.
My gosh!
Take this out now. Gosh!
Jeez!
With this much food,
it should go to the regular trash bin.
Come on. Take it out already.
-Gosh.
-Or go wash them.
Gosh! I can't believe this.
I have food delivered
so that I won't have to do the dishes.
-I don't have time for that.
-Don't be ridiculous.
You don't even have a job.
Take them all out already.
-Gosh.
-Gosh. What to do with you?
By the way,
why is Unit 506 moving out suddenly?
I don't know. How am I supposed to know?
Gosh. Why don't you know?
You two hang out all the time.
You seemed to have gotten closer
after all that quarreling.
Now, you won't have anyone to fight with.
You'll get lonely.
No, I wouldn't.
It feels great to finally be
free from all the drama.
Well, if it feels so great,
why do you look so sulky?
By the way, I wonder why Unit 506 took
the sneakers someone dumped here.
Well, I guess she liked them.
The white ones?
-Those with colorful patches?
-Yes.
-Those with the air soles?
They're mine.
What?
You threw them away anyway.
No, I didn't.
I didn't throw them away.
They accidentally got mixed in the trash.
And even if I threw them away,
she can't take them just like that.
What kind of a lunatic does that?
Gosh, this is infuriating.
I've got to talk some sense into her.
What's his problem?
Geez.
Look at him all excited
to go pick a fight with her.
Honey!
I'll get the door!
I told you to put your shoes aside!
How many honeys do you have?
Sorry to bother your date,
but I'm here to get my sneakers
that you picked up earlier.
Give them back to me.
Yes, there they are.
There. Give them back to me.
Those are mine.
But you threw them away.
Hey, lady.
I may have thrown them away,
but I changed my mind
and went to take them back.
And, you know,
if I had known you would take them,
I wouldn't have thrown them away.
So stop being stubborn
and give my sneakers back.
They're right there. Give them back to me.
Come on. Hurry.
This isn't what I expected.
Hurry up, okay?
Do you think this is
reserve forces training?
-Check out that lady.
-I'm putting them on now!
Are you okay? Wake up.
-Ma'am, wake up.
-What?
-Button it up.
-Do you recognize where you are?
I don't know.
How much did she drink
to end up like that?
I told you we are a couple.
What kind of lovers get wasted like…
-Hey. Take him away.
-Yes, sir.
Get your hands off me.
I can go by myself. Damn it.
-Hey.
-Hey, I found Yang's stuff.
What?
What do I do?
After all the fuss,
now you've locked yourself out.
Damn it. What's wrong with this?
Darn it.
What was it?
What's wrong? Can't you open it?
I don't know. I changed the passcode,
and now the door won't open.
I don't know why.
Seriously.
Use your left brain, okay?
It's driving me nuts!
010-0128-4550
LOCKSMITH
Hi. We tried to change the passcode
and something seems to have gone wrong.
The door won't open.
Hongjik Apartment.
It'll take about two hours?
Sure. Please come over.
This is Unit 506 of Building 105.
Okay. Bye.
He says he can open the door
without breaking the lock.
He's coming in two hours,
so wait until he comes.
But I definitely followed
the instructions.
Well, I guess you accidentally
pressed some other button.
Bye now.
Are you…
going to wait there like that?
Yes.
I can't go anywhere.
Both my phone and wallet are inside.
You can stay in my place if you want.
I was about to go out anyway.
Never mind if you don't want to.
Anyway, the passcode is 2345 and star.
INTERROGATION ROOM
Hey, the headquarters will come back
any minute to transfer him!
Come on. I can finish it in ten…
No, five minutes.
I'll finish it in five. Wait here.
Keep watch here.
Look, I told you everything.
You said you'd order me some soup.
What now?
It's coming.
We ordered one from a famous restaurant,
and it's on its way here now.
You know Yang, right?
Yang?
Of course!
Who's Yang?
What's his name?
Well, obviously, Yang is Yang.
That's just what they're called.
Why would we go by our real names?
I see.
Then what does Yang look like?
Well, obviously, Yang looks like Yang.
We're not doing anything good here.
What's the point
of knowing each other's faces?
So you're saying you don't know
Yang's name or his face.
That means you don't know him, idiot.
Why did you act like you knew him?
You're really getting on my nerves.
Then tell me.
Do you know Gangnam Mad Dog?
Of course I do!
No junkie in the business
doesn't know about Gangnam Mad Dog.
I heard he's a nutcase.
That nutcase is me, asshole.
It's dark in here.
What did you say earlier?
You tell us you know everything,
but you won't tell us anything.
What did you say earlier? Tell me.
Something about soup?
I'm going to thrust the radish pickles
up your nostrils, so you can't breathe!
Gangnam Mad Dog has still got it.
I'm not lying.
These days, we use the deep web
and social media for business.
There's no reason for a small fry like me
to see a head honcho.
Then how do you get the drugs?
I go to the bar Yang tells me to go to
and ask the waiter for the "keep bottle."
Then there's this little thing
inside the liquor bottle.
Wait.
Did you say the waiter?
One second.
So, all the footage from the entrance
and inside the bar were deleted.
This is all that's left.
The dashcam footage
from a car at the entrance.
Wait. Stop.
Damn it…
Damn it!
Zoom in.
Oh, my. You're awake.
Sorry. I tried to be quiet.
Hello.
I live next door,
but I got locked out of my apartment,
so Hwi-oh let me stay here.
That's one long story
to say you're his girlfriend.
-Please have a seat.
-I'm not his girlfriend.
I'm really not.
I should get going now.
I'm sorry.
You're not leaving.
You said Hwi-oh told you to stay here.
Help yourself. Eating alone
is what I hate the most.
Okay.
I'm really not Hwi-oh's girlfriend
or anything.
I just want to make that clear.
Okay. I get it.
Now eat up. Help yourself.
Okay.
It's tasty.
Eat up.
Well then. Thanks for the meal.
Are you a good cook?
No, I don't know how to cook.
I just eat out or get delivery food.
Oh, well.
That's great.
Don't ever learn how to cook.
You have to keep doing it once you do.
If you're good at it, it's just a pain.
Hwi-oh was such a tiny and weak baby
when he was born.
That's why he's such a picky eater.
Hey, mom.
Hey, son.
Go wash up.
When did you come…
What?
Why are you still here?
I told her to stay and have dinner.
Wait. Where were we?
Right.
Hwi-oh was born so tiny.
I took him to the women's sauna
until he was 11,
and nobody stopped me.
-So…
-Mom.
So you have one older sister.
-Is she married?
-Yes.
I guess your family wants you
to hurry and get married too.
What's your date and time of birth?
-I was born in April, 1991.
-That's the Year of the Sheep.
Come on. If you're finished,
you should go now.
Come on. Stand up.
Hey. She only had one bite.
She's finished.
Come on and stand up.
Come on. Stand up.
-Son, she can't just leave like…
-Come on. Hurry up.
Thanks for the food.
What are you thanking me for?
You didn't even get to finish.
-Goodbye.
-Gosh, I'm so sorry.
My goodness.
Come again, okay?
Why did you have to
send her away like that?
You really disappointed me.
She might be your savior.
Savior, my foot.
It's not like what you think.
She got locked out of her apartment,
so I let her stay here for a while.
I know. She told me.
She said the realtor
who got her the apartment
tried to unlock her door
in the middle of the night.
She must've been so scared.
You may not know it,
there are so many things to fear
when a woman lives alone.
There are so many things to fear
This is why Buddha said
one must not take
making acquaintances lightly.
Hey, unlock it.
This won't go in with the lock in the way.
What is that?
What you desperately need right now.
If you're not opening the door,
I'll just leave. What do you say?
Never mind. I'll just go.
Wait.
Gosh, where should I start?
Good. Now, it looks like a place
where a man lives.
Now, the bad guys
who try to get in here will think
Don Lee is living here
and run away.
I know you like him.
Don Lee.
Yes.
So did you decide
to move out?
When?
Well, when the place gets sold.
Okay. Then give my things back to me
when you move out.
That will do.
I'll get going then.
I guess this is like
a farewell party then.
What's wrong? Are you upset
now that I'm actually moving out?
Well, it's quite upsetting.
Now, I'll be the only crazy one
around here.
Well…
I guess we can't have
two suns under one sky.
You know…
if I'm the reason why you're moving out,
you shouldn't go.
I'm pretty used to you now.
I also like the free food I get sometimes.
And every day, I wonder
what will happen this time.
And…
You're not significant enough to me
to affect my decisions in life.
Get over yourself.
Are you that scared of people?
Is it so hard to trust them?
Yes.
I told you,
I can't trust anyone.
And the person I can't trust the most
is myself.
I'm not sure if I turned off the stove,
closed the window,
or turned off the gas valve.
And that scares me.
I saw an old lady on TV before,
who was beating a pot the entire day
with a mask on, saying she smells gas.
I might end up like her.
Actually…
I might end up worse than that.
I'm sure you will beat
something even weirder than a pot.
Something like a drum.
You might even bend back and play a gong.
Stupid idiot!
You just cursed at me, didn't you?
Gosh.
I hate rain.
I feel horrible.
I can't trust you either.
I can't trust what you say.
You said you can't beat women.
You only said that to look cool, right?
What?
"Hi, I don't beat women."
Is this supposed to make women like me?
Well, I'm a man. It's just normal.
Some men are not like that.
What kind of an asshole does that?
The kind of asshole
that whispers all sorts of sweet talk
in your ear,
but everything he says
turns out to be a lie.
A married asshole.
When things didn't go his way,
he would suddenly change and…
And that's not all.
He said I flirted with him,
knowing he was married.
He said I was a crazy, obsessive bitch
who threatened to
destroy his family.
He said that's why he beat me.
He said I deserved it.
People always told me
that I'm mean and crazy about money.
They called me a bitch
and a hussy.
Did you
just let them talk like that?
You should have said that's not true!
Who knows?
I might have actually known
that he was married.
Do you think I didn't know?
I'm not even sure if I turned off
the gas valve or not,
so how can I be sure
whether I knew or not?
It might be that
those people wished it was true.
They were probably jealous
because you're so pretty.
So don't listen to them.
In fact, people don't care about others
as much as you think.
Some people still think
that Choi Bool-am and Kim Hye-ja
are really a married couple.
From Country Diaries?
I know. I may not look old enough
to remember that show.
Fine.
I will go crazy,
if that's what you guys want.
Today on, I'm going to let myself go!
Speaking of which…
What?
Do you want to sleep with me tonight?
What do you mean by, "speaking of which"?
Is that what you meant by going crazy?
Are you saying
sleeping with me is going crazy?
I'm sorry.
I love the sound of police sirens.
I feel like they're coming to save me.
It must be your birthday. Congratulations.
Congratulations.
This is an ambulance.
And a fire truck goes…
But…
This one is a little sad.
Right?
The rain's stopped. Let's go.
Excuse me. Check, please.
Bye, then.
Bye.
Was the valve turned off?
What?
Yes.
How about the windows? Were they closed?
See?
So trust yourself.
You're one meticulous woman,
and there's no way
you let him fool you like that.
I'm saying…
you didn't do anything wrong.
Hey, wait.
Well…
Howi wants to say something to you.
"Hey, thanks for helping me the other day.
Do you want to come over for ramyeon?"
HI, I'M HOWI
I'M BUSY (LOOKING FOR TREATS)
IN THE MORNING
HWI-OH'S PLACE NEVER HAS
ANYTHING TO EAT
I'M HUNGRY
HERE WE GO
WHERE'S MIN-KYUNG?
IS THAT HER?
I GOT SOME TREATS
TIME FOR A WALK WITH
HWI-OH (HEART) MIN-KYUNG
THE AIR IS CLEAR TODAY
HWI-OH SAID I GET A TREAT
IF I PLAY DEAD WELL
WHO IS IT…
AT THIS HOUR…
I'M A GOOD PUP WHO GOES TO BED EARLY
AND WAKES UP EARLY
SEE YOU TOMORROW (WINK)
Subtitle translation by: Sun-young Baek