[This series's characters, behaviors, places,
organizations, professions, and events]
[are fictional and created for entertainment.
They are not intended to guide or encourage]
[any actions in the story.
Please use your discretion.]
Trust me, I can defeat lawyer Win this time.
Lawyer Prao got the highest score.
[Previously on LAW-LESS]
A lawyer who helps the mafia.
The mafia is a human.
I've been running from the truth
of that city for a long time.
It's time to go back and sort everything out.
Why are you here?
I'm here to chase the moneylenders
out of this office.
We build this place for
your law firm, boss, okay?
Dad, what happened?
Those loan sharks took stuff for the debt.
Did you come all the way here to harass me?
Is being a mafia lawyer not enough
to live on? That's why you became a loan shark.
That's the past.
Tomorrow, this place will be a law firm.
Oh, then all of my dad's debt is over.
Hey, no way.
I just changed business. The debt remains.
Being my assistant is the only way
to pay off your father's debt.
I want to handle your case.
I have the best lawyer.
Why should I trust you two?
I don't want you to die in prison, Sargent.
Hello.
I'm lawyer Boripat.
I just opened a law firm in this city.
I've heard a lot about Attorney Koson.
I want to introduce myself to you.
A young and energetic lawyer who wants to
initiate a work. I'm happy to support you.
Thank you very much.
If you don't mind,
can I buy the former mayor's murder case?
I'm happy to pay the full amount
to get this case in our hands.
Look, our law firm is setting up.
If we get this case, we'll be famous.
The young generation wants to
build a career by all means, huh?
Have some dignity, Mr. Lawyer.
Listen, If you want to settle in this city,
you better start from…
being an assistant in the law firm.
Are you thinking of eating a big fish?
Please consider it.
I'm happy to pay the full amount.
Hey, Itt.
Lawyer Koson is hastily arranging
evidence for you.
I'm also lobbying the prosecutor.
But these guys are so demanding.
I want to leave now.
Do whatever you need!
Don't worry.
Everything will be fine.
How's my mom?
I sent someone to watch over her.
I'll send her whatever she needs.
I told her that you sent it.
And right now, you're busy
chasing the thief who killed the former mayor.
Your mom believes you.
Thanks a lot, man.
Yeah.
The new lawyer came from nowhere and told me
to choose him as my new lawyer.
He said that
you guys would let me die in prison.
Just a new guy who wants fame.
New-graduated lawyers have no dignity.
They want to do big cases
so they can be famous.
They also came to ask me for a job.
Hey, we've helped each other many times.
You have to be as confident as I am.
Everything will be fine.
I didn't expect you to order durian from me.
Durian from my farm
is not as beautiful as others.
But I guarantee you it's sweet in every seed.
You did it all by myself.
You must be exhausted, auntie.
I have to do it anyway.
My son is busy.
He is a policeman.
He barely comes home.
He's chasing thieves.
You're so proud of him, huh?
Not exactly. He hasn't come home…
for a long time. Just sending stuff.
I miss you, Mom.
I'm waiting for your
birthday present this year.
No matter where you are,
or how long I have to wait for you.
I assign the case of the former mayor to you.
I'm glad to see you grow up as I expected.
You gave me opportunities.
No, it's because you're capable.
Our city's justice
lies in a new generation like you.
Thank you to her, Aeri.
I apologize, ma'am.
The young generation
does not really pay respect.
No need, no.
I raised her from the beginning.
Don't be fussy.
Sorry.
Come on, Prao.
Oh my gosh.
Is this my scholar reunion party?
Have a seat.
I'm glad to give you both the law scholarship.
As a fund secretary,
I can't help but feel sorry.
The scholarship student's license was revoked.
And she hasn't won a single case.
I'm sorry.
How's it going, Prao?
The lawyer you work with.
I heard you had an issue with him.
So, a fellowship lawyer works with illegals?
Did you get a job already?
Well, I was just happy for nothing.
I thought you would help me out.
But if you want to work
with the city prosecutor's office,
you should have a clear record.
Also, you don't have a license.
You'll get a license soon.
You can work with me once you get it.
I want both of you to help me.
You can help Aeri at the office.
You two grew up together.
You are a prosecutor now.
You can teach her.
I mean…
I want to take the job that I promised
and finish it.
I'll think of another later.
If you promised someone,
you have to do your best.
This is…
the first step of a law enforcement officer.
Oh, then…
I'll go home.
If you can't take it or are uncomfortable,
you can come back anytime.
Yes, ma'am.
Thank you very much.
Goodbye.
Bye.
Take care of yourself.
Right now.
Our law firm's employee position is fulfilled.
I want to announce the opening
of a law firm called…
Uh, what's a name do you think, boss?
A law firm full of lawless people.
Yes, sir.
A lawless law firm.
Someday, this town will be real.
Everyone,
from what I've investigated with Hook,
lawyer Koson and Olarn are very close.
And lawyer Koson
handled legal matters for the Olarn Group.
There are documents that the former mayor
suspended several important projects
of the Olarn Group,
especially the latest project
before he was killed.
And the New Tulakham project
has already been supported
by a banker, Mr. Vasu.
And this is…
Mr. Pradit,
the auditor.
He's now in jail.
However,
all this news quickly disappeared
because of someone…
had manipulated this town.
That's this guy, Editor Harn.
[Court of Tulakham]
Hello, ma'am.
How's your new job?
Well… It's strange, but it's going smoothly.
That's good.
If you need my help, tell me.
I still owe your mother a lot.
But I don't give up on my mother.
Oh… ma'am.
We are suspicious in Olarn.
But I'm not so sure.
If the evidence is unclear,
anything is possible.
But you look tired.
Let's go for a ride.
Don't kick it out of the field.
Dribble ball. Dribble ball.
Roll it here.
Don't kick it out of the field.
Be careful.
I used to study here.
Your mother must have studied here, too.
When I'm discouraged
or hesitating about what I'm doing.
When I see the kids, I can't give up.
I want them to grow up in a good environment
and no fear.
And for you,
I don't want you to be discouraged,
no matter what.
Yes.
What's up, kids?
We believe that you're not the killer.
But we don't believe that your lawyer
will get you out of here.
You must not leave here,
and they will benefit.
Excuse me, can I talk to him alone?
If you mess with my mom,
I'll kill you!
Remember!
You can't kill me.
You can't kill me 18 years ago, until now.
Let me go. Let me go.
Shut up!
You stay still!
Ouch!
Hey!
I will drag you out of here
for what you did 18 years ago by myself.
Guard! Come get me!
Guard, help me, come get me.
You can't use force in here.
Take me away, take me away.
Go.
What have you done?
Are you crazy?
I'm sorry.
Why is it so slow?
I'm going crazy in here.
You don't know what I've been through.
You better tell me.
Will you help me or let me rot in here?
Tell me clearly.
What the hell are you talking about?
Think of your mom.
Your mom is sick now.
I take good care of her.
Even if you leave now, what can you do?
I'm now doing it for everyone,
for this city,
and for you.
You have no choice but to help me.
Whatever I say, you must do it.
Sir, Itt requested to change lawyer.
Contact Shin.
Yes, sir.
Itt agree to change lawyer.
Call lawyer Prao, and let's meet at the court.
Now.
- Let's go!
- Yay!
We've been through a lot.
I have this day because of you.
Why did you believe
that powerless lawyer over me?
You don't understand what I'm doing.
My mother is old.
The more you care for your mother,
the more you have to listen to me.
Are you threatening me?
I'm not.
But I'm doing it for this city.
No one can change me.
And the best way is…
I have to die in this prison.
Right!
Oh!
Assistant Prao has yet to arrive.
That's really strange.
Hello.
Hello, Lawyer.
Do you remember this client?
I'm busy, can't talk.
Hey, wait.
Aren't you going to care, Win?
That Lawyer Prao is here.
Do whatever you want.
That woman is just a debtor.
Oh, Win.
Hello, Win.
Gosh!
He doesn't care about me.
I'm just a debtor.
I hate him just as much as you do.
But since we're here, anyway.
Even though Win doesn't care about you,
I do care.
Do you know that?
Kidnapping and confinement is a crimes
under the Criminal Code, Section ADL123.
You'll get a big jail term.
Oh, that's scary.
I'm so scared.
Lawyer Prao is with Shin.
We'll handle this ourselves. Don't worry, bro.
They're playing with fire.
So, what's the progress on
the New Tulakham project?
It's all fine.
All the surrounding land belongs to you.
The project will go on soon.
It must be fun in the court today.
Attorney Erika Phongpinij
filed a lawsuit against Police Sergeant,
Itt Kaew Udon.
The defendant was charged
with the murder of the Tulakham mayor.
The court has suspended the trial
for both parties
to find more witnesses and evidence,
so that the court can conduct the trial fairly.
Where is Lawyer Boripat?
Why he's not here?
Relax.
My boss never makes mistakes.
Then who will be my lawyer?
The trial begins.
Prosecutor, please.
I am Prosecutor Erika Phongpinij.
I want to inform you of the charges.
Police Sergeant Itt Kaew Udon is a defendant.
He committed the murder of the Tulakham mayor.
Please invite the defense lawyer
for cross-examination.
I'm Tankhun Sopharak, the defense lawyer,
May I conduct an investigation?
I dispute the prosecutor's accusation.
From examining the evidence,
it was found that the traces of his walking,
which had a crippled leg,
were different from the traces at the scene,
your honor.
Excuse me.
That's my subordinate and debtor.
If you want to do something,
You have to ask for my permission.
You owe me once again.
Aren't you rushing to the court?
Untie me, come on.
The defendant is a police officer.
Why would he commit the crime
and leave evidence?
That's right.
The defendant is a police officer.
He should know the law.
Yeah. This is correct.
It's just like my house.
I have a durian plantation,
but I don't plant durian.
I plant durian
but I don't plant Monthong durian
despite its fragrant, crispy,
and delicious taste.
It's worldwide famous.
Objection, your honor.
Your honor,
he talked about issues unrelated to the case.
But I still need to finish…
the durian topic.
I agree with the prosecutor.
Your point is not related to the case.
I want the prosecutor
to question the defendant.
I'd like to submit additional evidence
to consider.
Objection!
I'd like to protest the submission of evidence.
Overruled.
I accept additional documents
to consider the case.
Defense lawyer, please continue.
Do you have any additional issues?
If not…
Yes, ma'am.
Please.
Your honor,
you are the idol of justice.
You have judged the case,
and dealt with many influential in Tulakham.
Is it possible
there will be a wrong decision in the case?
Objection!
It's not relevant to the case.
I request to examine the defense lawyer.
Please show your license.
You can't do this.
Objection, your honor.
I request that the prosecutor be examined, too.
Yes, I protest.
Yes, I want to protest.
I'm Boripat Preechachai, the defense lawyer.
Let's go, see you later.
I create chaos in the court
by postponing the trial.
Then, we find more evidence in the prison.
End of trial.
The court will set the date for the trial.
Wait!
What do I do now?
Remember,
you're a lawyer,
even though your license is suspended.
I have to be like this because I helped you.
You have to take responsibility.
Are you working at a law firm or a gangster?
He's alone, but you can't fight him.
What else can you do, Shin?
Sir, sir.
Don't give up on me, sir.
Get out.
I don't want to see you.
There you go, sir.
Hello.
I want to speak to the judge.
She's not available right now.
Please make an appointment for me.
It's important.
Hello.
I was born in Tulakham.
I know every corner of it.
I'm the only one who knows
how to make it better.
I haven't been to jail in years.
I feel like…
coming to a memorable place.
Bro, I can walk with my eyes closed.
Mr. Pradit, the auditor.
He's now in jail.
How are you? Mr. Pradit.
You!
What the hell are you doing?
Will you put me in jail?
They're trying to stop me.
I'm going to change the lawyer.
I'm trying to help you.
What do you know about Olarn?
Do you know what he's thinking?
Obviously, he doesn't want you to get out.
I'm the only one
who wants you to get out as soon as possible.
Don't forget.
I was born here.
I grew up in this city's market.
I ate leftover food from a rice soup shop.
I slept in this shrine.
I built myself from sweat and countless scars.
I can call myself a son of Tulakham.
Therefore, I have established
the Jaibun Than Khun Pandin Foundation
to protect our people of Tulakham.
I now announce that our foundation
aims to protect our Tulakham people
from all the influential people.
I set up a foundation to provide refuge
for the people.
I'm from this city.
Therefore, contributing to my hometown
is the best thing I can do.
Besides what you're doing now,
is there anything else you want to do?
That's a very good question.
It's education.
I'm happy to support education.
For example, the judge's foundation.
She has a perfect idea of education.
It's worth supporting.
She gives scholarships to young people
to study law.
This is very good.
Our young generation
will have the opportunity to study.
They will become good lawyers,
a good attorney.
They're not just a good lawyer,
but a great one.
Who the hell are you?
What do you want?
Stay out.
Leave me alone.
You're going to have a hard time
living in peace.
Fresh air.
How's my law firm?
The worst thing about the law
is when someone like you
gets a few days in jail.
What do you say, Tan?
You have to thank the judge.
You came out so fast.
He just went to work.
When he finished, he came out.
Grilled squid here is the best.
If you feed me,
I'll reduce your debt by two thousand.
There you go.
Bro,
look at Olarn.
He's bragging big time.
We need to hurry up.
Otherwise, Sargent Itt will never come out.
If Itt is not the murderer,
we must find the real murderer.
You must answer me.
Where were you exactly
on the day of the incident?
Your answer is the key to get you out of here.
Now, Olarn, who you trust,
will definitely run for the mayor.
You should think carefully
about whether he let you get out.
If you want to survive,
you must speak out.
Sargent,
your mother is waiting.
Sir.
That lawyer Win and his gang
are investigating about Itt all over town.
What do you want me to do with them?
He's interesting.
I have a gut feeling
I must deal with him for a long time.
This area is a construction zone
of the New Tulakham project.
Olarn bought up the land here.
Anyone who used to live here must move out.
If anyone refuses to move out,
they will be evicted.
All locals moved to other places.
Some people…
are living on a boat.
Why do you want to be a lawyer?
I want to know
whether I can use the law and justice.
The one I love tried to prove it.
And did they prove it?
I won't prove it.
But I'll make it happen.
The law must provide justice
to everyone equally.
Hello, how are you?
Oh, Mr. Olarn, Hello.
Oh, hello.
This is so fresh.
- Oh.
- Hello, Mr. Olarn.
Hello, how are you? Come on.
Hello. Hey, Come on.
Great, great.
Olarn is very hot right now,
especially the merchants,
and the people in the degraded area.
Ignore others.
How about a job I assigned you?
Are you finished?
The foundation donation account is fine.
Whatever's in my hands, there's no mistake.
Red groupers.
Yes, fresh, Mr. Olarn.
- Oh, right?
- Yes.
- This is a barracuda.
- Just arrived.
It's a barracuda.
This looks good.
Oh yeah.
Thank you.
Yes, hello.
This is a good shrimp. See?
Yes, that's right.
- Thank you. See you.
- Thank you.
Alright, everyone, see you soon.
We're hunting down a suspect
who will be the key to solving
the assassination case of the former mayor.
Is it related to influential people?
Maybe…
This case may shake the justice system.
Lawyer, Are you concerned about your safety?
What I'm doing
might offend the influencer.
But I believe and hope that
the press will prioritize,
and keep an eye on this case.
Do you know? I never hated the fish smell, man.
Because it gave me life.
When I succeeded I built up this fish market
to repay this city.
When we have power and money
they won't see us as just fishermen
who are low-class.
What's up?
Sir,
that lawyer Boripat is lawyer
Chawanan's son and he's Prem's grandson.
- Get in, get in.
- Let me go.
Let me go.
Hey! Let me go.
Let me out, let me go.
That kid is alive.
Itt didn't kill him.
And now he's a lawyer like his mother.
He's trying to get Itt's case to take me down.
Tell Kom to find the killer.
And take this bastard.
Yes, sir.
How are you going to handle this, Kom?
It won't bother me, will it?
Of course, sir.
Sir, can I help you?
Thank you very much, man. I'll come back later.
How was it?
I investigated.
What's up?
Someone asked my friend to make fake documents
to escape the country.
And?
He was appointed to receive the documents.
Around…
the old factory.
Old factory?
You wait in the car.
Tan, watch out for me.
No, I'll go with you.
Don't be a liability.
Watch out for me.
Yes, bro.
If you don't want me to go,
You need to help Win.
Tan!
I got this.
If she dies, you die.
I caught the agent who got the mayor killed.
[Next Episode]
You can't hold up, huh?
When my boss says he has new evidence.
The best evidence is now
in the prosecutor's hands.
How can you survive?
I'll be a mayor of Tulakham.
After this, I will have to bother you.
Our Tulakham needs a leader.