Hello? Where are you?
I’ve been waiting
for you for a while now.
You know I’m supposed
to pick up the kids.
It’s hard to find a tricycle here.
What? You’re still fixing your tricycle?
It’s been a while!
What! What...
Help! Someone stole my phone!
- Hey! My vape!
- My phone was stolen.
I haven’t finished paying for that!
Nice.
Got something good.
- Hi, Noli!
- Babe...
Babe, look at what I scored.
It’s brand new.
- Not bad! We can sell that.
- Of course.
Let’s test it out first before we sell it.
Let’s head in.
You go ahead, babe.
Come on.
How about you, babe?
What did you get?
I don’t have any.
Just for soft drinks—
money is slow right now.
Come on, eat some sardines,
I’ve sautéed some.
All right!
This is delicious!
Thank you, babe.
You’re welcome.
Damn it...
What are you doing?
Didn't I tell you?
Never ever accept anything
from that foolish Captain!
What are you saying?
His people were the ones
who brought this,
not Captain himself.
Do you still see each other?
You know what?
You just threw away
what should have been our food.
You’re not thinking straight!
Have it your way.
Babe.
I’m sorry. Don’t be mad anymore.
- Whatever! You’re annoying.
- Fine, I’m sorry.
You act like you’re
still not used to me.
I’ll make it up to you.
- This is my favorite.
- Yeah, I know.
- Babe... babe.
- Hmm?
This is great!
[speaking in foreign language]
- Oh...
- Oh!
- Sorry... I’m very very sorry.
- It’s okay. Are you okay?
Yes, I’m okay.
Ah! Your... polo...
- Pardon?
- have wrinkles.
- Have wrinkles there.
- Oh, okay...
- Single?
- You guessed it right. And you?
- No. Bye-bye.
- No? Oh, bye.
Babe, you were so good
at speaking English earlier.
You even had an accent.
Of course!
I was Best in English
back in kindergarten.
- Really?
- Yes.
Does that even exist?
- Well, you didn’t study.
- That’s fine.
- I’m good at other things.
- Like what?
- You already know.
- Hmm...
Esme, Noli...
- Captain.
- So it’s you guys. How are you?
We’re good. Let’s go.
Oh, by the way,
there’s a job opening
at the barangay,
maybe you’re interested, Esme?
That would be extra income for you.
The work is simple...
It’s not really necessary.
I can provide everything
my wife needs.
Here, look— our dinner is so delicious.
Right, babe?
Let’s go.
That bastard!
He thinks he’s someone great!
Just because he’s wearing a polo!
That idiot only won
because of cheating...
Huh?
Why does your face look like that?
What? Why?
Do you regret choosing me
as your boyfriend?
Where is that coming from?
You’ve been so quiet on our way home.
I’m sorry, okay!
This is just who I am!
I’m just poor, that’s all.
- Unlike Captain, right?
- Where is this coming from?
It’s so hard dealing with you,
you’re way too insecure.
Fine... I admit it, I’m insecure...
Can you blame me?
That bastard Francis tried
to take you away from me!
Did I let him?
No.
You know what,
we’ve had this issue for so long.
You still haven’t moved on.
Fine. Alright.
I said I’m sorry.
Wait...
Babe...
I promise you,
I’ll do my best to be enough for you.
I’ll be rich.
So that our future kids won’t have
to eat food that came from theft.
Do you accept
as your husband,
Noli, Esmeralda?
For richer, or for richest,
'til death do us part? Huh?
Even for poorer, or for poorest,
I will marry you, Noli...
That sounds so good.
- Come on, let’s eat.
- Yeah, that’s a good idea.
Babe, have some coffee too.
Oh, you’re having coffee again?
My sleeping problem came back.
I thought that was already fixed?
It came back.
Our family really has trouble sleeping.
By the way, how much
change do you have left?
Pay the rent right away...
The water and electricity bills too.
Then whatever’s left,
keep it for yourself.
No need. Let’s prioritize
your check-up first.
It might get worse later.
No need.
That’s yours.
I can handle this.
Go shopping.
It’s been a while since
I bought you new clothes.
Really?
Of course. You deserve it!
You’re so stubborn.
Thank you!
Bro! Esme!
- Not, come eat!
- Hey!
No thanks.
I won’t be long.
Bro, I got a tip.
Looks like we can score
something good here.
Great!
Hello, Oca, can you pick us up now?
Right there, bro.
I studied that couple’s schedule.
Damn.
Looks like we’re
gonna hit big on this one.
Yeah, bro.
Wherever you decide to marry Esme,
you can make it happen.
Awesome!
You know the plan, right?
Same plan as before.
I’ll wait for you in the alley.
Alright, I got this.
- Oh my God! Honey, my bag!
- What the? You bastard!
Come back here!
I can't chase...
Hey! What happened?
God! Just, don’t worry.
I’ll get you a new bag.
Not!
- Not!
- Hey!
- Bro, I’m sorry.
- Not?
I’m sorry, bro.
I really need the money.
What the, Notnot.
Damn you, Not.
Why? Why, Not?
You bastard!
Son of a bitch!
Ma’am.
Here is the running bill
that you requested.
And this is the prescription
from the doctor.
Do we need this now?
Right away?
Yes, because all of them
are antibiotics.
Also, there’s a schedule
for when you need
to administer them to the patient.
That's all of it.
Excuse me.
Esme.
How are you feeling, babe?
I’m all right.
I’m fine.
I heard what Notnot did to you.
You know, I want
to report him to the police,
but you might get dragged into it.
That bastard!
Don’t worry.
I already sent the others
to look for him.
What’s that?
Your hospital bill and prescription.
How much does it cost?
Don’t worry,
I’ll take care of it.
I’ll find a way.
I’m sorry, babe.
I never thought
that bastard Notnot
would betray me like that.
It’s okay.
It’s all good.
What’s important is that you’re alive.
Because…
I don’t know what
I would do if I lost you.
I don’t think I can handle it, Noli.
Make sure everyone gets their share.
- Yes, Captain.
Go house to house,
family by family.
- Yes, Captain.
- Alright, go ahead.
[sighs]
Francis.
- Captain.
- Oh!
Esme, what brings you here?
Sit down.
I need your help.
What kind of help?
I need money.
Noli got stabbed.
He’s in the hospital right now.
Hm...
So that’s what I’ve been
hearing my staff talk about.
How much do you need?
Twenty thousand.
That’s quite a lot.
There’s medical assistance
available here in the barangay.
But that’s a long process.
It will take quite some time.
How long?
About a month, or even longer.
Besides...
There are others
who need it more than Noli.
People undergoing dialysis,
people with cancer.
Decent people, unlike Noli.
But you,
you already had a chance
to change your life,
yet you still chose trouble.
Are you lending me
the money, or not?
Because if not, I’ll just leave.
You talk too much.
I’ll lend you the money.
Here.
Twenty thousand.
But there’s a catch.
Can you handle it?
Forget it.
What are you going to do?
Are you going to let Noli die?
Huh? Can you do that?
Can you?
You love him so much, right?
Here, thirty thousand.
What? Are you going to be picky now?
Just think of it as
finding another hustle.
It’s just a different kind of itch
you’ll be scratching now.
So?
Don’t just stand there!
Damn it!
That’s thirty thousand right there!
Babe?
What took you so long?
I managed to score some medicine.
I came from the pharmacy.
How much did it cost?
Thirty thousand.
That's a lot.
Where did you get the money?
At the market.
The phone was still new,
so I was able to sell it at a high price.
Thank you, babe.
I love you so much, Noli.
I'll do everything for you.
I love you so much too, Esme.
Your wound is about to heal.
Just a few more days.
Maybe you want to go somewhere?
I'll take you out.
No need.
Just focus on recovering.
You need to rest.
Who said that?
You’re talking about me.
Can you see that?
See?
You're so arrogant.
That's why you
always get into trouble.
But thank you, babe,
for taking care of me.
Geez, you're so dramatic.
I'm serious.
I'll never find
another woman like you.
So,
I'll make it up to you, okay?
Hi, Noli!
It’s been a while.
So, you’ve been discharged.
Since a week ago.
How are you?
You really had me worried!
I was actually planning
to visit you in the hospital
to take care of you.
No need.
Esme was there.
She stayed by my side
24/7 at the hospital.
Hmm?
It doesn’t seem like it.
I actually saw her
at the barangay the other day.
Barangay? What was she doing there?
Why don’t you ask her yourself?
You know, when the cat is away,
the mice will play.
Alright, I’ll go now
before I say something else.
Okay, bye-bye.
You’re smoking again?
Give me that.
Where did the money you used
to pay for the hospital come from?
Hmm?
Didn't I tell you that
I already sold a cellphone?
Ah... cellphone.
I don't believe it.
Then don't.
Alright,
let’s do it this way.
Let's just play
a guessing game.
Is this a person?
Huh?
- What kind of trip is this?
- Animal?
Demon?
Is it Captain?
Why do you always
think about Captain?
Because someone told me something.
Who?
Secret.
You know, whoever they are,
they're an idiot.
You've been caught red-handed,
and you still won't admit it!
Let go of me... Ouch!
Sorry, babe, sorry...
Sorry... sorry...
Sorry. Forgive me.
Sorry, babe. Sorry...
Forgive me.
I... I'm really trying, babe, okay?
I'm trying...
Please forgive me, okay?
Come on, come on... Sorry.
Sorry, babe.
Ah, alright.
Okay, let's just meet there.
Okay, sure.
Alright, thank you.
See you... Okay.
- Take it already.
- How much is that?
- Twenty thousand is enough!
- Alright...
You're really
a son of a bitch, Francis!
What the hell!
What are you doing?
- Damn it... your iPad is trash.
- Hey, sorry, okay?
I'm not buying that anymore.
Look, they left because of you!
You're so stupid!
That was money turned into dust!
You're really annoying...
Don’t follow me!
Damn it, Francis!
Get away from me!
What was that?
What do you mean,
"What was that?"
I was about to sell the iPad...
and you had to interfere.
I already said sorry, didn't I?
What more do you want?
What I want is for you
to fix your way of thinking!
You're so dumb...
You keep talking about Captain.
Who’s that?
Nothing... Someone from cable,
someone wants a connection installed.
Hello, what time is it...
where are you?
Huh?
What time is it?
Damn it!
Damn it...
Shit!
Shit! So unlucky!
Damn it again.
That was money... money!
- Special delivery.
- Thanks, I guess...
Can I get some water?
Is that okay?
You haven't shown up
at the barangay, huh?
I was just busy.
I was actually
planning to go see you...
Out of everything I hate, it's waiting.
What the hell... Let go of me.
I said let go of me! Let me go!
I told you to let me go!
Let me go!
Let me go...
What the hell! Let me go!
Let go...
I said let go of me...
Let me go...
Son of a bitch!
What?
You're disgusting!
Try me!
- Noli...
- Damn you!
You're a rapist!
I'm reporting you to the police!
What? You're going to report me?
Son of a bitch... who would
even believe you with your record?
Damn you!
And what are you even
saying about rape, huh?
Esme wanted it.
- You son of a bitch
- Oh, isn't that right, Esme?
Get out!
You know...
the money she used
to get you out of the hospital,
that was my money.
- You already know what that mean—
- Bastard! Get out!
Don't believe him.
You know he likes me,
but he can't have me,
so he's doing this.
Who’s better in bed, me or him?
Huh?
Where did you do it?
At the barangay?
Damn you!
Did you enjoy it, huh?
Sorry, babe... Sorry...
I only did it because I love you.
Damn you!
Hey, Noli, how are you?
Where have you been?
Babe?
You know, I understand
where you’re coming from.
But think about it,
I tried every way possible
to pay for the hospital.
I borrowed money...
I looked for work at the market—
but I had nowhere else to turn.
I didn’t want give
myself to the Captain.
I hope you understand that.
I did it because I love you, Noli.
Really?
You really love me?
Ouch! No! Noli,
not there, please!
No— Not there. No...
It hurts!
Please stop!
Babe, eat up.
Is that your breakfast again?
Come here, let’s eat.
Babe.
You’re so serious.
How are you, Noli?
I heard that what Esme did
to you is all over the place.
Hey, I wasn’t the one
who spread it, okay?
I just heard about it...
But if I were you,
I’d get revenge.
Esme can’t be
the only one happy, right?
I can help you,
if you want...
You son of a bitch.
Why’d you stop?
Why? Noli?
Come here— Wait...
Where were you?
With Captain?
What are you saying?
I’m asking you where were you?
Can’t you see? I got beaten up.
Who did this to you?
Just a bad deal.
I— I got it... I got it.
Who did this to you?
- Just a bad deal.
- This is the last time, okay?
Next time, I won’t let you
do these deals alone.
Does it hurt?
Sorry. Sorry.
It’s okay.
I just miss you
taking care of me, Noli.
Can we start over?
Forget about Captain.
Enough!
Why? Do you think I wanted
to have sex with him? Huh?
You don’t know,
I have nightmares every night!
No matter how much I shower,
I feel disgusted with myself!
I did it because I love you.
But what did you do?
Huh?
I said enough!
I did it because I love you!
What about me?
I’m sorry.
Stop crying.
I love you so much too, Esme.
Babe, do you see that?
Over there.
Wow.
You already know, huh?
Hey— sorry, sorry.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, I’m okay.
- Yeah, it wasn’t hard. I’m okay.
Alright then...
- Here. Thank you, thank you.
- Alright, thank you.
Let’s check what’s inside.
- Hold it, babe, count it.
- Hey, dollars.
Nice. This is a lot, babe.
You’re really amazing.
Oh, right?
- Now, buy your makeup, okay?
- Yes!
- Okay.
- Let’s put it back inside.
You’re really amazing.
That’s why I choose you.
Nice.
Babe, look, the lipstick I bought
at the market is so pretty.
Why are you fixing yourself?
Going somewhere?
No. I just want to look good for you.
Erase that.
- What? What are you doing?
- Erase it!
Who’s that? Captain?
What are you talking about?
Him again?
That’s the buyer of the iPad.
And I thought we were okay now?
We already talked about that, right?
Fine, whatever.
Babe.
Babe...
Ouch! What are you doing?
Ouch! Stop...
Stop! It hurts!
Ouch! Ouch!
Ouch!
Stop it— Stop!
Stop...
It hurts.
Stop.
Didn’t you say...
you’d do anything,
because you love me?
Ouch! Stop! Ouch! Stop!
Hi, Noli!
Noli?
Noli, are you okay?
Noli.
Why? What happened?
Noli?
Maybe it’s better if I take you home.
Come on.
Come on, Noli.
I’ll talk to Esme first.
Maybe she needs
to take you to the hospital.
Noli?
Noli!
Damn you!
Traitor!
Noli!
Where’s Captain?
Come on! Tell me where Captain is.
- Where’s Captain?
- What? Captain’s not here!
Noli...
Liar.
This is not true.
This isn’t true— No...
No, no...
No!
Babe, I promise you,
I’ll fix my life.
I’ll get rich so
we don’t have to steal again.
I don’t want our future kids
to eat from stolen money.
Noli.
Hi, ma'am.
How is he, nurse?
He’s doing better now
compared to the past few days.
His episodes have lessened.
- Alright, ma’am, I’ll get going now.
- Alright, thank you.
Noli, how are you?
Sorry it took me
a while to visit again.
I have a job now at a factory.
It’s nearby.
I have money for your medicine now.
Look.
- What’s that?
- My love gave me this.
I’m sorry for bringing you here.
I had to. But...
once you’re better,
I’ll take you home, okay?
Okay?
I really, really miss you.