♪We are both dim light♪
♪Will time erase us♪
♪Those who fade away
in the shadows silently♪
♪Also crave a life
under the bright sun openly♪
♪How can I break free
from the chains of fate?♪
♪Who whispers in my ear♪
♪That I'm bound to fall?♪
♪Then burn me♪
♪Burn my stubbornness♪
♪The surging bitterness♪
♪The hot tears♪
♪Nobody knows♪
♪Entangling in the past♪
♪Silence in the darkness♪
♪The dim light finally turns♪
[Kill Me Love Me]
♪Into the fire of rebirth♪
[Episode 3]
[Tingyun Pavilion]
Beauty?
Third Brother.
Oh, my big brother.
Your hands are so soft.
You never cease
to be mischievous.
Your Highness, please have some tea.
My lord.
Sober-up tea.
Lianxiu?
Were you the one who waited on Mother
back in the day, eh?
Your Highness, indeed,
you never forget a thing.
These years,
my brother has been well cared for.
Thank you.
It's my job, Your Highness.
You can go now.
When we were young,
we secretly drank wine.
Mother punished us
to kneel in the prayer hall.
It was Lianxiu who brewed tea
for us to sober up.
It was me who was wild and unruly,
often angering Mother.
In the end,
it was also I who caused Mother's death.
Luckily, you were there to company her,
until her death.
We grew up together.
Mother treated me as her own son.
I was just fulfilling my duty.
Third Brother,
this medicine formula,
I acquired it from a famed healer.
It is best for mending broken bones.
The medicine is prepared. Try it.
This leg of mine...
is a curse.
I won't treat it.
How about this?
After the alliance banquet,
I'll ask Father to grant you
a warmer residence.
The cold of Jingbei
isn't good for your leg.
If you truly wish to help me,
then let me stay in Zhaojing.
Zhaojing's lands are nurturing,
and,
if free,
you could come visit me.
That would be great.
The Rising Sun Bow?
Everything here hasn't changed.
The Rising Sun Bow is still here.
In the 10th year of the Zhaoming era,
the Lushan Hunt,
I was lost by a horse,
yet the precious fell to you.
You were just being generous.
Actually, in both word and might,
we are equal.
Why do you always let me win?
Nonsense.
You are now the Crown Prince.
From now on,
you don't have to do so.
It's kind of patronizing
to keep treating me with kid gloves
just because I'm not as able-bodied.
At the alliance banquet,
I will let you win again.
I heard you've taken a liking
to a Xiyan beauty.
Who is she?
I wouldn't want
to take what's dear to you.
Big Brother,
that woman wants to harm me.
If you want her, take her.
Better if you kill her.
Kill her?
She wants to harm you?
What happened?
That beauty,
gave me lovesickness.
Yet she won't yield to me.
What say you, should she be killed?
Other matters,
I'll shoulder for you,
but while you may jest and joke,
you must not jeopardize the nation.
This event is of great importance.
Father values it deeply.
Alright.
Father just scolded me, now it's you.
Best not to stay in Zhaojing, then.
Annoying.
Fine. I'll stop.
Rest well.
Take care, Big Brother.
[In Memory of Yang Donghu, Deputy General
of Great Yan's Weibei Army]
It is them.
I know it.
I saw it myself.
They're the ones who set the fire.
They deserve to die.
Kill them.
I swear on my life,
not a single Weibei Army soldier
would dare set fire.
Let's put out the fire first, everyone.
Kill them.
Don't let him get away!
The Weibei Army didn't set the fire.
I saw it with my own eyes.
Extinguish the flames first.
Everyone, stay calm.
Stay calm.
Hold.
Do not point blades at the people.
Yang.
My lord.
Let me go.
My lord, it's dangerous.
Let go of me.
Yang.
Go.
Yang!
[In Memory of Yang Donghu, Deputy General
of Great Yan's Weibei Army]
[In Memory of Wu He, Officer
[In Memory of Huang Qing, Guard
of Great Yan's Weibei Army]
[In Memory of Zhang Futian, Officer
They knew we Weibei Army was disciplined
and never harmed the people.
So they incited the Qingzhou people
to besiege the camp.
This time,
I won't be merciful.
The Weibei Army
is a righteous army.
Great Yan
will seek justice for you.
Tomorrow's alliance banquet
is your last chance.
What happened
during the Qingzhou Fire?
Boring.
You weren't scared at all?
Why are you here?
There's something to decide.
To do or not to do,
I am unsure what to choose.
I, too, struggle with choices.
Since I was a child,
my father always chose for me.
But no worries.
Wait here for me.
If there's no choice,
then let us pray.
Hope the Emperor of Great Yan
is kind and does not scold or beat.
Best if he's kind like my brother.
Forget it.
There will never
be another like him.
As long as the Emperor
doesn't kill people
like that disabled man, I'm fine.
Look at that.
A real blessing.
Is this real?
You've never played this?
Wonderful.
First wishes work best.
Give it a try.
Your Highness.
Your Highness,
His Highness is returning.
I got it.
Go ahead and try.
I know what to do now.
Father, Mother,
please bless me.
[Changxi Pavilion]
Mr. Yue Qin.
[Yue Qin, Xiyan Prince]
Zigu detests confinement.
Get a maid familiar with Yan etiquette,
to guide her in the palace.
Oh,
have you changed the incense?
Zigu sleeps best with familiar scents.
If there's a familiar scent,
maybe she can sleep better..
You may rest assured.
[Shumo]
I prepared her incense yesterday,
and by the way,
arranged everything to her liking.
Mei Lin.
Wait for me, Your Highness.
It's a Qingzhou knot,
a charm from Qingzhou folk.
Mei Lin,
is that you?
Your Highness,
was it really her?
The beauties
include Xiyan exiles from Qingzhou.
Others know the Qingzhou Knot, too.
Your Highness.
It's time to go.
Her Highness awaits.
Brother's craftsmanship is unmatched.
His Highness must've put in much effort.
Zigu.
Brother.
I missed you so much.
Brother, look.
I'm all grown up now.
No longer the tearful little fairy.
But I still think
that's the you I find most adorable.
Brother,
they say after the alliance banquet,
you'll return to Xiyan.
I won't go anywhere
until you're settled
and everything is done.
What if I never settle?
I can't protect you forever.
Does the Emperor of Great Yan
kill people at his will?
No,
he's a wise ruler.
No need to worry.
Is he handsome?
Forget it.
Handsome or not, he's still an old man.
Brother,
do you have a girl you like?
What about you, Zigu?
Ziyu used to mock me,
saying no one dares to take this.
Now, it seems, she is true.
I wouldn't even know
what it feels like
to have a special someone.
What you think of each day.
What you dream of each night.
Brother,
do you have someone in your heart?
Tell me, who is she?
I fear that in this life,
I will be fated to miss her.
Zigu,
tomorrow, after the alliance banquet,
you will be Concubine Yan of Yan Dynasty.
The jade ring not being given away
is both a regret and a blessing.
The palace rules are complex,
one wrong step...
And it may bring harm to Xiyan.
I know.
No, it would harm you.
Xiyan needs a princess's marriage
to secure peace with Yan Dynasty,
but you owe Xiyan nothing.
Wait for me.
Is this not the dagger
Mother gave to you, Brother?
Now,
it is yours.
If, one day,
you face a dilemma,
I hope you
can prioritize protecting yourself.
Mother doesn't wish for me
to wield weapons.
You've grown up, Zigu,
and should learn how to use a blade.
[Imperial Palace]
Princess Zigu of Xiyan
greets Your Majesty of Great Yan.
May Your Majesty be blessed
with health and a long reign.
Proceed.
To Princess Zigu of Xiyan:
Regal and demure,
gentle and graceful,
wise and reserved,
virtuous in conduct,
and fit for the inner palace.
Thus,
appointed as Concubine Yan,
granting residence in Fanghua Palace.
Execute as decreed.
The proclamation is now complete.
Now, Great Yan and Xiyan
forge ties of harmony.
Let the people of both lands
live as one family
in eternal peace and joy.
Long live Your Majesty's wisdom.
[Taichi Palace]
Twenty chests of lacquered potteries.
Six new gilt sapphire loongs.
Ten pairs of agate cups
in the shape of animal heads.
Ten jars of fermented mare's milk.
Ten jars of Yangpuli wine.
Ten hu of East Sea pearls.
[*Ancient Chinese unit of volume]
Two Liuli phoenix-tail fans.
[*Chinese traditional colored glaze]
Twenty Ferghana horses.
Two bottles of Toxin-Neutralizing
Red Coix Seed Potion.
The 18 Tribes of Xiyan congratulate
Concubine Yan on her marriage.
Concubine Yan, you've come from afar.
I've had imperial cooks
specially prepare
Xiyan's bamboo brew
to ease your homesickness.
Well,
Your Majesty...
Concubine Yan, no need for formalities.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Today is a day of joy.
All in the palace may feast.
There's no need for restraint.
Let the first group of beauties line up.
[Noble Consort Yin]
The beauties of Xiyan
are all remarkably graceful.
Marrying Xiyan beauties
to Yan Dynasty officials
also serves the peace
between our nations.
Since the Eastern Palace
leads the noble clans,
Crown Prince
shall make the first choice.
Thank you, Father.
What is your name?
Your Highness,
my name is Mei Lin.
Judging by your features,
you look like one of our own.
I was born
on the Xiyan-Great Yan border
and have lived
within Great Yan territory.
Welcome to the Eastern Palace.
Here, take this jade pendant.
Wait.
Third Brother, you...
Son,
your leg...
My leg is healed.
Father,
I was so focused on the beauty.
I feared Big Brother
would pick her first.
In my haste,
I actually stood up on my own.
That's good news.
But you should still have
Imperial Healer Zhang examine it.
Yes, Father.
You aren't the true culprit
of the massacre.
I have proof.
Save me.
Son!
Your Majesty!
Your Majesty, rest assured.
Thankfully, Prince Jing
wore a Gold Silk Armor.
It was truly
a divine intervention
that saved his life.
Easy there.
Father,
I am fine,
just a few scrapes.
But I
was shaken.
Third Brother,
you can walk,
yet you've used a wheelchair.
This
can be a crime against the throne.
Father,
Big Brother,
I had no choice.
Even as a disabled man,
I attract assassins.
Were I to stand up fully,
I doubt
If I'd live longer.
Fortunately, I was prepared,
and that saved me this time.
Son,
for all these years,
you have suffered in Jingbei.
Now that you can stand, all is well.
Back then, I thought
your leg couldn't be saved.
The healer said,
only by breaking and resetting the bone
do you stand a chance to walk again.
Heavens blessed you.
You are truly fortunate.
I never expected
that Xiyan beauty
had seduced me
just to try and assassinate me.
Father,
how would you handle her?
Do not worry.
I will see to it
personally.
First, recover well.
Father,
those Xiyan people hate me,
but would not dare
assassinate me so openly,
jeopardizing the peace-making marriage.
You mean to say?
Within the court,
someone wish to use them
to rid me for good.
Who do you suspect?
Of everyone in court,
only you, Big Brother,
would never harm me.
Father,
I request
that the Eastern Palace
lead the investigation.
Son,
this is related to Xiyan.
Handle this with utmost caution.
Rest assured, Third Brother.
I'll uncover
who's behind this.
[Imperial Prison]
Fear not, Your Highness.
No one leaves here with secrets intact
after facing these instruments
of torture.
Your Highness,
Minister Zhang
has waited outside for long.
He claims the woman has no ties to him.
If this woman isn't Zhang Yin's agent,
then she must be Third Brother's.
Ten years on,
Prince Jing still uses
this "feigned injury" ploy,
proving he has no other evidence
beyond Momai Warriors.
The Qingzhou incident was flawless.
Even with ten more years,
Prince Jing wouldn't be able
to trace it back to Your Highness.
Tell Zhang Yin to hold steady.
Now, go and summon my third brother.
Yes, Your Highness.
You aren't the true culprit
of the massacre.
I have proof.
Save me.
She even pierced the Gold Silk Armor
yet deliberately spared me.
My lord.
The medicine is cold now.
Qingyan,
could there be clues out there?
Clues that we missed?
Even if there are,
none would expose the Crown Prince.
Years of effort
only led to Zhang Yin.
If not for Your Highness recognizing
that Eastern Palace advisor
among the mob,
we'd never have suspected
the Crown Prince
was behind the Qingzhou arson.
Now, Mei Lin's assassination attempt
exposes the Momai on her.
It'll eventually trace back
to Zhang Yin's Momai Warriors.
All we need to do
is wait for Zhang Yin to make his move.
If he silences Mei Lin,
he'll bear the blame
for this assassination.
Unable to shoulder such a charge,
he'll turn to the Crown Prince.
And the Crown Prince,
to protect himself,
will discard Zhang Yin.
Zhang Yin then has but one option
to accuse the Eastern Palace.
Though his confession
won't topple the Crown Prince,
it will sow seeds of doubt
in our father's heart.
Then we'll have grounds
to investigate
the Qingzhou affair openly.
Someone reported
Zhang Yin waited hours outside prison
but never saw the Crown Prince.
Zhang Yin values profit over loyalty.
A good dog
when in favor,
but a deadly one
when betrayed.
The Crown Prince won't see him,
he'll surely
silence Mei Lin himself.
Your Highness,
the Crown Prince wants you
to visit the prison.
It seems Big Brother has guessed
Mei Lin was a bait I laid.
As ever, Your Highness,
your strategy is sound.
The Shadow Works was founded
to gather truths of old,
and now executes
the Momai plan.
Only Mei Lin
bears the Momai poison.
Even under torture,
it will be traced solely to Zhang Yin.
Did she confess?
No,
she hasn't uttered a word.
No rush.
Once she's been through everything,
even her iron will shall break.
With these tools of torture
at our disposal,
any secrets she holds
will be revealed as we wish.
Whether she speaks,
or what she says,
no longer matters.
True enough.
To withstand such torture,
she never said a thing.
This shows something.
You're right.
She's no mere Xiyan beauty
but a trained assassin.
The mark on her arm
tells of her fate
in the hands of Momai poison.
How do you know this so clearly?
It's not hard to obtain the poison.
But as to who slipped it to her,
only she holds the key to that mystery.
Why haven't you spoken yet?
Waiting for an antidote?
Your master deceived you.
There is no antidote.
Who ordered you to attack Prince Jing?
Speak.
No one ordered me.
Hold.
Reveal what you know,
and I'll grant you a quick death.
A quick death
is mercy.
But after all you've suffered,
how could I show her mercy?
If I granted her quick death,
how would I account to Father?
I
cannot die.
An attempted assassination in the court
will only lead to your execution.
From the start,
you were someone's pawn,
dead the moment you failed.
To imagine otherwise is folly.
Brother, don't waste time on her.
She won't reveal what you seek.
She's merely a tool
who knows nothing of her master.
[Prince Jing's Mansion]
Minister Zhang,
how was the show
I arranged for you?
Your Highness, I don't get it.
Please enlighten me.
In the 14th year of the Zhaoming era,
when we first met,
you were but
a minor border patrol officer.
Now, a decade later,
you are the Minister of Defense,
leaping six ranks in ten years.
Tell me,
what kind of lucky streak
have you been riding on?
I am unworthy, Your Highness.
It's all thanks
to your heroic deeds
in recovering Qingzhou.
When Qingzhou's battle began,
you dismissed me for cowardice.
But when Weibei Army suffered defeat,
I survived and gained my fortune.
Yet I, as their general, still live.
Weibei Army
won't bear this shame in vain.
However lucky streak
you may have been riding on,
if the tide turns,
you'll end up in hot water.
As someone I hate,
guess what will happen to you?
Your Highness,
I don't understand.
Please enlighten me.
She's no mere beauty.
She's a death warrior
with the Momai poison in her.
Momai Warriors.
I encountered them
in Qingzhou.
Your Highness,
I have no ties to this woman.
The prison's methods
are effective,
but a prince's assassination,
not even your master
could afford the consequences.
If things go south for your benefactor,
your fate is clear:
be silenced,
or be the scapegoat.
You know I lost a whole bunch
of my best men.
So, whether you survive or not
depends on my mood.
♪We are♪
♪Both♪
♪Dim light♪
♪Will time erase us?♪
♪Those who fade away
in the shadows silently♪
♪Also crave a life
under the bright sun openly♪
♪How can I break free♪
♪From the chains of fate?♪
♪Who whispers in my ear♪
♪That I'm bound♪
♪To fall?♪
♪Then burn me♪
♪Burn away my fears♪
Un-
dy-
ing.
Un-
dy-
ing.
What did you say, my lord?
♪Cut through all those...♪
Keep watching.
Zhang Yin will soon silence her.
I fear Mei Lin may not last.
I've seen the prison's methods.
Tendons pulled, skin peeled...
She will endure.
Years of training,
all for this day.
♪The wind scatters the spring flowers♪
♪The dream was filled with sorrow
for the entire night♪
♪Troubled thoughts shatter
into a sky full of stars♪
♪If fate is too unbearable♪
♪I am mired in the mud♪
♪Love is helpless,
falling into the abyss♪
♪If life is a predetermined sorrow♪
♪Love is an endless wandering♪
♪A place in the heart
from which there is no return♪
♪It's a vain hope, it's in imagination♪
♪It's the distinguished light♪
♪If life is a predetermined sorrow♪
♪Love is an endless wandering♪
♪A place in the heart
from which there is no return♪
♪It's a vain hope, it's in imagination♪
♪It's the distinguished light♪
♪If life is a predetermined sorrow♪
♪Love is an endless wandering♪
♪A place in the heart
from which there is no return♪
♪It's a vain hope, it's in imagination♪
♪It's the distinguished light♪