♪We are both dim light♪
♪Will time erase us?♪
♪Those who fade away
in the shadows silently♪
♪Also crave a life
under the bright sun openly♪
♪How can I break free
from the chains of fate?♪
♪Who whispers in my ear♪
♪That I'm bound to fall?♪
♪Then burn me♪
♪Burn my stubbornness♪
♪The surging bitterness♪
♪The hot tears♪
♪Nobody knows♪
♪Entangling in the past♪
♪Silence in the darkness♪
♪The dim light finally turns♪
[Kill Me Love Me]
♪Into the fire of rebirth♪
[Episode 18]
The Red Fruits are sweet.
The wheat is fragrant.
Tianjing Grass fills the storehouse.
The Red Fruits are sweet.
The wheat is fragrant.
Tianjing Grass fills the storehouse.
Can't you chop the filling?
You have greater strength.
Actually, it's my first time
making Meat Dragons.
Don't worry.
I've already made it known
that my wife and I will make sure
it's cooked,
despite the taste.
Don't add too much of this old dough,
or it will turn sour.
I didn't add much.
You are using too much strength.
You have greater strength
than the cook in my army.
You'll make the dough too hard.
You are covering it now?
Did you add alkali water?
Murong Jinghe.
If you don't add alkali water,
it'll turn sour.
Murong Jinghe,
go burn the wood.
Burn the wood.
You have greater strength than me.
I just have great strength.
My mother said that I have been strong
since I was a child.
She was always worried
that I would drive away my husband
who we'd get with great effort.
What kind of son-in-law
would your mother like?
He should be nice
and have a good temper.
He should be able to help my father
with his work.
He should know how to read and write
so that he can teach our kids.
He'd better be able to help
with the accounts for the shop.
My father was a rough man.
My mother always complained
that he couldn't keep the books right.
Your mother wasn't looking
for a son-in-law.
It's more like she was hiring a laborer.
What about you?
What kind of husband would you like?
Me?
I haven't thought about it.
As long as my mother could be satisfied.
It's much more delicious
than the dragon meat I cooked.
You are better than me.
Erniu's mother said
you can do needlework
and look after children.
She says you are very capable.
My wife,
you know martial arts
and can make Meat Dragons.
You're also very capable.
There is flour on your face.
On your hair, too.
I'll clean it.
Let me help you.
What about you?
What?
What
kind of wife would you like?
My wife...
I haven't thought much about it.
At that time,
I had my heart set on going to war
and even made a bold vow
that I would not get married
until I defeated Xiyan.
The Empress must be very worried
about your marriage.
Indeed.
Later, I couldn't refuse
my mother any longer,
so I agreed to get married.
At that time, I thought
I must find someone I didn't like
to be my wife.
Someone you don't like?
Without feelings or love,
there will be no attachments.
Only in this way
can I be fearless and selfless
on the battlefield.
Your wife is so pitiful.
However,
later, someone changed my mind.
I now feel
that love
is both a weakness
and armor.
Having someone you want to protect
gives you the strength
to survive on the battlefield.
Regardless of whether I can
go to war in the future,
when choosing a wife,
I want to choose someone I truly love.
Don't you want to ask me
what type of woman I like?
What type of woman
do you like?
I like
a good woman.
She's a good person who would rather
harm herself
than let an innocent suffer.
Her personality is resilient
and stubborn.
Once she makes up her mind,
she will never give up.
Her words and actions
are straightforward
and sincere.
Her frown
and her smile
can easily get to me.
She is the most special woman
in this world.
She knows martial arts,
how to embroider,
and how to make Meat Dragons.
She
won't give in to me on everything.
She can be quite fierce
when we argue.
You know
I hate to lose
the most.
But I'm willing
to lose to her for the rest of my life.
Sir,
are the Meat Dragons ready?
Yes.
Brat,
you really picked a good time.
The harvest banquet is about to begin.
Hurry up.
Come on.
Cheers.
Cheers!
Bottoms up.
Come on. Bottoms up!
Here.
Here. Try this.
I'll pour you some wine.
Thank you.
Don't talk for now.
I've said
all I want to say.
Previously, I felt they were strange.
They don't look like siblings.
It turns out the couple had a quarrel.
They reconciled a long time ago.
Couples don't hold grudges
for long, right?
Right.
Wei,
Madam.
Take a seat.
Are these Meat Dragons?
Wei,
did you brew the Red Fruit Wine
yourself?
Yes.
This wine is very sweet. Try it.
Here.
Give it to me.
You have a weak spleen and stomach.
When you recover,
I'll drink with you.
See?
Big boy,
I'll drink to you.
Actually, you have very good taste.
However,
she is mine.
You are not allowed
to think about her anymore.
I've come around.
I won't compete with you
for Mei Lin anymore.
You are no match for me.
Sir, Miss,
I'll drink to you.
I will repay the life-saving grace
of you two.
I'll drink up.
It's the right thing to do.
Yeah.
Good.
Mei Lin,
your husband can make Meat Dragons.
He is really skilled in cooking.
Actually, I didn't make
the Meat Dragons.
My wife did.
I only needed to burn the wood.
Look.
Mei Lin, your husband is really nice.
You have the best taste
in choosing a husband.
Madam, she didn't pick me.
My mother-in-law did.
I'm their live-in husband.
Her mother has the final say
about the choice
of her live-in son-in-law.
He is good at putting on an act.
It's hard to tell whether his words
and actions are true or false.
Don't let him fool you.
Look at them.
Do you still think
I'm putting on an act now?
When they first came to our village,
this girl simply wouldn't let go
of his hand.
I asked her if he was her husband.
However, she said no.
It's like
birds of the same kind live together.
You are both good at putting on an act.
Am I right?
Yes.
You are right.
I can put on an act, too.
You brat are being naughty again.
I'll beat you.
Stop there!
Wei,
get us some more wine.
Okay.
Can I talk to her?
Mei Lin.
Madam.
Tell me the truth.
Are you satisfied with your husband?
He has
many shortcomings,
but he is a good guy.
He...
He treats me very well.
He's willing to give in
after an argument.
He...
Anyway, my mother should be satisfied
with him.
I'm asking you.
Why do you talk about your mother?
My mother is satisfied.
So am I.
You girl!
♪My heart is actually your♪
♪Rippling♪
♪Past events are like rain,
creating ripples♪
♪Nameless are the flowers and grass♪
♪Heartless is the wind♪
♪Why are we destined to be together?♪
Is that true?
What?
Is what you just said true?
Are you willing to take me,
Murong Jinghe,
as your live-in husband?
♪It's you♪
I'm not good at making up stories
or putting on an act.
Every word I say is true.
Don't bite me.
♪I am still♪
♪Wandering in your eyes♪
♪March flowers scent
the hem of my dress♪
♪My worries fall like dust♪
♪Drifting toward a sea of longing♪
♪How I look forward♪
♪To the future with you♪
♪I am still♪
♪Waiting through your years♪
♪Who can truly understand
the joy and sorrow of life?♪
What are you doing?
♪The snow is all over the sky♪
♪How to bury♪
We...
We are catching fireflies.
Sir,
please take me with you.
Where to?
To the outside world.
I hate to be beaten.
I don't want to stay
in the Laowozi Village anymore.
Erniu,
there are many ferocious beasts outside.
They eat people.
Your mother beats you
because she wants to protect you.
Home is the safest place.
Why don't you go home?
Because we...
Because her parents
were eaten
by a ferocious man-eating beast.
So
we need to go outside
to catch that ferocious beast.
Only then can I give her a new home.
Sir,
you must catch that ferocious beast.
Don't worry.
Let's go.
I am really
not worth you wasting
any more effort on me.
Your Highness,
His Majesty's Imperial Guards
have been following us secretly.
Fortunately, Your Highness
made preparations in advance.
With the excuse
of seeking the culprit Mei Lin,
we can cover it up.
It's just that
with the Imperial Guards around,
we face many constraints in our actions.
It'll be harder to find Prince Jing.
Even if Prince Jing comes back,
the throne may not necessarily be his.
But Luomei
must be mine.
I want Father to grant me
the marriage of Luomei.
But how can His Majesty agree
to let Your Highness marry
a Crown Princess
who holds military power?
Besides, General Yin is...
It depends on what we make of it.
They have no other choice.
Send this to the Fengyi Palace.
I heard my aunt's headache
is getting more and more serious.
Her Highness' headache stems
from emotional distress.
Her Highness is worried
about your marriage,
but you are solely focused
on military affairs
and show no interest in getting married.
This dress
was custom-made for you
by the best embroiderer
in the tailor's workshop
at Her Highness's request.
If you are willing to wear
women's clothing for Her Highness,
it will alleviate
her headache considerably.
Okay.
Thank you, General.
Luomei, are you alright?
Luomei.
Wait.
I crossed the line just now.
My aunt did this.
She wants to force His Majesty
to grant the marriage.
General,
just forget
about what happened today.
Don't feel pressured.
Your Majesty,
Fengyi Palace has just collected
lotus dew today.
It's best for making tea.
Stay here.
I'll deal with this.
Luomei,
don't worry.
I got this.
[Fengyi Palace]
Father.
Your Highness.
Your Highness,
where is Luomei?
Did you see her?
No.
Maybe I missed her.
Why are you here?
I heard Her Highness is sick.
So
I've come to see her.
Your Majesty,
I caught a cold at night recently.
I feel quite feeble.
I'm getting better now.
Your Majesty,
please come in.
I accidentally
broke Your Highness's screen.
Please go to another place to have tea.
Is Luomei inside?
Is there anything we can't see?
Xuanlie,
go to Yanming Palace.
Why did he change the plan?
Luomei,
I...
Actually, you didn't have to do this.
Father,
I want to marry Yin Luomei.
Only she
can be my Crown Princess.
Rascal!
Your third brother has just passed away.
How can you...
The third Brother is dead.
Father, how much longer
will you keep thinking about him?
You!
You did it!
Yes.
I hate him
and I'm jealous of him.
All the things I strive for so hard,
including your favor
and Luomei's affection,
have been obtained by him effortlessly.
Yet he doesn't care at all.
I wish I could kill him
with my own hands.
But if he had really died in my hands,
it would ruin my reputation
and I would have no chance
to get what I want.
You suspect me.
I don't want to explain.
After we find Mei Lin
and interrogate her,
the truth will be revealed.
Everything was due to his own fault.
Xuanlie,
you've been sensible
since you were little.
Your third brother was mischievous,
When he got into trouble,
he'd seek your protection,
and you'd protect him.
I am aware that you suffered
many punishments because of this.
I had thought that the two of you
caring for each other was a good thing,
but in the end,
it still caused you suffering.
Father,
if I can marry Luomei,
all the suffering
would not matter.
You are the Crown Prince.
You will take the throne
and be the Emperor.
In the future, you will take
this dragon throne
and manage the affairs of the realm!
Indulging in personal emotions
will eventually lead to your downfall.
I know
what you are afraid of, Father.
Holding military power
by relatives of the Empress
has always been a great concern.
I did not forget
the lessons from the fall
of previous dynasties.
You may not believe in the loyalty
of the Yin family,
but you should at least trust me.
I will not allow anyone
to overthrow our Murong family's reign.
But I have granted Luomei
the freedom to choose a husband.
Luomei will agree sooner or later.
If I cannot even
win her heart,
how can I assure you
that the Great Yan's reign
will remain secure?
[Yanming Palace]
Your Highness,
I bear the responsibility
of the Yin family and the Pingnan Army.
It's okay now.
Don't worry.
No matter what my father says,
just follow your heart.
Actually, if my aunt hadn't done it,
I would write your name
in the imperial edict
for the arranged marriage.
I am a martial artist.
I don't quite understand love.
But I will strive to reciprocate
the genuine feelings you have shown me.
Your Highness,
why did you change the plan?
just now,
Luomei agreed.
That was a smart scheme of yours.
You know how strong-willed Luomei is.
Using an aphrodisiac to force
intercourse with her
might provoke her rebellious nature.
What I want
has always been
her willingness.
Mr. Li,
it's been a while.
It's been a while.
I can help you
bring down the Crown Prince.
However,
I need to meet your master first.
Sir, His Majesty has withdrawn
all the Imperial Guards.
Those who are watching us now
are all the Crown Prince's men.
His Majesty wants to marry
General Yin into the Eastern Palace.
It seems
the Crown Prince has dispelled
His Majesty's doubts.
Send a secret message to Prince Jing
and wait for his order.
Yes.
I guess I'll have to find my own way
back to the capital.
Little drunkard,
you can't drink anymore.
I know my own condition.
I'm happy these days.
I want to drink.
Well,
after we leave Laowozi Village,
will we have such happy days?
As long as it's a day you enjoy,
I am willing to spend it with you.
Well?
You don't believe it?
Qingyan says in the letter
that Li Qing has been cured.
We need to hurry back then.
There's no rush.
Qingyan has been targeted.
We may need to go back
to the capital by ourselves.
It's going to be a rough trip.
No trip can be more difficult
than the one in Zhongshan.
Li Qing is now the key witness.
Since he has been disposed of
after serving his purpose,
he must hate the Crown Prince
even more than we do.
In all,
when we go back to the capital,
we can bring down the Crown Prince.
After we bring down the Crown Prince,
when the situation is stable,
we will go back to Qingzhou together.
You'll open a fruit cake shop
and I'll be General Weibei.
In times of leisure,
we'll paint and do what we like.
In times of turmoil,
we'll wield our swords
to defend the country.
Would you like
such a life?
Yes.
Come back if you encounter
any difficulties outside.
Okay.
Come back to see us when you can.
Don't worry.
These days...
Erniu said
you've been to the battlefield.
I lied to him.
I don't dare to kill a chicken.
How can I kill men?
I dare
to kill a chicken.
Awesome.
Jinghe,
you wrote so many prescriptions for me.
Here is your reward.
Tianjing Grass can be eaten
and also used to treat illnesses.
It truly is a wonderful thing.
Thank you, doctor.
It's getting late.
Let's set off.
Go ahead.
Madam, we're leaving.
Take care.
There is someone behind us.
Wei.
I...
I will go with you.
I can protect you.
Why do you think I can't protect her?
You don't dare to kill a chicken,
but I dare.
Wei,
please go back.
We can protect ourselves.
I told you.
Since you saved my life,
I will repay you.
I have great strength.
I can help you.
How is it?
Wei,
you can't survive outside
relying solely on brute force.
You are smart,
so I'll follow you.
I want to see the outside world, too.
Wei,
can you pull up that tree?
That tree?
I can.
Let's go.
Do you think he has gone back?
Whether he goes back or not,
it's his choice.
We don't need to worry about him.
What are you picking?
Red Fruit seeds.
Don't you love them?
I'll grow them for you when we're back.
I've never seen these Red Fruits
in other places.
Could it be
they can only grow in the soil here?
It makes sense.
Let's bring some soil back.
The fruits will definitely
taste the same.
Let's make a bet.
If I can grow Red Fruits,
you will marry me.
I won't make a bet with you.
I won't be married off.
I'll just take a live-in husband.
My family won't agree, I'm afraid.
Unless you write a promise,
stating that you will always
admit defeat first
whenever we argue.
Didn't you say you are willing
to lose to me forever?
I'm willing to lose
to my princess forever.
Liar.
Alright now.
Let's get married
when we return to Qingzhou.
Anyway, Qingzhou is so far away.
My father can't interfere.
You need to first grow the Red Fruits.
Didn't you say you wouldn't
make a bet with me?
It's too late now.
Liar.
Qingzhou.
[Memorial to Empress Dejia of Great Yan]
Empress Dejia,
I am indebted to you.
As a father,
I believed I never owed Jinghe anything,
but it turns out I ended up harming him.
Maybe I
shouldn't have summoned Jinghe
back to the capital.
Everyone in the court believes that
I intended to change the heir.
I am the one who made Jinghe a target.
When it comes to the ruling,
Jinghe fell short compared to Xuanlie.
My choice was not wrong.
I had given him a chance,
but Qingzhou...
As an Emperor,
I treated him fairly.
Now, Jinghe has been buried.
As for
who killed him,
I don't want to know,
and I don't have to know it.
[Memorial to Empress Dejia of Great Yan]
Empress Dejia,
when I first ascended the throne,
your Yuchi family served with merit.
Jinghe suffered such a calamity
because I've broken my promise.
I am indebted to you
and
the Yuchi family.
Concubine Yan heard Your Majesty
had withdrawn the Imperial Guards
searching for Mei Lin.
Her Highness is worried.
Tell Concubine Yan
to consider Mei Lin already dead,
and say that it is my order.
Yes, Your Majesty.
His Majesty has his own difficulties.
I'll look for Mei Lin
myself.
The Prince Heir of Xiyan will arrive
in the capital soon.
Tell Xuanlie to receive him.
Yes, Your Majesty.
My Lord,
here is a message from General Qingyan.
On the day the Prince Heir of Xiyan
enters the capital, the Crown Prince
will replace all the city gate guards
with the Eastern Palace's Xuantie Guards
under the pretext of welcoming
the Prince Heir into the city.
Set off immediately.
Let's go back to the capital
before the Prince Heir of Xiyan.
Your Highness.
[Zigu]
Brother,
Mei Lin is missing.
Go ahead.
Stop.
Go.
Stop the carriage.
Officer, these are the herbs collected
by Yongtai Pharmacy.
Yongtai Pharmacy belongs
to Jining Marquis.
Look.
Whoever you are,
you have to be inspected.
Conduct the inspection!
Yes.
It seems we need to reconsider
how to enter the city.
[Zhaojing]
When will the Prince Heir of Xiyan
arrive in the capital?
Tomorrow at the earliest.
It took him only a few months
to ascend to the position
of the Prince Heir
from being a Hostage Prince,
whereas it has taken me over 20 years.
This is truly shameful.
Don't feel that way, Your Highness.
Everybody knows he has become
the Prince Heir
with the support
of the Emperor of Great Yan.
From now on,
send the items to Concubine Yan
according to the regulations
of Fengyi Palace.
Your Highness,
you are perhaps placing
too much importance
on the Prince Heir of Xiyan.
This pair of siblings is crucial
to the future of both countries.
If we can draw them over to our side,
it will not be a bad thing for us.
Understood.
My Lord.
♪The wind scatters the spring flowers♪
♪The dream was filled with sorrow
for the entire night♪
♪Troubled thoughts shatter
into a sky full of stars♪
♪If fate is too unbearable♪
♪I am mired in the mud♪
♪Love is helpless,
falling into the abyss♪
♪If life is a predetermined sorrow♪
♪Love is an endless wandering♪
♪A place in the heart
from which there is no return♪
♪It's a vain hope, it's in imagination♪
♪It's the distinguished light♪
♪If life is a predetermined sorrow♪
♪Love is an endless wandering♪
♪A place in the heart
from which there is no return♪
♪It's a vain hope, it's in imagination♪
♪It's the distinguished light♪
♪If life is a predetermined sorrow♪
♪Love is an endless wandering♪
♪A place in the heart
from which there is no return♪
♪It's a vain hope, it's in imagination♪
♪It's the distinguished light♪