♪We are both dim light♪
♪Will time erase us?♪
♪Those who fade away
in the shadows silently♪
♪Also crave a life
under the bright sun openly♪
♪How can I break free
from the chains of fate?♪
♪Who whispers in my ear♪
♪That I'm bound to fall?♪
♪Then burn me♪
♪Burn my stubbornness♪
♪The surging bitterness♪
♪The hot tears♪
♪Nobody knows♪
♪Entangling in the past♪
♪Silence in the darkness♪
♪The dim light finally turns♪
[Kill Me Love Me]
♪Into the fire of rebirth♪
[Episode 12]
I heard
that all the beauties with burns
will follow Mr. Yue Qin back to Xiyan
under the pretense
of failing their studies.
Really?
We're going back to Xiyan?
I don't want to return to Xiyan.
My father sold me
to the peace-making marriage delegation.
I don't have a home anymore.
I'd rather stay
in Great Yan and seek fortune.
Jia,
it's alright.
You can come to my home.
My home will be your home too.
I'm not going.
What if
your cute neighbor falls for me?
What will you do then?
[Qingqu Courtyard]
That won't happen.
He only likes me.
He never said he liked you.
How do you know?
It is raining.
He...
He took good care of me.
How did he take care of you?
What did he do?
He...
When it was cold,
he told me to put on more clothes.
When we ate,
he worried I hadn't eaten enough.
Is that love?
Yeah.
I also tell you to eat and dress warmly.
Well,
when I was happy, he was happy.
When I was upset, he cheered me up.
And he
remembers everything I say,
sometimes better than I do.
So,
that must be love, right?
I don't know if he likes you,
but
I know you like him.
Stop that.
Mei,
what do you think?
Does he like me?
Why don't you ask him yourself?
Exactly.
When you return to Xiyan, ask him.
If he doesn't dare admit he likes you,
then forget about him.
Mei,
try this.
The flower cakes at the Court
of State Ceremonial look beautiful
but don't taste sweet.
It's sweet.
Mei, where are you going?
It's still raining.
Mei!
The beauties are about to be ennobled.
No peace-making marriage beauty is allowed
to leave the Court of State Ceremonial
without an imperial edict.
She has already taken leave
from Attendant Shang.
Mr. Yue Qin.
Miss.
The Emperor's decree forbids any beauty
from leaving the Court of State Ceremonial
before the ennobling ceremony.
Even with leave granted,
they can't go out.
I've heard
this restriction
is because of the Xiyan spies.
Before,
it was easy to take leave
because you were helping.
But now that you're returning to Xiyan,
please be cautious
to avoid
bringing trouble yourself.
Thank you for the reminder.
Apologies,
I couldn't help you this time.
I see now why it was so easy
to take leave before.
It was because you were helping me.
Thanks, Mr. Yue Qin.
Let me walk you back.
Your Highness.
I've uncovered something.
The beauty burns were caused
by people from Prince Jing's mansion.
That's the real reason
they're being sent back to Xiyan.
So it wasn't about spies.
They were just pawns
in Great Yan's power struggle.
Mei Lin.
How would they care about pawns?
Your Highness.
Should we warn her?
Of course,
but not yet.
Send word to the Fanghua Palace
that I need Zigu's help.
Yes.
Jinghe's affairs
are now widely known.
With that Mei Lin around,
Luomei won't choose him.
Your Majesty,
this is this year's new tea.
I selected it myself.
Please have a taste.
Excuse me, Your Majesty.
Concubine Yan,
do you have something to tell me?
Your Majesty,
I have a request.
If you're asking for the dagger back,
it's still too soon.
No, it's not that.
Then what is it?
I give you my permission
to see your brother off to Xiyan.
Really?
Your Majesty,
you truly are the best in the world.
In the future,
just tell me what you want.
Does that mean
you'll agree to everything I ask?
That depends on what you ask for.
This is the first thing
I've ever asked of you.
You'll say yes, right?
Didn't I already grant your wish?
I'm letting you see your brother off,
aren't I?
That doesn't count.
I didn't ask for that.
You offered it yourself.
Now, I'm curious.
What is it that you want?
Your Majesty,
tomorrow is the ennobling ceremony
for the peace-making marriage beauties.
I'd like to ask you
to place Mei Lin in Fanghua Palace.
Mei Lin?
Jinghe's woman?
Your Majesty,
Mei Lin once saved my life
on our journey to the capital.
I merely want to repay her kindness.
People at the Court
of State Ceremonial say
Prince Jing is deeply in love with her.
But I worry she might be wronged.
After all...
Good thing I caught myself,
so it doesn't count
as defying your will.
Are you worried that Jinghe
will take revenge on her privately?
Do not worry.
He won't.
Your Majesty,
please let Mei Lin stay
in the Fanghua Palace
for one year.
When she marries,
she can leave from there,
which will raise her status
and fulfill my debt of gratitude.
If Prince Jing's love is true,
he won't be afraid of the test of time.
[West Mountain Mine]
The West Mountain Mine
and Lushan Hunting Grounds
are only 50 li apart.
[*Equal to half a kilometer]
My lord,
isn't this too risky?
This is the only way
to win.
If we rescue the hostage, Li Qing,
we can bring down the Crown Prince
in one move.
[Scripture]
[Wan'an Hall]
Your Highness,
Mr. Yue Qin has come
to bid farewell.
What are you doing...?
In the three years in Yan,
I received much care from you.
As I am about to depart,
I bring a small gift
to express my thanks.
You are my father's friend.
It's not even considered offering care.
I'm ashamed
to accept the gift.
Please,
Your Highness.
don't be too hasty to refuse.
[Ink, Sima's Code]
[Triple Teachings, Mirror of Antiquity]
These are
collections of folk legends
I've gathered over the years.
His Majesty often reads them
for both entertainment
and understanding the people.
Also,
this
is a specially blended incense
containing tianmu,
[*Fritillaria monantha]
longxian,
[*Ambergris]
sandalwood,
and agarwood.
It calms the mind,
dispels negativity,
and clears the senses.
His Majesty has been using this
to ease his burden of state affairs.
So that's the incense Father uses.
No wonder
you're such close friends with him.
Well then,
thank you.
Such a precious gift,
Mr. Yue Qin,
you should send one
to Prince Jing as well.
A gift
expresses gratitude for the past
and goodwill for the future.
In my view,
the future of Great Yan rests with you,
Your Highness.
So this gift
is only for you.
Very well.
But,
Mr. Yue Qin,
there's something else
I'd like to ask of you.
Please speak.
It's about the ten beauties
who are to return with you to Xiyan.
I've been thinking
about their suspicious origins.
Father doesn't want to delve deeper
because of the political implications,
but to avoid trouble in the future,
they cannot live.
If you
are willing to ease my burden,
why not come over
and have a cup of tea with me?
May I have the honor
of sailing the same boat as you,
Your Highness?
Good.
Certainly.
Also, in my view,
the future of Xiyan rests with you.
I
wish you great success
upon your return.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Mr. Yue Qin,
I had thought
you were a gentleman
who avoided the fray.
I
am just seeking a new path.
My lord,
you haven't slept all night.
You should rest.
Zhanyue Pavilion isn't that way.
Where is he going?
[Shuanglin Courtyard]
My lord.
You've come early.
The beauties
won't be sent to their mansions
until the Wu hour.
[*11 AM to 1 PM]
What time is it now?
Just past the Chen hour.
[*7 AM to 9 AM]
You'll go
and personally fetch her
when the time comes.
Yes, my lord.
Her Majesty used to say
that when you marry the one
you truly love,
you'll know what it means
to long for someone day and night.
Who would have thought we'd be so lucky
returning to Xiyan after all?
Visiting Great Yan
has certainly been an eye-opener.
Pity
Dai didn't get to return with us.
Yi.
Jia.
Take care on your journey.
Mei,
you take care as well.
If Prince Jing doesn't treat you well,
just run.
- Don't worry.
- I...
Mei is more capable than any of us.
Wherever she goes, she'll be fine.
Send word
when you've arrived.
Take care, Mei.
Get on the carriage.
Take care!
Brother,
if you can't bear it,
just come back to Great Yan
and bring Mei Lin away.
Take care of yourself
when I'm not here.
If Prince Jing gives you trouble...
Go to the Emperor for help.
Do not worry.
I'll remember everything you said.
Mei Lin,
Mei Lin!
Your Highness.
My brother says
he'll return to Great Yan soon.
Brother,
both Mei Lin and I
will be waiting for you.
Mr. Yue Qin,
come back soon.
Take care.
Be careful.
Mr. Yue Qin,
it's getting late.
Mei Lin,
we need to hurry.
The imperial decree is coming soon.
Okay.
Yunyan, Yigu, Eastern Palace.
Lan, Lingcao, Prince Qing's mansion.
Ming, Yan, General Yin's mansion.
This person...
I think I've seen him before.
He's one
of the Eastern Palace's secret guards.
I need to inform Mr. Yue Qin now.
Mei Lin.
Mei Lin!
Your decree is coming soon.
- Your Highness...
- The imperial decree has arrived.
Mei Lin, receive the decree.
Mei Lin from Xiyan,
for your virtuous character
and exceptional talent,
you are chosen to serve
in the Fanghua Palace
under the care of Concubine Yan.
The proclamation is now complete.
Mei Lin,
aren't you happy?
I wasn't allowed to tell you before
because His Majesty
didn't want Prince Jing
to know and interfere.
So...
Your Highness,
I understand your concerns.
But I forgot to give something
to Mr. Yue Qin.
I need to hurry and deliver it.
Then go.
You look better
with a simple appearance.
Actually, your festive look is nice too.
My lord.
- Has she...
- My lord.
Miss Mei Lin has been assigned
to Fanghua Palace.
My lord.
Concubine Yan asked me to inform you
that Miss Mei Lin,
unwilling to part from Mr. Yue Qin,
has gone to see him off.
There's no need for you
to make the trip.
Qingyan,
follow the Xiyan delegation.
Yes, my lord.
Mei Lin?
It's my failure.
I couldn't protect them.
Jia.
Jia, wake up.
Wake up.
Jia.
Yi.
Don't sleep.
Get up.
Wake up.
Mei Lin,
I'll take them back.
I'll bring them home.
Stay calm.
They shouldn't have gone home like this.
They were innocent,
caught in a deadly power struggle
in Great Yan.
And I'm no more than a pawn.
Even with the will,
I lack the power to save them.
When you left,
I saw it.
I saw an Eastern Palace secret guard
following you.
Was this the Crown Prince's doing?
Mei Lin, don't be rash.
You now belong to Fanghua Palace.
Our fates are intertwined.
Believe me,
no one will dare harm you.
Live and wait for me to return.
If you really want to know the truth,
ask Prince Jing.
The girls,
I'll take them home.
Mr. Yue Qin,
I leave them in your care.
You mustn't be seen,
or the Crown Prince's hands
will never be clean.
I can't bear to see another Dai
die in front of me.
The Crown Prince couldn't deal with you,
so he mimicked your burn mark
to frame me,
claiming I'm using the Xiyan beauties
to bribe court officials
and threaten
the Crown Prince's position.
What have you done?
Bandits killed my Xiyan people
for profit.
They have been dealt with.
Now,
both Great Yan and Xiyan
have their answers.
Mr. Yue Qin,
you are so thorough.
Let me beg the Crown Prince
for mercy
so I can bring their bodies
back to Xiyan for burial.
Mr. Yue Qin.
You're also so compassionate.
It's done.
I must return to the Eastern Palace
to report.
Farewell,
Mr. Yue Qin.
Farewell.
[Guests Like Clouds]
My lord,
time is running out.
We must go.
The matter of the beauties is settled.
His Majesty won't see you.
My lord,
please return.
I'll find another way.
No matter what,
I won't let you...
What did you do to those ten beauties?
The burn marks on their wrists,
did you do that?
Yes.
I asked you before,
and you lied to me.
Why?
You burned yourself too,
but you didn't tell me.
Like you,
I was buying time.
But you knew
Dai died because of that.
I had no intention of killing anyone.
But when you burned them,
you were killing them.
Those ten beauties didn't know anything.
They became pawns
because you chose them.
And now look at them.
I'm your pawn too.
And I thought
we were partners in vengeance.
Isn't it funny?
A player
and a pawn
work together to win,
not to flip the board.
A pawn
can never be a winner.
All I wanted
was justice for the innocent.
Do you think
I wanted anything different?
Everything I did
was to make sure the ones responsible
for the fire were punished.
That the Weibei Army was vindicated.
That the 100,000 innocent souls
in Qingzhou
could rest in peace.
But the way you seek justice
for the innocent,
doesn't it sound absurd even to you?
Fighting the man
who slaughtered 100,000 people,
does it matter
if the methods are absurd?
This is what sounds absurd to me.
Do you know who we're up against?
Our enemy is the Crown Prince.
Court politics are no less brutal
than the battlefield.
On the battlefield,
the only thing that matters is victory.
I won't work with you
from this moment on.
My lord,
the ten beauties have been silenced
by the Crown Prince.
What?
When I reached the delegation,
Miss Mei Lin already knew
about the deaths.
Yue Qin has likely formed an alliance
with the Crown Prince.
There's no way the silencing
could've gone so smoothly without help.
Tell me everything you know.
[Guests Like Clouds]
Sir,
after they loaded the bodies, they left.
I didn't see anything else.
I'll take my leave now.
It's Xiyan's closed-breath pill.
My lord,
the manager of the way station said
Wang Quan
from the Eastern Palace was here.
You were right.
Yue Qin and the Crown Prince
have formed an alliance.
Qingyan,
we underestimated him.
Mr. Yue Qin,
don't worry.
Thanks to the closed-breath pills,
we've deceived the Crown Prince.
It is late.
Let's rest briefly,
and then continue on our journey.
Mr. Yue Qin,
you have truly done a good job,
killing two birds with one stone.
My Xiyan people shouldn't die in vain.
And Mei Lin
shouldn't be deceived by you either.
My lord.
All of you,
write a letter to Mei Lin,
telling her you're safe.
She's already burdened
by the 100,000 souls of Qingzhou.
Don't add ten more lives to that burden.
No need for them to write.
This letter
was meant to be delivered to her
upon our return to Xiyan.
But since you're here,
[To Mei Lin]
I'll leave it in your care.
Your Highness,
your lies will be exposed.
There's no need for me
to use all these lives for a charade.
Murong Jinghe,
you are not worthy
of walking this path with her.
Let's go.
Aren't you going to read the letter?
At least he won't harm her.
But what if Mr. Yue Qin
added lies to the letter?
Then Miss Mei Lin
will hate you even more.
[To Mei Lin]
The letter is meant for her.
I shouldn't read it.
[Fanghua Palace]
I've noticed
you haven't been happy lately.
Are you not used to it here?
No.
I know Fanghua Palace
has a lot of rules,
but we can find ways around them.
Look.
I brought you something.
This is the bamboo brew
my brother left behind.
Now,
we can drink whenever we want.
I know you like drinking.
Whenever I'm unhappy,
I drink this bamboo brew.
Come, Your Highness.
Cheers!
I'll tell you something.
On the day of the ennobling ceremony,
Prince Jing came to see His Majesty,
hoping to take you back to his mansion.
But His Majesty turned him away.
I thought he'd make a scene,
but he's been surprisingly quiet.
Your Highness,
Prince Jing wants to see you.
Prince Jing.
This is Fanghua Palace,
I have an imperial decree.
You can't take her away.
Your Highness, you need not worry.
Since Mei Lin has been assigned
to Fanghua Palace,
I wouldn't dare take her away.
I just want to say a few words.
Then I'll leave.
I won't work with you
from this moment on.
I have nothing more
to say to you.
Those beauties aren't dead.
Even if you don't trust me,
trust him.
[To Mei Lin]
Mei Lin,
do not worry.
The girls have safely returned to Xiyan.
I kept the truth hidden out of necessity
to deceive the Crown Prince.
Take care.
Live and wait for me to return.
I never intended
to kill them.
I know.
But their lives
were never your priority.
This was meant for you.
I brought it from Shuanglin Courtyard.
Since we're going our separate ways,
there's no need
to pretend you love me anymore.
Goodbye.
[Fragrant Waterside]
My lord.
Since you're already in the palace,
His Majesty wishes to see you.
Father.
Please, have some tea.
What?
You think I'm nagging?
Father,
I understand your intentions.
Since you understand,
you're not
to visit Fanghua Palace anymore.
Son,
it's time you took a wife.
Your mother indulged your whims,
but I won't.
General Yin is here.
Your Majesty.
My respects.
General Yin, you may rise.
The hunt in Lushan is approaching.
I've checked the spots.
Everything is ready.
Great.
General Yin,
sit.
Luomei,
you've returned to the capital,
and it's time
you thought about marriage.
With Great Yan's borders unsettled,
I...
Marriage and succession
are the natural order.
We cannot delay your future
for public affairs.
Don't worry.
Choose according to your heart.
My focus is on serving the empire,
not marriage.
How about this?
The one who claims the prize
at the spring hunt,
no matter their status,
will be my future spouse.
Very well.
The champion will be a hero,
worthy of General Yin.
Jinghe,
I remember
you were the champion every year.
I'm sure this year
will be no different.
If Prince Jing aims to win,
the prize
is certainly his.
Good.
After the spring hunt,
I'll issue the decree.
Father,
my body is no longer what it was.
These days,
I can only hunt rabbits.
I've promised General Yin
that she will have the final say.
Whoever she chooses,
I'll grant it.
At the spring hunt,
I'll give Your Majesty an answer.
[Fanghua Palace]
I never intended to kill them.
♪The wind scatters the spring flowers♪
♪The dream was filled with sorrow
for the entire night♪
♪Troubled thoughts shatter
into a sky full of stars♪
♪If fate is too unbearable♪
♪I am mired in the mud♪
♪Love is helpless♪
♪Falling into the abyss♪
My mansion recently hired a chef
from Qingzhou.
When you come,
and once your taste returns,
whether the chef is a good one or not,
you can judge his cooking yourself.
♪An endless wandering♪
♪A place in the heart♪
I'll be holding
onto your hairpin for now.
Once we've taken down the Crown Prince,
If you want to talk to your mother,
come to me.
[Shuanglin Courtyard]
Mother,
what kind of person is he?
I can't tell.
Mei Lin.
- Mei Lin!
- Your Highness.
Do not worry.
Prince Jing won't bother you anymore.
His Majesty has forbidden him
from visiting Fanghua Palace.
[Shuanglin Courtyard]
Is this painted by Prince Jing?
Could it be that the rumors
about his love for you
are true after all?
No.
Prince Jing can't possibly be sincere.
My mother said
the ones who truly care for you
in the palace
are those who love you quietly.
Loud displays of affection
only bring harm.
There must be a hidden agenda
behind his affection for you.
No.
We need to pray to the gods
to make him stop pestering you.
Pray to the gods?
This is our Xiyan Forget-Sorrow Flower.
When you use it to pray to the gods,
if it sinks to the bottom of the water,
you'll never see the person
who troubles you again.
Forget-Sorrow Flower.
It works.
When Ziyu bullied me,
I prayed with the Forget-Sorrow Flower,
and the next day,
I was in the peace-making marriage.
Whether
he loves me or not,
we've already become strangers.
It doesn't matter anymore.
Let's go, Your Highness.
Wait!
It's about to sink!
Just wait a little longer.
The paper flower is already wet.
It'll sink sooner or later.
Let's go.
[Shuanglin Courtyard]
♪The wind scatters the spring flowers♪
♪The dream was filled with sorrow
for the entire night♪
♪Troubled thoughts shatter
into a sky full of stars♪
♪If fate is too unbearable♪
♪I am mired in the mud♪
♪Love is helpless,
falling into the abyss♪
♪If life is a predetermined sorrow♪
♪Love is an endless wandering♪
♪A place in the heart
from which there is no return♪
♪It's a vain hope, it's in imagination♪
♪It's the distinguished light♪
♪If life is a predetermined sorrow♪
♪Love is an endless wandering♪
♪A place in the heart
from which there is no return♪
♪It's a vain hope, it's in imagination♪
♪It's the distinguished light♪
♪If life is a predetermined sorrow♪
♪Love is an endless wandering♪
♪A place in the heart
from which there is no return♪
♪It's a vain hope, it's in imagination♪
♪It's the distinguished light♪