I've been craving this braised pork, Mom.
Oh, you two are back.
I was just saying...
These past few days,
the air in this house has been so tense,
it's about to explode.
Your dad won't sleep, day or night.
Just like taming a hawk.
If you say anything to him,
he snaps back with something nasty.
Lao Kezi and I both just steer clear of him.
It's been so hard on you, Mom.
But still,
Uncle told me,
and I think Uncle's got a point.
If you really want to make the Three-Zhang-Three,
you really do need Hongxing Factory.
Don't let him hear you say that.
So what if he does?
It's the truth. I'm not lying.
Here's what I think:
since Chairman Guan Shan
is so eager to make this happen,
I'll go have a word with Secretary Peng,
and see if Chairman Guan Shan can
talk to Uncle Xuan in person.
See? See there?
Miss Lin really is the clever one.
You'd never have thought of that.
That's a good plan.
Good.
That's what you call finding a graceful exit.
Right.
But the mule has to want to step down.
I say mule, you say mule.
Who exactly are we talking about?
You get to say it,
Don't talk nonsense. Honestly, you.
Actually, when we got the Three-Zhang-Three
research and development assignment,
everyone in the group was raring to go.
But if you really intend to bring in
Master Xuan Yongnian,
an outsider, as Chief Engineer,
have you thought about
how all our veteran masters here
would feel about it?
Bringing in Xuan Yongnian, what's that supposed to mean?
Is Hongxing Factory really out of capable people?
Chairman, Chief Man,
think carefully.
Uncle Man, what's your view?
Making the Three-Zhang-Three great Xuan paper,
no one's ever done it, past or present.
No one can swear they'll pull it off.
I'm a retired man now too.
If old Xuan comes,
and we all pool our ideas and work together,
I think the Three-Zhang-Three great Xuan paper
would stand a real chance.
Then let me say it again.
Go ahead.
Chairman,
the Three-Zhang-Three great Xuan paper,
it can't be done by one person alone.
It requires dozens of people working together.
We all know Xuan Yongnian's temperament.
If he comes back and acts like he did years ago,
and can't bring us all
together as one,
then how could we ever succeed?
Making the Three-Zhang-Three,
it's the honor of our Hongxing Factory.
There's no way to hand such a great honor
over to an outsider.
Chairman,
we can't just labor for Xuan Yongnian's gain.
Our workshop earns such a great honor,
and we'd give it to an outsider?
Watch your tone.
Everything you say comes out so harsh.
Now the higher-ups have assigned the Three-Zhang-Three project
to us.
We not only have to complete it,
but also guarantee it succeeds.
At a time like this,
do we weigh everyone's feelings,
or the bigger picture?
Uncle Lao Kezi.
Madam.
Xiao Min is here.
Xiao Min.
Master's still shut up in his room.
He's in there.
Perfect, I'll go keep him company.
No, don't go see him.
Even Uncle Lao Kezi and I don't dare go near him.
Right now he's just like a fighting cock.
He snaps at anyone who comes close.
He says all sorts of nasty things.
Just leave him be.
Madam, I'm not afraid of a scolding.
It's hardly the first time.
I'll just
go help him think it through, offer some ideas.
Just watch me.
Xiao Min,
just take my advice.
Right now your Master
is like a cicada molting its shell.
No matter how much he's hurting,
he has to fight through it himself.
I'm just afraid if you go in,
he'll say something cruel and hurt you.
Madam,
I'm not afraid of being hurt.
I just feel for Master.
I'm afraid...
I'm afraid in the end the Three-Zhang-Three won't get made,
and Master ruins his health over it.
I appreciate the thought.
Here's what we'll do.
If anything happens with your Master,
I'll have Xuan Ying call you, all right?
All right.
Chairman, may I say a few words?
Go ahead.
Everyone's had plenty to say just now.
What I want to say is this.
From the founding of the nation until today,
our Xuan paper industry's quality,
capacity, and brand influence
have been carried by our state-run Hongxing Factory.
Now, bringing in Master Xuan
leaves everyone feeling uneasy.
I can understand that.
But hearing the Chairman's big-picture view,
we should all understand this.
As the only state-owned enterprise,
as the leading force in the Xuan paper industry,
our stance matters a great deal.
Yes.
Twenty-eight years ago,
Master Xuan and I did have a falling out.
But back then, I was young and foolish.
Let me speak from the bottom of my heart.
In my heart, Master Xuan
has always been my Master.
And always will be.
Well said.
Everyone's misgivings and concerns,
I understand them all now.
So why don't we
look back at our history together.
In the early years, our superiors
brought in from Peach Blossom Town
the elite core from every paper mill.
That's what formed
the backbone team of our Hongxing Factory.
It also solidified Hongxing Factory's foundation.
So tell me,
how could the Xuan paper firms of Peach Blossom Town
ever be considered outsiders?
In what way is he an outsider?
And take Master Xuan.
Xuan Yongnian's grandfather
was our factory's
first deputy director in charge of production.
And his father
devoted his whole life to Hongxing Factory.
As for Xuan Yongnian,
he even served as our factory's
director in charge of production.
How can anyone call him an outsider?
Even now,
we're still splitting hairs over insider and outsider.
Is that right?
Master Man
and Master Xuan,
these are Peach Blossom Town's
only two national Intangible Heritage Inheritors.
Especially at this moment,
I believe
we can't do without either of them.
The success of the Three-Zhang-Three project
isn't just Hongxing Factory's glory.
It's the glory of our entire
Chinese papermaking industry.
Well said!
Uncles, elders,
I'm Xiao Min.
All of these
are gifts from Little Min to all of you.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Of course, of course, no need for that.
Thank you.
You're all the most experienced
papermaking masters in Peach Blossom Town.
I invited you all here today
to talk about the Three-Zhang-Three.
As the old saying goes,
unity is strength,
even dirt can turn to gold.
Right.
So, what have you all decided?
Well, Little Min,
how do we set the paper stack?
It's not that simple.
Am I right?
Yes, yes, yes.
Count it out on your fingers.
How many people can we find?
More than forty skilled hands.
Where would we ever find them?
Exactly.
Right, right, right.
Little Min,
in a week,
even in a month you couldn't train them.
They can't even lift it.
It's no joke. What do you all say?
Right.
That's right.
We've been talking for a good while now,
and everyone's raised plenty of good ideas.
Right.
All the different methods,
all their pros and cons,
we've gone through them all.
Everyone unanimously agrees
it has to be Hongxing Factory.
Right, right, right.
It's got to be Hongxing Factory.
Isn't it strange?
People, you know,
they just can't fight against fate.
Director Xuan.
Liu Shiguang.
Director Xuan, you still remember me.
Here's the thing.
They're all waiting for you inside.
I won't take up any more of your time.
Go on in.
Sure, sure.
We'll chat later.
Director Xuan.
Really? Director Xuan?
It really is you, Director Xuan!
Hello, Master.
Director Xuan, hello.
I'm Xuan Yongnian.
Hello.
Hello, hello.
I never expected to see you here at the factory.
You all know me?
Of course we all know you.
Our director often mentions you.
He tells us to learn what you taught,
that making paper is like shaping a person.
Yes.
Yes, yes, yes.
Director Xuan.
Hello, Director Xuan.
Master.
Director Xuan, Director Xuan.
Hello, Master. Hello, Master.
You've come back.
I'm so thrilled.
It's me, Xiao Liuzi!
Hello, Master. Hello, Master.
Hello, Master. Hello, hello, Master.
Director Xuan.
Hello, everyone.
Ah, Shi Quan.
Master.
Come out here.
Stand right here.
Who let you be the Chief Papermaker?
Did you get my permission?
And you just took the mould.
I was just trying it for fun.
Making paper isn't a game.
And it can't be played with.
You stand right here for me.
Stand for one hour.
Reflect on what you've done.
What are you so smug about?
Chief and assistant papermaker, back in the day,
they were all called paper beggars.
What did you say?
Say that again.
In your eyes,
we're all just paper beggars?
Little Stone.
You're still so young.
Why do you degrade yourself like this?
With your attitude toward papermaking,
how could you ever make good paper?
How will you live your life?
How will you stand in this world?
Director Xuan.
All day it's standing punishments or reciting ancestral teachings.
Treating yourself like a feudal Shed Master.
You want to be the Shed Master of a paper shed?
This is a state-owned factory.
It's not one of those old paper sheds.
And there's no Shed Master here.
Little Stone already has gray hair.
Shi Quan, just like you back then,
is now a production director too.
Director Shi now.
Master.
For 28 years, I've always wanted to say...
I was wrong.
It's been such a long time now.
There's no right or wrong anymore.
Little Stone.
Go fetch me some Wu Spring Water.
Master, you...
I want to take a sip.
Go on, hurry.
Hello, everyone.
Good, good, hello Director Xuan.
I'm so happy to see the masters of our factory.
I haven't seen Uncle Xuan this happy in a long time.
Right, because we're all Xuan paper artisans.
This is good water.
Only water this good
can make good paper.
Wonderful, wonderful.
To be honest,
before Master Xuan arrived,
deep down, I wasn't sure
we could pull this off.
After all,
what we're doing this time
is to break new ground
in the thousand-year history of Xuan paper.
But you know,
when I saw Master Xuan's spirit today,
my heart lit right up.
No more need for words.
Master Xuan,
it's settled then.
The Three-Zhang-Three large Xuan paper,
we're not just going to make it,
we'll make it, and make it well.
Master Xuan's partnership with our Hongxing Factory
can only succeed.
Failure is not an option.
Now our project's leadership team
is fully assembled and ready.
Master Xuan,
you and Master Lao Man
will jointly serve as Chief Engineers of this project.
How's that?
Deputy Manager Jiang Chen,
you'll handle the execution details.
All right.
Good.
My job is,
from everyone's daily needs
to the workshops,
the raw materials,
the technical support, and so on,
in every aspect,
to mobilize every resource we can
and fully support
the smooth progress of our project.
And to provide everyone
with the best service in everything.
Are you all satisfied?
Great!
Master Xuan,
everyone,
twenty-eight years ago,
the factory appointed Master Xuan
as Hongxing Factory's Chief Engineer.
This appointment letter was signed back then.
But in a fit of anger, you resigned.
Look at that, what a shame.
And so,
this appointment letter
sat in the archives for twenty-eight years.
Now,
I formally announce,
on behalf of Hongxing Factory,
that this long-overdue,
twenty-eight-year-old appointment letter
is officially presented to Master Xuan Yongnian.
Keep it as a memento.
Thank you, thank you, Chairman Guan.
Let's give him a round of applause.
Good, good.
This Hongxing Factory, normally,
keeps a pretty low profile.
But when something big comes up,
that boldness of theirs really shows.
This time they set up six teams.
Just the sheet-forming section alone,
they split it into two teams.
A paper vat team and a mould frame team.
And there's a mechanical team too.
A mould frame this huge,
they have to raise it with pulley machinery.
So they set up mechanical rails too.
And there's one more thing,
I bet none of you have ever seen it.
I sure never have.
The workshop.
It's enormous.
Never mind Three-Zhang-Three,
even Four-Zhang-Two Xuan paper,
they could make it, no problem.
And there's more.
There's also a labor team.
They set it all up exactly as I asked.
Out of over 300 sheet-forming workers,
they picked 43 people.
And every one of them's a master.
And the most crucial part?
Their Chief Papermaker captain,
they want me to pick him myself.
To make the final call myself.
Now that's impressive.
On top of that, Hongxing Factory
even has a dedicated technical team.
And what does that technical team handle?
Like what materials to use.
Wood, or steel,
or aluminum alloy.
Weight, tensile strength, all that data.
They calculate it all crystal clear.
Here, Dad, have some water.
There's a material selection team too.
Just the material selection team alone,
they assigned me four people for it.
All the processed bark and straw,
we pick only the very best.
They want me to select it myself.
To decide it myself.
Yongnian,
the way you're hyping it all up,
somehow I feel like
you're commanding a mighty army.
I'm not exaggerating.
At my age,
why would I make a fuss?
Exactly.
Let's be honest here.
Hongxing Factory really is impressive.
Well-organized and powerful.
Back when my dad was at our factory,
how many people could he manage?
Now Hongxing has so many people,
it's honestly hard to keep up.
Yongnian,
have you decided the mould frame material?
Fir wood.
For one, it's lightweight.
And another thing,
it absorbs and dries quickly.
A mould frame this big
absolutely has to be lightweight,
and the key is it can't warp.
I laid out three requirements,
and they agreed to all of them.
First,
it must be wild fir wood,
both hardness and toughness
have to be excellent.
Second,
the length must be 12 meters.
Third,
it must be naturally air-dried.
Kiln-dried won't do.
That's not easy to find.
Lao Kezi
called me on my way over just now.
He found it.
Wants me to come see it this afternoon.
That fast?
I know, right?
How can I not be thrilled?
Of course.
Yongnian,
look at how energetic you are.
Like you're 20 years younger.
Our Yongnian's about to do something big.
Almost 70 years old,
and 20 years younger, huh?
But still,
I'm confident.
I think the Three-Zhang-Three Xuan paper
just might be possible.
Fir wood 12 meters long,
same thickness at both ends, right?
Good, very good.
It's naturally grown, isn't it?
Get in touch about this one too.
Come take a look at this.
Have you contacted this one?
Why would I ask you for cultivated wood?
Cultivated wood isn't sturdy enough.
Old Xiao, Old Xiao, Old Xiao.
Air-dried, not kiln-dried.
Air-dried, kiln-dried won't do.
You hear me? Air-dried.
Hurry and find it for me, ask around.
Quick, quick.
Air-dried wood absorbs less water.
You got it?
Yes, yes, yes.
Aren't our requirements a bit too high?
Exactly.
Right.
High standards have their reasons.
This time, even if my Master
wanted Sun Wukong's Golden Cudgel,
I'd still have to find it for him.
That won't do.
This one, this won't work, no good.
Swap it out, swap it out.
Oh right, I just remembered.
Which of us has a relative from Jiangxi?
Someone who deals in timber purchasing.
Pretty well-known around Jiangxi.
Who's from Jiangxi?
I heard Er Hu might have a relative there.
Right, it's Er Hu.
Er Hu.
Er Hu, hey Er Hu!
Look, this is all our family's timber.
Take a look.
It's still not quite right.
Thank you, boss.
You're welcome.
Thank you, Director.
It's fine, it's fine, no problem.
Sorry for the trouble.
Come by anytime!
Alright, you get back to work.
No need to see me off, really.
Alright, goodbye.
How much longer till we get there?
About another hour.
My third uncle's factory
is famous all over Jiangxi.
They've got every kind of wood.
Take a break.
Go a bit faster.
Chief Xuan.
There's another workshop next door.
It's just a bit small.
How about we go take a look?
Forget it.
These places all carry the same stuff.
Chief Xuan.
Don't you think our standards are a bit too high?
Should we or not?
So, Brother Min, didn't I tell you?
Big enough, right?
We've got every kind of wood there is.
All right.
Third Uncle.
So, how is it?
It's shade-dried,
but it isn't wild.
Boss,
don't play games with me now.
You want it 12 meters long.
Cultivated ones can grow tall enough,
but where would you find wild ones 12 meters long?
There's nothing I can do.
We insist on the wild ones.
All right then, go and look around.
If you find them,
I'll pay ten times the price.
Thank you, boss.
We'll look elsewhere.
Oh my goodness.
Chief Xuan.
We've asked everyone we could.
We've pulled every string too.
There really aren't any.
For a mould frame this big,
only wild wood will do.
Cultivated wood lacks resilience,
and once it's lifted up,
it warps easily.
Besides, cultivated fir wood
absorbs way too much water.
How could the sheet-formers ever lift it?
We simply can't find any.
We really can't find any.
Can't find any...
We have to find it anyway.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
Nine, ten.
That's enough.
Min.
Uncle, Uncle.
Come take a look at this, Uncle.
Come here and check it for me.
Tell me if this is wild fir wood.
All right, let me have a look.
Come on, come on.
It's fine, it's fine.
Easy now, easy.
Let me take a look.
Just those three pieces.
Yes.
Are you sure?
I'm sure.
This is wild fir wood.
Master.
Take a look.
Master Xuan is here.
Old Xuan!
Come, come, come.
Wild fir, naturally air-dried.
That's right, isn't it?
Take a look, take a look.
Now that's more like it.
Truly rare.
Absolutely.
This fir has some age to it.
Wild fir this precious, these days,
is extremely rare.
This apprentice of yours
really put his heart into it.
We even found fir this precious.
That's a good omen, I'd say.
How does that saying go again?
It's a long march ahead,
and this is the first step.
Master,
this credit
isn't mine alone.
We should thank Er Hu too.
Without him,
we'd never have found this lucky start.
That's right.
These two wild firs aren't cheap.
Xiao Min,
you can't pay for this out of your own pocket.
No, no, no, it's just pocket change.
I'll cover it.
Master Xuan,
You and President Xiao look after me so much.
These two logs are on me.
Your heart's in the right place,
but things should be done properly.
Let's do it by the rules.
All right.
Lao Man,
this money should come from us.
Say something.
Master Xuan,
if you approve of these two materials,
as for the money,
don't you worry about it.
You've got me, after all.
Fine, as long as he says it's proper.
Right.
Master,
if you're satisfied,
where should we deliver this wood?
Xiao Guo,
drive it straight back to the factory.
Put it by the mould workshop door.
Got it.
Be careful.
Let's go.
The length's enough.
More than enough.
Plenty.
Master Xuan,
now that the materials are chosen,
shouldn't we pick the people too?
The sheet-forming masters at Hongxing Factory
are all quite good.
They meet the requirements too.
Now all that's left is
height and arm length.
These all need to meet the standard.
The key is finding the right leader.
That's crucial.
Master,
let me do it.
Master Xuan,
let me take part too.
We'll all sign up.
Lao Xuan,
I know
you want to find the Chief Papermaker.
Besides the Chief Papermaker,
drying and trimming
both need a leader too.
As for sheet forming,
Lao Man, you know it best.
You speak up.
Each has his own strengths.
It's really hard to choose.
A Chief Papermaker over forty-odd men,
I've never had to pick one before.
You'd better take a look yourself.
Master Xuan,
how about we do this,
the way I see it,
everyone's here anyway.
Let all the qualified ones step up.
Let's go and pick them on the spot.
All right.
Let's go.
You don't have to stop what you're doing,
but hear me out for a moment.
Being able to make Three-Zhang-Three paper
is a truly glorious thing.
But if you can become the head Chief Papermaker,
that's the highest honor of all.
You all remember Master Xuan Yongnian, right?
The old Master Xuan
who used to work at our factory.
In a little while,
he'll be coming over here
to pick the head Chief Papermaker.
So show off your very best skills.
If any of you gets picked
as the head Chief Papermaker,
I'll treat you to a meal and drinks.
Master Xuan.
Hard at work, Master?
Old Xuan.
I've looked through all these workshops.
So many master craftsmen,
but not a single one
is fit to be a Chief Papermaker.
They're all seasoned masters,
and their skills are good too.
But still,
to lead the sheet-forming team,
none of them quite measure up.
With so many excellent masters here,
you can tell just from a single glance?
No need to look. Use your ears.
Use... your ears?
A true expert doesn't need to look.
Just listen to the first scoop of water,
and everything becomes clear.
Is there really no one else?
Every qualified master is right here.
In the craft of papermaking,
only the sheet-forming master is a true artisan.
There's truth to that saying.
The shape of the paper
carries the personality of the sheet-forming master.
You know this.
Whether it's a drive for perfection,
or an untamed, defiant spirit.
In short, the sheet-forming master has character,
and the paper he makes,
that's when it becomes living paper.
That reminds me of someone.
Who?
Wei Jianzhi.
The single vat is off today, so he's not here.
Right, he works a single vat now.
No one will partner with him.
Anyone paired with him can't last three days.
The last master who partnered with him,
the two nearly got into a fight.
And why was that?
The man had made paper for twenty years,
yet Wei insisted he couldn't form sheets at all,
said he'd picked the wrong trade,
that he'd never truly learned the craft.
Let's go check out his workshop.
Old Xuan.
This is the vat where Master Wei forms his sheets.
How long has Wei Jianzhi
worked at this vat?
Almost two years now.
He's the one.
Meet with him tomorrow and have a talk.
No, no, Master Xuan.
You... you haven't even met the man yet,
and you already think he'll do?
Nine times out of ten.
Take a look.
Look closely.
He's worn a tiny groove here.
Now look at the others'.
Theirs are flat, just a small patch.
What does that tell you?
It means his hands are steady.
Now look at where his feet stand.
He's worn marks where he always stands,
as if he's stood there for years.
Right.
It means his feet are steady.
Steady hands, steady feet,
that means his heart is steady too.
He's a meticulous man.
And a man like that
can turn out fine work.
So it's that simple?
Not simple at all.
First scoop hugs the body,
second scoop breaks the heart,
two hands set the thickness,
two feet reveal the spirit,
the mould lifts a thousand layers of snow,
the paper falls into eternal spring.
Look, so far
we've opened 34 stores.
Apart from a few like this one,
where we picked a poor location,
all the other 31 cultural stores
have all exceeded profit expectations.
That many?
Is that a lot?
Let me see.
What are you looking at? You can't read it.
Fine, fine, fine.
Stop drinking now.
You can't read it.
Let me see.
Fine, fine, fine.
Can you two stop staring at the money?
Can you show a little concern for me?
You're not allowed to drink any more.
Master...
When Master picked the Chief Papermaker,
why didn't he choose me?
When your top disciple steps up,
I can breeze through it.
I can handle anything.
He didn't even consider my feelings,
he just stood up and left.
Stomped right off.
I was standing right here,
and he didn't even glance at me.
He just went and picked someone else.
If he'd at least looked at me once,
I'd feel a little better inside.
All right, all right, let me go check on him.
You two stay here and talk business.
Sure, sure, it's fine, it's fine.
He'll be fine once he throws up.
Sit, sit, sit.
He's always like this, it's fine.
Well, at any rate, right now,
our momentum is really strong.
Every store we open becomes a hit.
So I'm thinking,
let's concentrate our cash flow,
and open 20 new stores right away.
We need to get on it fast.
You can't just
focus on the money.
Then what should we focus on?
You've got to focus on me.
We're a team, right?
We're all one team.
Aren't we?
We are.
Why do I have to patch up
that whole mess with my master?
Do you get it?
I get it, I get it.
I'm not drinking.
Just have one sip.
If you don't become the Chief Papermaker,
is your life over or something?
Wrong.
I'm doing it to live a better life.
When I left the Xuan family,
they cursed me for betraying my master.
Was I wrong?
I... I don't think I was wrong.
Brother Xiao Min,
you're not from Hongxing Factory, why pick you?
Good, very good.
Well said.
Hurry, go on.
Fill it up.
Slow down, slow down.
What are you filling up so much for?
Fill the glass with wine.
Fill it up.
Sit, sit, sit down, sit down.
But this time, the old man,
he's partnering with Hongxing Factory.
Right?
Hongxing Factory is full of talent.
Would it ever come around to you?
No way.
If the old man forced you into that spot,
an apprentice who hasn't formed sheets in 20 years,
pushing you up there,
how would he explain that to Hongxing Factory?
No one would accept it.
You understand?
I understand.
If I were you,
right about now,
I'd stick close to the old man,
stay right by his side.
Do whatever I can do.
Odd jobs and chores,
boiling water, fetching his shoes.
Do whatever you can.
Use your sincerity
to move heaven and earth.
The old man will notice it.
Is something wrong with you?
Yes.
What's wrong then?
Why can't you work with anyone?
I won't partner with people who have no integrity.
Watch your mouth!
Who has no integrity?
Not respecting your own craft
is no different from trashing your own integrity.
You're the Chief Papermaker for the team.
But
if none of the sheet-forming crew respects you,
then I'll have to replace you.
Old Wei.
Get yourself well prepared.
Cao Deyong.
Here.
Joined the factory in 2004 to learn sheet forming.
Chief Papermaker for 16 years.
Zhang Qingliang.
Here.
Joined the factory in 2001 to learn sheet forming.
Chief Papermaker for 18 years.
Man Xiaochuan.
Here.