There's one more thing.
I wanted to ask you.
On your way back just now,
did Zhang Du say anything?
He didn't say much.
Don't you know what your dad means?
Dad, are you still undecided
about whether to keep him or not?
What do you think?
I'd rather not give my opinion.
I'm heading out.
Son.
Xuan Yan.
I know I usually
don't handle things well.
I always take it out on you.
This time, it's all up to you.
As long as you kids are okay,
that's better than anything.
I'm off.
Son.
When you're done, come home.
Don't forget your mom and dad are here.
I know.
Senior brother
Just leave the clothes there
I'll wash them
It's just two pieces
I can handle it myself
Two pieces, let me do it
You go rest
Zhang Du
Master's wife
Is something wrong?
I...
I came to say goodbye
Do you really have to leave?
Aren't you going to say goodbye to your master?
Alright, Master's wife
Master.
I have been reckless and unworthy.
I'm sorry.
Let bygones be bygones.
What are your plans now?
Still making paper?
Yes.
Making Ancient-Method Paper.
Master, whether you understand or not,
this is the only way for me.
Everyone walks their own path.
No one can walk it for another.
Zhang Du.
Master's wife.
I can't bear to see you go.
When the factory was struggling,
you never took a single cent.
Such devotion is rare.
Your master and I will never forget it.
But the Xuan family has its rules.
We can't owe you your wages.
And I don't have your account number.
Here are your wages and allowances
plus interest, bonuses, and such.
I've been saving it all for you.
I didn't take good care of you.
Take it.
No, Master's wife.
I can't accept this.
Take it.
You'll need money out there.
Be good now, be good.
If you have nowhere to go,
this old house of mine,
though it's a bit old and shabby,
still,
you can come stay anytime.
When you've made something of yourself,
if you want to move out,
that's up to you.
Thank you, Master.
Thank you, Master's wife.
Our Twelve Beauties of Jinling series.
These are the first six we're releasing.
Take a look.
The first six in this release,
we're offering at a special price today.
The other six will be released soon.
Each one better than the last.
Today,
it's our promotion day.
We're launching a 7th premium Hengheng.
If today you
collect all six of the previous ones,
today's premium Hengheng is yours free.
And right now,
the results are pretty good.
Our cultural booths draw a big crowd.
I'm getting more and more confident.
I'm
planning
to expand our Blind Box series
with a few more lines.
Like legendary Chinese figures,
Spirits of the Four Treasures of the Study
Whichever sells best,
we'll push as our flagship.
You just focus on your designs.
We'll back you all the way.
Here, this way.
But I wouldn't recommend
putting energy into horizontal expansion.
I think you should dig deeper vertically,
create characters with more cultural depth
and stories behind them.
If I'm understanding you right,
you're implying my work lacks depth.
I...
That's not what I meant.
I'm just saying,
while you're providing
Emotional Value to consumers,
your cultural foundation
could be a bit more substantial,
a bit richer.
It's just a suggestion.
President Xin, here's your coffee.
Hey, what are you laughing at?
It's kind of scary, so sudden.
No, I'm laughing because
you actually consider others' feelings now.
That's not really like you.
I was afraid if I was too blunt,
you couldn't handle it.
You haven't even tried.
How do you know I can't handle it?
Come on.
Say it straight. Let me hear.
My opinion is:
content first, narrative-driven.
Cultural products without cultural roots
are just fast-moving consumer goods.
And Emotional Value isn't to please buyers.
It's about creating emotional resonance.
And cultural products
must be built upon
the cultural foundation of Xuan paper.
Dig into the cultural logic of Xuan paper
and its handcrafted value,
and with your audience,
build a deep emotional connection.
Otherwise, it's like a dog chasing its tail,
just spinning in the fast-consumer cycle.
Well, that really stings.
Nicely done.
Hello
I'll notify President Xin right away
Sister Xin
What is it?
The Chairman is at the company
He's calling all executives for 1-on-1s
You're the last one on the list
And I also heard
that apart from Vice President Zhang
no one knew the Chairman was coming today
When Vice President Zhang went to pick him up
he didn't even bring a driver
Before the Chairman even arrived, he...
Get to the point
What the Chairman's asking about
is all about your cultural-creative work
What's there to ask about that?
The tree seeks calm but the wind blows on
You'd better handle this carefully
Whatever you do, don't clash with him
You know me
My biggest trait is being open-minded
I'm willing to trust everyone around me
But
that person has to be worthy of my trust
Understood
Sister Xin, look
Zhang. Accounts.
Whose number is this?
No idea
Probably someone's burner number
The meaning is pretty clear
Zhang
Vice President Zhang
Accounts
The Chairman is auditing the books
For an audit, he'd just call finance in
and that would be enough
He's not auditing the company's books
He's auditing mine
For the Chairman to act like this
is really disheartening
He trusts no one
Who's going to work hard for him?
He trusts Vice President Zhang too much.
About that purchase on the 2nd,
Here's what happened
I asked Vice President Zhang to sign it
but he was away on a business trip
So I went to President Xin
She said production couldn't be delayed
So she told me to take the detailed list
and organize it clearly
and ensure the inventory logs were signed
and keep clear records
She even explained things to finance
saying to disburse the purchase funds first
and get Vice President Zhang to sign later
Afterwards, this was truly my fault
Once things got busy
I missed Vice President Zhang's signature
But
I guarantee the entire purchasing process
was fully documented
The amount matches previous ones exactly
All of this
you can verify yourself
Last month's entertainment expenses doubled
Are you aware of this?
I think this wooden one, you know,
sometimes I'm afraid
you have to consider the audience, right?
Chairman, thank you for the long trip.
Go on with your work.
You must be tired from the trip.
Here, here.
I made you a cup of coffee.
Thank you, thank you.
You're welcome.
You see,
it's the same coffee,
but yours tastes completely different.
Thank you for the compliment, Chairman.
I was on a business trip nearby,
so I dropped by to see you all.
Sit.
All of us
hope the Chairman
can visit us more often,
give us some feedback,
so we'll have more room to improve.
Don't just think about advancing.
Sometimes retreating in big strides
is for advancing in big strides tomorrow.
I'd love to charge in tonight
and by tomorrow morning
wipe out the enemy's million-strong army.
But we can't, comrade.
Business is a battlefield.
President Xin,
I
want to discuss something with you.
Go ahead.
Let's end the Blind Box project here.
Starting today,
all of the company's business
returns to thread-bound books.
Chairman, perhaps you're not fully aware
of the current status of this project.
I don't need to be aware.
This is the group's decision.
Then,
may I know why?
Does a group decision need a reason?
Chairman,
when this project first started,
I promised everyone the world.
If we suddenly halt it now,
I need to give everyone an explanation.
Otherwise,
I won't be able to do my job going forward.
No one will believe anything I say.
President Xin,
you're pressuring me here.
I'm not pressuring you.
I just want your trust.
I've been giving this project my all.
I'm doing this for your own good.
Why don't you understand?
The company's returns must exceed 50%.
That was your own promise, wasn't it?
You haven't forgotten, have you?
I haven't forgotten.
I can do it.
How will you do it?
Chairman,
right now in the market
we're getting very positive feedback.
We just need a little more time.
I believe...
It's not about you believing.
It's about me believing,
and the market believing.
What's the top principle of management?
Controllable risk, right?
It's not gambling.
Eight million just went down the drain.
And the returns?
I haven't seen any returns.
Chairman
Are you questioning the 8-million expense?
I give you eight million,
and you bring back ten million.
Of course I'd happily put all the money
straight into your own pocket.
So the Chairman is now suspecting me?
I won't hear it.
I'll emphasize just one thing.
Starting today,
Dayazhai will not spend a single cent
on the Blind Box project.
Stop, all of you, stop!
Drop everything you're working on, now!
Old Huang, come here.
What is all this?
Working day and night
just to make this money-losing junk?
It's just a waste of time!
This, this...
Look at what this is!
Isn't the company's loss still a loss?
Let me tell you,
from this point on,
any work related to these lousy Blind Boxes,
stop it all, right now!
As for the next step,
wait for me to assign it in a meeting.
Oh, right.
Hurry up
and bring this quarter's financial reports
to my office.
Immediately.
Boss, has there been a change?
Stop looking at me.
Xuan Yan, let me toast you again.
Let this meal
be our farewell dinner.
Wait, hold on, hold on, hold on.
Don't talk about breaking up yet.
You just said your Vice President Zhang,
representing the Chairman,
shut down the cultural production line.
So the 50% growth
you promised your Chairman
just goes up in smoke?
Next, Vice President Zhang
will fully take over your company.
You'll have no place left in the company.
Everything you said is right.
But right now I have no options.
There's nothing I can do.
Sister Xin seems tough on the outside,
but she's still too kind-hearted.
Otherwise, how would a petty upstart
like Vice President Zhang get his way?
And the Chairman,
did Vice President Zhang brainwash him?
Yuqing, the Chairman faces huge pressure.
The group is preparing for its IPO.
There's no room for any mistakes.
And you're still defending him?
Xin Ran,
it's not that there's nothing you can do.
During our time working together,
you've been doing everything.
Now leave the rest to me.
Not only will we keep the business going,
we'll learn how to fight back.
We have to handle things one at a time.
The most important thing right now
is finding third-party funding for backup.
As long as we have third-party capital
investing in the project,
we're bound to win this fight.
The promises you made your Chairman
can all be fulfilled.
Do you know what you should do right now?
Go tell your Chairman
that stopping now
means early investments go down the drain.
And now
that the funding is in place,
even if we lose,
he won't suffer any loss.
I know you want to help me.
But Xuan Yan, do you realize
we'll need two to three million more?
Where will you find that kind of money?
Don't you worry about that.
I have my own piggy bank.
Piggy bank?
Out with it.
What kind of trap
are you setting for me this time?
Tricking you into getting rich.
You say that every time.
I'm sick and tired of it.
Try something new.
I was thinking
of cutting you in on some money.
Guess I'll just
work with President Xin on my own.
Just give me the gist.
Forget it.
It's all just my scheming.
You lay your traps,
whether I fall in is up to me.
Aren't you being tacky?
Toying with me, huh?
Fine. Xuan Yan.
Comrade Xiao Min,
I take this conversation very seriously.
Please sit down and hear me out.
Go ahead.
Actually, there's no need for you to rush.
In your current state,
even if things develop with President Xin,
it'll only ever be friendship.
Awkwardly calling each other bro and sis,
it will never be the sweet romance
you've been longing for.
You know why?
Why?
President Xin isn't into your type at all.
You two are on completely different levels.
You're on the basic level,
content with food on the table,
and you're satisfied.
But President Xin? What's she?
She's on the top tier.
What she pursues
is maximizing her own self-worth.
No, no, no.
You're making my head spin.
Can you just say it plainly?
What do you mean?
Upgrade your own tier.
Get into the culture industry.
Isn't making paper the culture industry?
What does your business license say?
Production and processing, manufacturing.
Does it say "culture" anywhere?
Then how do I go about it?
How? Doing what?
Something that raises your tier,
and also lets you and President Xin
take your relationship
to the next level.
Partner with President Xin in culture.
Two birds, one stone.
President Xin, right now,
is going through a rough patch.
If you lend her a hand right now,
and give her your full support,
what do you call that?
That's a hero saving the damsel.
That's double the impact.
That's Emotional Value maxed out.
I get it, I get it.
This idea of yours is really great.
It's a good thing, a good thing.
But this culture industry,
I really don't know a thing about it.
So tell me,
are the market prospects any good?
You tell me.
It doesn't matter if you understand it.
You've got me, don't you?
Now, tell me right now...
Come in.
President Xin.
Hello, President Xin.
Hello, President Xin. Hello.
I've come to learn from you.
And find some room to grow.
Learn from you, learn from you.
President Xiao, you're too kind.
Please, have a seat.
Sure.
I'll pour you some tea.
No, no, no.
I'm not thirsty. Not thirsty at all.
President Xiao, are you hot?
I'll turn the AC down a bit.
No, no, no. Don't trouble yourself.
I'll just unbutton this.
Honestly speaking,
I usually dress pretty casually.
But today, just to meet you,
that's why I dressed so formally.
Since we're going to be family from now on,
I don't need to be so formal, right?
President Xiao,
the production plan I sent over,
along with the financial statements,
have you looked through them?
You really didn't need to send them.
I have absolute trust in you, President Xin.
Trust is just the basis of cooperation.
Once we have that trust,
our future development
will go much more smoothly.
So I still
hope you'll look closely, President Xiao.
After all, this is no small investment.
It's all well within my means.
You can rest assured about my capability.
As for the second round of funding,
I've decided that once the project reaches
the promotional campaign phase,
I'll follow up promptly.
That'll help avoid any capacity issues.
What are you laughing at?
President Xiao, oh, President Xiao.
You've read the proposal very carefully.
This proposal,
you worked so hard on it, President Xin.
If I didn't read it carefully,
I'd really be letting you down.
Don't worry.
I'll do everything in my power
to secure your returns, President Xiao.
Good.
Wonderful.
So beautiful!
President Xiao.
Shall I have someone show you the workshop?
No, no, no.
Your management skills,
I've long since witnessed them.
I have complete confidence.
On production and sales,
I won't interfere at all.
I'll only be in charge of solving
the money problems.
I'm truly so grateful
for your timely help, President Xiao.
No need to thank me, no need at all.
You have so many books here.
So many books.
Have you read them all?
President Xiao.
Was there something else?
What... what do you mean?
Auntie Xin!
Why did you come in again?
Didn't I tell you to wait outside?
You...
This kid never listens.
Auntie Xin, I just took a look around.
Your place is amazing.
Compared to this, my dad's factory
looks totally shabby.
This kid...
Just got off school,
and kept pestering me,
insisting on coming to see you.
Said she missed you.
I just love Auntie Xin.
Auntie loves you too.
I even dreamed about you at school.
What did you dream about Auntie?
Dad.
Are you
trying to have me play matchmaker for you?
Smart girl.
Truly my daughter.
You're so old,
your face is all wrinkled when you smile,
and yet your skin is so thin.
How could Auntie Xin Ran ever like you?
That's why Dad's asking for your help.
I can help you,
but I have my principles.
Go on.
How much money are you asking for?
A thousand.
Oh, you're too kind-hearted.
That Vice President Zhang of yours,
he's just waiting for his moment,
lying in wait on your path,
ready the instant he sees an opening
to sink his fangs into you like a viper.
Right.
We need to hit him hard,
pull out all his venomous fangs.
Otherwise, endless trouble awaits.
I know what to do.
Our Dayazhai
has a contract with Wu Yuliang in town.
All paper scraps from our production line
all go to him.
Per year,
he pays us 100,000 yuan.
But
I know Vice President Zhang often sneaks
the paper scraps to scrap yards to sell.
And he's made quite a bit.
Mr. Zhang, Mr. Zhang is here.
Mr. Zhang, you're here.
Don't, don't, don't.
Cut the act.
What do you mean?
Two tons? Impossible.
I weighed it properly at the factory.
Three and a half tons.
It's definitely two tons.
When it was weighed,
I took photos. Let me show you.
I don't need to see. I see these.
Who's this?
What are you doing?
Hurry up, get down here now.
Boss,
I'm renovating my house.
I want to buy some scrap cardboard.
I've packed them all. Not selling.
Boss,
I'll pay you a little extra.
Do me a favor.
I need them urgently.
Okay, then wait a moment.
Okay, okay.
Let me tell you, Old Seven,
don't try any tricks with me.
Otherwise, we won't work together anymore.
Mr. Zhang, calm down, calm down.
I'll count it as three tons then.
No more haggling.
Fine.
All right.
Just transfer the money to me quickly.
Okay.
Mr. Zhang, take it easy.
Drive safe, Mr. Zhang.
How many did you want just now?
Weren't you asking for cardboard?
About the cardboard,
I'll ask my wife tomorrow.
Weren't you in a hurry just now?
She's not in a hurry.
This matter is urgent.
What are you...
What are you doing? Who are you?
Know Wu Yuliang from the scrap company?
Who doesn't know Mr. Wu?
He's the top boss in our industry.
I'm Mr. Wu's assistant.
Let's have a chat.
You asked for it.
Let's handle this as it should be handled.
You can't guard against a thief within.
I pay my lease fees on time every year,
and you steal from me and sell it off?
You want everyone to find out, huh?
I've got the video right here!
I'll call the cops right now to arrest you!
I'm sorry!
Can't we talk this out?
Talk, my ass!
Watch yourself when working for me!
Enough, stop hitting him!
Stop it!
Come on, get back to what you were doing.
Watching a show, huh?
Enough!
President Wu, stop!
President Wu!
If someone at Dayazhai messed up,
we can settle it properly.
Lose the fight, but keep your dignity.
You're beating and cursing him on my turf.
That's hardly appropriate.
I'm not making a scene.
I just ask President Xin for justice.
Alright. Yuqing,
please take President Wu and his men
to the reception room for some tea.
This way, please.
Right this way.
If you don't give me an answer today,
I won't let him off.
Alright,
get up.
Stop embarrassing yourself.
Let's talk inside.
Xin, Xin, Xin...
Please, help me!
I was such a jerk before.
In front of the Chairman,
I even ratted on you.
I went against you at every turn.
I swear I'll never do it again, okay?
You...
Let go.
Please help me, help me!
I'll be at your beck and call from now on.
Please save me, save me!
Don't talk about it out here.
Let's go inside.
You're in serious trouble now.
If the Chairman finds out about this,
you won't be able to stay at Dayazhai.
Getting fired isn't even the main problem.
Wu Yuliang has you cornered now.
If he really presses charges,
Yuqing.
Did you look it up?
Yes, I did.
According to the Criminal Law,
Article 264,
theft of public or private property
involving 30,000 to under 100,000 yuan
carries a sentence of three to ten years,
plus a fine.
The scrapyard owner confessed
Vice President Zhang sold to him 3 times.
What's the total amount?
I'd rather not say.
President Xin,
I can't go to prison.
I've got elderly parents and young kids.
I'm begging you, please help me.
I'll wait on you hand and foot from now on.
I'll burn the first incense for you.
I'm not dead yet.
Stop crying.
Yuqing.
Go invite President Wu in.
Okay.
President Wu,
please have a seat.
So how do we handle this?
Do you pay compensation,
or do I call the police?
Sit down and let's talk.
Have some tea first.
President Wu,
about this matter,
I've got a clear picture now.
Strictly speaking,
it's between you and Vice President Zhang.
It has nothing to do with Dayazhai.
I could get involved,
or I could stay out of it.
But,
considering all the years you've
worked with our company,
I can put myself in your shoes
and offer you two pieces of advice.
Not sure if you'll hear me out.
Go ahead.
You can press charges
and send him to prison.
But there's one thing
I need to remind you of.
Vice President Zhang
is someone our Chairman deeply trusts.
If you push this too far
and get him locked up,
then your business with Dayazhai
comes to an end.
I can drop the charges,
but he still has to pay up, right?
That's exactly my second point.
President Wu,
you and I don't know each other.
I've never had a bite of food from you,
never had a sip of tea from you either.
So there's no personal history between us.
As for you,
you signed with our former GM.
Dayazhai gives you a year's paper scraps
at a package price of 100,000.
You've made a killing already, haven't you?
But now I'm Dayazhai's general manager.
President Wu.
Let me be honest with you.
Our contract expires this year.
I don't want to renew it with you.
I did a rough calculation.
It's about 500,000 to 600,000 a year.
So why on earth
should I let you earn that money?
I can use my company's own connections.
President Xin.
I've heard, you know,
that this guy doesn't treat you well.
Yet here you are helping him.
For your sake,
even if we don't cooperate,
I'll still sue him and put him away.
President Wu.
Whether he treats me well
is an internal matter of our company.
It's none of your business.
And if you really want to sue him,
you might not even succeed.
Those papers he hauled to the scrapyard,
if I say they're paper scraps,
then they're paper scraps.
If I say they're finished paper,
then they're finished paper.
How they're classified
is up to me.
So now,
I'm telling you,
those are our company's finished paper.
This matter has nothing to do with you.
If you put it that way,
I have nothing more to say.
But
you can't just let me swallow this loss.
President Wu, didn't I just say?
I originally didn't want to work with you.
But since you're giving me face today,
I'll leave you a way to make money.
The contract,
we'll keep signing it.
Fine.
Since President Xin is being so generous,
I won't hold it against him.
Next time,
I'll bring you some tea.
Kid, you'd better learn from this.
Thank President Xin properly.
President Xin.
I'll be off now.
Take care, President Wu.
President Xin.
Thank you.
Your great kindness,
I'll never forget it.
What are you doing?
From now on, you're my godmother.
Let go.
Never seen Vice President Zhang so tame.
Reporting in morning and night,
treating your every word as gospel.
But I think you're still too merciful.
Someone like Vice President Zhang
should be dealt with harshly.
Sentence him to a few years.
After all, he has a family to support.
Give people a break when you can.
If I get rid of Vice President Zhang,
the group will just send someone else,
President Li, President Tang.
I'd still have to keep fighting them.
If all my energy goes into scheming,
how can Dayazhai keep developing?
You've got a point.
Keeping the status quo is fine too.
Family of Su Min,
take the slip and pay the fee.
Taozi.
You're up, right?
Yeah, well...
I'm at the hospital picking up...
picking up my mom to check out.
So, um...
Could you lend me some money?
I'll pay you back later.
Thanks, Taozi.
Yiran.
Did you finish the discharge paperwork?
There's so much stuff you need to pack up.
These clothes are so uncomfortable.
I need to change right away.
Auntie.
Mom and I are on our way.
Yeah, she just got discharged.
But she's recovering pretty well.
Okay, see you in a bit.
Thanks, Auntie.
What do you mean?
We're not going home?
Where are we going?
We'll stay at Auntie's for a couple days.
Look at your uncle-in-law, what a half-wit.
I can't stand looking at his face.
I'm not going.
If you don't like him, just ignore him.
Besides, he plays cards every day.
He barely comes home anyway.
Mom, let me be honest with you.
I don't have much money right now.
I can't afford to hire a caregiver for you.
What I earn isn't even as much as...
I don't even earn as much as a caregiver.
You know?
Did I ask you to hire a caregiver?
I already said I can manage.
I'm perfectly fine at home by myself.
I can take care of myself.
Driver, pull over.
I'm not going.
Mom, what are you doing?
Pull over! I said pull over!
Mom, can't you put yourself in my shoes?
Think about me for once.
Put myself in your shoes?
It'd be best if you got transferred back.
Mom, are you being reasonable at all?
Driver.
Turn around.
To Taohua Town.
Got it.
Yiran.
How's it going?
Did you bring Auntie back?
Just got here.
So where are you having her stay?
I don't know yet.
I was thinking of getting Mom food first,
then finding her a place to stay.
Why go through all that trouble?
She can stay in our dorm.
I'll make room for Auntie.
No need, that's too much trouble.
If Auntie stays here,
I can just go stay at my bestie's place.
Go get some food for Auntie.
I'll head to the dorm to check on her.
Thank you, Taozi.
You can watch it now.
But, Uncle,
I have to warn you upfront.
Once you start binging these mini-dramas,
you just can't stop.
I don't have time to watch during the day.
I'll just watch a bit at night.
This doesn't cost money, right?
Is there money on your phone?
Oh, right.
Your mom manages all my money.
That time... how do I...
Dad.
That little album of Qianlong Jade Paper,
you made it for me, didn't you?
What nonsense are you on about?
I said,
that little album of Qianlong Jade Paper,
you made it for me, right?
Can't hear you. I'm working.
I know you're working, so I'm asking.
What Qianlong Jade Paper?
Why are you meddling in everything?
Sounds pretty profitable.
Get back to work.
You can't leave me out of this.
You little rascal.
I'm just asking.
Up ahead there.
Director Hao.
That's our Secretary Peng.
Secretary Peng.
This is Yiran's mother.
She's here to see you.
Oh, Yiran's mother.
Hello, hello, hello.
Have you eaten yet?
Come on, come on.
Grab a bite at the canteen.
No, no, no.
I won't eat.
I just want a quick word alone with you.
Okay.
Let's talk in the office.
No, no.
No need to go to the office.
Just a couple of words.
I'll be quick.
Alright, alright.
What is it? Go ahead.
It's like this.
Our Yiran, she's still young.
She didn't really discuss it with me,
and just took the exam to come here.
No, no.
I'm not saying Taohua Town isn't good.
That's not what I mean.
The main thing is,
it's just too far from our home.
Her dad has passed away,
and my health hasn't been great lately.
I...
Yiran's mother,
just tell me directly what you want.
Secretary Peng, you have kids, right?
Yes, I do.
See?
That's great, then.
Who wants their kid in the countryside?
And she's just a young girl.
When she gets married and has kids someday,
it'll be so inconvenient.
Kids can't see that far ahead.
As mothers,
we have to plan for their future.
Don't you agree?
Yiran's mother,
you've said so much,
but what exactly do you want me to do?
Secretary Peng,
you're Ranran's boss.
Please, do us a favor.
Transfer her to the county.
Even a temporary assignment would do.
As long as you can make this happen,
we'll be forever grateful to you.
Yiran's mother,
actually,
many cadres in our town are young people,
and many aren't from around here.
Every family has its own difficulties.
You just asked me earlier,
I'm a mother too, right?
We both have children.
But what I want to tell you is,
we mothers
should respect our kids' choices, right?