This smell is off.
Here.
Why is it sticky?
There's glue in it.
Clearly someone tampered
with this spray bottle and added glue.
Could you do me a favor?
Zhang Du, go with him to the committee.
Report this situation.
Hurry up.
Okay.
Thank you.
What time at night did this happen?
At 2:28 last night.
Rewind it and play it again.
He's spraying glue.
With glue, the paper can't be peeled off.
The lights in the factory were all off.
The image quality is no good.
You can't tell who this is.
Stop.
Play.
Play it again.
If we can't keep the 100-sheet yield,
we'll lose our spot in the competition.
There's no time. Stop spraying.
It's too dry. Can it be peeled off?
Let me do it. Let me.
Only half an hour left.
This way you'll ruin all the paper.
If you don't get on with it,
how long will the drying take?
Better to ruin some than just wait.
Get out of my way.
Slow, slow down. Let me see.
Do it in reverse.
Good.
Drying the paper.
A traditional craft passed down by our ancestors.
It requires eighteen brush strokes.
Namely, the corner-hang,
support-dry, center-pull, half-brush, edge-break,
the figure-eight, window-close, and so on.
There's a folk saying:
"to have a couple of brushes,"
which originates from paper-drying workers
mastering the force of the brush.
Got it.
Good.
Seal the edge.
We've got a shot.
You really should learn from Master Xuan.
Do things steadily.
Not like you.
Panicking at the slightest thing.
I get it.
What are you standing there for?
Hurry up and dry the paper!
There's no time left.
The Xuan family's quality is secured!
We're going to win for sure.
A sure win.
Now we enter
the weighing round.
Target weight: six jin five liang per stack.
The closest to the set weight
wins.
Now,
the weighing begins.
Why include a weighing round?
Comparing scooping speed
and drying yield rate
isn't the main point.
Matching the set weight
is what truly shows a master's skill.
Scooping one hundred sheets,
all hundred weighing the same.
Six and a half jin means exactly that.
Without a master's skill,
how could anyone do it?
The Duan family of Yunling:
six jin six liang.
Six jin four point six liang.
Now it's the Jiang family's turn.
Six jin, five liang, two qian.
On the competition floor,
to deliver such a result —
Jiang Yousan,
truly remarkable.
Xuan Yongnian of the Xuan family:
six jin, five liang.
Exact to the last bit.
Master Xuan, well done!
I object.
This isn't fair.
One hundred sheets totaling six jin five liang
doesn't prove
Xuan Yongnian's sheets are all exactly equal.
This one ten grams,
that one fifteen grams —
just a blind cat stumbling on a dead mouse.
Hardly convincing.
The rules were set in advance.
You can't kick up a fuss like this.
Only weighing each sheet counts.
One hundred sheets at six and a half jin
means each sheet is 32.5 grams.
Right.
Weigh Xuan Yongnian's sheets
and see how many of them
come out to 32.5 grams.
I agree to single-sheet weighing.
32.5 grams.
Excellent!
Next is the experts' brush-test round.
Everyone, quiet please.
Please be seated.
After the competition and the yield-rate check,
the total scores are in.
I now announce
the top three scorers.
Jiang family: paper-scooping speed, five points.
Yield rate, four points.
Brush test, four points.
Weight accuracy, four points.
Total: seventeen points.
Great, great, great!
Yes!
However,
because the Jiang family's contestant,
Jiang Erhu, deliberately cheated
and seriously compromised the results,
the judges have unanimously decided
to disqualify their score.
Yes! Yes! Yes!
I know exactly who he is.
Jiang Erhu.
We grew up together since childhood.
The way he walks,
and his habit of using his left hand,
I know them all too well.
Chairman Xiao,
with something this outrageous happening,
surely the Xuan Paper Association has a stance?
We will deal with this strictly.
Good.
You're a disgrace!
Quiet, quiet.
Please sit.
Everyone, settle down.
Xuan Family Paper Mill,
it's our turn.
Scooping speed, three points.
Brush test, five points.
Weight accuracy, five points.
Yield rate, two points.
Total: fifteen points.
The judges unanimously agreed
that the quality of Xuan Yongnian's paper,
both in craftsmanship and brush performance,
ranks as the very best.
However,
on scooping speed and yield rate,
he lost too many points.
So regrettably,
he must settle for second place.
That's plenty good.
Chairman Xiao's Huihuang Paper Co.:
Scooping speed, four points.
Yield rate, five points.
Brush test, three points.
Weight accuracy, four points.
Total: sixteen points.
Therefore, I now declare
our final champion,
our Paper King is...
Xiao Min's Huihuang Paper Co.!
Yes! Yes! Yes!
Huihuang! Huihuang! Huihuang!
Congratulations, congratulations.
Great, great, great.
Paper King!
Fantastic!
Well-deserved indeed!
Right.
Take it slow.
Slow, slow, slow.
Okay, okay, okay.
Okay.
Good.
Easy, easy, easy.
Slowly, slowly.
Easy now.
Uncle Xuan.
I'm truly sorry about this.
But the association,
it has its own rules.
There's nothing we can do.
Take him away.
Easy, easy.
Go.
Come on, come on
Easy, easy, easy
Chairman Xiao
Congratulations, Chairman Xiao
Chairman
Congratulations, congratulations
Congratulations, Chairman Xiao
Who told you to go take the plaque?
Who told you to take it?
What's going on here?
We did this by the association's rules
Exactly
Do you realize that by doing this,
you're slapping my master in the face?
And slapping me even harder!
Send the plaque back
Send it back
We can't send it back
How could we possibly send it back?
Send it back
If you really send it back now,
that would really slap your master's face
Exactly
No way we can send it back now
So you won't send it back, huh?
Don't, don't, don't
Send it or not? Send it or not?
You want it? I want it!
You actually want it?
I'll haul it away in a bit, okay?
You're a well-deserved Paper King too
The Xuan family can't be Paper King every year
You gotta leave some scraps for the rest of us
Exactly
My master earned it with real skill
And you?
I've got real skill too!
Without my little bit of skill,
could you even be Paper King?
Screw you
Watch your mouth
Do you have any idea, Jiang Erhu,
how much loss you caused my master?
How are we supposed to cover the hole?
You treat him as your master,
but does he treat you as his disciple?
Hold your tongue, Erhu
Starting today,
Don't, don't, don't
I'll expel you from the association today, believe it?
You expel me?
这协会是我家
Having you in it is a disgrace
I'm telling you,
today,
the association must expel you
Erhu
You don't care about family at all!
Stop talking
We compiled data from all online platforms
about the Paper King Competition,
including related news and short videos.
Total views exceeded 100 million.
For our Taohua Town's
Xuan paper industry and culture,
it brought a huge wave of traffic
and created excellent positive publicity.
For this reason,
the county's top leaders called
to give this Paper King Competition
strong affirmation and high praise.
Now, please welcome Secretary Peng to speak.
Comrades,
after the negative impact occurred this time,
our town's leadership team
responded swiftly.
Think about it, from deciding to hold the contest
to its successful conclusion,
we only took half a month.
Half a month!
About a hundred people participated, right?
Yes.
Transport, food and lodging for so many,
safety, publicity, every little detail,
our Lin Yiran and her teammates
did a great job.
And judging from the results,
they pulled it off beautifully.
Director Liao,
if this had been in the past,
it wouldn't have been likely, right?
Secretary Peng,
fellow leaders,
the Jiang Erhu cheating incident
that happened at this Paper King Competition
is my responsibility.
I offer my self-criticism before this meeting.
That's a fairly proper attitude.
Lin Yiran, sit down.
Sit down.
Of course,
throughout the entire competition process,
some problems did indeed arise.
I think in this matter,
I also bear responsibility.
But what I want to tell everyone today,
some comrades may not yet know:
Before the Paper King Competition began,
this young woman Lin Yiran
made a solemn pledge to me.
I'm deeply moved.
I was thinking,
if every one of our officials
could shoulder this kind of responsibility,
what work could we possibly fail to do well?
Good.
You know what,
I should find time to visit the Xuan family.
Master Xuan got played by Erhu.
He didn't win the championship.
I'm partly to blame too.
Xiao Lin.
Hey, Xiao Lin.
Wait, I mean Yiran.
Yiran.
I remember you wrote something on
the "Reporting System for Above-Scale Enterprises,"
that report, right?
Yes, I did.
I sent it to you,
and also to Director Ge.
Right, right, no worries.
When you have time, send me the digital copy.
If it's inconvenient, though—
No, no, no.
It's fine, totally fine.
I'll send it to you shortly.
Alright, alright.
Thanks for the trouble then.
One more thing.
The dynamic monitoring of poverty relapse,
and the survey of key individuals,
coordinate well with the village officials.
Get on it quickly.
The home visits for key individuals,
not a single household can be missed.
Especially the ones flagged
by warnings from higher authorities.
Not only must visits be thorough,
but we also need concrete plans.
That way we can promptly
report back to our superiors, right?
Okay.
Alright, get back to work then.
I'll head off now.
Bye, bye, bye.
Goodbye, Mayor.
Wait
Is Deputy Mayor Luo really this polite?
First "Xiao Lin," then "Yiran."
Is there a difference?
He's polite to you
because he's afraid you'll snap at him.
You snap at everyone, top to bottom.
Who wouldn't be afraid?
The leaders are even more scared.
Terrified one word might set you off,
and you'd embarrass them in public.
Is that really how people see me?
And quite vividly, too.
You, right now,
among all the officials in town,
have a widely known nickname.
"Snappy Lin."
Me?
Oh my god.
Uncle Xuan.
Here, try this.
It's a back massager I bought for you.
Here.
What?
What is it?
It's, it's moving around like that.
This thing's way too fancy.
Xiao Lin, we can't accept this.
You must. I bought it myself.
If you don't accept it,
I'll really feel hurt.
Uncle Xuan, your craftsmanship is so good,
but you didn't win Paper King.
That was a failure on my part.
It's my responsibility.
Don't ever think that way.
Come, come, come.
Sit down, sit down.
Don't take it to heart.
The way things are done these days,
plenty of folks don't play by the rules.
They've got their own little schemes,
pulling tricks here and there.
That's all pretty common.
It's got nothing to do with you.
Don't gossip about others.
Am I wrong, though?
A few years back, the association met
saying we'd resist unfair competition,
standardize paper quality and prices.
And what happened?
Only our family actually did it.
Others either cut corners,
or sold at low prices,
and just like that, we lost our customers.
This guy in our family,
all he knows is work, work, work,
never bothers to look at the road ahead.
The Xuan family has come this far,
thirty-five generations,
we've walked over a thousand years.
Why would I need to look at the road?
Look too much, overthink it,
and your steps will only stumble.
That's exactly what I mean.
You're hanging yourself on one tree,
and you still think you're so capable.
Uncle Xuan,
I feel your mindset
is just like fine Xuan paper,
soft yet resilient, pure white as jade.
Why not say he's stubborn and pig-headed?
Xiao Lin,
let me show you some prime Xuan paper.
Are you interested?
That'd be wonderful!
Careful, it's dark in here.
You go slow too, Uncle Xuan.
After you.
This was used for ancient imperial exams.
This is for ministers' memorials to the throne.
And also,
the emperor used this paper
to make imperial decrees.
All of these
were made with our Xuan family's Xuan paper.
So your paper was tribute paper, then.
You could put it that way.
Since our Xuan family's first ancestor,
we've sent tribute paper to the court.
Later, Beijing's Songhe Zhai
bought paper from our Xuan family,
used it for memorials and exam papers,
and presented them to the court.
I know Beijing's Songhe Zhai.
A century-old brand, very famous.
Indeed, indeed.
Take a look.
This kind of Xuan paper—
Republic-era presidential appointment letters,
and several of his presidential orders,
were all made with this Xuan paper.
These are treasures that have witnessed history.
As for these three types,
they're our Mianliao, Jingpi, and Tejingpi.
You masters can try them out first.
See how they feel.
If you find they're not suitable,
we can also do custom orders.
Raw Xuan, processed Xuan,
single-layer, double-layer—we make them all.
Masters,
about our family's paper—
Mianliao suits calligraphy and fine-brush painting.
Jingpi and Tejingpi suit freehand landscapes.
They're all masters here.
Lecturing them on basics is just embarrassing.
Mr. Xiao.
Go ahead and try it first.
Your Jingpi and Tejingpi,
what's the wholesale price?
Where did you buy from before?
The Xuan family.
Then why come to me now?
To be honest with you,
we've always sold high-end goods,
collector-grade paper.
Give us a better price,
and we'll do business with you.
I'll be honest with you too.
My paper isn't collector-grade.
A big paper mill boss like you,
talking like an outsider.
Good paper gets pricier with age.
Who actually paints on collector paper?
Mr. Xiao,
you're the Paper King now.
Honestly speaking,
the Xuan family's paper
is way too expensive.
I'm buying your Paper King reputation.
It'll move well in the market.
Exactly.
Mutual benefit.
Everyone makes money. Isn't that great?
Yes, yes, yes.
Mutual benefit
is definitely a good thing.
Who doesn't want to earn more these days?
But my Paper King title is fake.
In our Taohua Town,
only the Xuan family
sells collector-grade paper.
We have to do business with integrity.
Right?
Gentlemen,
how was the test?
These two buyers
used to buy paper from my master, the Xuans.
Today they came specifically to me.
Please give your honest opinions, gentlemen,
on how my paper is.
This Jingpi of yours,
the ink spread doesn't feel smooth enough.
Its ink absorption
seems a bit lacking.
I'm certain
the sandalwood bark content
definitely doesn't exceed 60 percent.
What's my philosophy on choosing paper?
Choose by spirit, not by form.
What do you mean?
Many calligraphers and painters say,
"I pick raw, sized, or semi-sized Xuan,
whatever suits me, what I can master."
I think that view is wrong.
If you've mastered it,
how can the paper's spirit emerge?
I believe it's not mastery,
it's interaction.
Interaction is best.
Didn't you just say "spirit, not form"?
Sorry, sorry.
I forgot to introduce him.
Allow me to formally introduce
Director Liao Shanming.
He is our Taohua Town's
renowned Xuan paper theory expert.
His research on Xuan paper theory
runs very deep.
Don't rush, everyone.
Let me explain slowly.
Interaction ties right into choosing by spirit.
For example,
Qi Baishi
focused on precise brushstroke expression,
while Huang Zhou needed
Jingpi and Tejingpi to support
his sweeping creative energy.
The brush follows the heart,
the heart follows the ink,
and how the ink moves depends on the paper.
Thank you.
What?
Where's my bag?
What bag?
The bag and the water bottle!
Sir!
Director Liao! Director Liao!
We can't catch up.
This...
I... I have a scooter.
I have a scooter, I have one!
Okay, let's go!
I have a scooter.
Hurry!
Wait, can we even catch up?
We have to try anyway.
This whole thing just shows
you don't take your boss seriously at all.
Sorry. If it's lost, I'll pay for it.
This isn't about paying me back.
It's about your attitude.
With an attitude like yours,
it's clear you have no "drive."
What drive?
The drive to advance.
Well, I don't care about that drive.
What did you say?
I just do my job well, that's enough.
Whether I advance or not, I don't care.
What do you mean you don't care?
Don't follow Taozi's example, I'm telling you.
You don't have her advantages.
Fine. Thank you for the lecture, boss.
Tell me the truth.
Did you lose my bag
on purpose?
No, how could you say that?
I didn't.
Don't play games with me.
I'm telling you,
I can see right through everything.
I really didn't.
Yeah, right.
Excuse me, comrade.
E-scooters aren't allowed to carry
adults over sixteen years old.
Didn't you know that?
And you're not wearing a helmet.
You have to accept the penalty.
Sir!
This is the guy, right?
Yes, yes, yes!
I... let me, let me!
Sir.
This is your bottle, right?
Yes.
The bag.
Thank you so much, sir!
No need, no need.
It's what anyone would do.
Thank you, sir! Thank you, sir!
Thank you so much, sir!
It's nothing, really.
It's fine, it's fine.
Let me treat you to a meal.
No, no, no need.
I'm off.
Thank you, sir!
Look at his sense of duty.
That Manager Hu who used to order paper from us
ran off to order from old Ren's place.
Don't talk nonsense.
Who's talking nonsense?
I saw it with my own eyes!
This time, Xiao Yu really isn't making it up.
At this Paper King Contest,
over thirty buyers showed up.
Seven or eight of them were familiar faces.
They all used to order from the Xuan family.
After we lost the contest,
not a single one showed up.
These people are such opportunists.
Just shut up already.
Enough of your nonsense.
Go haul your paperboards.
I'm just worried, that's all.
I'm just saying.
We've got wages this month,
but next month is anyone's guess.
The Calligraphy Association's payment still hasn't come in.
Have you checked?
Of course I checked.
I checked yesterday,
and I checked again today.
Nothing's come in.
Which account did you check?
How many accounts do we even have?
Just this one.
I checked the shipping too.
They received the goods a week ago.
They wouldn't stiff us, would they?
Old Sun's worked with us for decades.
He shouldn't pull something like that.
Let's wait a bit longer.
Maybe it'll come in tonight.
This morning,
the workers were already talking about wages.
They all know payday is today.
They're waiting.
Hard at work.
Brother Xuan Yi.
Xuan Yi.
Uncle Ye.
Uncle.
What are you doing, Zhang Du?
You don't need a whole ritual just to scoop paper.
Paper-scooping is paid by the piece.
If Uncle Ye's family all worked like you,
they'd have starved long ago.
Scooping paper and scooping good paper are two different things.
Xiao Man, did you hear that?
You'd better help the master scoop it properly.
It's got to be good paper.
He thinks I'm too dim-witted,
beyond hope of mastering this.
You're just not devoted enough. Look at him.
Brother Yi.
We're getting paid today, right?
Beanpole, what are you on about?
The exact time isn't clear yet,
but my mom was already
sorting through pay slips last night.
I'd say within a day or two.
Got it.
Is this guy nuts?
Who's that?
Hey, hey!
What are you doing?
Stop, stop!
What's going on?
What are you people doing?
You think this is your house?
Honking the horn like crazy.
Returning the goods.
Returning what goods?
A return is a return.
Meaning all the goods you shipped
have been sent back, untouched.
Get it now?
This time, wages really can't be paid.
Old Xuan.
You've heard already, right?
Heard what?
They just refuse it, just like that.
We put in so much cost.
A whole crew worked for a month.
Where's the sense in that?
Don't get worked up.
They bought my paper
for investment and collection.
Now that the Paper King title is gone,
the investment and collection value
has taken a hit.
Even if you're not the Paper King,
you're still an intangible heritage inheritor.
Right?
You lose one competition,
and they bail on the order?
We've already paid the costs.
They still owe us the money.
Forget it.
You can lead an ox to water,
but you can't force its head down.
That's just how it is.
When they want paper, they sweet-talk you.
When they don't want it,
they sweet-talk you all the same.
These people...
Once they get the goods,
they stop paying.
Try chasing them for money,
and they act like we owe them.
So now you finally figured it out?
Back then, I told them
they had to pay a deposit.
And you said, "No need, no need, no need."
"It's fine."
Well, look at us now.
The money's not coming in,
wages can't be paid.
You figure it out yourself.
The orders are still coming in, aren't they?
They haven't stopped, right?
I'm telling you, you're really something.
You only think about the income,
not the expenses.
Let me do the math for you.
Our workers,
they earn the highest wages in town, right?
The social security and insurance we provide,
isn't that also the highest standard?
Other factories,
when business is slow,
they just lay the workers off.
But us, oh no,
slow season, busy season,
we keep paying the workers.
And the drying yard,
don't we have to manage all that too?
Making the bleached bark ourselves,
how high is that cost?
You've never done the math on any of this.
You're selling tofu at the price of meat.
Being generous when you're broke,
that's exactly the kind of person you are.
Come in.
Master, Madam.
Uncle Lao Cheng, the straw maker, is here.
I told him you were sick,
but he said he came just to see you.
This... this is...
He came to ask for money.
Here's the thing.
My second daughter, Shanqin,
she's busy with work in the provincial capital.
She blames us for not helping raise her child.
Every single time she comes back,
she gets upset every time.
Our eldest daughter's child,
the two of us raised her.
But the second one,
we didn't help take care of hers,
so she's been holding a grudge.
So the two of us have been thinking,
maybe we should just move to the city.
But if we do that,
next year, the bleached straw,
we won't be able to make it anymore.
After all these decades of friendship,
I... these words, I...
I really don't know how to say it.
Xiumei
Go check
how much we've got left in the account
Forget everything else for now
Scrape together what we owe Lao Cheng first
Lao Xuan, this...
Just go
This is so embarrassing
It's fine
Sister Xu
Busy, huh?
Look at this pork
How much is the pork today?
Today, eighteen a jin
The price keeps going up day by day
Give me a discount
Cheaper, I'm a regular
Sixteen
I'll take all three chunks for sixteen
Deal
Okay, okay
Go weigh it
Alright, alright
Mom
Haggling over a dime or a buck
is it really worth the fuss?
They have it tough too
I have it tough myself
Save where you can
How much per jin for tomatoes?
Eighty cents
Eighty cents?
What's going on here?
Tomatoes, eighty cents
Hold on
What, do we have to fight for these?
Come over here, quick
Come on, bag them up, hurry
This stall is cheaper
My hands are full, Mom
Put your stuff on the ground
Hurry, grab a couple more bags
Quick, his is cheaper
We don't really need this many
Big family, big appetite
Don't pick the ones that are too...
Don't shove, don't shove
Don't pick the soft ones
Get the slightly firmer ones
Bag them up
Bagging, bagging, I'm on it
Oh my goodness
Buying this much, we can't finish it, it's a waste
Not a waste
We've got lots of mouths to feed
Don't worry
Mom, you really know how to pinch a penny
If I don't, who will?
Anyone who holds out their hand,
your dad just hands it over
So then I have to give too, right?
Come on, come on
If I weren't running this household,
who knows if you'd even have made it this far
Come on, Mom, it's not that bad
What do you mean it's not that bad?
From the daily groceries
to the factory's books
which part don't I have to worry about?
Rely on your dad?
Come on, come on
If there's no money to pay wages,
no money to keep things running,
your dad comes running to me
Rely on him?
Mom
Our paper scooping and drying
is all piece-rate work
Just scoop less
and you save on everything
Go tell your dad that
Fish, half price!
Dad.
Mom's got dinner ready.
Come down and eat.
Mom said,
we can't cover this month's wages.
She's at her wit's end,
so she sent me over
to talk it over with you.
Do you have any good ideas?
Well, since you're asking, I'll say it.
It's not just my opinion,
it's how business works.
We're running a business, not a charity.
Right?
If we can't pay the wages,
we shut down one vat.
And if that doesn't work,
we just halt operations for a while.
Look,
we've still got this much paper in stock.
Let's find a way to sell off the inventory first.
What business in trouble
doesn't cut its losses to survive?
The business has to survive first,
then the workers can put food on the table.
That's how you secure their jobs.
These are the basic rules of survival.
Our Xuan family ancestors
laid down a rule like this:
We can't just make money when times are good,
then when next year turns bad,
ignore whether the workers live or die
and just kick them out.
That breaks people's hearts.
Later, if you want them back,
it'll be extremely hard.