THIS DRAMA IS CREATED
FOR ENTERTAINMENT PURPOSES
ALL CHARACTERS, SETTINGS
AND EVENTS ARE ENTIRELY FICTITIOUS
THERE IS NO INTENT TO REFERENCE
ANY REAL INDIVIDUALS OR ENTITIES
NOR TO PROMOTE INAPPROPRIATE BEHAVIOR
OR UNDERMINE MORAL STANDARDS
Even when the killer
is standing right in front of you,
the police still can't do a damn thing.
Shoot her, Bank.
Hey, wait.
We don't know where Kitti is hiding.
Captain.
When are you going to arrest me?
You want to arrest me?
There he is!
- Hey, Phleng.
- Phleng!
Ah!
Kitti!
Huh? Kitti.
Kitti.
Kitti!
Naree!
What happened?!
Aunt Nan, what happened to Mom?!
Tell me!
- Panter, get her out of here.
- What's wrong with my mom?!
What happened to her?!
Aunt Nan, what happened to her?!
Kram, take Sara and run.
Go.
Captain!
- Let's hide.
- Bank!
SHE'S CRAZY
It was self-defense.
You saw I was injured, right?
Ugh!
Naree, please surrender.
Stop.
Drop the gun.
Drop it!
- Phleng, come here!
- Hey!
Ma'am, watch out.
- Phleng, get Sara out of here!
- Go now.
Where are you running to?!
Let go!
Go!
Hurry up.
- Come on.
- Sara, hurry.
Stop!
Phleng!
Sara, go! Run!
Sara.
ARE THEY GOING TO SURVIVE?
I CAN'T WATCH IT ANYMORE
SHE'S CRAZY
Where are you going?
HIT HER MORE
Phleng, get up.
Let's go.
HIT HER AGAIN
SHE GOT UP
KILL HER
WHY IS SHE SO TOUGH?
SHE'S CRAZY
CRAZY
SHE'S SCARY
KILL HER
SHE'S SO DAMN CRAZY
SHE'S A PSYCHOPATH
Kamon.
CRAZY
Phleng.
SHE'S CRAZY
Where are you?
CRAZY PSYCHOPATH
Let's guess, you all.
SHE'S A PSYCHOPATH
CRAZY WOMAN
Phleng IS PRETTY, DON'T DIE
MURDERER
Look, Kamon.
The viewers are reacting
with so much anger.
Come out.
PSYCHOPATH
CRAZY
Careful. This madwoman
might be waiting outside your house.
Stop!
Clear.
Spread out and search for Sara. Now!
- Yes, sir. Let's go.
- That way, Officer.
Are you okay?
Let's go, Sara.
You!
Do it.
Shoot her, Sara.
Do it. Shoot me.
Shoot.
Shoot!
- It's from upstairs.
- Let's go.
Kulnaree, you crazy bitch!
Sara, shoot her again!
SHE'LL DIE FOR SURE
Ugh!
You wanna fight?!
Phleng!
LIVE
Let go of her!
NOW SHE'LL DIE
DIE
Is Mom okay?
Phleng.
Stay awake.
Look at me.
Do you hear me?
Do you hear me, Phleng?
Sara. Phleng.
Sara.
Hold on, Phleng.
One suspect has fallen.
Presumed dead.
I was the one…
who pushed her.
Phleng.
Hello? Someone's severely injured.
Please send an ambulance now.
Keep on living
and see this all through with me.
They'll all pay.
You hear me?
I've seen it.
I saw you seek justice…
with your own hands.
No, you have to see this through.
I'm so tired…
No, Phleng! No, don't.
No. Don't go, Phleng.
- Let me rest.
- No, you can't.
No, Phleng.
Phleng, wake up!
Phleng! Wake up!
Phleng!
Phleng, wake up!
Phleng, no!
Phleng, no! Wake up!
Phleng! Wake up!
From last night's shocking incident
that went viral online,
a female suspect
in a 19-year-old murder case
went on a rampage with a firearm,
hunting down a survivor
and whistleblowers of the case.
They had a severe fight.
The suspect is Mrs. Kulnaree Lerthanakul,
heiress to a well-known
real estate empire.
The incident resulted
in injuries and casualties.
Initial reports confirm
that Mrs. Kulnaree has died.
This is also connected to many
other people involved in the case.
And the case has now
entered court proceedings.
Seoul?
- Seoul's awake. Seoul.
- Seoul.
Seoul, are you okay?
Where is everyone?
Where's Mom?
What happened?
What happened to Mom?
Your mom…
is no longer with us.
Today,
I brought your favorite food, Mom.
I don't know
where you are now,
but don't worry.
We're not fighting anymore.
From now on, I'll take care of her.
The patient has passed the critical stage.
Her body is recovering
faster than we expected.
From what I can tell,
she'll definitely regain consciousness.
Just wait a little longer.
How are you today?
Today, Sara and I
picked out flowers for you.
You hate them, right?
Then just wake up and scold me.
I'm waiting.
It's tomorrow, isn't it?
Are you ready?
Yes.
Don't worry.
The evidence is solid.
How do you feel now that you've succeeded?
A sense of relief…
comes hand in hand with pain.
Not just mine,
but everyone's involved in this.
There's no use sitting here regretting
what we already decided to do.
At best, what we can do
is accept it.
Learn from it.
You can move forward now.
Nin.
Thank you for everything.
Thank you.
Kamon deserves justice!
Save Kamon! Save Kamon!
- Louder, everyone.
- Save Kamon! Save Kamon!
Save Kamon! Save Kamon!
- Right now,
the court is reading the verdict
of a high-profile case
that's been buried for 19 years.
- Today marks an important step
- Save Kamon!
- in restoring dignity to the victims
- and reminding us all that justice
- Save Kamon!
- still exists in Thai society.
- We'll continue following the verdict
- Save Kamon!
- and report it to you
- after the court announces its decision.
- Save Kamon!
Save Kamon!
Criminal case
between the public prosecutor
and Ms. Kamon Tisraksa
as joint plaintiffs
and Mrs. Jira, first defendant,
Mr. Phathi, second defendant,
Mr. Chawadon, third defendant,
Mrs. Woranan, fourth defendant,
and Mr. Chayut, fifth defendant.
After reviewing
all evidence and testimony,
the facts accepted are as follows.
Today on Daily Big Issues,
we're joined by Mr. Sura, attorney at law,
to discuss the trending case
involving the Lerthanakul family.
- Welcome, Mr. Sura.
- Hello.
Let me ask this first.
Now that the verdict is out,
what are the penalties for each defendant?
As we all know,
the main perpetrator, Mrs. Kulnaree,
has passed away.
So, only those who helped
conceal the crime remain.
The evidence
clearly proves that Mrs. Kulnaree
did commit the crime.
Therefore, the remaining defendants
each face different sentences.
Mrs. Jira, though paralyzed,
committed a serious offense
and will be transferred
to the Correctional Hospital.
Mr. Phathi and Mr. Chawadon
also face additional charges.
Mm.
There is child molestation and fraud.
- They'll serve sentences for all offenses.
- Are you messing with me, you jerk?!
- All offenses combined,
- Huh?!
both Mr. Phathi and Mr. Chawadon
- are sentenced to ten years in prison.
- Shut your damn mouth!
Ten years?
- Will it really be ten years?
- Damn you! Hey!
Not some
- reduced sentence scheme?
- They'll get you inside, I swear!
We hope that's the case.
How about Mrs. Woranan, who turned
state witness for the victims?
Despite her involvement,
her testimony benefited the case,
so the court decided
to suspend her sentence.
And Mr. Chayut has Alzheimer's.
Though his symptoms occasionally improve,
the disease is incurable
and still requires ongoing medical care.
The court ruled he be placed
under supervision at a hospital
or suitable facility.
WE BELIEVE IN THE TRUTH
NINETEEN YEARS OF WAITING
JUSTICE EXISTS
WE FIGHT TOGETHER
DON'T LET INJUSTICE WIN
MR. CHAI TISRAKSA
MRS. NAPHA TISRAKSA
It's over now…
Dad…
MR. CHAI TISRAKSA
MRS. NAPHA TISRAKSA
Mom.
I've won…
justice…
for our family.
They've all received punishment.
I wish you both could be here with me.
I'll try
to live happily.
No.
I will live happily.
Please don't worry anymore.
MR. CHAI TISRAKSA
MRS. NAPHA TISRAKSA
Mom, since you're out
for specialized physical therapy today,
I brought the kids to visit you.
We wanted to visit you, Grandma.
I'll ask Aun Nan to bring us here often,
so you won't feel lonely.
I was angry about what you did to me.
But I've decided.
I forgive you.
And I hope you'll forgive me
for being such a disappointment.
Don't worry, Grandma.
We've learned from our mistakes.
And we won't repeat them.
Hey.
I made a new one for you.
Thank you.
You'll be abroad for treatment
for how long?
I'm not sure yet.
Keep in touch, okay?
Why?
Looking to buy anything from the US?
Oh, Kram.
- Coming to send her off too?
- Uh…
You stay with the kids.
I have Nin with me. I'll be fine.
Well then…
Safe travels.
Let me know when you land.
Here you go.
Enjoy your meal.
- Can I take a photo with you?
- Of course.
Enjoy your meal.
Time cannot turn back
Our clock stopped
On the day you said goodbye
I understand you had your reasons to leave
And I respect your decision
Even if it broke my heart
No matter how long it's been
Phleng?
Nurse.
The patient is awake.
I still want to tell you that to me
You're still an important part
Of my everyday life
No matter how long it's been
- You are still…
- It hurts.
Oh! Did that hurt?
Sorry.
It still feels like you're right beside me
No matter how much time passes
I still miss you
I wonder how you're doing over there
Do you ever think back
To our old memories?
Because I think about us every single day
The time we had together
Still feels so vivid
No matter how long it's been
Or how far we are
I still want to tell you that to me
You're still an important part
Of my everyday life
No matter how long it's been
You're still a part of my everyday
As if you were still by my side
THREE YEARS LATER
Here.
Here you go. Please enjoy.
Is table five's almost done?
- Almost. Give me a sec.
- Okay.
Here you go.
I wonder how you're doing over there
Do you ever think back…
Chai.
Napha.
Kamon.
An important part
- Kram.
- Yes?
Don't forget to dedicate merits
to Chai and Napha.
I always do, Dad.
And where's Mom?
She's at work.
Oh.
Well, when she gets back,
let's go have barbecue together.
Okay, Dad.
Sure.
Let me see what you've done.
Here.
Well,
let's go get a PS5.
- Okay?
- Sure.
Are you okay?
Be more careful next time.
And if it was an accident,
you should say sorry.
I'm sorry.
It's okay. This shirt can be washed.
Happy birthday to you.
Today I tried making a new dish.
The customers loved it.
And I also went to the temple
to make merit for your parents.
How are you?
What's the weather like over there?
I miss you.
I saw the news.
There's a storm over there.
Are you okay?
That's a lot. Why don't you just call her?
I'm not as rude as you.
Maybe she just
doesn't have time to read it.
Three years and she hasn't replied.
Guess she really doesn't have time.
No need to be sarcastic.
I'm doing it because I want to. Look.
She started a new IG account
and posted pictures. See?
She keeps posting
but won't respond to you.
What's there to be happy about?
You just don't get it, do you?
The fact that she's posting
means she's safe and doing well.
She probably just
wants to settle everything first.
But she needs more time.
I'll say it again.
It's been three years.
Judo.
You're fired.
I won't leave.
Hey.
Come on. It's almost New Year's.
Why joke like this? It's not April Fools'.
Fired? Come on.
I'll go take the trash out.
You idiot.
Who are you visiting?
Hope I'm not intruding.
You never texted me back.
Are you upset?
I saw you liked my pictures all the time.
I liked all of them nonstop,
hoping you'd notice and text me back.
I'm sorry.
I just wanted to really
settle everything first.
Why are you laughing?
I just said the exact same thing to Judo,
that you probably wanted
to settle everything first.
See? Even from afar,
I still know you well.
Hm. If you really knew me,
you'd know standing here talking
is super hot.
Of course I know.
Why don't I? I know it's hot outside.
Let's talk inside, shall we?
Let's go.
Actually,
I've been back for two weeks.
But I visited Phleng and Bank,
took care of some things,
and just had free time now.
And are you okay?
I mean, with the treatment.
Yeah, I'm fine.
Right now,
I'm doing really well.
That's good.
And I'm happy for you.
I heard the restaurant won
several awards. You're blowing up.
Well, it's all thanks
to the stir-fried tofu and miso soup
I taught you to make back then.
Let me know when you're free again.
I'll cook it for you.
Sure.
- This time, I promise I'll eat it.
- Perfect.
And Uncle Chayut…
How is he?
He's stable.
He's in the hospital,
but I visit often.
Next time, can I come along?
Of course.
He'd be happy to see you.
Kamon.
I missed you.
Hang on a sec.
Guess who's here?
Sara.
Nan.
How are you?
Here.
Need help picking?
- This one too.
- This one.
Hi there.
- Oh, hello.
- Hello.
The traffic was insane.
- Really?
- But wow, you got here fast.
You missed someone so much,
you rushed over?
What?
Even though we've been through
so much pain,
in the end,
to live is to keep moving forward
and growing every day.
Someone once said
growing up
doesn't mean hurting less.
It means understanding
that pain,
no matter how bad,
will pass.
And today I'm starting to understand that
a little more.
Your food's ready.
Stir-fried tofu and miso soup,
made by me.
Is it not good?
It's the same recipe I once taught you.
It's delicious, Kram.
I missed…
your cooking.
Now,
I can eat
without looking around
or feeling paranoid
that someone might put
something into my food.
Thank you
for trusting me.
The moment we've all been waiting for
is just seconds away.
- We're about to enter a new year
- Oh.
- together.
- Are they setting off fireworks?
- Are you ready to celebrate?
- Wanna go watch the fireworks?
Oh.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
- Happy New Year!
Subtitle translation by: Panuwat Baikeawon