Just like how I didn't know
I would meet you,
find you, and fall in love with you.
Just like
how we don't know
what our ending would be.
Great job, really.
It took me a long time.
I was
lost in a dark and long tunnel
for a long time.
It was so long without an end.
I thought I would never
be able to get out.
I finally found
the exit.
Finally.
Lee Yeon-seo.
Be my Giselle.
Giselle?
Goodness, I got caught.
You wanted to come and roll around
on the sandy beach on your day off?
I was going to stay quiet,
but the guard post was way too old.
Stop smiling. You're annoying me.
What was it like to watch me in secret?
I must have looked like a complete fool
to get so easily deceived
to dance around.
It was so pretty.
It was really pretty.
This part of my body felt itchy,
and I became sad
and happy.
Don't be so cheeky.
What do you know about dance?
Because I don't know anything,
and because there was nothing I could do,
I decided to make this.
I wanted to do something for you,
but as you said,
I don't know anything about ballet.
Then you should just sit still.
Yes, you're useless.
You can't drive. You can't do judo.
And you get on my nerves
saying I'm too mean.
That's enough.
Stop going behind my back.
Should we go now?
Let's go to Fantasia's Night.
Let's show the sponsors
who the prima ballerina is.
What should I prepare?
A dress that is way too showy?
My business smile?
Don't be sarcastic.
You know that this is necessary.
Not all sponsors are perverted
or dirty.
It's the dancer's job to receive attention
and endure it.
Not yours, our outspoken director.
Over the ten years
of my life as a director, I never made
my ballerinas stand around as flowers.
Trust me.
No!
There's a saying,
"There must not be even
a hint of immorality,
or of any kind of impurity, or of greed."
Hey, you cult member.
What are you talking about?
Don't go. Your dance is more than enough.
There's no reason to prove
yourself any further.
There is no need to bear the wickedness.
Mr. Ji, do you think this is why I--
-Hey.
-You're right.
It could be dirty and uncomfortable.
And it could be worse.
But still, we shouldn't
avoid this, Yeon-seo.
I'll fight with you.
I want to see you become the center
of Fantasia.
I'll manage. Mind your business.
Both of you.
Is this what they call a dream?
Goodness!
How did you know about that beach?
Even I couldn't remember,
so how could you?
You're smiling brightly, aren't you?
You look pretty.
Can you stop saying that?
Are you teasing me?
It is said that a useless servant
should do what he can.
I may be useless,
but I will continue to call
something pretty if it is.
Because I can do that.
I'm sorry.
You said you didn't like me.
So why are you doing this?
YEONHWA ISLAND
THE DAY I STARTED BALLET ONCE AGAIN!
THE MOMENT YOU'VE STEPPED INTO
OUR ACADEMY,
IT'S AS IF YOU'VE ALREADY ACQUIRED
YOUR LICENSE
Your registration has been completed.
Thank you.
Are you Mr. Kim Dan?
-Yes.
-Come over here.
We'll start immediately.
Thank you, sir!
Brakes!
How many times do I need to repeat myself?
First, belt. Second, brakes.
Third.
Third, start the engine!
Again.
Brakes.
Start the engine.
We're pretty much crawling.
That's my report!
Wait! Come on!
Disqualified.
-Hu!
-What is it?
Are you seriously keeping an eye on me?
What?
Can't you see that I'm doing my best
to help you drive here?
Why do I sound like this?
I'm trying so hard to help you.
Then you should've told me earlier!
Thanks to you, I'm already disqualified!
There. Remember the steps and begin.
How could an angel threaten someone
and adopt an expedient?
Begin.
-Fine.
-Are you ready? Begin.
-No!
-Hey, hey!
Do it again.
Which one's the accelerator?
-The right side!
-Here I go.
-Good, good!
-Which one's the brakes?
-Stop!
Make it go back again!
Why is it going this way?
Stop! You did it!
No wonder you always cause trouble.
You're not smart, to begin with.
I'm never going to learn
anything from you!
You little...
Hey, Dan.
Dan!
You're pretty much a human now.
You're actually angry.
You were too harsh! It was my first time!
-Goodness.
-I didn't know anything.
I didn't know what I was doing.
But you shouted and criticized me!
I wasn't happy with what you were doing,
so I wanted you to snap out of it.
Animals were your only clients.
I was worried you wouldn't know which way
to lead your human client
and ultimately fail.
What do you mean?
I know this is your first
time dealing with humans.
This is your first time
in a human body too.
But still, don't you think
this was a bit too much?
Listen to this.
"Lee Yeon-seo danced.
She was beautiful.
It was the prettiest thing
I saw on earth."
She overworked herself.
I was scared
that she'd suffer and become unhappy.
But when she was dancing, her face glowed.
She was definitely happy.
How many times did you mention her?
There are 20 lines about her.
In the end, you wrote, "She hugged Rib."
It was just that one sentence.
What kind of report is this?
It's the truth!
Since we're talking about it,
I have a question.
Do you think he's a strong one?
What are you saying?
Her life has just begun!
She needs a strong, good rib beside her
for her to become happy.
Could you
look into it for me?
THE LATE CHOI SEOL-HUI
Are you scared?
Well. No.
I'll be with you.
-Kang-woo.
-It's dangerous.
Stay back.
Listen, Angel Raporas.
You had received a mission of
inspiring artists
so that they would be able to draw things
that would give joy to the deity.
However, you betrayed your mission
and even decided to abandon the deity.
Therefore, you will be judged.
I've fulfilled my mission as an angel.
From now on,
I'd like to become a muse
for one person only.
Becoming an angel,
becoming a human,
starting a life,
and ending a life
all depend on the deity's will.
Don't come.
Don't come. Please.
This is cruel.
Then
why did the deity give me a heart?
Giving me a heart
and telling me to overcome my feelings
are the doings of a devil!
I will take everything
that the deity has given
from you.
Please, no.
Please.
THE LATE CHOI SEOL-HUI
I desperately wanted to become a human,
but not in the world
where you don't exist.
I could neither die
nor live a proper life.
I was lost for 15 years.
I think
it will work out really well this time.
You must have lost someone dear to you.
I can still see waves
of yearning in your eyes.
As you loved the person
with all of your heart,
I am sure your loved one
will be in paradise.
And I can only assume
that she will be in peace.
Does "peace" really exist?
Living is already a torment.
Wishing to be born again
is a silly thought.
And wishing for peace on the other side
sounds lame, doesn't it?
Then,
what is it that you want?
Will you really attend the event?
"If you leave your home,
there will be trouble.
Stay at home."
That's your horoscope for today.
Doesn't this sound too eerie?
One person warns me with some saying.
And the other with my horoscope.
It's because
we don't feel good about this.
Horoscopes are big data
that contain the principles of
the universe and human history.
-If you ignore it, you'll be in trouble.
-I'll face it.
I probably can't avoid it
even if I want to.
Fine.
If you're going to attend,
might as well go and announce it
with a bright smile.
"Fantasia belongs to me. This is where
I should be." Make it official.
I'll be out after I get changed.
Okay.
Do you like me?
Just say yes or no.
Did you like me?
Do you?
No.
Hello. What would you like?
Something to help me be okay on my own.
-Pardon?
-Relaxing pills,
sedatives, or stimulant drugs.
I don't care what it is.
I've been
relying on people too much.
I've been relying on a guy
who doesn't even like me.
I'm not the type of person
who easily gets attached.
I must have lost my mind
for a second or something.
Give me some medicine
that will make me be okay
without that jerk.
Darn it.
Gosh.
What is he...
Hold on. Get out of the car.
I'll move the car for you.
Let me keep trying.
Sure.
Behind you. Watch out for the gate.
Goodness. You're in my way.
Get out of my way. I'm parking here.
Were you really parking?
I was keeping a safe distance, you know?
-When did you get your driver's license?
-What are you talking about?
Your driver's license...
You're not supposed to park your car here.
-Come on.
-Goodness.
What is that?
Did you get a driver's license?
Yes.
Why don't you ride with me today?
For safety reasons.
That would be better.
Welcome, Yeon-seo.
Welcome.
He is our special guest today.
This is Seiji Ishikawa.
Ms. Lee, it's very nice to meet you.
Thank you.
Have a good time today.
Okay.
Why don't you escort Mr. Seiji, Yeon-seo?
Mr. Seiji, hello.
I'm Fantasia's Artistic Director,
Ji Kang-woo.
-Nice to meet you.
-I see.
Why don't we go in?
-Sure.
-Okay.
You're wearing the earrings.
How beautiful. They look great on you.
They don't suit my taste, but I'm being
considerate for the one who gave it to me.
I'm very grateful.
Your attendance at the event means a lot.
You will make the official announcement
in front of the sponsors, right?
When will you announce it?
I'll announce it as soon as the show ends.
Don't worry, Yeon-seo.
Enjoy the event as much as you can.
I'll go check on the dancers.
Wait for me here.
I'll go inside first.
I can go in by myself.
-No, you can't.
-No.
Let me escort you.
Do not leave Yeon-seo alone
until I get there. Understood?
Just hurry back.
Hey, don't kid yourself.
I can walk just fine without you now.
I know that. I didn't say anything.
Let's go.
Check for anything
that could fall around Ms. Lee first.
Like lights or anything else.
Ms. Lee.
Do you really think someone might be
trying to harm Ms. Lee?
But she's their family.
Think about it.
Think about how the chandelier fell.
She was in a car accident.
And the light fell on her.
Scary things keep happening to her.
I'm just worried.
Attention.
Don't get too excited.
-No injuries. Okay?
-Yes, sir.
The floor might be slippery.
-Apply a lot of resin.
-Yes, sir.
We'll get the sponsors
to donate a lot of money.
We're not here to beg for money.
Don't smile to make good impressions.
And don't overdo it
by looking too serious.
Just show them that what we do is worth
all the money that they spend. That's all.
Okay? Keep up the good work.
It's an honor to meet
the legendary Ms. Lee this close.
Sure. Let us keep this good relationship.
What is this?
The world-renowned Ms. Lee is next to me,
but I can't even hold her hand.
I am so sorry.
Instead, choose a girl you like
among them.
I will
take her to you later
for a private meeting.
I like the one in the center.
I especially like her thighs.
Ballerinas tend to be way too skinny.
Ms. Lee, it is such an honor to meet you.
Will you please
show me a short performance?
That wasn't a part of our plan.
You should see that on a good stage.
We'll reserve a VIP seat
for you at her comeback performance.
Please interpret that.
She just declined.
She's being difficult.
If she is truly a genius,
she can surprise everyone
with an improvisation.
Not bad at putting up with those rogues.
Eat up, Yeon-seo.
Bring what I prepared.
Yes.
There won't be any security cameras
because it's a private party.
What's important is the people.
Don't miss anyone who looks suspicious.
Who are you? What are you doing here?
I was trying to smoke.
I'm so sorry.
I know smoking is prohibited here,
but my hands began to shake.
No, I'm sorry.
Are you nervous
to stand in front of the sponsors?
I lived all my life
getting attention on stage.
Nervous? No way.
What's important is the people.
Don't miss anyone who looks suspicious.
Wait
What's going on?
-What happened?
-Why did he fall?
I'm sorry.
-What was that?
-Goodness.
What are you doing?
Hey, just leave
before everyone stares at you.
Make two more glasses.
Hurry!
It's okay. Get back to work.
Gwang-il.
Chairman Keum.
I was following the order
of the General Director--
I know.
But you can't.
Never.
You shouldn't hurt a person
no matter who gave you the order.
Why isn't he coming?
She'll be making a speech
after that segment.
Mr. Park won't come.
How did you know?
What is this?
A sleeping pill? Sedative?
Were you going to
let Yeon-seo collapse
in front of everyone?
I told her that we shouldn't do it.
I told her that it cannot happen.
I mean it, Ki-chun.
You.
How much do you know?
You already know
that Mr. Park is a pushover.
Why do you keep taking a risk?
Did you all enjoy the performances?
Your precious contribution
made Fantasia what it is today.
We truly thank you.
And now,
I would like to make
an important announcement.
As of now,
I, Choi Yeong-ja,
who loved Fantasia with all of her heart,
who worked as
the General Director of Fantasia,
will resign.
Let me introduce the lady
who will take charge of Fantasia's future.
Please welcome my niece,
whom I love dearly,
Lee Yeon-seo, with a round of applause.
I was trying to smoke.
You fool!
What's going on?
My goodness!
What did you say?
You can't even hold my hand?
You pervert.
You can't differentiate ballet
with pornography?
This isn't a brothel, you scumbag!
You speak Japanese?
I can even say "scumbag" in French.
What are you doing?
My goodness. What is it?
-Please!
-You...
You ignorant idiots!
Please, I beg you.
Could you please
spend your filthy money elsewhere?
You guys make me sick!
You are disgusting!
Please, everyone.
Stop acting so sophisticated.
Sorry, sir.
Let's get out of here.
What's going on?
Hey, you pervert!
Where are you going?
Let's see what else you are thinking.
Wait, Yeon-seo.
You Japanese geezer.
You wanted me to dance?
Where are you going?
-Where are you going?
-Ms. Lee!
Fine!
I'll show you then.
Music!
It's you again?
Yes.
It's me.
It's always you.
You stupid idiot.
Don't go.
Are you awake?
How did I come home yesterday?
Do you really not remember anything?
You pervert.
You can't differentiate ballet
with pornography?
You guys make me sick!
You are disgusting!
Darn it.
Where's Dan?
He took care of you all night and then
switched with me,
saying he had somewhere to go.
Were you in that much pain
that you had to drink?
Still, you said you'd be careful.
I didn't even finish a glass of wine.
Ms. Jung, could you bring me my phone?
JI KANG-WOO
Please call Dr. Lee.
Are you feeling sick?
Is Lee Yeon-seo out of her mind?
That's why I told you
that she was still
physically and mentally unstable.
And it seems to be getting worse.
That prima ballerina,
chairwoman, or whatever she may be
swore in front of us
which was absolutely unforgivable.
But on top of that, are we supposed
to condone that young artistic director's
brazen attitude?
Are we? Why?
Sir, will you please calm down
for my sake, at least?
It's also impressive
how you and your daughter
maintained your temporary positions
for so long.
That mad heiress will run
this ballet theater and also perform?
Please give me a logical reason
why I should invest my precious money
into this preposterous ballet theater.
Director Ji, say something.
Do as you please.
-What?
-What is he saying?
But if you back out now,
I won't allow you to become a sponsor
for Giselle.
It's a chance for your name to be listed
under Korea's best performance.
This is your last chance.
Are you telling us not to miss out
on a chance to spend our money?
I will
no longer support this ballet theater.
I don't know what you all may think.
But our company
will cease to do any business
that concerns Fantasia.
Director Ji.
-How is that possible?
-It's ridiculous.
-I can't believe it.
-Hey.
A strike?
Everyone on that ship saw it.
It's ridiculous for her
to become the prima ballerina.
What if she suddenly
acts out while performing a lift?
Who will be responsible for her injuries?
Are you done?
Keum Ni-na.
Do you have anything to say?
I think it's a problem if the corps
cannot acknowledge the prima ballerina.
The prima ballerina should be someone
whom everyone can approve of.
I'm baffled.
I thought Lee Yeon-seo would be the one
to bail out, not you people.
Are you saying that she's going to quit?
No.
I'm talking about performing with you all.
I was worried she'd say
that she wouldn't be able to perform
with such an incompetent corps.
The five who performed Spanish.
Did you know the angles of
your elbows were terrible?
Ui-geon.
I said not to smile or frown excessively.
But you had a stiff face all night long.
Were you at a funeral?
Keum Ni-na!
You were too focused on keeping the rhythm
that your dance moves were dull.
Yet you talk about acknowledgment
and approval?
I couldn't feel anything.
Do you even listen to music?
Do you even understand the story?
With Yeon-seo, she could
just stand in front of me,
and my body would feel electrified.
So how?
How are all your dance moves
so empty?
Why?
With Yeon-seo,
she could just stand in front of me,
and my body would feel electrified.
So how?
How are all your dance moves
so empty?
Why?
This is awful.
I'm being awful to myself.
It's so awful that I'm not Yeon-seo!
What's there to yell about?
You're totally wasted in broad daylight.
Is that her?
Ms. Elena?
Ms. Elena!
Ms. Elena.
Isn't that you, Ms. Elena?
It's me, Ni-na.
I learned ballet from you when I was a kid
for the first time. I'm Keum Ni-na!
Get lost!
I...
I thought about you from time to time.
I missed you.
I told you to get lost.
A mere mention of Fantasia disgusts me.
It makes me furious!
Go away!
I must be having a terrible day today.
You want a list of guests and agencies
that participated in yesterday's event?
Yes, there's something
I want to look into.
Please.
That's too bad.
I can't share personal
information like that.
Then,
why don't we investigate together?
Investigate what?
Are you thinking that someone
could have harmed Yeon-seo yesterday?
I would like to believe that I'm wrong.
That's why
I want to look into this.
Yeon-seo recently got her surgery.
And she worked too much
to return as a dancer.
Considering her circumstances,
a glass of wine is enough
to push her over the edge.
To clarify, you already made up your mind
that it is completely
Yeon-seo's fault.
There's no reason to deny that.
Logically speaking.
I understand.
Actually, I expected
that you would be eager
to help me investigate
because you're her family.
What brings you here?
Director Ji isn't here now.
Excuse me.
What do you think you're doing?
Before I report you
for obstruction of business,
leave immediately.
I'll take care of him.
Just keep an eye on him for now.
He's cute.
If I run the blood test now, I'll get
the result tonight at the earliest.
Please take care of it.
And you too.
Don't you worry.
I know a glass of wine
won't get you that drunk.
Once we get the result,
we might be able to catch who it is.
I went to the ballet theater.
How is it there?
Actually, it's so obvious.
The sponsors probably
demanded to kick me out.
And dancers will be gossiping about me.
"She's unbelievable. She was crazy."
Everything will get resolved.
I believe that it wasn't your fault.
How will belief resolve anything?
My gosh, you look gaunt.
Why are you here?
What do you want to know?
Don't be so harsh.
I barely managed to
calm down those sponsors
who wanted to barge in here.
What do they want?
Do they want me to kneel down?
It would be great if it was that simple.
Mr. Park.
WITHDRAWAL AGREEMENT
ON THE POWER OF ATTORNEY
I truly did my best to help you.
When you weren't at your best,
I tried to protect you
by extending the power of attorney.
And when you stubbornly
asked me to give it back,
I even announced
that I would be resigning.
You know what?
Power of attorney or extension.
Forget about it all.
Give everything to me.
You must.
I don't need money
from those perverted sponsors.
I'll sell the house
to pay for the show if I need to.
That's enough, right?
It's not just about money.
They even said that we should send you
to a mental institution.
They questioned how we could let a girl
who isn't in her right mind take over
this big foundation
and the ballet theater.
I made
one mistake that day.
Or it could be a trap someone set up.
There you go again.
Who on earth
would set up this meticulous trap
and go through all that trouble
just to kick you out?
Oh, right.
The ballet theater will go on a strike.
They can't perform with a girl like you.
You understand that, right?
Don't live in your
memories like an old lady.
You're not the same Yeon-seo.
No one is welcoming you back.
Did you get that?
Excuse me, ma'am!
Gosh, you startled me.
Did you just yell at me?
There is a saying.
"Abstain from every form of evil.
Greed gives birth to sin.
When it's full-grown,
it gives birth to death."
Hey, Dan. What's the matter with you?
What's going on here?
Have both of you gone crazy?
I understand that you may get carried
away. I know that temptation is strong,
but you're the only family Yeon-seo has.
Why don't you cherish her?
Why don't you love her?
How could you treat her
no better than a stranger?
Why do you hurt her like this? Why?
You are surely blessed with
having a loyal secretary.
Mr. Cho and now this guy.
They'll do everything for you.
You must feel reassured
even without your family.
Leave now.
Don't you ever come to see me.
I'll give you 12 hours.
Resign on your own.
If you continue to be stubborn,
all of the sponsors will leave.
And once the reputation
of Fantasia is tainted,
this foundation your parents established
will vanish into thin air.
And the only person to stop that
from happening is me, Choi Yeong-ja.
Keep that in mind.
Thank you for the juice.
It's almost ready.
After you drink this,
don't think about anything
and just get some sleep.
Let's go upstairs.
What are you doing?
No, don't drink.
Who do you think you are?
Don't be such a fool.
You went through so much yesterday.
What is this?
You requested a blood test.
When we get the result--
It'll be useless.
I'm sure someone put
stimulant drugs somewhere.
But
alcohol and sedative
were found in your blood too.
Did you take any medications?
Everything is mixed up,
so they aren't sure
if it could be used as evidence.
They can't find out if what I had was
poison, medication, or alcohol,
or who did it to me.
I must really have gone crazy.
It's all my fault.
I tried my best to be on the lookout.
I wanted to make sure I protect you.
It's my fault.
-No.
-You said
greed gives birth to sin.
I guess it was greed for me to wish
to do ballet again.
No. It isn't.
My first audience said
that my dance was the prettiest thing
he has ever seen in his life.
A kid who doesn't know what ballet is
became touched and cried.
I know.
I felt that way too.
I was so happy back then.
He helped me realize that I'm happy
when I dance.
But I forgot that for such a long time.
I finally
found my goal again,
but
it's too tough.
It's tough.
Ms. Lee.
Can't you just give up on everything?
I hate to see you suffer.
You don't have to keep dancing
for Fantasia.
If you need an audience to dance,
I will watch you.
Okay?
Should I?
Should I give up on everything,
only show my dance to you,
and live forever with you?
Okay.
I will give you my first performance.
This piece is called
Giselle.
It's you again.
Dan.
Yes, Ms. Lee.
Why do you always save me?
You save me
and help me out.
But why don't you like me?
Figures.
No one in this world likes me.
I don't care about that.
But it's not okay for you
to not like me.
I hate it.
It's frustrating.
You said I'm good.
You said I'm pretty.
But...
But why don't you like me?
How can you not like me?
How?
Dan.
I
cannot like you.
And I
can't stay by your side forever.
That really
breaks my heart.
Yeon-seo.
How can I
not like you?
Don't go.
How do you really feel?
Are you worried he isn't the real one?
Or are you wishing that
he isn't the real one?
I'm in huge trouble, aren't I?
-What are you doing?
-No, what's with you?
-Let go of me. Let go
-You can't run away.
Tell me you'll disappear
from Yeon-seo's life now.
What are you talking about?
I warned you, didn't I?
That I won't let you live
if you interfere.
Who do you think you are to tell her
to give up on dancing?
I said, let go!
You promised me that whatever you do,
you'll do it to make Yeon-seo happy.
Why am I like this?
He really gets on my nerves.
Hey, what are you doing?
Whatever you decide to do,
you are no longer alone.
I'll make you like it.
I'll make you love it. I'll do that.
What are you doing to Yeon-seo?
Kim Dan. No. Angel Dan.
Why are you here?