If angels could also regret,
my only regret would be that day.
♫  Just stay, stay with me  ♫
♫  I'm here  ♫
♫  As how it is now  ♫
♫   Just you and I  ♫
I shouldn't have done that.
I shouldn't have saved that person.
That was something I shouldn't have done.
No. Please!
You're late.
I told you that was your last warning.
Yes. There was a car accident.
This is Highway 8 going to Yangpyung. Please hurry!
Mister, please respond.
I'm scared.
Who are you?
You're fine now. It's all fine.
Now that I am here,
Lee Yeon Seo.
It's here.
Like smoke. Like dust.
A place where you rot.
Hear me, Angel Dan.
An angel is a messenger for God
and has to be indifferent to human matters.
However, this angel
often broke the rules.
However, we were hoping that he would do the right thing by himself.
He has intervened in a human life in the end.
He deserves to be punished severely at once.
Therefore, this angel will now
disappear.
What are you doing?
I didn't disappear yet?
How?
No. Why?!
From now on, you will not be an angel,
but you will become human Kim Dan.
This is now your last, last chance.
As a human, pursue your last mission.
Senior!
They say that the humans and animals you saved by breaking the rules
are filling the sky up with thank you prayers for saving them.
I'm not sure whether to say "good job" for causing accidents
or to scold you for causing this disaster, you dumbhead.
Thank you. Thank you so much!
You only have a hundred days. It was hard even getting those hundred days.
The doors will open once you succeed in your mission in a hundred days.
You must never pass a hundred days.
Yes. I will do everything I can.
If you tell me to move the mountain from here to there or order me to bring that sea to this sea, I will do it.
There is no problem. If you tell me to bring all the feathers of the birds in this world, I will do it.
So what is it, my last mission?
Love.
Find love? For who?
Oh, it's so sunny.
Oh. My shadow.
Oh! Oh!
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
You're a nice person, Mister.
Person?
Oh yeah, I'm a human!
♫  I like where we are heading now ♫
♫  These little feelings are so "Oh!"  ♫
♫  I'm crazy over you~ ♫
That love?
I'll find it for you, including trust and hope, as a full package.
I will fulfill the mission!
♫  I'm in love with...  ♫
Yeah!
How is it? Can you see?
The sunset...
It's pretty, isn't it?
Knowing that you'd opened your eyes, Heaven must have set it before you.
It's beautiful, isn't it?
Quite beautiful...
Yeon Seo! Hang on tight!
Why?! What's going on?
Yeon Seo, are you okay?
Let's lie you down, okay?
But why are you wearing black?
What about Mister?
Oh!
She's really gone crazy, hasn't she?
Your words are a bit harsh. She's hurt.
Harsh? Me?
She wouldn't be behaving that way if she didn't still think of us as servants.
Putting it plainly, were we responsible for Butler Jo's death?
Did I kill him?
I am the one who flipped about corneas or something.
Dear!
Let's go. We've done all we can.
Everyone head on in.
I'll stay with Yeon Seo tonight.
Will you?
You can't!
Come here already! After being humiliated by her like that yesterday, why would you stay with her?
I understand how Yeon Seo feels. How confused and scared she must be.
Her sight, and Mister's death.
If it were me, I'd have fainted.
That's why we should give her a little space until she accepts reality.
I'll ask them to take good care of her, so don't worry.
I have no idea how I gave birth to such a lamb of a girl.
She took after me, as kind as an angel.
Head in first, Dear. I'll be staying at the funeral a bit longer.
Why go back? You finished paying your respects already.
You know he didn't have any family.
He's way too much of a softie.
My god.
Room 502.
I'll see for myself.
Till then I won't believe it. I refuse to believe.
Room 502.
What's this?
You came?
Do you have a grudge against liquor? Why are you drinking so aggressively?
- Don't drink too much.
- It feels so vivid.
He was down-to-earth.
And whenever we met, he was smiling to greet me.
He insisted that he shouldn't send me off with nothing.
He packed me fruits and Korean desserts.
My fridge is still filled with those.
Geez.
Who can we blame that there is no order for dying?
He was a kindhearted person and did good deeds in the end.
He must be in a better place now.
Let's remember him.
Yes.
I will remember everything for you, so you can forget everything:
including scary things, creepy things,
and unfair things you had to suffer. Forget all those and rest in peace.
Unfair? What are you talking about?
I feel so bad for Secretary Jo.
She used him. She and her father worked him to the bone. In the end, Mr. Jo even gave her his corneas.
Did you hear that?
This accident may have been planned.
Wow, so unexpected.
- By who?
- Why?
Of course, I don't know that.
In any case, he did all medical tests in advance and appointed the receiver for the corneas.
I heard that Lee Yeon Seo knew about it already.
No way. She can't be that mean.
Where there is light, there is darkness. Where there is good, there is evil.
Where there is life, there is death.
May he rest in peace.
I'm late, Mr. Jo.
I want to see you smiling brightly like you did back then,
just one more time.
- What's wrong with her?
- She must be crazy.
Room 502's patient, Lee Yeon Seo, has been reported as leaving the mortuary.
Room 502?!
I heard that she left after smiling at the funeral of someone who was in the same car with her. I will look for her.
"Gildam Hospital Room 502."
Lee Yeon Seo?
Yeah, what room was it?
Room 502? Okay.
Oh, what about the surgery? It went well, right?
All right, I understand.
Where would you like me to take you?
Please take me home.
♫  The stillness that pushes your heart  ♫
♫  The warmth that disappeared  ♫
♫  Like a miracle  ♫
♫  Come back to me  ♫
♫  Your dreams that came up white  ♫
♫  That unsuspectingly soothing bland smile  ♫
♫  Gently shaking my heart  ♫
♫  Without trace on the streets  ♫
♫  Like strangers  ♫
♫  Wandering back and forth every day   ♫
♫  With these tough hearts  ♫
♫  At the end of a long wait  ♫
♫  Without the sound of delicate rain  ♫
♫  It's the tears that make me soaked  ♫
♫  At the end of a season   ♫
♫  Our time together  ♫
♫  Will be shining brilliantly like a gleaming shining light  ♫
♫  I like it  ♫
♫  Without trace on the streets  ♫
♫  Like strangers  ♫
♫  Wandering back and forth every day   ♫
♫  With these tough hearts  ♫
Come here! Come here!
Now for the only person I trust in this world, Seung Hwan!"
Tada!
When I'm not there with you, treat Mr. Jo like your father
Got it?
I don't want to. You are my dad and Mr. Jo is "Mister."
I see.
Mr. Jo is my most beloved Mister in the world!
Here I come!
Whoa.
♫  Will be shining brilliantly like a gleaming shining light  ♫
If you give me some more time,
I'll get you back to the right place.
How? Will you give me your eyes?
Yeon Seo...
Get my place back? Who are you to say that?
If you act like my father one more time,
I'll fire you for real.
Who gave you the right to give me your eyes?
Who gave you the right to die?
How dare you die!
Who said that everyone except me could die first?!
♫  Will be shining brilliantly like a gleaming shining light  ♫
♫  I like it  ♫
What?
Please open, Senior!
Why are you doing this? This isn't right!
That girl treated her cornea donation like it was nothing and was smiling like this at the donor's funeral portrait!
She was already heartless and now she's not even sane!
How can a person like that love someone?
Change the mission! Change it, please! Come on!
Darn it!
Good day!
You must be here for the sunrise mass?
Uh yes, yes.
He looks like a beggar.
Hey!
As a tip for the future, humans die early deaths if they sleep in cold places.
You've been made human, as well? Are you on a special mission, too?
When you're at my level, taking on the human form is a cakewalk.
I'm jealous.
Your precious time is ticking away. Why are you just wasting it?
Actually, I needed to think of it from a human's perspective.
A person who had a nasty personality from the beginning,
loses her sight on top of that and turns cruel as can be.
But then one day she suddenly gains her vision back after going through a death-like accident.
Oh my, she must be so grateful. Wouldn't she be absolutely over the moon?
You would think so, right? But the new eyes turn out to be from the person who used to be absolutely fond of her.
But she used to be snappish towards him.
How do you think she'd feel then?
From a human's perspective?
Won't she still be thankful?
Why, why, why?
Wrong! She'd go crazy, of course! Humans can go plain bonkers you know!
I've given it a lot of thought,
and I think that must be why she smiled like that.
No way!  There's no way.
Her heart is so dried up.
It's so dry that I can't seed love in her heart.
I can't do it, I can't do it.
Then just give up your mission early and turn to dust if you want.
Why does is it have to be that woman? Why?
Why did you have to save "that woman?"
That's becau—
My last advice: shine brightly.
What did you just say?
Whoa.
Oh my. Senior!
Senior!
Miss.
Miss!
I came back after sending off Secretary Jo early in the morning (buried him).
Were you going through this all night?
Yes.
Did you put in your eye drops?
No, right? Because it's with me.
What are you doing?
I should ask you that. What are you doing?
These are Mr. Jo's eyes.
You can choose to be starved, hurt yourself or skip sleeping for your body,
except for your eyes!
Since those are from Mr. Jo!
I didn't ask for them.
Then, cut them out.
I meant there is no one to pamper you now.
You may not know it but Mr. Jo was a very special person to everyone.
He remembered all of our birthdays even including our family members.
If you have his eyes, you shouldn't waste them.
I will ask this of you.
If you are fond of him that much, you should have treated him better.
You played hooky, leaving your duties to him.
Other staff all asked favors of him and now you get angry to lose him?
I heard you well.
It was so  touching.
Did you forget?
That annoying thing we asked him to do was  you.
Right. Be snappish. That suits you the best.
What'wrong with you?
I can't go.
I know it well.
I can see it well,
but my feet won't move.
Psychological trauma?
This happens often to people when they lose the person that was closest to them.
They become unable to do the things they used to do together with that person.
There was once a husband who lost his wife that used to go bowling with him every Sunday.
He'd get nauseous at the mere sight of a bowling pin and even experienced panic attacks at times.
The closer you are to the person, the stronger the symptoms.
You should get admitted to the hospital again. It's only been a few days since the accident.
People hallucinate when they get weak, right?
I just talked to the doctor. Her inflammation and leucocyte counts are normal.
If she gets discharged and takes rest at home, she will recover soon.
You're saying my mind is the problem?
And that I won't be able to do the things I used to do with him?
I did everything with him.
Walking, running, eating, everything.
I'm not going to be able to do any of that?
Even though... even though I can see now?