Let me go!
What? For your lover?
You are just a lustful pervert!
You're right.
I'm just in love with you.
I'm going to make you mine.
Miss, you're awake.
Are you okay?
Where is Fan Xingxu?
Marquis?
He left early this morning.
My Lady,
the Old Lady asked me to tell you
it's time to greet her.
Grandma, may you be in good health.
My Lady.
What?
Just garbage thrown away by others
You're a disgrace,
yet you dare to enter our house?
How shameless!
What do you mean?
I've just married.
Is this how
you treat a new bride?
Nonsense!
Don't slander our family!
You're the one who's unfaithful,
yet you dare to accuse me!
On our wedding night,
but there's no blood.
You're not a virgin.
How dare you
be the Marquise of Wei Yuan?
I'll go to your Shen family
and ask for an explanation.
Are you just being guilty
or are you crazy?
What should I be guilty about?
I'm laughing at your ignorance.
Whether there's a bloodstain on the wedding night
has nothing to do with whether she's a virgin.
Anyone who has read a few medical books
wouldn't be so ignorant.
If I'm garbage,
then your noble Marquis of Wei Yuan
is a rotten dustbin.
You...
What did you say?
I said garbage and dustbin make a perfect pair.
He found the guy himself,
and insisted on the marriage.
If you have the guts,
go find him yourselves!
As women,
you resort to baseless rumors
to slander other women.
I'm ashamed
to be in the same category as you.
You sharp-tongued b***h!
You're so arrogant.
Guards!
Hold her down!
Punish her!
What are you doing?
What?
Let me go!
Be quiet.
Hold her down.
Let me go!
Let go of me!
You need a lesson!
My Lady,
I heard Minister Shen's wife died young,
so his daughter grew up without proper guidance.
It's no surprise.
Like mother, like daughter.
Given her behavior,
her mother wasn't much better.
Grandma,
She's really crazy.
Someone's gonna die.
What do we do?
Let go.
I'll be visiting my parents in three days.
After that,
I'll have to pay respects to the Queen.
I'll pretend nothing happened today.
Grandma, you must protect me.
If I
feel unwell,
I'll drag you
down with me
to the grave.
You...
Grandma, may you live long and prosper.
My days
are numbered.
Crazy.
She's crazy.
Miss,
you must be in pain.
Why don't you explain?
You didn't consummate the marriage last night.
False accusations
are always wrong.
Someone wants to harm you.
You can't guard against it.
I thought you were going to be killed.
There were so many of them.
I couldn't beat them.
But I knew their selfishness and fear.
So I picked the biggest one
and bit it hard.
I wanted to scare them.
I won the bet.
Ah.
I'm sorry, Miss.
How could he
just leave you alone
after marrying you?
It's just what Fan Xingxu wants.
He wants me to suffer
and be in pain.
I'll show him.
I saw it.
Not enough.
Get out.
My dear,
I heard you won the bet.
I didn't know
you were such a gambler.
Why don't you bet with me?
What are you up to?
I'll give you a chance.
If you can make your beloved
give up all his fame and fortune
and run away with you,
I'll let go of all grudges
and grant you freedom.
In this mansion,
I'm the one with nothing.
I bet
you'll keep your word.
Deal.
My lord hasn't slept all night.
He's been waiting
for your return.
Dad.
As long as you're safe.
Father-in-law.
Hmph.
My Lord.
Don't forget your promise to me.
That depends on your lover
whether he wants to or not.
I've already bribed the carriage driver.
He will help us.
We'll leave tonight.
Marquis Wei Yuan's Mansion.
I can't stay here a moment longer.
The final exam is about to start.
I can't leave the capital.
Didn't you say
you were taking the exam
to match my status
and marry me?
Now I'm forced to marry
and endure humiliation.
What's more important than
saving me from this?
Yuan Zhi,
stop dreaming.
Even if we run away,
we can't escape the capital.
Marquis Weyuan won't let us go.
Gu Hengyuan, look clearly.
These injuries were all for you.
Shen Yuanzhi,
all the suffering I've endured in my life
is nothing compared to what you've put me through.
Are you going to break my heart?
Yuan Zhi, calm down.
What if someone finds out?
How about this?
We can discuss this matter further.
When things take a turn...
No.
After my imperial examination,
wait for my message.
Take care of yourself.
Are you done?
As you wish.
Aren't you curious
why your beloved
is so ruthless?
What do you mean?
Shen Yuanzhi wants to run away with you?
Keep your voice down.
How dare she?
Marquis Wei Yuan is so powerful.
She won't be afraid of being caught
and punished.
She must have had a tough time
in the Wei Yuan Marquis's residence.
I'm just worried
she might spill the beans
about us.
Then we're done for.
What's there to fear?
By then,
we can say that she couldn't stand loneliness
and seduced you.
A married daughter is like water that's been spilled.
Even the Lord
couldn't protect her.
You're the most scheming.
Even if I'm scheming,
I'm still yours.
Right?
Yuan Zhi.
Let me explain.
I thought I was smart,
but I'm just a joke.
No.
Good.
Great.
Shen Yuanzhi.
If you dare to spread this,
I'll have Hengyuan tell Marquis Wei Yuan
Tell him you're not a good wife
and seduce...
You let him go!
I want to see
what he'll say about me.
Yuan Zhi.
My dear.
What happened?
Who hurt you?
You already knew.
You did it on purpose, right?
Does it matter?
You said
you'd make me feel all the pain,
heartbroken,
and worse than death.
You've done it.
I feel
so much pain,
so much pain.
But how can I
bear this pain alone?
Aren't you curious
about how your beloved
died?