Come on, be careful.
Are you okay?
Xing Ge?
Xing Ge!
I want to ask you...
What?
You and Xing Yi-
It's so hot here.
Did you drink
the wine other people gave you?
I don't quite remember.
I don’t know if I take it or no.
Are you okay?
I-
Lu Wenxi?
Feel better now?
Good morning.
Morning.
How about marring me?
Wenxi,
marry me.
Why are you sighing?
I proposed to him today.
He just ignored me.
How about you?
He proposed to me.
Oh, how good!
Not at all.
It’s not like you don’t know that
I don't want to get married at all now.
Dating is okay,
but marriage
will kill me!
Is it that scary?
There is a famous saying-
anyway a famous guy said,
let a man and a woman
live together continuously for a long time,
from a biological perspective
this is totally
extremely unnatural state.
Is it necessary to make it that grand?
Yes.
Marriage is a relationship
with responsibility in law and morals.
I'm used to freedom and afraid of responsibility.
I don't want to be bound by marriage.
I don't want to spend my time and energy
on all the quarrels in marriage.
You don't quarrel with your boyfriend?
I do.
But I can break up with him when dating.
But you can't just get a divorce, right?
It seems to make sense.
So you still want to get married?
Yes, why not?
I can only get the shares if I get married
and then can I inherit the company.
Congratulations.
You have reached
a state of confusion and clarity.
Wish you get married soon.
Thank you.
But what if I got the wrong person?
How about asking my parents to adopt you?
You can be my dad's another daughter.
Sacrifice yourself for me, your sister.
Don't.
It shouldn't matter even if you got the wrong one.
They are all sons of the Xing family,
I think they are all the same.
What do you think?
I don't know either.
What did you say?
You will say yes?
What about the Xing family?
Will you go back?
I will never go back.
Listen carefully,
you said it yourself that
she tried to marry you
just for Xing family's share.
Don't blame me for not reminding you.
Didn’t she lie to you before
and make up so many stories?
You are willing to marry her?
It smells so good.
One, two, three, four...
Hello?
Miss Su, bad news.
You're chasing the wrong person.
What do you mean?
The one you should get is Xing Yi, not Xing Ge.
Xing Ge
is Mr. Xing and his first wife's kid.
I heard that
because of his mom,
Xing Ge hated his dad.
He basically has nothing to do with the Xing family.
Are you sure?
Ye-yeah, I'm sure.
Miss Su, don't propose to him.
I'm back.
Niannian? Niannian?
Su Nian!
Hello,
the user you called is temporarily unavailable...
Where has she been?
It's so late. Where has she been?
Wenxi broke up with her boyfriend.
I need to go stay with her.
Go after having dinner, see how many dishes  you made.