What are you doing here?
Wenxi, I want to
take responsibility for what happened that day.
I like you.
So,
let's get married.
Wenxi,
I'm too direct, right?
I really think that after what happened that day,
I should be responsible for you.
And I really like you.
So let's get married.
Wenxi!
Well...
Xing Yi, I think you may have misunderstood.
Yes, when I'm with you,
I'm quite happy.
I believe you are too.
But that's all we can...
Let's put it this way,
if you want to be responsible for me
for what happened that day,
I don't need that.
Lu Wenxi, I’m serious.
I'll give you time to think about it.
Please think about it and then reply to me.
What day is it today?
So many dishes.
It's weekend now.
I want to have dinner with you.
You actually have sense of ritual?
In fact, I also prepared a gift for you.
Xing Ge.
What?
I have something to tell you.
Very important thing.
I made a mistake.
I mistook you with the one I should get married with.
You mistook?
I have always told you that
my family is poor
and I lost my job.
These are all lies to get your sympathy.
So you are telling me these now,
because you mistook and
you want to stop your loss in time?
Anything else?
Sorry.
Since Ms. Su wants to stop the loss in time,
goodbye.
I really got the wrong person.
So do you like him?
That doesn't matter at all.
The person I should marry is Xing Yi.
What should we do now?
Actually, Niannian,
you should learn about
what happened between Xing Ge and his father.
If it wasn’t severe problem,
there should still be a chance to make up.
Right.
Father and son won't really hate each other.
I should try to learn more about the situation.
I'm really a fool.
Why didn't I
leave myself a way out just now.
It's okay.
We will have solutions.
You will be fine.
I will go back home to ask my dad.
He must know what happened.
Okay, stop talking about me.
You can't just avoid Xing Yi
by not going back home.
I don't know what happened to him.
Suddenly he is like a different person.
Could it be just because we
well, did that?
Nowadays, people are more open than before,
but some people are still conservative.
Maybe he's that kind of person.
Don't people always say
for a woman,
marriage is like the second life.
And I've never seen
a good second life.
Think about my mom.
She has second life twice.
And that almost killed her.
To save my life,
I will never get married.
What about Xing Yi?
I will find a time to explain it to him.
Come on.
Hurry! Hurry!
Wenxi, what are you doing?
What's going on?
Get in first.
Wenxi, are you okay?
No.
You don't understand.
The way he proposed
is like a teacher
asks you do you want to study hard
with a ferule in his hand.
Isn't it scary?
Hello?
Okay I see.
We'll go back right away.
Come on, go to my home with me.
What's wrong?
Xing Yi went to see my dad.
Uncle Xing is also there.
We need to get there right now.
I don't need to appear right?
My future sister-in-law, you won't come with me?
Okay, okay!
Let's go.
Dad, Uncle Xing.
Hello, uncles.
Come here.
Dad, this is the person I want to marry.
Don't make such a joke.
It's a misunderstanding.
Su Nian,
what's going on?
Didn't you say that
you has been with Xing Yi?
I-
Xiao Su,
if Xing Yi didn't treat you nice,
tell me.
I will teach him a lesson for you.
It's not like that, uncle Xing.
Please listen to me.
Actually...
Dad, uncle Su,
the one dating Su Nian is my brother.
What did you say?
The one dating Su Nian is my brother,
your another son, Xing Ge.
Lao Xing,
didn’t Xing Ge leave home long ago?
How do you know that's him?
When I knew that I need to marry Su Nian,
I tried to get to know her,
so I asked someone to investigate her.
Sorry,
when I knew,
Su Nian has already been with my brother.
I need to talk to you privately.
He won't beat Xing Yi, will he?
That's his son,
of course he won't.
No,
why do you care about him so much?
I don't care about him.