Marry me, Mr. Xing
Hi handsome.
What's the matter, gorgeous?
What can I help you?
Is that guy Xing Ge?
No.
Over there,
that guy is Xing Ge.
Brother, I'm back.
Dad asked me to develop my career in China.
Good.
When will you come back home?
If you have nothing else to say,
I need to go.
Okay.
I won't keep you any longer.
Let's talk later.
Gorgeous, try to get him?
Is this how his name written?
Yeah.
But I have to remind you,
he is very hard to get.
Give me the strongest liquor here.
Good luck.
Handsome.
What's up?
Give me a chance to know you.
I'm not interested.
I heard that you are the boss of this bar.
Yeah.
So,
shouldn't the boss here
take care of your customer?
You will satisfy
your customer's need, won't you?
Er-well,
can you drink this?
Miss Su, no, no!
You have to do what I said.
You are afraid that I may put something in it?
Don't dare to drink it?
Let me drink it first.
No way! He bites the bait so soon.
Even kids won't use this trick.
You may die alone if you are such a boring person.
Are you sure he is Xing Ge,
but not a blind bear?
I'm sure, Miss Su.
Don't worry, I'll help you.
Gorgeous, you are alone here.
What are you doing? Go away.
Come on, let's have some drinks.
Leave me alone.
You are upset?
I can comfort you.
What are you doing? Let me go.
Gorgeous, wait for me a moment.
Hurts! It hurts!
Let me play with you.
If you don't let go, I will scream now.
I-
Brother Xing Brother Xing Brother Xing
Go away.
Yes, yes, sir.
Xing Ge,
now we can get to know each other, right?
Don't get me wrong.
I will help everyone in need.
After all, you helped me.
Let's go grab some midnight snacks.
Although I don't know why you tried to get close to me,
this method is low, don't bother to do that again.
What the hell?
Wait and see,
one day I will get you.
Doctor, how is my father doing?
The patient's condition is currently stable.
He need a good rest after this.
Thank you, doctor.
You're welcome.
Mom, don't worry.
Dad will be fine.
Miss Su.
What's going on in company?
Board of directors
has already known
you father got brain hemorrhage.
Now they are electing
an acting chairman.
They are so impatient.
Someone is adding fuel to the fire.
the person should be Cao Sipeng.
It should be Cao Sipeng
He is ambitious,
coveting Nianqiao Group for many years.
But my father's company must not fall into his hands.
Miss Su,
but your father Chairman Su also thought
Mr. Cao is a suitable candidate.
If you try to stop him,
you may offend many people.
Besides,
don't you remember your father's requirement for you?
I have my own solution for that.
Okay.
Morning, Miss Su.
Good morning, Miss Su.
How many times have I told you do not make my cringy!
I'm tired of it.
Okay, go back to work.
Xiao Nian, how is your father?
Thank you Uncle Cao for your concerns.
My father is fine.
He has received the best treatment in hospital.
Oh, that's good.
Tell your father stay at home to have a good rest.
And don't worry about the company.
I'm here to take care of our business.
Uncle Cao, you don't have to.
After all Nianqiao Group belongs to Su family.
I don't want to bother others.
I need to go, goodbye.
Miss Su, maybe you shouldn't
be that aggressive to him now?
Last month,
he lined his pockets from the project in Dongcheng district.
I think I'm tolerate enough.
Doesn’t he want to be the chairman of Nianqiao Group?
As long as my shares can be an absolute majority,
he can't get what he covets.
So you are going to
marry the guy your father asked you to marry?
Xing family doesn't have many shares,
but that part can play an play a decisive role.
How about the guy I asked you to investigate?
Miss Su, I tried my best.
And that's all you got?
Actually I only got three things about him.
I think it's unnecessary to write it down,
I can just tell you directly.
But-but I promise
I really tried my best.
This Mr. Xing has studied abroad since he was a kid,
so no one except his family knows about him.
Tell me then.
The man you need to marry is Xing-
Xing-Xing...
Xing Ge!
Yeah, Xing Ge.
185 cm,
fit,
handsome and charming.
That's all?
There is also another important thing.
After coming back China,
he has run a bar called Tingfeng.
A bar?
Xing Ge...
Which Ge is that in his name?
This is definitely not Ge.
This is Ge!
Can you really read and write?