Is it beautiful?
The yellow lights
are sparkling with energy.
With energy.
Want to have a contest?
To see who can keep it up longer.
Yeah.
I used to be afraid of happy times.
Because the more I enjoyed them,
the more it hurt when they were gone.
I knew that.
Or at least, I should have.
This is a story about the days
when I had an unseen love with you...
who would run beneath the clear sky.
[Episode 1]
My life motto is to avoid
getting deeply involved with people.
I have no interest
in having a rich campus life.
Kakeru, how was your summer break?
It was just okay.
Nothing special happened?
Not really.
Oh! Well, see you later then.
Hey.
Superficial chats and relationships.
That's all I need.
[Can you make it to
Haruto's third-year memorial service?]
Why do I have to go to your class reunion?
They said I could bring a friend.
We're just roommates.
Don't be like that!
Kakeru, you should enjoy college life too!
- Hey, guys!
- Hey.
That looks good!
Let's start with a beer!
Huh? Kakeru?
I can't believe you're here.
So Yuuko and Kakeru go way back, huh?
A touching reunion!
We see each other on campus.
But this is our first night out, right?
You must be happy too, Kakeru.
I'm even more determined to leave
after the first round.
- Why?
- Come on!
Ah, your glass. Twelve o'clock.
Thanks, Yuuko.
Do you have trouble seeing?
Yes, I do.
I can't see at all.
Hmm.
This is Koharu Fuyutsuki.
A bright-eyed freshman, and my best friend.
I've never been to a drinking party,
so I wanted to try it.
That's awesome.
I'm Ushio Narumi.
And sitting across from you is...
Kakeru.
Nice to meet you.
Excuse me. Oolong tea.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Kakeru, were you
in Cultural Anthropology this morning?
Huh? Yeah.
I knew it! I saw you leaving the classroom.
What a relief!
Why?
Well, I help Koharu with her classes.
The volunteer club helps out, too.
Oh?
But no one can make
the Monday morning class.
I've been really worried.
So, Kakeru, could you sit
with Koharu during class?
What?
Meet her at the student plaza
before class and guide her...
Wait.
Yuuko, you can't just...
But I'm worried!
Hey, you should just do it.
Please!
Okay?
Is that you, Kakeru?
Huh?
Thanks for coming today.
Right.
I'll get it.
Sorry about that.
Lost items are the worst
for the visually impaired.
I see.
I dropped a very important bookmark
the other day.
Oh.
Shall we go?
[Temporary Class Cancellation Notice]
[Course: Cultural Anthropology]
Class is canceled...
Huh?
Sorry, I should have checked.
No, I should have too.
Oh... Well, then...
Um...
If you'd like, let's kill time together
until the next class?
How did you know it was me earlier?
Huh?
You called out to me
before I said anything.
Oh, it was your footsteps.
Footsteps?
They sounded like
the ones I heard at the party.
Oh.
Huh?
Oh, sorry.
You just seem unique, Kakeru.
People are usually overly careful with me.
Like earlier,
people moved out of my way, right?
You noticed?
It always makes me feel bad.
So when someone like you just says
"Oh," and moves on,
it puts me at ease.
Oh.
What's that? What are you reading?
"The Margin and the Bloom"
by Shuntaro Asama.
The Margin and the Bloom?
You like it too, Kakeru?
Oh, no, not really.
It's just the first novel I ever read.
Really?
It's so thick in braille.
Want to try reading it?
One page of a normal book
becomes about twice as long in braille.
"In that town, this flower
always bloomed when winter came."
Can you read braille?
No, I just remember the line.
You must really love it.
Oh.
That's the first time I've heard you laugh.
Yeah.
I'm home.
Welcome back.
Dinner's almost ready.
Okay.
Did something good happen?
Not really.
Don't forget your medicine.
Okay.
[Dr. Miura]
Reading together on the terrace?
So youthful.
We were just killing time.
But you had fun, right?
Koharu was cool, wasn't she?
She's always so positive.
Wait, why are you here, Yuuko?
What's the big deal?
I used to come over all the time.
What? Are you two...
Why does your mind always go there?
I'm so jealous...
Sorry, gotta take this call.
Okay.
Hello?
Hey.
Has Kakeru always been like that?
Like what?
Well, he talks fine,
but he never lets you get closer.
It's like he doesn't want to enjoy himself.
This is Kakeru in high school.
Huh?
Whoa!
That's a million-watt smile!
It's you, and this is...
Kakeru's best friend.
Hmm.
But he was in an accident.
Huh?
Actually, I might not be able to go.
I have class.
But it's his third-year memorial.
Haruto's mom was asking if you'd come.
Sorry.
That's why Kakeru is scared of having fun.
[I'm sorry, something urgent came up
and I can't make it today.]
[Okay!]
Kakeru.
Hey.
Did something happen?
I heard from Koharu.
Can I quit this support stuff?
Huh?
Someone else can do it, right?
You just asked out of convenience.
Sorry. Find someone else.
Wait!
It's not just for my convenience!
Of course, I asked
because I was worried about Koharu.
But...
I also thought it might be good for you
to connect with someone, too.
I'm sorry.
Is someone there?
Kakeru?
What are you doing?
Apparently, anyone's allowed
to play this piano.
So I thought I'd try.
Believe it or not,
but I used to want to be a pianist.
Oh?
Are you wondering
how I can play without seeing?
Well...
Yeah.
Those memories are still there.
Losing something...
doesn't mean it all becomes zero.
My body remembers
how much I enjoyed playing back then.
Doesn't that...
feel painful?
Remembering when you could still see...
It was, at first.
I mean, I couldn't even get
toothpaste on my toothbrush.
I thought I was pathetic.
But then I realized something.
You can't change the past,
but how you accept what happened
is up to you.
The hurdles became much higher.
But that doesn't mean I can't clear them.
In fact, it feels amazing
when you manage to jump over them.
Whatever it takes...
Sounds. Smells. Old memories.
I'll use everything.
Watch me, okay?
Koharu!
Kakeru?
Sorry for missing class today.
And about the bookmark, too.
Huh?
I actually saw it.
When you dropped the bookmark.
But... I didn't pick it up.
I didn't want to get involved.
I see.
But you said it yourself earlier.
That losing something
doesn't mean it all becomes zero.
The bookmark...
It was still there.
Starting next week...
I'll go to class again.
Okay.
By the way...
Yes?
What was on that bookmark?
It was in braille, right?
It's a list of things
I want to do in my life.
Oh.
The first one is...
To play the piano again.
And the second?
This one is quite a high hurdle.
So it's worth it, right?
The second is...
Why?
Why is it always her?
Isn't it unfair?
It's still just a possibility.
It took so long...
It took so long
to finally start looking forward.
The second is...
setting off fireworks.
Fireworks?
That was...
the beginning of us.
Asakusa on Sunday?
Watch out.
Get caught? Your arm.
Interacting with people
means getting to know them, right?
For example, what would you like to know?
Why did you lose your sight?