Music
Sound Effects
What's the point of bleeding?
It's just blood.
But my powerful witch summoned the Great God!
Enough! Don't summon them again!
Hmph! You! Come out!
Hey! You're so weird when you summon them!
There are so many witches here and there.
Are you unable to summon new ones?
Unable?
The god of the South Plateau has taken over the Ji Sheng.
Come out!
Xuan Pu!
De Ling!
I told you not to summon the beauties,
but you didn't have to summon the old lady!
Take off the salt stone on the fruit!
Listen to my summon! Come out!
Xu Chang Shi!
Summon!
What's the problem now?
I said this is also a competition!
Did you see that?
I can summon him too!
So what?
You think my old lady is more powerful?
Which eye are you looking at?
My old man has already suppressed your old lady!
You bastard!
It seems that it's not going to work if you don't use your real power!
Deep in the South Plateau, the secret end of the ancient road!
They're saying the same spell in Song Chang.
The Hell-slaying Spell.
The Hell-slaying Spell can transfer the power of the One Sword.
If it fails, the power is enough to wipe out everything in the world.
Then...
If they use it together...
Both of them will die.
The spell recorded on the back door!
Come to my side!
Become my sword!
Become my flag!
No...
No!
Stop!
Stop fighting!
What are you doing, little flower?
You bastard!
Bastard!
Spell!
Destroy the Hell!
The Hell-slaying Spell
Are you crazy?
You suddenly rushed over and wanted to die!
I shouldn't have come!
I should have let your brother blow you up!
Do you know how disgusting it is to abandon a child?
This is his home!
I left him at home!
What's wrong with that?
You're being unreasonable!
Who cares?
What you said is not worth mentioning.
I won't hate him for such a small thing.
But...
That's right.
Such a small thing.
Shut up!
You mean...
You don't care that he abandoned you.
Then why did you...
Are you done?
I have to keep fighting!
Shut up!
What he did...
is more disgusting than this!
What else did he do?
The day we met...
The day the sea of the sky was so blue...
I was young and was about to pick up some poisonous mushrooms
and give them to the old ladies next door.
Suddenly, I saw...
Kill them!
The steam of the black snake and the dragon
took me to the
Lost World.
There,
they killed the demons of the three realms.
And I...
hid behind the bodies of the demons
and waited for them to finish the battle.
Go home.
Then I went to the Demon Lord
and asked him to take me home.
But where is he?
I see.
You're the one who killed the demons.
You came here from the three realms.
I'll take you home now.
I just wanted to go home.
Your...
Your home...
My home is in the sea of the sky!
So the demon said he would take you to the three realms
because he thought this was your home!
Yes, Zhang Zheng Shu Jie!
He did it for the sake of the
I can tell you!
But Zheng Zheng Shu Jie has never come back!
So you tried to open the three-dimensional passage
not to invade my three realms?
I just wanted to go home.
I see.
Go home!
You killed the demons!
You're the one who killed the demons!
Then I'll take you home now!
Now...
Go home?
Even if you say that, I won't forgive you!
So open the passage now!
I'm not looking forward to it!
He agreed.
Can you handle your current power?
Just call me when the passage is open.
Go, go!
Chun Hua, come here.
Lady, I'm leaving.
But...
I don't belong here.
I'm just a passer-by who borrowed the tree.
I'll leave everything in the three realms to you.
You will be the queen of this place from now on.
Take good care of this place.
You must do better than me.
Because this is your home.
The door is open!
Let's go!
You're too loyal to the rules.
You don't know how to change.
You have to change this.
You have to learn to smile when you meet again.
I...
command you.
She's still here!
Dongfang, you're here again!
What?
Do you want to take that thing back?
Hey, Demon, what the hell is she talking about?
I don't know.
The time you sent me to the Three Realms,
was it really your first time there?
Yes.
That's strange.
There are many legends about you in the Three Realms.
Even in the deepest part,
there are your statues.
Just legends.
Let's go, let's go.
Go?
You're leaving again?
You'll come back.
You'll come back to beg me!
You'll come back, Dongfang!
No one came at all.
Will the spell really work?
What you've been through won't be wrong.
Maybe...
The power?
Let's go.
Isn't there no one on the island?
Why is there such a huge power?
It's the Space Spell.
Someone's here.
The door can only be reached here.
It's the Demon Lord.
What does it mean?
Someone will come to say their favorite words.
Lord Wang Meng taught me that.
Sea...
Light...
The tree has fallen.
Finally...
I see light again.
You've been in the Three Realms for so long.
You've worked so hard.
The Three Realms?
This guy is...
You have no power.
You were a dead man in the past.
How can you take revenge for your life?
Don't worry.
Let's figure out why the Demon Lord
is with the Three Realms.
The sea water is so cold.
Are you feeling better?
I don't know.
I feel like I'm dreaming
when I see the real world.
But I won't forgive you so easily.
You're a weak old man.
Watch your words.
That's what they say in books.
He...
He just called me old man.
Yes, it's gossip.
The biggest gossip in the Three Realms.
The Demon Lord has a daughter in the Three Realms?
What is gossip?
The future is full of questions about unknown things.
They call the surprising news gossip.
The future is so amazing.
Come on.
Let's attack the Sea of Cangyan.
Now?
You just hit me.
You want to hit me again?
Can you eat?
I can't eat.
You're talking nonsense while bleeding.
I'm telling you.
You can't beat anyone in the Sea of Cangyan.
He can't?
I can.
It's just a fight in the Sea of Cangyan.
It's nothing.
But why do you fight in the Sea of Cangyan?
Because...
That's what I should say.
Get them!
Yes, get them!
Kill them!
You...
Fine.
What else can I say?
Let's go.
Come on out, gossip.
Follow me.
I, Long Hua.
Coming.
I used this when I was at the Sky Tower.
Let's go.
Hey, big wood.
You don't need to use your hands.
I don't want to use them.
I'm so weak.
We're going to fight in the Sea of Cangyan.
You're going too?
Where is he going?
Where am I going?
But...
You're so weak.
He'll protect me if you go.
I see.
Black Eye.
No way.
I'll kill you.
The Sea of Cangyan.
They...
They just left like that?
It's okay.
They brought out a Shadow Three-Dimension from that space gate.
Do you know what that means?
That gate is the way to the Shadow Three-Dimension.
We have no power.
So what?
This is a new style.
Hey, big wood.
I think we should take a break.
Your body...
It doesn't matter.
Don't be so anxious.
But...
You're bleeding.
Blood will stop eventually.
It stopped!
I can't see it!
Don't worry.
He's fine.
Why are you so sure?
According to the ancient books,
a creature like Dad can't be killed.
Did you imagine Dad as something strange?
How far do you think we can fly?
Big wood.
Hey!
Oh my god!
The Shadow Six-Eye and White Eye are dead!
The sky is far away.
It's a long way.
But it's okay to move to the Nine-Eye.
Big wood!
I finally found you!
I wasn't hurt.
But over there...
What happened?
Lord Mo Xi!
He was negotiating with Wang Wang.
They were chatting in Songbai Peak.
Suddenly, they were...
They were like this.
And then...
They disappeared.
Time and space spell.
How did you know?
I didn't say anything.
Lord Mo Xi's power is incomparable.
Wang Wang has to attack.
He can only attack with his time and space spell.
I...
I was looking for you.
I wanted you to use your heavenly eyes to find me.
How is Songbai Peak now?
Don't jump around and talk.
I'm tired.
Here's the thing.
Just now,
Songbai Peak was so loud.
Then, the sky was full of fire.
I'm telling you,
it's been a long time since that happened.
Do you know?
The whole Water Cloud Sky was shocked.
All the nearby immortals rushed to save people.
But suddenly,
there were several spirits of the Clouds on the top of Songbai Peak.
The fire of the day is burning.
The light of the day is spreading across the sky.
The stars are falling.
The wind is blowing in the clouds.
The dead are the only ones who can't come.
The phantom is coming.
The Four-Spirit Realm.
It seems Wang Wang has prepared for it.
Yes.
They summoned a huge seal.
The entire Songbai Peak has been sealed.
No one knows what happened inside.
Because no one can enter.
Wang Wang has taken Lord Mo Xi away.
Why should we wait for the seal at Songbai Peak?
Let's go and see first.
Stop!
Kill him!
The Drops of Thunder,
the
The magic power is ineffective.
This...
It's the effect of the barrier.
Ying Jie, you're here.
This...
Wu Cheng Sun, why haven't you broken this yet?
Hey, why didn't you tell me about my husband?
You can try it yourself if you're capable.
Yeah, this thing has no weakness.
If you break the barrier, it will be useless.
What?
You have a way?
I'll show you.
The barrier is broken.
As expected, breaking this barrier can only be done from within.
But we can't get in.
This...
I've found the living.
I won't let you go.
Open.
As expected, within this barrier,
you still can't use the Great Formation.
Four people, four pillars,
and the power of the four sides.
If you want to destroy this barrier,
you can only kill four people.
And...
as the eye of the eye, you.
But to kill me,
you have to rely on physical strength.
I don't know if you're ready.
The wall of the Luo family in the mountain of the mountain of the mountain of the mountain of the Luo family.
I didn't expect you to become a ghost of Yun Mengze.
And...
You seem to have found the phone
that you lost in the Sui Mo Yuni River.
Lord Wang Mang worked hard to get me.
I'm a man of great security.
The Qingyuan Army is 72 times more powerful.
But the gun method seems to be less than mine.
When I was human, I was proud and fearless.
I became a ghost and still didn't change my arrogance.
I'm going to teach you today.
The essence of the wall of the Luo family.
Please,
the young king of Luo City.
You can awaken Yue San.
The time of three realms collapse.
The old and the new.
The three realms are full of trouble.
The spring and the autumn are cold.
The time of three realms collapse.
Who will I fight with?
The wind blows in the future.
The sky is full of stars.
I'll stand in the field.