Music
You are looking for Chen Xiang?
In the mortal world, it's only a few places that can be avoided by the pursuit of water and sky.
I knew it since I was a child.
You mean...
Yes.
That's great! Thank you!
But even if you find him, why would he believe what I said?
He doesn't know me.
That's true.
I...
You mean the
Should I explain?
I'm afraid of the evil eye.
Actually...
After I leave, you must stop dad from going to the Sea of Cangyan.
You must wait for me to meet with you.
Can you do it?
I will kill the devil no matter what!
Absolutely!
Devil Lord's
I'm not angry!
Take care!
Okay.
Now I don't even have a speaker.
When will the devil wake up?
No, it's troublesome if he wakes up.
But if he doesn't wake up, I will be bored.
Devil Lord?
He must be attracted by my magic power.
He won't attack the little devil, right?
Forget it.
What's that?
It hurts!
What a trouble!
I can guess it.
As long as the little devil is in danger,
Dad will come out no matter what.
The night has come.
Come out, the devil of the Moon.
You devil!
Get out!
You!
Who tied me up on the shelf?
He... actually...
The little devil did it.
No matter how much you remember, he did everything.
Really?
It's my best friend.
All my friends call me a honest and cute little bird.
So you didn't do anything to me?
He did everything.
But my ability is limited and I can't stop him.
I'm sorry, little devil.
I was forced to do it.
Where is he?
He escaped for the sake of the devil.
He is afraid that you will wake up.
He is afraid that he won't.
I'm sorry.
He is afraid of me?
In the three realms, who is not afraid of the devil?
That's true.
I'm really too powerful.
It's a sacrifice to have no opponent.
I'm so embarrassed.
I'm sorry.
But it seems that I'm in trouble.
All right, don't care about that little devil.
Let's go to the vast sea of Cangyan.
No, no, no, no, no!
What do you mean?
It's...
You think I'm not strong enough?
No, you are very strong, but...
But?
Everyone knows that you are powerful.
The rest...
For example?
Swordsmanship.
For example, swordsmanship.
Everyone doesn't know how powerful your swordsmanship is.
Everyone doesn't know how powerful my swordsmanship is.
You keep using summoning.
Everyone will misunderstand you.
Don't you think so?
Speaking of which,
his Shufeng Sword should be taken.
His?
Then we should...
Stretch out your hand.
Gu...
Gu Lan?
You are...
I've found my power back.
Although the spell is still there, I can't use it easily.
But I don't need it to protect myself.
But the demon is the risk of taking the sword.
So you need it.
Demon is...
Taking the sword?
You promised not to go to Cangyan Sea first.
I want everyone to know that
the best swordsmanship in the three realms is not mine.
Yes, yes, yes.
The most powerful swordsmanship of the demon.
Come out, Black Demon.
Honorable, honorable.
You...
Where were you just now?
Did you see anything?
No.
Honorable sister, except for the magic power, I disappeared naturally.
Fortunately, I almost got caught.
Listen to my order.
Yes.
Dragon painting.
I said, Black Demon,
haven't you recovered your magic power?
Are you leaving or not?
I...
Come on.
I said, Black Demon,
haven't you recovered your magic power?
You...
Protection spell?
You are...
The demon is in the deep pool.
It's faster to go into the water.
But...
Black Demon,
head.
What are you yelling?
You can't get in with my protection spell.
So,
can I say it completely?
Say it.
Haven't you recovered your magic power?
Why don't you use the sword?
I did it on purpose.
You know, just now...
Have you already set your IQ on the meat?
Open the door.
Open it.
Turn around.
I...
It's really convenient to see the door.
But it lacks the scenery along the way.
You are so stubborn.
But this place is the same as before.
And it seems to be night and day.
Brother.
Do you want some new Dodo?
I...
Go, go, go.
One day,
I will destroy all the Dodo.
Yes, yes.
Dodo should have been destroyed long ago.
But did we get the sword back first?
What if someone stole it?
The magic is in the magic.
Who else can go except me?
That's the case.
So...
Shuo Feng was taken away?
Yes.
The sword was taken away as soon as it was made.
You dare to let others take the sword?
Today, all the heroes of the three realms will be killed.
No.
You took my sword.
My Lord is afraid that Shuo Feng sword will kill people with cold air.
So he came here to take Shuo Feng sword away.
He has been in the Snow Palace for a long time.
When he was in the Lianyao,
he sent a girl to pick him up.
What did you say?
I will take you to take the sword.
Can't you hear me?
You are so cruel.
I said I would take you to take your Shuo Feng.
You are the one who is cruel.
Your strategy is reliable.
You are crazy.
I will take you to take the sword.
You will be crazy, right?
I can't take it.
Take it.
You are crazy.
I am crazy.
Take it.
You are crazy.
You heard what you said.
So you took the sword?
Yes.
You know it's my sword.
You dare to take it without permission.
Your courage is not small.
I'm flattered.
But if you want to take back Shuo Feng sword,
you need to follow me.
I don't need you to take me.
I will go by myself.
You...
You know me?
No.
Then how can you go?
I hate you.
So I will go by myself.
But you don't know me.
So what?
Remember.
When I find your master,
you will be the first to mess him up.
Just leave like this?
It doesn't matter.
They took a shadow three-dimensional person from that space gate.
Do you know what it means?
That gate is the way to the shadow three-dimensional world.
We have no power.
So what?
I appreciate your temper.
This is the shadow three-dimensional world?
No.
It should be the way to the barrier.
Damn it.
How long will it take to reach the shadow three-dimensional world?
What's the hurry?
What?
You came from outside.
You have no power.
But you want to enter the shadow three-dimensional world.
Are you going to die?
You...
You are from the shadow three-dimensional world?
Yes.
I will kill you.
We don't know each other.
But you want to kill me.
How can you be so rude in the three-dimensional world?
No need for excuses.
I just want to kill the people in the shadow three-dimensional world.
Come up.
You...
Come down.
Come down?
You are a stupid guy who can't even fly.
Who said I couldn't come up?
Wait.
You seem to be able to understand people.
Do you want to negotiate?
What are you doing in the shadow three-dimensional world?
Revenge.
Kill all the people in the shadow three-dimensional world.
You are joking.
Very serious.
You can't do it.
Why?
A-Yin.
I can help you.
No.
Why?
Because you don't have a choice.
Now I am the highest ruler in the shadow three-dimensional world.
But I need to go to the three-dimensional world.
I need to be taken in.
You help me get in.
I will give the shadow three-dimensional world to you.
How to deal with it,
it's up to you.
Who are you?
You are so bold.
The current female emperor of the shadow three-dimensional world,
Zhang Chunhua.
I am curious.
You are so lonely.
What do you want to do in the three-dimensional world?
I have no desire.
I just want to follow someone.
This is a good reason.
The deal is accepted.
Negotiation is done.
The three-dimensional world
A shovel?
I only know that there is a shovel in the depth of the shadow three-dimensional world.
Dig it.
Maybe we will find it.
Do you really think we are the Kuli?
We are.
Do you think we are the Kuli?
Dig a hole and find mud.
Dig it.
The conditions are good.
Why don't you dig?
You want revenge, I don't need it.
Such a big knife,
how long will it take to dig?
It's collapsed.
It seems that there is another hole below.
Interesting.
I didn't expect that the inside of Qianyin Island is empty.
Why are there so many talismans?
Is this the real face of the formation of Qianyin Island?
No, look around carefully.
Is the arrangement of this place familiar?
It's the formation of Shuiyuntian.
There is a Shuiyuntian formation under Qianyin Island.
Interesting.
The arrangement seems to be a formation that secures the power to eliminate the pursuit.
The person who sets up the formation wants to hide something, right?
Maybe it's hiding himself.
The empty golden gate.
Looking at the place inside,
this gate leads to the three-dimensional world.
There is a seal in the gate.
This gate has been sealed to death.
This seal...
Could it be...
It's the God of War seal of Shuiyuntian.
That's right.
But when did Lord Jiuyuan...
It's not Jiuyuan.
This seal is from the internal seal.
Lord Jiuyuan has never been to the three realms.
How did he do it?
But the God of War seal is only the one I, Shuiyuntian, call God of War.
Could it be...
That's right.
It should be him.
After fighting with the Demon Lord, he disappeared from the three realms.
After that, the thousand realms disappeared.
He...
Could it be that he went to the three realms?
The God of War of the previous generation.
The God of War.
Brother.
Don't go.
Look at this two-dimensional horse.
Isn't it as cute as me?
The owner said that he could get the latest news and special benefits by scanning.
There are melons to eat together.
You mean...
Our world and people now have experienced five restartations.
No.
Not everyone.
Not all the worlds.
The Eastern Qing Cang never died.
Every time the world restarted,
it would wake up somewhere.
It just lost its memory.
And every time it woke up, the locations were the same.
The three realms were destroyed.
The three realms.
The End
Thank you for watching.