=Ancient Bracelet=
=Episode 23=
=Do You Wish to Be My Brother's Bride?=
I should find a place
to settle in first.
Wait.
Have we
met before?
Why do you feel so familiar to me?
Ying Du,
we...
(We were once deeply in love.)
You know my name.
(Indeed.)
(At this time, he hadn't met me.)
Yes.
I know more than just your name.
I know you are cool outside
but warm inside,
a fool who'd give his life for love.
A fool?
Come in.
Snow's falling hard.
Do you plan on standing
in the wild all day?
(Wuyue tribe)
Miss,
why are you crying nonstop?
Did my brother just make you cry?
I just...
I just miss home.
Every time I cry,
my brother picks plum blossoms
and makes sweet congee to cheer me up.
Du,
can you make some
for her
to cheer her up?
Little one,
he's your brother?
Then where are your parents?
Why
haven't I seen them around?
I've never met them.
I only have my brother.
Do you want to be my brother's bride?
I...
Well, I...
Little one,
what's your name?
Fengwu.
My brother gave me that name.
Feng as in whispering winds,
and Wu as in secret dealings.
What a coincidence.
Grandmother used to call me Fengwu too.
You shouldn't have come.
Your Majesty.
You can't change anything.
Why wager everything on one move?
But, Your Majesty,
Puluo State needs you.
(He is...)
(Luo Cheng of this lifetime.)
I spent three years
helping Puluo State end the turmoil,
turning a small frontier tribe
into what is now the Puluo State.
Puluo no longer needs me.
According to our pact, my duty now is
to protect Fengwu.
Your Majesty,
four years ago,
what kind of pact did you make
with the Goddess?
May I know the truth?
I promise
never again to disturb your life
with Fengwu.
Four years earlier,
Puluo suffered a crushing defeat.
Thousands of comrades
were trapped deep within enemy lines,
with their fate unknown.
To rescue them,
I sought the help of the Goddess.
I foresaw that my daughter
would face a fatal calamity.
If you are willing
to make a pact with me,
protect her forever,
and help her overcome all misfortune
after my death,
(Goddess Xingyue)
I shall grant you
my supreme power
to aid you through Puluo's crisis.
Do you accept that?
If it can bring thousands of soldiers
back to life,
I'll do whatever it takes.
I beg of you.
For Puluo State,
I have fulfilled my mission.
But for Fengwu,
I must protect her
and honor my promise.
Your Majesty,
I understand.
(Ying Du made a pact with the Goddess.)
(But why did he later become the ruler)
(and even cross paths with me?)
You've heard the whole story.
Still planning to hide?
Are you talking about me?
Who else could it be?
I...
I didn't mean to eavesdrop.
I just...
Just what?
I only wanted to know
what pact you made with the Goddess.
Who exactly are you?
Where did you come from?
Why do you know me so well?
I...
Du.
Careful now.
How did you get out?
Du, let her go.
She hasn't agreed
- to be your bride.
- Fengwu...
Bride? Fengwu is making that up.
We...
You can turn back time too?
Who exactly are you?
What's your name?
Zhaoli.
My name is Zhaoli.
Ying Du, don't forget me.
(Year 11 of Rongxi)
Why am I
still here?
What are you doing here?
You look so familiar.
Have we met
(9-year-old Fengwu)
somewhere before?
Zhaoli,
have you finished picking
the plum blossoms?
It's you.
I've waited for you for four years.
At last, you've come.
You've been waiting for me?
Zhaoli,
come here.
Ying Du, what did you just call her?
Zhaoli.
Four years ago, you suddenly vanished.
Since then,
in my brother's dreams,
he'd been calling your name,
lost and restless all day long.
So, I took the name Zhaoli.
That way, when he calls for Zhaoli,
he won't be reminded of you.
Since you refuse
to be my brother's bride,
please, stay away from him.
(Fengwu is Zhaoli,)
(which means me.)
Zhaoli, stop talking.
(Why don't I remember anything?)
(Could they be Ying Du and me)
(from another time and space?)
Zhaoli,
no matter what, you must trust Ying Du.
Do not harm him.
Promise me.
What are you talking about?
Do you remember?
♪Snow falls upon my brows,
blurring suddenly♪
♪Memories turn,
forgiving time after time♪
♪Tears or snowflakes, sweet or bitter♪
♪Hard to tell them apart♪
♪Vowing to give you
three lifetimes' happiness♪
♪In this life, I still run toward you♪
♪No matter the homeward journey♪
♪Falling to the deepest place
in your heart♪
♪And that is enough♪
♪Ahead lies a path without snow or wind♪
♪Begonia blooms across the branches♪
♪One more glance
may let love stand still♪
♪Snow falls upon my brows,
blurring suddenly♪
♪Memories turn,
forgiving time after time♪
♪Tears or snowflakes, sweet or bitter♪
♪Hard to tell them apart♪
♪Vowing to give you
three lifetimes' happiness♪
♪In this life, I still run toward you♪
♪No matter the homeward journey♪
♪Falling to the deepest place
in your heart♪
♪And that is enough♪
♪Ahead lies a path without snow or wind♪
♪Begonia blooms across the branches♪
♪One more glance
may let love stand still♪
♪One more glance may let love♪
♪Stand still♪