=Ancient Bracelet=
=Episode 17=
=It's Alright; I'm Here=
Hurry up, all of you.
Wu Luoluo?
Weren't you locked away in the dungeon?
How did you get out?
You even slipped me Boneless Powder.
You can still recognize me?
So, you're not entirely clueless.
As for how I got out,
that's none of your concern.
We are both women here.
Why use such underhanded means?
Underhanded?
Why not speak of your fickle ways?
As Che's wife,
you slept with the ruler.
I thought once you stayed
with the ruler,
Che would cast you aside,
so I used a little drug to help you.
Who would've thought
Che would care even more about you?
How could you drug me?
If I desired you,
I'd never stoop to such means.
So, it was you who drugged me.
You made me lose face before him.
I can make you suffer even more.
Once you're utterly disgraced,
the ruler will surely execute you,
the woman he deems impure.
By then,
when you're gone,
I'll be the one standing by Che's side.
One day,
he'll marry me.
My beauty,
don't you worry.
I'll be gentle with you.
Stay back!
Get away!
Let go of me!
Move aside!
Step away!
Don't touch me!
Zhaoli!
It's me.
I'm Ying Du.
Ying Du...
It's all right now.
I'm here.
Let's go.
Hurry!
Zhaoli.
You're safe now, Zhaoli.
It's over.
Let's go home.
It seems Ying Du
is not as powerful as before.
My chance has finally come.
Your Highness,
what should we do now?
If the ruler finds out,
he will never let me off.
Your Highness, I acted strictly
according to your instructions.
You will help me, won't you?
Rest assured.
With me here,
no harm will come to you.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Because I'll never
let the ruler catch you.
You can't even guard yourself,
yet you claim you can kill me.
That's a separate matter.
Thank you for saving me today.
Don't move.
Zhaoli,
you don't need to thank me.
No matter what happens,
I'll always keep you safe.
But you don't know a single move.
If one day I'm gone,
how will you protect yourself?
(Ying Du,)
(you slaughtered my people,)
(yet you shielded me)
(and saved me)
(from peril.)
(Which one of you is the real you?)
(Can I still trust you?)
(Zhaoli,)
(before the truth is known,)
(you can't trust him again.)
If you stop pestering me,
that will be the greatest protection.
But I can't help myself.
My heart belongs to you.
You rogue.
What are you doing?
The Bracelet is useless
to you right now.
I'll take it back for now.
When the time is right,
I'll return it to you.
Ying Du,
you clearly know everything,
yet you keep everything hidden.
And this.
You can't heal it yourself.
Does it have something to do
with the Bracelet's damage?
Are you concerned about me?
I'm asking why the Bracelet broke.
You keep saying I'm in danger;
you told me to stay away from Che.
Is it because he might harm me,
or are you trying to turn me
against him?
So, you'd rather doubt me
than believe I'm sincere toward you?
I just haven't seen it with my eyes.
I trust no one.
I'll make you believe me.
You should rest for now.
Your Majesty,
we've found the two
who insulted Zhaoli.
They are Lai and Hu
from the Wuyue tribe.
You summoned me.
What's the matter?
Come here.
Hu.
Lai.
What do you want to do to my people?
Ying Du, let me go.
Today, I'll teach you
a few self-defense moves.
For times when I'm not around,
they'll be enough to keep you safe.
Lai!
What are you doing?
You're out of your mind.
How could you use my hands
to harm my own people?
Try it.
Zhaoli.
Please, spare me.
Zhaoli, spare me.
Zhaoli.
No.
No, please.
Zhaoli.
Please, spare me.
They hurt you.
No.
Don't let your heart soften.
Zhaoli.
Please, don't kill me.
Zhaoli, please don't kill me.
- Zhaoli.
- Grandmother.
It's me, your grandmother.
Grandmother.
Ying Du killed Grandmother.
He killed Grandmother.
You killed Grandmother.
♪Snow falls upon my brows,
blurring suddenly♪
♪Memories turn,
forgiving time after time♪
♪Tears or snowflakes, sweet or bitter♪
♪Hard to tell them apart♪
♪Vowing to give you
three lifetimes' happiness♪
♪In this life, I still run toward you♪
♪No matter the homeward journey♪
♪Falling to the deepest place
in your heart♪
♪And that is enough♪
♪Ahead lies a path without snow or wind♪
♪Begonia blooms across the branches♪
♪One more glance
may let love stand still♪
♪Snow falls upon my brows,
blurring suddenly♪
♪Memories turn,
forgiving time after time♪
♪Tears or snowflakes, sweet or bitter♪
♪Hard to tell them apart♪
♪Vowing to give you
three lifetimes' happiness♪
♪In this life, I still run toward you♪
♪No matter the homeward journey♪
♪Falling to the deepest place
in your heart♪
♪And that is enough♪
♪Ahead lies a path without snow or wind♪
♪Begonia blooms across the branches♪
♪One more glance
may let love stand still♪
♪One more glance may let love♪
♪Stand still♪