Let’s register our marriage.
Rin… are you serious?
Yes.
And then…
After that…
We’ll have kids.
Rin…
Wait a second, Mai.
What’s this, Mai?
My usual chicken curry puffs from my favorite shop.
You’ve had this before, haven’t you, boss?
No, that’s not it. I mean…
Why do they smell a bit odd today?
Are they starting to spoil?
I don’t think so.
I just bought it. It came straight out of the oven.
Mai… but I think—
It’s about to spoil.
Really?
Boss...
are you okay?
Mai, curry puffs are incredibly strong.
Please take it away.
Okay.
I really feel unwell.
Boss…
Slowly.
Are you alright?
I have an inhaler here.
Easy now and take a deep breath.
Just the smell of food makes you want to throw up?
And that ‘family heir project’ you said you were working on…
Have you checked again yet whether it worked or not?
You’re never like this normally.
It’s just like when…
My little sister was pregnant with her first son.
Then should I go get Khem?
I’ll tell her you’re not feeling well.
It’s fine. I’ll call her up myself.
You may now go back to work, Mai.
Then I’ll postpone the marketing meeting…
for about an hour.
So you can rest a bit if you’re still not better.
Since we decided to have children,
we registered our marriage,
and attentively started looking for a specialized clinic overseas
to conceive twins.
Khom and I chose a Japanese sperm donor
so our children would resemble us as much as possible.
The eggs were Khemjira’s,
because she didn’t want the burden to fall on me alone.
No matter what happens,
these children
are still the children of both of us.
Khem,
You scared me!
By the way,
Whose flowers are those?
They’re for my wife, of course.
It’s Valentine’s Day today.
They were selling them at the café.
So I bought one for you.
I actually wanted to buy a whole bouquet, but…
I’m sorry.
I completely forgot.
That today is Valentine’s Day.
And I don’t have anything for you.
It’s okay.
You don’t have to worry about it.
This evening,
we can go out to eat together.
Thank you.
And…
You called me over here,
Do you have instructions for the staff today, Boss?
No.
I just…
I want to smell my husband's scent.
It’s so comforting.
You just want my scent?
But…
I’m working right now.
People might say I’m slacking off using my CEO-husband privileges.
I just want to smell you.
Five or ten minutes won’t hurt.
Are you getting exhausted?
Want something sweet to boost your energy?
No, it’s fine.
It’s just that…
The baby makes me crave your scent.
Huh…?
Did you forget?
I have a pregnancy checkup today.
I didn’t forget.
But…
I thought you’d test at home.
You already tested?
What was the result?
Did it work?
Are you in pain anywhere?
Are you okay, Rin?
This…
Isn’t that a COVID test kit?
Hey.
No.
It’s just…
I’ve been feeling unwell for the past few days.
I’m pregnant.
Rin…
I’m so happy.
I’m happy too.
I haven’t been able to focus on work at all.
Before I managed to call you…
I had to pull myself together for a long time.
Should I go see a doctor right away?
Yes.
The sooner, the better.
Have you told your father yet?
Not yet.
You’re the first person I told.
Then…
Rin,
should we go to the hospital now?
Let me come with you.
Please.
Are you free right now?
I am.
I just finished clearing my work.
I’ll ask my department head for a short leave.
Okay?
Please.
Rin…
Rin...Rin
Slow down.
No, I’ll carry it for you.
You know,
I’m pregnant…
I’m not an elderly.
Sure
Walk slowly, Rin.
This evening, come up to see me.
Then we’ll go out to eat together.
Khem!
Get up right now!
Why are you lying on the floor? It’s dirty.
Khem!
I’m just so happy.
I don’t know how to act.
We’re really going to have children now.
And I’m still this young.
I don’t know if I’ll be able to raise them properly.
You have to help me, okay?
Please
I know.
Well,
About what you said earlier…
that you’d come see me every hour,
that’s a bit too much.
Come only when you’re free.
If you’re busy, it’s fine.
Absolutely no skipping work.
Or I’ll lecture you myself.
Yes…
May I show this to everyone.
Please
Baby…
What do you think, baby?
Is Mommy beautiful?
My cheeks are bruised already.
So, how is it?
Busy lately?
Not really.
Unless someone calls me over just to tease me.
But even if they do,
I don’t mind.
Because I want to see my wife and our children.
Then call me over to tease me often.
No.
I already told you.
You can see me any time
But, only come when you're free.
Can I say something?
I want a rich wife.
I don’t want to work anymore.
I want to stay home with my wife and still get paid.
I’ll guard my wife twenty-four hours a day.
Hey.
I’m not fish at a market stall.
No one’s going to snatch me away like that.
And even if they tried,
I wouldn’t go.
Why?
Because…
You already love me, right?
Ugh.
So full of yourself.
But do you love me?
Of course I do.
My little puppy.
I love you too.
Love you so much
And more than anything.
Then…
between me and the kids,
who do you love more?
You're my number 1
Romantically speaking.
What kind of answer is that?
Khem, wait for me now!
I wonder what the kids will look like…
What are you doing?
Why are you smiling to yourself?
I’m looking at pictures of our babies.
I accidentally showed everyone too.
And they all said
our kids are really cute.
Really?
So you took advantage and stole a kiss from me just now?
Well, you’ve done it amazingly.
All three of you are strong and healthy.
The doctor couldn’t stop praising you.
Isn’t it because you took such good care of me?
You’ve been so attentive.
You look after me, indulge me,
and you’ve followed every guideline the doctor gave us.
You’re really good at this.
Because I love you and our children.
Then…
Right now, I want to watch a series.
Can you help me find something to watch?
Of course.
I’ll find a channel for you.
I’ll take the best care of our children, Khem.
Khem…
Khem, I can’t take this pain anymore.
Rin!
Rin, what’s wrong?
Khem…
Yes?
All of a sudden, my stomach really hurts.
Stomach pain?
Or…
Are our little troublemakers about to come out?
I don’t know.
Go get someone. Anyone.
Wait here for a second, Rin.
You, go call my father. Anyone. Hurry.
Okay, okay.
Come help me!
I’ll go get your father first.
Uncle,
is she about to give birth?
Not yet.
Khem is still inside.
Once everything’s settled, she’ll come out.
Please let everything go smoothly.
Amen.
Khwanrin.
Yes?
How’s work been lately?
Well…
It’s been okay.
Not too exhausting,
but not exactly easy either.
Would you mind
if I asked you
to quit your full-time job
and help take care of the kids?
What?
I’ll need to hire a nanny anyway.
And if there’s someone
I trust the most,
it’s you.
I still have to run the company.
Khem has to work too.
And for Rin,
she probably can’t manage two babies alone.
But I have a full-time job, Uncle…
Regarding your experience
You’ve taken such good care of my daughter-in-law.
That’s why I want you to be the nanny.
Help look after the kids
until they start school.
After that, if you want to work again,
you can come work at my company instead.
I just want someone I can trust
to help care for my grandchildren.
Alright.
I’ll help Rin take care of the children myself.
Thank you.
You're welcome
Khem,
how is it?
Is everyone safe?
Everyone’s fine, Dad.
Rin should be coming out soon.
Your grandchildren are very strong.
The granddaughter came out first,
then the grandson.
They look just like Khem and Rin.
I’m so excited
I probably won’t be able to sleep tonight.
In that case,
At...
tomorrow morning
I’ll go make merit for your mother.
Let me go with you, Dad.
I don’t think I’ll be able to sleep either.
Of course.
I’m so happy for you, Khem.
I just spoke with Uncle earlier.
I told him I’d help take care of the kids.
Thank you, Sister Rin.
Shall we wait to see the babies together?
They should be out soon.
I can’t wait to see them.
So exciting
Khwanrin.
Yes?
I’m entrusting my children to you.
Of course, Rin.
Please take care of them, Sister Rin.
I will.
Thank you.
Anytime.
Everyone,
today
I have an important announcement.
From now on,
our group of companies
will have a new CEO
to take my place.
Phraenarin,
My daughter.
Thank you, Father.
Come here.
Thank you, Dad.
Well,
I’m excited
and deeply honored.
I promise
with me
to work hard,
to develop the company,
to listen to opinions,
and respect differing views.
I’ll make sure
everyone receives bonuses every three months.
And not just that,
I'll include
other additional benefits as well.
For example,
Mental health leave,
gender-affirming surgery leave,
childcare leave,
birthday leave,
Or even leave...
for hangover
or to go see
your favorite artist.
I'm cool with that,
but at least,
notify me three days in advance,
so you don’t have to keep submitting medical certificates.
Most importantly,
I will respect
the basic rights
of every employee.
Thank you.
Thank you, Dad.
You did great, my child.
Come here.
Quick
Congratulations, Wifey
May I come in?
Anytime.
Sorry, we’re a bit loud.
Your dream finally came true.
Eventually, this friend of ours
has got adorable kids,
a wonderful husband,
and also
the position you always wanted.
This year is truly your golden year.
We’re so proud of you, Rin.
Seriously.
Soon we’ll probably see
a female CEO carrying her twins to the office.
Let’s take a picture.
Okay.
My arms are too short.
Seriously?
I do it better.
So take it!
Put on the crown.
Do we really have to do this?
Come on.
Like.
One, two, three.
Okay
Khem
Yes?
I think
our CEO seems tired.
Why don’t you take her to rest, Khem?
Of course, Dad.
Excuse us.
We need rest
Thank you, Dad.
See you later.
Please take care of my friend.
Be classy
and behave!
If there hadn’t been so many guests,
I would’ve carried you already.
What are you saying?
You’re exaggerating.
Well,
I’m just deeply in love.
Don’t you know that?
A woman like you, Rin,
the more age you attain
the more beautiful you are.
The more time passes, the more I love you.
Ugh,
You flatterer.
Before this,
you used to tease me
about getting old.
Rest for a bit.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Lie down for a moment.
Do you feel better?
A little.
I’m just tired.
Yesterday I was busy at work,
then I had to take care of the kids.
Oh,
Once today is over,
everything will calm down again.
Then
rest for a bit.
But
the babies need to eat soon.
I'm afraid they're being difficult
It’s fine; they’ll be okay.
No…
Can I..
lean here for a moment?
Are you happy lately?
I am.
Very happy.
You and the kids
make me truly happy.
Even if I’m tired,
I’m happy.
You’re amazing, Rin.
I’ll help you more from now on.
I have a question.
What is it?
Well,
Actually,
I asked you this before the babies were born.
Now that they’re here,
I want to ask again.
Between
me and the children,
who do you love more?
That’s a hard question.
Well,
It’s okay.
Umm,
Just answer honestly.
If I said
I love the kids more than you,
would you be upset?
And what if
I said
I love you more than the kids?
Either way is fine.
But no matter what,
I want you to know this.
I love you and our children
more than my own life.
Hey
You’re such a smooth talker.
People might think I have a third child.
Who would mistake that?
Hey,
I’m your husband.
Alright.
Can I rest my eyes for a bit?
Of course.
Khem.
Yes?
I love you and our children so much.
Do you know that?
I love you and the kids
with my whole life.
How lucky am I to be your bride?
Hey, where are you going?
I’m not going anywhere.
I’m going to eat.
You’re carrying food already.
Didn’t you say at lunch we have talk to talk?
that salesperson who snapped at you,
I really want to know how she looked like.
Hold up
Spill it
Fine, Hong
Just get up first.
I’ll confess.
I want to eat with my wife.
And I want to see my kids.
As for gossip,
let’s do it later at work.
Just in case that Jay and Balloon join us
It wouldn't be that spicy if there're only us two
Fine, go.
Don’t forget
to say hi to Rin for me.
I will.
See you later.
Bye
Rin will be so proud.
Mrs. Wifey,
I missed you so much.
My cheeks are covered in your lipstick.
I miss you and the kids.
This is your third visit today.
My cheeks are bruised.
I miss you every time.
If I could swallow you whole,
I would’ve done it already.
You’re ridiculous.
Are the kids fussy today?
Did they bother your working?
Not really.
They’re well-behaved.
You know,
When they’re full,
they sleep.
If not, they just lie there babbling.
Hey, little ones.
Are you cold?
Don’t kick off the blanket.
Go to sleep.
Khem,
eat first, then come play with the kids.
They’re not fussy at all, see?
They’re adorable.
Well,
Rin.
Hmm?
I made you an omelet too.
Oh,
It smells so good.
Thank you.
Eat a lot, okay?
So you’ll have enough milk.
For nowadays,
Isn’t it already a lot?
It is.
But I..
want it to last until they’re fully weaned.
I like watching you feed them,
You pervert
I'm not
I just really like watching you feed our kids,
I think it’s cute.
Those tiny mouths…
drinking from breasts
it’s adorable.
But if I stare at your chest at other times,
you can call me perverted.
No complaints.
You are...
indescribable
Rin, that hurts.
Khem.
Yes?
Shall we go out to eat today?
I already asked Khwanrin to watch the kids.
Our wedding anniversary,
Isn't it?
Yes
Let’s have some nice foods at the night market.
I want to experience life
the way you did when you were young.
Okay.
I’ll take you back in time.
How's it going?
Careful what you'd wished for
Go!
Do it!
Khem, be careful.
The smell is nice.
What Is it?
Rin...
There’s so much food here.
You sit and save a table.
I’ll go buy something.
Wait here.
I’ll be right back.
Hurry back.
Boo!
Looking tasty
I'm back.
Careful!
Rin,
here you are
I bought orange juice for you beautiful.
It smells nice, didn't it?
Agree
Here, Flamingo sausage.
Do you know why
it’s called that?
Look at them
their color is like a flamingo.
as if they made of flamingo meat.
My last warnings,
It’s so good that you could shoots light out of your mouth.
Try it, if you're in doubt.
Nope
I’m scared.
Come on.
I’ll feed you.
Khem
Yes?
No more teasing now
Yum
How is it?
It’s really good.
I like it.
Do you like the sausage?
I like you.
I like being anywhere as long as you’re there.
Me too.
Khem...
Yes?
I'll be back soon,
Wait here for a moment.
Where are you going?
Just wait.
It won't be long.
Be here
Sit here
and eat here
She'll be back
Okay.
Leave some for me.
Rin, be back quickly
Khem...
Rin...
Happy third anniversary.
My puppy girl...
You?
what are you doing?
The flowers might poke your eye.
I’m shy.
Thank you, Rin
So,
When did you prepare this?
I don't know anything
I had someone help.
Rin,
Wait here, I’ll be right back.
Hey,
shouldn’t you put the flowers down?
No.
What are you up to?
Khem,
what are you doing?
Everyone’s staring.
Stand up as usual, please
No
Khemjira!
Why are you so loud now
I love you the most in the world.
I love you too, Khomjira.
Wait…
Why...
I prepared something for you too.
I asked Jay and Balloon to help.
which costs me to pay for their somtum
What a coincidence.
We really think alike.
Not only flowers,
but hydrangeas too.
Thank you,Khem
Because we’re a perfect match.
Do you know what hydrangeas mean?
Of course.
That’s why I chose them.
I like that.
You like them too, right?
Yes
I really do.
Even if this place isn’t romantic,
but
I’m happiest being with you.
Me too.
And I think it’s nice.
So many witnesses to our love.
Khem.
Yes?
Will you marry me?
But we’re already married.
Here it is
Our wedding ring
Well, it wasn't...
I know back then,
I married you
without loving you.
The wedding was terrible.
I didn’t honor you at all.
No good couple photos.
Even when we took them, I was reluctant.
Back then...
My kiss was unknowingly bad
But now,
I can say it clearly.
I love you very much.
Khem.
Yes?
Marry me again.
When…when do you want to?
20th of the next month.
Isn’t that too sudden?
Why?
Aren’t you ready?
My heart is ready,
But
my body isn’t.
Well,
I gained weight.
I’m afraid I won’t look good in the dress
Hey
You’ve always been beautiful.
Listen to me,
This body will look great in a wedding dress
Even look better
than the first wedding.
Trust me.
Does it mean
that you were already attracted to me back then?
When you claimed you didn't love me
or didn't like me,
You've had feeling for me a little,
But you were in denial.
Okay, okay.
If you say I’m beautiful,
then I’ll believe it.
Then
let’s get married again.
Let me help plan everything,
So,
the mother of our children won’t be too tired.
Thank you.
I love you, Khemjira.
Very much.
I love you too, Rin.