Prae.
Please marry Wichan.
But I don't love Mr. Wichan anymore.
I love you.
I love you too, Prae.
I love you very much.
Shall we go now, Mr. Rut?
Hello, Ms. Praewilai.
Please don't do this again.
If you want to go somewhere,
tell me first. I won't stop you.
If it could be like that, it'd be good.
Then it has to be like that.
I won't let you go anywhere alone
and have something like this happen again.
Thank you.
Yes.
- Nong.
- Yes?
If I were to talk about Warat
with Sin, what do you think?
What did you say?
Sin is the vengeful type.
All he thinks about
is destroying the Vanich family.
I'm afraid.
Afraid he might hurt Warat.
If you're thinking of doing that
to protect Warat,
I think it won't work.
Don't forget that even if Sin knows
Warat is really your son,
he won't change his mind.
The person he truly hates
is Praewilai, Warat's mother.
What if I offer
half of Warat's share
of the assets to Sin?
Why would Sin take just half,
when he clearly has
the right to take everything?
Nong.
How many times do I have to tell you?
I will never let that happen.
Don't get angry yet.
Calm down. No matter what,
I'm on your side.
I will try to talk Sin into it.
The best way is
to make those two reconcile.
Sin gets his share,
and Mr. Warat gets what belongs to him.
If it could be like that,
it would be wonderful.
Then I could finally die in peace.
I understand.
Thank you.
Rest now, please. Take your medicine.
You heard it, didn't you?
So we just keep doing our part.
I'm not telling you to stop.
And I still insist
I'll do everything to let Naree,
your mother, rest in peace.
Even if you hadn't said anything,
I'd still do it anyway.
For now, just do what Uncle Rut wants.
And the day Warat gets everything
from Vanich Mall,
that day will be ours.
If I hadn't heard everything today,
it would've been hard for me
to bring myself to do it.
That's why I wanted you to hear it
straight from Mr. Rut's mouth.
Alright, Auntie.
Mrs. Wanee already adores me.
The more I support Warat,
the more she'll trust me.
So,
you handle everything
on your side as much as you can.
It's a win-win for us, Auntie.
Aunt Nong, I really hate
coming around here. It smells so bad.
That's the smell of my flowers.
What, Sin?
You've smelled it since you were a kid
and you're still not used to it?
Auntie, that's clearly a rotting smell.
I can't take it anymore. I'm leaving.
You sure you can drive?
If I say I can, then I can.
I usually don't drive
because I have my reasons.
And the reason is?
Uh, I'll tell you later.
But for now, can you check the pin
for Grandma Aom's house again?
See if there's another route.
I think there's an accident up ahead.
We should change routes.
There, see? One already.
What did you see?
Nothing. Nothing at all.
Hey, Kluay, you're driving.
Why are you closing your eyes?
- I'm sending merit.
- Huh?
Sending merit?
Yes. When I drive,
I have to concentrate a lot.
And I'll see things…
And when I see things,
I have to send merit.
Sometimes it works, but I have to do it.
So what do you see now?
Full force.
Pull over. I'll take off the cast.
Are you sure?
Of course.
You're driving with your eyes closed.
I'm not risking my life. Pull over.
Okay.
Don't go looking for them again.
They'll think you want to see them.
Don't scold me.
I don't want to see them at all.
Honestly,
your special power is pretty cool.
It comes and goes whenever it wants.
You see things all the time.
It's a miracle you haven't died of shock.
Thank you for the blessing.
But about Ms. Mysterious,
I've figured out the pattern.
I need to touch you,
or touch something related to the past
to see visions.
You need concentration too, right?
You learn fast.
Are you being sarcastic?
But when you…
took off my cast,
you didn't see anything, did you?
How do you know I didn't?
Maybe I did, but I just didn't tell you.
Someone like you
wouldn't be able to lie to anyone.
You talk like you know me so well.
Then try telling me.
What kind of person am I?
I don't waste time meddling
in other people's lives. I'm busy.
Alright.
Ugh, again.
Here we go again.
Ugh.
It's okay, it's okay. Don't be scared.
Are they gone?
They're gone.
It's around here.
But the house number doesn't match.
What do you expect
from the location on the phone?
Let's just get out and ask the locals.
Where are they?
The locals you said we'd ask.
I'm looking right now. Just a second.
Hey.
Excuse me, Grandma.
Do you happen to know Grandma Aom?
That's me. I'm Grandma Aom.
That's great. What a coincidence. I…
Here we go again, Kluay.
You can no longer tell
who's a ghost and who's a person?
Sometimes I can, sometimes I can't.
Can I really rely on you?
Thank you.
She's just a playful old lady.
You still praise her?
Let's go. I feel strange.
It's really hot too.
How can we leave?
Since we're already here,
I think I'll ask around a bit more.
What are you smiling at?
There's only one amulet.
Oh, right.
Then let's go together. Come on.
- Grandma Aom?
- Yes.
Grandma Aom Thongsawat.
Her mother's name was Muat Thongsawat,
and her father was Suan Thongsawat.
I don't know her.
But that surname sounds familiar.
You can try driving
about ten kilometers out of town
and you'll reach a village.
People's surnames there start with Thong.
Thongsawat, Thongkon,
Thongnamthip. People around there
all have Thong surnames.
Thank… Oh.
Thank you.
Ten kilometers?
No way I'm going along with that.
And we still have to ask around
about Grandma Aom. I think it'll be late.
Then stay here for a night.
How did he hear that?
Is that a person or what?
He's a person. It's nothing.
He probably just wants customers.
Honestly, staying one night sounds fine.
Help support them a bit.
With the economy like this,
just surviving is impressive enough.
Okay then, let's flip a coin.
If it's heads, we stay here and deal with
Grandma Aom first thing in the morning.
If it's tails, we go back to Bangkok first
and drive back again tomorrow morning.
So you want me to go back
to being the same again?
Take the cast off, put it back on.
You go back to seeing ghosts again.
Just thinking about it is exhausting.
Alright, heads it is.
Let's get it over with.
We're staying here.
Hey.
Should we change hotels?
I don't think there's anything.
Don't overthink it.
What if there's something?
Your room looks nice.
Your room is over there, sir.
The rooms are right next to each other.
You checked properly, right?
There's no room
with two beds,
a twin or anything like that?
No, ma'am.
They're all fully booked.
Oh.
Didn't you say you didn't see anything?
Not seeing doesn't mean
there's nothing there.
Come on. If anything happens,
you can knock on my door
anytime tonight, okay?
Mr. Warat, I think
you should wear the amulet.
No need.
You're the one who sees things, not me.
Good night.
Wow, that looks really tasty.
Tell me first who did that to Kluay,
or you don't get to eat.
I already told you.
Just some Karen.
So this is how you're going to be, Arnon?
Fine. I'll investigate it myself.
I'll just call the fake news unit
and dig and dig until I find the culprit.
Alright, alright.
I'll tell you.
But Kluay told me not to tell anyone.
See? You lied to me, didn't you?
- I'll put the whole plate into your mouth.
- Som, Som, don't.
- Why did you do this? Why lie to me?
- Som, it hurts.
- I just can't say it.
- What's all the noise?
Why were you yelling at him like that?
I can hear you
all the way from the prayer room.
Hello, Mama Toi.
You came just in time to help.
Oh? You're tattling now?
That's enough, Som.
Mr. Arnon, don't indulge her too much.
She plays rough and never holds back.
Yes, I'll remember that.
So what's going on?
Don't tell me it's about Kluay.
- No, it's nothing.
- No.
It's really nothing, Mom. Kluay is fine.
You didn't hear or see anything, did you?
What happened? What do you mean?
Som was just asking, just in case.
In case you were missing Ms. Kluay. Right?
- Yes, yes.
- Yes.
It's late now. Let him go rest.
Who tied his legs up?
He won't go back on his own.
I'll take my leave then.
Mama Toi, goodbye.
- Goodbye. Uh, Mr. Arnon.
- Yes?
Will you come here tomorrow?
Is there something
you'd like me to help with?
Let's talk tomorrow. Thank you very much.
- Alright. Goodbye again.
- Goodbye.
Wait, Mom.
What did you want to talk to Arnon about?
About Kluay.
I want him to help investigate
her parents. Uh…
No, Mom, don't do this.
Kluay is my sister.
I won't let her go anywhere.
It's not like that, Som.
- Listen to me.
- I'm not listening.
Did you forget
that Dad died because of things like this?
I don't want it to happen again.
I feel sorry for Kluay.
Som. Som.
Is this what you call nice?
Why does Mr. Warat
praise this place so much?
Please don't let me run into anything.
It's Mr. Warat's room.
Who is he talking to?
Oh, so this is why
he wouldn't let me stay in the same room.
Uh, why is he like this?
WARAT
Hello? You still have time to call me?
I just realized
what kind of person you are.
Good. Now you know.
Go wherever you want. Don't bother me.
What? Mr. Warat,
why are you talking to me like this?
I'm sick of you. Stay away from me.
I hate you.
Hey. Are you out of your mind?
What did I do to you?
Hello? Mr. Warat?
What's wrong with him?
He didn't have to show the girl
how much he hates me.
He's crazy.
Or…
Uh, what's that plate?
He ordered food, ma'am.
Then why are there two plates?
Why didn't he answer?
Mr. Arnon.
I'll ask Mr. Arnon to help talk to him.
Now my battery dies?
And I didn't bring my charger.
Whoa.
Excuse me, sorry, is anyone there?
I'd like to borrow a charger.
What should I do?
Excuse me, sir.
Are there any shops open around here?
They're all closed, kid.
People here go to bed early.
You're from somewhere else?
Yes, I'm from Bangkok.
Again?
What do you mean by that?
No one stays here.
Only people who get lost wander in.
If there's a man,
you should go somewhere else if possible.
- The widow ghost will take his soul.
- Huh?
- They have ghosts here.
Mr. Warat.
Hey, what did you put in my friend's food?
Why is he knocked out like this?
I'm asking you. Answer me.
Do you know this is illegal?
I'll call the police.
I'll make sure you pay for this.
Mr. Warat. Mr. Warat.
Mr. Warat, can you hear me?
Mr. Warat. Mr. Warat, can you hear me?
One, two, three.
Ow, Mr. Warat.
How can they do this in movies?
What do I do now?
Yes.
Oh god, this is a total disaster.
Fighting people in the morning,
fighting ghosts at night.
You can do it. You can do it.
Mr. Warat.
Mr. Warat. Mr. Warat. Mr. Warat.
Mr. Warat, wake up.
Hey, Mr. Warat.
Mr. Warat.
Let's just stay out of each other's lives.
You have no right to this man.
The reason you're stuck in this loop
is because you won't stop the karma.
Go. And I'll make merit for you.
Mr. Warat, wake up already. Wake up.
Don't do that. You can't do that.
He's my husband.
Go on if…
you want to receive a full-on punishment
in hell. Do you know
that stealing someone else's husband
means climbing the spiky fig tree?
Huh? Still not stopping?
You still don't believe me, do you?
Fine. Look at this.
Ugh, why do I
have to do something like this?
Mr. Warat.
I told you not to stay here.
Ow, you ignored me.
Hey.
Are you really that scared of ghosts?
Kluay.
Kluay, wake up.
Morning? Morning what?
What's wrong with her?
Please check it for me.
I'll write up a report and send it later.
Okay, thank you very much.
Just because there's no twin bed,
you're filing a complaint
against the hotel?
Yes. I can't let it slide.
You're really something, you know that?
Didn't you say
you didn't want trouble with anyone?
With people, yes.
But with ghosts, I'm not so sure.
You still haven't told me.
Why did you come sleep
in my room last night?
You still have the nerve to ask?
You're so charming, aren't you?
Why take your anger
at the hotel out on me?
Don't tell me
you did something to me last night.
What? Are you crazy?
What could I possibly do to you?
I was just scared of ghosts, so I went
to sleep in your room. That's it.
We're here.
The intersection up ahead
is the entrance to Grandma Aom's village.
I'm sorry, Mom,
for not calling ahead first.
I thought Mr. Warat had returned home,
so I stopped by.
It's alright.
Rat only called to tell me last night
that he'd be staying overnight
at the worksite in Hua Hin.
And when I saw that
Kluay went with him, I felt at ease.
That's good, very good, Mom.
Ms. Kluay is helping look after him.
With Mr. Warat's business background
and Kluay assisting with so many things,
I think many good things
will happen for Vanich.
Still, I can't help worrying a little.
You're all still new.
Most importantly,
you need to take it slow.
Adjust gradually.
Forgive each other when things get rough.
Yes, Mom.
Seeing this,
I feel relieved.
Thank you, Sin, for looking out for Warat.
Yes.
I feel the same as you do, Supol.
With the utmost respect, ma'am,
I wouldn't have thought
much of it before this.
But once I learned that Mr. Jirasin
is connected to Mr. Sarut and his wife,
I felt we should perhaps
keep an eye on them, shouldn't we?
When we took Jirasin and his sister
into the care of the Vanich Fund,
no relatives ever showed up.
Yes, ma'am.
And now, Mr. Sarut, his uncle-in-law
and Ms. Anong, his biological aunt,
have suddenly appeared. That's why I think
we should observe them a bit longer.
But there are positive signs.
Sin has shown kindness.
He even brought gifts to visit Rat here.
I'm very tired already.
If there's something
we can compromise on, let's do it.
If it helps put my mind at ease
and lets the younger generation
take over Vanich,
that would be good for me.
Yes, ma'am.
Hello.
After quitting work
at a wealthy household in Bangkok,
Grandma Aom moved here
over twenty years ago.
At that time, I was working in the city
and didn't know much about her.
You can talk to her yourselves.
- Thank you.
- She should be awake by now.
Careful, Grandma.
Oh, Grandma.
Mr. Warat, are you doing well?
And did Madam come too?
It's just the two of us.
You know me too, Grandma?
Of course I do.
You're… Mr. Warat.
And this is …
Miss…
Thank you so much for coming all this way.
If Som knew,
she'd definitely be angry with you.
Don't worry about her. I can handle it.
Alright, I'll get straight to the point.
So you don't have to waste your time.
Sure.
It's about Kluay.
Honestly,
I'm not comfortable doing this either,
since she's already an adult.
I'm worried it might violate her rights.
You can say it first.
I'll tell you what can and can't be done.
- Oh, okay.
- Alright.
Som's dad cared deeply about
the background of every kid who came here.
He insisted on investigating thoroughly
whether a child truly had no parents
or guardians.
All for the child's own benefit.
That's very admirable.
But in Kluay's case,
the investigation was never completed
because he passed away first,
in a car accident.
I'm very sorry.
Thank you.
My husband's friend, a police officer,
suspected it might have been murder.
Because my husband had been investigating
a car with a swapped license plate
involved in the accident
that killed Kluay's parents.
Your husband believed
it was a staged killing
of Ms. Kluay's family?
Yes.
If that's true, then the perpetrators
must have been very influential,
or had extremely strong motives.
That's why his friend
asked me to stop everything,
out of fear that Som and I
would be targeted.
That makes sense.
But there's one thing
that's been weighing heavily on me.
I feel that Kluay herself
has the right to know who she really is.
That's a difficult question
for me too, ma'am.
This was found on Kluay
when she was brought in.
I've kept it quietly for a long time.
An anklet for a child.
Since Kluay reached adulthood,
I've been torn
about whether to return it to her.
It's like you knew there was a way
to trace Ms. Kluay's past,
yet you chose to keep it a secret
for everyone's safety.
I must seem very selfish, right?
Please don't blame yourself like that.
Keeping it secret
was what kept Ms. Kluay safe.
Who knows,
the people who intended to harm her family
might still be at large.
If you or Ms. Kluay made a scene
trying to track down her family,
they might strike again.
Yes. I've thought the same.
Let's do this.
I'll try sounding Ms. Kluay out a bit
and see how she feels about her origins.
Thank you so much, Mr. Arnon.
You're welcome.
Ms. Ampha, you're the mother of…
NEXT EPISODE
If Ms. Ampha was not related to me,
why does she keep following me?
These fruits
are from the basket
Mr. Jirasin brought for you yesterday.
What are you doing, Boonsita?
Mr. Warat, where are you going?
Dad and Ms. Ampha are right here.
That's not true. Get a grip.
Subtitle translation by: Panuwat Baikeawon