Hello, Arnon.
Arnon…
Grandma.
I don't understand.
Don't tell me you believe him.
I've seen the documents. I already know.
- And?
- It's not that I believe Jirasin.
Then why did you let him go like that?
Rat,
if we're going to be the kind of people
who can manage others,
we have to balance authority and mercy.
Don't forget that Jirasin
can still be very useful to us.
Right now,
you've already used authority with him.
So I have to use mercy.
Most importantly,
I believe that right now,
Jirasin wouldn't dare step out of line.
Because he knows you're watching him.
And more importantly, Jirasin's work
will have to come out well too.
Because he wants to prove to me
that he's capable, that he has value,
and that he's loyal.
To manage people,
you don't need to say everything you know.
What matters
is knowing the right moment to say it.
But I don't understand.
Why do you always give in to Jirasin?
How's the child?
Has he had medicine yet?
If there's anything we can help with,
just let us know.
Anything at all.
Because I don't want this child to grow up
feeling like
life has gone wrong in every way.
You need to understand, Rat.
Everyone's origin
and background is different.
You can't use one ruler
to judge the whole world.
People are born different.
They think differently.
Their lives are not the same.
But if you're going to let things happen
and keep pretending not to see them,
that won't work, Grandma.
Everything has its ending.
It just depends on
how we choose to let it end.
And I don't see why
this has to end as a tragedy.
That's what she said.
I still have another concern
about fraudulent transactions.
Jirasin shouldn't be
holding Vanich shares.
What do you think?
Jirasin shouldn't be
holding any shares at all.
Do you have any good ideas?
You suddenly got so many Vanich shares.
You really are impressive.
Patience always pays off.
And the payoff is well worth it.
What's your next move?
Next, we need to make sure the new CEO
goes to inspect the site.
Hello?
Mr. Golf?
Oh, Kluay, you're awake?
I think I'm going to stop by the office.
Why? Is there urgent work?
No.
But I don't know if I'm imagining it,
about Mr. Warat.
What now?
I feel like he's acting strange.
Like he's hiding something.
There's nothing.
You're overthinking again.
I think you should go back and rest.
No, I'm already awake.
And I can't stop worrying.
If you're going, fine.
But I'm going with you.
Then before we go, sit down.
Let me eat a little more.
Okay.
Want some?
- Thank you for letting me come in.
- Of course.
You already know
about Ameena and Warat, right?
Roughly.
About these two…
I understand.
But actually, didn't Ameena
already have a boyfriend?
So how did she end up with Warat?
I don't know
what exactly is going on between them.
We'll probably have to let them
sort it out themselves.
But Ameena told me
that the baby in her womb…
If she said that,
then we'll have to get clarity on it,
so both sides can have peace of mind.
Mrs. Wanee.
I have a reputation in society too.
I don't want people saying
my daughter is pregnant with no father.
Oh, you don't have to worry about that.
If the child in her womb
really is Warat's,
we are willing
to take full responsibility.
I have to apologize, Grandma.
I really didn't want
something like this to happen.
You don't need to apologize.
You didn't do anything wrong.
I think for now,
it would be better
if we focused on finding a solution.
But this is such a big matter,
Warat should be here to hear it too.
How about this?
Let's have dinner together this evening.
That way, I can bring Warat too.
Most importantly,
I think it would be better
if the two of them talked directly
and figured out a way through this.
That'd be better.
Alright.
Is there anything you want to tell me?
Don't ever go
looking for me like that again.
Then you're not allowed
to disappear like that again either, okay?
I'm sorry.
I forgive you.
I never wanted things
to turn out like this, Kluay.
Is there anything else that I should know?
Well, I'm not Mr. Wichan's son.
Then…
whose son are you?
It feels like
I've been lying to you this whole time.
But I swear I never meant to. I'm sorry.
It's okay.
It's such a small thing.
I'm not thinking too much about it.
- I'm going to find Waree.
- Mm.
- And…
- I'm going to return everything to her.
She's the real Vanich heir.
And after that?
Then at that point,
I might end up with nothing at all.
Mm.
That's okay.
I don't care about that at all.
I don't care if you are a somebody
or what kind of family you come from.
So, whose son are you?
I'm Mr. Sarut's son.
Hm, no, you're not.
Maybe it's just a coincidence.
You are Mr. Warat.
Mr. Wichan's son, Mrs. Wanee's grandson.
And maybe you just happen
to have a little of Mr. Sarut's blood.
But it's not right.
I… I shouldn't accept things that…
aren't mine. You get what I mean?
Why not?
Everything, the will,
the assets, this mall.
If you don't want it,
you can just return it to Grandma.
Does she know the truth yet?
She does.
And did she kick you out
or ask for everything back?
No.
See? That means
she loves you for who you are.
It has nothing to do with
whether you have
the family's blood or not.
Just like how I love you.
I love you for who you are.
It doesn't matter
whether you have wealth or not.
- Really?
- Mm.
But I also have something
to talk to you about.
Yesterday, Ameena came
to see me while you were gone.
Why?
She wanted to talk to you…
about the baby.
The baby?
She said you got her pregnant.
- Me?
- Mm.
Uh, Mr. Warat,
Mrs. Wanee would like to see you.
- Is something wrong?
- It's about Ms. Ameena.
What about her?
CONTACT PHOTO AND POSTER
There's a delivery for you.
CALL
Thank you.
SOM
Hello, Arnon.
Even though
it's not much,
it's something I got within my means.
I hope this pendant
can represent my feelings for you.
If you don't mind,
will you be my girlfriend?
Arnon…
Yes!
So, you've seen the new
shareholder structure of Vanich.
What do you think?
In my opinion,
Mr. Warat is in danger.
In what way?
If you, the second-largest shareholder,
wants to take over everything,
it would be very easy.
Grandma must trust that
- I wouldn't do something like that.
- Yes.
So she gave me quite a lot of shares…
thinking that I wouldn't betray Warat.
If I wanted to become
the majority shareholder
and make you
the new executive instead of Warat,
would that be an interesting idea?
And what do you want?
When we hold shares in a company,
we want to see profit, right?
I just want to own a company
with the right management.
Someone who earns
the position through ability,
not connections.
So how can I help you?
If I acquire all your shares,
I'll become the majority shareholder.
Then I'll remove Warat
and appoint you in his place.
- And…
- A company at this level,
if you become the executive,
imagine how much the stock would rise.
When everything is settled,
I'll sell the shares back to you
at the original price
if you want.
When will you start the process
of removing Warat?
It already started even
before Grandma announced the will.
Grandma.
Ameena came earlier.
- Yes, Grandma.
- What happened?
Nothing.
Nothing?
Then why did her father come and say…
That I slept with her?
And what's the truth?
Maybe I'm actually
suitable for Ameena, Grandma.
Warat, does that mean
you really got her pregnant?
If you did,
you have to take responsibility.
Kluay.
What did Grandma say?
Huh? What did you say?
What exactly happened that night?
Mm…
What did you say?
What did Grandma say?
She just said…
if it's true,
I have to take responsibility. Kluay,
I don't remember anything at all.
Okay, I understand.
Kluay, no, you don't really understand.
But no matter what, it already happened.
You have to take responsibility.
Take care of her family well.
Kluay, it's… it's not like that.
You know I don't feel anything for Ameena.
Not even a little.
You know that, right?
Whether you feel something or not
doesn't matter.
What matters is you already did it.
Did what? I didn't do anything.
Are you sure about that?
I didn't do it.
I'm sure
that Ameena drugged me.
This was her plan.
I wasn't conscious.
I don't remember anything.
Okay.
I'll tell you.
When I walked…
into that bar, I asked her, "Ameena,
where's Kluay?"
She said you were in the room
waiting for me. Then I drank water.
Yes, I drank water.
And I was just passed out.
I can't remember anything.
Seriously, Kluay.
It was her plan.
But no matter what, it already happened.
What if the baby is yours?
What baby? Kluay, it's…
I didn't do anything.
Okay, the baby, right?
If that child is really mine,
I'll take responsibility.
But it has nothing to do with Ameena.
Every couple
faces obstacles.
And we do too, right?
But what matters is
do we love each other enough?
When we face problems,
will we still hold hands like this?
Do we still trust each other?
See? You're smiling again.
I'm not smiling.
You look really cute when you smile.
That's it. There's nothing. Okay?
I'll find out the truth.
Then I'll find the truth my way too.
Okay. I'll find the truth my way as well.
- Okay.
- So what truth are you going to look for?
I'm going to talk to Det.
- No, come on.
- Uh, uh.
No. Don't talk to him, okay?
Why not? You can still talk to Ameena.
Hello, are you there already?
Okay, I'll hurry over.
Can you promise me something?
If anything bad happens, tell me.
Call me immediately, okay?
Okay.
I'm going.
Som.
What are you doing today?
Preparing procurement documents.
Are you free tonight?
Want to have dinner with me?
- I'm not free.
- Where are you going?
I have plans with the kids at home.
- Oh, then I'll go with you.
- No need.
Then how are you getting there?
I can go by myself.
You don't have to bother.
But I'm free. I can go.
You're not free.
What do you want from me, Arnon?
- I just…
- If you love her, go with her.
What do you take me for?
What do you mean?
You bought something for her too.
What did you hear?
I heard everything.
What, you think I wouldn't know
that you've been talking to someone else?
Som…
I love her.
Do you know
how I've felt
all this time?
Why are you doing this to me?
What am I to you?
Don't you see my feelings at all?
I'm sorry.
But today,
I was planning
to confess my love to the person I like.
Okay.
I understand.
Will you be my girlfriend?
I'm not rich,
but I'll take the best care of you.
What do you mean?
Then the person you've been talking to…
I was practicing.
Practicing for you.
Oh…
So? Are you okay with it?
Okay with what?
Being my girlfriend.
You already know what I'm going to say.
How would I know?
What did you ask me again?
Will you be my girlfriend?
What does that mean?
Yes.
What does "yes" mean?
Ugh, it means I'll be your girlfriend.
Yes, Mr. Warat.
Oh, okay.
Som, head home. And pick up Ms. Kluay too.
Go back to the Vanich house.
I'll be late tonight.
- Okay.
- Mm.
No.
"Okay, darling."
You're crazy. Go.
- Darling.
- Go.
Darling.
Mr. Arnon,
what do you think I should do about Kluay?
What about her?
I feel like I'm taking advantage of her.
Why do you think that?
When I asked her to be my girlfriend,
I was Warat of the Vanich family.
But now that I know
I might not be that Warat anymore,
I feel like I'm holding her back.
So what are you going to do?
I'll find Waree,
return everything to Grandma,
- and go live where I really belong.
- Hey.
Wait, you don't have to do that.
- I have to. I have to do…
- What?
Did Mrs. Wanee kick you out?
- No.
- Right.
- Did Ms. Kluay break up with you?
- No.
So,
why would you do that
when no one wants things
to be this way?
I have to do what's right.
I have to do it.
- But…
- Ms. Kluay
already told you, didn't she?
That she doesn't want you
to disappear again.
Okay. Then this time,
I'll talk to her honestly. Okay?
Mm.
Sis.
You sound cheerful.
Let's go home.
Oh, it's already evening?
I didn't even check the time.
Som, you go home first.
I still have something to do.
Something? Wait a second.
You never say that to me.
Where are you going?
To see a guy.
I just have someone I need to talk to.
Who?
Det.
Det? Again?
Every time you talk to him,
there's trouble.
Haven't you learned?
This time it's serious. I have to go.
What now?
Another problem with that crazy Ameena?
Probably not this time.
Why are you so soft-hearted?
How can you believe people like them?
Det said he broke up with Ameena.
I just want to know what really happened.
Fine. I'm going with you.
It's Det's personal business.
I don't want him to feel uncomfortable.
I don't care. I'm going with you.
I'll just sit far away.
I'm going.
I don't know Sarut very well,
but from what I've seen, I think he knows.
- If he already knows, then why…?
- Or…
Maybe he's waiting for Mr. Warat
to receive the inheritance first.
And if he can prove
that he's really Warat's father,
then he himself
will get a share of the inheritance too.
With the utmost respect, ma'am,
if anything happens to Mr. Warat,
all the assets
will be transferred to Mr. Sarut,
his biological father,
not returned to you, ma'am.
Darling!
- Arnon.
- What?
Why are you calling me that?
Well, we're a couple now.
I know, but…
it's too soon. It gives me goosebumps.
Come on, it's like this at first.
After a while,
you'll get used to it, okey-dokey?
Stop. Stop right there.
- Oh?
- Who taught you to say "okey-dokey"?
I heard that
when couples say "okey-dokey,"
it sounds cute.
Ugh, then I don't want that.
Why not, Somnao?
Hey, why do I have to be
- "Somnao"?
- Uh…
Arnon, where's the balance?
Do you know what moderation is?
Okay, got it.
So why did Mrs. Wanee call Mr. Warat in?
Well, Mr. Warat
is going to break up with Ms. Kluay.
What? Break up?
Why would he do that?
They love each other so much.
Uh, Mr. Warat…
What about him? Say it.
He'll tell you himself.
Oh, so now you're keeping secrets from me?
- No, no…
- We've been together for an hour,
and you already have secrets?
Oh, is that how it is? Fine.
Oh, Som…
Hello, Kluay.
I'm out now.
You can wait for me at Baan Saeng.
And what about Det…?
He's not that bad.
I can trust him.
We studied together for five years, okay?
Fine.
But if anything happens,
call me immediately, okay?
Will she be okay?
She'll be fine. If anything happens,
she'll call.
Don't go home yet. We'll go back together.
Where are you going?
I have something important
to discuss with Jirasin.
BANK
The money's in, Mr. Chatchai.
You're amazing.
I sold it way above market price.
Can't believe someone stupid bought it.
If Mr. Golf gets your shares,
he'll become the owner of Vanich Mall
instead of Warat. Worth it.
- But I think…
- From now on, just sit back,
count the money,
and watch Warat fall apart.
About what you said
that you broke up with Ameena,
what's going on?
Yes.
I broke up with her yesterday.
But yesterday, Ameena came to see me.
She came to see you? Where?
Actually,
she intended to meet Mrs. Wanee.
Mrs. Wanee?
But Mrs. Wanee was busy,
so,
she asked me to pass on
the message instead.
What message?
It's not something good.
I thought you…
might…
I know already.
Yeah, that.
But what Ameena said might not be true.
So you mean Ameena isn't pregnant?
Actually,
she probably is pregnant.
But she went to Mrs. Wanee
to say the baby
is Warat's.
You know what?
I believe…
I believe in my partner.
At first, I was angry
when Ameena told me.
She told me
after calling me just a servant's son.
Det…
Well…
At first I was angry…
so I said
the baby isn't mine.
Det.
But…
I know the truth. Actually…
the baby is mine.
Then just tell Ameena that.
This morning,
her father called me.
He told me to stay away from her.
How is that possible?
Because he said
the baby is Warat's.
How could that be?
Anything's possible.
Her father has already planned everything.
So,
- what are you going to do?
- Well.
Kluay…
Can you help me?
I want my family back.
Oh, I've known for a long time already
that you two like each other.
NEXT EPISODE
You call me "bro"? But you lied to me.
You lied to everyone! Why?!
I…
I didn't want to do this.
Did your father tell you to?
I think you should start packing now.
Because tomorrow, Mr. Warat will fire you.
Hit me.
Go on, hit me.
I did what I had to do
to protect Vanich.
Subtitle translation by: Panuwat Baikeawon