All characters, behaviors, places, occupations, and events in this series are fictional and created for entertainment purposes.
There is no intention to promote any actions depicted. Viewer discretion is advised.
Good morning!
It’s been so hot the past few days, hasn’t it?
The Meteorological Department announced that due to the effects of global warming,
it will rain at night throughout November
in the Bangkok Metropolitan Region for 30 consecutive days.
Prepare yourself for the upcoming rain.
Plan your commute before leaving.
Prepare all the essentials to protect yourself from the rain.
Sometimes bad luck brings good luck. Some of you might find what you've been searching for.
I hope all the single people out there meet their soulmate in the rain.
Get ready to see all the vivid colors!
If any of you meet your soulmate, I hope you both fall deeply in love.
If luck hasn't favored you yet, or if you're soulmate blind, please don't be sad.
Don't forget to love yourself and take care of your health first.
Let's continue with international news.
Heng!
Bro, I've got a plan.
Did you hear the news?
What is it? What news?
They said it will rain for 30 consecutive days.
You're not going to ask me about my plan?
Fine. What is your plan?
If it rains heavily, I won't be able to go out to deliver. Why don't we start selling umbrellas instead?
Where do we get the umbrellas from?
From your store.
Most of the people might want to get wet in the rain.
They won't buy umbrellas.
Really?
Single people looking for their soulmates,
they'll dash into the rain!
I'm so jealous of those people
who can see their soulmates in the rain.
Oh, right.
You're soulmate blind.
You don't have to repeat that.
I'm sorry.
But really,
who would be crazy enough to run into the rain just to see their soulmate?
They'll just end up with pneumonia instead.
Exactly!
So what do you think? Are you in?
I can't go to sell umbrellas with you.
I have to look after this store.
How about this?
You can stay here.
And I'll go out there to sell them.
And we can share the profits, seventy-thirty.
Are you crazy?
Sixty-fourty.
Come on, bro!
Sixty-five to thirty-five. No more negotiation. The deal is done.
Fine. You win again.
I'll go get the umbrellas then.
Okay.
Whoa.
Are you crazy?
I'm off!
What!
You should pay first.
Add it to my bill. I'll come back to pay later. I'm leaving. Bye!
Gosh!
Clumsy as always.
Dad is definitely going to scold me.
What should we eat for dinner?
I want to eat Italian food.
Look at him!
What kind of outfit is that?
Why is he all covered up?
Exactly. I guess he's scared to die of pneumonia.
Look at Dol.
The way he dresses is so strange.
Do you want an umbrella?
Do you want one?
Oh, you already have it. What about you?
I already have mine.
But my umbrellas are prettier. Look at the color.
No, thank you.
Do you want a raincoat?
No, thanks.
Bro, do you want a raincoat? I have umbrellas too.
You don't want one?
You want to buy?
Choose whichever color you like. I have this one as well.
How about the green one? It suits you.
You want the pink one?
Who is that guy?
I don't know too.
Heng!
Bro!
I'm in trouble now!
I met my soulmate.
Huh? What do you mean?
I got wet in the rain, and then I saw him in full color.
Aren't you soulmate blind?
Maybe...
Your boyfriend lied to you.
Ex-boyfriend!
Oh, right, ex-boyfriend.
Au definitely lied to you.
He said you're his soulmate, so you wouldn't dare to break up with him.
We've already broken up.
You keep saying that.
How many times have you broken up already? You'll get back with him again.
This time, we really broke up for good.
I hope it's true.
But you should stop acting like a bank that lends money first.
How much did he waste on football betting?
I know.
I'm so done with him.
But are you sure?
That you actually met your soulmate.
I'm sure!
He's a man.
He was waiting for the van to go home.
He's handsome too!
Wait a minute.
So that means he's working in this area.
You're right!
I know what to do.
I have to prove it.
Tomorrow, I'll go to the bus stop and wait for him, and I'll ask him,
'Do you see me in color?'
I can see you in color!
What do you think?
Or maybe there's something wrong with my body.
Am I going to die? Oh my God!
You're talking nonsense.
Come on!
I think this plan will work.
I'm going now.
Hey! Pay for your cat food first.
Add it to my bill. I'll come back to pay later.
I knew it.
Eh?
Who gave you the food?
It's okay.
I'll give you an umbrella instead.
There you go.
It's going to rain for 30 days.
Use this umbrella so you won't get wet.
Umbrellas!
Mister!
You're feeding the Midnight gang?
What are you talking about?
You don't have to raise your voice.
What's your name?
Is your office in this area?
Really?
Let's get straight to business.
Can you please confirm the answer for me?
I see you in color. Do you see me in color as well?
If it's a yes,
then we're soulmates.
It doesn't matter.
Yes, it is! We're soulmates!
How about this?
Can I get to know you more? Please.
Let's be on our own paths.
Why?
Eh?
Mister!
Why is he playing hard to get?
Au: Can we go back to how things used to be?
Really?
Yes.
I can see you in color.
You've never heard of 'soulmate blind'?
1% of people in this world cannot see their soulmate.
I guess you're one of them.
This sucks.
It's already hard to find your own soulmate.
And I'm also in that 1% of people.
It's okay.
Just know that we're soulmates. That's enough.
Delete.
Here you go.
So, is there any update?
I wish! I came back empty-handed.
He got angry when I started talking about soulmates.
Did you annoy him?
Me? Annoyed him? Are you mad?
Also, the way he dressed was completely covered up.
He was wearing a raincoat and boots.
Why is he so afraid of the rain? What a weirdo.
Whoa, look at you!
It's not like you're not weird.
I'm weird? I'm completely normal and handsome.
I won't back down.
I won't give up.
I will keep approaching him.
Whatever.
Bro, there's an order. See you later.
Alright, see you.
Count the money too. Make sure it's correct
Hello.
Your food is here.
I'm waiting in front of the building.
Sure.
Okay.
I'm here to pick up my food.
Oh, here you go.
And you're... Dol, right?
Are you working here?
Thank you.
I always deliver food here. How come I’ve never seen you before?
Also, if you don't want to get wet from the rain, I can come to pick you up.
Mister! It's free for you!
Mister!
You want to go to the bus stop, right? I'll take you there.
It's okay.
Come on. We know each other now. No need to worry!
Please.
It's okay.
Please. It's free. I won't add extra charges just for you.
No, thank you.
Please, let me give you a ride.
I told you no.
Mister!
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
Let me help you.
You can hardly walk, and you still say you're fine?
I'm fine, seriously.
Will you let me buy that word from you so you won't say it again?
You're so stubborn.
I'll take you to get your wound treated.
Walk slowly.
May I?
Are you okay?
Let's go. I can assure you of your safety.
Trust me.
Let me see.
I told you I would drop you off. You're so stubborn.
You see? You were grazed by the motorcycle.
It's not that serious.
It is.
You shouldn't keep saying that everything is fine when you're hurt.
If it hurts, then just say so. Do you understand?
Let me put it on for you.
It will hurt a bit.
And don't forget to put the medicine on your ankle too.
It will definitely throb tomorrow.
Here. Take it.
- Thank you.
- What?
Thank you.
Your welcome.
It's nothing.
By the way, can I ask you something?
When I see you, you always dress so covered up.
Don't you feel hot?
It's about to rain.
So I have to wear a raincoat.
I understand.
But I guess you're really scared of the rain, aren't you?
Yeah.
But rain...
It makes us see each other in color.
Are you going to talk about this same topic again?
But we're actually soulmates, aren't we?
You can see me in color.
I can see you in color too.
Is this real?
Yes.
I can see you in color.
- So that means--
- I don't believe in such things.
Oh.
There're so many people who love each other even though they're not soulmates.
And their life as a couple can be good.
There are some couples...
who are soulmates,
but it doesn't work out.
The Rain-Color Verse and all those soulmate beliefs are meaningless to me.
Aren't you happy?
The chance that you will meet your soulmate...
It's very hard.
Why don't you give it a try?
No.
Just give it a try. If it doesn't work, then we can figure it out later.
Where can I grab a taxi here?
Why get a taxi? I can drop you off instead.
It's okay. I can call a car using an app.
Why do you have to use the app? It costs you an extra fee. If you go with me, it’s all free.
The extra fee isn't much. I can find a taxi on my own.
Please, just let me give you a ride.
I can use the app.
Come on.
You see? I can drop you off here, and it’s all free.
Yeah.
Thank you.
By the way, if your office needs a messenger, feel free to contact me.
Or if you need someone to take you anywhere and drop you off, just call me.
I drive safely, and I have a free helmet for you.
Are you trying to hard sell me?
No, I'm not. I see that your arm hurts, you leg hurts too.
So I just want to help.
By the way,
can I have your number?
No.
But I work hard and I work fast.
There's no need.
Please. Please give me your number.
No.
Don't be so mean. Please give me your number.
There's no need.
Give me your number instead.
Oh, so you’re asking for my number?
I didn't mean it that way.
Say no more.
Actually, I already have your number since you ordered the food.
But I'm asking for your permission first.
Don't scold me.
You were the one who asked for my number.
One, two, seven, eight, two seven, eight...
Seven, eight, seven, eight. What the heck?
Two, seven, eight...
What a big smile on your face.
What?
What is two, seven, eight?
Guess.
I don't know!
I got his number! Aren't I great?
Who?
Your soulmate?
That's right. Who else would it be?
That guy who came to the store and you treated his wound?
That's correct.
I see.
Well, he doesn't look bad.
Good for you. You can finally move on.
I'll text him now.
Au: Why aren’t you picking up the phone?
Speak of the devil.
I've moved on already.
I'm deleting his text, you see?
You better be.
I better text that guy now. What should I say?
Hello.
Who?
- There's only one person I'm talking about!
- Okay, okay.
Mr. Soulmate.
Ohhh.
You think it's a good idea?
Go for it.
Dol, please help me with this.
It's not that far.
Er, okay--
Hello.
Here.
Yes, sir.
I forgot my wallet upstairs.
It's okay. You can transfer via Promptpay. My number is 081-616-763-442
I'll keep repeating it until you know my number by heart.
I know. I already saved it.
You can call me when you miss me.
I have to go now.
I've transferred the money already.
Alright.
Let me put it on for you.
- Here you go.
- Thank you so much.
This one is for you.
You bought a coffee for me?
Yes.
Hey.
You don't have to.
You like to look at the sky, right?
I don't.
But I just can't help it.
Why?
Because life gets troublesome when it rains.
You're saying it like you know when it's going to rain.
I know.
That single cloud over there.
It's called a cumulus.
It means the weather is still nice.
But the weather forecast says it’s going to rain for quite some time.
That's because, as the day goes on,
cumulus clouds combine into cumulonimbus clouds.
More commonly known as thunderclouds.
What is it called again?
Something bus? What a funny name.
Actually, clouds have many names.
Like Stratus.
Stratocumulus.
Nimbostratus.
There are more types of clouds as we go higher.
You're finally looking at my face.
Huh?
Usually, you’re always looking at the sky.
That's not true.
Fine, whatever you say.
Tell me more about that nitrobus something.
I want to listen. Please.
Your ice-cream is melting.
Give it to me.
Hold it this way so your hands don't get dirty.
Finish eating so we can go home.
It's going to rain soon.
I’m not scared of the rain.
It's good if it rains every day
so I can see you in color.
If you really like the rain that much, why don’t you ride a boat instead of a motorcycle?
You're ruining the mood.
Mom
Hello.
Not yet.
I don't think he will call.
Maybe he forgets about it.
It's okay as long as I remember.
Thank you.
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday, happy birthday.
Happy birthday!
Thank you.
Wishing you lots of happiness.
Let's eat.
Boss, there's an urgent task coming up.
Okay.
Thank you.
Hello.
Hello, Dol.
I'll be late to pick you up today because I have to go get a very important parcel.
It's okay.
I can go back by myself.
Dol!
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday, happy birthday.
Happy birthday to you, Dol.
Yay!
Happy birthday, Dol.
I wish you immense happiness!
How do you know that today is my birthday?
It's in the app.
I didn't know that.
It's about to rain.
You can keep the cake and eat it at home later.
No need.
Why?
You're not going to eat my cake?
You're so mean.
Let's eat it together.
I'll take you to a place to eat.
Oh, hello.
What's your order number?
No, bro.
I'm here to eat this time.
I thought you're here to take your order.
Scan for the menu right here.
Order whatever you want. It's on me.
You're going to treat me?
There's no need. I feel bad for it.
It's in return for the cake.
Don't feel bad about it.
Dol.
Isn't this too much?
We'll eat here.
Alright.
Total is 520 baht.
I'll scan to pay.
It's so yummy.
Of course, this is a famous place.
I know it's famous.
But I don't have that much money.
So I never tried eating it before.
You seem to have a lot of work.
I see you busy with work all the time.
Nope.
It's not that much.
Just enough to live.
But at least my mom doesn't ask me for more money
because she has a happy life now with her boyfriend.
So I decided to leave and take care of myself.
I do miss my dad, though.
My dad passed away since I was 3 years old.
I couldn't even remember his face.
If he was still here, my life would be better than this.
Dol.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry. I shouldn't have told you.
It's okay.
You can tell me.
Actually, that's all.
My mom met her soulmate and now she's happy.
I feel happy for her.
I understand now.
Is this why you're so interested in soulmate stuff?
You don't like it?
No.
I think it's nonesense.
People can love each other even if they aren’t soulmates.
And even soulmates can break up in the end.
You're not romantic at all!
You're not selling umbrellas anymore?
Nope. Not anymore.
I want to spend my time...
flirting with you.
Should I?
Actually, I really admire you.
You can do so many things.
You're a rider.
A messenger, delivering parcels.
You can also make time to sell umbrellas.
I don't think I can do all this.
You're making me blush now.
Do you think I'm amazing?
Of course, you are.
You like me, don't you?
Just eat your cake.
It's going to melt.
Hello.
Dol.
Was it your birthday yesterday?
Yes, that's right.
Happy belated birthday.
Thank you.
Do you want to eat lunch together?
Join us. We can find someplace nice to eat.
Let's go. My treat today. Let's all go together.
But... I can't go.
Why not?
I can't go unless you let me treat you all.
Great! You pay then.
Alright!
Yes!
Should we go now?
Of course. A boss like me can do anything.
Let's go. I'm so hungry.
I'll show you how to drift a motorcycle.
Do it then.
You should drive carefully.
I'm always careful.
Do you know these cats have their own gang?
Really?
That's good. They won't be lonely.
They are called the Midnight Gang. Isn’t that cool?
It's cute.
Sun.
Why did you not pick up my call?
Who's this?
He's my customer.
Can we talk later?
No.
Answer me first. Did you even read my text?
I didn't.
Let's go.
Wait, Sun.
We have to talk about this.
Can you just leave me alone?
We've already broken up
I've never agreed to that. We're not broken up yet.
It's all in your head.
Stop threatening to break up every time we fight.
Why do you like to run away from the problem?
We should help each other to find the solution.
Not just say you want to break up.
Sun.
Can you give me one more chance?
Let's talk about this.
That's enough, Au!
Stop lying to me.
Stop lying that we're soulmates.
You didn't see the color from me.
He's the one who sees me in color.
That's not right. I told you that you're soulmate blind.
I'm not soulmate blind!
You lied to me about this too!
How could it be?
Because I can see him in color!
You suddenly have a change of heart just because you see someone else in color?
So what if that’s true?
People shouldn’t be in a relationship just because someone says they’re your soulmate.
I didn't just say it.
I really do see you in color.
You don't believe me?
No. I don't belive you.
Let's go.
No! Sun.
Let go of me!
Do it then!
Just do whatever you want!
There are many people here watching. They will know who you really are.
No!
Hey!
I think that's enough.
It's none of your business.
Let him go.
No.
I'll call the police then.
I will do it.
Let him go!
Thank you.
And I'm sorry for involving you in this.
Who's that?
Your ex-boyfriend?
Yes.
We've already broken up, but he won't let me go. I don't know what to do.
I won't go back to him this time. We're so incompatible.
So that means you guys have made up a couple of times already?
Yeah.
It doesn't sound good, does it?
I'm stupid.
Did you really mean what you said?
About what?
That you like someone else now.
Because he's your soulmate.
Oh, you want me to say it right here?
I feel shy now.
Well, then.
I just want to ask you.
All this time,
do you like me for who I am,
or is it just because I'm your soulmate?
Come on, Dol. I can't give you the answer right now. It's raining. We should go.
Let's go.
Come on, let's go.
Dol!
I'm the one who's taking care of everything!
I'm the one who goes out to work!
What do you do?
You're just keeping complaining!
Do you know how tiring it is to look after your child alone?
Why are you making a fuss?
Sun
What's up?
Are you heartbroken?
What?
How do you know?
Au came here last night. I saw him.
Yeah.
Everyone around here probably knew.
What's wrong? Did you two have a fight because of Au?
Not really.
Or maybe it was.
He suddenly asked if I like him or not.
Do I like him for who he is,
or is it just because he's my soulmate?
What did you tell him?
I didn't answer.
I didn't know what to say. He asked suddenly,
and I didn't have time to prepare myself for it.
So do you like him?
How do I know that?
What! Are you trying to annoy me?
You're the one with experience, not me.
Right.
Don't you want to be with someone?
Well...
I don't want to be with anyone.
I'm not interested in love.
I can be happy
without love.
I hope there's a place for someone like me in this world.
Sadhu.
Maybe
the answer is very simple.
Do you feel happy when you’re with him?
Am I happy?
Hold it this way so your hands don't get dirty.
Just eat your cake.
You're right! I'm happy!
That's it. That's your answer.
Can't stop smiling now, huh?
So do you have the answer now?
Stop teasing me. You already know my answer.
I'm late now. I should go see him first.
I have to go. See you!
Damn! I forgot my motorcycle. I'll be right back, bro!
Whatever.
Hello.
Oh, Sun!
Why do you come back so early?
There aren't many orders today?
No, I'm off work today.
I'm going to see my soulmate.
I have to go now! See you later!
You found one already?
Hey! Who are you?
Sun.
Au.
How's it going today?
- Lots of work today.
- It's a rough day.
It's already 6 PM.
You're right.
Wait!
Can we talk now?
How much money did you lose this time?
Why do you think of me like that?
You're making me sad.
It's obvious that you're here to steal my money.
My necklace.
Where's my necklace?
Where is it?
Au!
This is my mom's necklace!
Who is it?
Who?
That guy?
Dol.
I'm going first.
Alright.
Do you want to come with us?
It's okay.
See you then.
See you.
Excuse me.
Sun is not here?
Sun has been out for a while now.
He doesn't pick up the phone?
I think he might be having a fight with his ex.
Where does he live?
Let me go!
No!
Do you think I would go back to you if you do this?
Why not? You always come crawling back to me.
A person like you doesn't have many places to go.
Who would love you except me?
That's not true!
There must be someone who truly loves me!
Who?
That asshole?
You just met him, and now you're already in love?
I don't love him yet.
But when I'm with him, I feel happy.
Not like when I'm with you!
All we do is fight!
- Happiness has disappeared a long time ago!
- It's because you don't try hard enough!
You always wanted to break up every time we fought!
How could we be happy?
Stop blaming on me.
In the end, you never liked me.
You just liked being able to mess with my head and control me.
Who is it? Who told you?
That asshole, right?
Fine!
I told you there's no one!
If you're going to hurt him,
then just do it to me instead.
You want this, right?
You want it, huh?
You want it?
You want more, don't you?
You want it so bad, right?
That's enough!
Stop bothering him.
Good that you're here.
We can sort this out now.
That's enough, Au!
I won't go back to you.
I want to love someone who values me.
Stop it, Au!
I'm going to call the police!
Stop right there!
Everyone in my building is scared now.
Why are you just standing there? Go arrest him!
Let go of me!
Get out of here!
Go away!
Don't ever come back here again! I will call the police to put you in jail!
Damn it!
Are you alright?
It's okay, Sun.
You'll be alright.
Will you get sick?
You went out in the rain just to help me.
It's not a big deal.
I will get well soon.
Thank you so much.
Don't think too much about it.
Dol.
I know the answer now.
I don’t like you
just because you’re my soulmate.
I like you
for who you really are.
Well...
Me too.
♪ It’s the melody of my heart ♪
♪ You’re the one who weaves the tale ♪
♪ It took us time to find our love ♪
♪ To become the dreams we unveil ♪
♪ Never forget about this ♪
♪ Can you promise me that you will never forget me? ♪
I’m going to pass the company down to my grandson.
Prin Prasertrungruangtham.
Hello, Mr. Prin. I'm First Ekdanai.
I will be your secretary.
I’ll give you your first task.
Find me 10 marketing agencies to choose from.
Mr. Prin, you work so hard, but sometimes you're too stressed.
You should find something else to do.
Like what?
Find someone who understands you.