All characters, behaviors, places, occupations, and events in this series are fictional and created for entertainment purposes.
There is no intention to promote any actions depicted. Viewer discretion is advised.
Phukan!
Why didn’t you answer my call?
Why are you hiding from me?
I'm not ready to talk.
Please leave.
What the heck is wrong with you?
Huh?
I've come all the way here.
Why are you shouting?
Why are you acting like I did something wrong?
Answer me!
Why are you running away from me?
Why aren't you saying anything?
Answer me!
I'm telling you to answer me!
You can talk to each other nicely.
Why are you butting in?
Blue is not ready to talk to you.
Just leave.
No!
I will talk things out with him today.
Blue!
I said my person is not ready to talk to you!
Just go back now!
Do you hear me?
I will talk to him anyway.
Are you hungry?
Shall we eat?
Let's go.
You told her that I'm here, right?
Answer me.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
I didn’t expect her to come and bother you like this.
I was just curious about who was calling you all the time.
I'm sorry for crossing the line.
It's my fault.
I'm leaving.
Blue.
Blue!
Is Blue here?
No.
You should go.
I knew it.
Wait.
Can I ask you about Blue?
Can I?
Sure.
Tell us.
I want to know too.
Well...
Blue and I were friends at the university.
But we had a fight
because Blue submitted the drawing I helped him create into the contest,
and he won first prize.
So?
Wasn't that great?
It was.
But my name was not included.
That's not true.
My brother is not that kind of person.
Exactly.
I know that he's not that kind of person.
That's why I want to know what happened.
Since then, he wouldn’t pick up my calls
or reply to my texts.
Green.
Where can I find your brother?
Think fast.
Green.
Are you sure he's not home today?
Yes, I'm sure.
He told me that.
Well...
Where did you put my bag?
Er...
Around the sofa, do you see it?
Oh.
Okay, I found it.
Phukan!
Can we talk now?
I don't know where to start.
Let's start from answering all my questions.
Why did you hide from me?
Do you realize what you did wrong now?
Yes.
I know what I did was wrong.
But I had no bad intentions.
And I didn't want to run away from you.
Actually, the day I won the first prize,
it was the best day of my life.
Dear Mr. Patchara Phansit. The acceptance letter for finalists in the project with MAIOSIAM Artist Management Company.
You know how much that day meant to me, right?
I wanted to tell everyone that
it's you I had to thank.
Because you were the one who started that project.
You were also the inspiration for me to finish it.
But I didn't know why.
That day...
I just wanted everyone to think I could do it
and that I was good at it.
So I didn't mention your name.
That day passed.
And then a month passed, a year passed.
I couldn't clear things up with you.
And I let it be.
I let you think that...
we don't have to be friends anymore.
Why did you think that way?
Because I'm scared.
I’m scared to tell you the truth, and I’m scared to face you like this.
So you decided to hide from me, just like that?
How do you think I feel?
I'm sorry.
I...
am not a fool.
Hm?
I was never mad at you.
Because I know
my friend had his own reasons.
I just want you to tell the truth.
You didn't mean to do it.
Actually,
the success of that project, just as we both imagined,
was because of you.
Really?
Of course.
You're talented.
You're so talented.
Thank you.
It took us ages to talk like this.
There's nothing much I want to say.
I just want to give you the invitation card.
Well,
I'm going to open a gallery in the US.
- You want to invite me?
- Yes.
The day you were successful,
I was standing there.
It's my turn now.
I...
I want you to see it too.
You...
Gosh, you're so...
- Thank you so much.
- What's wrong with you?
You're crying like a baby.
You're that not young anymore.
I'm happy.
Don't forget to come.
You know that you can talk to me about anything, right?
Don't cry, you silly!
Hmm!
I'm sorry.
I know.
I know you didn't mean to do it.
Well then.
I'm leaving now.
I'm going with you.
What?
I'm going to celebrate your new gallery.
I don't think so.
I think there's someone is waiting to talk to you after me.
See you later, my friend.
Talk to you later.
Your turn.
So?
Your issue is solved.
Right now...
it's my turn.
I have something to tell you.
Follow me.
Blue.
This used to be my ex's room.
We had a good time together here.
This is too sad! Are you heartbroken?
Aww, my baby boy.
Of course, I'm sad.
I can't come up with any lyrics right now.
Everyone, take a look.
I will continue writing.
Sian.
Hm?
Don't push yourself too hard.
Things you like
might turn into something you hate.
As for me,
I'll be waiting to hear all the songs you write from now on.
Okay?
What?
Answer me. Why are you so quiet?
Do you want to get married?
What are you saying?
I can't come up with the lyrics,
so I want something new
to inspire my song.
Be serious.
You like to be half joking, half serious.
I'll give you one more chance to say it.
I just want you to always be my inspiration like this.
Um.
See, it's not that hard.
You can say it out loud.
So what do you say?
Marry me or not.
If you do,
I already have a ring.
Where did you get it from?
I'm well prepared.
Until one day...
Hello, Mom.
What are you saying?
James.
Why are you sitting over there?
Come here.
Okay?
James.
You look so handsome! It’s been a while.
You still like to wear this favorite shirt.
Let's go sleep, James.
Sleep here.
I'm sleepy now.
Let's sleep, James.
Sleep.
Sleep right here.
I'll sleep right next to you.
Okay?
I'm sorry to hear that.
It's okay.
I kept this room locked for a really long time.
I thought I couldn't accept it yet.
But the truth is,
I wanted to hide my weakness.
I'm fine now,
and I can enter this room without any bad feelings.
James...
is my starting point and my inspiration
for playing music.
You don't have to try to forget him.
He's important to you.
He's worth remembering.
James and I said goodbye with a smile.
Let him be a memory.
And I will keep moving forward
with this person,
the one I love.
The person who makes me want...
to be with him all the time.
And I won't let you go again.
I think...
I can't live without you.
Thank you.
I'm sleepy now.
I won't send you home today.
You better to sleep here.
It's not that far.
But my body is aching.
I want you to give me a massage.
What are you tired of?
Just send me home.
No.
It's already late. I have to go home.
Are you sure you want to go?
Hm?
Well, let’s take a shower first,
and we can talk later.
I would like a deposit first.
Let's go!
Do you like me that much?
If you're done drawing,
can I have it?
No.
Why not? It's a picture of me.
But I'm the one who's drawing it.
I should be the one who owns it.
Fine, I won't have it.
Well,
I'm going to get dressed.
Don't change the body wash.
Why?
You like it?
I've always liked it.
It smells good.
You're working hard to make sure I don't finish drawing today.
There's something
we can finish faster if we do it together.
I can't help it.
You're making me crazy in love.
Why are you so shocked?
I'm not going anywhere.
The song I wrote for you,
it's done now.
It's called...
Every Tears.
Wait a minute.
That's the same name...
It's because of your painting that I was able to finish the song.
You're lying.
And the sentence that you told me you liked it before.
Music is medicine of the broken heart.
You're right. It doesn't suit me.
Do you know why?
Because when I'm feeling blue, having you is the best medicine.
Yuck.
Actually, I don’t want our art to depend on each other.
Apart from that thing,
music is another one of my weapons.
Do you want to listen to it?
♪ How many stories have brought me pain? ♪
♪ How many stories have made me smile? ♪
♪ You are there ♪
♪ In my dreams and reality ♪
♪ As long as you're with me ♪
♪ From now on, everything will be okay ♪
You agreed!
♪ How many drops of tears have I shed for love? ♪
♪ Streaming down my face since that day ♪
♪ It took us time to discover our love ♪
♪ To become the dreams we unveil ♪
♪ Never forget about this ♪
♪ Can you do that? ♪
♪ It’s the melody of my heart ♪
♪ You’re the one who weaves the tale ♪
♪ It took us time to find our love ♪
♪ To become the dreams we unveil ♪
♪ Never forget about this ♪
♪ Can you promise me that you will never forget me? ♪
I already used music as a weapon.
So there's one weapon left.
Do you know
that you're my favorite musical note?
You're also the work of art I love the most.
What are you guys doing?
Green!
Green, get out of here!
- It's still too early for this!
- Green, get out!
♪ How many drops of tears have I shed for love? ♪
♪ Streaming down my face since that day ♪
♪ It took us time to discover our love ♪
Green, get out of here!
♪ Never forget about this ♪
Why are you just standing there laughing?
♪ Can you promise me that you will never forget me? ♪
- I'm telling you to get out of here!
- No!
Set, ready.
- Sound!
- Speed.
- End slate.
And action!
Just keep practicing, and you will get used to it.
Okay.
So...
when are you going to teach me new chords?
I'm waiting to learn something new.
Here you go.
Let's eat.
Why are there only egg dishes these days?
Look at that.
Braised eggs.
Egg drop soup, omelette.
Umm...
Teacher,
give me your plate.
I'll get the rice for you.
Nah.
You have to eat a lot too.
You like to eat eggs, don't you?
I can't eat that much.
My heart is already full.
Cut! Slate.
Hit it.
I think what's between us
should stop here.
What do you mean?
I mean what I say.
Let's break up.
I told you I don't like it when you say that.
I'm serious this time.
I'm tired!
I want our relationship to continue,
but neither of us is trying to change.
I think we can only come this far.
I'm not trying to change?
No, you're not!
I asked you to care about my feelings.
Pay a little attention to me
But you never do!
You only care about yourself!
You care about everything
except me.
You don't care about me at all.
Even right now,
you still...
don't care about me.
Pun!
You're not me,
you don't understand.
Let's just break up, Inn.
Thank you.
Let's go.
Hello, everyone.
Welcome to the set of 'You and Your Beautiful Soul.'
We're going to shoot the second scene, which is the opening scene of 'Blue.'
The characters are Sian and Blue.
We'll start shooting in 20 minutes.
Okay.
Is everything ready?
Yes.
You're so handsome today.
I know, right? But I'm still a kid this time.
They are calling us now. Let's hurry.
Alright.
- The assistant director always rushes us.
- No need to hurry.
- Always in a hurry. What for?
- Exactly.
- We always get to eat last.
- That's right.
And we have to start working earlier than others.
By the time we get to eat, it's already late.
Where's the lipstick?
You guys are gossiping too much. He might barge in at any time.
You're right. He will come to rush us again.
What's up?
You thought no one would know because you’re wearing sunglasses?
That you were crying all night.
No one cried.
Hello.
Pun, Inn.
Do you want to practice the lines?
Sure, let's do it.
Who goes first?
Here we go.
It's too early.
Everyone.
Can I have ten minutes?
Hey.
Hello, Otto.
- Come on, bro.
- Hi.
I just came.
Come on, please help me.
You also act in this one?
How come I didn't know?
I'm not in this.
I'm here as an assistant director.
You're so cool!
Since when have you started working behind the scenes?
We just have to try new things, don’t we?
You're right, bro.
You're my idol!
Come on, Smile.
You say that to everyone.
Bro, just look at him.
Guys.
I'm going to change the breakdown since it's about to rain.
I don't want to risk it.
We're going to film the scene in the house first.
The first scene is scene 21.
I'm telling you guys first so that you can all get ready.
Bro.
Scene 21 is the sofa scene, right?
Yes.
Shooting the love scene first
is very hard.
It's not that hard. I know you guys can do it.
How about...
other scenes in the house?
Why don't we shoot that first?
We can't.
Those scenes will be filmed tomorrow,
so the art team hasn't prepared the props yet.
Just think of it as helping the crew so there won't be any overtime.
Um.
Okay?
Otto!
Please come see me on set right now.
Alright, I'll be right there.
10 more minutes, okay?
Please hurry up.
I'm coming.
Bro, am I in scene 21?
No.
But do you want to do it in my place?
Are you being sarcastic?
I'm just answering his question.
How can that be sarcastic?
Action!
Can we do it again?
Come on.
I’m really tired from earlier.
And you!
Why are you so strong?
Please, let's do it one more time.
One more.
No!
I have to clean dishes after this.
I have to cook.
And clean the house.
And wash your blanket too.
All you do is teach my brother guitar.
It's not that tiring for you.
I'm exhausted.
You're not me, you don't understand.
Cut!
Pun.
You took too long just now.
Make it sharper.
Okay.
You guys can continue where we left off.
Wait for Inn to say, 'You're not me, you don't understand.'
Let's start from here.
Okay.
Okay, everyone, let's get ready. Camera, sound!
Everyone gets ready.
Save speed!
Sound!
Everyone, ready.
Save speed!
4/21, cut 1, take 2.
And action!
You're not me,
you don't understand.
I'm...
I'm sorry.
Cut!
Pun, what's wrong?
You seem distracted.
Go outside and try to get your senses back.
Go!
Come back when you're ready.
Everyone, let’s keep the set as it is.
Otto, go check on him. What a waste of time!
There're so many scenes left.
If he's not ready, don't come back. Make sure it's sorted out.
Gosh!
The weather is being so unkind to me today.
It’s like it wants to tease me.
What are you complaning about?
Just look.
It didn't rain in the end.
We wouldn't have to shoot the sofa scene first.
You two have a problem, right?
Who wanted to break up first this time?
You're crazy.
You're thinking too much.
- I bet it was Inn.
- It was me!
I knew it.
I think I'm going to quit acting.
Wait.
Did you two have a big fight?
It's not about Inn.
It's because of me.
I saw you, and now I want to work behind the scenes too.
It's true that I work in production now,
but I still accept acting roles.
I know.
But I also have my own dream.
Also,
I didn't want to be an actor from the beginning.
You want to be a director.
You know that?
Why wouldn't I know?
You always say that whenever you give an interview.
Is it that obvious?
But right now, you have to focus on your work here.
Why are you here today?
I heard that the main actor has a problem,
so I intend to step in.
I'm just kidding! Don't think too much.
Excuse me.
Can I take a few behind-the-scenes photos?
Of course! I'd love to.
- Please be quick. We have to get back to shooting.
- Okay, sure.
Come inside when you're done.
- 3, 2 --
- Okay, everyone!
Can you move a bit closer?
3, 2, 1.
Thank you.
Pun!
Let's go.
The photos look nice.
- Hello, I've bought some snacks for you.
- Thank you so much, Pat. You come to the set every day.
Please take care of this.
How are you these days?
I'm always available.
Feel free to reach me anytime.
- You're free now?
- Yes.
- Okay, if I have a new project, I'll contact you.
- Great!
Let's talk later.
Okay, let's continue.
Give me back the script.
Let's do it.
Give me.
Okay!
Alright.
Wait.
Pun, take off your shirt.
Costume team, please check.
Okay, okay. Let me.
Slate, don't go in yet. Slow down.
- Okay, please hurry. We're running out of time. Come on, come on.
- Alright.
- Maintain your emotions.
- Thank you so much. Sorry!
Okay, the actors are on standby. Everyone, get ready.
Slate, not yet.
Camera.
- Sound!
- The crew, ready.
Slate, come in!
Save speed.
4/21, cut 1, take 3.
And action!
You're not me, you don't understand.
I'm sorry.
I don’t want to be in this movie because of Inn.
Cut!
This is already the eighth take!
Don’t ruin this.
- What the hell are you thinking?
- Just look at what you're doing now!
I’ve decided we should put a halt to this project.
What?