=Legal Boy=
=Episode 15=
You're here.
Why are you here?
Don't just stand there.
Come sit.
Brother, take a seat.
Dashui.
Dashui,
sit here.
Zhang Chongrui?
Why are you here?
Well,
to be honest,
I used your names
without asking today
just to show
my appreciation to Gouwa's friend.
Who do you think you are?
Legal Boy,
let's go.
Gouwa.
Look.
I think your brother means well.
Let's just dine here.
- Dashui.
- It's not that.
You're different now.
Every man
needs a watch.
My bad.
I forgot to get you a gift.
Well...
Take this.
Liu,
your watch
looks fancy.
Mr. Zhang, it's...
Here, be my guest.
Dashui.
Don't take it.
Thank you.
Much pricier than Liu's, right?
You shouldn't take it.
- Give it back.
- Gouwa.
Do you know what he...
Your brother seems sincere.
Why not give him a chance
and have a meal with him?
Sorry.
I want to sit next to Legal Boy.
Dashui,
it's okay. Sit here.
I'll sit over there.
Dashui,
Jinling means
Dashui is our guest of honor.
Please.
The head seat.
Breaking news:
Fang Finance Group's in cash flow crisis
due to mismanagement.
Fang Tuo came to you
and wanted you to acquire his company?
Yes.
I came to see you
right after he left.
Mr. Lu,
if the Zhang and Lu families
unite through marriage
and jointly acquire FFG,
we'll control all
commercial real estate projects
in Kanglan City.
We?
Isn't it a bit early
to say that?
If you don't trust me,
I can prove myself to you.
What do you mean?
I'll marry Miss Lu
and work in your family.
If you don't trust me,
I can hand Dongcan over to you.
I'll pretend I didn't hear that.
You should go.
Grandpa,
why was that weasel here?
Jinling,
I'm getting old.
Lu Group will
be yours sooner or later.
Grandpa,
what did that weasel say to you?
A marriage alliance with the Zhangs
is indeed
our best choice.
As for Legal Boy,
you need to clear the air
and get
a reply from him soon.
Did you set up Fang Tuo's account?
Chongrui,
I'm worried.
Worried about what?
I...
Love,
you've helped me so many times.
This is the last time.
Just help me finish this.
Then we can get away together.
Really?
Yes.
You're not lying again, are you?
Of course not.
Gouwa.
Dashui, come here.
Have a seat.
I was just about
to look for you.
I...
I need to talk to you.
I have something to tell you first.
Dashui,
I have
found you a job.
It's a warehouse position.
Considering your leg issue,
I mentioned it to Liu,
and he agreed.
Yes, Dashui.
The warehouse job is easy,
and the pay is high.
- Yes.
- It's a good job.
That's not what I meant.
Liu.
Alright.
Dashui, I'm off.
I'll leave you to it.
What's going on?
You know what?
I can offer you that.
I want to manage the site.
Do you trust Xia Dashui
to manage the site?
Legal Boy.
I need to talk to you.
My Lady.
What's up? Say it.
Sit down.
What's going on?
Tell me.
Come with me
to meet
my set-up date.