our love will be forever.
Episode 18
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday, baby.
Who is he?
Why are you back?
People say
don't give a surprise to your partner.
Because a surprise
can be a shock.
Let me see you.
About this,
I am at the height step of Ohャ you.
I didn't just want some one
to tell me how to Crazy Girl.
I just want you to see these
as your great fieldwork.
When you are on a part of make-up
I've never thought that I would be so depressed
after being educated so much.
I've never thought that my boyfriend who I loved for 7 years
would betray me.
Master, let's go to Yangshan Old Street.
Are you here for a trip?
No, I'm here to settle down.
You have such a good taste.
The food we have in Wuxi is incredible.
We have a lot of delicious food.
We can't wait to eat them all.
What do you mean by that?
You'll know it later.
Look forward to it.
I'm also looking forward to the future.
Yangshan Old Street
There's no noise here.
There's no fast-paced life.
I really like it here.
How about we settle down here
and open a homestay?
Okay.
I'll be the boss.
You'll be the man behind the boss.
May I ask
what name this smart and talented gentleman
gave us?
Let's call it
Qiyue Little House.
No way.
You just thought of this.
Qiyue,
no matter what it's called,
as long as I can be with you, it's good.
Then I'll design
this homestay in the future.
Okay, I'll listen to you.
As long as you're happy.
Yangshan Old Street
Now that we'veatan
the meeting should be starting.
Our company is responsible for the renovation project
of the old street in Yangshan.
The project has been promoted by 70%.
Most of the tenants
are very cooperative with us.
They are willing to communicate with us
about the decoration in the store.
But
only this one.
The owner of this homestay
is very uncooperative with our work.
He means
the decoration of this store
has taken a lot of effort.
So,
they are not very satisfied
with the compensation.
We should discuss with them
and try to give them
a satisfactory answer.
But our budget
is limited.
The compensation they want
is much more than our budget.
Leave this matter to me.
Miss, the cake shop is here.
Over. Over.
Touch me.
Mr. Gu, I can't understand.
Why are you in stereo
doing something explicarable?
Next question.
Why do all the bossy presidents like to pretend to be so unpredictable?
I heard it.
Mr. Gu, I'll buy you a milk tea.
The design is very Richard's late-night style. I like it.
You know a lot about the industry.
Did you also learn architecture when you came?
No, it's just my personal preference.
You said everything was Belgique style.
She's nothing more than a typical Questo-style beauty.
Baby
There are people I admire
all regard I am
and will be
However one day
where I go
there is a man
watching for me
A star
that shines bright
is walking towards me
I don't lose an eye
cold or hurt
I don't go
Then who am I?
Meng Tian.
Enough, stop talking.
How long have you been together?
Seven years.
Seven years?
You've been together for seven years?
Dong Zhuo, you bastard!
I finally know why this homestay is called Seven Months' House.
You lied to me that
it was because we've been together for seven months,
that's why it's called this name.
How did I fall in love with someone like you?
And I paid you five years' rent?
I'll give you two days to transfer the money to my card.
Otherwise, we're not done.
Why did you suddenly come back?
If you didn't come back,
there wouldn't be so many things.
Dong Zhuo.
You're so disgusting now.
Song Qi Yue, why are you blaming me?
Where have you been?
All these years we've been together,
it's all up to you.
You said you went abroad to study, so you went abroad to study.
Have you considered my feelings?
I'm a man, too.
I need company, too.
Have you seen a woman's clothes all these years?
Get out of here!
Devil.
Although you designed this homestay,
you paid the decoration fee.
But the rent contract was signed by me.
I'm the owner of this store.
Give me back my decoration fee.
Your money is all on this bridge.
If you're capable, you can tear it down.
You...
Hello.
Do you need help?
Everything is about life.
Nothing is too big.
Everything will be fine.
Life will always be like our Taiwan.
But after the rain, it will be sunny.
Come on.
There are many good people in Wuxi.
You won't be alone.
That's right.
I met someone today.
This person must be a ghost.
Please cherish it.
Time is so silent.
But it's so hard to remember.
It leaves no traces.
It's said to wait for you.
The wind blows in the new moon.
The four seasons stop at the sword.
No word can explain it.
Even in the mountains and mountains,
I will follow your path.
Just like the wind and the rain.
Even in the mountains and mountains,
I will follow your path.
Just like the wind and the rain.