our love
is right beside each other.
Episode 18
Hello, sir.
Do you have a reservation?
Zhao Yunyi booked a room.
Okay, let me check.
Zhao Yunyi
Yunyi is here for the video.
Yunyi
We just arrived.
We are in the middle of the night.
I have to get ready.
Have you had your meals?
I have ordered take-out for you.
No, no.
I am not hungry.
We have eaten a lot.
Good boy.
Okay.
You should have a rest.
I have arranged the schedule for tomorrow.
I will send it to your family.
Okay, okay.
I won't talk about it.
Your room is ready.
Room 203 on the second floor.
The big bedroom.
Go up and turn left.
Miss
Can you change the romantic big bedroom
into a standard room?
The romantic theme room you booked
is on the Internet.
The standard room will be more expensive.
Our big bedroom has a very good view.
It also has a light and double bathtub.
This is the standard room.
The kind of room where two beds are separated.
Yes, yes.
The price is the same.
I will check it for you.
Please wait a moment.
Have a rest.
Call me if you need anything.
Okay, thank you.
Bye.
It's so strange.
This couple is very polite and well-mannered.
But from the beginning to the end,
they didn't say a word.
It's like they have a grudge.
Do you think
they are not a real couple?
Then what are they?
Or
they are the high-class special forces
disguised as a couple.
Don't scare him.
They are a real couple.
Their daughters are all real.
They are not a couple.
They are a real couple.
Their daughters are all WeChat.
They even sent me several messages.
Listen.
Hello, sorry to bother you.
I am the daughter of the couple in the house.
I need your help.
Please help me see
how they are in real status.
I grew up in a happy family.
The relationship between parents is very harmonious.
But I always feel that
they have something to hide from me.
Sometimes I go home after school.
I see them
signing some kind of agreement.
I want to see
why mom wants to drive me away.
I started to live in the school in high school.
Every weekend, I go home,
I find that
dad sleeps in the living room at night.
And I find that
in their bedroom,
there are almost all of mom's things.
So after the college entrance examination,
I decided to
book this trip for them.
I really want to know
what's wrong with them.
Look at this.
I have a good card.
But I have a 3.
Do you think
this question
will appear on this 3?
I think this thing
has nothing to do with 3.
Shut up.
I think
this thing
has nothing to do with 3.
Why are you so bold?
You should let me go.
You don't have any tacit understanding.
We haven't won
a single game.
You can
fight with Duo Duo.
You think I don't want to?
It's not up to me.
I don't want to fight with you.
So some things
are not decided by us
from the beginning.
Since you have made a choice,
you should just go ahead.
Hello.
Do you need any help?
Can you open another store for me?
Sorry, sir.
Our room is full.
Sir.
It's so late.
Where is he going?
I didn't want him to go.
So I lied to him that there was no room.
I didn't expect him to go.
How can I tell his daughter?
Gu Ci'an,
you have to find a way.
I'll go out and get him back.
Duo Duo, what should we do?
Call him.
Yes.
Call his daughter.
Hello, Zhu Gu Li.
Go and arrange it.
What are you doing?
I...
I called his daughter
and asked her to call his father back.
It's almost 12 o'clock.
How much are you worried about him now?
What do you think we should do?
It's a three-day trip.
They broke up on the first night.
I wanted to play a trick.
I didn't expect to make it work.
Don't worry.
In an hour,
he will definitely come back.
Are you sure?
When did I lie to you?
You two go to rest first.
I'll wait here.
So handsome.
Duo Duo, let's go.
Hello, Zhu Gu Li.
How did you do this?
All the hotels in the five kilometers
of the Qimeng District
have been notified
of the arrival of the president
and the arrival of the upper and lower part
of the 50-yuan hotel.
Okay.
I got it.
He's back.
Brother,
we've been waiting for you.
You should drink.
I'll go to rest.
I've been waiting for you.
You should drink.
Brother,
my daughter is getting married.
I should drink to celebrate.
Yes, you should.
Brother, I'll take you to your room.
You should drink with me.
More?
Yes, you're familiar with this area.
Let's find a place to drink.
Brother.
Brother,
I'm calling you to drink with me.
I'm not asking you to drink.
You should drink some noodle soup
to relieve your hangover.
I didn't drink too much.
Kun Shan Ouzhao Noodles
is fresh and warm.
You can drink it like this.
It can relieve hangover
and nourish your stomach.
Really?
I'm really looking for the wrong person.
To be honest,
I just want to try
the delicious food in Wuxi
and see the scenery of Huishan.
Don't worry.
Go back to your room.
Have a good rest.
I'll give you and your aunt
a double-edged sword in the afternoon.
What's wrong?
I've discussed with Kai.
I'll go out on the first day.
He'll rest in the hotel.
I'll rest when he goes out on the second day.
Why don't you go out together?
Going out together
is not a fight.
It's not happy.
It's been so many years.
It's all the past.
Eat it.
Congratulations, aunt.
Yiyi got into the 985.
It's a good thing.
Yes.
I've completed
my mission with her dad.
It's a pity that uncle is not here.
Otherwise, we can celebrate at noon.
Don't.
She celebrates her.
I celebrate mine.
It's good to be together without disturbing each other.
The landowner.
Why are these three cards so bad?
There's no way.
That's the rule.
Since you've chosen,
you can't go back on your words.
I'd rather be a farmer.
With these three cards,
I don't know how to get them.
How can I get them?
Just make a mistake.
Hurry up.
Aunt, I have a message.
I don't know if it's good or bad.
What's wrong?
Yiyi said today is your and uncle's
wedding anniversary.
Really?
We've been together for a long time.
Yiyi said she wanted to give you a surprise.
She's off the plane.
What?
What are you playing?
Let's get her dad back.
The two suitable people
are like sugar in a wuxi xiaolong bag.
It sounds incredible.
In fact, it's very sweet and delicious.
If the two people who are not suitable are together,
will it be like winter dates with bananas?
They are all delicious.
Eating together is a smell.
These two foods won't be together.
Maybe they will appear in the fruit plate.
To make it look good.
This winter date can be replaced with apples.
Yes.
Bananas can also be replaced with star anise.
The wind blows in the wind
The sky is full of fragrance
Time is silent
But remember the memories
Don't leave a trace
The secret under the peach tree
The wind in July is sweet
The four seasons are over
No word can describe
Even in the mountains and mountains
I have to pursue your path
Just like the wind and the rain
Even in the mountains and mountains
I have to pursue your path
Just like the wind and the rain