K-foodie meets J-foodie.
This is insane.
OSAKA, JAPAN
OSAKA, THE NO. 1 GOURMET TRAVEL SPOT
THE JAPANESE COMFORT FOOD
THAT RIVALS JJAJANGMYEON
JJAJANGMYEON VS YAKISOBA
-Next time…
-Yes.
-…we'll go to Sakai in Osaka…
-Okay.
…and I'll take you to an okonomiyaki place
where the owner turns
everything into a masterpiece.
I want to go there.
EPISODE 19
MATJJIGAE'S ALL-TIME FAVORITE YAKISOBA
Where are we?
-We're in…
-Yes.
…Sakai.
Sakai is located just south of Osaka…
30 MINUTES BY CAR
…and it's actually pretty rich in culture
-and history.
-I see.
-But it's kind of low-key.
-Is it?
-I once stayed here…
-Okay.
…when I was filming
a YouTube show at a place in Sakai
that makes knives and Japanese swords.
Since I was already here,
I wanted to eat something delicious,
so I kept walking.
-Like Goro?
-Just like him.
When I was about to give up,
thinking, "Guess there's nothing here,"
I arrived in front of this shop
that was packed.
I went around looking for other places,
-but nothing stood out.
-Okay.
So I figured I should
check this place one more time
and asked, "Do you have a seat now?"
They said, "We'll make one for you,"
so I ended up going in.
It's a rather embarrassing story.
-It was meant to be.
-Right.
It's an okonomiyaki place.
The Kansai region
is famous for flour-based dishes,
so there are many good okonomiyaki places,
-but this one exceeded my expectations.
-Was it the best?
Everything that came out was delicious.
-Back in Korea…
-Yes.
-Was it jjajangmyeon?
-Right. At Seohojang.
That dish ties in…
-That makes sense.
-…with this place.
Koreans have jjajangmyeon,
-and the Japanese have yakisoba, right?
-Yes.
Yakisoba makes
us Japanese feel nostalgic too.
They serve old-school favorites
like yakisoba, okonomiyaki,
and other griddle dishes.
Is that the place?
-Nice vibe, right?
-It's great.
-Fukuya.
FUKUYA
YAKISOBA, OKONOMIYAKI
-Excuse me.
-Welcome.
Come on in.
-I'm back again.
-Thank you.
-Of course.
Good to see you.
-Hello. I'm Sung Si-kyung.
-Thank you.
-Welcome.
-Nice to see you again.
-I look forward to eating here.
-I'm a bit embarrassed.
Honestly, the last thing I wanted
was to promote this place.
-But I think the secret's getting out.
-Really?
We have your autograph on the wall.
It seems like people
are looking up our place online.
-He also mentioned this place…
-Yes.
…a few times on Korean TV.
-That there's a legendary place in Osaka.
-I saw that.
A place with the best okonomiyaki ever.
-I met Yu Jae-seok.
-Yes.
He's Korea's version of Sanma Akashiya.
Yes, I saw the show.
-The actress, Shim Eun-kyung…
-Right.
-…who won the Japan Academy Prize…
-Yes.
-…was also with you.
-Exactly.
People thought
you might've meant this place.
I definitely meant this place.
That's too much praise.
I really didn't want this place
to become well-known.
This might be the worst episode ever.
It is. And we're on Netflix too.
Netflix.
-People might come from around the world.
-Koreans will flock here.
I'm truly sorry.
-This is his griddle.
-He does everything.
The owner makes everything himself.
He keeps grilling like a griddle magician.
No, don't say that.
He must feel pressured!
You've been praising him for ten minutes.
This is his stage.
75 YEARS OF GRIDDLE TRADITION
PASSED DOWN THROUGH THREE GENERATIONS
ALL KINDS OF DISHES BORN ON THE GRIDDLE
MAIN DISH
OKONOMIYAKI &amp; YAKISOBA
Delicious.
This really is amazing.
This place really is the best.
I think it's the best in Japan.
Yakisoba. This is insane.
I wish I'd known this place sooner…
This really is
the best okonomiyaki I've ever had.
This is dangerously good.
What should we order first?
You should tell me what to get.
Should we save the okonomiyaki
and yakisoba for later?
Personally,
-there are…
-Yes.
…some griddle dishes I'd eat first.
-Right.
-We'll eat those first,
-and finish with okonomiyaki and yakisoba.
-Okay.
-Should I do that?
-Sure.
-Okay.
-When you come here, you have to try
the tomato dish.
What?
The tomato dish…
It's the grilled mochi tomato cheese.
-Yes, that's it.
-Right.
That and something shrimp.
-Mayo shrimp.
-Okay.
-We should have intestines too, right?
-The stamina dish.
-Stamina stir-fry. Got it.
THREE APPETIZERS ORDERED
COOKING BEGINS ON THE COOKING GRIDDLE
WARMING GRIDDLE
WARMING GRIDDLE ON
I wanted to ask you something.
In Korea, griddle cooking gives off
a somewhat upscale vibe.
In Japan, there are two types.
-Right.
-The fancy kind
-is where they grill…
-Yes.
-At hotels.
-…steak in front of you.
And then you have
these okonomiyaki places.
In the past,
there were always places like this
near elementary schools.
-There were casual eateries.…
-Like tteokbokki stalls.
…where kids could grab a bite
with their allowance.
Dak-kalbi plays a similar part in Korea.
Dak-kalbi?
It's spicy stir-fried chicken
made on a round griddle.
There was always a good dak-kalbi place
in front of every school
-back then.
-I see.
It's affordable.
We should try it too sometime.
APPETIZER
MAYO SHRIMP
Excuse me.
-Here's your mayo shrimp.
-That's cute.
-Enjoy.
-Bon appétit.
Try some.
MAYO SHRIMP
6,000 WON, 600 YEN
-Let's eat.
-Bon appétit!
We have to start with this.
No surprise there. It's amazing.
How could it not be?
For those watching from Korea,
it's just like you'd expect.
It tastes exactly as it looks.
By the way,
this might be a little rude to say,
but it's such a simple combination.
-Right.
-And there are a lot of dishes like this.
I tried making it at home,
since it’s not a complicated dish.
-But I can't get this flavor.
-You can't?
I don't know why.
Maybe the vibe plays a role too.
Having a griddle in front of you,
the owner cooking before your eyes,
and eating it fresh off the griddle.
When you're sharing food
in a noisy, smoky place
full of chatter and laughter,
you start wondering,
"Why can't I recreate this at home?"
The owner makes everything over there.
He's cooking nonstop.
But I have to say,
Japanese mayonnaise really is delicious.
There are so many kinds of mayo in Japan.
Pollock roe mayo is famous in Fukuoka.
And there are healthier options
like half-calorie mayo
or ones with richer flavors.
There are so many varieties,
so I always take some home.
I see.
That's the grilled mochi tomato cheese.
APPETIZER
GRILLED MOCHI TOMATO CHEESE
Here's your grilled mochi tomato cheese.
8,000 WON, 800 YEN
-It kind of looks like pizza.
-This is…
-It almost seems like Italian food.
-It does.
Thank you.
This is so good.
It's not just ketchup,
and not just tomato.
The two together create
-such a delicious flavor.
-I agree.
These go so well together.
I love it.
It's got that Italian vibe,
so it adds a nice twist.
This is seriously good.
It's the best.
It feels like a Western dish,
but there's mochi, which is very Asian.
This feels like a theme park of flavors.
Every bite is a different ride.
Everyone would enjoy this.
This is the kind of dish you crave
no matter how old you are.
It feels like I'm at
a casual Western-style restaurant.
Should I drizzle this on top?
-Did you add more mayo?
-Yes.
It's good.
-It is.
-Very tasty.
It would also be great on bread.
You could just put this on top.
The scraped-off cheese bits.
That crispy part is irresistible.
-What's this?
-Stamina stir-fry intestines.
This is really good too.
STAMINA STIR-FRY INTESTINES
7,800 WON, 780 YEN
APPETIZER
STAMINA STIR-FRY INTESTINES
Why do Japanese dishes
use the word "stamina?"
Do people believe eating intestines
gives you stamina?
-Why would that be?
-Because of the garlic.
-Oh, the garlic.
-Yes.
Any dish with garlic
get labeled "stamina."
Does that mean it boosts your virility?
I think you mean energy.
Virility is…
Choose your words carefully.
Virility doesn't necessarily mean
sexual energy in Korean.
It can also just mean energy.
-That's true.
-Yes.
These are the intestines.
This is insane.
Are these pork intestines?
No, they're beef.
-Beef intestines.
-Yes.
Which part is this?
It seems like makchang.
-It's akasen in Japanese.
-Okay.
It's the cow's fourth stomach.
I think the part you liked the most
when we had gopchang in Korea
-was this one.
-I remember.
-Really?
-Makchang.
-Yes, it has a nice texture.
And there's not much fat.
It feels like we just went from
a Western restaurant to a yakiniku place.
Right?
You can travel the world here.
Ichimi chili powder.
-Is it good?
-It's the best.
This is so well-seasoned
and the texture is incredible.
It's amazing.
The sweetness of
the veggies is irresistible.
I agree. The sweetness of the vegetables…
-And that sound is so nice, too.
-Isn’t it?
It lets you know that
someone is making it with care.
Should we have okonomiyaki and yakisoba?
Sure. Yakisoba.
-Is okonomiyaki with everything the best?
-Right.
-With everything.
-Yes.
And for yakisoba…
Are there that many kinds?
I'm trying to decide
what toppings to put in it.
A lot of customers order
the one with everything.
-It comes with a fried egg on top.
-Then we'll go with that!
-Sounds good.
-Okay.
What's the difference between
Hiroshima-style
and Osaka-style okonomiyaki?
Koreans don't really know.
Really?
-They look pretty similar.
-Well, that's…
If you say, "They’re all the same,"
Osaka people get mad,
and Hiroshima people say,
"They’re different!"
OSAKA-STYLE VS HIROSHIMA-STYLE
THE NEVER-ENDING DEBATE
We use more batter in Osaka.
OSAKA-STYLE
EVERYTHING IS MIXED
INTO THE BATTER AND GRILLED
In Hiroshima, they stack the cabbage
and steam it on the griddle.
HIROSHIMA-STYLE
GRILLED IN LAYERS, STEAMED FROM WITHIN
MAIN DISH
OKONOMIYAKI
He keeps his gaze on the food.
He's cooking with care.
-He's in tune with the food.
-That's impressive.
I just stand here and zone out.
You're like, "I will make this delicious!"
Even when it's busy,
you just stand there, focused.
That is true.
-When you work on several dishes at once…
-Yes.
-…they cook at different times.
-Right.
How do you know which one's done?
Just by instinct?
I just know.
That's like his stage.
-Here.
-Okay.
-Excuse me.
-It's here.
Okonomiyaki with everything.
Finally!
OKONOMIYAKI WITH EVERYTHING
6,800 WON, 680 YEN
-There's green laver powder…
-Okay
…and bonito powder.
-Good.
-Add to your taste.
-All right.
-Okay.
I'll sprinkle a little.
It's bonito powder.
He knows what he's doing.
Isn't that too much?
Not at all.
-Is this okay?
-Yes.
You can add as much as you want.
-Let me use this for a second.
-Sure.
And then you add
mayonnaise to your taste.
Exactly.
You're like an okonomiyaki warrior.
-There. Let's dig in!
-Okay.
I'm going to go wild…
with mayo.
MATJJIGAE'S STYLE
PILING ON THE MAYO
SI-KYUNG'S STYLE
ADD MAYO
AND SAUCE
-I'll start.
-Enjoy.
It's delicious.
-It's good.
-Isn't it?
It's light.
-It just melts in your mouth.
-Right.
You only notice the cabbage by its flavor.
I can taste it, but I can't feel it.
-Very airy, right?
-Yes.
You know, okonomiyaki
is usually on the heavier side.
It can be quite dense with batter.
But with this one, the cabbage
just kind of melts away,
so you could eat a lot more.
I can keep going.
-I told you.
-Yes.
It just keeps going in.
I've never had anything like this.
It changes your idea
of okonomiyaki, doesn't it?
This is beyond fluffy.
He really knows
how to add air to the batter.
It puffed up beautifully.
This is amazing.
It's got volume, but when you chew it…
It's airy.
Right. Airy.
This place is incredible. Really.
If you think anyone can make this dish,
you're seriously mistaken.
-I agree.
-The way…
he adds air is something else.
Adding air is everything, right?
-When you mix it.
-When we mix it?
There's no special technique, though.
There isn't?
That was humblebragging.
I think this is the best okonomiyaki
I've had in Osaka.
No doubt about it.
I think it's the best in Japan.
-This place is on another level.
-It really is.
It's in a different league.
I never thought
I'd want to bring my parents
to a place with sauce-covered okonomiyaki.
It's usually heavy.
But here, I'd love to come back
with my parents or seniors.
They'd definitely say,
-"This is amazing."
-Right.
They'd definitely love it.
I hope Koreans get to try this too.
This might be the first time I've had
such a light, airy okonomiyaki.
If you think this is
what okonomiyaki is supposed to be,
you won't be satisfied anywhere else.
And you didn't find this place online.
You just stumbled upon it.
Basically, some higher power led me here.
I heard cabbage prices in Japan
skyrocketed. It must've been tough.
It must have been tough
when cabbage prices went up.
Yes, it was rough.
But we had to buy it anyway.
We can't run the business without it.
True.
If napa cabbage prices go up in Korea,
-restaurants really struggle.
-I bet.
-Because kimchi is free.
-Right.
-For restaurants in Japan…
-So it's tough.
…the only thing you get for free
is water that they give you
at the beginning.
Even otoshi,
a small appetizer, isn't free.
Do you have otoshi in Korea?
-No.
-Really?
-Yes.
-Maybe someone should speak up and say,
"Let's stop giving out free kimchi."
If I ever said that,
I'd probably have to retire.
You'd be done for.
If you're okay with that,
maybe you should say it.
Think of the people who make kimchi.
We should start a campaign.
"Time to charge for kimchi!"
Making kimchi takes so much work.
So most restaurants have given up
making it themselves
-and just import it, which is sad.
-That's…
-just bad for everyone.
-I agree.
People would want real Korean kimchi,
even if they had to pay.
It might be better to charge customers
for properly-made Korean kimchi.
Here's your yakisoba.
This sound.
YAKISOBA WITH EVERYTHING
7,300 WON, 730 YEN
MAIN DISH
YAKISOBA
Jjajangmyeon led us to this.
-This is what we came for.
-Right.
-I don't know if it's okay to say this…
-Yes?
But it’s like eating
the most basic yakisoba
without any vegetables.
Yakisoba has a nostalgic taste,
and jjajangmyeon is the same.
-This is the real deal.
-Do we eat it as is?
You can sprinkle
green laver powder if you want.
How is it?
Delicious.
They're all sauce-based dishes
but they all taste different.
In some places, you can't even tell
what you ate.
Their dishes taste the same.
What do you think?
I could eat three servings of this
all by myself.
Right?
Everyone who comes here
gulps down the food
as if they're going to order
the entire menu.
This is the best.
It tastes kind of like jjajangmyeon too.
-Doesn't it?
-Yes.
Even Japanese people who've eaten
yakisoba and okonomiyaki to death
-would be blown away.
-Totally.
-Right?
-I was really shocked.
It's so good.
This is so delicious.
Thank you.
Deep down,
I wanted to keep this place to myself.
I'm sorry.
There's no going back now.
I really didn't want to tell anyone.
This is dangerous.
I just can't stop eating.
What should I do?
You should come here again.
You'll have to come back soon.
I should stop eating.
I genuinely want to come here again.
Nice.
What time do you open?
We open at 11:30 a.m.
When do we leave,
the day after tomorrow?
NEXT INSANELY GOOD SPOT
Love is in the air.
HANGANG RIVER RAMYEON VS KYOTO MONT BLANC
DATE SPOT BATTLE
Because of instant ramyeon,
you need to stop by
a Hangang River convenience store
this time of the year.
It's really delicious and kind of fun.
It almost felt like a date.
Subtitle translation by Soya Back