This program is for ages 19 and over
because it contains adult elements,
violence, and risk of impersonation
This program contains ads
indirect and virtual advertising
All characters, names, events and
everything else in this drama is fictitious.
Episode 5
[Subtitles translation by @ADrama_Lovers team]
Said she is going back to America,
and left for airport about two hours ago.
Let's go to the airport.
If she left for the airport two hours ago,
there's still a chance we'll find her.
According to the nurse, Its not because of Laura Caine
doesn't know Korean well.
Even though I don't know how to say it,
but she understood roughly.
So she pretended to not know?
I mean she can communicate
with Lee Sung-Gon.
At least, understand to some extent
what Lee Sung-Gon said.
After Laura Caine
met Lee Sung-Gon...
You said she was treated
in the hospital for shock?
Yes.
Please tell her,
when you see her again.
If, I hope she remembers...
What I said and stay alive.
Murderer.
Lee Sung-Gon told Laura Caine,
about the crimes he committed.
3F . departure
Detective,
Too late.
Maybe she will call after she reaches America?
Who knows.
There's no reason to talk yourself,
especially how her older brother became a murderer
and how she must live the rest of her life,
as the killer's sister.
Detective,
Forgive me.
I have sinned.
I lied to you two
When you were little,
your father was a barber isn't he?
Did Laura Caine's mother help your father
running a barbershop?
The reason you put a white robe
on your victims,
is because of bad memories,
that you had as a child.
Isn't that right?
Isn't that unfair, Detective?
It's all because of that woman and her mother.
Why only I have to experience it
and live like this? Why?
The woman eats well and lives well
in America, whereas why only me.
Why should I live
with pain? Why?
Hey!
Unlucky! Why are you wearing lipstick
red again?
Why? I told you
not to wear it.
Which other man are you seducing!
Hey.
Come here! Here!
Why don't you listen to me, why!
Where else are you going?
you left me,
You can't go anywhere.
I will follow you to hell.
Now let it all go.
You have to be free
from that pain now.
If you keep holding on,
you will only continue to suffer.
This...
You killed them all?
All five?
Then among the five,
is there a woman you didn't kill?
Who's she?
How can I find out?
Isn't that something only known
by the real killer?
You said you killed them all,
This bastard!
When?
I never said that
with my mouth.
Aren't you supposed to record this?
I never said it.
Isn't that unfair, Detective?
It's all because of that woman and her mother.
Why only I have to experience it
and live like this? Why?
The woman eats well and lives well
in America, whereas why only me.
Why should I live
with pain? Why?
Is this your motive?
It...
Could it be my motive?
Killing people for that reason?
Yes?
Okay.
You are right.
No excuses for you in the first place.
You only blame others
at your uncontrollable urge,
to kill.
Killing weapon. your past.
The traces you left
Everyone says you did it.
You can't dodge.
Whether you killed five or four,
You will never come back
to this society in the end.
Only,
just say you
didn't kill Jung Hee-Joo.
For the deceased Jung Hee-Joo.
For her bereaved family.
This is the last and only way
you can make someone imitate you, that's all.
It was a funny joke.
Think about it.
If I confess I didn't kill her,
did i kill the rest?
No, why should I tell like that?
Why? Why?
You will be remembered forever for sure.
As the protagonist of the serial killer case.
which even created imitators.
Not a childish impersonator
imitating others.
Arrest him.
But ..
now I,
won't meet them again right?
Too bad, even though they
are lovely people.
Fast.
Did Lee Sung-Gon said anything,
that I should know?
Oh Ji-Hyeok.
Tell him about us meeting
with Lee Sung-Gon's younger sister.
What was that?
I'll send you the sound recording.
This will be very helpful in uncovering
Lee Sung-Gon's murder motive.
Fine, I will Make sure to mention you guys as
source in the report.
you don't have to,
Just say that we
have found the motive.
On the contrary,
you just need to remember that we
have shared content.
Shit!
Embarrassing.
Why?
One who doesn't even look like a human,
I became emotional to when I was speaking,
about Jung Hee-Joo's family,
though I can't get it.
Why am I like this, lately?
- You must be going through puberty.
- What?
Puberty and moderate menopause
overlap each other.
Although the case is rare.
Right. As you said,
it seems true this is puberty.
My body is aging,
but my mind is still a child.
What a shame.
Detective!
This is the translation of the statement from
Lee Sung-Gon's sister.
It became clear why he
killed those women that way.
I think it will be useful in court.
Who told you to judge?
- Yes?
- I make the decisions.
Don't rush ahead.
Watch your mouth, got it?
I understand.
Forgive me.
I have sinned.
My stepdad cut my mom's throat with his razor blade.
and her white robe was stained with blood.
I still remember like yesterday.
and I think the memories have stuck forever for my brother too
Why did your stepdad kill your mother?
He got mad because,
my mom put red lipstick on her lips.
I was so young, that's all i remember.
It reminds you of bad memories
from your childhood, right?
So you put white dress on your victims,
and put lipstick on them.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Otherwise, by chance,
Did serial killing technique of Kim Hyeong Bok reminded,
you of your hidden past?
"That's why I followed
Kim Hyeong-Bok method,"
"and committed the crime of impersonation."
What's that?
Between both?
But,
No matter what, you're still trash.
But, Detective,
first of all I didn't kill anyone.
Then imitate?
That is not true.
I was just trying to scare her.
Of course,
From the Detective's point of view,
it will be better for you
if I become a copycat, right?
That's what you said to the reporters.
You don't have to think about
from our point of view.
Then, apart from this case,
just say it,
that I'm the culprit.
How?
However, I didn't kill anyone.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
But do you know?
I don't need confession
from a bastard like you.
You just have to say
in front of people,
that you are only guilty of
using drugs and kidnapping people.
Lee Sung-Gon, you have the right to refuse
any statement that can,
be used against you as evidence in court.
You also have rights to a lawyer.
Oh, yes.
One more.
If you want, we can refer you
to a professional for mental evaluation.
That bastard,
just going to talk nonsense
in front of the prosecutor?
These people have strange talents.
He won't.
There is only one thought
in his head now,
that he has to survive
somehow.
So,
he can kill people again.
- He's out.
- Already out.
Do you admit to all the accusations?
I,
told to the police,
the truth of every thing
which I have done.
Without missing a single one.
Like what happened.
What kind of crime are you talking about?
I sincerely,
apologize,
to the victim,
who is hurt because of me.
I was only
trying to scare her.
Only up to here.
- Wait a moment.
- Please step aside.
Do you feel guilty?
Lee Sung-Gon's investigation is complete
and sent to the prosecutor
It is known that he admitted to kidnapping
and attempted murder
Not admitting to the crime of impersonation
What was your motive?
Shit!
Didn't we predict that
he would come out with something like that?
The question is whether
Seoul Investigation Team,
have the desire to investigate
Lee Sung-Gon to the end.
The two of them would have definitely agreed,
to do it this way, like that.
However, in the end Kim Hyeong-Bok is
still a serial killer, right?
Damn, this makes no sense.
Everything we found gave
to seoul team,
from that bus route map,
shouldn't Lee Sung-Gon be the culprit?
Team leader, should we just keep quiet like this?
The results of the investigation haven't come out yet, have they?
- Let's take our time..
- What should we pay attention to?
It is clear. We know everything.
Isn't that what it should be done by our chief?
You punk.
Why do you want to face the chief?
Isn't the chief responsible for that job?
You said he wouldn't fall so easily.
So try talking to him.
He have been nagging me,
some time ago,
so I'm avoiding him.
Kang Do-Chang, Oh Ji-Hyeok you two
talk to the chief.
If I'm the team leader, telling you guys
talk like that, definitely pass.
Why didn't this person give me
such a case?
Sir!
Detective,
What should we do?
Because of puberty, these days
I have a lot on my mind.
Give me some time to think.
I'll go home first,
See you tomorrow.
- Goodbye.
- Yes.
What is it?
- What puberty?
- You guys don't know puberty?
This is a time for a storm of anger and frustration.
Very noisy.
- This.
- Is everything done?
Yes.
You should also take this.
And also...
Please eat this too.
Diabetes,
is not just an adult disease.
This is also a disease that is even found in small children,
for genetic or congenital reasons.
I didn't know at first.
When you grow up,
you start to question it.
When the other friends run,
why should I only suffer from this?
Why is there a devil,
which lives in my body since birth.
The devil demands,
daily insulin injections.
And it takes away the feeling of happiness,
from daily life.
Several times a day I ask,
to the devil inside of me.
Why should it be me?
Why did you,
choose me?
Please answer that question,
to the children who suffer,
same as me..
There's nothing wrong with you,
I promise to plant,
the tree of hope again in your body.
Thank you
Thank you for being here.
Thank you Thank you
Isn't it obvious?
What does Na-Na want?
This is an event
intended only for her.
Because of loneliness.
I don't like the President's opinion.
It's just an attempt
to change public opinion.
Sacrifice for your father
while uncovering the bottle
even the dirtiest?
Then it must be beautiful.
Geez!
Geez! What brings you here, sir?
Hello.
You must be busy,
but thank you so much for coming.
I had to come.
It's a good show.
Sir, should I take your picture?
Yes, that's good.
Photos only when no one is nearby
Well.
I think you guys are pretty close
with our group,
am i the only one thinking
like that?
I'm the picky type of person.
So, I'm wary of friends.
Because it's clearly visible
there is a purpose.
How about this?
We won't be able to see you
comfortably until,
till your term is over.
Please contact me
at the end of your term.
Because I thought we would have
more work to help.
Hey, Im Chang-Soo.
Honestly say.
Did you come to see me?
Or did you come for Na-Na?
- Have you checked it?
- Yes.
I'm having trouble finding
edited version and check it out.
Yes, here.
In one hour,
- will appear in the program.
- Did you know about the PD program?
Yes. I met him for a while
and suggest it,
- but he's not a very good friend.
- In that case, okay.
Send text messages with mobile number of PD or any higher ups.
Fine, I understand.
Are you leaving now?
Yes, you're busy.
I also have to do something.
Okay.
Thank you for coming.
But is that okay?
- The price of the art you bought is not cheap.
- Hey, come on.
No problem.
I know my company's money.
- I'll call you later.
- Yes.
How much time till TJ's content being broadcast?
4 minutes 58 seconds.
But is it okay if
we broadcast it?
The response will be very strong.
There's no need to be afraid. Trust me.
Director!
'Cause it seems you already know,
I'll get straight to the point.
Call them and cancel the broadcast.
Yes?
Suddenly?
You are eating your own flesh.
The President received a warrant of arrest.
If the case of the vice president will be
uncovered, the stock price will fall.
Why?
Did the vice president
make any mistake?
If the stock price falls,
this must be serious.
Did you tell
McQueen headquarters?
In this case, it seems that there are many who will want to talk to you.
You love your wife, right?
It seems so.
Na-Na is such a person.
Her husband is the one who will
do anything for her,
and she can do anything for him.
Will it appear on TV broadcasts?
You didn't invite many reporters
to this event.
This event is not held
to broadcast on TV.
If this is an event for the President,
should not it be
known to the general public?
I do this with a sincere heart.
No other intentions.
Really?
In that case,
Woo Tae-Ho lied to me apparently.
Deputy Director.
Let's talk for a moment.
Okay.
What are you talking about?
How did he know?
Some time ago,
I was contacted by the Japan branch office.
That you are caught in a fraud case.
This case will be broadcast
on the news program in an hour.
What kind of person is he really?
The one who knows my weakness.
McQueen.
He can be crazy.
I will be humiliated,
and if Daddy finds out, he won't even
treat me as a human.
Woo Tae Ho.
Please save me.
I really beg you.
We've messed up enough already
because of no ads,
is there any reason
for us to reject it?
Please think again
for the company's income.
I beg.
What did he say?
Did he threaten you
to remove all the ads?
- We have to reduce the duration.
- Yes?
Suddenly a lot of ads will be
aired after our program.
We have to eliminate
more than five minutes
and edit the rest properly.
Thank you
With this I have decided.
If you don't change your mind,
you and me,
we will walk till the end.
Please go in.
I am going.
This is the only one that didn't sell.
Is the price too high?
Yet this is very good work.
I blocked it.
I had to block it.
Why?
Na-Na,
do you think you can handle it
with your own strength?
You think Cheon Sang-Woo will
stop if you ask?
The President will never
let go of Cheon Sang-Woo.
I understand that more than anyone.
you, could it be,
You're not interested in Cheon Sang-Woo,
but on the president?
Na-Na,
That's really crazy stuff.
What is your purpose in coming here?
What?
Didn't you come because you're my husband?
As a sister, I thank you
for the help you gave.
as Son-in-law of Choi Sung-Dae,
as brother-in-law of Choi Sang-Woo,
everyone would be proud.
And also as the husband of Cheon Na-Na.
Do you know why I chose you?
You were the first one to lower your head.
In front of a prosecutor like you.
It was Really cool that I,
Can't forget it.
I won't forget that.
There will be a closing party after this,
don't stay away from me.
You caught Lee Sung-Gon, right?
Right.
Then that person named Lee Sung-Gon,
is he the culprit?
Or as the news said,
he only scared people?
Lee Sung-Gon is indeed the culprit.
In that case,
did he kill Hee-Joo too?
We also don't know for sure.
Haven't you been
caught many suspects before?
Didn't you catch him
because you are sure that he is the culprit?
You don't accuse someone who isn't
guilty of murder, right?
No.
You caught him
for some reason, right?
I am begging you.
"That person did it."
"That guy killed Hee-Joo."
Please say that.
I don't know, I don't know either.
How can I know that
if that person killed your granddaughter?
I don't even know!
Only the killer knows.
Detectives aren't that great.
Unless we see the crime
with our own eyes,
we don't know anything.
We also can't answer
whether he really did it or not.
it seems like I,
have put too much pressure on you.
I...
I've been too selfish.
Forgive me.
Thanks for the tea.
Eun-Hye, over there is food
which I wrapped.
- Bring it here and give it to Grandpa.
- No need.
I do not want to trouble you more than this.
Quickly give it to him!
Yes.
Grandpa.
Grandpa!
Please accept this.
Please dont be like this.
Don't make me a shameless old man.
Yes.
Then, be careful on the road.
Thank you
Why were you like that?
What? What? Are you?
You should speak with well manners with older people.
He must be very sad
because he lost his granddaughter.
"The culprit has been caught.
now you can rest easy."
- You could have told him like that.
- That's enough!
Why should I take responsibility
for such a person?
I'm tired. I feel like my brain is going to explode.
I also have to live in peace!
Then why did you become a detective,
If you live for yourself?
I don't know either.
Why do I have to live like this.
It is not like that,
why did you lose confidence?
You said detective
is a noble job.
I don't fit, I dont fit at all.
That's why you left in the middle
your own wedding party,
to catch the culprit.
Hey!
Why are you bringing that up?
you used to be,..
you said you have no regrets.
You were satisfied because you
managed to catch the culprit
and soothe the victim's feelings.
Isn't that the pride of a detective?
At that time I just, I don't know.
Uncle,
uncle you were even married?
Hey.
You know how stupid this human is?
In the midst of his wedding feast,
The culprit was right in front of his eyes.
Just try it ,if you
tell this to Eun-Hye,
I will throw you on the street!
Eun-Hye please clean this,
if he drinks more in
In this situation, he will be really messed up.
Okay.
I haven't finished drinking yet.
Uncle, stop drinking
and rest.
Please.
I warn you,
don't tell her anything.
Brother,
After thinking about it,
You can't work in an office.
There is no travel allowance
and too much overtime.
Because we moved and got
lots of debt, there was no other choice.
that you have to work in a strong team.
What a mess.
Aren't you curious?
Why can't he marry and live
as a person with many problems?
You're forbidden to tell.
else you will get thrown.
His greatest achievement is
only bronze medal in local race.
I'm a national gold medal holder.
Who do you think
will be slammed into the street?
Then you can tell me.
The bride is coming.
Hey.
Do-Chang!
What are you doing here?
Hye-Ok!
Hye-Ok...
I am really, really sorry.
There have been many victims
caused by that person.
I really had to
catch him as soon as possible.
But it seems that the person
attended the wedding as an acquintance.
Then I saw...
Hye-Ok, I am begging you to understand.
I am really, really sorry.
Get out.
Dont dare to appear before me again.
Hye-Ok.
Wait.
Wait!
I think I'm really crazy.
Yes?
Did you reach home?
Not yet, why?
I have something to show you at the office.
But if you're tired,
don't come here.
If you know I'm tired, you shouldnt have called me you punk.
You think I'm happy for
you to suck my blood like this?
you blood sucking leech!
I quit being a nun
because I thought I dont deserve to be one.
After I came back to the states,
I kept thinking about, what I...
What I should do
for my brother, and...
You think I'm that helpless?
It is not like that.
I am alright.
Don't worry about me, just go.
Thanks for the oranges.
Keep pushing my uncle.
Then maybe Uncle will
find out what you want to know.
Okay.
I know he's a good person.
I don't want to add to someone's burden
who already have a lot of work.
I also don't have anyone
to share stories.
But Uncle listened to me.
Uncle said he would prove my father is innocent.
It's not something
that he had to do.
He also doesn't need to be sweared at
But,
he did.
Is that so?
You think I should depend on him?
We have to rely in times of trouble.
Thats why he is paid by the country.
Alright, alright. I'll think about it.
It is late. You should go home.
Well.
Take a rest.
No, no. wait a moment.
This.
How about you?
I am alright. Don't worry.
Take it.
Okay thank you.
What is that?
I bought an umbrella
from the mini market.
After you gave this to me,
you have to go home in the rain.
It's not expensive.
Why you have to soak in
rain because of me?
Because If you get wet in the rain,
you will get the flu.
You know I can't sleep if I'm
Afraid that you dont return home soon,right?
Stop working and hurry back home. Yes?
Its Raining , go in.
Its raining, hurry back in!
I know!
I am going
What do we get after coming this far?
What's good we got from there?
Is a detective is same as a
businessman?
to take advantage
of something like this.
Team Leader Oh.
What's the probability of
Lee Sung-Gon opening his mouth?
About 10 percent.
In that case,
what is the probability of me being promoted?
How could I
predict it?
Tell the truth,
I won't be angry though even if
you say zero percent.
If I tell you the truth,its
not zero percent, but about...
nine percent?
Okay thank you
for telling the truth.
In that case,
if Lee Sung-Gon opens his mouth,
then I report it to the head office,
If so, what is the probability of me being promoted?
Around...
three percent?
Then, actually...
Why should I join in
this mess, Kang Do-Chang?
Team Leader,
what is the probability that the chief will
still be respected by our detectives,
if this case is successful?
If that,
ninety-nine percent.
These bastards.
Good grief.
Thank you for taking your time
at a busy time like this.
What happened exactly?
Welcome.
Our detectives want to show
something to you.
We've done all the investigations.
We have submitted the data to the prosecutor's office.
It's useless even if Lee Sung-Gon
changes his statement now.
He won't change either.
But, why are they like that
obsessed with him?
I don't know what the reason is.
I also do not know.
So you mean,
You can't lead and control
the people under you?
Kang Do-Chang, that person,
on his wedding day,
he is the one who went to catch
criminals at the time of his marriage.
Between us,
no police can
control that person.
Please listen.
What did your little sister say?
I quiet being a nun because,
I thought I dont deserve to be one.
after I came back to the states I kept thinking about what I...
What I should do for my brother, and
my brother said that,
that he killed people because of me.
This crrazy woman.
I have done him wrong.
too much wrong,
my life has been too happy,
in a way that he has never been able to feel or experience.
I never did I ever considered the amount of pain,
that he must have went though
I'm so sorry.
What is she talking?
What are you doing? Yes?
If you show this,
do you think i will confess?
I didn't kill anyone.
You already told Laura Caine.
that You killed people because of her.
So what?
So, what can she do?
Yes?
Bring her here. Bring her and tell her to
say this to people.
I'm just saying I didnt kill.
Yes?
It will not happen.
I can confirm it.
She won't come.
Why will she come here from America?
Yes?
She must be crazy to do that.
Because this is someone else's business.
She definitely won't come.
Yes. She won't come.
because she cant come here.
Because she's dead.
Because she had committed suicide.
What?
What are you saying?
I know,
I know how much my brother loved his dad.
And I know how much pain he feels just,
just to see me live and go on.
Please tell my brother that,
that i'm sorry I left him when I remember,
how much he cared for me,
and I didnt come looking for him sooner.
And there's no need for him to hate anyone.
Because because its me,
who messed up,
Just,
Just hate me.
So please...
Please stop.
Why?
Why? Why?
Why did she do that?
I don't know.
She sacrificed herself for you.
To make you stop.
Crazy woman!
The mad woman died as she pleased!
Crazy woman.
Because who am I like this?
Because who?
Because who am I killing people?
What? Sacrifice?
Don't say nonsense.
If it weren't for this woman and her mother,
my father would not have died
and I would not have killed people.
All of this happened because of this woman.
So, what does sacrifice mean?
Don't say nonsense!
Shit.
Shit.. Very good.
Yes. Very good.
She really is a crazy woman.
she knew why I kill people.
Very good.
Shit.
Kang So Jung.
20 years old.
A new employee.
Jung Hye-Jin. 26 years old.
A bank employee.
Choi Yoon Ah. 25 years old.
A kindergarten teacher.
Park Seon Mi.
21 years old. A student.
And,
Jung Hee-Joo.
28 years old.
A company employee.
Kang So-Jung, Jung Hye-Jin,
Choi Yoon Ah,
Park Seon Mi,
and the unsuccessful Seong Ju-Ri
you kill.
The five of them are people
who were on the city bus you drive.
But,
Jung Hee-Joo never got on that bus.
Why?
Why is only Jung Hee-Joo different?
Is she Jung Hee-Joo?
Such a girl is not suitable
with red lipstick.
Someone else killed her.
- Chief Woo.
- Yes.
Today's statement was recorded, right?
Yes. Of course.
So, hand over this data
to these people.
Yes. I will do it.
If you are busy, we will deliver
directly to the prosecutor.
What should we do?
You've worked hard.
Forever,
live with problems.
Shit.
Lee Sung-Gon who previously denied
his crimes,
he has confessed to the crime.
So, are the perpetrators of the five cases
is Lee Sung-Gon?
No.
The fourth murder is denied.
The victim's name is Jung Hee-Joo.
Was that Lee Sung-Gon's statement?
Or is this an exposed fact?
Currently, we are
doing an investigation.
Is this unrelated
with Kim Hyeong-Bok,
who was accused of being the culprit?
Yes, right.
He has nothing to do with it at all.
For this time,
to Kim Hyeong-Bok
who died unjustly,
I,representing the entire police force,
I offer my apologies
and deep condolences.
Lee Sung-Gon Case Press Conference
Investigation Team Leader, apologizes
on the death of Kim Hyeong-Bok
The detectives on the front lines,
over-investigated,
we plead guilty
on the death of Kim Hyeong-Bok.
- Good grief.
- The cause of Kim Hyeong-Bok's death,
we will investigate
overall,
and we will be responsible
for everything.
Hey, you.
What should we do
with this situation?
What should I do?
We have to find
perpetrator of the Jung Hee-Joo case.
That's not the problem.
They say the death of Kim Hyeong-Bok was
due to over-investigation.
Is not that true?
- What?
- Hey, you.
It happened when Kim Hyeong-Bok was
on the run. Why do we...
If the inspection team makes a problem,
please leave it to me.
You just wait for my instructions.
Don't you now owe someone
for moving and selling shop?
How will you handle it
if there is a pay cut?
Do not worry about me.
You just take care of your own life.
So, how about this?
How about we leave it to
the richest among us...
Right. Right.
Among us, there are people whose credit card has no limit,
To that person...
This pay cut wont be an issue.
This is because there is a problem with the promotion.
Are there any between us?
who doesn't care about promotions?
It's for people who have
family responsibilities.
Hey, you. There's nothing between us
people who...
Yes, here.
I'm the first to know
whereabouts of Kim Hyeong-Bok.
I'm the most responsible
for everything.
Why do you say that?
People will definitely think
I delegate the matter to my subordinates.
No.
The person under you?
You are the Assistant Inspector.
He is the Inspector.
Who is taller?
Detectives don't see rank.
The most important thing is experience.
Just take it as I am
responsible.
- Great.
Hey, you.
Why did you interfere?
Compared to you, my rank
higher, my money more,
academic, appearance.
I have nothing to lose.
- Great.
Is the exhibition over?
Yes,
The content was good.
Will people not
think we are too relaxed?
We've tried our best.
Think in a good direction.
Tae-Ho, you can't even think.
Yes?
Don't think about paying too much to media.
Those people too,
they also have their own limits.
If we cross that line,
we will die together.
Because it happened suddenly,
we couldn't cover it.
But, that's enough of a warning
to McQueen.
I'm going straight to the broadcasting station
to avoid misunderstanding.
Looks like I gave a wrong habit to you.
At least,
I should teach you how to
solve the problem you created.
- Yes.
- I think you're wrong.
What?
Let your brother solve the problem.
Because you keep covering it up,
he keeps getting into trouble.
Yes. I understand.
going forward,
don't force yourself to help me.
You are more important to the TJ Group.
TJ Group will also fall together.
We have to change the appearance of TJ Group.
From Cheomseongdae,
to heaven.
It was to defend TJ Group.
That was the President's decision.
Only the time is getting faster.
No problem.
Because from the start,
I'm invisible in their eyes.
Hey, Na-Na.
This is the only way
which we can now choose.
We?
If you are in the place
appointed by the President,
you and I are not us.
Why do we do it, the
Jung Hee-Joo's case?
Seoul Investigation Team People should solve it.
Hey, Team Leader.
We caught Lee Sung-Gon.
We also received
Lee Sung-Gon's confession.
Shouldn't we finish
last problem?
Isn't that right, Criminal Team Two?
- Yes.
You guys really are.
First, Kim Hyeong-Bok,
we must finish that over-investigation,
Even though we face
disciplinary actions,
Kim Hyeong-Bok's family will apply
complaints after seeing the news.
The problem will be serious.
- Team leader.
- Yes?
There's a package came for our team.
Who sent it?
Park Geum-Soon.
Kim Hyeong-Bok's mother.
Dongsan Church
Good grief.
My dear son.
My Hyeong-bok.
You are going to a beautiful place.
I believe that.
Good grief.
I miss you.
My kind son.
Can you drink?
I only drink when I feel good.
Should we be happy?
Aren't detectives like that?
giving pain,
and then give medicine.
This time, we're not the ones giving the medicine.
Kim Hyeong-Bok's mother gave us medicine.
Geez.
The medicine is too sweet.
You're so annoying.
Hey, Na-Na.
Hey, Na-Na!
Let me go!
What are you doing?
Leave me alone.
Who are you?
Why are you like a child?
Why?
Can't i eat when I want to eat,
and do what i want to do?
Hey, Na-Na.
Can't you feel satisfied
with what you have now?
You can be happy.
Are you tired?
No.
Yes.
Yes. I'm tired.
Am I too,
making you feel tired ?
Please tell me.
With your own mouth.
"In this world,
You're not alone."
"You don't have to live in loneliness."
"So,
Don't live alone."
I'm sorry for leaving you alone.
Don't try too hard.
Yes. I understand.
I'll call you again.
See you.
Dont you have a lot of free time now a days?
Let's have a drink in a nice place .
Yes, good.
Seems like it would be hard to expect from the
Seoul Investigation Team.
Team leader has been suspended.
- How is Jung Hee-Joo's investigation?
- Of course starting from scratch.
It will be handed over to the local police.
- Incheon Police?
- Yes.
Is there anyone
who can be contacted there?
For now, no connection is there which will benefit us.
Oh Ji-Hyeok.
- He can't be controlled?
- Yes.
Let's think about Jung Hee-Joo's case.
Most likely he will use the
case of Jung Hee-Joo,
to link
with the case two years ago.
Don't let him into the company.
Yes, understood.
But, if they brought
warrant...
Warrants will not be issued.
Yes. I understand.
- Please go.
- Yes.
Legal Team Leader, Woo Tae-Ho
Who killed Jung Hee-Joo?
This.
These are Jung Hee-Joo's item's.
The company sent it.
You haven't checked the contents?
Yes, not yet.
Yes. I understand.
We will return it
after we are done with checking.
- Come on.
- Yes.
That day,
I was little frustrated.
I apologize.
You really are a fool.
Yes?
You should have just said it is Lee Sung-Gon
who killed Jung Hee-Joo.
You don't have to look for anyone
who killed Jung Hee-Joo then.
You are a person
who create your own problems.
Eun-Hye said that to me.
That I can expect from you.
That's why the state gives you a salary.
Good grief. Why did she say things
which are not important?
Thank you for choosing
hard road.
I know what you want.
A little bit more...
You just need to be patient a little longer.
Yes. Okay.
October two,
Team Leader Woo Tae-Ho's police call
October five,
Design-related data collection
October six, the morning meeting of the legal team
You are beautiful.
Looks like that position is
only for beautiful people.
The previous person was also beautiful.
Just like you.
Did you mean Jung Hee-Joo?
Who passed away sometimes ago.
Do you feel uncomfortable?
I can transfer you, if it's not convenient.
Not. Not.
Nothing to do with work.
Have you never worked
in law before?
Yes.
But, why Manager Choi
recommend to the legal team?
Yes?
I heard one of your family member works in this field.
My father is a police chief.
Really?
Where?
West Incheon Police.
Really?
Do you know Detective Oh Ji-Hyeok?
Yes.
- A little...
- How do you know?
I didn't know before.
I know him because he has something to do
with the legal team here.
Isn't he very handsome?
- Don't know.
- If You are close to him,
can you provide information
about him?
Yes?
I'm just curious.
Yes. Okay.
I will look for information.
But,
there's something I want to ask.
After I investigated,
the case about Jung Hee-Joo,
the person in charge is the one who is serving my father.
It,
Was that the reason,
am I in this position?
Besides that,
I can meet people of
high ranks like you,
is that the reason?
How old are you?
I, 24 years old.
Shouldn't you understand?
Nothing is by chance in this world.
Just decide for yourself.
But,
company wants people
who are willing to work for the company.
You just need to remember that.
Yes. Okay.
I understand.
You're interesting.
Fingerprints are left when ripping it off.
What does it mean?
Is it like a password?
Team Leader Woo Tae-Ho's police call
Yes. Thank you
Yes.
Team Leader Woo Tae-Ho
called the prosecutor that day.
During the investigation, there was a search
against TJ Group's legal team.
They carried out searches
when there was no Team Leader.
There would definitely be a commotion
during a legal team search.
She wrote in an emergency
and tore it up.
What's with this number?
You know the prosecutor and the police are separate organizations, right?
Yes. I know.
I was a policeman
but now in the prosecutor's office.
Don't make my position difficult.
Only I will know.
Thank you
Have you opened this?
Yes. I've opened and checked.
But, I can't open this for you.
No need to do that.
This. This...
Call Details List
That day, Woo Tae-Ho
called Jung Hee-Joo.
The time is the same as the search time.
Woo Tae-Ho gave the password
to Jung Hee-Joo.
Jung Hee-Joo took something
from the safe.
In the call list,
an interesting name is there.
Who?
Person I can't reach.
What?
West Incheon Police.
The phone is not being picked up.
Are there any other suspicious numbers?
There are numbers that don't have names.
Looks like a disposable phone.
Try calling.
I can't go out today
because i feel bit sick.
Lately I have a lot of
mental difficulties.
See you later.
You killed him because of me, right?
I'm talking about Jung Hee-Joo.
You told the detective?
What's your relationship?
Something to do with the case two years ago
with the Jung Hee-Joo case.
Have you found the
perpetrator of the case?
I suspect someone.
Should I think about him?
Where did you get these photos from?
There is a possibility of forgery.
Send Na-Na to America.
It's better that she's doesnt stay here.
This is a shitty investigation.
If you bring important evidence,
we can make a deal.