This program is for ages 15 and over
because it contains adult elements,
violence, and the risk of impersonation.
This program contains
indirect advertisements and virtual advertisements.
All characters, names, events,
etc. in this drama are fictional.
subtitles provided by/Summer Fouad
please
Sorry Hee-Joo.
In his world now,
Hee-Joo will also definitely
beg for forgiveness.
Excuse me, Director Cheon.
What do I have to do?
I will serve him.
He is an honored guest.
Would you like some coffee?
Yes thank you.
Please wait a moment.
Yes, it's okay.
Please speak, Director Cheon.
All right, Director.
I'll be there soon.
Oh my gosh, Hee-Joo.
Good grief.
Why don't you answer my phone?
Did something happen?
Director Cheon.
Yes
Are you Director Cheon?
That's what they call me.
is
Hee-Joo also calls you like that?
Right.
But,
why are you suddenly asking that?
Oh ,, Yeah
I suddenly remembered
when Hee-Joo said
"Director Cheon" on the phone.
Come to think of it,
I remember talking to her
on the phone.
Jung Hee-Joo
tenders her resignation from the company.
I wanted to hold her
so I asked to meet.
I do not want
lost talented people
due to personal problems.
Is that right?
Episode 13
- Who is that man?
- Yeah, so it's like this.
You know the guy who stole the cash
at Cheonma-dong's pool, right?
The culprit is this man.
Okay.
You found the gun?
It...
- Here's the gun.
- Okay.
But, that's not it.
Hey!
you hit
behind the owner's head.
Everything was caught on CCTV cameras.
It's a regular billiard ball.
The ball I use
to hit is billiard ball.
It's the same.
Of course it's different.
The billiard ball is much smaller.
Stop it.
You guys playing around?
Check the CCTV,
and find the right weapon!
Well.
Do-Chang.
What did the prosecutor say?
Did Cheon Sang-Woo appeal?
Isn't that obvious?
Hey, if we lose here,
wouldn't our position be difficult?
Didn't you hear what the Chief said?
We don't need to care about it.
How can you not care?
If Cheon Sang-Woo comes back to life,
we will die.
- Jae-Hong.
- Seriously.
Jae-Hong.
We both have caught the culprit!
Moreover, within the day
after the murder.
Well, good job.
There is an article about us.
Criminal Team at Incheon West Office
seems to have been active to
reveal Cheon Sang-Woo's crimes.
Dong Wook.
They can't
just call it "Criminal Team."
They should have made it clear
that it was Team Criminal 2.
- Where's that?
- Hey.
Hey! You think because the pool ball
is smaller it makes your penalty smaller?
Your story is over.
Follow me.
Yoo Ji-Sook, Cheon Sung-Dae's brother, is the founder of
Ketua TJ Group
At the scene there is also Cheon Na-Na
who is Yoon Ji-Sook's daughter.
Everyone just saw something
high.
Do you think people will see
perpetrators hitting people
with a billiard ball versus
a big company guy?
I don't know if they
make a big difference.
They are the same,
be it the leader of a large corporation,
or a robber.
The ratings are slightly different.
Everything looks the same to me.
One person was hit six times,
and the other was hit five times.
These days, your standard of living
is a lottery draw.
Life is a lottery draw.
Oh, itu Eun-Hee!
What the hell is that?
Looks like Eun-Hee has a boyfriend.
Ajussi
Can She be like that?
She is a mother.
Who cares?
She can date for herself
Good grief.
The car is very good.
- Looks like he's a rich man.
- Hey, Ji-Woong.
You don't know that kind of face?
"I'm a bad person."
Are you really a detective?
He looks like a bad guy.
We have to investigate that person.
But,
why today
Eun-Hee looks so beautiful?
What are they doing?
Are you Director Cheon?
Na-Na.
You killed Woo Tae-Ho, didn't you?
I wonder
what Woo Tae-Ho thinks
before he died.
Father has come?
Meanwhile,
I will not go forward.
Dad should go out and rest.
Dad's been in trouble.
Seems like it doesn't need to be like that.
I'll be keeping an eye on the situation
for a while.
What would you do?
I don't know either.
What should I do?
What should I do
to you?
Sang-Woo keeps blaming you.
Na-Na, I think you have made the situation
like this.
I'm not doing well.
But,
I didn't do
anything wrong either.
It was Sang-Woo's fault.
He must take responsibility
and handle it yourself.
You think I don't know
what have you done?
Ayah.
- I...
- Na-Na.
Shouldn't
you be thanking me?
I have accepted you
as my daughter.
Therefore,
You just need to have
what I give you.
When you want something else,
You are not qualified
to be my daughter.
You have to be lower.
Humble yourself
to the bottom and shrink.
Only that
how to make you
still be my daughter.
I've tried calling him,
but he won't talk.
He didn't pick up the phone again.
It could happen.
He is the most innocent person
among his friends.
Perhaps he was afraid
of harming the detectives.
He can't talk.
Right after Woo Tae-Ho's accident,
The Traffic Crimes Department
moved him to the countryside.
There must be a reason.
Police station
- A man?
- Right.
Eun-Hee went out with the guy last night.
It...
There's no law Eun-Hee
can't date a man.
You can't blame me for that, can you?
Right.
But when I checked the car,
it is a rental car.
This fool girl
She really doesn't have
good male taste.
What will we do?
We have to investigate.
You might be
even more humiliated if you missed it.
I'm back.
Have you met him?
Yes, I met him.
What did he say?
Woo Tae-Ho didn't kill himself.
What do you want to talk about?
What's with this bad premonition
that isn't even a hopeful story?
Today,
I, Oh Ji-Hyeok, Shim Dong-Wook
met a policeman.
His name is Kim Chang-Seo.
He is a friend of the
Traffic Criminal Investigation section
who had investigated
the case of Woo Tae-Ho's death.
Now he is expelled,
and is in the local district.
Are you going to reveal
Woo Tae-Hoo's death?
Why my bad feeling
never wrong?
- Then?
- Hey, Dong-Wook.
Tell me what you heard
from your partner.
I heard there's an inspection
against the car involved
in Woo Tae-Ho's death.
They found two fingerprints on the car.
Woo Tae-Ho who died,
and Cheon Na-Na who also came.
Isn't that an obvious thing?
We found Cheon Na-Na's fingerprints
on the seat belt switch and steering wheel.
It was Woo Tae-Ho who was driving at the time of the accident.
Married couples
can take turns driving.
What's wrong with that?
Cheon Na-Na was drunk in an accident.
It was confirmed at the hospital
where Cheon Na Na was treated.
A situation where he can't drive.
Not that it's proof
to reverse the case, right?
This is our best way.
Just do
what I want this time.
I'll take care of everything.
I'm sorry.
I don't believe you.
You heard it in the middle of the conversation, right?
It was the sound of unbuckling the seat belt.
Cheon Na-Na stated
that Woo Tae-Ho had
unbuckled his own seat belt.
If Cheon Na-Na's fingerprint
is from that switch,
that means he let her go.
Then,
Cheon Na-Na took over the steering wheel,
and changed direction.
Towards a truck coming from the other direction.
Therefore,
we got
Cheon Na-Na's fingerprint from the steering wheel.
Hey.
It's because of you, Oh Ji-Hyeok
think that Cheon Na-Na
killed Woo Tae-Ho,
so he adapts
everything you think.
That's your own opinion.
Detective Oh isn't the only one
who thinks that way.
My partner also has the same suspicions
as Detective Oh.
That's why the Traffic Crime Department questioned this,
and became the reason
why my friend got kicked out.
He was under external pressure.
But he asked the
unnecessary question,
so I told him to move.
Isn't that a familiar scenario?
So, what's the bottom line?
We're going to arrest the top brass of TJ Group
on charges of murder.
Then, we catch Cheon Na-Na,
daughter of the chairman of TJ Group,
for the murder of her husband?
Is that it ?
Hey guys
Chairman Cheon Sung-Dae is free.
We sent his son
who was like gold into prison,
and she only has an only daughter.
If we catch Cheon Na-Na
as the murderer of her husband,
do you think they will let us?
He has wealth
over trillions of won.
Ten billion for each of your necks,
won't make him poor.
Do you still want to do it?
Okay.
In that case,
let's redefine it.
Raise your hand
if you risk your life
to investigate again.
One two three...
Because there are eight people inside...
Why all of a sudden you?
Dong-Wook was investigating, wasn't he?
I'm his mentor.
As his mentor, I was a little embarrassed.
Okay.
All right, like that.
Four.
What's wrong with you?
I'm the Team Leader.
After I heard,
it's not a baseless story.
It's already five people.
That's more than half, Mr. Head.
But,
in a case like this,
it's not the majority.
There must be the approval
of more than one third of the quorum.
- What's wrong with you?
- I...
I don't like the number five.
One two three four five six.
- Looks like it's already perfect.
- I also?
Put your hands down.
I only need six figures.
That's a bonus.
Seven in total?
Even though the Head has given permission,
we still haven't had a chance.
If we investigate everything
for no reason,
just like the Chief of Police said,
only we can run into trouble.
Well.
I'll be looking for further clues .
Looks like we should go
and move together then.
Everyone believes in you.
If you have no hope,
quickly give up.
It's a way for the whole team.
Well.
Please come in. See you tomorrow.
What is it?
Ya, how do-chang.
The rental car I said before,
the car owner right now,
Is in the shop.
What?
- Hello.
- Let's meet.
I want to ask you something.
Where are you?
You must
make time tomorrow.
Yeah, I'll go
when I've closed everything.
I'll be there soon.
Thanks for the fried chicken.
Yes, enjoy.
Wait.
I forgot something.
That Jerk
Wait a minute.
We'll catch him together.
Let's follow them.
He must have left the car
somewhere.
Just because you drive a rental car,
that doesn't mean you're a criminal.
Of course. Maybe he
brought his friend's car to a date
That is enough.
We continue with the next case
please
I can go crazy seeing things like that.
Excuse me.
Do you own this car?
Can.
Right, this is my car.
We are detectives from...
Hey!
Why did you run?
why did you run away you stupid jerk
What did you do to make you run?
Can't you be nice?
Good grief.
Why does it have to be a man like you?
Why?
Who are you?
Ak Oh Ji-Hyeok from Incheon West Office.
Yes, I heard about you.
Please come in.
Open the door.
Please sit there.
What do you want to ask of me?
Protect me.
I want you to stop being a detective
and protect me.
Tell me your requirements.
I will listen to everything.
Forgive me.
That's a request I can't accept.
My offer is only once.
I will never do it again.
I already told you that
this request is unreasonable.
Then you will become my enemy.
You
know the reason why I could die.
If my dad finds out what I did
to Sang-Woo,
my father will kill me.
Just you and me,
who knows about this.
I already promised.
I won't do anything
to harm you.
Then you should
n't have turned down my offer.
There's nothing I can do.
If you don't believe me,
I am your enemy
as you say.
So, now we have finished
our relationship.
Too bad.
I thought you were the only friend
who has the same past
as me.
Your mother died because of you, right?
My mother also killed herself because of me.
We are both murderers.
A killer who kills
her mother.
Is...
You really think
your mother died because of you?
Isn't it because you're looking for an excuse
to satisfy yourself?
Your mother, Yoon Ji-Sook,
is preparing a lawsuit
against Chairman Cheon Sung-Dae.
It was a demand
to have you as an official princess.
Your mother thinks that Cheon Sung-Dae
and Cheon Sang-Woo are after money.
You put pressure on your mother.
That's the reason why
your mother committed suicide.
It's because of me.
She died to save me.
They sent me to America.
My mother sacrificed herself
to protect me.
You were there at the time of the suicide.
You just left her
You think your mother is an object
to be recognized as a princess.
I was on a plane
to the United States at the time.
It's your past being manipulated.
A past made up
to hide the truth.
No
At that time, my father and brother
only spoke to the press
to hide their sins.
Do not tell,
you really believe in the past
that you fake?
Detective Oh Ji-Hyeok.
You can go now.
I already know enough
what you think of me.
So, hurry up and go.
Remember that.
You were the one who strangled me first.
Remember well.
You strangled me first.
You were the one who strangled me first.
Because of that...
Open the door.
Don't behave too much,
quickly open the door!
I know what you're thinking.
I know you're after money!
It won't go your way!
It won't! Hurry
give up and open the door!
Open the door!
Mother
Na-Na.
You want to go with mom?
I wasn't here at that time.
He's been a criminal five times.
I haven't done it.
I am currently doing a legal business.
- Why bring a fake license plate car?
- It...
I bought it to save tax.
Then why did you run away?
He's a car insurance scammer.
You must be using a fake license plate car,
because I want to cheat again.
Did you know I'm a detective
and deliberately approached my sister?
You think I'm crazy?
I'm so unlucky.
You Jerk,, what do you say?
Enough already.
It's okay if he doesn't know that.
From now on you better
not see my sister.
If she finds out you're a bad person,
not me, but my sister
who will finish you off.
Sis Eun-Hee is
a national judo gold medal holder.
He can finish you off
with just one hand.
Understand?
Really?
I do not know that.
Even though she looked very weak.
In your eyes my sister looks weak?
Yes
Honestly I have no other intentions.
She looks lonely.
Therefore, I just wanted to cheer her up.
Investigate this person.
And all,
find out also the provider
of fake car plates for him,
and we caught them all.
- I go first.
- Goodbye.
Goodbye.
Where did you get that fake license plate from?
You must have stolen it
and then replaced the plate, right?
I really don't know.
I bought it on the internet.
Hey.
You want me to investigate this?
You want me to make you open your mouth?
No, no.
I will say.
- You have eaten?
- I have no appetite.
Gosh, why aren't you eating yet?
I brought leftover chicken, will I just give you that?
That man
I caught him today.
Who?
the man you are meeting
the man who kissed your forehead.
Why?
He's a swindler with fake license plates.
If you want to date
people, be picky about the people.
Why do you always date
a moron like that?
Did you know for sure?
He committed the crime 5 times.
Damn!!
That Jerk
It's not that I can't understand you.
But isn't it a bit too fast?
You just got divorced.
I did that because I was lonely.
Can't I really feel lonely?
Indeed I...
have to go on living just take care of you?
Did someone tell you to take care of me?
Therefore I beg you,
Brother is also looking for a companion.
Let me also live my life.
We both live like this,
don't you think it's sad?
- Uncle are you home?
- Yes.
Jae-Woong, you still haven't slept?
Why are you drinking alcohol again?
You also play games in the bathroom.
Mother told me
to play only one hour a day.
Why are you taking your anger out on him?
Let's go out, uncle
will buy some good food.
Jae-Woong is my son,
why did his uncle interfere?
Brother just do your job.
Do not do anything unnecessary.
please
Let's get out. Today your mother
is not happy.
When out, play the game for a while
. Mom said just one hour.
Jae-Woong,
do you feel
uncomfortable living with uncle?
I'm fine, but...
I'm fine, but...?
Mother...
Tell me that mom feels sorry for uncle.
He says uncle will not be
able to marry because of us.
Why is that?
Uncle is quite famous among women.
Not that I can't, I just don't want to.
But...
Mom says my uncle
is getting old and ugly.
And...
Mom too...
So?
I didn't think of that before.
It's because of stupid uncle.
What's this?
132N 1193.
- It's me...
- Please check this car.
... There's a car in front of the warehouse.
Fine I understand.
The car was reported stolen yesterday.
Oh Ji-Hyeok.
Go there and check it out.
Okey
- This isn't your car?
- No.
Oops, sorry.
- Good grief.
- Is this your car?
- Yes, I needed to pee.
- Move quickly.
Okey
Hey Hey.
What are you doing?
Hey.
Run!
Do-Chang.
Come in and check it out.
Why? What is it?
Why?
I'm looking for traces of deleting machine numbers,
but there's something strange in here.
- It's a tracker, right?
- Yes.
Position tracker.
Yesterday I drank too much.
Yes Haha, damn.
No
Nothing happened, right?
Ah
subtitles provided by : Summer fouad
Just send it to another team.
I'll tell the Team Leader over there.
Ok
The trunk of the car opens
Damn.
There are also some
fake account holders who agree.
The money that was confiscated was
sent by me.
You said you wanted to send it
by account, right?
If it's from an account, will it be easy to find out?
Wouldn't it be safer to use this way?
It must have been recorded that someone
put money in the trunk.
If it is revealed,
it will be proof i
accept corruption...
Oh, on purpose?
What Team Leader Choi Young-Geun said,
what agreement is there between us?
I moved only
because I trusted the team leader...
I don't know the details.
He says will be my hands and feet.
But now my hands
and feet are tied.
Then
shouldn't someone replace it
role to keep
the deal going?
I will do it.
Your assessment is very fast.
From now on, I will
determine how the money will be given.
Team Leader Jang and I,
in a way that only the
two of us know.
Yes
Ki Dong-Jae?
This was recorded on the day Ki Dong-Jae was released.
Then 3 hours later,
the same car is recorded
from the opposite direction.
What's this?
You know Gu Jae-Chun, right?
Gangnam gang boss.
That's his subordinate.
According to the person who was caught earlier,
he sold the car.
So Ki Dong-Jae went
with this car,
then Gangnam gang people brought him again?
They killed Ki Dong-Jae
then snatched his car
Because it's a shame if the car is thrown away.
Then sold.
So it was Gu Jae-Chun who
killed Ki Dong-Jae.
Lucky to avenge Jo Sang-Pil.
Obviously the reason to kill him.
But Ki Dong-Jae had no
reason to see Gu Jae-Chun.
Someone handed Ki Dong-Jae
to Gu Jae-Chun.
- Who?
- In the car that Ki Dong-Jae was riding,
there is a position tracking device.
I've checked the data.
Among the recorded positions,
there is a prison where Ki Dong-Jae was released.
After checking the nearby CCTV,
i found this.
Oh.
So Ki Dong-Jae got a car from here.
The one who gave the car,
is Jang Ki-Jin.
Jang Ki-Jin, Chief of the Seoul Investigation Team?
He gives this car to
Ki Dong-Jae after installing the tracking device.
Then he told
Gu Jae-Chun his position,
and got Ki Dong-Jae killed.
Even though it was Gu Jae-Chun who did it,
but the one who actually killed
Ki Dong-Jae was Jang Ki-Jin.
Looks like you need surgery.
You should have had surgery when
you were hospitalized before.
It's really getting worse.
I can't go straight into surgery right now.
I still have something to do.
What is this, sir?
You've been working hard all this time.
Please eat together
with your friends.
Nope. We cannot
accept this kind of thing. And also...
We've made you suffer so much,
how can we accept this?
If you don't want to accept it,
it means I still owe it.
It means you put me in debt.
I give this to make
me feel comfortable.
Yes thank you.
I will use it well.
Wait, my shoes do
n't fit you?
Detectives rarely wear shoes like that.
Because we had to run
to catch the culprit.
Oh, that's right.
I forgot that.
But when I go anywhere
else, I definitely wear those shoes.
Because of those shoes,
my colleagues say
I'm like the boss of the company.
Good luck.
By the way, Detective Kang.
The reason my grandson died,
nothing to do
with Director Cheon, right?
You mean Director Cheon is
Cheon Na-Na?
Yes
Based on the results of our investigation
, there is no connection.
She even helped with our research.
If she wasn't there,
we won't be able to
catch Cheon Sang-Woo.
Oh I see. Good luck.
The main thing is,
Cheon Sang-Woo had
people kill my grand daughter
And Ki Dong-Jae who
killed my grand daughter
- Keep it that way, right?
- Yes that's right.
- Please wait a moment.
- Yes.
Halo?
Have you caught him?
All right, I'll be right there. Wait.
Good grief.
Again I keep people
busy for too long. Please go.
Fine, then excuse me.
Thank you
Sir
I will come to
your shop with chicken.
I'll tell you a lot of
things while we drink.
Thank you, thank you very much.
Excuse me.
Yes, I'm there.
This car that Ki Dong-Jae brought,
you brought it back.
After that Ki Dong-Jaedisappeared without a trace.
You killed Ki Dong-Jae?
Why are you like this?
Why should I kill brother Dong-Jae?
If it wasn't you,
someone else would have killed him.
Tell me who killed him.
I do not know.
Then why did you bring the car
that Ki Dong-Jae brought?
It...
Brother Dong-Jae gave
the car to me.
And he asked me to sell it.
So I sold the car.
Hey, it said recently that you guys wanted to
capture and kill Ki Dong-Jae.
But Ki Dong-Jae asked the person
who wanted to kill him to sell the car?
You think that makes sense?
Jae-Chun?
Surely Jae-Chun killed Ki Dong-Jae,
then told you to take care of the car.
Because it's a shame to throw it away.
So sold to be able to add money.
- Right?
- I admit I sold the car.
But I really do
n't know anything other than that.
Think carefully.
If you're stubborn,
you might end up doing it all on your own.
From now on, on
this CCTV day,
tell me what you
did, who did you meet,
tell me everything.
If it doesn't match, we
'll investigate you right away.
Has Si Dong-Jae's body been found?
Don't you know that
he's dead or not yet?
I'm sure that Ki Dong-Jae was murdered.
It was obvious, seeing
him mention corpses.
Otherwise, he wouldn't have said that.
You know how difficult it is to
prove murder without a corpse.
We could be tired of investigating
but ended just like that.
But the reason for killing him is clear.
It doesn't make sense for us
to let go of our hands even though we know that.
Ki Dong-Jae is a murderer.
But Ki Dong-Jae's family,
too, deserves to know why he died,
and how he could die.
Is not that,
we should also know the reason Jang Ki-Jin
gave Ki Dong-Jae to Gu Jae-Chun?
Therefore before Cheon Sang-Woo's trial,
is it possible to
protect Cheon Sang-Woo?
That's not the whole reason
Ki Dong-Jae died.
By the day Woo Tae-Ho died,
Woo Tae-Ho meets Ki Dong-Jae.
It seemed until before that, he
assumed Cheon Sang-Woo was the culprit.
But after meeting Ki Dong-Jae,
whatever he thought, he
immediately met Cheon Na-Na.
Then he called us.
He said he had something to say.
Then,
he had an accident.
Indeed,
what did he hear from Ki Dong-Jae,
to suddenly do that?
Isn't that obvious?
What else
would Ki Dong-Jae say?
"I never killed her."
I think so
"I didn't kill Jung Hee-Joo."
The culprit is someone else.
The reason Ki Dong-Jae died was
because he said that to Woo Tae-Ho.
Excuse me.
Welcome.
We're from the Incheon West Office Criminal Team .
What's the matter?
Is it true that you are
Ki Dong-Jae's older brother?
Right.
Are you related
to your brother?
As you know,
that person is dead.
Then when was the last time
you met?
I have never met that idiot yet.
The last time I saw him,
was at my father's ancestral ceremony
about ten years ago.
Have you ever been contacted
by telephone?
Why should I answer
a call from an assassin?
Like you said, we thought
Ki Dong-Jae was dead too.
But shouldn't we
find the body?
If you have anything
to help with the investigation,
please tell me.
That way, we can
find the killer...
Please don't look for the killer.
Don't even look for his body.
If you please
But...
There's nothing more we can get.
Just leave him be
I will leave
my same card here.
Please contact me if you
remember anything.
Oh Ji-Hyeok
I'm a little confused.
Who
are we actually doing all this for now?
The truth must be revealed.
We have to reveal it.
The hidden truth.
Hasn't the truth been revealed?
The culprit was Cheon Sang-Woo.
That person is the killer
Whoever killed her with his own hands
nothing has changed.
Do you think Ki Dong-Jae
is not Jung Hee-Joo's killer?
Think carefully.
Like you said, if Ki Dong-Jae
didn't kill Jung Hee-Joo,
then we managed to figure it out,
Cheon Sang-Woo could be
said to be innocent.
Come on let go of this,
and try this one.
Try it, try it.
Right?
Yes, it's convenient.
How do you know my son's shoe size?
Grandpa could tell shoe size
by just looking at a person's feet.
Oh God.
Is it true that by just looking
at one's feet,
You can immediately find out
the shoe size.
Yes. Because it's my job.
Then, sorry, but...
Can you tell
my shoe size?
For that, please
try these shoes.
Oh my, how is this.
If so...
- I will try it.
- Yes.
Will this fit?
Good grief.
Good grief. This is just right!
Gosh, this is so awesome!
It fits perfectly, Grandpa!
I am very grateful.
These shoes are very beautiful.
Jae-Woong quickly stood up,
and say thank you to Grandpa.
Thank you
Oh, over and over.
You must listen to
your mother's words carefully.
If you don't listen to
your mother's words and make her sad,
These shoes will narrow
and make your feet hurt.
Is it true?
These are magic shoes!
Magic shoes for a kind child.
Did you hear?
You should listen to mom carefully.
Otherwise these shoes will make
your heels peel off all over.
Do you understand?
Yes
Grandpa, how can I repay him.
Oh no. Nothing
compared to what I got.
You gave me fried chicken.
That makes me very happy.
The chicken is not much.
I have to say goodbye now.
If later the shoes feel uncomfortable,
please contact me immediately.
No, how do you just walk
away?
Eun-Hye don't let
grandpa just leave.
- Yes.
- No need...
Please wait a moment,
I'll make a nice snack.
Okay.
Welcome.
For how many people?
- There will be two more.
- Okay, please sit over there.
Why do the detectives
want to see us again?
It's because of Brother Dong-Jae.
Was it because of Jung Hee-Joo's murder?
Isn't that over?
- He's not the killer.
- What?
While drinking he had told
me everything.
He said that
he wasn't the killer,
and he just doing a favor for someone
Damn
Was he just making excuses?
Hey, the proof is there!
Brother gave it to me,
and he said he would hand it over
one day so that he would be free from accusations.
By the way,
Don't tell
the detectives about this later.
Brother is dead,
so what's the point now?
This only bothers us.
Hello
- Welcome!
- Sister!
- Did you two come alone?
- No, we have an appointment here.
- All right.
- Yes.
Long time no see.
How are you guys doing?
- You missed us, didn't you?
- Why did you guys call us again?
We just wanted to see you friend,
haven't we seen each other for a long time?
- Looks like you're skinny.
- Is that true?
Hey, isn't this great?
While drinking we can talk
about the idiot Ki Dong-Jae.
Shouldn't you be looking for
your brother?
Determine whether it is alive
or dead.
I just saw you.
I was in the packaging department.
Really? I do not know.
- Hello.
Excuse me.
Is it true that Ki Dong-Jae
is not Jung Hee-Joo's killer?
They just talk to each other,
you can't believe it.
Still, there's some reason
for them to say that, right?
Then we will ask
and confirm it first.
You don't have to think about it.
We will do
a thorough research.
- and also check the evidence.
- I confirmed it in court too.
Nonetheless,
that's what i heard.
If I may be honest,
if what they say is true,
things will get more complicated.
If something went wrong, it was likely that
Cheon Sang-Woo would also be free.
That can't happen.
I heard it myself
that Cheon Sang-Woo told him
to kill my grandson.
That absolutely cannot happen.
The children from the Incheon West Office
arrested one of our children.
They are looking for Ki Dong-Jae.
His body will never be found.
But, we will narrow down the investigation
and clear the existing accusations.
The problem was Oh Ji-Hyeok.
He will continue to bite until the end.
That's your business.
I never told
you to kill Ki Dong-Jae.
Right.
But we're not the only ones who have
reasons for his murder, right?
You guys should have
killed him too, right?
There was a story he told me
before he died.
Brother Please help...
listen to my explanation first.
Brother , I'm hiding something.
It could change your life.
Look, if it's nothing,
fine, I won't kill you.
Here.
Hyungnim, Brother
One of TJ's Cheon family members,
has killed someone.
I have the proof.
Then?
Let me make
just one phone call,
and it's with my older brother he can get it.
Then if you threaten TJ with that,
Brother can earn
a very large amount of money.
Alright, give it a try then.
Dong-Jae
Didn't pick up?
I'll try it one more time.
Stop being rude!
You're right bastard, you dragged your brother
so you can live?
You're such a fool, little fool.
Get rid of this nonsense!
Hyungnim , Brother
Someone from the Cheon family
that Ki Dong-Jae spoke of,
Didn't the tycoon order
and hand over Ki Dong-Jae to us?
Team Leader.
We are both on the same side.
You're also a really
tough little brat.
There it is.
He is Ki Dong-Su, who you say is
Ki Dong-Jae's older brother.
Okay.
You've worked hard.
There's evidence.
He handed it over to his brother.
and he said to hand him over for
a moment so that he would be freed from the accusation.
- Excuse me.
- Yes.
Can I help you?
Yes, I am the grandfather of a child
named Jung Hee-Joo.
Then?
I'm here to talk about something.
Are you here
to apologize?
My brother is guilty of murder.
I'm sorry for my younger brother's  mistake.
Is that enough?
I don't have any feelings
for your family.
So what do you want?
It...
Do you have anything
that your younger brother left with you?
There isn't any.
I didn't mean
to do anything with it.
I just want to know.
Who exactly killed my grand daughter ?
I need to know that because then
I close my eyes comfortably.
Isn't the trial over?
The police have also disclosed it.
It's true if my brother is the idiot
who killed her
I don't know why you came
and did this to me.
Why should I...
I don't understand why
I have to suffer again,
because of that bastard?
Is my coming...
make you suffer?
I've forgotten it.
I had forgotten the fact
that that bastard was my younger brother
However, you just...
made me remember
the stupidity again.
Oh my gosh, I'm sorry.
I don't think...
I didn't think about your position.
Just because of my greed.
I have wronged you.
I'm sorry.
Why is Grandpa like this?
The case regarding your grand daughter
has been resolved, hasn't it?
The culprit has been caught
and Dong-Jae is also dead.
Aren't you now enough
to live comfortably?
Why are you even thinking
about other unimportant things?
This will only annoy you.
This is because I still have regrets
inside of me.
"I can die peacefully
without any regrets now."
I just wanted to die
after saying that one sentence.
Okay.
So, he didn't leave
anything to you.
Yes
I understand.
I didn't know that someone
who lost a family member,
or a member of the murderer's family,
can feel the pain together.
Okay.
I won't look for you anymore.
Dong-Jae, he doesn't entrust
anything to me.
I found something,
which he hid while cleaning
his things.
If you open it, your
regrets will disappear.
The one who killed Grandpa's grand daughter ..
is Dong-Jae.
Now you don't have to
think about anything else.
Be careful on the road.
Hee-Joo.
Halo.
Jeez, what need did you come?
I have something to give.
Wait for a while. Wait for a while.
This time, we plan
to create a scholarship foundation,
- on behalf of Jung Hee-Joo.
- Yes?
So what?
That means we sincerely apologize
for Jung Hee-Joo's death,
and remind us
not to forget it.
Is that true?
There will be a celebration event
for the foundation's establishment.
Before that, I came
to get permission from Grandpa.
Of course.
Maybe Hee-Joo will be happy too.
Then I assume
that you have allowed it.
Yes, please.
I really didn't think,
that the Director would think
of Hee-Joo like this.
Thank you very much.
goodbye
Can I help you?
What, what are you guys doing?
What is this?
What do you want to do?
- What is this?
- Close the door!
What is this?
What do you want to do?
Are you Dong-Jae's brother?
Answer!
What?
Are you sure that grandpa
took it?
I understand.
I'll think about it,
and call you in a minute.
This will take a lot of time.
Thank you
Have you notified
Team Leader Choi Yong-Geun?
About?
The method of sending money has changed.
No, I haven't.
Actually that is
not too necessary to do either.
What's the reason you called me
to check it out?
No, I just want to know.
It's true that Ki Dong-Jae killed
Jung Hee-Joo, right?
Right.
Did you find
the clothes Jung Hee-Joo was wearing,
when Ki Dong-Jae killed Jung Hee-Joo?
No
But why
did Jung Hee-Joo's grandfather have it?
How do you know that?
I just checked it too.
I have seen it
with my own eyes.
Today at Jung Hee-Joo's grandfather's shop.
How did you know that it
was Jung Hee-Joo's clothes?
I met Jung Hee-Joo
on the day she was murdered.
It was the same outfit she was wearing
back then.
On that day you met Jung Hee-Joo?
Is it weird for me
to meet my employees?
No, it's okay.
But, what makes you curious?
Honestly I'm worried.
Perhaps because of
the late evidence,
will change the outcome of the trial.
I hope it stays the way it is now.
The fact that the grandfather had evidence,
meaning he hasn't
told the detectives about it.
I hope the evidence does
n't reach the detectives.
Because I don't know what
Cheon Sang-Woo will do with it.
After all, if he is free,
I don't know what
he will do to me.
Maybe he will kill me.
No
He will kill me.
Please get rid of that evidence.
All traces.
Okay. I will do it.
Starting today,
you will be my savior.
By the way
have you ever killed anyone?
what?
Detectives have
killed people too, haven't they?
I'm just asking out of curiosity.
No matter how easily
a detective kills,
killing someone
is not an easy thing.
I never did.
For now.
Are you saying that you
and I are on the same side?
Yes, that's what I said.
I mean, let's help each other.
Because we're on the same ship.
That's from your point of view.
From my point of view,
I brought you guys.
On the ship I ride.
Do you understand?
Yes. That's right.
The Team Leader is correct.
Then do as I say.
Eun-Hye
There is no evidence that Ki Dong-Jae
was not the culprit.
However, there is also no evidence
that Ki Dong-Jae is the killer.
This is taken from the direction of the murder scene.
No Jung Hee-joo.
He says he brought
Jung Hee-Joo who has been killed.
I mean, you don't kill,
Jeong Hee-Joo in a neglected place.
If you see this,
Choi Yong-Geun asks Ki Dong-Jae
where is he and Jung Hee-Joo's corpse?
He asked for sure because he already knew
Jung Hee-Joo's death, right?
He doesn't even ask
how Jung Hee-Joo died.
Judging by just looking at
these recordings,
By disguising a slain corpse
as a serial killer victim,
it looks like Ki Dong-Jae is only in charge
of leaving the corpse.
So someone else
killed Jung Hee-Joo,
and there is a possibility that Ki Dong-Jae
was only used as a scapegoat.
Right.
This is Oh Ji-Hyeok from the Criminal Team
Incheon West Office.
Grandpa is in danger.
- Can't you reach him?
- Yeah, he's not picking up the phone.
- Have you tracked the phone's location?
- Yes.
Hurry up!
Grandpa.
Grandpa?
Is grandpa not home?
Eun-Hye, Grandpa has lived
as long as I can.
Now I will go to my grand daughter .
Live happily!
The location of the phone has been found.
Where?
What is this?
My goodness.
Truly!
Hold on for a moment.
You will soon see your grand daughter
Subtitles provided manually by : Summer Fouad
Why did you let grandpa
be like that?
I'm not a policeman anymore .
But a perpetrator.
Where you can't see,
where I can't see,
you have to be there.
Who gave you the body?
Woo Tae-Ho.
Detectives only have
one reason to the National Forensic Service.
Make sure it is not
a blood stain of one person.
If there is a problem, they will accuse
we are hiding evidence, right?
If you stop here,
nothing will happen.
Are you saying
the culprit stopped too?
If the culprit is me...
I think so.