JUNG Myeongcheol
as Taeha
YOON Hyunkwon
as Jaemin
LEE Suyeon
as Suyeon
LEE Jaehyeop
as Minwoo
KIM Hyunseo
as Yooha
Sweetheart Service
Chapter 12: Blue Sky 1/2
Removing dust.
Master, there is too much trash.
Master, you just sighed.
Stress levels detected. Playing calming music.
Master, there is too much trash.
- Is something wrong?
- Where is Yooha?
Yooha...
why do you ask?
I have something to say to Yooha.
Why not just call?
I... um...
It’s just...
He’s doing a nude modeling gig.
It should’ve started by now.
Thank you.
Ah...
You met Taeha, right?
Yes.
He’ll come back, won’t he?
Taeha.
Taeha, are you okay?
Without Yooha... I don’t know how to live anymore.
I really...
don’t know.
Then...
I’ll show you how.
Sorry.
I’m really sorry, I just...
Taeha.
- I’ll head in first.
- Okay.
Here... I want you to have this.
This is... me?
Don’t laugh.
I’m sorry.
I hurt you with my thoughtlessness.
I’m sorry too.
I shouldn’t have ended it so abruptly...
You were too much for me.
Just being near you was overwhelming.
I think I broke.
But even so...
being with you made me happy.
You break me...
but I don’t mind being
broken like that.
I want to trust you now.
And I want to
keep seeing your smile.
Even so...
could we?
Are you...
acting right now?
Sweetheart Service