Ever since I met you,
you did nothing
but help me sort my life out.
You don't get it
because my life isn't your life.
Hi.
Lulu party?
- Cheers!
I like you.
Aren't you even going to say anything?
What, you didn't ask a question.
Do you like me?
"Lulu"
(Episode 8: Ending, Beginning)
Hey.
Good morning!
I cooked.
Brunch for us.
Have a seat.
There's so many food!
No, you can bring the rest later
on your way back to Manila.
Also, I brewed some coffee,
because I'm not great at making smoothies.
Let's eat.
So, will you be staying at Tricia's?
No, I have a friend
who recommended a B and B.
It's nearby.
I already booked.
It's right in the next town.
Will you be taking all the groceries?
We'll split them. Let's divide it later.
Alright.
I won't be bringing much with me.
Just the canned goods and noodles.
For emergencies.
You can have all the meats
and the fish in the freezer.
Because I'm sure they will be serving meals
where I'm going.
Okay.
Yeah.
I'll help you bring your things to the car.
Okay, thank you.
Are you staying with your mom?
Yes.
I'll crash there for now.
I see.
Let's go swimming.
What?
Just because.
We won't be leaving until later, anyway.
And loading the stuff
in the car won't take long.
It's just the groceries.
Let's go for a swim before we part ways.
Okay, I guess.
Yeah.
Let's check out the spot at the far end.
For a different view.
Okay.
Hang on.
Damnit.
Okay, wait. Here.
That's it.
I got it! That's it.
Sorry, bestie. Signal is weak around here,
as you know.
Girl, what happened to you?
Your mom said you're going back to Manila?
Yes.
What happened?
Nothing.
I'll just stay there during the lockdown.
What the hell. I wouldn't mind being stuck
in that place during lockdown.
You have the beach, fresh air…
And you want to rush into
the toxic city of Manila?
Seriously?
What really happened?
Did you have a fight with your tenant...
what's her name?
Abi?
It's not that.
She's cool.
It's just…
I don't know.
But she's very nice.
Caring,
moody, but…
she can be very sweet
when she's making up for it.
And I learned a lot from her.
So you like her?
How could you possibly know that?
How can you tell?
It's so fun to catch you!
You're so fun to pick on.
Woo! My best friend's a lesbian now!
Stop teasing me.
I hate you.
What's wrong with that?
Nothing, it's just…
Because she's a girl?
No, it's not that.
It's totally that.
Hold on.
Have you guys had sex?
What is wrong with you!
Of course not!
Damn, we're in trouble.
What do you mean?
It doesn't sound like a casual thing.
Stop. You're totally wrong.
So what if turns into something serious?
You're single.
Is she single?
Yes.
Well then, that's all that matters.
You don't have to overthink
when it comes to love.
Let it flow, okay?
These days, love is genderless.
If you fell for her,
then there's no question about it.
That's just how it is.
So relax.
Enjoy the ride.
That's the thing.
I already confessed to her.
Now, look at you.
I'm here spouting
advice like some Love Guru,
but you guys are moving along nicely.
What did she say?
Well. Here we are.
We're parting ways.
I'm going back to Manila
and she's transferring to another B and B.
So you're not her type?
I don't know.
Maybe...
just as a friend.
So you're going home
because she turned you down.
Too bad. She would have been
your first girlfriend, but you got dumped.
Not exactly.
She just has her reasons.
It's not because she doesn't like me.
Then what?
She's going through some stuff.
What are you keeping it in suspense for?
Never mind! Never mind that.
Well,
if you truly care about someone,
you wouldn't just leave them like that.
Just try.
If it doesn't work, then fine.
At least you tried.
It's her loss, not yours.
Oh, well.
Wait.
I thought you were leaving.
Are you going for a swim?
My trip's not until later.
Abi and I are going swimming.
Then why are you wearing makeup?
Is that makeup?
What?
It's just lipstick and a little blush-on.
Okay, fine. You're right,
I put on some eyeliner, too.
You're unbelievable!
You'll look like a zombie
when you get out of the water!
Come on. I'm wearing waterproof.
Okay, I'll see you later! Let's talk later.
She's waiting for me.
Okay.
Enjoy your last day with her with a bang!
As in bang! Bang! Bang!
Yeah, whatever. I have to go retouch.
Retouch?!
- Don't you think it's too much?
- Whatever you say.
Bye!
What are you even doing, Sophie?
Let me just retouch.
Abi.
Hey! Abi!
What happened to you?
What?
Where are you off to, Madame?
Why are you teasing me? Don't I look great?
We're just going for a dip.
You're all dressed up.
Why, does it look bad?
No. Not really.
No, tell me! Is it ugly?
No! It's pretty. It is.
It's pretty.
You're very pretty.
Ready to go?
Let's go.
I got a pedicure!
Little ginger toes!
You're mean!
Wow! This place is beautiful!
I haven't been here before.
This is the place I was asking
the lady over at the alley about.
Maybe you shouldn't
drink too much because...
you'll be driving, right?
It's just one bottle.
And we have plenty of time.
Okay.
Sophie…
What?
Thank you.
For what?
For everything.
For letting me stay at your B and B.
You do pay rent.
For cooking food for me.
They don't even taste good,
and they're already covered in the fees.
For mixing those drinks,
cocktails, the cool drinks.
It's the least I could do
since you provided the alcohol.
For doing my laundry.
Well, you sorted my medicine and put
a bunch in every corner of the house.
Sophie, I want to thank you…
because you always make me smile.
And somehow,
it has helped me forget
the things I'm going through.
You literally saved my life.
Twice.
When...
I almost drowned,
and when I couldn't breathe.
And you helped me take out the trash.
You helped me piece myself together.
I discovered who I was.
So if I happen to make you smile,
I don't know that I do.
All I want is,
for you to be happy, too.
You saved my life, Sophie.
No…
I tried saving your life.
But I failed.
That's enough of that!
Luuuululululu!
Come on! That's enough!
I'll miss you!
I'll miss you, too.
Luuuululululu!
Here.
For the road.
This is a lot.
These aren't our leftovers from earlier.
No, I made some quick-fix food for you.
Where's yours?
What?
I don't need them. I'm sure
they'll serve food where I'm staying.
It's just in the next town.
Okay.
Oh, wait.
Surprise!
Wow!
What is this?
Go on, open it!
Where did you get this?
Somewhere in town.
When I saw that, I was reminded of you.
Actually, Abi...
I want to confess something.
Since we're parting ways anyway…
I know you're going to get upset.
But what can go wrong? We won't be
seeing each other anymore, right?
But I hope you don't hate me
for this, please?
Just get to the point.
What else are you going to tell me
apart from you like me?
- Ouch.
- Get over yourself!
But it's true!
Even so.
So what were you going to say?
I was the one who killed Kaki.
What?
Well, I thought…
I thought she had to be watered everyday.
That's what you do to plants, right?
Water them regularly?
I didn't know the rules
were different with cactuses.
Sorry about that.
Is that it?
Go on, then. Get mad at me. I'll take it.
No, I'm not mad.
I thought you were going to
confess something else.
Like what?
I don't know…
That you changed your mind...
That you can't get me out of your head…
That you can't bear to let me go after all.
The nerve! Get over yourself!
You're so sensitive!
What's going to happen to your B and B?
My mom hired a caretaker to take over.
I'll just hand them the key.
I'll take care of it.
You sure you're going to be okay?
Yes!
I got it covered.
Okay.
It's getting late.
We don't want go beyond the curfew.
Okay. Let's go.
Let's go.
Thank you, Abi.
Thank you, Sophie.
- Okay.
- Let's go?
- Thank you.
- Let's go.
Let me help you.
Alright. Thank you.
Bye, Lulu.
Thank you.
Sophie, don't cry, Sophie.
Please, don't cry.
I told you not to cry.
You're such a crybaby, Sophie.
I already miss you, Lulu.
It's a shame you never met Kakie.
What should I name you?
I know.
Lulubel.
Hi, Lulubel.
You know what, Sophie will be glad
when she learns your name.
Who's Sophie?
She's your mom.
Well, yes, I am your mom.
Hey, she's not a grouch.
She's actually really fun to be with.
She's funny,
and a crybaby.
Who, me?
About to cry?
Of course not.
There's just dust in my eye.
I haven't even left and I miss her already.
I already miss you, Lulu.
Oh, Abi.
What should I do now?
Sure, I'm a loudmouth…
I'm annoying…
But I won't give up.
I won't give up on you, Abi.
Abi.
Sophie.
Are you back in Manila?
That was quick.
No. I'm not yet in Manila.
What? Where are you?
Is there a problem?
Did your ride break down?
No, no, no.
Then what happened?
I'm still here at the B and B.
I didn't leave.
I know you've arrived at your new lodging.
But don't worry about it, okay?
I just wanted to let you know that
I didn't really leave.
Why?
Abi.
I know you've made up your mind.
But I've also decided,
that I'll be here.
I'll support whatever your decision is.
Really?
Why are you doing this?
I'm not really sure either.
All I know is,
I want to be here for you until the end.
Even if you get hurt?
Pain will always be there.
It's not going anywhere.
But wouldn't it be nice if you had someone
with you as you go through it?
Can I be with you?
That was fast. How did you get here?
Bonfire?
Do you want to?
Barbeque?
Camping?
Slurp, slurp?
Let's go.
Come on.
Wow, I see the effort. Love the lights!
Of course. So it looks special.
What are we watching?
Just wait for it. It's a surprise! Relax.
Wait, wait, wait.
How did you know that I didn't leave?
I didn't.
I just wanted to come back.
Come back to you.
You ready?
Game!
What's that?!
Oh my god! You don't remember this?
What is this? Why did you...
I took a video of you
while you were sleeping.
You always have saliva dripping
from your mouth.
Oh my god!
So wasted!
What's this?!
Watch this!
Just when you thought you can leave
everything behind...
When you thought you were drowning...
Oh my god!
Somebody comes along to save you.
That was you, Sophie.
You're the one who gave meaning to my life
just when I thought it was ending.
When in fact, it was just beginning.
This is the start of our life together.
Yes!
Thank you.
I'm glad you liked it.
Of course!
Sophie.
I like you.
Are you okay?
Hey.
Are you having an attack?
Drink this.
Why did you throw it?
So, what do we call this?
A quaranfling?
Or...
Quaranthing?
Quarantungs!
Luuuuululululu!
- Luuuuululululu!
I'll undergo chemotherapy first
to shrink the tumor.
Then I'll undergo operation.
So?
I'll do it.
Sophie, I'm scared.
Don't be.
I'm here. We're going to face it together.
You're not alone.
Just promise me that you'll fight, okay?
For you.
No!
For us.
♪ Hey, you! ♪
♪ You, yes, you! ♪
♪ Don't you know ♪
♪ That I like being around you ♪
♪ But ♪
♪ Oh my god! ♪
♪ I don't know ♪
♪ where this is going ♪
♪ but it is what it is ♪
♪ It doesn't matter ♪
♪ if it's just for a little while,
as long as ♪
♪ I get to be with you again tomorrow ♪
♪ Can I be swept away? ♪
♪ You're the cure to this meaninglessness ♪
♪ Stay for a while, Lulu! ♪
♪ Don't you know ♪
♪ that I really like you ♪
♪ Lulu ♪
♪ Don't you know ♪
♪ that I really like you ♪
♪ I don't know what will happen ♪
♪ So why don't you come with me ♪
♪ You can move in closer ♪
♪ Lulu ♪
♪ Don't you know ♪
♪ that I really like you ♪
♪ Lulu ♪
♪ I don' t know ♪
♪ but I think I'm in love with you ♪
♪ I just do ♪