[Life is Drama]
[Episode 8]
If you're willing to
sincerely follow me,
to be on my side,
I promise to give
the Wang family more face
in the Shangguan family.
Since Mr. Shangguan wants me
to be by your side,
then I'll follow you.
You're really obedient.
I'm used to it.
Ah!
Why are you so childish?
Actually,
there's something I've been
wanting to ask you.
Aren't you
my father's biggest competitor?
Why did you help him so much?
I've said it before,
it's just your misunderstanding.
Stop being so insincere.
I knew
you and my father
were childhood friends.
When you were young,
you used to call him brother.
However,
my father was very good,
you could never beat him.
Who told you that?
Aunt Dabao.
I asked her many things,
including matters about you.
Stop denying it.
You're just being childish,
always wanting to win against him.
Deep down,
you still see him
as the best elder brother.
Who sees him as an elder brother?
Just swing on your swing.
Why are you so nosy?
What are you doing?
Since you're here, just have fun.
Why so serious?
This is not a meeting.
When I was little, my father used to
bring me here to swing.
Every time,
I could swing until sunset.
It's almost sunset!
I'm not playing.
Just play for a bit.
Go!
How was it?
Fun, right?
Grandpa,
what did you call us here for this time?
Chunyan.
Next week,
during Shangguan Group's event,
bring Feng Dongdong to Wang Tianye
and have him assign her a position.
This girl is quite smart.
It's a pity she's just a servant.
Grandpa,
isn't that inappropriate?
All right, I'll make the arrangements.
This time, we must unite, right?
I never thought
that after fighting
with each other for so long,
we'd actually join forces
to deal with a servant.
No.
I think that woman isn't so simple.
Don't you think she looks familiar?
What do you mean?
I have a feeling
that he has known her for a long time.
Known her for a long time?
Could it be...
Who is she?
Don't you think
she looks like Shangguan Xiao?
Shangguan Xiao?
I've sent the photo to your phone.
That's the current situation
with the Shangguan family.
Feng Dongdong.
Okay, I got it.
We can't do anything
to her for the time being.
Why?
Don't ask too much.
Okay, I got it.
Even if I'm not allowed to,
I'll do it anyway.
What did the boss say?
He said to give her some threat.
However, Grandpa
sides with her very much now.
I dare not.
Don't you find it strange?
Yun Su,
my boss,
and my father
all value her so much.
I don't know if you remember
what my father said.
He said he'd leave most of his property
to Shangguan Xiao's daughter.
If Shangguan Chunxiao is real,
then all our efforts will be in vain.
[Life is Drama]