[Life is Drama]
[Episode 4]
What are you doing?
Hurry up!
My wife will be back soon.
How do I explain this injury to her?
Chi Xi!
Miss Chuxue is back.
I'll leave first.
Hey!
Chi Xi!
I was only gone for a few days,
and you're messing around at home.
Do you have no shame?
Ouch.
I didn't do anything.
It's clearly Feng Dongdong's fault.
She got me drunk.
Beast!
Miss Chuxue!
Your husband is a beast!
He wanted to take advantage of Dongdong.
If Dongdong hadn't been smart,
she would've...
She would've been abused!
Do you know?
You don't
need to discipline my man.
So annoying.
You're fired.
Miss Chuxue, I'm begging you.
Please don't fire me.
I have elderly parents
and children to support.
Get lost!
Miss Chuxue.
I won't pursue this matter further
and won't spread it outside.
Please spare Aunt Dabao.
Spare her?
I haven't even said I'll spare you yet.
I want you to take care of me,
not my husband.
Cheap woman.
Being beautiful is a curse.
Oh, oh.
Dear niece,
who bullied you again?
Auntie,
I'm just dealing with a few servants.
You don't need to worry.
Did my niece hit you?
Do you want to call the police
or ask for compensation?
I'll help you.
Shangguan Chunyan,
what's wrong with you?
You don't even call me auntie.
So rude!
I'll tell Dad about this.
How can you manage others
with such arrogance?
If you can't manage people,
how can you manage our family's assets?
All right.
You're dismissed.
I'll let you off today.
Miss Chuxue,
I have evidence
of your husband's infidelity.
You don't love him.
What do you mean?
The wedding ring.
You were wearing it
when you left that day.
You went to see the other man.
So what?
Why do you have such a good memory?
I have your husband's backup phone.
Its contents
may be useful for your divorce case.
Together with my testimony,
it's enough to leave him penniless.
I didn't expect to find
what I've been looking for for so long,
and it's found by you.
What do you want?
I want to be a person
with influence in this family
and earn more money.
You're so direct.
I like it.
I'll consider it.
Then I'll take my leave for now.
She's so clever.
Looks like she can't stay here.
Mr. Yun,
are you going
to the Shangguan's tomorrow
to see Shangguan Chunyan
or to see the lady from last time?
I think
you've been too free lately.
I'm just worried that Shangguan Chunyan
would use this incident
to stir up gossip.
Who doesn't know?
She just wants to
improve her family status
by marrying you.
Only you know, huh?
It's because I care about you.
You're already so old
and haven't been in any relationships.
There are so many women around you,
but you're not interested in any.
Are you interested
in...
You're holding the book upside down.
Aren't you also holding it upside down?
All right,
I'll stop.
I wonder what that girl is doing now.
Who is this girl?
She's a newcomer to the Shangguan's.
[Wang Mufeng]
Mufeng, are you still waiting?
It's been hours, right?
I'm used to it.
Mr. Shangguan has always been
like this with us.
You've worked hard, Mufeng.
It's okay, Dad.
I'm just delivering a document for you.
It's no big deal.
Wang Mufeng,
don't wait anymore.
Mr. Shangguan has gone to bed.
What?
Please leave.
I've...
What are you complaining about?
The Shangguan's are keeping you
because they expect full obedience.
Don't be like that new girl over there
who lacks discipline.
What are you
looking at?
I'm looking at the moon.
The moon?
It's not a full moon.
What's there to look at?
It used to be
so perfect.
By the way,
who are you?
Just an errand boy for the Shangguan's.
I see.
I was quite unhappy just now,
but seeing you
made me feel much better.
[Life is Drama]