[Life is Drama]
[Episode 19]
I assume
you've already made up your mind?
Chuxia,
I'm on your side this time.
I've worked for the Shangguan family
for so many years.
Now, I want to live with dignity.
Mr. Wang,
since we've agreed to work together,
I'll be frank.
I've found out
that Liu Zhiqiang and Shangguan Chunyan
framed my father,
but there's someone else
hiding behind the scenes,
and I haven't been able
to uncover their identity.
You should know more
about this matter, right?
I've kept it to myself
for a long time.
Before I tell you,
you have to be prepared.
The day after tomorrow
is the company's listing.
Let's have
a good celebration tonight.
Cheers.
Congratulations,
my good friend.
The Yun family and Shangguan family
are one.
Thank you, Yun Su.
You two are awfully close.
What about me?
Look at you, Mr. Xiao.
Here. I'll drink with you.
No need.
I want to thank my wife.
What's wrong?
Do you want to go back and rest first?
With so many people,
I can't leave.
Shangguan Xiao,
I didn't know
you were such a lightweight.
Already swaying after a few drinks?
Come on. Get up.
Let me.
My husband needs
to pick up something in his room.
He'll be right back.
My husband needs
to pick up something in his room.
He'll be right back.
All right.
Let's go.
I'll take you back to your room.
Mr. Wang,
who took my father?
Well…
Please tell me.
Yun Su.
You're back.
Mhm.
Do you want to ask me what's wrong?
You'll tell me
if you want to.
But I know even if you don't.
It's because of me.
You know?
I'm sorry.
You took my father?
You deleted the security footage.
Only you have access
because you're the shareholder.
Yes.
Why?
Why did you set my dad up?
Were you the one who put that woman
in the room with him?
Did you install a camera
and send the footage to the media?
Will you believe me
if I say no?
Fine.
I'll give you
a chance to explain yourself.
Say it now!
I've told you everything.
I moved your father inside.
I didn't hire that woman.
I deleted the footage,
but I deleted the hallway footage
for your father's safety!
Nonsense!
You've been using me all along.
You were after my father's data.
You wanted to use it to gain
the Shangguan family's resources
for the sake of the Yun family!
Shangguan Chuxia.
Is this what
you think of me?
Chuxia!
Chuxia, can you please calm down?
How can I calm down?
You were the person I trusted the most.
Why did you lie to me?
How can I believe you now?
I just want the truth.
Chuxia…
Let go of me!
Can you just let me explain?
I can resolve all of this soon.
Don't follow me anymore.
And don't contact me.
Chuxia!
Hello?
Look into Wang Mufeng for me.
[Life is Drama]