[Life is Drama]
[Episode 15]
I know
you're the real Shangguan Chuxia.
Let's meet tomorrow.
I'll help you.
Feng Dongdong
or Shangguan Chuxia,
it matters not to me.
You really don't care?
That identity is yours.
I don't care.
I do.
Wang Mufeng,
I don't believe it's appropriate of you
to call my fiance at this hour.
Brother Yun Su.
I'm not your brother.
I'm your elder.
You should call me uncle.
Never contact her again.
Block him.
What do you have against Mufeng?
Mufeng?
The Wang father and son
are not as simple as they appear to be.
What did he say?
He said he wanted to see me tomorrow.
He wants to see you?
Fine.
I'd like to see him too.
Tell him
to bring his father along.
The four of us will meet.
It's late.
Come to bed.
Get upstairs.
I've invited you here today
to hear your thoughts.
Will you continue to support
the Shangguan family
or will you
help me?
What brought this up?
Has the Shangguan family declared war
with the Yun family?
There is an impostor
in the Shangguan family.
But I think
you know very well
who the real deal is.
It's a huge undertaking.
Shangguan Chunyan
can't pull it off alone.
Who is the mastermind?
I hope
the Wang family isn't part of it.
The Wang family
may be part of the Shangguan family,
but we really don't know anything
about this.
Of course, we believe you.
We wouldn't be sitting here
otherwise.
So,
what's the plan?
We start from the imposter, of course.
These are just your words.
Then continue to consider.
We won't force you.
We won't insist.
We don't have to cooperate
with the Wang family.
What's going on?
Why were you in such a hurry to see me?
Shangguan Chuxia didn't reveal anything,
did she?
No.
Aren't you afraid the old man
will find out
you came to see me so late?
He's at the company.
Oh, right.
Shangguan Chuxia came to me.
It's all right.
Even with the Yun family on her side,
she can't stir up any trouble.
The Yun family is assisting her
with their shares.
Yun Su.
No big deal.
What is love?
Money matters more.
Keep your eyes peeled.
The old man may be well for now.
According to Mr. Liu the butler,
he has a terminal illness.
His days are numbered.
When the time comes,
we can get a fake Chuxia to fool him.
Once the old man is gone,
the money will be ours.
True.
It doesn't matter
if she's the real deal or not.
We'll do the same to Shangguan Chuxia
as we did Shangguan Xiao.
We'll squash them.
[Life is Drama]