Your Majesty.
Does it look good?
Lan'er, you look stunning
in anything you wear.
Lan'er.
What's wrong, Lan'er?
It hurts. It hurts so much.
Lan'er!
Your Highness!
What happened to her?
Doctor! Summon the royal physician!
Yes, sir.
Your Majesty...
The Noble Consort appears to have been exposed to heart-devouring poison.
Heart-devouring poison?
This poison mainly comes from the Western Regions.
Women who touch it with their skin will be severely poisoned.
The pain feels like one's heart is being devoured.
Fortunately, we discovered it in time.
I will give the Noble Consort the antidote
which will neutralize the poison.
Why would such a thing appear in my palace?
Xianglin replaced the musk with heart-devouring poison.
Empress, you can't escape now.
Your Majesty.
I started feeling unwell after wearing
the clothes gifted by the Empress.
Are you saying...
Please have the physician thoroughly examine
if there's poison on that garment.
Wait.
Before investigating the clothes I provided,
perhaps the physician should check if the Noble Consort is pregnant.
Empress, what are you implying?
The physician has examined me many times
in front of His Majesty these past days.
Are you suggesting I conspired with the physician to deceive the Emperor?
Don't worry, my dear.
The royal physician will know after an examination.
With the fake pregnancy pills,
what tricks can you possibly pull?
Your Majesty,
the Noble Consort is not pregnant.
What?
Impossible!
Your Majesty,
please,
please summon another physician.
Summon all the imperial physicians
to My presence immediately.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Noble Consort is not with child.
You're lying!
I wouldn't dare, Your Highness.
Your Highness is weak and deficient in vital energy,
but there is absolutely no pregnancy pulse.
My diagnosis is the same.
How can this be?
Could all these physicians be in collusion with the Empress?
I'm here to check Your Highness's pulse.
Thank goodness Moyan is here.
Noble Consort,
the fake pregnancy pills have lost their effect.
You can't hide it anymore.
What did you say?
Your Majesty,
the Noble Consort recently bribed me with this.
She asked me to make fake pregnancy pills for her.
She planned to bring down the Empress by faking a pregnancy and miscarriage.
I foolishly agreed in a moment of confusion.
However...
However what?
But these pills are extremely harmful to the body.
They may cause infertility.
As a physician,
I couldn't bear the guilt on my conscience.
Later, I added ingredients to the Noble Consort's daily tonics
that would neutralize the fake pregnancy pills.
I hope Your Majesty will consider
that I have seen the error of my ways.
Please forgive me.
Moyan!
You...
Is what he said true?
If Your Majesty still doesn't believe it,
let the palace matrons examine the Consort.
A woman who has never been pregnant
is different from one who has.
Matron.
Yes.
Your Highness.
Examine her thoroughly for me.
Yes.
Let go of me!
What right do you have to examine me?
What if I order an inspection?
So everything they said is true, isn't it?
Yes.
Why?
I know what you've been plotting.
You used me. I don't care.
I was willing to be used by you.
But why did you take fake pregnancy pills?
Do you despise having my child that much?
Yes.
After all this time,
have you never had genuine feelings for me?
Never.
I...
I never want to see you again.
Imperial Consort,
you have trampled on His Majesty's sincere affection,
deceived with a fake pregnancy and framed the Empress.
Your crimes are unforgivable.
Guards!
Strip the Imperial Consort of her title.
Banished to the Cold Palace
never to leave again.
Sincerity?
Who has ever shown me true sincerity?
I have.
You?
Mo Yan.
In the entire palace,
you were the person I trusted most.
Why did you betray me?
Why?
Sister Ruya.
Do you love me?
I would die for you, don't you believe me?
Let go of me.
Every time I see you with His Majesty
or with the Prince,
I want nothing more than to kill them.
I've been suppressing my love for you.
As long as you're happy, I'm happy.
Do you know
how much I've suffered?
So you decided to destroy me?
When did you
start conspiring with the Empress?
The day you became His Majesty's woman.