Please rest early, miss.
This smoke is poisonous.
Thank you, Lady Consort.
Where did this wild sparrow come from?
Dreaming of becoming a phoenix.
Fire!
Help!
The fire is too strong!
Quickly, get more water!
Your Majesty, Miss Yulan is still inside.
Your Majesty,
your safety is more important.
Look!
Miss Yulan!
She made it out by herself.
Miss Yulan, a fragile young woman,
managed to escape the fire unharmed.
It's truly astonishing.
Your Majesty.
I'm fine.
His Majesty has decreed.
Miss Yulan is bestowed the title of Lady Lan.
This is your chamber,
Lanyu Pavilion.
Now that you have your own chamber,
we can see each other whenever we want.
I never thought my first step into the palace
would be a fight for my life.
This belongs to Lady Li
who dropped it in panic during the fire.
What do you plan to do?
Useless!
We agreed she would die in that fire,
but instead she performed a phoenix rebirth
that completely captivated His Majesty.
He brought her back to the palace
and even titled her Beauty Lan.
I had planned everything perfectly.
Who knows what tricks that wretched girl used
to escape without a scratch.
In a fire,
you just need to wet your clothes with water,
quickly escape from the fire,
and you can temporarily avoid injury.
Greetings to Concubine Yushu
and Concubine Lijie.
How dare you!
A mere beauty like you
dares to enter without announcement
and intrude into my chambers.
I've come to present a gift.
My sachet.
You can't possibly think you can use this sachet
to threaten me.
I already said
I came to offer a gift.
The sachet has already been burned.
Whether it's a gift or a threat,
I have no interest in making deals with you.
The gift is not the sachet,
but rather
me.
Have I seen you before?
Jiya
something terrible has happened to my family.
My father has been accused of major corruption
and our family is implicated.
You still come to see me?
Are you trying to get me
implicated in this as well?
My father has lived an honest life.
He must have been framed by villains.
If Your Highness fears being implicated,
I will see His Majesty alone
to seek justice for my father.
You think you can just see the Emperor?
Back then, I didn't want to enter the palace.
But you forced me into the selection of palace ladies
and imprisoned me in the palace cage.
And now that I have power,
you still dare to come asking for favors.
It was Aunt
who was dissatisfied with the marriage my mother arranged for you.
It was to secure you a better family
that she sent you to the palace.
What does this have to do with Father?
Shut up.
Stop making excuses for your selfishness.
From now on, you are a criminal.
There's a world of difference between you and me.
Ji Ruya.
Remember your place.
Jiya.
Speak.
I am but a common woman.
I have no one to rely on in this palace.
I have no intention to compete for favor.
That's why I've come seeking Lady Yu Shu's protection.
Ji Ruya is a criminal.
How dare she enter the palace if she's alive?
I must be confused.
Such a pitiful, lovely face.
How could I possibly feel at ease?
Bring me scissors.
Why don't I just destroy
this face of yours?
Then you'll never be able to bewitch His Majesty again.
Even if you scarred Yulan's face,
there are so many women in this world.
The Emperor's heart is as vast as the sea.
Beautiful women are like spring grass,
wildfire cannot burn them all.
How could you possibly eliminate them all?
I believe
if one wishes to secure favor,
one should make His Majesty unable to live without you.
In this imperial harem,
the Empress is as mild as a chrysanthemum,
only Consort Chun and Noble Consort Ning are close rivals.
But her family background far exceeds yours.
If she bears a child first...
In the imperial harem,
discussing those of higher rank can be punishable by death.
I never intended to enter the palace,
but since I am here,
I naturally must seek
protection for my future.
Very good.
You have ambition.
But if you don't seek the Emperor's favor,
what do you want?