How is it?
Qing'er died for me.
The Empress already knows my identity.
I must move faster to bring her down.
What do you plan to do?
I've been favored for a long time.
I need to have a child now.
You mean...
The false pregnancy pills I asked you to make
how are they coming along?
You'll be diagnosed as pregnant the next day.
However...
This medicine is extremely harmful to the body.
It may cause infertility.
As long as I can avenge the entire Ji family,
what does this matter?
Your Majesty.
The palace consorts are deeply connected with court officials,
pull one thread and everything is affected.
I know you have your preferences now,
but I must speak frankly.
Please don't let one magnolia tree
cause the entire imperial garden to wither,
affecting everything else.
I have indeed been favoring the Imperial Consort lately,
neglecting the other consorts.
Fortunately, you reminded me in time,
so I won't be lost in romantic affairs
and disappoint the senior court officials.
It is my duty.
I hope Your Majesty doesn't find me nagging.
Having such a wise empress as you,
is all I could ask for.
Bring the tribute from Dongling Kingdom,
the glowing green fox pendant.
I wish to reward the Empress generously.
Yes.
This glowing green fox pendant is extremely rare,
there's only one in the entire world.
I am not worthy of such a gift.
You are my empress.
If you're not worthy, then who is?
Your Majesty.
I just heard about that green fox pendant.
I want one too.
Have you forgotten what you just promised me?
Am I carrying your royal heir
and still not worthy of a fox pendant?
Noble Consort,
are you with child?
I just summoned several royal physicians.
They all confirmed I'm over two months pregnant.
That's wonderful!
My Consort,
you will surely bear me
a brilliant little prince.
Your Majesty.
The Emerald Fox pendant.
From this day forward,
whatever you desire,
I will give it all to you.
Your Majesty,
you are so kind.
This is only the beginning.
The Emperor rewards his Consort.
Your Majesty.
The Imperial Consort
Your Highness.
Are you all right?
Today is the 15th.
His Majesty will surely come to my chambers.
I told you to prepare the meal. Why did you come back?
Your Majesty,
I just ran into Eunuch Zhao.
Why don't we let him tell you himself?
Your Majesty,
His Majesty will be spending tonight with the Imperial Concubine
and won't be coming here.
I understand.
There's one more thing.
The Imperial Concubine heard that before you were married,
you were skilled at needlework.
She requests that you personally
embroider a pearl and silver robe for her,
symbolizing prosperity for her and the royal child.
Of course,
this is also His Majesty's wish.
I understand.
Lady Lan.
She's gone too far.
Taking advantage of carrying the royal heir to humiliate you.
Making you personally sew clothes for her.
She's just from a merchant family.
Is she worthy?
Yes.
Of course she is.
My lady.
I heard that in the Empress's palace
many teacups and vases were broken.
She must be
absolutely furious with you.
When a dog is cornered,
it will jump over the wall.
She won't tolerate this pregnancy.
What are you so happy about?
Your Majesty.
I've told you
that you're pregnant
and needn't bow to me.
Yes.
This is...
This is a safety knot I made myself.
It's a bit ugly.
Your Majesty...
I
just want to keep you and our child safe.
It's a pity
I'm destined to disappoint you.
Your Majesty,
the clothes you asked me to embroider
for the Noble Consort's sister are ready.
Please take a look.
The inner embroidery shows a hundred blessings,
and the outer silk is smooth.
The Empress truly has exquisite taste.
It's so intricate and beautiful.
I love it.
Your Majesty,
I want to wear it right now.
Good. Attend to the Noble Consort's change of clothes.
Yes.
She couldn't resist after all.
The threads of this garment were soaked in large amounts of musk.
Once worn,
not even the greatest physician could save her.
But the Empress is very shrewd.
If you miscarry after wearing the clothes she sent,
suspicion could easily fall on her.
Xianglian.
Go check the Empress's chambers.
In the Empress's palace,
there must be a garment identical to this one.
Find it
and replace it with the heart-consuming poison.
Yes.
Your Majesty.
You cannot escape the charge of attempting to murder the favored concubine today.