Your Majesty.
That eunuch is indeed suspicious.
It's the love incense.
Brother.
Lady Lan.
What's wrong with you?
This is bad.
It's the love incense.
This is terrible.
Help...
I'm burning up.
Lady Lan.
Lady Lan,
stay conscious.
Lady Lan.
Your Highness.
Your Highness,
I've finally found you.
What's so urgent?
According to palace servants,
Prince Huai and Lady Lan were seen
entering Guibao Palace one after another.
And there were some
indecent sounds coming from inside.
They must be engaging in
an illicit affair within the palace.
Lady Chun.
Don't speak nonsense about this matter.
This could
damage the royal family's reputation.
Your Highness, you'll see for yourself when you go there.
I assure you
it's absolutely true.
Lady Lan.
I've blocked my acupuncture points,
but I can only resist this love incense temporarily.
Today's incident
is likely a trap set by someone with ill intentions.
Lady Lan.
Don't go.
Don't leave.
Don't abandon me.
This is bad.
Don't leave me.
How dare you, Lady Lan!
She dares to have an affair with the prince
and commit such indecent acts in the palace.
Guards!
Seize this woman who disregards palace rules
and behaves with such wanton immorality!
Yes!
I'd like to see who dares to be so impudent.
Your Majesty!
How can it be you?
This is my kingdom,
my home.
She is my woman.
Am I not allowed to come here?
As for you all,
coming here in the middle of the night with the Empress.
What?
Do I need your permission
to favor my own concubine?
No,
that's not it.
I heard that
Lady Lan and Prince Huai
were committing indecent acts in the Guibao Palace.
That's why I specially invited the Empress to investigate.
I did it all for you!
Your Majesty.
For my sake
You spread rumors just for my sake
and falsely accused Lady Lan.
Pure Consort
I've told you before
that such treasonous matters
should never be based on hearsay.
Yet you still spread rumors with such conviction.
Hurry and accept your punishment from His Majesty.
Your Majesty
please forgive this humble servant.
Enough!
I've spoiled you too much.
Guards!
At your service.
Consort Chun has made baseless accusations,
spread rumors,
and trespassed into the palace.
Confine her for three months.
The Empress has failed to manage the harem properly,
her supervision is lax.
Reduce her salary for half a year.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty.
Get out!
All of you, get out!
Thank you for coming in time, brother.
About the aphrodisiac incense...
Someone must have deliberately arranged this
to lure us both here.
The palace intrigues never end.
You've suffered so much, Lan'er.
My lady, I went to investigate.
There was indeed something suspicious at Guibao Palace.
Someone had lit aphrodisiac incense there.
Then I'll go with the flow.
Go quickly to Zhaoyang Palace and inform His Majesty.
We can use this to eliminate our enemies.
I'll put myself in the game.
It's worth it.
Brother.
Lady Lan's poison
requires you to cure it personally.
I shall take my leave now.
Your Majesty.
Brother.
What are you doing?
The antidote for the aphrodisiac incense.
She has been affected by the incense.
I cannot take advantage of her situation.
Your Majesty! Something terrible has happened!
Someone has taken Lady Lan away.
What?
My lady has been taken.
But she doesn't seem worried.
No one has ever dared to use me as a pawn.
However,
if that person is you...
Where does the melancholy flute sound come from?
One melody from the south brings all things to life.
Wild birds also rejoice with the spring.
At night, the jade flute plays, envying the clear skies.
I was quite abrupt that day.
Are you feeling much better now?
I'm feeling much better now.
Thank you, Prince Huai.
Prince Huai always carries his flute.
These scholars pride themselves on being refined.
You should be careful.
I specially instructed the imperial kitchen
to prepare some dishes to replenish your blood and energy.
What's wrong?
Don't you like it?
Your Majesty.
I'm having my period.
So I'm feeling a bit unwell.
That's why I have no appetite.
As long as you're getting better,
I can rest easy.
Then tonight...
Tonight I'll be reviewing memorials at Zhaoyang Palace.
You should rest well.
No need to attend to me.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
You're so kind.
No need to see me out.
Go back and rest early.
Yes.
Xianglian.
Did you find the flute I asked for?
Get some rest early tonight.
You don't need to attend to me.
Yes.