Rinkham,
where have you been loitering this time?
Have you been mischievous again?
I only came to watch the soldiers today.
This is my friend.
Have you come to enlist as a soldier?
Yes, sir.
Record his name.
Are these all the real deal?
My Lady, please don't play with that.
It is dangerous!
Wow, this is pretty heavy.
Oh my!
That was a close!
Are you always this mischievous?
I used to sneak out my dad's sword to play with when I was a child.
But dad would never teach me how to use it.
Come on,
try sparring with me for a bit.
Let's see if you are fit to be a soldier.
Put it down.
It's dangerous.
If that's the case,
then come make me put it down.
Oh! Please be careful.
Do you know how dangerous that was?
Sometimes, danger excites me.
Can you teach me the way of the sword?
Fall in!
I have to go line up now.
Go for it! Kaew,
my brave soldier.
Isn't his face a bit too clean and pretty?
He’s so small, can he even be a soldier?
Hey... we’re talking to you. Why aren't you answering?
You’re talking nonsense.
Why should I answer you?
We’re speaking to you nicely.
Are you trying to be a smartass with us?
And why are you bothering me in the first place?
So you can learn that you don't belong here!
Then, Am I fit to be a soldier now?
You dare to slash my throat?
I would never use my dad's sword to spill the blood of an unworthy enemy.
Have you been here long?
Why do you ask?
No reason.
What are you doing here anyway?
I just wanted to come and watch what just happened.
You’re much better than I thought.
It would have been a shame if you didn't make the cut.
Let’s go,
they’re about to announce the results in front of the house.
Thong-ek.
Yes, sir.
Suea.
Chai.
Yes, sir.
Man.
And the last one... Klao.
Yes, sir.
I told you, you shouldn't have wasted your time applying.
Someone like you... could never be a soldier.
If you don't want a repeat of what just happened,
keep your mouth shut.
Stop.
You are Kaew, right?
Yes, sir.
You possess great skill.
You know how to restrain yourself
and keep your emotions in check.
I need someone like you to be Rinkham's bodyguard.
Dad!
But I don't want someone tailing me everywhere.
Your safety is paramount, my daughter.
Well, are you interested?
Even though I enjoy having fun with you,
I don’t want someone following me wherever I go.
But I have already given my word to Luang Witsanu.
Therefore, it is my duty to stay by your side and protect you.
I am not an easy person to take care of, you know.
And I am not someone who gives up easily either.
Well then, let's just see about that.
The situation lately has been unstable.
I request approval for additional weapons and troops.
It is not yet necessary.
But the news of the other side's movements...
I know!
Do not let paranoia drive you to overreact.
I have made my decision, and you must follow it.
Yes sir.
This person is such a nuisance.
He refuses everything I ask for.
It seems I will have to find a way to eliminate him...
I need to find...
a weakness to take him down.
Are you Kaew, the new bodyguard for Lady Rinkham?
Yes, I am.
By the way... which way is the Young Miss's room?
Over that way.
Thank you.
Lady Rinkham is quite a handful.
He'll probably be running scared before the day is out.
Lady Rinkham?
She has gone out.
Gone where?
I do not know,
She has been out since before dawn.
Then why did no one follow her?
Well… She strictly forbade anyone from following her..