(Matsunaga) According to the doctor, there will be pain for a while, but
he says it will be alright if you rest.
(Haruka) I'm glad it ended with just this.
(Rihito) I'm glad Matsuri-chan is safe too.
(Amamiya Matsuri) Yamato carried me here,
so I was able to get treatment right away.
(Amamiya Azusa) I can do it.
I'll definitely be at the awards.
No, I'll decline.
Huh...?
PRISM will probably have to do two slots worth.
PRISM is also in the middle of a problem...
I refuse.
I'm definitely going to go and win the Grand Prix.
(Yamato) Don't say stupid things.
There's no way you can stand on stage like that.
・～
(Yamato) Just give up gracefully.
Don't show your fans a lame side of yourself.
Sigh... *slam* (door sound)
When I stand on stage,
I play a cool and perfect version of myself.
That's what I am as an idol.
Just listen to Yamato and stay put.
Terzetto's performance is off.
・～
I'll put it here.
Well then.
Are you going home already?
I don't want to be by Azusa-kun's side anymore.
Huh?
I'm causing trouble and making you worry…
And on top of that, I made you get hurt…
I don't have the confidence to be by your side.
Are you worrying about that now?
Huh?
If you're going to say that, I'm always causing you trouble too.
I'm not that reliable →
I try to help, but I end up getting hurt.
That's…
It's better to only show you my →
cool side on TV.
・～
But just being admired from afar is →
something I don't want anymore.
If you don't have confidence, then properly complete the stage →
I'll prove it.
That Matsuri's place is next to me.
But the injury… Matsuri.
Believe in us.
We'll be at the awards.
And we'll give the best performance →
and win the Grand Prix.
・～
Hey, Matsuri.
Don't you have any words for me yet?→
"I don't want to be by your side"?
・～
"Do your best."
Yeah.
・～
There's no way that's possible. (Haruka, Rihito) Please!
(Matsunaga) A person who is currently hospitalized→
can't possibly stand on stage the day after tomorrow. (Haruka) Please!→
Azusa is fine. With willpower....
(Kisaragi) This isn't amateur hour! PRISM will fill the void in Terzetto.
That's the decision.
(Saionji Subaru) From us too...→
Please.
(Kisaragi) You guys are fine. Focus on your lessons.→
This is your chance. (Kei) Terzetto is, to us,→
an important rival.
I want to fight fair and square.
(Kisaragi) You're not in a position to act cool.
You, who were thought to be an elegant and perfect prince,→
are now a selfish, willful,
self-centered man.
You guys are being forced to carry→
an incredible handicap.
(Haruka) Please.
(Matsunaga) Hey.
(Rihito)
We will never break the fans' dreams.
I also will never do anything→
that would disappoint you.
(Maki) Please→
let both of our teams participate. And→
let us seize the title of Japan's number one idol
with our own hands.
(All 5) Please!
・～
Will we make it in time? Formation change.
(Haruka) Of course. We're brothers.
(Masato) We can manage anything.
...
(Yamato) Should we do it too?
Let's be reborn from
a refined prince to a selfish and willful ->
Egotistical man.
Thanks.
(Kei) Of course. ->
Aren't we comrades?
(Ken)
We're not brothers, but we're bound by fate.
(Yamato) Right.
Shall we do it?
(Yamato) Yeah.
...
Hmm...
Haa...
...
It's okay. We can do it.
...Knock knock. Yes?
Click (door sound) Oh, Matsuri.
You came. PRISM is ->
Our older brothers' rival, but thank you very much, so ->
Here's a little something. Thank you.
Oh, and...
Here's this for Subaru-nii.
Huh? A good luck charm.
Subaru-nii is
actually kinder and more ->
Sensitive than anyone else, so it will definitely get through.
Those articles are going to be okay.
If you're worried about me that much, then →
It wouldn't be so bad if an article came out about it.
What are you saying...? Huh?
Matsuri,
Once today's stage is over →
Become mine.
・～
He doesn't seem like Subaru-nii at all....
That's right.
Selfish and self-centered →
A totally self-important guy.
If I was a prince until now →
I guess... →
A king?
・(Yamato)
Subaru-kun~ Makeup time!
Well then, look forward to the stage, Matsuri.
Click
Ah.
Ah, would you like some coffee?
No, thank you.
Ah... this is a small gift.
See you.
(Yamato)
Hot! Ouch, I got burned....
Huh? Huh? No way! Are you okay?
Ah, are you okay?
Crap.
Ah~ um, um... →
Ah, water! Water! Water! Here.
I don't dislike it.
That stupidly kind-hearted side of you.
Huh...? Ah, just a little...
Can I have it?
Ha... have what?
The promise.
・～
Crunch…
Ouch!
Ah… ah, sorry. Did it hurt?
I can't believe this!
Hey, what are you going to do about this tooth mark!
Call it a ring.
It's a tooth mark!
This is ridiculous.
・～
I'm going to perform for you now.
Come jump into my arms when it's over.
・～
Excuse me.
Ah…
Painkillers, please.
This is the last time I can prescribe them.
(Haruka) I think I'll eat Matsumoto's croissant sandwich.
(Rihito) Me too, me too.
(Haruka) Hey, you→
Take it from this side.
(Rihito) What's wrong with just one?
(Haruka) I want to eat everything I got from Matsumoto.
(Rihito) You're not going to eat all four, are you?
(Haruka) I'm going to eat all four!→
If anything, I'll eat six. All of them… I'll eat three.
Give it here.
(Haruka) You're going to eat three too?→
You're eating too much.
Hahaha.
Hey, Matsuri, today,
watch over me from the side of the stage.
Huh?
When Matsuri-chan is there, →
I feel energized.
Because I can be with you until right before.
Yeah.
(Woman)
Hey, what do you think of Subaru's article?
It's awful, right? I think I've cooled off.
Because,
acting like such a prince →
I can't stand just a selfish guy.
...
Let's do it.
(Audience)
PRISM! PRISM! PRISM!
(Kei) It's quite an away game, but
I believe in you, Ace.
Yeah, leave it to me.
Let's go.
Alright!
Let's go!
(4 people) Shet!
(Cheers)
Kei-kun! Yamato!
Prince outfits are so cool!
Hehe.
Can I say a word before the song?
(Murmuring)
It's not bad to be loved as a prince.
But...
are you really satisfied
with us being kind and ideal? →
Are you really satisfied?
(Cheers)
...(My Prism)
The hands of the clock have started moving
I felt like I wouldn't see you again
Please, please, just the two of us
I want to start walking anew
・ My Prism
(Audience) Wait a minute →
I've never seen Subaru like that. ・ Even if I can't go back
・ Sparkling and shining
・ Memories are just let it be
・ Hold me tight
・ The town that saw off spring is dyed in summer
・ The scent of first love
・ Takes only you away
・ A faintly blurred station
・ The reborn me
・ Next to you
・ I'll hold your hand tight
・ I love you
・ Never again
・ Will I let you go
PRISM is the best after all!
Come with me, you guys!
(Audience) Kyaa~!
Drown in us more.
(Haruka) It's almost time. →
Are you okay?
I'm okay. I'm already switched on.
(Rihito) Good. That's what I want to see.
(Haruka) Look, Matsuri too.
Huh? Me too?
Of course. It's all thanks to you →
We are who we are now.
(Rihito) We didn't even talk properly before Matsuri-chan came.
So, see for yourself →
Our stage.
Come on.
・～
(Haruka) It's because you made us feel that way.
(Rihito) Watch. See how we've changed because of you.
I'm so glad that everyone is my older brother.
I'm really glad.
With the coolest older brothers in the world.
I'm really happy.
・～
Alright. Let's show them the new Terzetto.
(Staff) Terzetto, it's your turn. (Haruka) Yes, we're coming right now.
Let's go! Go! (Matsuri, Azusa, Rihito) Go!
(All 4) Go! Terzetto! (Haruka) Alright!
(Matsunaga) Alright, let's go. Clap, clap, clap... (Clapping sound)
・～
Matsuri, thank you.
For believing that we're number one.
Okay. Give me a reward when it's over, okay?
・(Audience) Terzetto! Terzetto!
・(Cheers)
・Princess, Love is Fleeting (Audience) Kyaa!
・Because I don't want to let go
・Let me hug, hug, hug, hug you tight, Lovin' you
・Let me be your only prince
(Haruka) Hello everyone~ We're Terzetto! (Rihito) Is everyone ready?
・(Haruka) Let's get hyped!
・A breeze blows through ordinary days
・Your colorful smile shines
・I thought I liked you, but
・"I still... I love you."
・Yeah~, I'm sure, absolutely, it's only you
・Flying over thousands of nights
・Let's go see the best scenery together
・My only Princess, Love is Sweet & Sweet
・ I want to feel it
・ I don't need difficult words
・ Hey Princess, love is fleeting
・ I don't want to let you go
・ Let me hug, hug, hug, hug you, Lovin' you
・ Let me be your only prince
・ If we can gaze into each other's eyes
・ Don't look away anymore
・ I miss your smile, voice, kiss
・ I love you
I love you, Princess.
(Audience) Kyaa~!
・ My only Princess, love is sweet & sweet
・ I want to feel it
You've transformed, Terzetto.
Huh?
・ I don't need difficult words
(Audience) Kyaa~!
・ Hey Princess, love is fleeting
・ I don't want to let you go
・ Let me hug, hug, hug, hug you, Lovin' you
・ Let me be your only prince
(Yamato) Aah~ Damn it!
・ You are my only Princess
・~ (My Only Princess)
(Audience) Kyaa~!
(Haruka) Thank you!
Thank you.
(Rihito) Thank you, everyone.
(Haruka) Thank you.
Thank you.
Good work~ (Haruka) Thank you.
Good work.
(Rihito) Good work.
Azusa-kun, you were the coolest in the world.
Huh?
Hurry up and give me my reward.
Huh….
Shall we be alone together?
・～
You know, I thought during today's stage,
I definitely want to be by Azusa's side.
No matter how pathetic I am...→
From the feeling of loving Azusa→
I don't want to run away anymore.
Hehe...
There's no way I'll let you escape.
I'll make you even more obsessed→
So you can never escape for the rest of your life.
・～
Matsuri→
I genuinely love my job as an idol.
Yeah.
I will definitely become a top idol.
But I love Matsuri even more than that→
I love Matsuri more than that.
Even if I searched the whole world,
there's no man who could make Matsuri→
As obsessed as I do.
I will definitely protect both with all my strength.
・～
Yes.
(Vibrate mode)
Huh?
(Haruka) Hey, what are you doing
instead of coming to the after-party?
Haruka-kun?
(Haruka) Oh, is Matsuri with you too?
(Rihito) Matsuri-chan?
(Haruka) Oh, Matsuri! Hmm...→
Hey, Matsuri,
Haruka-oniisama is number one, okay?→
And Azusa, don't you dare
lay a finger on Matsuri!
(Rihito) Matsuri-chan, come home right now
and take a bath with me.
(Haruka) You idiot!
(Matsuri, Azusa) Eh?
(Haruka) Matsuri,
Why don't we sleep together with my arm as your pillow? →
Hey, Maki, say something!
Come on.
(Maki) No, no, I have nothing to say.
(Haruka) Nothing to say, you say...?
Okay, Matsuri, let's get married.
(Haruka) Huh? You, talking about marriage, →
Don't even think about it, Mr. Sparkling Prince. You're absolutely not getting my sister!
(Yamato) Hey, little sister!
What's with that shy face?
Matsuri, →
Come back here.
(Haruka) Don't propose to her!
(Kei) Okay, okay,
What's so great about that youngest girl to everyone? →
(Haruka, Yamato) Huh?!
(Kei) We're top idols,
The choices are endless.
(Haruka) Listen, it can't be helped. Matsuri is →
The most important little sister to us,
right?
(Yamato) Not just an older brother! Matsuri →
You're like Subaru-nii from the old days... Huh?
(Haruka) What's wrong?
Haruka, this. What's going on?
(Haruka) Huh?
The screen is completely black! →
Hey, Azusa!
(Rihito) Matsuri-chan?
(Haruka) Matsuri, are you okay!
Matsuri?
・～