(Amamiya Azusa) I'll take off your bottoms too.
You can get mad at me later.
I'd rather have something
wrong with Matsuri than be hated.
・～
Get well soon.
(Amamiya Matsuri's inner voice)
≪Like I could ever hate→
…≫
・～
Huh? Big brother?
Tap, tap, tap…
(Sound of footsteps descending stairs)
・～
Azusa-kun?
You were originally
satisfied just watching us→
on TV, right? Just go back to that.
Bye-bye.
Bang
Sorry, did I wake you?
No.
I think your temperature has
mostly returned to normal.
What's wrong?
Don't leave me.
Please.
Don't go anywhere.
Don't… come to hate me.
I'll never hate you.
I love you.
Because…
Sorry.
I hate the me who was
Matsuri's boyfriend.
Huh?
What a small person I was, I got angry easily→
I have no composure, and besides…→
I become so possessive.
I want to tie you down so much.
・～
I have to concentrate properly on work
until the awards.
That's why
I asked you to let us go back to being siblings.
Sorry.
That's….
Right now, I have too little composure→
and I know I'm acting strange in many ways.
But I'll do my best.
・～
I'll definitely show Matsuri
the coolest prince→
in the world.
I'll absolutely be number one.
・～
So, please
watch me from the closest place.
・～
Okay.
Can I… kiss you?
No.
Why?
Why, you ask…
Absolutely not right now.
Why!
I said no!
Ugh~!
I'm trying hard not to touch you!
I told you.
Once I'm off stage,→
I'm just a normal high school student.
Yeah. I also→
want you to be normal with me
when it's just the two of us.
・～
Then, only at those times,→
can I have all of your Azusa-kun
to myself?
・～
No kissing…
When Matsuri is feeling better,
can you say that line again?
Then, let's continue this kiss.
Okay.
Please eat a lot.
(Saionji Subaru) Thank you.
(Masato) Thank you.
(Maki) Don't leave your tomatoes.
(Yamato) I don't like tomatoes.
(Haruka) Someone like that →
Doesn't deserve to eat Matsuri's food. Spit it out! (Yamato) Huh?
Seconds.
(Yamato) Oh, me too!
(Haruka) You think I'll let you eat more!
(Kisaragi) Don't eat too much.
Especially Kei, you gain weight easily.
(Kei) Me? I'm getting unfairly targeted.
Everyone,
let's eat our meals quietly.
(Masato) Agreed. Huh?
We rarely agree, do we? Hehe.
It's delicious, Matsuri. (Haruka) I'm glad you like →
I'm glad you like our cooking. Yeah, it's very delicious.
(Yamato) Ugh, this is the worst! What is this!
(Haruka) Eat properly.
(Yamato) Huh? Ugh, geez...
・(Murmuring)
(Reporters) Ah! Subaru-san!
Subaru-san →
Is the content of the article true?
(Reporter) What's the truth?
(Reporter) Please say something.
Oh? You're the... his partner...
Huh?
(Reporter) It's been reported that you're a tyrant who →
Uses your lover in your debut PV.
(Matsunaga)
Understood. I'll deal with it later.
Please calm down for a moment.
Please don't take pictures.
That's wrong...
That's wrong.
This is completely different from the truth.
(Yamato)
First of all, I was the one who recommended him for the PV.
(Kisaragi) The truth doesn't matter. The article is out. →
It's a common tactic to bring down someone who's riding high.
It's a common tactic.
We'll discuss it at the office.
The training camp is canceled. Don't leave the house.
A tyrant is the last thing he is...
・～
Matsuri.
Don't worry. It'll be okay.
・～
>
Do you feel like your head is full of Subaru?
I'm sorry... I understand you're worried and anxious, but→
Let's rest a bit.
It's okay. Subaru-nii is the one having a hard time.
Even so, my role is to worry about Matsuri.
Just listen to me. It's okay to think about Subaru.
Thank you.
No, I actually hate it.
It's incredibly complicated.
I'm sorry. But, Azusa-kun→
Isn't there something I can do to help?
What? I don't know, but...
What if I went to a weekly magazine and talked?
That's impossible. But→
They might write an article about it. That's no good.
But Subaru-nii is being written about, right?
That's what our job is!
That's not what our job is!
Matsuri...→
Me from Terzetto→
And Subaru from PRISM.
Which one do you like?
What are you saying? That's...
It's definitely Azusa-kun... Then→
Me→
Or Subaru-nii, who you used to love?
・～
Isn't Subaru the one who truly makes Matsuri feel safe?
You were too close to notice, but→
Hasn't Subaru always been in love with Matsuri?
・～
(Flashback) Matsuri
I'm sorry.
・～
(Sound of door opening) (Matsuri, Yamato) Ah.
Yamato…
(Yamato) What are you doing, little sister?
Hey, where's Subaru, bro?
(Yamato) He's talking with the president. It looks like it'll take a while.
Then, I'll wait outside.
(Yamato) It's cold. Are you okay?
Eh, wait…
No way. The media is here.
I'm saying this because I'm worried. Got it?
You're too close.
Even though we once shared a kiss? Tap, tap... (Footsteps)
(Matsunaga) "Shared a kiss"?
Ah! →
Ah… Ah, no.
(Matsunaga) You're the one who recommended the youngest for the PV, right? →
Could it be that, actually, it's not Subaru,
but you who's with the youngest…
That's not true!
Yamato isn't like that.
There's absolutely no deeper meaning.
Swish... (Sound of rain)
Matsuri?
Why! You're wet.
Subaru, bro,
I'm going to the weekly magazine's place →
and tell them it's a misunderstanding.
Stop it. There's no need.
Don't do anything unnecessary. It's a nuisance.
I don't want to
get you involved, idiot.
But, as your childhood friend,
I can prove it, right?
That Saienji Subaru has always been
kind since way back →
and everyone's hero.
Subaru, bro,
the truth is, you're not good at →
relying on others or showing weakness, right?
Please. I want to help.
・～
I love you.
Don't go to the publisher.
It's okay.
I'll take back what was stolen myself.
Position, honor, and you.
・～
I'm not the unreliable guy I used to be.
Don't underestimate me. I'm an idol.
I'm PRISM's ace.
・～
*Door slams* Welcome home.
Let's take a bath. I'll wash your feet.
Huh...?
I'm sorry...
What are you sorry for?
What for...?
For shaking off my hand and going to Subaru?
Or is there something else you feel guilty about?
Is there something you're hiding from me?
*Clattering sound (dropping the shower head)*
Huh...?
I'm really sorry.
You were worried about me, but I ran off.
I was going to tell Subaru-nii that I was going to the weekly magazine.
But
Subaru-nii also stopped me, so...
So...
And he seduced you in the process?
Huh? Of course he did.
When he's having a hard time, the girl he loves is...
Thinking about him all the time...
And worrying about him.
If you do that, he'll cherish you...
And he won't be able to hold back his feelings.
・～
Just become mine right now...
Be mine.
・～
Ah...
...
Ouch.
Ah, sorry, that's not it.
I was just surprised...
Sorry...
Haa...
(Kei) Only Subaru is supposed to be suspended. →
Why isn't Yamato coming too?
(Maki) Maybe he got the time wrong. →
He hasn't even read it yet.
Did you hear that the commercials are gone too?
(Maki) Yeah. They don't know how much the penalty will be.
Debuting and then this, it's fatal, right?
(Maki) Don't say that.
There are still things we can do.
Yeah...
Ding dong ding dong... (Chime)
(Female students) Eh? Eh? Eh...? (Female student) Eeeh~ He's so cool.
(Kei) Hey, hang out with me for a bit.
Huh? (Kei) The uniform is a problem, so →
Go home and change first.
I'll come pick you up. Huh?
...(Background music)
Hey, Kei-kun, why are you here...?
(Kei) I got a message that Yamato is slacking off here. →
So, please talk to him and persuade him.
Me? (Kei) Cooperate a little. →
Please. I'll go look for Yamato.
...(Background music)
Alone?
Ah, no....
I'm waiting for someone.
She's super cute.
Let's drink together.
Ah... I...
(Male)
Then, if you chug this →
I'll forgive you.
H-Let me go!
What's wrong?
(Yamato) Hey, mister →
Why don't you stop
messing with someone's date? →
Come on, let's go.
♪ ~ (Background music)
Seriously, Kei-kun, why do you
bring your little sister along?
(Kei)
They'd run away without bait, wouldn't they? →
Why are you skipping lessons?
(Yamato) There's no point in doing lessons anymore. →
No matter what we do, PRISM is over. →
A scandal at this timing
is the end, right?
Yamato, that's not true.
♪ ~ (Background music)
(Kei) I've already called a ride,
so take care of it by then.
Huh...?
Yamato, come back. →
PRISM isn't over. →
Of course, Subaru too, and you too.
♪ ~ (Background music)
Hey, your ride's coming.
Wait outside the store.
I'll take you all the way there.
Hey, Yamato, let's go home together.
Right now, you're worried about Subaru-kun, and →
Azusa-kun is important to you, isn't he?
Leave me alone.
There's no way I can leave you alone!
I know how serious you are
about PRISM and about being an idol! →
I know you're really serious!
That's why...
you're feeling down!
Because you're not getting
any attention from her.
Huh?
Ah!
(Yamato) This is the worst. →
I didn't mean to say it.
I hate having my pace thrown off by others.
But when you're involved →
I become more and more uncool. →
Even now, I'm really worried →
I'm scared of what will happen if PRISM disappears.
・～
I hate it, I do.
PRISM is my family.
Subaru isn't the only one hurting.
Look at me too!
Yamato…
More than you think, probably… →
I like you.
Eh...?
(Yamato) I want you… →
I'm desperately trying, which isn't like me.
(Man) Alright, alright, sorry to interrupt!
(Man) Okay, we're recording! Okay, smile, smile.
(Yamato) Hey! Oh, you know, looking at you →
It's Yamato from PRISM. Huh?
You're totally different from your TV persona. Huh…
(Yamato) Hey! Okay, no way!
I'll make your crush experience the same embarrassment →
And leak it online. You can freak out if you want.
(Man) Admit that your idol character was all a lie.
Or else I'll pour this whole drink on you.
You don't know anything...→
Don't interfere so easily!
Splash!
Haa... haa....
What's wrong with an idol maintaining their image for their fans!?
Don't betray their expectations,
stay cool and collected→
It's not easy at all!
Always trying to be
the figure fans admire→
We're working hard, okay!?
While being told all sorts of things→
Everyone
is desperately keeping a smile on their face!
Why don't you understand!?
Don't get cocky, you→
Brat!
Thud!
Clang!
Haa... that was close.
Eh...?
Are you hurt?
Azusa-kun...
Terzetto's performance is off.
Please.
I'll show you.
Are you really satisfied
with us being kind and just as you imagined?
After it's over,
come running to me.
I'll prove it.
Matsuri's place is→
Right next to me.