・～
(Azusa Amamiya)
I want to hold you tighter.
(Matsuri Amamiya)
W-wait a minute!
Haa... 30 seconds.
Please give me time to take a deep breath.
Denied.
Ehh~!?
Just kidding. Here.
I got to monopolize you
a lot, so →
Satisfied. I'll go buy a drink.
Thump!
Haa…
(Inner voice) >
>
・～
(Haruka) Ah~ I guess this relaxing time
won't be happening for a while...
Lessons start tomorrow.
That's tough…
But I'm looking forward to it.
(Haruka) Yeah.
I hope we can at least participate in the sports festival.
(Haruka) Definitely.
(Rihito) Huh? When is it?
Next weekend.
It's been a while since
I played basketball.
(Haruka) Definitely.
(Yamato) Little sister →
Can you even play sports?
You're so clumsy.
The devil's here!
(Haruka) Huh? Isn't PRISM →
supposed to be busy with
promotions for a while?
(Yamato) Yeah, that's why I came now. Being an idol is crazy, huh? →
There's too much to do.
It's completely different from when I was a dancer.
(Kei) I respect Terzetto
for continuing that.
(Haruka) Easy for you to say.
You guys keep breaking →
our debut records.
Our new song is on the same day, right? Give me a break.
At the sports festival, the siscon little sister has to do her best, right~.
The sports festival and siscon have nothing to do with each other, right?
Because apparently the MVP prize at the sports festival →
is the right to monopolize
Terzetto for a day.
(Matsuri, Azusa, Rihito, Haruka)
"The right to monopolize them"?
(The three of them)
Well, I guess it can't be helped…
(Kei) This cookie is delicious. >
・～
>
Hey~ Are you okay?
Matsuri, if you want, I →
can tell the executive committee
to make them stop?
Ah... I'm okay.
It'll definitely be exciting.
As expected of Terzetto.
As expected of the number one idol.
<<It's not right for me
to make a face and trouble them.>>
(Female student) Pass!
MVP!
Hmm!
MVP! Hmm!
Ah... sorry.
Could you practice a little more seriously?
Well, since we're siblings,
you don't need to monopolize me, right?
Ah～
You're laughing at us for being so desperate, aren't you?
Aren't you?
No!
Clumsy!
Thud (sound of ball bouncing)
(Yamato) Sorry about that!
This girl is clumsy,
she can't catch that pass.
(Female students) Kyaa!
(Yamato) This girl seems to be holding everyone back,
so I'll have her practice somewhere else.
Eh?
(Yamato) Come on, little sister. Eh?
Are you going?
Um, can I practice with you too...?
Um....
Thank you.
If we're seen together,
I don't know what they'll say again...
See ya.
You...
are so boring.
Huh?
(Yamato) You even appeared in PRISM's PV,
but you're still whining.
It's annoying to watch.
Ugh.
Haa...
You're scared of being talked about behind your back.
Get a grip!
Am I still your toy?
I don't intend to be a toy, but...
Are you that shocked
that your beloved Azusa-kun
is just spending a day with someone else?
Haa～, you're such a child～.
・～
MVP
Why don't you just take it?
Eh?
(Yamato) Instead of whining,
why don't you protect your brother yourself?
Work hard
and become worthy, right?
Did you forget because you're too stupid?
That's right! Eh, that's right.
I'm going to aim for MVP!
Yamato, thank you!
Yamato says things other than mean stuff, huh～.
Alright! I'll do my best!
Haa....
I'm trying not to say those things...
Idiot.
Bang (sound of door)
Sorry for calling you out, Azusa-kun.
Um... I'll be home late for a while.
The food is in the fridge.
Haa... Are you mad at me?
Not really. Just that you seem to have a lot of leeway.
Enough to skip class with Yamato.
I don't have leeway, really. That's why I'm practicing.
I want to be the MVP of the sports festival.
Wait, were you really upset?
Then should I go tell the committee...
I want to fight fair and square.
Azusa-kun, you just be there as an idol.
I'm going.
Eh, wait a minute...
・～
I'm quite popular as someone who isn't your brother.
Okay.
・～
I really want to, but I'll hold back until Matsuri wins me over.
I'll be patient.
・～
I'll be waiting.
Okay.
(Rihito) I'm off! (Haruka) Crap, I'm late!
Um...→
Okay!
Fuaah...
A cooking show?
・Chirp chirp... (bird sounds)
・～
Alright!
Amamiya-san, I'm sorry to ask, but...
Could you put the ball away in the storage room when you leave?
Ah... Okay.
Thanks. See you later.
Let's do our best tomorrow. Bye-bye. (Female Student) Bye-byee.
Alright!
Alright! All that's left is the real thing!
Bang. Clang (sound of a lock)
Because you're getting close to Yamato-kun.
・(Female Student) I'll let you out after tomorrow's sports festival...
Be quiet.
Seriously, that guy is so dense. (Female Student) Ahaha.
・Knock, knock, knock! (Sound of knocking on the door)
・Hey!
Somebody! Hey!
Ugh... Just a bit... Huh?
(Yamato) Huh? Huh... What time is it now?
Ah! Ah, crap.
I skipped class and fell asleep~.
Hey, Yamato, Yamato, Yamato!
Your phone! Do you have your phone?
Huh? What? What? Your phone!
(Yamato) Ah... Ah, sorry. What?
The door's locked... I can't get out.
Knock, knock! Knock, knock, knock...
Hey! Somebody! Hey!
(Yamato) Hey, it's dangerous. Seriously!
Let's calm down for a second.
It's the ball game tournament!
I promised to be MVP!
Knock, knock, knock, knock!
Somebody~! Hey!
I understand, but!
Let go of me already...
Aah!
>
Eeeh!?
(Matsunaga) The new song rankings are out. →
It's 2nd place.
(Haruka) Huh? 2nd place?
(Matsunaga) 1st place is PRISM.
Wait, are you kidding me?
We're in our third year since debut, you know.
(Matsunaga) The agency is completely
starting to push PRISM. →
It might be a matter of resolve.
The members of PRISM are →
putting their entire lives and careers
on the line.
They're different from you guys. →
We've been completely replaced.
Terzetto is over.
Bang! (Sound of hitting the desk) It's not over! Terzetto is not.
Rumble, rumble... (Sound of thunder)
Calling for help until morning
might be really impossible~.
・～
Hey, are you listening?
Haah!
I'm seriously
thinking about how to escape, →
can you seriously stop
thinking about perverted things?
Huh? I'm not thinking about anything!
And why is Yamato so calm?
We... kissed...
It was just an accident. Well, it was an accident, but...
Just a simple accident, though... Yeah, an accident.
That was definitely an accident.
An accident... It was nothing but an accident...
This is so annoying~!
All over a single kiss.
・～
Huh?
Don't cross
this line anymore.
Who would...
There's no way I would.
Ah~, that's good. You're
great as a toy but →
you're too childish and boring as a lover~.
I know that!
・Pishan! (Thunder) Whoa!
・Pishan! Rumble rumble rumble...・Zaah... (Rain sound)
Huh?
Sorry.
I... I really hate thunder...
>
(Rihito) Even if you tell me to be prepared...
Prepared?
Click
I... but still, I don't want to lose to PRISM.
(Rihito) Azusa, you're really competitive, aren't you?
Of course,
I'm annoyed too...
But how...?
(Saiyonji Subaru) Yo.
(Haruka) Wow, speak of the devil.
I just had a meeting upstairs.
(Maki) What? He's not here.
Where did that slacker go?
(Kei) Yamato, do you know?
Matsuri and Yamato, we haven't been able to reach them since evening.
Huh?
・Zaah...
Stop!
That's the line.
You crossed it earlier, Yamato.
Hmm... mine doesn't count.
Anyway, don't come any closer than that.
・Pishan! Eek! Ahh...
Haa... haa... haa... Ugh...
・Rumble rumble rumble...
I'll move away properly when the thunder stops.
Don't say such mean things like 'don't come near me'.
・～
It's not mean.
I was deliberately
keeping my distance from you.
Huh?
Because a kiss with me
would depress you even if it was an accident, right?→
Spending the whole morning
with a guy you hate like that→
I thought it would be pitiful...
・～
You're so stupid.
I don't want to hear that from you.
Someone like you who's scared of thunder
isn't scary at all...→
Achoo! Haa...
Sniff... Sniff... (sniffling)
・～
I'll warm you up. There, there... It's okay. It's alright.
I won't do anything.
No meanness or harassment.
So...
don't hate me that much.
(Haruka) Matsuri~! Where are you~!
Haruka!? Here! Over here!
(Haruka) Warehouse... It's a warehouse!
(Rihito) I figured, the GPS stopped at the school...
Huh?
It's the power of love.
Ugh!
Thump!
Matsuri!
(Haruka) It won't open!
Are you okay?
Haruka! Haruka, let me take over!
・Rattling!
Haa, haa... Huh?
Everyone...
(Subaru, Haruka) Matsuri!
(Haruka) Are you okay? Yeah.
(Rihito)
Matsuri-chan, are you okay?
Matsuri. Water.
(Haruka) What? I said "Matsuri."
Thank you. (Yamato) Lucky that it didn't become a big deal.
We got lucky.
Just ended with me kissing your precious little sister.
A kiss?
I'm going home~.
(Students cheering)
(Female student) Go, go, go!
Yes!
Matsuri-san!
Haaah~!
(Students) Waaah!
Tweet! (Whistle)
(Teacher) Game over! Winner, 1-B!
Yes!
(Yamato)
Hmm, I'm looking forward to your game.
What? Don't bother me.
No being mean.
I won't. Because even if you hate me...
I've decided I want to steal you away.
・~
(Yamato)
It's fine. Just give your brother away.
Give your brother to someone.
Don't touch my sister anymore than you already have.
Can I talk to you for a sec?
Huh?
Are you going to punch me?
Heh...
Hey, Azusa-kun...
Give me your sister.
Yamato, I won't give her to you.
Matsuri is mine.
You're not calm, are you, Azusa-kun?
You don't seem like an idol.
Is that why you're losing to PRISM?
And soon, your sister might be...
Taken by me.
・Tweet! Oh, the game's starting~. See you.
Tch! Haa...
Pass!
(Female Student) Nice, nice, nice.
Just 2 more points...
Hmph! You're persistent!
You should just give up!
I won't give up!
(Female Student) Ah!
...
Bee! (End buzzer)
(Teacher) Game over!
The winner is 1-B!
(Female Student) Amazing! We did it!
(Female Student) We won!
(Female Student) Yeah!
We did it!
(Teacher) This year's female MVP is...
1-B, Amamiya Matsuri.
Amamiya-san, please come up to the stage.
Amamiya-san? Amamiya Matsuri-san?
Amamiya-sa~n?
(Haruka) Sensei, excuse me for a moment.
Well~, the prize for MVP has been changed at her request.
(Students) Eh...
The prize has been declined.
Instead, for everyone...
A special live performance from us, Terzetto!
(Cheers)
Princess - Koi wa Utakata
Because I don't want to let go
Gyuutto Hug Hug Hug Hug, let me say Lovin' you
Let me be your one and only prince
(Cheers)
A breeze blows through ordinary days
Your colorful smile shines
I thought I liked you, but
(Yamato) You thought this through.
(Yamato)
With this, you can protect your brother
And not cause a scandal?
Yamato...
(Yamato) You won, so
You should have proudly monopolized it.
Once again, everyone
Understood that they like Terzetto.
Before, Azusa-kun said
That the audience's smiles are the best view.
I don't want to get in the way of those smiles.
Hmph...
After all,
Terzetto is number one.
Huh? Did you forget? My love confession.
Eh? But that was a joke, right?
Well, if you say something so cool about idols,
It's embarrassing to say, "I was serious about my confession."
Ah... Yamato, I...
Wait.
I don't need a rejection confirmation.
Besides, I haven't given up yet.
From now on, I'll try to be
a little more honest.
・～ ("My Only Princess")
I can't beat the prince
as a villain.
・～ ("My Only Princess")
Good work~. (Haruka) Thank you~.
Thank you so much. (Haruka) Yay~!
That was the best! (Rihito) Thank you.
Azusa-kun.
Thank you so much.
Sorry.
I'll go back to being siblings for a while.
Huh?
I'm going to be doing
an idol award show.
Yo.
Why did I get→
rejected...
I'm the most→
important girl in the world, you know.
Too close!
I'm hitting on you.
Azusa-kun...
I'll warm you up.