(Heart Pairing)
Going beyond simple flirting,
now, we show you young people
who want to date...
someone they want to marry.
Heart Pairing starts now.
(Are you ready to be with Heart Pairing?)
(Ready)
Heart Pairing is getting so popular.
We have heated responses.
People talk about this show a lot, right?
Many people have asked me
where their residence was...
and whether I knew the results.
They're curious about the pairing.
- Right.
- So,
I said that I didn't know yet.
I didn't know...
that when I was so immersed in a show,
I made such facial expressions.
I thought that was too much.
I don't know who it was, but you were
especially immersed in someone.
You got me.
- I support Ji Won consistently.
- Right.
- Ji Won.
- I support Ji Won.
I support Ji Won.
Last week, two couples were paired.
Woo Jae and Je Yeon,
and Chan Hyeong and Ha Neul
were the couples.
We managed to get it right.
I've watched the 1st episode
4 times so far.
- What? Really?
- Four times?
I've watched it four times,
and every clue is in the video.
- That's right.
- Right.
So if I watch the video carefully,
I can get the answer right today.
I came with that belief.
It was easy to guess
Chan Hyeong and Ha Neul's pairing,
but it was a bit hard to guess
Woo Jae and Je Yeon's pairing.
In fact, on the first day, Woo Jae...
- was interested in Ji Won.
- I know.
(During the first meeting,)
(Woo Jae had
a special feeling for Ji Won.)
(Woo Jae sent a text to Ji Won
on the first day.)
But after that, not to mention a date,
they rarely had an interaction.
But dating Je Yeon, Woo Jae...
had a good time...
and found common ground with her.
In addition,
at the end of the second episode,
Ji Min kind of provoked him.
Honestly, I'd never seen Woo Jae...
show that he was upset even for a moment.
- He looked like he lost his nerve.
- Exactly.
I think he rebelled against
Ji Min's provocation.
Woo Jae looks careful and delicate.
- Right.
- Yes.
Meanwhile, Ji Min is straightforward...
- and smart.
- Yes.
He's quite active.
Ji Min and Ji Won, after a date,
became totally estranged.
It really broke my heart.
Ji Won sent a text to Ji Min,
- but Ji Min leaned toward Je Yeon.
- Right.
- He's single-hearted.
The date that day didn't affect him.
He has his heart on Je Yeon.
- He's so loyal.
- He is.
That makes a woman's heart flutter.
However, Je Yeon...
sent a text to Woo Jae
since the first day.
Chan Hyeong and Ha Neul...
were paired twice in a row.
Will their pairing become solid
from the beginning?
I don't think so.
To me,
it didn't look like a relationship
with an intense attraction.
Rather than having tension
between a man and a woman,
their date looked too comfortable.
Do some people prefer that?
- I'm asking because I don't know.
- Some people do.
In many cases, a romance burgeons
from a comfortable relationship.
On the first day,
Ha Neul was looking at Ji Min.
- That look of hers lingers in my mind.
- Right.
Things might change from now on.
I like...
- Chan Hyeong.
- Do you?
- I thought so all along.
- I like Ji Won.
- Yes.
- Since he's my favorite,
I hope things turn out well for them.
And...
a catfish appeared
earlier than we expected.
- Chang Hwan has come.
- He's awesome.
Including on all seasons
of "Heart Signal,"
he's a catfish of a character
we've never seen.
He's so manly.
He cooked steak
with his sleeves rolled up.
Would Chang Hwan, the new guy,
be able to shake things up?
What do you think?
I think...
people may recognize his charms
as time goes on.
I think, whether it's a man or a woman,
when someone is cute,
that's the end of the game.
- That's right.
- And...
Chang Hwan looks like a guy
who'll look cute before long.
- Really?
- Yes, he has such charms.
It's getting harder to predict...
people's hearts on Heart Pairing.
Today, let's go to Italy once again.
(Pairing House, Italy)
(The fourth morning)
- Who's that?
- It's Ha Neul.
(Stretching in the Sunset Room)
That's cute.
(Stretching)
- She's flexible.
- Does she practice yoga?
(Stretching)
I'm a good horseback rider.
You're even a good horseback rider?
I mean, I'm not excellent,
but I can ride a horse by myself.
- I can ride it alone.
- That means you're good.
You surprised me.
(Ha Neul has amazing motor skills.)
She's so good.
(Is Ha Neul a former athlete?)
(Meanwhile, Chang Hwan is having coffee.)
This is Chang Hwan.
It's like a piece of art.
I love him.
(Immersed)
He's just my type.
- He's like a boy next door.
- He's wearing track pants in the morning.
He needs to feel the sentiment
early in the morning.
(Swinging his arm)
(Is Chang Hwan doing
his morning exercise too?)
(Patting)
Is he going to hit his back on the tree?
(Jumping)
I love that!
Oh, my.
He's my type.
(Doing pull-ups on wisteria)
He's having fun
in everyday life like that.
I like that kind of person very much.
He's so good, by the way.
(He can't lose his muscles in Italy.)
(Taking off his jacket)
I haven't worked out for quite a while.
(Taking a deep breath)
(Preparing to do his 2nd set right away)
I have this right here.
What a fool.
(Bringing equipment)
(Exhaling)
(Groaning)
(Ji Won is taking a morning walk.)
- It's Ji Won.
- Ji Won is out.
(Last night)
(Ji Won didn't get a text from Ji Min.)
- She didn't get a text yesterday.
- No.
Ji Won, it's okay.
It's okay, Ji Won.
She was upset that day.
It's okay not to get a text
on the first day.
You can do it.
Fourteen.
Fifteen.
(Exhaling)
One more.
- One more time.
There you go.
Well,
you need to see a man
who gets back up after taking a fall.
All right. He's doing great now.
Let me try just one more time.
- Eight, nine...
- Yes!
Ten!
(Groaning)
(Panting)
(Gasping)
Why am I doing this?
Chang Hwan has passion.
He has such a nice character.
(Same space, different energy)
There she goes.
I need to exercise my lower body.
(Jumping up to his feet)
I need to exercise the lower body
after the upper body.
Right?
I need to exercise my lower body.
- Who are you talking to?
- He keeps talking to himself.
He should.
Broadcasting stations would like him.
(He fills the audio up.)
Five, six,
seven, eight, nine,
ten, eleven, twelve... Gosh!
Chang Hwan is so energetic.
Oh, goodness.
Gosh.
Ji Won and Chang Hwan are going to meet.
No way.
(While Chang Hwan is catching his breath,)
(Ji Won passes him by.)
- Why?
- I guess she didn't see him.
- "Didn't see?"
- What was that?
- Did she pretend she didn't see him?
- When he has such a presence?
- Or...
- She didn't see him as she was thinking?
- Good morning.
Gosh.
I just worked out.
Did you work out?
How did you work out here?
I was hanging up there.
Really? That's amazing.
Bodyweight exercise is the best.
Did you sleep well?
Yes, I think so.
All right.
- That was natural.
- Did you just hear how he said it?
- "Did you sleep well?"
- He talked like Choi Min Su.
(The way he talks
reminds him of Choi Min Su.)
"Did you sleep well?"
Gosh.
- Did you take a rest?
- I worked out too hard.
You worked out too hard?
It's been a long time.
- It was made of steel, with the wisteria.
- Yes.
I shook it, and it seemed strong.
Did you work out using it?
I did pull-ups there...
- about 70 to 80 times.
- What?
(Surprised)
Is that possible?
- Was it 50 to 60 times? Anyway...
- What?
Oh, my. I can't do it even once.
Really?
I can do 100 push-ups.
(He shyly confesses his motor ability.)
You're so good at exercising.
(Grinning)
- It was so cold yesterday.
- Right.
So I took a cold medicine
before I went to sleep last night.
Really?
- I feel better after getting some sleep.
- Do you?
- Ji Won looks thinner than yesterday.
- Yes.
She looks gaunt.
I have attachable warmers.
- Really?
- Give her one.
Do you want one?
I brought three.
- Really?
- This much.
- I brought them,
- You're prepared.
but I haven't used one.
- I'll give you one.
- Thank you.
I have cold hands and feet,
although I'm a man.
No, I have cold feet only.
(He has cold feet only?)
He's cute.
"I have cold hands and feet,
although I'm a man." That's so funny,
(I have cold hands and feet,
although I'm a man.)
(No, I have cold feet only.)
- My hands sweat excessively.
- Is it because you're tall?
Maybe because I have big feet.
(Revealing his physical information)
That's a possibility.
My feet are 300mm.
I've never seen anyone like that.
May I show you?
(Lifting his feet)
He has a cute personality.
- What's your shoe size?
- It's 250mm.
- It's 250mm?
- Yes.
Your fingers are very...
You have beautiful hands.
Really?
- I have long fingers.
- Let me see.
He might touch her hands.
Your hands are really...
You have big hands too.
My hands.
It's because I did this so much
when I was little.
I can't make sounds doing it.
I just did it.
What? You just did it.
You didn't realize your skill.
He made Ji Won laugh.
Nice work, Chang Hwan.
The yellow book is Chang Hwan's.
- Right.
- Look at Chang Hwan's flirting skills.
"I have rather big hands.
So when a woman mentions my big hands,"
"I tell her to put our palms together.
When our hands meet,"
"I compare our hands,
and then hold her hand."
He holds her hand when their hands meet.
(Cutting)
(Chang Hwan, Ji Won, and Ha Neul
prepare breakfast.)
How do I cut onions
for stir-fried potatoes?
You can julienne them.
Cut them thinly.
I'll try.
They don't need to be very thin.
- You know what I'm saying?
- Yes.
I got it,
but I'm not sure if I can do that.
Anyway, I understand.
Ji Won is kind of falling for Chang Hwan.
- Cook them fully, to be safe.
- Okay.
- If it turns out...
- Right.
- raw...
- We need to cook them thoroughly.
That's right.
(Focused)
(Glancing)
Four eggs...
(At this moment,
Chang Hwan is serious about onions.)
All right.
(Cutting)
He's detailed.
(Detailed cutting with a solid body)
- Can you get me some butter?
- Butter?
- A cut one?
- I saw butter a while ago... No.
- Excuse me.
- It's okay.
Here it is.
(He completely figured out
what's in the fridge.)
The onions here are so spicy.
The onions here are especially spicy.
I guess they're different.
I know. They're foreign onions to us.
(It's not over until it's over.)
- You're good.
- I have no basics.
That's not true.
- She complimented him.
- Ji Won keeps complimenting him.
I went to a good place...
(Top-class wine and steak)
(Chang Hwan gave them
a strong first impression.)
For your partner,
is there something you can never allow?
As for me,
I don't like someone who bluffs.
He was paying attention then.
I shouldn't have cooked steak.
No, that wasn't bluffing.
You were really good.
(Working hard)
Shall I bring you a hoodie from upstairs?
You can zip it up in the front.
- You have a choice.
- Thank you.
You can wear a padded jacket...
- They're creating a nice mood.
- May I wear this one?
(He brings outerwear for Ji Won
who took a cold medicine.)
- What?
- What was that?
It makes my heart flutter.
Like this.
- It's big for me too.
- Did I wear it right?
- Be careful.
- Okay.
(Ji Won is in Chang Hwan's clothes.)
- But we have no chopsticks.
- No chopsticks.
Chopsticks...
- I think I saw them.
- Did you see them?
- Forks...
He's cute.
Why do I feel like I saw them?
(This man is a much warmer person
than his first impression.)
All right. Let's dig in.
- Thank you for the food.
- Thank you for your work.
Who cooked this?
(The three of them
prepared a delicious meal.)
- As expected.
- It truly is a sumptuous feast.
Oh, my. I spilled it.
- This is a potato dish, right?
- The chef cooked it.
Did you cook the potato dish?
Ha Neul is a good cook.
(Enjoying)
It tastes so nice.
- It's good.
- Chan Hyeong keeps looking at Ha Neul.
- The potato tastes so good.
- Does it?
- Is it seasoned all right?
- Yes.
- It tastes good.
- Does it?
(Proud)
The way she looks at Ji Min is different,
right?
Yes, it's so different.
You can't reach the potato, right?
Take some.
He cares about Ha Neul so much.
I got enough.
Chan Hyeong clearly has
a relaxed personality.
- You revealed your forehead.
- Yes.
- You covered it yesterday.
- I'll keep...
- Will you reveal it even more?
- revealing it more.
Later.
(Glancing)
Tell us what you talked about last night
among the men.
We talked about so many things.
- If I say it here, it won't be fun.
- I heard you guys didn't talk a lot.
We also talked about which book we chose.
- Really?
- Yes.
We haven't talked about that yet.
I know. Shall we talk about it today?
(Last night)
I think we need some time
to have 1-on-1 conversations.
- I thought of this as we talked today.
- You're right.
If we are going to do that,
we should do it now.
(The guys decided to try a 1-on-1 date.)
That's true.
Then...
Let's do that freely tomorrow, okay?
- Okay. Let's just wing it.
- Right.
I think that's what we should do.
He's trying to read the room.
(The women don't know about their plan.)
We've been talking about this and that.
We noticed that there wasn't much time...
to talk to each other. Especially 1-on-1.
- We thought it was a shame.
- I see.
We talked about
how we could talk to each other for long.
(Chan Hyeong suggests 1-on-1 dates.)
Chan Hyeong makes the suggestion.
We don't have to do that in the house.
- Right?
- Of course not.
We can put on something warm.
Let's put on something warm
and see Florence.
That sounds good.
Make sure you put on something warm today.
- Okay.
- All three of you.
Is there someone
you want to talk to first?
Am I too direct?
I want to talk to Je Yeon.
Okay.
He didn't hesitate.
Gosh. What do we do with Woo Jae?
He said it out loud.
Are we going to Florence?
She's not looking at him.
We'll do this in Florence?
We haven't decided on anything yet.
I just said it because we could go out.
Are you guys okay with going out to talk?
- We...
- Since we don't have much time.
Right?
Look at Woo Jae.
We can see their characters.
We'll do the dishes.
You can get ready.
(There's tension in the dining room.)
There's tension.
Shall we?
- Thank you for the food.
We enjoyed it.
They are not staying there for a month.
They only have a week in Italy.
I guess they want to make...
some good memories while they're in Italy.
This is what I have.
- That's it?
- Yes.
And it's too thin.
I think I should bring my coat.
(Sighing)
(The men are becoming impatient.)
(There are three women.)
- Goodness. He looks manly.
- Gosh. Look at Chang Hwan.
Look at him.
(If you don't muster up your courage,)
(you might miss your chance.)
He doesn't hesitate.
Chan Hyeong goes first as expected.
(Chan Hyeong goes first.)
Today... No one came before me, right?
(Whose room did Chan Hyeong go to?)
(Chan Hyeong chose Ha Neul.)
Do you want to go out with me today?
Let's go.
Let's decide where to go later, okay?
Okay. Bye.
(He's the first one to get a date.)
Chan Hyeong is so...
He has his way.
(Relaxed)
He was here just now for you.
Was it Ji Min?
Wasn't it his voice?
They talk about Ji Min
as soon as he leaves.
- The one just now.
- When I was in the bathroom?
- Right.
- Yes.
(Ji Min went outside
without crossing Je Yeon.)
(He's waiting for Je Yeon.)
You shouldn't be out there, Ji Min.
But he already said out loud
that he'll go on a date with Je Yeon.
Who will Woo Jae go to?
(Woo Jae is ready too.)
- Well...
- Yes?
- Is he...
- What?
going to ask Ha Neul out?
(Is he going to ask Ha Neul out?)
This makes me feel so nervous.
(Will Woo Jae...)
(ask her out?)
Yes?
Is she getting ready?
Yes.
Ji Min went to see Je Yeon,
but he couldn't.
She doesn't seem happy.
Gosh, it's so tense.
Is he there?
They told me that Ji Min came downstairs.
Did you ask someone out?
- How...
- You didn't, right?
Are you going to do it now?
You can ask someone on your mind.
You should do it.
If you want, you can do it here.
Let's ask them out here and go out.
But...
What I'm thinking is...
Well...
(What I'm thinking is...)
First,
I'll do as I like.
You'll see how it goes?
- Yes.
- Okay.
- If you hesitate,
- Yes?
I don't know who that will be,
but I could ask her out first.
- Oh, my.
- Right? So...
I see.
So he thinks about others
in situations like this.
- He doesn't step up.
- Woo Jae doesn't.
He's telling him to go first.
- Are they in their rooms?
- Yes, they are.
All of them?
I saw Je Yeon.
But I'm not sure about Ji Won.
- I'll ask her out then.
- Ji Min is going.
(I'll ask her out then.)
I think Ji Min will ask Je Yeon out.
I think so too.
(Ji Min goes to ask someone out
on a date.)
(Ji Won came out of her room
at that moment.)
(Knocking)
- Yes?
- He ran into Ji Won.
He didn't even look at her.
He could have said hi, at least.
(Upset)
How could this happen?
(It's so interesting.)
Yes?
(She stops.)
(Standing still)
Do you have a date?
Do you want to go out with me?
Okay.
- Now?
- No, a little later.
- Oh, no.
- It's all right, Ji Won.
(Ji Min leaves.)
You're going to feel cold again.
- I'm going to put on a coat.
- Do you want a warmer?
- Or you can stick it when you're there.
- Sure.
I'll take one now.
Are you going to go with him?
I'm not sure.
- You should come with me.
- Okay.
- Are you all right with that?
- Yes.
You can go anywhere if there's a place...
you want to go.
Sounds good.
- I'll go downstairs.
- Okay.
- Take your time.
(Ji Won will go on a date
with Chang Hwan.)
Good for her.
He asked her out so calmly.
I have a feeling...
- that Chang Hwan knows what women think.
- Really?
I think he instinctively knows
how to make them feel comfortable.
Ji Min saw Ji Won,
but he didn't even say hi.
I don't think Ji Min...
can see anyone else for now.
- Everyone but Je Yeon is blurred.
- But I think...
acting like Ji Min is...
the right way instead of confusing others.
- That's true.
- If he has no feelings for Ji Won,
it's better that he doesn't look at her...
No, he just couldn't see her.
Is that it?
- I think so.
- I don't think so.
But here's another thing.
Ji Won didn't see Chang Hwan earlier
either.
- That's true.
- She missed Chang Hwan.
But she had a reason to miss him.
She didn't need to see him.
She didn't.
Anyway,
there's only been three episodes,
but I don't think
Ji Min and Ji Won will work out.
That's why things need to go well
between her and Chang Hwan.
They must be taking a while to get ready.
Woo Jae, are you going to talk to anyone?
- I think we need...
- Yes?
some time to spend in groups of two.
So, will Woo Jae be alone?
His true colors are showing.
Oh, no.
So, you're yielding today?
Yes.
I mean,
I'm not being laid-back.
I feel like we need some time to do so.
- But I spent a day with her yesterday.
- Right.
I also spent some time with Ji Won
when I drove, although it was short.
I thought there should be a person
who lets others have a chance.
Just one.
Have you been thinking about
doing that since yesterday?
No. I just decided today.
- From what you saw today?
- Yes.
I'd want to spend at least one more day
with someone I like...
while I'm in Italy.
Maybe, you're far more generous than I am.
He's the bigger person.
(What outcome...)
(will Woo Jae's decision bring?)
Woo Jae might find those words
pretty disturbing.
- Yes.
- Right.
Ji Min and Woo Jae need to...
eat and sleep in the same house,
and they can be slightly in disagreement.
So, if they start liking the same girl,
- there will be some conflict.
- I'd love to see that.
- Yes.
- I...
I believe they already had...
three imaginary fights in their heads.
- They fought in their heads a few times.
- Yes, they did.
Woo Jae seemed to be deep in thought
at the table in the morning.
A man like Woo Jae...
needs some alone time
to think things through.
He texted Ji Won on the first day.
- On the second day, he texted Je Yeon.
- Je Yeon.
He might be pretty confused as well.
- You know, about his feelings.
- But...
it doesn't seem like a wise choice
as he's in a competition.
- What would you have done, Si Won?
- To be honest,
I could only see Chang Hwan
among the men today.
(So could I.)
He looks so charming.
(A date between Chan Hyeong and Ha Neul)
- You can get in first.
- Thank you.
(Affectionate)
I'll get the door for you.
- Ha Neul smiles so easily.
- They look cute together.
I like how cheerful she is.
- It's my 1st 1-on-1 date.
- Exactly.
- The very first one.
- We...
- It's my first time too!
- Is it?
- We've been together the whole time.
- Oh, you're right.
The whole time...
You're right.
Let's go.
(Squirming)
- You really laugh a lot.
- Do I?
(Nodding)
You're like that with everyone,
aren't you?
- You're always smiling, aren't you?
- No, I'm not.
I don't believe you.
Chan Hyeong can be
pretty straightforward too.
- He hopes she doesn't.
- Exactly.
(Their first private date)
I'm relieved
as I know you're a good driver.
I'll take you there safely.
This is lovely.
(They're excited from the beginning.)
Haven't you talked about this...
with other men?
Our jobs?
No, the women you're interested in.
We're a bit careful.
But they just told us...
when we didn't even ask.
Like, "I want to go on a date with her."
- So...
- They told you the truth?
So, I picked one first,
and they went next.
- They made a move pretty soon.
- I guess no one liked the same girl.
I went to you twice.
That was my second time.
- I heard.
- You did?
They said, "Chan Hyeong was here earlier."
(This morning)
(Snooping around)
Is Ha Neul here?
No?
(He failed in his first attempt
to ask her out.)
Oh, he went to her twice.
Yes?
Do you want to go out with me today?
Let's go.
(Nodding)
(He succeeded in asking her out.)
I could finally ask you out
after visiting twice.
There could have been more men
who wanted to get to know you.
- I find that hard to believe.
- I actually...
Chan Hyeong knows it.
You can tell from the number of texts.
I don't know.
- So it was more than one.
- I don't know.
- You got more than one.
There will be new events
when we go back to Seoul.
Like what?
- There will be a new girl.
- Oh, a new participant.
You look so happy!
That's not it.
I was just embarrassed.
- That's not...
- Seriously.
You know what I mean.
That wasn't what I meant.
I just thought it was funny.
That's all.
I'll check your face
once the new girl comes.
(Reading his face)
Chan Hyeong seems more into her, right?
Yes, he's definitely into her.
- He is.
- He asked her what he was wondering...
too early.
I feel like Ha Neul
is also starting to like him.
A little.
(They drove from Florence
for 20 minutes...)
(to arrive at Fiesole)
That's amazing.
Where should we go?
- I think that's the plaza.
- Right.
- This looks like the place, right?
- Yes.
Is it?
(A local bakery by the main square
of Fiesole)
Are those cookies?
(It's known for its welcoming owner
and celestial pastries.)
They smell so good.
How about this?
- Sure.
- Right?
This one and this one.
This and this?
You can get anything you want.
- We can keep them for later.
- Then, from here to there.
- I'm joking.
- "One of every kind, please."
- I'll get it.
- No, it's on me.
Then,
I'll buy you better things next time.
When we go back to Seoul.
Is she implying that
they should meet up in Seoul?
It'd be so interesting when we go back.
They're leaving the door open
to future possibilities.
(They feel closer already.)
I'll cut it now.
(Working hard)
He's delicate.
(Eating)
(Feeling proud)
- He's so cute!
- You're so cute, Chan Hyeong!
He can't hide his joy.
(Pressing)
You really do a lot of stuff.
You do horseback riding,
you play the violin,
and you're a good cook.
"That's right."
(Thinking)
What is this?
- Is her job being revealed?
- Is it what she does?
(We're revealing...)
(the versatile Ha Neul's job.)
(Using her elegant and beautiful lines,)
She must be a dancer.
(she touches people's hearts
with every movement of her body.)
That's why she was so flexible.
(She started dancing
when she was captivated by Korean dance.)
- Korean dance!
- Oh, she's a Korean dancer.
How gorgeous.
(And late at night,)
(she uses her natural-born charms
and expressiveness.)
What is it?
(She shows people...)
She's beautiful.
(another type of beauty.)
She's not so shy in front of cameras.
(A professional mindset)
(Ha Neul is a model and a dancer.)
She's a model and a dancer.
What else are you good at?
- What else?
- Yes.
(Thinking)
She's a good cook.
What else?
I'm not that eloquent.
What you're good at...
- must be connected to what you do.
- That's right.
- To her job.
- Yes. I almost gave it away.
He wants to know what she does for work.
What are you good at, then?
What am I good at?
(Thinking)
I...
never went to school.
Were you home-schooled?
Yes. With my older brother.
- That's interesting.
- Right?
- Were you abroad?
- I wasn't.
- You were in Korea? How fascinating.
- In Korea.
I think I got to try...
a lot of stuff during that period.
(Fascinated)
Since when?
I finished elementary school,
and then I was home-schooled.
(Amazed)
I was home-schooled for about three years.
- That was pretty short.
- Yes.
What about high school?
Then, I went straight to college.
- He went to college early.
- He's a genius.
Doesn't that mean he went to college
when he was a teenager?
(He went to college
after he was home-schooled for 3 years?)
They're telling us his job now.
Is it Chan Hyeong's job?
(As soon as he gets to work,)
(he takes out a white gown.)
(Flapping)
- He's a doctor?
- Is he a doctor?
(He's been practicing as an internal
medicine physician for 6 years.)
I do mostly two jobs.
I treat patients as a doctor...
He was home-schooled,
and he became a doctor?
That's impressive. He must be intelligent.
(After 2 years of pre-medical studies,
4 years of medical school,)
(followed by 5 years of internship
and residency training,)
(he became an internal medicine specialist
when he was 26 years old.)
(He started practicing
earlier than others.)
I will now begin the endoscopy.
He was confident for a reason.
You might feel uncomfortable
as it's gone deep now.
Every time they asked me
what my dream was in elementary school,
I wrote, "Doctor."
(His childhood dream, doctor)
So, I started studying for it
when I was home-schooled.
- That's incredible.
- I only studied at home,
so it took a toll on me
to keep studying...
for so long.
So, I went through the courses
faster than others...
and went to college early.
He must be gifted.
("The youngest person in Korea
to enter and complete medical school")
I became a medical student when I was 15.
Oh, my gosh.
He went to medical school
at the age of 15?
Oh, my gosh.
He became a doctor really fast.
He did.
(Little Chan Hyeong
dreamed of helping others,)
(so he chose internal medicine,
where he treated a cold to cancer.)
He's excellent.
That's so impressive.
(In the evening after his work)
I don't think that's all.
That's when I decided...
to do things that would create meaning.
So, I went on a medical volunteer trip
to Cambodia,
and I noticed that a lot of them...
already had phones.
But they had never seen a doctor before
in their lives.
I was like, "What?"
The devices are up-to-date,
but they weren't provided
with up-to-date medical care.
Treating them individually
would be helpful, but I thought...
numerous people could benefit
from systematic changes.
I thought I could make a difference
in an IT sense.
That's when I started going around,
looking for developers.
I'm currently working hard
as the CEO of a start-up company.
He started a company?
(For more people
to benefit from medical care)
The sky's the limit for him.
To be precise, we're looking to reach
Stage 8, but we'll start from Stage 6.
(He's busier than anyone else.)
As we keep executing it,
we'll be able to plan a digital system.
He's a doctor and a start-up CEO.
He's intelligent.
- I've never seen such qualifications.
- Exactly.
He's practically a genius.
He was the youngest person in Korea
to enter medical school.
He was the youngest person to enter...
- and earn a master's and doctoral degree.
- Gosh.
Considering his achievements,
we might be able to look him up...
in an encyclopedia.
I'm a parent of students,
so I'm like, "Chan Hyeong is impressive!"
(You want him as your son-in-law,
don't you?)
He's become the ace participant
of this show now.
You're number one!
- I wish I had a son like him.
- At the age of 15...
Yes, I also wish I had a son like him.
Only extraordinary people
can achieve what he did.
With such qualifications,
it's easy to be conceited.
- But he's considerate to others,
- Right.
and he had the ability to draw out...
people's best qualities.
(You're right.)
Ha Neul is also impressive.
She finished a master's program
in Korean dance.
Most of them have a master's degree
or a doctoral degree.
You have no place there
with only a bachelor's degree.
(Disappointed)
- I think she's also a model.
- She is.
I thought she was too pretty.
(Pondering)
Am I the only one who knows
that you were home-schooled?
Yes. No one else knows.
- Not even Ji Min?
- No one but you.
Really? But when you're sharing a room,
- you may bring it up.
- No, this is my first time.
- She keeps mentioning Ji Min.
- He still has a place in her heart.
You're making me curious.
(Glancing)
You seem really clever.
That's why I can't wear glasses.
- Will you look like an engineering major?
- When I wear a pair of glasses,
it might amplify that image of mine.
- Did you bring your glasses?
- I did.
- Show me later.
- When I'm working...
Well, there are two kinds.
(Serious)
Show me.
- That's cute.
- I'll show you one of them for now.
Sure.
I've gotten even more curious now, though.
- Sorry?
- I'm even more curious now.
Same here.
Well... How should I put this?
- Even yesterday...
- Right.
And this morning too, when I asked you...
to spend the day with me,
my curiosity toward you....
- It grew.
- grew.
I felt some sort...
of kinship with you.
- In many ways.
- But then,
I learned you did a lot of things.
Also,
you seem to be good at what you do.
I try hard.
Were you easily able to fit this trip...
in your schedule?
(Curious)
I have a job
that allows me to be flexible.
If I work harder, I can do a lot more
in the same time frame.
If I want to rest,
I can take some time off.
- Also, I can be flexible...
- That sounds great.
by talking it out
and asking for more time.
(I see.)
I wanted to meet someone
who was their own boss.
Because that's how I would define
my work and job as well.
- She could easily understand.
- Right.
- I wouldn't have to explain as much.
- Of course.
- You're right.
- It still won't be easy...
if both of us are busy,
especially if we're to start a family.
We wouldn't have enough time.
(An in-depth conversation continues.)
He mentioned having a family.
(Proud)
(A red sunset
envelops the nighttime of Fiesole)
It's really pretty.
They make a great couple.
- I can see the sun from here.
- You're right.
- Right?
- That's the right expression.
It's so pretty.
It's beautiful.
Why don't we observe from here?
- Sounds good.
- They're speaking casually now.
If you look over there,
you'll see the moon.
- Where?
- Over there.
- I don't see it.
- Look at it from here.
A plane just flew...
- over it.
- You're right. It's there.
(The moon photographed by Chan Hyeong)
Isn't it fascinating?
The sun and the moon...
- are together.
- They're together.
What makes it perfect is this branch.
You're right. It adds charm and romance.
(A charming and picturesque evening)
- This is interesting.
- Why am I so amused by this?
- We're the only ones here.
- Right.
The others are at the square.
- That's why I love it more.
- Right.
- I'm sure we had the most fun today.
- Also,
I bet we enjoyed
the most beautiful scenery.
Where they're at...
- It should be beautiful.
- would be beautiful too, but still.
(Snapping)
You're good at taking photos.
I noticed that.
(Flustered)
I knew you had been receiving texts.
You were aware of it.
There's a pattern to your words.
(A gentle nudge)
I guess I should've...
changed how I talked.
- I still would've known.
- Of course.
Goodness.
(Chan Hyeong has been
texting Ha Neul every night.)
Chan Hyeong's only been texting
one person.
(I hope the weather tomorrow
will be as good as today's!)
(I hope you have a restful night!)
That's how he sent his texts.
"I hope..."
No wonder Ha Neul pointed out the pattern.
Right.
Being consistent is a great quality.
Absolutely.
Being consistent is important.
It sure is.
I hope you won't change.
Goodness.
I wasn't expecting that.
Are you kidding me?
(Does it end here?)
- Come on!
- What?
(The bride enters.)
Gosh, the dates are really important.
- No way.
- They're so important.
Things rapidly progressed
between those two.
- They were fond of one another,
- Right.
but doesn't it feel like Ha Neul,
who seemed reserved,
- took a big step?
- A huge one.
- It was enough to solidify things.
- Right.
Chan Hyeong's great on 1-on-1 dates.
He reached deep into her heart.
To me, Ha Neul was the one
who delivered the last punch.
(Ha Neul's meaningful words)
- It signaled to a future.
- I wasn't expecting that.
Also, Chan Hyeong couldn't stop smiling.
- That's right.
- He was beaming.
- He likes her a lot.
- Absolutely.
Here's what I want to know.
Both of them have
positive energy and attitudes.
There's a good chance
they'll be going on dates...
- with other people.
- Right.
I wonder how he'll be...
with other women.
I bet he'll be nice to them.
Ha Neul smiles brightly
and engages in conversations too.
So even though the date went well,
I feel like we'll have to keep watching.
Because the two...
are naturally cheerful and kind.
There's a scene that's been bugging me.
The date was going just fine,
but Ha Neul suddenly asked
if Ji Min also knew it.
(During her date with Chan Hyeong,)
(Ha Neul mentioned Ji Min.)
There's a reason she brought him up,
and it must mean she was thinking
about Ji Min during their date.
(No way.)
- I'm bothered by how she mentioned him.
- I see.
Ha Neul, don't be like that.
Ha Neul, my gosh. Don't do that.
(Chang Hwan and Ji Won's date)
Are you cold? Should I turn it on?
It's funny how it looks so warm though.
I know.
It could be summer by the looks of it.
- This is so cool.
- I know.
- It's amazing.
- I'm curious about that building ahead.
- Is it a cathedral?
- Beats me. It does look like one.
It could be owned by the boss
of this town.
The town's richest person.
It's to symbolize who's boss.
(The scenery is a wonder.
How will their date go?)
Their conversation flows.
What's your preference
when it comes to trips?
Are there places you like to visit?
I pin a few locations on a map.
- Then...
- You save them on the app?
That's right.
But I don't stress out
when things become impromptu.
- Right.
- I actually find that amusing.
However, I don't take a single step...
without having a plan first.
Those who don't mind random trips...
don't even look up the transportation
they must take.
- They just head out the door first.
- I can't do that.
There are people like that.
It surprised me.
I wouldn't be able to sleep
due to the worry.
Exactly.
- They're on the same page.
- What a relief.
It seems like Ji Won's having a good time.
Chang Hwan makes people feel relaxed.
(Thinking)
What do you do in your spare time?
In my spare time?
I like baseball.
Do you like going to the stadium?
I don't go there often.
I watch the game on TV,
but at the stadium?
I have my cat and dog to look after.
He has both a cat and a dog?
It's obvious which book is yours.
- Busted.
- Oh, dear.
He's Mr. Yellow.
(Before leaving for Italy)
Could it be...
Who is it? Is that Ji Won?
(Smirking)
(The Pairing Book Ji Won selected)
Was it yellow?
(The Pairing Book Ji Won selected
was yellow.)
- I think you're right.
- I got goosebumps.
I got goosebumps.
(Ji Won...)
(chose Chang Hwan's Pairing Book.)
That's exciting.
There was a question about...
a normal day you'd like
to enjoy with your spouse.
"After coming home from work,"
"I'd like us to talk about our day
and how we felt..."
"over warm dinner
so that we could relate..."
"to how we each feel
and comfort each other."
That's about a 99-percent match...
to what I picture
as my everyday life with my spouse.
His view on marriage
seems to be similar...
to mine.
She figured out it was him
when he talked about his cat and dog.
Goodness.
("Because I have a cat and a dog,
I'm busy on my days off.")
(Glancing)
Look at her glancing at him.
She smiled.
(Is Chang Hwan from the yellow book
the person Ji Won imagined?)
- I'm curious about something.
- Sure.
Can a cat and dog live together?
My dog's on the sensitive side.
It's sensitive,
so rather than friends,
they're more like roommates.
- They're just roommates.
- That's cute.
- They're complete strangers, but...
- A cat as a roommate...
- and a dog as a roommate.
- That's right.
They don't hate each other,
but they don't like each other either.
They just live their own lives.
(Chang Hwan's dog, Seong)
- How adorable.
- It's so cute.
(His cat, Yeon)
And they live together?
Them being that close
means they get along.
A Chinese restaurant in Florence?
- They went to a Chinese restaurant?
- Shall we head farther in?
Doesn't this look
like a traditional Japanese ramen?
You're right.
Maybe that's what we should order.
We'll ask them
to make it exactly like this.
(Joking)
- It's ramen.
- That looks good.
That looks really good, though.
- Enjoy.
- And dim sum.
We'll enjoy it together.
- I'll enjoy it.
- It's good.
- Isn't it good?
- My body just melted.
- Doesn't it...
- remind you of tteokguk?
- Yes.
Ji Won's looking even more relaxed.
They seem relaxed around each other.
- It's delicious. My gosh.
- That's so good.
- It's so good.
- This is amazing.
My body's warming up,
- thanks to the tasty dish.
- Right?
I suddenly feel much kinder.
(Laughing)
That's a unique expression.
- When you're cold...
- You become snappier.
Snarkier and unkinder.
I don't think we need to order beef.
Or should we?
- I'm good.
- I'm good as well.
- This seems just right.
- Right.
I can't eat a lot in one sitting.
Same here.
Maybe, I have a small stomach.
I eat small amounts but often.
We're the same.
- They're compatible.
- In about 2 to 3 hours,
- Really?
- I might enter a shop,
saying I'm hungry.
That's why I always
carry around an energy bar.
That's what I always have for breakfast.
We seem to have similar lifestyles.
That's very important.
They're compatible.
They should marry.
We seem to have similar lifestyles.
- That's cute.
- What...
What's yours?
- Your favorite food.
- My favorite food?
Ever since I was a kid,
I enjoyed jjajangmyeon.
Jjajangmyeon.
- Likewise.
- What?
- Really?
- Yes.
Seriously?
I prefer ganjjajang.
Yes, that's what he wrote.
- Really?
- Yes, he wrote that.
I must say this, though.
There aren't many places
that make a good ganjjajang dish.
Do you have a favorite place
that serves a good one?
(Thinking)
- Around Mapo.
- Mapo?
From there, you travel up.
- Take me there once we're in Seoul.
- Sure.
(Startled)
Something got stuck.
(What on earth?)
- Ji Won.
- I love it.
(Please have ganjjajang in Seoul.)
(How adorable.)
- Do you have anything to ask?
- To ask?
(Pondering)
It can be anything.
What I want to know most
is what you do for a living.
That's something
I'm dying to know as well.
(The uniquely charming Chang Hwan is...)
- What does he do?
- Here we go.
What are we seeing?
- It's an airport.
- An airport?
I'm a commercial airline pilot.
A pilot that operates the Boeing 777.
- No way. Is he a pilot?
- Is he a pilot?
(A pilot?)
Seriously?
(No way!)
I've been a pilot for ten years already.
We constantly look at the sky...
and the clouds
when operating the aircraft.
- No way.
- I'm stunned by their beauty every time.
There are stunning moments...
that I hope everyone
gets to see at least once.
(The fluctuating sky has him on edge.)
(Beautiful scenery
one can't easily see...)
(Thunderclouds)
He's even seen the northern lights.
(He gets to enjoy beautiful scenery
one can't easily see.)
That's a shot of Jeju Island from above.
All I did was fly and land the plane,
but when...
the passengers thank me
for the safe flight,
- I feel proud.
- Gosh.
He's a pilot.
- That...
- That's unexpected.
(He's a seasoned pilot who is responsible
for his passengers' safe journey.)
That's so cool.
- He gets to travel around the world.
- Exactly.
On his first day,
I thought there must be a reason
he knew so much about wine.
Yes, of course. Exactly.
He's comfortable
being in foreign countries.
We don't get to see the pilot often.
- We rarely get the chance.
- At the airport,
- we see them when the crew walks by.
- That's right.
I don't remember seeing a pilot
that handsome before.
I'm amazed.
- I'd love to see him in his uniform.
- I bet he looks good.
- He'll look good for sure.
- Of course.
It was the same for "Heart Signal,"
but they seem different...
- once you know what they do.
- Of course.
- Right.
- Their profession adds another layer.
I'm a fan of Chang Hwan's.
(He now has a new bias.)
That's what I'm most curious about,
but it's not something I can ask.
- I'm now full.
- Right.
I ate too fast, and now I'm suddenly full.
- Let's go.
- Sure.
The food here was delicious, right?
I'm truly satisfied.
- They make a good couple too.
- Tell me about it.
- Isn't it pretty here?
- It is.
(The sparkling streets of Italy)
The shops and streets
have Christmas vibes now.
Right. Goodness.
- My gosh. This is nice.
- I love it.
(Here and there, you sense Christmas.)
- This is cute.
- It is.
Is that a cat or a dog? What is it?
- It's cute.
- I see, it's a dog.
I like things that are cute.
I don't seem that way though
because of my beard.
The videos I'm recommended
are about cute dogs, or...
- They leave you hooked.
- Right.
- How adorable.
- Look how cute it is!
Please try some.
(A gelateria famous for its pastries
and espresso that opened in 1921)
- I'll go ahead and try some first.
- Sure.
- Is it good?
- This is a flavor I like.
I like nutty flavors.
(Savoring)
- It's really good.
- It's warm and delicious.
How is everything today this good?
Ji Won is beaming right now.
I'm loving the atmosphere between them.
Chocolate cake or strawberry cake?
- Strawberry.
- Strawberry?
(A game of This or That suddenly begins.)
Yangnyeom fried chicken
or plain fried chicken?
A game of This or That?
This needs to be done well.
I wonder what she'll say.
(Will this also prove
that they're compatible?)
Yangnyeom fried chicken
or plain fried chicken?
(Laughing)
That's a tough one.
If I had to choose,
I'd go with plain fried chicken.
- Plain fried chicken?
- Yes. What about you?
I choose yangnyeom fried chicken.
- I see.
- Because...
there's this one dish I love.
- Which is?
- It's from this brand.
I know what it is.
This is what I should ask next.
The controversial ones.
- Such as?
- Like Hawaiian pizza.
Hawaiian pizza, like or dislike?
I don't mind it. I can't say I hate it.
- I don't hate it either.
- Right.
- I don't actively order it, though.
- Exactly.
Or like...
- Mint chocolate?
- Yes.
- I don't hate that either.
- I like mint chocolate.
- I actually prefer it.
- There are days...
when I really crave mint chocolate.
You crave that mintiness
in mint chocolate.
- What about coriander?
- I eat them.
We've got many options then.
The two get along well.
Pyeongyangnaengmyeon?
Do you like Pyeongyangnaengmyeon? I...
- I love them.
- Same here.
Really? Nice.
(Totally...)
(in sync)
I relieve my stress by eating.
We're the same in everything.
(Thinking)
What do you consider in marriage?
- "In marriage?"
- Like your partner.
- That's straightforward.
- Let's go.
Since I'll be living
with that person forever,
I've always...
wanted my spouse...
to be my best friend...
or something like that since I was young.
In short, you want him to be your lover
and your friend.
Yes.
A lover and a friend are different, but...
I get you.
It's better than
an uncomfortable relationship.
We'd talk more.
That's my ideal type.
Being able to communicate well
with my spouse...
is crucial.
- That was an important point.
- What she said was important.
Chang Hwan has the same standard.
- Nice.
- Really?
Yes.
Whether or not they can also
be your good friend...
- seems important too.
- Exactly.
(They have a serious talk
about marriage values.)
Isn't that the most essential?
Marriage is a reality.
You'll stay with that person all the time.
That's the one you'll live with forever.
What's your ideal?
A friendly person.
- Really?
- "A friendly person?"
It really depends. I'm sure everyone...
is friendly and kind in some situations.
But even in bad situations...
Some are born with friendliness,
while some are born with kindness.
Right. That's important.
(Nodding)
(Glancing)
That tendency won't ever change.
Are you good at dancing?
"Dancing?"
I liked dancing in school.
- I was in the dance club.
- Really?
(He realizes something.)
What did he realize?
(University dance club)
The dance club?
The Pairing Book.
(The Pairing Book owner
was in a dance club.)
(The owner of that very Pairing Book
is Ji Won.)
(Getting goosebumps)
They were on the same page.
Oh, my.
- That's fate.
- What?
(Chang Hwan and Ji Won
chose each other's Pairing Book.)
(And their favorite movie
of all time is...)
(6. The movie I love and a scene from it)
("About Time:" The main characters
enjoying the wedding...)
(despite the heavy rain was beautiful.)
- "About Time."
- Yes!
- The two wrote "About Time."
- I got goosebumps.
I watched it more than five times.
And I cried at the table tennis scene
every time I watched it.
That scene was the most...
I'm tearing up just talking about it.
It's meaningful in many ways.
It must feel strange at that moment.
- It's in "About Time."
- In what?
"About Time."
The father tells the son...
to marry a friendly woman.
- His heart must've fluttered.
- Right?
Even my heart is fluttering.
- What?
- Oh, gosh.
What? How exciting.
(A partner sharing the same
ideal marriage values)
(Tearing up)
(Touched)
It must feel strange at that moment.
We should take this couple out.
- Stop.
- Right?
- I'll set them aside like this.
- Okay.
(Chang Hwan and Ji Won)
It seemed like Ji Won
didn't have much expectation.
But didn't "About Time"
bring the situation to the climax?
- Isn't it like a movie?
- Exactly.
It started with ganjjajang,
then exploded with "About Time."
(A whirlpool of emotions)
I loved it.
(How cute.)
And for two people
to have so much in common?
It's called reciprocity of feelings.
You come to like the person who likes you.
Right.
That makes their feelings go deeper.
Especially when the movie they chose
ends up being the same,
it'll really boost those feelings.
To think there would be such a pairing.
I'm seeing Chang Hwan in a new light.
- Chang Hwan was so cool.
- Absolutely.
We have one couple left.
Ji Min and Je Yeon.
- And Woo Jae.
- As for Woo Jae,
what was he doing?
Let's continue.
Do you have a date?
Do you want to join me?
(I'm in.)
- Finally, it's Je Yeon and Ji Min.
- Right?
(Ji Min finally goes on a date
with Je Yeon.)
(Feeling nervous)
It could be cold.
But...
- It's here.
- You're right.
Wasn't all of it for Ji Won?
- I already gave it to her.
- Give me one.
- Is it attachable?
- I'm good.
(Je Yeon tidies her outfit
before the date.)
- You'll use it, right?
- Yes.
It's quite dirty.
(Being thorough)
A place we haven't been to yesterday.
(He notices her.)
Do you have a hand warmer?
I'm warm,
but I got one for you in advance.
- I'll give it to you.
- Thank you.
So this is how you take credit.
- It's not taking credit.
- Who did you get it from?
It's a technique I should learn.
(The hand warmer owner)
- It looks good on you.
- It does.
- You can have it.
- I feel dizzy.
I stuck it on.
- It's on my back.
- Good.
(Ji Min and Je Yeon's date)
- Cover yourself with this.
- Thank you.
- It's soft.
- It's super soft.
He gave his jacket.
- Is there silence between the two?
- Yes.
(Spacing out)
To Je Yeon, such silence...
- is nothing.
- Exactly.
(Smiling)
- You know,
- Yes?
out of all the facial expressions,
you have a spacing-out expression.
"A spacing-out expression?"
- What is it like?
- Quite often,
- you have a blank expression.
- "A blank expression?"
(During breakfast)
(She was smiling brightly,)
(then spacing out.)
The shrimp...
(Ji Min spotted Je Yeon
spacing out a couple of times.)
Were you thinking about something?
I just space out for real.
- I like spacing out.
- Really?
(Je Yeon has a reason for spacing out.)
- What's your favorite food?
- My favorite food?
Beef?
We had a lot of beef here,
- so now, I'm craving pork belly.
- Pork belly?
- So you like pork belly.
- Yes.
- I love pork belly too.
- Really?
I also like sashimi.
What type of sashimi?
I like yellowtail sashimi.
- Big yellowtail in season now?
- Yes.
- I also like rockfish and flatfish.
- I see.
But you don't drink soju?
If I had a high tolerance for alcohol,
- I would've drunk a lot.
- That's so fascinating.
It's possible not to drink soju
while eating big yellowtail?
Is there something unexpected?
I don't know.
Is this how you're going to play?
Surprisingly, now that he's with Je Yeon,
the way he talks became gentle.
Compared to when he was with the guys.
I remember the first impression
I had of you.
- Your first impression of me?
- Yes.
- You seemed very shy.
- Very shy?
Yes, that's how she was on the first day.
(Je Yeon seemed very shy
since the first day.)
I will try to adjust...
to your speed.
- My speed?
- Yes.
What speed are you talking about?
You seem to take your time slowly.
For what?
The time you take...
- to get to know someone.
- The time I take to get close to someone?
- Yes.
- I see.
I didn't know about that scene.
He's practically confessing
his love to her.
For Ji Min,
the difference is extremely clear...
- between friendship and love.
- It's very clear.
What I mean is that
you shouldn't feel pressured.
Okay.
You don't need to try...
- to break the silence.
- To break the silence,
- talking nonsense...
- You don't need to.
- I don't need to?
- No.
The weather is so beautiful.
Right.
- A lot happened in the car.
- Yes.
It's pretty here.
- What was this tree called?
- The name of this tree?
- Cypress tree.
- Cypress.
Do you know that
there's an avenue of cypresses?
- Is there?
- It's one of the tourist spots.
- I saw it in photos.
- I see.
Those trees are lined up.
- That sounds so beautiful.
- It's beautiful.
During the day, it's very sunny.
That'd be so beautiful.
Without buildings like these,
- Only the trees?
- there are only trees.
- It's like a forest.
- Yes.
After some time, we could go there.
Okay.
Is your first impression of someone
very important?
- He's very forward.
- First impression?
First impression?
(Smiling)
Don't answer. It seems hard for you.
- Let's skip it.
- I was recalling...
the past.
You seem way too contemplative.
It has been so long...
- Okay, never mind.
- that I can't remember.
That's enough.
(Thinking hard)
Things could change.
My first impression of someone
isn't everything.
You could become more interested
in someone as you get to know him.
- I see.
- Yes.
Once time passes,
as long as I'm not a bad person,
I think we can be close.
Yes.
- Pardon?
- What?
Ji Min looks so happy.
Okay.
- I think you're on the right track.
- Okay.
This is amazing.
It looks beautiful already.
Isn't it beautiful?
Seriously.
This isn't the bridge
that we saw yesterday.
You're right.
Ji Min, isn't it because you're seeing it
with someone else?
It's so beautiful.
(Even the view looks different today.)
Is it because it was cloudy yesterday?
- I think so.
- That looks beautiful.
It's a completely different place.
- We walked here yesterday.
- It looks so pretty.
Right.
It didn't look like this.
There wasn't a waterfall either.
(A new feeling, a new discovery)
I'm raising my voice.
(Giggling)
Gosh, they look great together.
Are you okay with walking for ten minutes?
Yes, I'm okay. It's not that cold.
- Really?
- Yes.
As the weather is nice,
it looks so beautiful.
I agree.
- I finally feel like I'm traveling.
- Exactly.
Do you usually walk fast?
I walk fast when I'm in a hurry.
That's needless to say.
- Do you usually walk slowly?
- It's needless to say.
I usually walk slowly.
Ji Min wants to be playful with her.
I tend to walk slowly.
To answer your question,
the type I like is...
I don't know if it's okay to say this,
but I like women who are elegant.
Elegant?
(A moment ago, in the car)
We had a lot of fun yesterday.
- The four of you?
- Yes.
All four of us have
different personalities.
I see.
Our ideal types are also different.
Did you talk about your ideal types?
Yes.
- Could you tell me?
- Whose type you want to know?
All four of you.
I'll tell you if you choose only one.
- Only one?
- Yes.
What type of women do you like?
Me?
You want to know about mine?
You told me to choose only one.
She's clever.
- She is.
- Je Yeon is also clever.
- I like women who are elegant.
- Elegant?
And calm.
Something like that.
Ji Min is very honest.
- Yes.
- Right.
Feel free to take photos
if you find it pretty.
I will.
If not, you can take photos of me.
Sure.
- I want to keep souvenirs.
- Okay.
I came back here after a long time.
Ji Min doesn't stop smiling.
I guess you can't hide your feelings.
It's beautiful. Look over here.
(Exclaiming)
There's another person kayaking.
- Are you cold?
- No.
Je Yeon, what type of men do you like?
- Type of men I like?
- Yes.
Like what I said.
(Well...)
Let me think about it.
I've never thought about it.
- Okay. Slowly.
- Slowly.
- Take your time.
- Okay.
Don't count to ten.
What he said is quite meaningful.
When he said, "Slowly."
Among men who say that
they'll match the woman's speed,
hardly any of them keep their promise.
(He's so honest.)
Is that so?
- They always do what they want.
- It's something you say...
- when things aren't going well.
- Right.
He wants to see things in the long run.
- Gosh.
- Oh, my.
That was smooth.
(On a street in Florence,)
(a Korean couple is taking
wedding photos.)
Mr. Groom, please step forward a little.
Ms. Bride, hold your hands in front.
(Rushing)
I wasn't the only one mistaken, was I?
- No.
- Right?
- Yes.
- I thought that she was talking to us.
(Something funny happens by chance.)
When she was calling for the bride...
Wait a minute.
(Flustered)
- We came the opposite way.
- The opposite?
Oh, no. I got lost.
- Then naturally...
- It's the complete opposite.
- Let's search for it again.
- Goodness.
Gosh, that startled me.
I felt so guilty.
(Thankfully,
they're going in the right direction.)
I almost broke out in a cold sweat.
(Their date is in full swing now.)
It's the merry-go-round from yesterday.
It's the plaza that I mentioned.
- Is it where you came ten years ago?
- That's right.
- With buskers in the evening?
- Yes.
(Ji Min has memories of Florence
Republic Square from 10 years ago.)
I came here.
I have good memories.
- Of this place?
- Did you walk here at night?
- I didn't walk here.
- It's so beautiful.
That's so pretty.
Ten years ago, I was there...
for 4 to 5 hours and spaced out
while feeling the breeze.
From 7 to 11 p.m.
I was alone then.
I saw couples spending time together
passing by.
I also saw old couples.
I have such a wonderful
and romantic memory of this place.
It's beautiful.
- Do people perform here?
- Yes.
This place came up when I looked up
"merry-go-round in Florence."
It must be the only place.
(Starting with a warm cup of coffee)
- It looks delicious.
- It does.
Tell me which one you like.
- One that I like?
- Yes.
- This one.
- The black one?
They look delicious.
Can we order here? Cool.
Shall we order these four?
That sounds good.
- I'll hold it.
- Thanks.
Which one do you want?
I'd like...
- You wanted this one, right?
- Yes, didn't he say...
- that it's coffee-flavored?
- Yes.
- Let's have one each.
- Okay.
(Eating)
He keeps looking at her. Goodness.
- It's good.
- It's so good.
It's really good.
It's very soft.
It's like chocolate.
Eating something good is making you
speak in a dialect.
(Flustered)
- It's very...
- It's very funny.
"It's good."
Aren't you speaking with an accent
right now?
- Me?
- Yes.
With people from Gyeongsang Province,
I speak with an accent.
I'm wondering if you've influenced me.
- That's cute.
- I didn't speak with an accent.
I can speak with an accent.
No, don't do it.
Why don't we...
- No?
- Don't do it.
Why don't they?
- Show us how cute you are.
- Show us.
Later,
why don't we do it at home...
for about ten minutes?
- He's making a promise.
- Speaking in an accent.
No way.
You'd be very different.
When I came to Seoul for the first time,
I was shocked.
- Because people are so friendly? Me too.
- Yes.
You know what I mean?
People speak so gently.
In the beginning, when people called me
with the Seoul accent,
I almost fell in love with them.
Wasn't that how you felt?
- People seem so friendly.
- Exactly.
They're on the same wavelength now.
It's delicious.
- Which one? Was chocolate the best?
- Yes.
I'm on a sugar high right now.
You know what I mean? A sugar high.
You seem more energetic.
It's because I had sugar.
She became very positive.
She looks hyper.
- I think...
- You became completely different.
I needed some sugar.
(Giggling)
We didn't eat anything sweet...
at home.
- Is that right?
- Don't you think?
For a month,
whenever I see chocolate,
I'll buy some for you.
Thank you.
- Goodness.
- He can't hide it.
(Naturally, they made a promise.)
What if you don't?
(Laughing)
We should take a photo of this.
(A photo by Ji Min, A photo by Je Yeon)
- You aren't cold, right?
- I'm not cold.
The warmer feels nice.
My back is warm.
(Surprised)
It's very...
(They notice caricatures on the street.)
- Hello.
- They're caricatures.
(They stop naturally.)
Shall we try it?
Don't we need to pay him in cash?
- Together. Yes.
- Together?
In his drawings,
the characters stand out...
when you look at the mouth.
They look funny.
Comical?
Yes, comical.
No, I mean...
Not comical.
A normal picture. Yes.
(Okay.)
It's making me nervous.
He's drawing without hesitation.
(Try to smile.)
(Smiling)
He's drawing the body too.
He draws well in detail.
Someone is busking.
(They hear music from somewhere.)
You must have thick eyelashes.
- Aren't you cold?
- No, I'm not.
- They look great together.
- I agree.
(The music is...)
(followed by bubbles.)
(Glancing)
(Smiling)
- Why are you laughing?
- It's nothing.
Why are you laughing? Tell me.
(They're laughing for no reason.)
- There's a good vibe between them.
- Yes.
(Feeling shy)
They're so nice.
(Fidgeting)
Are you good at drawing?
What was your drawing?
(Startled)
Was it a tree?
Was your drawing in the book a tree?
Was there a tree?
(He wants to know anything he can.)
(Watching carefully)
I look...
(The front teeth are protruding.)
- Did you see it?
- That's a funny drawing.
I haven't seen it yet.
Does it look funny?
(Laughing)
Do you know an animated series...
called "Attack on Titan?"
It looks like
one of the characters from it.
Is it a titan?
Yes.
(She notices the drawing.)
When he drew up to the eyes,
- I felt good.
- It looked good.
- But the mouth...
- The mouth...
- The teeth shouldn't be showing.
- You shouldn't have smiled.
I won't smile.
(Tight lips)
He closed his mouth.
No smile.
Smile.
- No smile.
- No?
No.
Are you only going to save yourself?
- Okay, I'll smile.
- Smile.
(Please draw me with a smile.)
(How will it look?)
(The front teeth couple's
drawing is ready.)
(Bursting out laughing)
Is that really me?
(The drawing shows both of their smiles.)
(Bravo.)
(The unexpected cuteness
made it a satisfying date.)
How much is it?
(Their memory in Florence
is colored like the sunset.)
I'll pay for it.
Would you like to take a photo
with the drawing?
(Their memory in Florence
is colored like the sunset.)
- That's memorable.
- They'll remember the drawing forever.
They'll remember it forever.
(Tonight,
you'll have dinner together in Florence.)
(Before dinner,)
(find a souvenir gift from Italy.)
Again...
(Thinking)
(The residents have to buy
a souvenir gift from Italy.)
What should I get as a gift?
I can't decide.
You should decide who it's for first,
and then think about the gift.
- A gift that'll suit them?
- Exactly.
We're currently here. It's a bit...
- There's a market over here.
- How about this route?
- Let's go up that road.
- Over there?
(Woo Jae chooses a gift alone.)
(Attentive)
- How cute.
- You could put olive oil in here.
(Everyone chooses a gift of their own.)
It has the vibes...
- of Florence.
- Yes. They're pretty.
I want to buy them all.
(He has chosen a heartfelt gift.)
One, two, three? Or only this?
I see. This one.
(Who will Woo Jae give the gift to?)
Shall we head to Piazzale Michelangelo?
- Okay.
- Good.
You don't take photos, do you?
How about one?
No, I'm good.
It'd be nice to take one
in Piazzale Michelangelo.
With the sun about to set...
- and all.
- I think I can take one.
Tell me one of the two.
When it's warm
and you're completely sober.
I like someone who's warmhearted.
Me too. But is that all?
I told you the other one
when everyone was there.
Someone with a bright smile.
Someone who smiles well.
He keeps smiling.
How cute.
(He keeps thinking about the ideal type.)
It's sort of...
I can kind of get the type you prefer.
- Really?
- Yes.
You feel like an office worker.
- She's speaking casually.
- Why all of a sudden?
It's the feeling I get.
After listening to me talk?
Accounting? Tax?
Sorry?
A tax accountant?
- Me?
- Yes.
- Does it suit me?
- Kind of.
I did like math.
(What does Ji Min, who seems good
with numbers, do for a living?)
But I'm not in that industry.
(Seocho-gu, Seoul)
What's this?
(Ji Min is busy
from early in the morning.)
I come up with plans...
in the Strategy Development Team.
(His wristwatch)
He works for a big company.
Samsung Electronics.
I majored in electrical engineering
at Sungkyunkwan University.
I got a job at LG...
and worked for them for two years.
My first transfer was to Hanhwa.
I was lucky enough to get a call
from a headhunter...
and started working
for Samsung Electronics in May.
He's in a core department.
The Strategy Development Team.
(Ji Min is competent, getting a call
from Korea's best company.)
You're an accountant. Aren't you?
(Who knows?)
I was surprised just now.
My friend is an executive.
He graduated from the same university,
majored in the same department,
and is the executive of the same company.
- I have a feeling he knows Ji Min.
- Right.
- An alumnus.
- Exactly.
I'll ask him.
From what I know,
only elites are chosen...
for that company's
Strategy Development Team.
- Yes.
- Right?
- Ji Min must have a brilliant mind...
- I agree.
- and be acknowledged.
- Yes.
We've got some competent people
with us today.
- As it's Heart Pairing,
- Exactly.
everyone has a splendid job.
All the participants are on the show
to get married.
Did you not guess
what other people's jobs might be?
Really? What did you think mine was?
I thought you must be a rookie
in an office.
I bet you grew up getting hurt a lot.
But I think you bottled it up inside
without expressing it.
(How funny.)
You looked quite softhearted.
(What does Je Yeon,
who looks softhearted, do?)
(Tapping)
(Seoul Central District Court)
Don't tell me...
Hi. My name is Lee Je Yeon.
I was born in 1995 and am an attorney.
(Je Yeon has been an attorney
for 5 years.)
An attorney?
(An attorney?)
(Behind her quiet personality...)
(is cool-headed rationality.)
(She passed the 10th bar exam in 2021.)
- Really?
- That's cool.
When it comes to companies,
there's this neatness.
Things just sit right in place.
It's fun.
Being able to figure out...
what the legal issue is right now.
I've dealt with fields
other than industries,
like real estate, inheritance, and more.
I knew I couldn't only do...
what I wanted to
once I opened my own office.
The accessibility to the court.
It has to be close enough
for me to dash out...
while getting ready.
(A legal expert ready to rush out)
(Charismatic)
Upon hearing that she's an attorney...
- Now that we know she's an attorney,
- We feel small.
my thoughts are becoming one-sided.
Je Yeon seems more rational.
(I totally get it.)
- I kind of understand.
- Right?
- There's a prejudice with occupations.
- But listen, Jong Shin.
Such prejudices...
All of a sudden, I can't help but think
she's more rational than emotional.
I never imagined her to be an attorney.
An attorney.
Did you think about her job?
Did an attorney cross your mind?
No.
People assume
attorneys are good at talking.
After watching Episodes 1 and 2,
I was worried she wouldn't speak up.
(Same here.)
She graduated from Yonsei University
with honors.
- Oh, my gosh.
- With honors?
- Law school.
- And she went to law school.
I doubt Ji Min can ever guess
she's an attorney.
- Ji Min is in great trouble.
- Seriously. True.
Ji Min will fall deeper in love
with Je Yeon...
after he figures out her job.
Three things he looks for
in a partner are...
sincerity, trust, and a strong mentality.
Aren't those the three qualifications
of an attorney?
(Totally.)
- Ji Min is in trouble.
- There was a reason...
he was attracted to her.
- Yes.
- A reason behind it.
Je Yeon could look after
Samsung Electronics.
(Laughing)
My lips are chapped.
Mine are too.
- Apply some of this.
- Thank you.
(Tapping)
- Do you already like it?
- It's already so pretty.
- It's pretty?
- Yes.
- It's gorgeous.
- The sky...
What? It's so pretty.
Look at the sunset.
(The colors of the sunset
have covered the sky.)
Seriously.
How nice.
That tree is pretty too.
It's gorgeous.
Everyone is standing over there.
(People are gathered at the big tree.)
You really won't take a photo?
I'll take one for you.
You want to take one now, right?
(Busted)
That's adorable.
- I'm right, aren't I?
- No.
It's nice to leave memories together.
True.
That's what I meant.
(An impressive and unforgettable moment)
How pretty.
- The sunset is more intense.
- Now...
The more beautiful it becomes
as time goes by.
The sunset is amazing.
I like pastel colors.
- Same here.
- Really?
- There's a pastel color.
- Over there?
- It looks so picturesque.
- Right.
It's so beautiful.
I guess someone'sbuskinghere.
Everyoneis sittingon the steps.
- I see. On the steps here?
- Yes.
(Skillful)
Did you take a pictureof the sunset?
I'm aboutto.
(Glancing)
(Clicking)
But the sunsetis that way.
(Embarrassed)
- He finds her cute.
- She's cute.
I wanted to take a picture
of the city too.
- Okay.
- Yes.
There's somethingabout him.
He can make her laugh.
(Tryingagain)
You're so funny.
- It's so beautiful. Seriously.
- Yes.
There are so many differentshades
of colors.
- Right. They're shades of pastel colors.
- Yes.
I think that's importantin relationships.
- It wasn't that funny.
- Right.
That's true.
(Turning)
The lights are on.
(Surprised)
It's so beautiful.How picturesque.
Truly.What a stunningview.
(The hour when Florenceis tinged
with an eveningglow)
- This is amazing.
- It looks beautifulover there too.
(They are mesmerized
by the night view of Florence.)
It's beautiful.
- This view here looks pretty too.
- Yes, it does.
You know what? This does look like...
- Right?
- a wallpaperon cell phones.
We only see the moon and a star.
- You're so right.
- Right?
I shouldtake a pictureof that.
(Clicking)
(Somethingelse grabs their attention.)
(The melodyof the guitarin Florence)
(Staring)
(The two of them becomequiet.)
(Glancing)
Are you satisfied?
(Totally.)
(They listen to the music for a moment.)
(What is...)
(on their mind now?)
(Glancing)
(Focused)
- Are you enjoyingthe music now?
- Yes.
- It's completelynight now.
The lights are shiningbrightlynow.
(The beautifulnightview,)
(accompaniedby the melodyof the guitar)
(Romance deepens amid the bright lights.)
(Captivated)
I stillcan't believethis.
Why am I in Italyagain?
I don't even know if I'm indeed
enjoying the view of Florence.
I see.
- Do you want me to take a picture of you?
- Why do I feel so shy?
But you stillwant to take a picture.
(Shy)
- So...
- I think you can stand there.
ShouldI take it like this?
Or shouldI not cover my face?
- Don't cover your face.
- Don't cover it?
- Could you take it from there?
- From there? The sunset?
It's cold.
(Ji Min shylyposes for the camera.)
You don't have to make me look tall.
Is that so? Okay.
(Chuckling)
(Enthusiastic)
But there are a lot of people
in the picture.
You can come closer to take it.
You can includethat in the picture.
That's not how you take it.
- What? What's goingon?
- What?
- Did you come here alone?
- Yes.
What?
(Woo Jae shows up out of the blue.)
(Teasing)
- Did you come here alone?
- Yes.
- Really?
- After buyingthe present.
- Were you here...
- Can you take the picturethen?
- the whole time?
- ShouldI take a pictureof you two?
- Oh, no. How could this happen?
- No. Of him.
- Yes, take a pictureof us too.
I'm not a good photographer.
(Exudingthe vibe of an expert)
Wait. That shouldbe in the picture.
Actually,I'm not that good either.
(Sighing)
- Ji Min must have mixedfeelings.
- I'm not good either.
But you just told me...
- I wasn't doinga good job.
- I was joking.
- You were joking?
- Here. Take it.
- No.
- Wait.
We shouldtake it here.
Look at Ji Min's facial expression.
- I don't think this is good.
- It's taking too long.
Let me zoom in a bit.
Is it too much?
(There's some awkwardtension
betweenJi Min and Woo Jae.)
I'll just take a lot of them.
No. I think that's good.
You took a lot of pictures.
- You reallydon't want to take one?
- Pardon?
- Let me take one for you.
- I won't.
- Why not?
- I'm shy.
Do you want me to take a pictureof you?
I'm good.
What did you do by yourself?
I walked around.
I boughtpresents.
- You boughtpresents?
- You did?
- I did.
- What did you buy?
- I didn't buy it yet.
- I just boughtsimple things.
What did you do?
We...
- We had coffee.
- You had coffee.
- We also had desserts.
We walked.
- What did we do next?
- The caricature.
We got the caricature done.
- Really?
- Yes.
(Smiling)
(Nodding)
- Where are you going next?
- Us?
We were goingto enjoythe view
and then go for dinner.
Right, we have to buy presents.
- You'll go and buy presents?
- Yes, we will.
It's 5 p.m.
It's... So we must be
at the restaurant by 7 p.m.
Right.
- What time is it?
- It's 5 p.m.
Two hours?
(Thinking)
Could you take a pictureof Ji Min?
- I...
- You mightnot like the picturesI took.
No. It's reallyokay.
- I'm awfulat takingpictures.
- I...
It doesn't matter...
- as long as you capturedthis.
- Really?
That's all I need.
(Checking)
(Staring)
- Okay.
Shouldwe leave around 5:30 p.m.?
To buy presents?
To buy presents?Okay.
(Glancing)
- Oh, my.
- Have fun.
What shouldI buy? Where will you go?
Where will you go?
I don't have a plan.
I thoughtabout gettingcoffee.
Where?
- Oh, no.
- Is that a cafe?
- We...
- Yes?
(Pondering)
Then we'll leave a littleearlier...
- and buy presents.
- Okay.
Do you want to join us later?
So we can head to the restauranttogether?
- Before the restaurant?
- Yes.
Sounds good.
- Then...
- We'll be around...
and quickly buy presents.
- Ji Min won't ask him to tag along.
- Okay.
Sounds good.
Then I'll see you guys
when you finishshopping.
(Let's do that.)
(Gazing)
Well, let me know once you're done.
- I'll have coffeein the meantime.
- Sure.
Sounds good.
- See you later.
Hey, check out the nightview.
(Woo Jae is alone again.)
Will he feel a bit lonely
if he goes to the cafe alone?
Oh, my.
I think Je Yeon sort of
wanted him to join them.
- Actually,Woo Jae was...
- Yes?
being consideratetoday.
He was considerate?
So...
Chan Hyeong alwayswent out
in a group of three.
- I see.
- It was alwaysthe three of them.
So they probablydidn'thave time
to talk to people 1-on-1.
He thoughtthat it was fair...
for Chan Hyeong
to have a 1-on-1 date today.
He didn'tmind sittingthis one out,
so he yieldedtoday.
He was beingconsiderate.
Right.
I was gratefuland felt bad
at the same time.
That's it. I thoughtyou shouldknow.
(She learns about
Woo Jae's thoughtfulaction only now.)
(He's back to walkingaround the city.)
(And he spends time alone.)
- It's so beautiful.
- Totally.
Shall we go?
- Are you done?
- Pardon?
- We can spend more time here.
- Shall we then?
Until 5:30 p.m.?
- You're really enjoying this.
- What?
- You must reallylike this place.
- I reallylike it.
Or we can enjoy the view on the steps.
Sounds good.
- But...
- Yes?
- you're wearinga skirt.
- Then... I see.
Right?
- Let me try it, though.
- What?
I'll try it.
If I don't think I can, I'll get up.
- I'll cover you when you sit down.
- Yes.
- Thank you.
- It's clean here.
Here?
Aren't you cold?
It's nice with this on my legs.
(Clicking)
(Leaningin)
(Surprised)
The song is over.
I missed the timing.Let me try again.
(As the night deepens,)
(they get closer.)
(Focused)
- Aren't you cold? Are you okay?
- I'm okay.
(Coveringhis face)
He keepsstaringat her.
He's lookingat her again.
(Immersed)
(They focus on listeningto the music,
forgettingabout the cold weather.)
(For some reason,
warmth embraces their body and heart.)
(Can you see couples that are pairedup?)
(Mission 3: Guess the results
of tonight's pairingnow.)
We'll be playingindividuallytoday.
- They will send messagesto each other.
- My gosh.
We must guess
how many couples are paired up.
Our guessing results will be important,
startingthis episode.
Starting today, the person...
who wins first place
of correctly guessingthe pairings...
until the last episode...
will get a chance to stay...
in the PairingHouse in Tuscany for
2 nights, which is worth 8,000 dollars.
- Among us?
- Wait.
- Amongus.
- Among us?
- First place amongus?
The winnercan stay in the house
for two nights.
- Really?
- My gosh.
- Is it the same house? Okay.
- Yes.
Can I also do pull-ups?
- Yes, you can.
- I see.
- I can do pull-ups there? Okay.
- Yes.
- So you have to buy a plane ticket...
- I'll take this seriously.
- to stay there for two nights.
- Okay.
That will probablycost more.
They won't cover the plane tickets?
- That will probablycost more.
- We must stillgo.
- I reallywant to win the voucher.
- I see.
- Then...
- It's equivalentto 8,000 dollars.
All right. Let's go around the room
and present our guesses.
Shouldwe start with the couple...
- we're certain about?
- Yes.
I chose Chang Hwan and Ji Won.
- Same here.
Toward the end of their date,
there was so much warmth on their faces.
- I can't forgetthat.
- Right.
That made me feel happyto watch.
Good, Ji Won.
All of us chose Chang Hwan and Ji Won.
- It's unanimous.
- So we got one couple.
- Yes.
- And this couple is our insurance.
- Chan Hyeong and Ha Neul.
I think they will pick each other too.
- Yes.
Chan Hyeong and Ha Neul.
Does everyoneagree?
- Yes.
It's unanimous.
What about Ji Min and Je Yeon?
Let's talk about them.
Gosh, I'm not sure.
Ji Min will choose Je Yeon, right?
- Yes.
- I agree.
I think Je Yeon will choose Ji Min too.
- Je Yeon too?
- Yes.
- Here's what I think.
- Yes?
They come back to the house and send
the message as they reflecton their day.
We saw three couples go on a date today.
I think they had the biggest
romanticchemistryamong all the dates.
That's true.
Je Yeon kept on smiling.
- The date went betterthan expected.
- Yes.
It was a satisfyingday for Je Yeon?
I think it was much better
than she expected.
(Je Yeon might send the messageto Ji Min
after enjoyingher day with him.)
- And...
- If they enjoythe date, do they...
- usuallysend messagesto each other?
- Yes.
Yes, I think so.
I'm not reallysure.
- Hold on, Chung Ah.
- Yes?
- Are you up for taking a risk?
- How?
Did you want to go
with Woo Jae and Je Yeon?
- Sort of.
- Same here.
- We now have a prize. Think carefully.
- Woo Jae...
- This is how people are.
- Right.
- You know, moneycan be a scarything.
- Yes.
You think Woo Jae and Je Yeon
will choose each other?
Yes. I get the feelingthat they will.
To be honest,I was certain...
that Woo Jae and Je Yeon
would be a fixed pairing.
But now, I'm not so sure.
Here's how Je Yeon could have taken it.
She could have been disappointed.
If Je Yeon had to ask the guys,
she would have asked Woo Jae out.
- But Woo Jae didn't do that.
- Right.
That could influenceher decision.
- Ji Min.
- I think she'll send it to Ji Min.
- When you go down the list,
- Yes. You're right.
- you end up with one person.
- Yes.
- We all paired three couples.
So our guess is three couples.
Now, let's think about Woo Jae
and guess where his heart lies.
I think he will text Ji Won.
- What?
- I see.
When Ji Won walked in on the first day,
- Woo Jae looked at her differently.
- It was so different.
- Right.
- I'd never seen him make that face.
But he barelyinteractedwith Ji Won.
No,
he could'vechosen her out of curiosity.
I think Woo Jae will send the message
to Je Yeon.
- I see. Woo Jae and Je Yeon.
- Here's why.
He mentionedthat he wanted...
to go to this squarewith her
in the 1st 2 episodes.
He must have gone there today
for a reason.
I agree.
- That's what I think.
- He was checkingit out in advance.
Ji Seon, you also chose...
- Je Yeon for Woo Jae's message.
- Yes.
- I think he will text Je Yeon.
- Je Yeon?
- She's his spokesperson.
- Woo Jae and Je Yeon.
If I'm the only one who gets this right,
I'll win the prize alone.
(Winning the accommodationvoucher)
That's crazy.
I'll sleep in all of those rooms.
That'll be amazing.
You can do that with wine.
Wait, his messagewon't play a role?
(It's importantto guess the pairings.)
- The numberof couples...
- I see.
I was gettingaheadof myself.
Then...
- All of our guessesare the same.
- Yes.
- I see. All right.
Let's check the results now.
We'll start with Chan Hyeong's decision.
(Will he choose Ha Neul
just like he did on the first day?)
(Who has he chosen?)
(Heart Pairing Love Line)
(Chan Hyeong chose Ha Neul.)
- It's Ha Neul. That's right.
- Chan Hyeong chose Ha Neul.
That's how it should go.
Let's check Ha Neul's decisionnext.
- Please.
- Who did she pick?
(Hoping)
(It's Day 3 in Italy. Are Chan Hyeong
and Ha Neul already going steady?)
(Ha Neul chose Chan Hyeong.)
- All right. That's one.
- It was Chan Hyeong.
Right.
Who did Chang Hwan choose?
(His date with Ji Won was like a scene
from his favoritemovie.)
(Did he meet someonekind today?)
It has to be Ji Won.
Wait. No way.
(Chang Hwan chose Ji Won.)
- There you go.
- That's it.
(She was indeedkind.)
- Great.
- Okay.
- Okay. Let's check Ji Won's decision.
- Great.
Who did Ji Won choose?
(Was it Chang Hwan
whom she had a lot in common with?)
- They can get marriedright now.
- Right.
- They were so compatible.
- Exactly.
(Heart Pairing Love Line)
(Ji Won chose Chang Hwan.)
(Chang Hwan and Ji Won's first pairing)
- Aren't they the most certain?
- Yes.
- Ji Min's consistent.
- Who did Ji Min choose?
(Who did the consistent Ji Min choose?)
(Heart pounding)
(He'd been waiting
for a 1-on-1 date with her.)
(Did Ji Min obviously choose his date,
Je Yeon?)
(Heart Pairing Love Line)
(Ji Min chose Je Yeon.)
- Yes.
- I knew it.
- Now, it's getting difficult. The last.
- Yes.
- Please.
- Shall we check Woo Jae first?
I was the only one with a different guess.
Let's see who's right.
Who did Woo Jae choose?
Oh, no.
(Who did Woo Jae,
who did not ask anyone out, choose?)
(Curious)
(Between Ji Won whom he chose
for the first impression...)
(and Je Yeon whom he went
on his first date with)
- Did he really choose Je Yeon?
- Je Yeon.
(Heart Pairing Love Line)
(Woo Jae chose Je Yeon.)
(Only Jong Shin was wrong.)
- I knew it.
- I was right.
- He didn't want to lose her.
- I'm excited.
That was unexpected.
He's manly.
If he was going to choose her,
he should've asked her out on a date.
Exactly.
Now, it's the last person.
I can't wait to check Je Yeon's choice.
- Please.
- Until yesterday,
- Woo Jae.
- she liked Woo Jae.
- Oh, my gosh.
- If it's wrong, we all fail.
If it's right, we all pass.
Lastly, who did Je Yeon choose?
Please.
(Ji Min whom she had a good time with
on a date?)
(Woo Jae who expressed her heart
until yesterday?)
I'm suddenly getting anxious.
Still, be nice.
(Heart Pairing Love Line)
(Je Yeon chose Ji Min.)
(Everyone succeeded in guessing.)
She changed her mind!
I took your advice.
We succeeded in guessing today.
(Everyone passed.)
I almost got Woo Jae wrong,
but that wasn't in the rules.
(The person of the Pairing House
becomes a mystery again.)
(Chan Hyeong, Ha Neul)
(Chang Hwan, Ji Won)
(Ji Min, Je Yeon)
(A date with the person they dreamed of)
(What kind of change did it bring?)
(A 1-on-1 conversation for the 1st time)
I realized he was...
more amazing than I expected.
Am I the only one who knows
that you were home-schooled?
- No one else knows.
- I just wanted her to know.
It felt different.
We now have a secret...
that no one else knows.
It felt special.
(I was very happy to talk to you today.
Were you?)
(I want to know more about you.
I had a good time today.)
I tend to...
get excited...
when people compliment me.
Everything we're having today tastes good.
(Getting up)
She makes enthusiastic reactions.
She was like, "I love it."
She was cute.
(It was cold, but it wasn't cold.)
That kind of amazed me.
Chang Hwan...
exercised properly outside.
I never expected someone
to exercise in Italy.
When he talks,
he smiles like a fool sometimes.
He wasn't stubborn or strong...
like I expected.
(The man who made her laugh unexpectedly)
It felt therapeutic.
(I look forward to having a good time
in Italy.)
Florence Republic Square I mentioned.
(He wanted to share his memories
from 10 years ago with Je Yeon.)
That also meant that
I wanted to go with Je Yeon.
(Ji Min's wish...)
(came true today.)
It meant a lot.
It was her first time traveling in Europe.
It's beautiful.
She enjoyed it...
from the bottom of her heart.
She reminded me of me ten years ago.
She seems very pure.
She looked beautiful.
(Take a warm shower and rest
so you won't catch a cold.)
He said he'd match my speed.
I will try to adjust to your speed.
What speed are you talking about?
A turtle?
Is he saying I'm that slow?
(He'd keep up with her slow speed.)
- It seemed...
- Are you cold?
his emotions or thoughts
would be his highest priority.
He wasn't how he appeared to be.
We can spend more time here.
Until 5:30 p.m.?
It must've been very cold,
yet he waited for me
while I watched the night view.
He cared a lot about me.
He was being considerate.
(Another person at the square)
- I'll have coffeein the meantime.
- I felt bad about him.
- See you later.
(How did Woo Jae feel today?)
The possibility...
(Glancing)
(I enjoyed visiting the square
and the night view.)
(It was nice talking to you. Good night.)
After I chose her,
I kept thinking that maybe,
I shouldn't have done that.
(Despite his regrets)
It's not that I'm not at ease.
That's just who I am.
I choose Je Yeon.
I thought about...
having that time because...
it was nice to be alone
than with three people.
Of course, it was a bummer.
(On the previous date,)
(they had to wait for the next chance.)
"This is the last time I do this."
It was a decision I could make
because it was my first time.
(I hope you had a good day today.
Good night.)
(How will this change
affect their hearts?)
(The residents gathered
in a restaurant after the date.)
We should get some wine.
Even just a small bottle.
- We should.
- What?
They're late.
(Bugged)
(And...)
(a mysterious empty seat)
We'll have to watch the look
on men's faces.
Yes.
Hello.
- Hello.
- What did you order? I don't know what...
- Excuse me.
- Can you recommend her wine?
- Yes.
- Do you see what's written on the top?
Take your time.
I was kind of nervous.
This is our first and last time.
I was excited to see who was coming.
I wanted to meet you today.
I'm curious about you the most.
I want to hear your story.
We'll know after a few more dates.
Do you have any regrets?
I have a lot on my mind.
How you felt until now.
Can I say it?
Dramaday.me