[Goodbye My Princess]
[Episode 8]
Are you awake?
Gu Xiaowu?
Serves you right for running away without me.
Sorry. I shouldn't have ditched you in the town of Gongyue.
Xiaowu, I'm so happy to see you.
Xiaowu, we need to get out of here now.
- To where?
- To get back up.
To get back up?
You said Khan Tömür's tent is at least 150 kilometers away.
It's too far away to help. The Protectorate General Office is closer. Why don't you ask them for help?
You don't understand. The different states in the Western Border all adhere to the same taboo.
The Central Plains emperor does not get involved in the fights amongst ourselves.
All under the sky is the territory of the emperor and all men are his subjects. Everything that takes place here concerns the emperor.
Besides, the Protectorate General Office was established to ensure peace and stability in the region.
It's time to teach those disrespectful Shuobo a lesson!
Twenty-five kilometers toward the south is a border base camp.
Colonel Pei of the Protectorate General Office of the Western Border has been patrolling in the borders lately. We are friends. Let's go there to ask for reinforcements first.
I hear you. It's more important to save Heshi.
Sir, why aren't you going with them?
Not anybody can enter Khan Tömür's tent.
Fifth Prince must gain Xiaofeng's trust to know where the tent is.
I'm going to Colonel Pei's camp for a while. You tell my godfather that we've found the person.
- Take care, Young Master.
- Okay.
Xiaowu, where is this base camp?
We've walked for so long, but I haven't even seen a shadow of it.
We should be there soon. Keep on walking.
- I'm really hot.
- I'm hot, too.
I'm thirsty.
I'm thirsty, too.
Can we ride the horse?
No, it's more tired than you.
- Xiaowu, I...
- Don't talk.
Save some of your strength.
I, Gu Jian, greets Colonel Pei.
Brother Gu.
Brother Gu, aren't you supposed to be with Fifth Prince.
On the way to finding the camp of the Danchi's khan, we were attacked by Shuobo soldiers.
Danchi's Khan Tömür's troops led by Heshi to welcome Ninth Princess
are still fighting Shuobo's soldiers right now. Fifth Prince and Ninth Princess should be en route to the borders to seek help.
I hope Colonel Pei will lend a hand to help Heshi.
It's my duty to maintain peace among the kingdoms in the Western Border.
Also, when you meet Ninth Princess, please do not reveal Fifth Prince's true identity.
All right.
But does Fifth Prince know that the border camp has been moved here?
He doesn't. I only found out from my godfather how to reach you here.
Because of the rainy season, sands are soaked with water and the quicksands have expanded.
I have just recently moved the camp here. So I'm afraid that Fifth Prince won't be able to find us.
Quicksands?
Water is here, Xiaofeng!
Awesome!
Hurry up!
Xiaowu, don't move! It's quicksand!
Catch this, Xiaowu!
Hold on tight, Xiaowu!
Little red horse, move backward!
Xiaowu, hold it!
Xiaowu, hold tight!
Little red horse, pull hard!
Xiaofeng!
Xiaofeng, let go!
Don't let me drag you down!
I won't let go! We came together, so we must leave together!
Let go!
Xiaowu, hold on tight!
Xiaowu, hold tight!
Don't let go!
Xiaofeng!
No!
I'm sorry.
Xiaowu!
Xiaowu! Xiaowu!
Don't let go!
Hold on tight!
You are not allowed to let go!
Hold on!
I am Xi State's ninth princess.
My father is the king of Xi State.
My mother is the daughter of the khan of Danchi.
My grandfather is the fiercest Khan Tömür of Danchi.
Xiaofeng, sorry.
I've been using you right from the beginning.
No, hold on to it!
You are not allowed to leave me!
We are still going to look for reinforcements!
I can't swim!
I found it.
Gu Xiaowu!
Hold on to it!
Gu Xiaowu, you dummy!
Xiaofeng, you must live well.
You can't leave me alone!
Hold on to it!
Xiaowu!
Are you all right?
Xiaowu, wake up!
Xiaowu.
Xiaofeng, this place is too dangerous. Let's go to base camp.
Xiaowu, come.
Slowly.
- Let's go!
- Slowly.
Your Imperial Majesty! Prince Xuande has already handed Batuer,
the Danchi assassin who murdered the crown prince, to us.
This is Batuer's confession letter. General Gao Xian has investigated this matter himself.
Will Your Imperial Majesty please take a look?
[Cao Ji, Head Eunuch of the Li Empire]
Was all the content of this confession letter
found to be true?
Very much, Your Imperial Majesty!
Anything missing?
None.
Where is that criminal Batuer?
This humble servant has handed him to the Ministry of Justice
and is now just waiting for your judgment.
- Stand up!
- Thank you, Your Imperial Majesty!
Your Imperial Majesty, in my view, Tömür ordered the assassination of the crown prince
to hinder the marriage bond between the Central Plains and Xi State. This proves that he has fervent ambition.
He might've already had the idea of taking over Central Plains.
Should this troubling Danchi issue persist,
there will not be a safe day around our borders. Your humble servant boldly
asks Your Imperial Majesty to please send troops to annihilate Danchi,
so as to relieve the anxiety at the borders.
And to avenge the murder of the crown prince.
This matter is of great importance and does not allow for any mistakes.
Continuing to wage wars will render the people furious.
I think we should try fair means before resorting to force.
Send envoys to negotiate with Danchi first.
Then make the final decision after getting the truth. That would be the best solution.
Absurd! All the evidence is solid, what more is there to negotiate?
Our Li Empire is evidently a large nation.
Why would we be afraid of a tiny tribal state like Danchi?
Khan Tömür sent an assassin to murder the crown prince.
Obviously, he looks down on us.
If we could even tolerate the murder of our crown prince,
please tell me where the dignity of the Li Empire is?
If we can't justify doing this,
then what other good reason is there for waging a war?
Young Lord Wu.
Colonel Pei, how have you been doing?
Right, this person is—
I am Danchi General Heshi's little sister, A'Du.
My brother is now surrounded by the Shuobo Army below Sky Span Mountain.
I earnestly ask Colonel Pei to send your men to assist my brother.
I ask Colonel Pei to send your men to assist General Heshi.
If that's the case, I will tell my men to immediately prepare.
We will proceed in two hours.
Thank you very much, Colonel Pei!
Thank you for your work!
You are all welcome! I am just doing my job.
I will go get ready now.
Oh right, Xiaowu. Why were you apologizing to me earlier?
I was just...
I was just worried that the most beautiful ninth princess in this world,
would jump into the sand and die because of saving the life of a tea businessman from Central Plains.
Had that happened, your father and grandfather would surely go after me.
You just love mocking me.
We will be setting out soon. Let me treat your wound first and let Xiaowu rest.
Your Imperial Majesty, based on reports, Tömür has governed Danchi for more than ten years.
He is open and aboveboard, deeply loved by his citizens.
It might be possible that he doesn't know about the assassination of the crown prince.
The war affects citizens. Once we start the war, It will not only deplete our resources and our men,
it will displace our citizens along the borders. In addition, the areas bordering Danchi are difficult to navigate.
Even if we have a massive army, the long-distance travel
will not make the war 100% to our favor.
You are overestimating our enemy or underestimating ourselves.
We have well trained soldiers, well stocked food, as well as the expertise of the Protectorate General Office located in the Western Border.
Not just Danchi, even the whole Western Border,
is ours to take.
Seeing how you are so protective of Tömür and reluctant to send troops,
do you possibly have any secret ties with Danchi?
Are you preparing to rebel?
At the royal court, we argue political matters.
We see things how they are. Why do you need to wrongfully blame others?
This issue involves our country; moreover, it also involves the people.
May Your Imperial Majesty decide.
Transfer Batuer to the Court of Judicial Review.
I myself will interrogate him.
You have suffered a lot this time.
I am fine. All thanks to Xiaowu.
Teacher, you are right. Xiaowu is really nice.
I will never lie to you.
After this, I have come to understand many things.
I think that the feeling between men is sometimes like quicksand.
The more you struggle, the more you can't escape.
Before, I kept pestering you for warmth and support.
Maybe for you, I am the quicksand that bounds you down.
Do you feel that these words shouldn't be coming out from my mouth?
Do you think that I have grown up?
I still like you a lot, but you don't have to feel burdened by it.
This feeling is like your liking for me.
You are forever my best teacher.
I will take my leave.
Fifth Prince.
Ah Zhao.
Fifth Prince, please have a seat.
Ah Zhao, I am now a normal tea businessman, not a prince.
Unbelievable. When the meticulous Colonel Pei starts acting,
there is not even room for a flaw.
Stop teasing me.
Right. How's the investigation on my brother's assassination?
Not long ago, I seized a Danchi assassin called Batuer.
He has confessed to Prince Xuande and confirmed that assassinating the crown prince
was an act from the Danchi people.
So it was really them.
I will make them pay a hundred and a thousand times back.
If the culprit has confessed,
why would His Imperial Majesty still want to personally interrogate?
Could he be doubtful of this case?
And that he suspects the assassin's real identity?
Actually, it does not make a difference if the assassin is real or not.
Uncle, what do you mean?
What is important is
whether His Imperial Majesty wants to clash with Danchi or not.
If not, then the assassin is fake.
If otherwise, the assassin is real.
In your opinion,
does His Imperial Majesty want to start a war or not start a war?
Have you arranged that assassin properly?
I have.
It's not easy to deceive the emperor.
Do not allow a single mistake!
Father, please set your heart at rest.
This man is Prince Xuande's suicide fighter. He is loyal until the end.
Heshi!
You better be all right.
Reporting!
General, we found the Shuobo Army around ten kilometers from here.
Lead the left flank to go around their back. Wait for my command.
Yes. Left flank, follow me!
Let's go!
Heshi, I respect that you're Danchi's number one warrior.
If you surrender, I might even spare your life.
If you want to fight, we'll fight. The people of Danchi
would rather die than surrender. Come on!
Okay, then don't blame me for not giving you a chance.
Brothers, don't let one person live! Kill!
Who are you?
General Pei Zhao of the Western Border Protectorate General Office.
Danchi General Heshi's sister came to my camp for help.
She said that you guys kidnapped General Heshi.
It's my responsibility to mediate and stop this.
So it's Colonel Pei.
This is a matter between Shuobo and Danchi.
It doesn't involve the Li Empire.
So, I suggest that Colonel Pei
- shouldn't get involved.
- All this land belongs to the emperor,
so everyone on this land is a citizen of his.
Sky Span Mountain is an area under the Protectorate General Office's control.
How can you say that this doesn't involve the Li Empire?
It's the responsibility of the Protectorate General Office to preserve peace among the kingdoms in the Western Border.
You disobeyed the law and recklessly killed people.
Are you declaring war on the Li Empire?
Colonel Pei, you're mistaken.
Shuobo has never had any contact with your Li Empire.
And today, I don't want to escalate this matter.
Or else, the harmonious relationship between us might be affected.
How about this? I'll give you respect today.
Let them go!
Let's go!
- Heshi!
- Little Princess!
Heshi!
You scared me.
I thought I would never see you again.
Little Princess, don't forget.
I am Danchi's number one hero.
How could I get injured?
As long as you're all right, then everything is fine.
Little Princess, why did you bring the Central Plains' army here?
I was scared that I couldn't find grandfather,
so I went to the Western Border Protectorate General Office to ask Colonel Pei for help.
I told them I was A'Du.
I'm Colonel Pei of the Du Cavalry.
Thank you, Colonel Pei.
It is my responsibility. You don't have to say thank you.
Heshi, this is my teacher Gu Jian.
Thanks to Brother Gu for taking care of my sister.
There's another person you have to thank.
Gu Xiaowu. He's my friend and my teacher's cousin.
Even though he's just a tea trader,
has okay looks,
and has a bad temperament,
he's really brave and smart.
He's the reason why I was able to find you.
This is the first time I've heard my sister compliment someone.
I want to thank everyone again for saving me.
General, no need to bow.
I don't think the Shuobo Army will quit that easily.
You and your fellow warriors have injuries.
Why don't we have General Pei escort you to Danchi's border?
Don't worry, Brother Gu.
I will surely ensure that everyone safely arrives home.
Not long ago, I seized a Danchi assassin
called Batuer. He has confessed to Prince Xuande
and confirmed that Danchi assassinated the crown prince.
General Pei!
General Pei, have you seen my teacher and Gu Xiaowu?
They must be tired from traveling so they went back to rest.
Oh right, General Pei, thank you for saving Heshi.
When I reach my grandfather's place in a few days, I'll have him thank you.
What reward do you want?
This is what I should be doing.
You actually know how to smile?
These couple of days together, you barely talked and only had one expression.
I thought your face was like the snow on Sky Span Mountain that never melts.
Your smile looks really good.
What kind of instrument is that?
This is a hichiriki from the Xi State. Does it sound good?
This makes me think of home.
If you like it, I'll teach you.
Wait for me.
Brother, give it to me.
Look it here.
You're a lady,
but you're so loose in front of men. Do you understand proper etiquette?
Everyone who grew up on the grasslands is like this.
Here, the sky and earth are given by Heaven.
We are all the sons and daughters of Heaven.
We aren't so particular like the ladies in the Central Plains.
That's it?
What are you doing?
There is a meteor star!
What's so special about it.
When you see the meteor, tie a knot on your clothes so that your wish will come true.
But I always forget to tie a knot or make a wish.
I'm always too late.
Sing me a song.
Why don't you sing? I want to hear you sing.
I don't know how.
Why would anybody not know how to sing?
Sing the song your mother taught when you were little.
I don't have a mother.
Then I'll sing you one.
♫ A fox sitting on top of the sand dune ♫
♫ Sitting on top of the sand dune, looking at the moon ♫
♫ But actually, it's not watching the moon ♫
♫ It's waiting for the shepherd girl to come back ♫
Enough already.
It's so bad. Can we change to another one?
I only know this one.
What is this song?
This is a famous Danchi war song.
It tells the story of a beautiful Danchi lady
whose lover went to war. He wasn't able to come back.
Only his horse came back.
So, she held onto the horse's leash,
looked at the arrows her lover didn't get to use,
and she sang this song.
"Pity their bones lying by the River Wuding,
while their wives still dream of them coming back by springtime."
This is a poem from the Central Plains. It has the same meaning as your song.
I heard from Consort Mingyuan
that many of your poems have stories inside them.
Tell me some?
- I forgot.
- Forgot?
But... I have another story. Do you want to hear it?
Long, long ago, there was the Zixu Kingdom.
In the Zixu Kingdom, there lived a small prince.
His mother...
passed away when he was young.
Te Zixu Kingdom's queen didn't have a child,
so she adopted the little prince.
She raised him and taught him.
The little prince treated the queen like his birth mother.
But he didn't know
that the one who killed his birth mother
was the queen.
When he grew up,
he found out the truth.
He decided to get justice for his mother.
Is that little prince planning to kill the queen?
The queen had too much power. The little prince wouldn't be able to put up a fight.
If he wanted to overthrow the queen, he had only one option.
What option?
He had to become the heir to the throne of the Zixu Kingdom.
The little prince disliked the fight for power the most.
Because in the Zixu Kingdom,
there were only a few heirs that could live past 30 years old.
Some were assassinated. Some were abolished by their father and imprisoned until death.
Some heirs
even tried to seize the opportunity and kill their father to claim the thrown.
The little prince's older brother once told him
that the Eastern Palace
was actually a blood-filled imperial palace.
Must the little prince be that way?
Can't he walk another path?
♫ The night has yet to fade ♫
♫ The cold moonlight shines on the window ♫
♫ Matters of the past life ♫
♫ are carefully being considered ♫
♫ A long dream ♫
♫ Yet always gathering and separating into uncertainty ♫
♫ Watery eyes are wishing for your return ♫
♫ Wounds have frosted in my heart ♫
♫ Can't forget your image in my mind ♫
♫ Looking back to our first meeting ♫
♫ That first moment when we saw each other ♫
♫ Can't hold onto the fingertips that you’ve extended ♫
♫ Parting shattered the heart ♫
♫ Useless tears for the person isn't coming back ♫
♫ The River of Oblivion ♫
♫ Silently gazes unto the troubles of the mundane world ♫
♫ Time reverses ♫f
♫ With a sip to forget love ♫
♫ If we meet for the first time again, who are we returning to ♫
♫ Parting shattered the heart ♫
♫ Useless tears for the person isn't coming back ♫
♫ The River of Oblivion ♫
♫ Silently gazes unto the troubles of the mundane world ♫
♫ Time reverses ♫
♫ With a sip to forget love ♫
♫ If we meet for the first time again, who are we returning to ♫
♫ Fall goes and spring comes again ♫
♫  Dream and awakening are just in cycle ♫