[Goodbye My Princess]
[Episode 19]
Mi Luo!
Mi Luo.
- I'm back.
- Xiaofeng, so you're back.
Look, A'Du has been here waiting for you for a long time.
I don't know who has provoked her.
She's so angry that she can't even breathe!
It's all right, A'Du.
Well...
How about, Mingyue, since you and everyone are here today,
I'll buy everyone a drink.
- That's right!
- Go. Let's go!
Go over there and help me bring out the dishes.
- Go help.
- I'll get you some delicious food to eat.
Mingyue, let's go!
Here, try this.
You all go ahead and eat. I'll have to go and greet the guests.
Wait. I have to go with you to get the cold dispelling wine. I may forget about it if I get drunk later on.
Let's go, A'Du.
Brother Gu Jian, I didn't think you were still alive.
Yan'er.
I'm now Mingyue of Singing Jade Brothel.
I'm not the Chen family's Yan'er anymore.
I don't deserve that name.
You should just call me Mingyue.
But how could you be at Singing Jade Brothel?
What are you talking about?
Hold it carefully.
Sister Mingyue, don't be sad.
In my opinion, those rich men are all disgusting.
What's so great about looking so arrogant and unstoppable.
Just because they like Sister Mingyue, must you then do what they want?
Does the Li Empire even have laws anymore?
You don't understand.
The Gao and Zhao families are top government officials.
Especially that Gao Zhen.
He is Shangjing City's infamous young ruffian.
No one dares to defy him.
I don't believe that. Is there no one who can control him?
Sister Mingyue, you keep being fought over by those people.
Have you never thought about leaving Singing Jade Brothel?
Xiaofeng is right.
Miss Mingyue, you indeed should leave this kind of place.
Leave?
Where would I even go?
Who is it?
Jian'er...
Where have you been these last few months?
I heard from Pei Zhao that someone snuck into the palace a few days ago.
Was it you?
Why didn't you come and find me when you got to Shangjing?
Are you still blaming me?
I saw Yan'er.
Yan'er?
She's still alive?
Where is she?
Singing Jade Brothel.
These past years, she has been residing in Singing Jade Brothel and became a courtesan.
It's my fault.
You didn't tell her that
I was still alive, right?
Good.
It's good that you didn't tell her.
Jian'er!
Where are you going?
I just came to tell you about Yan'er.
If you want to find me, come to Mi Luo Drinking House.
It's dangerous outside.
Why don't you move back in?
No thanks.
I have already obtained the badge that would allow me to enter the six ministries without a problem.
Where should we start investigating?
Ministry of Revenue.
Your Highness Prince Yi.
Ninth Princess?
What's wrong?
Last time, didn't you get sick because of me?
I especially used our Xi State's grape wine to make you a cold dispelling medicine.
Also, the aged ginger in here was boiled by me for six hours.
Try it!
Ninth Princess, my cold is all cured.
Thank you for worrying about me.
How could you recover so quickly?
Even if you're not sick, you can still drink it. It tastes really good!
I am telling you, this tastes way better than the white spirits from your Li Empire.
Plus, I snuck out of the palace just to get this. It's from a friend of mine. Here.
Friend?
Ninth Princess, you haven't been out of the palace in these last three months, have you?
Where did you make this friend?
Oh, right.
You don't have to care that much. But anyway, just drink a bit every day.
I guarantee you'll get completely cured in three to five days.
You hold it for him.
Shi'en.
I truly want to thank you.
You saved me twice. I want to be friends with you.
You really want to thank me?
How could that be false? Tell me. What do you want?
I guarantee that I can fulfill it.
Fine. I'll pretend that you truly want to thank me.
Regarding the gift of gratitude, I have not yet thought it through. Allow me some more time to think.
- Okay.
-  Ninth Princess!
- Ninth Princess!
- Oh, no.
Hurry up and hold it. Just tell me when you have thought of something.
I'm coming!
Your Highness.
Young Lord.
Young Lord Gu, we are closing.
Young Lord Gu!
Young Lord, you drank too much.
Young Lord Gu, where do you live?
How about I ask someone to take you home?
I have no home.
I see that Young Lord has a lot on your mind.
How about... telling me about it?
Those with the same misfortune sympathize with each other.
Grandfather passed away, I have no relatives either.
I don't know where to go.
If there's really no place where you can go, then go to the capital.
[Mi Luo Drinking House]
Greetings to Imperial Great Grandmother!
Sit, please.
Can you all see those?
Recently, there were some envoys from vassal states
who gifted us with so many tributary gifts.
Your Imperial Majesty sent me some superior ones.
Do you want to see?
Little ladies like yourselves will surely like them.
Go pick.
Pick whichever one you like.
Take whichever you want.
Imperial Great Grandmother, I pick these.
That's not for yourself, it's for your mother consort.
Since Great Grandmother already said so, I might as well pick some more.
Great Grandmother, I like this one.
Really, take it if you like it.
If you like anything else, go take another look.
Is the food more precious or the treasures?
Of course, it's the food!
What they took can only be looked at, can't be eaten.
It would just gather dust in my room.
If I wear it, I'll just worry about it getting lost. I don't like it.
What do you like?
I like to go out and play!
Foolish little girl, only cares about going out to play.
Do you want to go outside?
Then go out.
Really?
Xiaofeng, do you like cuju?
['cuju' is the ancient Chinese form of soccer]
Tomorrow, there will be a "cuju" game at the Forbidden Park.
All the sons of the royal family and high officials will be there.
"Cuju?"
Not only do I like it, I also know how to play.
At our great plains,
there's an annual "cuju" competition. It's so much fun!
Can I go play tomorrow?
No way. You dare join a men's "cuju" game?
My future sister-in-law, don't scare my crown prince brother.
What is the problem?
Since you have such an interest, why don't we...
Tomorrow, let Yingqiao take you all out.
Kicking is not possible, but watching is doable.
Sure! Sure! Thank you, Great Grandmother!
Why are we changing the audience's seating at the last minute?
Official Zhao, sorry for causing any inconvenience.
This morning, Grand Empress Dowager ordered me to
bring the princesses here to watch the match.
Originally, there weren't seats for females here.
Now, we have to change the seats around,
and let the officials originally seated on the east side to transfer to the west.
Let the imperial consorts just sit a bit closer with the different royal relatives on the east side.
That way, we can fulfill Grand Empress Dowager's wishes without breaking the palace rules.
Please forgive us for any trouble we've caused.
Fine. Fine. Let's go.
Sister Yingqiao!
- This way please.
- Thank you.
- Xiaofeng!
Luoxi! Yongning! You're here already.
- You sit here.
- Why?
Why are you both here so early?
Because someone wants to see not only the "cuju" game.
Yongning.
Whose family do those two young lords belong to?
That one is Prime Minister Gao Yuming's youngest son, Gao Zhen.
See that one? He is the son of General Zhao of the Second Rank, Zhao Shixuan.
He's also Zhao Sese's brother.
Gao Zhen is a master when it comes to "cuju,"
but this time he's playing against Zhao Shixuan,
so he's slightly at a disadvantage.
Why?
It's because even though Gao Zhen is good at this game,
his team is composed of ordinary guards from his manor.
It's different with Zhao Shixuan.
His team is formed by members carefully selected
by him from General Zhao's Shuoyang Army.
They are all good players.
Gao Zhen won't be able to win this time.
Oh no! Oh no!
Then, Gao Zhen might get into a fight with Zhao Shixuan.
Why would Gao Zhen get into a fight with Zhao Shixuan?
Do you know those two?
No, I don't know them! I'm just guessing.
Hopefully, nothing happens.
Good!
Good! Good!
That's fantastic! Bravo!
Let's go again!
Listen up. With Prince Yi behind us, the Zhao team won't dare touch us.
When we start again, you go ahead and use your killing strikes.
How come this Zhao Shixuan doesn't know to back off a little?
This Gao Zhen is definitely looking for revenge.
What revenge?
Is there any conflict between them?
You don't know. It's to fight for the top courtesan at Singing Jade Brothel.
Gao Zhen hasn't liked Zhao Shixuan for quite some time.
This time, they'll probably get into a real fight.
Singing Jade Brothel?
Older Brother!
Gao Zhen, you are clearly hurting people with bad intentions.
In the "cuju" field, the victor is the king.
Who told him to have such a weak body?
- That doesn't mean you can kick people!
- Right!
Stop!
Brother, are you all right?
Imperial doctor! Imperial doctor!
Your Highness the Crown Prince, Assistant Minister Zhao is hurt badly.
It was just an accident during the ball game. How could it be that serious?
Crown Prince, I saw with my own eyes that Gao Zhen purposely kicked my brother.
Sese, you misunderstood. In a "cuju" game, it is impossible to avoid some injury.
I was on the side earlier. Gao Zhen didn't mean to hurt your brother.
But—
Brother!
Sese, drop it.
Hurry and carry him away!
Sese!
Be careful.
Your Highness!
Zhao Shixuan and Gao Zhen have been
competing for the top courtesan Mingyue's affection for a while.
Everyone in town knows about this already.
That Mingyue even asked her madam not to make her see Gao Zhen anymore.
If we're talking about looks, Zhao Shixuan is indeed more handsome.
Let's talk about official business.
There's news from the palace that since yesterday, Li Chengyin has claimed to be ill
and practically locked himself inside the Luminous Benevolence Hall.
He is probably too embarrassed to see people.
I understand Prince Yi less and less.
Although the Zhao family is not as powerful as the Gao family and the Pei family,
their army has always been stationed at the southwestern region.
If the Zhao family allies with Prince Yi, then it's also allying with Prime Minister Gao.
We have to prevent that.
I initially thought Li Chengyin was just a romantic.
I never thought that he was wooing Zhao Sese for this reason.
I also used to look down on the Zhao family.
But Zhao Jingyu has repeatedly expressed his desire to marry his daughter to me as a second rank consort.
I never expected that Zhao Sese would fall in love with Prince Yi.
I'll have to reconsider that decision then.
If Zhao Jingyu has this idea,
why doesn't Your Highness just accept her?
Besides, it's not that big of a deal.
We'll have to see what Miss Zhao thinks.
If she supports Prince Yi wholeheartedly, then it would be complicated.
Crown Prince, Miss Zhao sent this box over.
[Letter from Miss Zhao]
Miss Zhao thanks me for being thoughtful of her
and says she'll repay the favor in the future.
Your Highness, whatever you desire is indeed coming true.
Enough. It's all right that your act is stiff.
It'll become more natural the more you do it.
The most important part is knowing the rules of the palace.
Recite the Lessons for Women.
I wish to know how much you understand.
Yes.
"Refined and gentle, chaste, with moral principles
are the inner virtues that a woman should have.
Plus, the external virtues filial piety, respect, benevolence, being insightful,
kindness, peaceful relations, gentleness, and submissiveness: a woman would then be completely virtuous.
A person...
A person..."
What is it?
- ...is born with these virtues—
- Directress Fang!
I am here!
You've taught the Ninth Princess for so long.
Why can't she even recite the "Lessons of a Woman" completely? (T/N: Should actually be the "Virtuous Nature" chapter of "Teachings for the Inner Court" by Empress Renxiaowen of the Ming Empire)
You're even the top female official at the ceremonial services.
I think your reputation is exaggerated.
Empress is right. I am truly at fault.
Since it's your fault, you need to receive punishment.
As of today, you are demoted two ranks, and your wage is deducted by four taels of silver every month.
Thank you, Empress, for your kindness.
Empress!
Yongniang, Grand Empress Dowager sent you to take care of the Ninth Princess.
Why haven't you monitored her to study better?
I heard that you visited Garden of Fragrance some days ago
and accidentally fell in the lake and caught a cold.
Are you not yet recovered?
Yongniang, you are the experienced lady-in-waiting here.
Why are you not more diligent?
If the princess is still unwell, you should've inform me and let her rest in her room.
To have her travel all the way here,
the cold wind probably made her sicker.
Informing Empress, Prince Yi asked Shi'en earlier to relay a message.
He was originally coming to read the sutra with you this afternoon.
However, he is not feeling well and will need to postpone it.
He begs for your permission.
This child... He's already rejected me twice.
What exactly is wrong with him? Has the imperial doctor checked on him?
Empress, I've already sent someone to check.
His Highness is very healthy.
He is just feeling fatigued and doesn't want to see people.
There are talks among the palace servants that
His Highness is lovesick.
Rubbish!
Prince Yi is still young, how can he be lovesick?
I heard that because His Highness sided with Gao Zhen during the "cuju" game,
Zhao Sese got so upset that she wouldn't see him.
His Highness then waited at the Zhao Manor for several days but wasn't able to see her.
So he refused to step out of his Luminous Benevolence Hall anymore.
Call Zhao Sese to come into the palace.
Yes.
Directress Fang, I'm very sorry.
Today, it was all because of me
that you were punished by the empress.
I promise!
From now on I won’t mess around. I’ll definitely be more diligent in learning.
Even your clothes are messy.
Life is boring inside the palace.
Everyone is usually following the rules, just going to their duties as assigned.
Your arrival has injected vibrancy in this boring life.
You were born with an unrestrained nature and you don't like to study.
But during these days that I spent with you,
I find you very interesting.
Directress Fang, are you complimenting me?
I'll take my leave.
I just realized today Directress Fang is not as annoying as I always thought.
She's adorable.
Your Highness Prince Yi.
Ninth Princess, you've been coming over quite frequently.
Ninth Princess.
I’ve heard... that you have lovesickness.
What are you talking about?! Who has lovesickness?!
You're not sick? That's bad.
This is bad.
Someone's in trouble because of you.
What do you mean?
The empress has ordered Miss Zhao to come into the palace earlier.
It's true. I was just at the empress' palace earlier.
That's why I sneaked over here to tell you this.
This doesn't count as a thank you gift.
I didn’t say it was a thank you gift.
Then what is it for?
I'm a person that returns a favor.
Since you've saved my life, I consider you a friend so I'm telling you this.
Being my friend isn’t a good thing.
I don’t believe these words. Best if you find another excuse.
My name is Sese. Greetings, Empress.
General Zhao's daughter is really beautiful.
I heard that you have outstanding literary knowledge.
Have you studied the "Lessons of a Woman"?
Yes, I have.
Do you know what womanly virtue means?
"Refined and gentle, chaste, with moral principles,
(T/N: an excerpt from "Lessons of a Woman" by Ban Zhao)
have shame, speaks and acts with propriety: those are the womanly virtues."
Do you understand their true meaning?
A person that is refined, gentle, and chaste is sluggish for external matters, but anxious for internal concerns.
She does not have any desires or lust, and focuses on cultivating virtue and expanding her contributions.
She doesn't seek to make higher connections, nor be addicted to romantic follies.
A person with moral principles doesn't have excessive aspirations,
uncontrollable arrogance, or unbridled desires.
She knows to prioritize when dealing with matters.
She knows that there are things that she can and can't do. A person with shame—
Very good.
Knowing what you can and can't do.
You are a well-educated girl. You should understand
that the most important requirement as a woman is to not go out of bounds.
If you forget your boundary, it's like forgetting yourself.
You start aspiring for what you should not reach for.
I am terrified!
If you really know fear, you wouldn’t have any entanglement with Prince Yi.
I sincerely love and admire His Highness Prince Yi.
I don’t have any impure thoughts about him!
No impure thoughts?
Good! I'll tell you the truth.
The future princess consort of Prince Yi has long been designated. She is Duke Wei of the State's granddaughter.
Everyone has a different fate. Don't blame me for being heartless.
If you really care about Prince Yi,
then quit teasing him.
[Clean and Peaceful Palace]
Sese! Sese!
What's the matter?
Did my imperial mother say something to you?
Your Highness, please maintain proper decorum.
I am beneath your rank and do not dare harbor inappropriate thoughts
of being with Your Highness forever.
From now on, I will never intrude upon you again.
I will not have any relationship with you again.
I also ask that you never come and find me again.
Do not affect my thoughts.
Don't let me harbor any hopes about you again.
Sese. Se...
A while ago, Prince Yi would indeed go to Zhao Manor every day,
but Miss Zhao keeps refusing to see him.
These past days, Prince Yi seems to have grown tired of it and doesn't go to Zhao Manor anymore.
Usually, he either stays in his own manor or goes to the Grand Literature Library.
By the way, Xi State's Ninth Princess will sometimes go to the library, too.
I got it, Chan'er. You've worked hard.
Go get your reward.
Yes.
[General of the Second Rank Manor]
Your Highness Prince Yi, my daughter lacks manners and refuses to see you.
I hope you won't lower yourself to her level and make a fuss about it.
Greetings, Your Highness the Crown Prince.
Good poems.
I didn't think a warrior like General Zhao
was also a talented scholar.
You are too kind.
I'm only a simple soldier.
I don't wish to be ridiculed by others.
So I learned a few words.
General is too humble and cautious.
Just by looking at the writing of your daughter,
we know you are no simple soldier.
[Letter from Miss Zhao to the crown prince thanking him for lending her his cloak on the day she fell into the pond]
Please forgive my daughter's offense.
Oh? What offense?
Crown Prince knows what I want.
If you don't mind, we would like be your supporters.
We will follow your order with all our hearts.
There is a rumor in the palace that your daughter loves my fifth brother, Prince Yi.
She was not clearheaded and caused these unnecessary talks.
Our Zhao family never had any dealings with the Gao family, and we will never be connected from now on.
My daughter has also suffered some setbacks.
She learned her lesson and understood that she should entrust her future to Your Highness.
Please rest assured, Your Highness.
To receive but to not reciprocate is bad manners.
Please give this to your daughter.
It's a small token to show my appreciation and also my promise.
Thank you, Your Highness the Crown Prince.
By the way, how is Xuan recovering?
Thank you for caring.
Shixuan still cannot walk yet.
But he has studied martial arts since childhood, he'll recover faster than regular people.
In two months, he should be able to walk and move around again.
In the future, we'll look for the right time
to vent this grievance that Xuan suffered.
Yes.
Lately, I have received many memorials rushing me to decide
on who to name as the North Subduing Marquis.
Today, we'll discuss
who would be the best candidate.
Crown Prince, tell us what you think.
Your Imperial Majesty, I have thought of a perfect choice.
Who?
According to the people here,
we shouldn't shy away from recommending people we favor,
or select from a national security standpoint. Everybody has their point.
I think that neither General Gao Xian
or Li Yan of the Ministry of War are a good choice.
They are pillars of our nation. But Danchi is a special place.
Danchi not only frequently invaded our border,
but their other neighbor of Western Border as well. Their ambition is obvious.
But God is kind.
Genocide is too tragic.
General Gao, to us Li Empire, is the champion who defeated Danchi.
But to Danchi people...
If he were to be the North Subduing Marquis,
those people would revolt against him in time.
If we want the Danchi people to truly surrender to us,
to have them settle down in their land,
General Gao is not the best candidate.
If I can I have my choice,
I will send Assistant Minister Li.
But the north is a harsh place to live. He had suffered an injury during the war.
If we sent him back to that bitter cold place,
it will seem too cruel of me.
What you said makes sense.
So who is your choice?
It's Bulwark General Zhao Jingyu.
How come it's him?
Why him?
- That would be a great choice.
- Yes, I agree.
He is really good.
Zhao Jingyu.
I'm here.
I know you did a really great job supervising the southwestern border.
I also heard you liked reading the teachings of Lao-tze and Chuang-tze (the founders of Taoism).
Are you still reading those books?
Your Imperial Majesty, I remember you reprimanded me when I was young
that a warrior should not be content with being a fighter.
I wrote what you said over my bed so that I can see it every day.
I do not dare to even forget it by a day.
Excellent!
Then I shall issue a decree today
to appoint you as the North Subduing Marquis.
You will leave for your job in three days!
I shall abide!
♫ The night has yet to fade ♫
♫ The cold moonlight shines on the window ♫
♫ Matters of the past life ♫
♫ are carefully being considered ♫
♫ A long dream ♫
♫ Yet always gathering and separating into uncertainty ♫
♫ Watery eyes are wishing for your return ♫
♫ Wounds have frosted in my heart ♫
♫ Can't forget your image in my mind ♫
♫ Looking back to our first meeting ♫
♫ That first moment when we saw each other ♫
♫ Can't hold onto the fingertips that you've extended ♫
♫ Parting shattered the heart ♫
♫ Useless tears for the person isn't coming back ♫
♫ The River of Oblivion ♫
♫ Silently gazes unto the troubles of the mundane world ♫
♫ Time reverses ♫
♫ With a sip to forget love ♫
♫ If we meet for the first time again, who are we returning to ♫
♫ Parting shattered the heart ♫
♫ Useless tears for the person isn't coming back ♫
♫ The River of Oblivion ♫
♫ Silently gazes unto the troubles of the mundane world ♫
♫ Time reverses ♫
♫ With a sip to forget love ♫
♫ If we meet for the first time again, who are we returning to ♫
♫ Fall goes and spring comes again ♫
♫ Dream and awakening are just in cycle ♫