♫ As dusk starts, I look at the setting sun in the horizon ♫
♫  I faintly remember the outline of your face ♫
♫  After all, it can't be helped to feel more sentimental when one reminisces  ♫
♫  I sigh softly at our happy times ♫
♫  The night hasn't ended, so many stars fall into the rim of my eyes  ♫
♫  Collecting a soft and gentle light  ♫
♫ The sky is clear, the scenery are good ♫
♫ If you're not by my side ♫
♫ so what if I can go up the Firmament ♫
♫ The boat passes an empty harbor and feeds the loneliness ♫
♫ Frost falls over the wilderness, drooping the tears ♫
♫ Who caused my sun to fall from the sky ♫
♫ It’s your face that took away my entire light ♫
♫ For only you are my heaven ♫
[Goodbye My Princess]
[Episode 22]
[Embracing the Moon Pavilion]
Yongniang.
Princess.
The imperial doctor already said that you need to rest after spraining your ankle!
Just lie down and rest.
Let me and A'Du take care of things for you.
I just wanted to take a walk in the backyard.
You hurt your foot in the yard!
I just hate myself for not watching you more carefully and let you come back late.
My foot is already fine now!
Princess, your wedding is in less than a month!
If anything bad happens that will delay the wedding, I will lose my life.
And you, Miss A'Du, stop wearing that set of clothes!
You are the personal maidservant of the princess.
You keep refusing to assimilate with the palace rules. What will other people think of the princess?
And... I told you not to sleep on the roof. How many times do I have to tell you?
Let's go. I'll bring you to go to sleep now.
Rest early, My Princess.
Is it interesting to sleep on the roof?
Gu Jian?!
Xiaofeng, I finally waited for you.
You... How did you know I was going to come out from here?
It's like waiting at a tree for a rabbit.
When you wait long enough, a rabbit will definitely come by.
I'm not a rabbit!
There aren't many horse merchants in the capital.
I looked several days before finding this one.
He is yours from now on.
He looks a lot like my little red horse.
I also belong to you from now on.
I am your guardian. You can call me anytime.
How do I call you?
Whenever you want to see me or need my help,
just shoot this whistle arrow towards the sky and I'll appear.
Why would I look for you for no reason?
Besides, I have plenty of guards protecting me in the palace.
You might not need it now, but you'll definitely need it in the future.
Such as, when you want to leave the palace but can't get out.
All right, you make a point.
But I don't think I'll use it.
- I can't talk to you anymore. I have something urgent to do.
- What about?
I'm going to see Mi Luo and have her investigate something in the Temple of Ten Thousand Buddhas.
The Temple of Ten Thousand Buddhas?
That's a royal temple.
Mi Luo has her wine house to take care of. Why involve her in this matter?
But I don't know anyone else in the capital.
You?
You forgot it that fast?
Didn't I just tell you that I am your guardian? So, naturally, I will ensure your safety.
Then, let's go.
- Slow down.
- Be careful.
- Okay.
- Over here.
- Here.
- Okay, be careful.
Over here.
Be a bit more careful.
Over here, spread a bit here.
They are—
- Hurry. Hurry.
- Okay.
It's good. It's good. Right.
I will have to trouble you with this piece.
- Look closer, okay?
- I think this is almost done.
Okay.
In a few more days, it will be the Lunar New Year's Day.
You have not celebrated the Lunar New Year in the capital, right?
During the Lunar New Year, it gets very festive in the capital.
First, we offer sacrifices to the gods
and then we have a large banquet that happens once a year.
It is all very festive and noisy up to the fifteenth night of the month.
There are all sorts of celebrations that go on and on.
Do you not like it when everything is lively and bustling?
Xiaofeng?
I am talking to you.
Imperial Great Grandmother, I am going to tell on someone.
Do what?
Didn't you and His Imperial Majesty decree Prince Yi and I
to investigate and verify that copper coins case?
He has clearly found evidence, but he does not want to make a report.
And he even returned all the evidence back.
Tell me. Does he not have selfish motives?
From my perspective, he does.
Recently, the palace has been preparing for the New Year's Eve dinner.
You seem to be very tired.
Although trivial matters of the palace require a great amount of effort, it's not really mentally exhausting.
The only things that waste my mental energy involve you.
Yin'er, you are the one who defeated Danchi,
but you instead demanded a laborious task of compiling a book.
I originally thought that compiling a book was just a pretense.
That perhaps, you had some idea on how to make your imperial father change his mind
and confer you the crown prince title.
But I did not think that you would indeed be sincerely compiling a book.
Imperial Mother, actually—
What? Have I said something wrong?
Imperial Mother, I actually do have a matter I would like you to help me make a decision on.
What is it?
My Lady. Reporting to Empress.
His Imperial Majesty is calling for Prince Yi to immediately go to Assuming the Rites Hall to see him.
Imperial Father.
I've heard that these two days, you didn't summon for the book writing officials.
You must be investigating the copper coins.
What's the progress on it?
Imperial Father, I still don't have any leads.
Do you not have any leads or are you scared to tell me?
Your Imperial Majesty.
Princess, tell me what did you discover?
Replying back to Your Imperial Majesty, Prince Yi already found leads from the account books of the Ministry of Revenue.
I even went with him to the Temple of Ten Thousand Buddhas—
Imperial Father, the evidence that Ninth Princess is referring to are all speculations.
It can't be presented as evidence to the court.
I clearly saw them putting copper powder on a clay sculpture of Buddha in the middle of the night.
You dare to leave the palace at night?
You do not dare to openly investigate, so why can't I privately investigate?
Enough. Who is supervising the construction of the Temple of Ten Thousand Buddhas?
Responding to Your Majesty, it is Li Yan.
Tell him to come here.
Yes.
Wait. Bring the crown prince as well.
I will obey.
What does this have to do with the crown prince?
Shut your mouth.
The crown prince is here!
- Imperial Father.
- Your Imperial Majesty.
It's... It's... It's him, Your Imperial Majesty.
The person that I saw at the Temple of Ten Thousand Buddhas was him!
Plus, when I knocked on the Buddha statue, he became flustered.
If he didn't know that the Buddha statue was made of clay,
why would he be flustered?
What are you saying, Ninth Princess?
I was ordered to make the statues.
What's wrong with me being slightly worried about the statues?
Let me ask you then. Where did you get the copper for making the statues?
Of course, it was given by the Ministry of Revenue.
Given by the Ministry of Revenue? Let me tell you this.
Prince Yi and I have investigated the Ministry of Revenue.
Every year, the Li Empire only mines no more than 150,000 kilograms of copper.
Out of all this, 50,000 kilograms are used to make official coins.
But currently, there are counterfeit coins that are double the number of official coins circulating in the market.
That means the total amount of copper on the market has now surpassed 150,000 kilograms of copper.
With that said, the origin of your copper must not be simple.
Prince Yi and you dared to privately investigate my Ministry of Revenue's accounting book.
When I was working on the Xi State Annals, I accidentally saw that among the archives.
Your Imperial Majesty, I don't know how I've offended Prince Yi and Ninth Princess.
I am unjustly accused. Your Imperial Majesty, please take charge.
Crown Prince, what do you think?
Imperial Father, I am very close to Li Yan.
I don't dare to discuss it since I may be considered biased.
I'm allowing you to say it.
Li Yan puts a lot of effort in watching over the production of the Buddhist statues in the Temple of Ten Thousand Buddhas.
I cannot say that he did his job perfectly, but he tried his best.
However, embezzlement of the copper used for the Buddhist statues is a grave crime.
I believe that Li Yan would not do such things.
With only Ninth Princess' words,
I am afraid it is too unreliable.
What do you mean?
Your Imperial Majesty, I don't understand what goes on in the court and I don't have any grudges with anyone.
I'm just acting under your command and I want to find the truth.
If they don't believe me, they can go to the Temple of Ten Thousand Buddhas and just open up the statues.
Your Majesty, the Buddhist statues have already been put up for people to pay their respects.
If we open them up, I am afraid that the faithful will be outraged.
It is against the way of Buddha.
I am afraid it will lead to unwanted disasters, Your Imperial Majesty!
Isn't producing a fake statue also against the way of Buddha?
If we open the statues but find no problems,
who will take the responsibility for angering the gods and the faithful?
This is actually not a hard choice.
If we don't open up the statues, how would we know if there's any problem?
Your Imperial Majesty, we can tell if it's real or fake without breaking open the statues.
You know how?
If a statue is made from mud,
then its weight will be different from the copper weight recorded by the Ministry of Revenue.
Therefore, why don't we just weigh it?
Good, let's do it that way.
To prevent anyone doing any tricks...
- Ceng Xian.
- Present.
Take the Shenwu (Divine Military) Army to close the temple immediately.
Tomorrow, I will personally preside over the investigation.
Yes, Your Imperial Majesty!
[Temple of Ten Thousand Buddhas]
Look, how large!
Yes.
- Where is it dragging it to?
- I've never seen anything like this before.
It's the first time I've seen such a scene.
Wow, I wish my wife was here to see this.
It's coming.
Why use the elephant to drag the statue?
Weighing the statue. They will use a boat to weigh the statue.
This is the first time.
Look at that!
What a grand sight.
Your Imperial Majesty, the copper statue's weight
is completely identical to what's recorded in the Ministry of Revenue's records.
Ninth Princess, how about it now?
Do we need to weigh another statue?
Your Imperial Majesty, I witnessed people brushing a mud statue with copper paint.
Someone must have exchanged the statue.
Your Imperial Majesty, I personally guarded overnight at the Temple of Ten Thousand Buddhas.
It's impossible that the statue was exchanged.
Impossible, I saw it myself.
Someone bet their life to force a military command.
Now, they want to deny it in public.
Li Yan, be forgiving when you win.
Ninth Princess is not in the military. What military command?
Let's treat it as setting up a stage and accompanying Ninth Princess and Fifth Little Brother to watch a show.
Imperial Father, since Ninth Princess insists that she witnessed it herself,
I recommend that we check one more statue as suggested by her.
Ridiculous! Do you think our royal reputation is a child's game to play?
Ninth Princess, from now on, these situations should be discussed with me.
Prince Yi!
Thank yoiu for talking on my behalf earlier.
No need.
I got you involved in this problem.
It doesn't make sense for only you to be wronged,
but you should stop here.
You're on your own.
Your Highness, are you confused?
How could you have stopped the emperor today and say those words?
She was fighting on the front line. I can't just cower behind her. Right?
Besides, it started with me, so I should stand by her.
Your reckless behavior today will upset Prime Minister Gao.
We haven't made a firm footing yet. We can't afford to alienate Prime Minister Gao.
Yes, I will take care of things with him.
Your Highness, you must think thrice before acting in the future.
Do not let your emotions get the better of you.
Yes, I understand.
Grand Uncle.
Your Highness, it's already very late. May I know—
Grand Uncle, sit first.
- Why are you here? Why?
- Please take a seat.
Come, sit down.
Your Highness, tell me why.
I am here to beg forgiveness to Grand Uncle.
I was reckless and ruined a good plan that you and Uncle had arranged for me.
Hence, I made such a big blunder.
You are still young. It's understandable that you get impulsive.
Grand Uncle, I was just thinking at the time that since the matter had come to that,
someone had to speak up for Ninth Princess because of her prestigious position.
So, I stood up.
I was too impulsive.
From now on, I will closely remember the teachings from you and Imperial Mother.
I will not do things without your knowledge.
Forget it.
Make a mistake, learn a lesson. Just remember these lessons well.
Yes.
[Eastern Palace]
Whenever I think of how Li Chengyin rushed to get scolded today, I just want to laugh.
He and Ninth Princess have become the biggest joke in the world.
- Father.
- You, get down!
I need to thank you for today, Uncle.
It's all thanks to your cautious undertaking to switch the statues.
Otherwise, Li Yan and I wouldn't have been able to get out of this.
Your Highness is overstating what I did.
It's still old ginger that's the spiciest.
So what if Li Chengyin has Prime Minister Gao behind him? He's no match with my dad.
Shut your mouth!
You made such a huge mistake. You almost lost your head!
Dad, isn't everything solved now?
You couldn't even deal with a teenager.
If... If not because she's the future crown princess consort, I would have taken care of her.
Even though we stopped the problem here,
Fifth has already found out about the secret dealings.
We can't maneuver anymore.
Fifth Brother knows too much. I am very concerned.
If you ask me, just get rid of him, so he won't trouble us anymore.
Quit your ridiculous talk.
This is the capital, not the Western Border.
Uncle is exactly right.
This is the capital; hence, we should use the capital's methods.
It seems Your Highness has new ideas.
Your Highness!
Sese! Why are you here?
Hurry! Go inside. Come.
[Prince Yi Manor]
Come.
You could have sent someone to tell me you were coming.
Why stand outside by yourself for so long?
I heard what happened in the palace today and was very worried.
I could only think about seeing Your Highness quickly.
I didn't come to blame Your Highness.
I know that you always do things with your own principles.
No matter what, I will always support you.
Sese, thank you for being concerned.
But Your Highness and that ninth princess... are...
We were just ordered by His Imperial Majesty to investigate this case together.
She is the future crown princess consort.
You need to watch your distance with her,
so that there won't be speculations and rumors.
Everyone knows that you and I like each other, so why would there be rumors about someone else?
With those words, all my worries are gone.
[Embracing the Moon Pavilion]
Come.
They are here! Hurry!
Princess—
Quick!
- Xiaofeng!
- Yongning! Luoxi! You two are finally here!
The snow is so heavy today. I thought you wouldn't come.
How could we not? It wasn't easy to get this from Imperial Great Grandmother.
From what I can tell, you used Xiaofeng as a cover to convince Great Grandmother to allow us.
And for whom did I do it?
I heard that someone else is going today so that's why it must be today.
It's a good thing that it's snowing so much.
We can bathe in the hot spring, then drink tea while enjoying the beautiful snowy scenery.
That's the beauty of life.
Let's not talk anymore and leave now,
so we can bathe in the hot spring around 3:00 p.m. to 5:00 p.m.
Let's hurry and leave now then.
Let's go!
[Clear Dew Hall]
Let's go, Xiaofeng! I'll take you to find Yongning.
It's so beautiful!
Yongning runs so fast.
We only took a slightly longer route, and she has already gone in!
Be quiet. I'll scare her a little.
Okay, let's go.
I caught you!
Xiaofeng!
Your Highness, are you okay?
Do not turn around.
- Take Luoxi away.
- Okay.
Let's go.
You still are not leaving? It's disrespectful to look!
You are the one who burst in.
Why do I have to leave? It makes no sense.
If you do not wish to go, I am fine with that.
I will not leave then. What can you do to me?
Why does your head hurt again?
Am I your nemesis, causing your head to hurt every time you see me?
Fortunately, I do not have to marry you.
Then, I have to thank you for your kindness in not marrying me.
With a gentle and virtuous Lady Zhao,
it must be the world's best marriage.
- Xiaofeng, you are...
- Your Highness the Crown Prince.
I did not run into you, did I?
I did not think you would be here. Where are you headed to?
I cannot find Luoxi.
I just saw someone hastily rushing towards the Side Hall.
It seemed like it was Luoxi.
Xiaofeng!
This ninth princess, she is supposed to marry you, but why does she run away from you when she sees you?
Where can she run to?
Spare me! Spare me!
Halt!
Prince Yi, I beg you! Please save me!
Your Highness Prince Yi!
Prince Yi?
Are you not satisfied with the Buddhist statue incident that you have to meddle with the Crown Prince's affair now?
This is my servant.
Even if she is to be punished, there are palace regulations to follow.
It is not your place to privately punish her.
This despicable servant frightened the crown prince's horse.
If I flogged her or even if she died one hundred times,
it would not be a pity.
Her punishment should be up to me, her master.
No need for Heir Apparent to exert any effort on it.
Chan'er, get up. Let's go.
Yes.
Prince Yi, could this lowly servant be your lover? Why are you defending her like this?
As the heir apparent, you should watch your words.
Do not be like a lowly servant.
What did you say?
Imperial Brother, I will naturally handle my servants.
I will take away this servant then.
- Let's go.
- Fifth Brother!
Today, this servant defied me.
I wish for her to stay here and I will bring her back to my manor to punish her.
Unless you believe that I do not handle matters fairly?
I do not dare.
I assumed you would not.
Imperial Brother, the two of us should not become unhappy because of a servant.
Since Imperial Brother wishes to personally mete out the punishment,
then in a few days, I will send someone to fetch her.
I ask Imperial Brother that for my sake, allow her to live.
Xiaofeng!
- Luoxi, do you two not know?
- Yongning, what is it?
- Yongning.
Just now, Fifth Brother and Li Yan got into an argument over a servant.
Fifth Brother got stopped by the men of the crown prince, and later left in a rage.
That severe? Then, what about General Pei Zhao?
He left. If you chase him now, you might be able to catch him.
Luoxi, have you three had dinner yet?
Responding to Brother Crown Prince, not yet.
At this time, if you head back to the palace, you will miss dinner.
I have already had people prepare dinner.
Once you all have eaten, I can send you three back to the palace.
There is no need, Crown Prince...
Xiaofeng, you seem to really love drinking white fungus snow pear soup.
This is quite delicious.
Girls like sweet foods.
If you love to drink it, I can let you have my bowl.
There is no need, Crown Prince. How could I want your things?
There is no harm. In the future, we will be husband and wife.
Not just a bowl of soup, but I will give you whatever you want.
Thank you, Your Highness the Crown Prince.
Even if you love drinking it, you should drink a bit slower. Otherwise, you will choke on it.
Yongning. Luoxi. Would you two like some sweets as well?
No, thank you, Brother Crown Prince.
Xiaofeng.
Xiaofeng, what is wrong with you?
What is wrong?
Xiaofeng! Xiaofeng! Xiaofeng!
Xiaofeng!
The emperor has arrived!
- Greetings, Your Imperial Majesty. Greetings, Empress.
- Greetings, Imperial Father. Greetings, Empress.
How could she be poisoned? How is she now?
Responding to Your Imperial Majesty, the ninth princess was heavily poisoned.
For now, I have performed acupuncture on her to delay the poison.
But if the ninth princess does not consume the antidote within three days, I am afraid...
Then, why are you not concocting the antidote?
The poison is very peculiar.
I... also cannot tell exactly what this is.
Let me tell you! No matter what, you must get her to wake up!
Yes!
Seal off the Imperial Villa and investigate thoroughly. The assailant must be found.
I have received your orders.
You. Bring her in.
No, it is not me! No!
What have you discovered? Quickly, tell me.
Responding to Your Imperial Majesty.
I thoroughly investigated the food that the ninth princess took yesterday.
Aside from a bowl of white fungus snow pear soup,
nothing else contained poison.
Responding to Your Imperial Majesty.
I have already interrogated and investigated all the servants in the Imperial Buttery of the Imperial Villa.
No one was suspicious.
I also didn't find any poison hidden in the entire villa.
Then, in these past two days, who has entered the Imperial Villa?
Responding to Your Imperial Majesty and Your Highness the Crown Prince.
I, Lu Pingzhang, am the chief steward of the Imperial Villa.
Up until yesterday, only His Highness the Crown Prince, Prince Yi, Princess Yongning,
Princess Luoxi, Xi State's Ninth Princess,
and the people that Heir Apparent Li brought with him have entered the Imperial Villa.
Because Prince Yi arrived around noon,
he initially planned to leave until after lunch today.
But at around 5:00 p.m. to 7:00 p.m. last night, he had left with General Pei.
Princess Yongning, Princess Luoxi, and the Ninth Princess arrived between 3:00 p.m. and 5:00 p.m.
His Highness the Crown Prince and the Heir Apparent both arrived at the end of this time.
Apart from this, except for some of their entourage that followed them,
no one else entered the Imperial Villa.
Tell me clearly. Why did Prince Yi leave early?
Prince Yi was... was because...
Your Imperial Majesty, yesterday Prince Yi and I nearly got into a fight before he left.
Li Yan, be polite in front of His Imperial Majesty.
Your Imperial Majesty, allow me to clearly explain it.
Continue.
Yesterday, one of Prince Yi's servants scared the Crown Prince's horse,
so I wished to teach the servant a lesson on behalf of the crown prince.
But who would have thought that Prince Yi would stop me before I even said anything?
I also just barely escaped being hit by Prince Yi.
Later, due to Crown Prince's
strenuous persuasion, Prince Yi let the matter drop.
That day, Prince Yi brought General Pei with him.
From the look of things, if a fight had erupted,
I am afraid that they would have even fought Crown Prince.
Stop talking. His Imperial Majesty wishes for us, brothers, to be friendly.
It's my fault for not being able to stop him today.
Imperial Father, this is all my fault.
Lu Pingzhang, continue speaking.
Yes, I meticulously interrogated and investigated the servants in the Imperial Buttery, but no outsiders went in there.
Your Imperial Majesty, if there was no outsider, then that means it's someone from within.
Then, who exactly sent the sweet snacks?
Responding to Your Imperial Majesty. It was I who was assigned to deliver them.
But Prince Yi's servant, Chan'er, took the sweets from me outside the hall.
She personally delivered it inside.
Do not speak nonsense!
I personally saw this myself!
Bring her in.
Yes!
Bring her in!
Your Imperial Majesty, I have been wronged. I have been wronged.
Responding to Your Majesty. When we were catching this maidservant,
she was dumping the contents of this pouch into a pond.
♫ The night has yet to fade ♫
♫ The cold moonlight shines on the window ♫
♫ Matters of the past life ♫
♫ are carefully being considered ♫
♫ A long dream ♫
♫ Yet always gathering and separating into uncertainty ♫
♫ Watery eyes are wishing for your return ♫
♫ Wounds have frosted in my heart ♫
♫ Can't forget your image in my mind ♫
♫ Looking back to our first meeting ♫
♫ That first moment when we saw each other ♫
♫ Can't hold onto the fingertips that you've extended ♫
♫ Parting shattered the heart ♫
♫ Useless tears for the person isn't coming back ♫
♫ The River of Oblivion ♫
♫ Silently gazes unto the troubles of the mundane world ♫
♫ Time reverses ♫
♫ With a sip to forget love ♫
♫ If we meet for the first time again, who are we returning to ♫
♫ Fall goes and spring comes again ♫
♫ Dream and awakening are just in cycle ♫
♫ The night has yet to fade ♫
♫ The cold moonlight shines on the window ♫
♫ Matters of the past life ♫
♫ are carefully being considered ♫
♫ A long dream ♫
♫ Yet always gathering and separating into uncertainty ♫
♫ Watery eyes are wishing for your return ♫
♫ Parting shattered the heart ♫
♫ Useless tears for the person isn't coming back ♫
♫ The River of Oblivion ♫
♫ Silently gazes unto the troubles of the mundane world ♫
♫ Time reverses ♫
♫ With a sip to forget love ♫
♫ If we meet for the first time again, who are we returning to ♫
♫ Parting shattered the heart ♫
♫ Useless tears for the person isn't coming back ♫
♫ The River of Oblivion ♫
♫ Silently gazes unto the troubles of the mundane world ♫
♫ Time reverses ♫
♫ With a sip to forget love ♫
♫ If we meet for the first time again, who are we returning to ♫
♫ Fall goes and spring comes again ♫
♫ Dream and awakening are just in cycle ♫