♫ As dusk starts, I look at the setting sun in the horizon ♫
♫  I faintly remember the outline of your face ♫
♫  After all, it can't be helped to feel more sentimental when one reminisces  ♫
♫  I sigh softly at our happy times ♫
♫  The night hasn't ended, so many stars fall into the
rim of my eyes  ♫
♫  Collecting a soft and gentle light  ♫
♫ The sky is clear, the scenery are good ♫
♫ If you're not by my side♫
♫ So what if I can go up the Firmament ♫
♫ The boat passes an empty harbor and feeds the loneliness ♫
♫ Frost falls over the wilderness, drooping the tears ♫
♫ Who caused my sun to fall from the sky. It’s your face that took away my entire light ♫
♫ For only you are my heaven ♫
[Goodbye My Princess]
[Episode 25]
[Supreme Ultimate Hall]
Second Brother, stop now. This is an insurgency.
Insurgency? Our existence...
is in itself an insurgency.
Your Imperial Majesty! All rebels have been vanquished.
Crown Prince has been taken to Court of Judicial Review to await your sentence.
"Cries of the parent birds resonate in the sky,
exhausting their voices, yet unable to call them back.
Returning to an empty nest,
chirping sadly the entire night."
[Court of Judicial Review]
You already dared to raise an insurrection. Who else would you not kill?
If I were able to sit on your throne, I would kill whomever I pleased.
However, I didn't succeed.
Refusing to come to one's senses.
Didn't you also ascend to the throne in such fashion?
You should understand that in the royal family,
it's impossible for true brotherly love and respect.
As the crown prince, you diverted the copper for Buddha statues of the Temple of Ten Thousand Buddhas,
secretly cast coins, and disturbed state governance.
Now, all the believers are still waiting for my explanation. You think that you
only committed a crime of slaughtering one's brother?
If I didn't have so many charges, I wouldn't have started an insurgency.
But everything was caused by you. It's you!
You were the one who was showing favoritism.You insisted on appointing that useless eldest brother as the crown prince.
You forced me to compete. Now, you're criticizing me for harming my own brother?
Even when you appointed me as the crown prince, you still indulged Fifth to investigate me.
Allowing my crown princess consort to investigate the case with him!
In your heart, you never really acknowledged me!
I... have always known...
that Chengji's death was related to you.
I still appointed you as the crown prince!
You say that I played favoritism. Yes, I am partial.
I am partial to you!
Prince Yi is also my son.
Do you still want me to lose a son for the second time?
Do you think Fifth is a good person?! The filthy stuff inside him is no less than mine.
Behind him is the Gao clan that you hate the most. Don't you have any suspicions of him?
Now, I failed.
If you really pass the crown prince position to him, just wait and see
if this empire will still belong to the Li's or to the Gao's!
If you weren't this prejudiced,
this throne, this empire,
would have been yours eventually.
You are the son
that I most wanted to appoint.
Imperial Father!
Grand Empress Dowager, this contrite subject boldly ventures
to beg you to save my entire clan!
Grand Empress Dowager, you are the most benevolent and generous!
Please save my clan!
Grand Empress Dowager, this contrite subject boldly ventures
to beg you to save my entire clan!
Li Yan... was my only son!
I've educated my son improperly. I ended up...
seeing my child dying before myself!
I can't blame anyone. I can't hate anyone.
But my clan's old and young are truly innocent!
This charge of insurgency is truly unbearable!
I...
No! I, your grandson,
am willing to use my life
in exchange for my clan's survival.
I beg that Grand Empress Dowager consider how Heaven has the virtue of favoring life.
Please speak on our behalf
and make a suggestion to the emperor.
Grand Empress Dowager...
Reporting to Your Imperial Majesty, the cases of the deceased crown prince's assassination, the Buddha copper statues of the Temple of Ten Thousand Buddhas,
and the poisoning of Xi State's princess have all been tried by the Court of Judicial Review.
The perpetrators are the crown prince and Li Yan.
I've brought the trial proceedings.
May Your Imperial Majesty give your judgment.
Your Imperial Majesty, the crown prince committed a grave mistake. Li Yan is probably guilty of instigating him.
Li Yan is already dead. The whole clan of Elder Prince Zhong should be punished by law.
But considering that the crown prince had done many merits for the empire, I wish that Your Imperial Majesty
will be lenient.
Grand Empress Dowager arrives!
Please rise. With all bent over,
I can't recognize any of you.
Thank you, Grand Empress Dowager!
Imperial Grandmother, you could have just sent a message for any matter. Why must you come here in person?
Your Imperial Majesty.
I am here firstly for to ask for a favor.
Imperial Grandmother, you are making things difficult for me.
Please let me finish,
then see if it is difficult or not difficult.
Please tell.
I ask Your Imperial Majesty
to take away Elder Prince Zhong's imperial grace of having a hereditary nobility title and confiscate his entire assets.
Among the four clans and three generations of Elder Prince Zhong, from henceforth, they may not
enter the court as officials.
Since Imperial Grandmother has spoken,
I will definitely give you this favor.
What about Li Chengye?
Imperial Grandmother!
Li Chengye brought in an army late at night, charging through the Gate of Heavenly Purity.
He attempted to commit patricide and usurp the throne. He also masterminded the three cases of assassinating the former crown prince,
misappropriating the copper meant for the Buddha statues, and poisoning the Xi State's ninth princess,
then framing it on Prince Yi.
My Li Empire definitely cannot tolerate
a crown prince with such a wolfish nature!
Considering that he is my son,
I will leave his corpse intact.
I bestow upon him a cup of poisoned wine.
He is to be buried outside the ancestral tomb.
I never expected that Grand Empress Dowager wouldn't consider Elder Prince Zhong as being a son from her own maiden family.
She pulled out the House of Elder Prince Zhong up to its roots.
Grand Empress Dowager is formidable. It only took three statements to finalize the cosmos.
What does that mean?
For those offenses that Li Yan and the crown prince committed, if judged harshly,
it is acceptable to even have the entire clan annihilated.
What the Grand Empress Dowager said might appear as a harsh punishment,
but in reality, she only took the right of serving the government from Elder Prince Zhong's clan. No one lost their lives.
This is like when our own child fought with someone outside. When that child family come to confront us,
if you go up and slap your child a couple of times and give him a good scolding,
would they still dare to give him a piece of their mind?
Oh, so that's it.
Brother, are you being sarcastic to me?
It's still Kun'er who can understand it all.
I just don't understand
why His Imperial Majesty would rather let Elder Prince Zhong go,
but not leave his own son a way to live.
Dad, why are you caring about Li Chengye now?
If he dies, everyone will be happy.
Father is only saying that the emperor's heart is ruthless.
His Imperial Majesty is here!
Grandmother. Everyone can leave now.
Your Imperial Majesty, why did you come?
I heard you got sick after coming back, so I came to visit.
Grandmother, please do not get angry and overtax yourself.
Acting this way can damage your body.
Overtaxing myself?
Your Imperial Majesty, you should know
why I am so sad.
They are all your closest kin!
Why must you be this heartless?!
Grandmother,
when Chengye made his first step,
he should've anticipated an outcome like this today.
If I do not severely punish him, make him an example,
then next time, the other princes will imitate him.
If there is any problem, they would just rebel and try to kill their father.
Will my empire still be at peace?
It's not that I don't know how cruel the power struggle has been in every generation, in every dynasty.
But how come you think
that the person who's able to eat up all his prey is the one suitable to inherit your throne? Hence, you've been
allowing these princes to...
fight openly and secretly.
Isn't all this your doing?! They are all children.
They are all our children!
The reason why
Chengye went this far...
Have you thought about it? It's all because you spoiled him.
You taught him to be like that.
I am not wrong. My way isn't wrong.
He went wrong because he had a prejudiced heart.
Grandmother, to be the sovereign of a nation, he should be thinking of the people
and conducting himself righteously.
But Chengye, he deviated too much.
Your Imperial Majesty,
Chengye may indeed be too prejudiced,
but you proclaimed him as the crown prince.
You gave him the power.
If you don't want to repeat the tragedy,
why do you still insist on
the doctrine of the winner takes all? You should be proclaiming
a mild-mannered person to be the crown prince.
Am I right?
Grandmother, you are tired. Get some rest.
The inner palace and the imperial court
are ultimately two different places.
Li Chengye's situation is hopeless.
What else is Your Highness worrying about?
Insurgency.
Our very existence... itself is insurgency.
Sir Chai,
I actually never thought of forcing Second Brother to rebel.
Even less wanted him to lose his life over this matter.
Before I went to Xi State, this position of the crown prince was really not so important,
but it has already caused so many people to spill their blood.
I do not know if what I am doing is really meaningful.
Li Chengye has a stubborn and bigoted personality. Rebelling
is his own decision. It has no relations with you.
What about Xiaofeng?
She got involved in our sibling fight and almost lost her life!
Sir Chai, how could I not feel fear or regret?
In your opinion then, how did the matter develop to this current stage?
If Your Highness was able to be resolute back then, you wouldn't have had partnered with Ninth Princess to investigate the case together.
The more you shouldn't have defended her after the statue was weighed;
hence, putting her life in danger.
All of this was because your heart...
your heart is too soft. You gave Li Chengye the opportunity to find your weakness.
Your Highness, from henceforward, the enemies that you will encounter
will be stronger than Li Chengye by a thousand times more. If you cannot maintain a clear head,
what you will lose... will be much more than one elder brother.
If Your Highness wishes to reduce the harm to a minimum,
you must learn to become a merciless person.
Only once your heart is as hard as stone, will it be impenetrable by spears and swords.
You would then be able to protect the people you want to protect.
Princess, these are all your favorite deserts. Eat something.
I can't eat.
I know you are anxious about all these major events in the palace.
But you haven't eaten anything all day. You shouldn't let your worries destroy your health.
Yongniang, how can I not have lingering fear? This palace was originally calm and peaceful.
Suddenly, there was a mutiny. Suddenly, the crown prince was punished to commit suicide.
Only then did I know that the person I was going to marry was so scary.
You tell me. With this crown prince position being so full of danger, did every person who had risen and was given that title, do so by stepping on the blood of others?
Ninth Princess, you absolutely cannot speak this way.
The future crown prince will definitely have outstanding morality and conduct.
I understand. Yongniang, you should quickly go rest now.
I want to write a letter to my mom and dad.
Yes.
Yongniang actually knows everything.
She only wants to say nice things to humor me.
A'Du, quickly come here! Come!
Now that the crown prince is gone,
can I not get married anymore?
If it's like this, then I'll write to Dad
and have him take us back.
Let's go back to the Xi State.
What do you think? Is that all right?
Yes. Yes. I'll do that.
Fourth Little Brother, think thrice before making a move.
Since your fourth little brother can't make a decision,
Chengwen, you come and help him.
I will obey.
Chengyin, what do you think?
I am weak in chess and dare not offer any opinion.
Come over here and try it.
Imperial Father, it's a "bent four in the corner."
There are no more moves that I can do and this game is over. Even I am unable to reverse this desperate situation.
Imperial Father, your chess game skill is superb. We are ashamed of our inferiority.
No need to feel uneasy.
I asked you all to come for a get-together today and worked your brains hard.
You all go back and rest.
We are leaving.
Your Imperial Majesty, it's time for you to eat.
Cao Ji, what do you think about the chess match today?
I am slow-witted and don't understand chess.
You have an answer in your heart. Say it.
Prince Yun is very cautious about his moves and thinks for a long time,
but he's too wary.
Prince Yong is very ambitious and brazen.
When he makes his move, it is clean and precise,
but he never thinks about the whole game.
Prince Yi continued to play this losing game.
His attack and defensive moves were all reasonable. Even though he only placed a few chess pieces,
he was able to change the losing situation of the game.
But he said that this was a lost game.
You saw that, too.
This chess game was actually 50-50 even.
Prince Yi had a chance to redeem the game, but he gave up.
Very intelligent. He knows when to advance and when to retreat.
He would surely be able to shoulder greater responsibility in the future.
Too bad.
We'll have to see if he has the skills to compete.
[Longevity and Benevolence Palace]
I want to go see her.
See who? Lady Zhao?
"Go southwest...
to the protectorate...
to the protectorate office..."
"Three hundred..."
Li Cheng—
Your Highness Prince Yi!
Ninth Princess.
Prince Yi, why are you here?
I just came out from the Grand Literature Library
and was getting ready to leave the palace so I passed by here.
Isn't the Grand Literature Library over there?
From now on, I might not be able to come to the palace often.
From now on, it will indeed be hard for us to see each other.
Oh right! Wait for a while.
This kongming lock is super complicated. I can't unlock it.
I'll just give it back to you. I don't like complicated things like this.
The cheap tricks here in the Eastern Palace are like this kongming lock.
It looks simple, but it's actually complicated.
You should learn to protect yourself no matter what is ahead of you.
Don't ever easily believe in someone.
Do you understand?
Does that mean I can't believe you either?
Greetings, Empress.
Please rise.
I was about to have someone summon you. I didn't expect you to come here instead.
Is that a gift for me?
It turns out you have one, too.
What a coincidence!
This was a congratulatory gift from your Xi State's envoy.
Light and warm.
It's just that the red color is a little too bright.
Your black one is more formal. It fits my taste more.
It's good that you like it.
- That, you said a congratulatory gift from the Xi State's envoy?
- Yes.
What congratulatory gift?
Of course, a gift for your marriage with the crown prince.
Wasn't the crown prince dethroned?
Xiaofeng, you are the crown princess consort of our Li Empire.
You are marrying the crown prince of our empire.
Chengye was indeed removed from his post,
but our Li Empire will have its next crown prince.
Who's going to be the next crown prince then?
No matter who the next crown prince is,
you will always be Li Empire's crown princess consort.
You just have to wait for marriage.
I want to go home!
I don't want to go anywhere else!
Mi Luo. Mi Luo.
Let me tell you.
I'm... just like...
that fox stole.
I'm being gifted here,
and then gifted there later.
Gifted here and gifted there.
I want to go home, Mi Luo!
I actually want to go home!
I just want to go home!
I miss my dad.
I miss my mom.
My name is Qu Xiaofeng.
You know that I don't want to get married over there! I only want to remain here in the grassland!
You said before
that you cared for me the most.
- Be good.
- Mi Luo, I want to go home.
I want to go home...
Is Xiaofeng here?
This place is a drinking house.
People who come in to drink are my guests.
I only answer the questions of my guests.
I don't have time to joke around with you.
Is Xiaofeng here or not?
Come in, drink a glass of wine, and I'll answer your question.
Tell me.
She didn't come here.
General Pei!
General Pei, slow down!
Are you all right?
This wine of mine has a nickname called "Fall in Half a Jug."
You drank a whole jug in one breath and drank it so quickly.
How could you not get drunk?
I don't have time for this nonsense with you.
Don't worry. She'll be all right.
She was indeed here?!
Was it Gu Jian who took Xiaofeng away?
I believe that Gu Jian will make sure Xiaofeng is safe.
You don't understand anything.
I...
How could I not understand?
I should have let you drink two jugs.
♫ The night has yet to fade ♫
♫ The cold moonlight shines on the window ♫
♫ Matters of the past life ♫
♫ are carefully being considered ♫
♫ A long dream ♫
♫ Yet always gathering and separating into uncertainty ♫
♫ Watery eyes are wishing for your return ♫
♫ Wounds have frosted in my heart ♫
♫ Can't forget your image in my mind ♫
♫ Looking back to our first meeting ♫
♫ That first moment when we saw each other ♫
♫ Can't hold onto the fingertips that you've extended ♫
♫ Parting shattered the heart ♫
♫ Useless tears for the person isn't coming back ♫
♫ The River of Oblivion ♫
♫ Silently gazes unto the troubles of the mundane world ♫
♫ Time reverses ♫
♫ With a sip to forget love ♫
♫ If we meet for the first time again, who are we returning to ♫
♫ Fall goes and spring comes again ♫
♫ Dream and awakening are just in cycle ♫
♫ The night has yet to fade ♫
♫ The cold moonlight shines on the window ♫
♫ Matters of the past life ♫
♫ are carefully being considered ♫
♫ A long dream ♫
♫ Yet always gathering and separating into uncertainty ♫
♫ Watery eyes are wishing for your return ♫
♫ Parting shattered the heart ♫
♫ Useless tears for the person isn't coming back ♫
♫ The River of Oblivion ♫
♫ Silently gazes unto the troubles of the mundane world ♫
♫ Time reverses ♫
♫ With a sip to forget love ♫
♫ If we meet for the first time again, who are we returning to ♫
♫ Parting shattered the heart ♫
♫ Useless tears for the person isn't coming back ♫
♫ The River of Oblivion ♫
♫ Silently gazes unto the troubles of the mundane world ♫
♫ Time reverses ♫
♫ With a sip to forget love ♫
♫ If we meet for the first time again, who are we returning to ♫
♫ Fall goes and spring comes again ♫
♫ Dream and awakening are just in cycle ♫