♫ As dusk starts, I look at the setting sun in the horizon ♫
♫  I faintly remember the outline of your face ♫
♫  After all, it can't be helped to feel more sentimental
when one reminisces  ♫
♫  I sigh softly at our happy times ♫
♫  The night hasn't ended, so many stars fall into the
rim of my eyes  ♫
♫  Collecting a soft and gentle light  ♫
♫ The sky is clear, the scenery are good ♫
♫ If you're not by my side ♫
♫ So what if I can go up the Firmament ♫
♫ The boat passes an empty harbor and feeds the loneliness ♫
♫ Frost falls over the wilderness, drooping the tears ♫
♫ Who caused my sun to fall from the sky ♫
♫ It’s your face that took away my entire light ♫
♫  For only you are my heaven ♫
[Goodbye My Princess]
[Episode 48]
Imperial Father, everything I said is the truth. It's Minister Gao. Minister Gao had bribed them.
As the head proctor, Gao Yuming violated the law and disrupted the exam system by buying and selling court positions.
He allowed countless mediocre or useless candidates to serve in the government.
If even you are blinded by those who ignore the law of the land,
allowing them to violate the rules and shake the country's foundation,
one day we will lose the heart of the people; and therefore, the country.
Leave!
I've stayed comfortably on my crown prince position for 20 some years.
I've never said "no" to you, Imperial Father.
I don't understand why you don't want to clear up the case.
Are you ignoring the laws so you can protect those criminals?
Do you really want to be known as a fatuous emperor by history?
I don't have your cold-bloodedness.
Father is being arbitrary. You don't want to know the truth.
Maybe when the party of Gao has taken over the Li Empire,
you will finally understand what I'm saying.
Today, I saw everyone kneeling at the court.
I still feel glad about it whenever I think about it.
That's showing off too much.
It's not advantageous for us to show all our strength.
Didn't you see that the emperor still wanted the crown prince to investigate me?
Father, the crown prince is on our side.
I used to think that even though he called you uncle,
he was still distant from us by a few layers.
After today, I think I was too narrow-minded.
That Zong Hwan should be easy. After all, he is one of our people.
We just need to prepare some gold and jewelry, pass the word, and this matter is done.
Frame this calligraphy and send it to Zong Hwan.
"There are lots of people but only a few who really know me."
(T/N: From the poem "Entrusting my Sentiments to Bingzhou" by Xue Neng)
"If one doesn't have a bosom friend, he will end up loving wine."
"I always fear that without you here, there won't be any fun in living."
"It was a waste how my younger years were spent in Bingzhou."
Father, this is...
Zong Hwan has high integrity.
He's made many enemies these past years in court.
Without my recommendation and promotion,
he would not have reached his present-day glory.
Even though he has been a government official for many years,
I think he is still proud of his virtues.
To this kind of person, money will create the opposite effect.
This calligraphy is to remind him not to ever forget
how a poor but talented person reached where he is today.
As for the money, use it on the family of those scholars that committed suicide.
Seal their mouths tightly.
Father, you are really smart.
Who does that Xi Qingzhuo think he is to dispute you?
We should think of something to straighten him up.
Just an old stubborn scholar. No need to waste anything on him.
The key point is, where did that bloodletter come from?
Should we look into those that followed the previous Crown Prince Li Chengji?
Old Master! Old Master.
What is it?
Prime Minister Gao has sent you a calligraphy painting.
Good, let's take a look.
Old Master, look.
"There are lots of people but only a few who really know me."
"If one doesn't have a bosom friend, he will end up loving wine."
"I always fear that without you here, there won't be any fun in living."
"It was a waste of how my younger years were spent in Bingzhou."
Gao Yuming is truly smart.
He knows I will not accept gold or precious items.
So, he sent over this calligraphy
to remind me to repay his recognition of me.
Gao Yuming, Gao Yuming...
You should never have
written down the words "Bingzhou."
Master, should we hang it up?
- Put it in storage.
- Yes, Old Master.
Xiaowu, I caught one!
I caught... I caught... I caught...
I caught...
The rock is so slippery.
No need, I'll do it myself.
Why hasn't A'Du returned? It's been a long time.
We didn't get any fish either. We can only wait for A'Du to bring some yams back.
We'll bake them together later.
All right.
The water is too cold. I shouldn't have let you get into it to catch fish.
It's all right.
Come.
My hands are warmer.
A'Du.
I really feel that I'm lucky.
I initially thought that here in the Central Plains that you were my only loved one.
But now, there's also Gu Xiaowu.
I thank Heaven for letting me find him again.
For remembering him.
What else can I ask for?
A'Du, look. There are so many stars in the sky.
But I still don't think that they are as bright as the ones in Xi State.
Li Chengyin, I'm going back to Xi State soon.
Gu Xiaowu!
Gu Xiaowu! Gu Xiaowu! Gu Xiaowu!
Your Imperial Highness, although the crown princess consort was taken by the assassin,
it's good that we now know
she is all right.
Zhao, do you think Xiaofeng has been taken away
or that she really wanted to leave?
Your Imperial Highness, you are overthinking. Crown Princess Consort has always been full of ideas.
She probably has her thoughts on why she did it.
She has usually been so simple-minded,
but so full of mischievous ideas. She loved causing trouble
and so stubborn like a bull.
Her stubbornness not only brought her trouble.
Sometimes, she was able to hit the right path and helped us big time.
But I didn't want her to get involved in our conflicts.
I only wanted her to stay simple-minded every day.
I only wanted her to fight with me,
argue with me, make a ruckus every day.
I only wanted... her to stay in the Eastern Palace
and wait for me to return.
Zhao, could it be she doesn't like Shangjing?
Does she want to return to Xi State?
Do you feel homesick?
Yes... I do when I feel happy,
and I do when I feel sad.
So, are you feeling happy or sad now?
Happy!
Do you have a problem?
None.
Rest early. We'll leave the city first thing in the morning.
Xiaowu, I'm thinking that it would be the Shangyuan Festival soon.
Why don't we leave after the festival instead?
The longer we stay here, the easier it will be for the guards to find us.
Also, there are so many people during the Shangyuan Festival. It is not convenient for us to go out in the streets.
Why so? There will surely be a lot of people out in the streets that day.
If we mixed within the crowd, it would be harder to be noticed.
Also, other than grilling fish and roasting yams,
we haven't eaten anything else these past two days.
I want to go to Mi Luo's place and have a good meal.
Are you unable to put Li Chengyin down?
No such thing. Now that I know that you are Gu Xiaowu,
I won't allow my heart to have someone else.
What if I wasn't Gu Xiaowu?
How could you not be Gu Xiaowu?
You clearly look the same as the man in my dream.
Also, you have the scent of Xi State on you. That can't fool anyone, right?
Xiaowu, I don't want to leave this place so hastily.
Can't we say farewell to this place in a magnanimous manner before leaving?
Okay. After the Shangyuan Festival, we will immediately leave.
Xiaowu, believe me. I will always stay by your side.
We will be together forever. I promise.
"From late night 'til dawn,"
(T/N: From the poem "Encourage Learning" by Yan Zhen Qing)
"It's the best time for the youth to study."
"Not knowing they should study hard when they were young."
"They will regret as they turn old."
Teacher, you said, "From late night until dawn was the best time to study."
But late at night, my mother is still busy in weaving and cultivating silkworms.
And at dawn, my father gets up to pasture cattle and plow the fields.
They can't read or write.
You will have cloth only by weaving and cultivating silkworms.
And you will have food by pasturing cattle and plowing fields.
Teacher, if we have clothes to wear and food to eat,
why do we still need to study?
A scholar, even if he doesn't have enough to eat or wear,
he will not feel miserable.
This is because a gentleman will persevere in the face of difficulty.
The more knowledge one has, the higher one will stand, and his horizon will be broadened.
He will no longer pay attention to a comfortable life and secular magnificence.
When your mind is occupied with the country, you will only focus on
peace and misery; these two things.
Teacher, what are peace and misery?
Peace, when people have enough to eat and wear.
Misery is when people don't have enough to eat and wear.
I understand now. A learned person doesn't care about his own happiness,
but other people's happiness.
To become a gentleman, one needs to work hard for peace on Earth.
Well said!
But not all learned men are gentlemen.
When you're growing up, you have to learn to be a real gentleman.
A true gentleman lives for his aspiration and dies for his aspiration.
Yes, Teacher!
Let's go! Let's go!
Let's go. Going home!
Hurry!
Let's go!
Catch up!
Slow down!
It's a blessing that in my life, I've lived like a gentleman.
Father, we found that grand preceptor that you asked me to search for.
It's just that when we found him, he had already committed suicide.
His corpse is even hanging inside his house.
It looks like he just died recently.
I fear that he knew long before that we'd go find him.
This matter is indeed not that simple.
Who is this person behind the scenes? The crown prince?
The crown prince? No way.
The emperor?
I fear that someone has long started a slow fire to stew something, while we thought all along that it was just cooking soup.
Write to your brother.
If we want to end this matter with us being safe, we can only rely on him
in earning us merit from His Imperial Majesty.
[Protectorate General Office]
Yuan Tong!
I'm here!
- General.
- How much money do we still have? Do we have 20,000 taels?
Replying to General. I fear that we can't come up with that much immediately.
Swallow it down first.
Hasn't the salary for last month not been distributed yet?
It doesn't seem proper to touch that.
Why not?
Don't worry. In a few days, there will be money to fill the gap.
Since Danchi has been eliminated, it's been so long since we played a good act.
What General means is...
Do this. Immediately come up with the money.
Write the king of Shuobo a secret message.
Tell him that I want to invite him for a drink.
My Lord, an urgent report from the Western Border Protectorate General Office. The Shuobo Tribe was able to conquer the three cities
Huaibian, Xizhu, and Youshan in just one whole day.
How is that possible? Any news from the Protectorate General Office?
The two parties fought, but the Western Border Protectorate General Office couldn't resist them and was forced to retreat.
What is this Gao Xian trying to do?
My Lord, are we going to go there and provide reinforcement?
No. Order the whole army to be on guard and stay put.
- Let's wait for what Shangjing will say.
- Yes.
Xiaofeng wants to wait after the Shangyuan Festival before returning to Xi State.
What? We can't do so.
The more we delay it, the more it would be dangerous. You better convince the ninth princess not to do so.
Let us just satisfy her wish.
She has to truly let go of everything here.
I have thought about it. We can use the disturbance during the Shangyuan Festival
to directly leave the city through the Bearing the Heaven Gate.
Usually, when there are few people, it will be harder to go out of the city.
Okay.
What? Shuobo is suddenly making rebellious movements?
What then are the people of the Protectorate General Office doing?
Where is Gao Xian?
Your Imperial Majesty, this is an urgent memorial from General Gao.
What sandstorm?! Not enough rations, soldiers, and horses?!
Why did he not report this before?! He only thought of reporting it now!
What has Gao Xian been doing?!
Your Imperial Majesty, on behalf of my son, I ask for punishment.
May Your Imperial Majesty take back Gao Xian's military badge and be reassigned.
Your Imperial Majesty, there is an urgent war at the borders now. General Gao lost the first battle.
However, he has numerous experiences when it comes to the war at the border.
He is the only choice in pacifying the uprising of the Shuobo Tribe. As long as we send over more rations and military equipment,
there is still a chance to pacify the Shuobo uprising.
I ask Your Imperial Majesty to punish me for my crime.
Prime Minister Gao, what crime have you committed?
In the rebellion of Shuobo, Gao Xian is the main commander, yet he failed to resist the enemy.
I am his father.
I was unable to teach my son well and that is my first crime. I am the head of the cabinet of the current empire.
The army garrisoned in the Western Border lacks rations and men.
I failed to know this and that is an oversight of mine. That's my second crime.
May Your Imperial Majesty punish me sternly.
Prime Minister, please rise.
Prime Minister Gao, I know of your loyalty.
Promulgate my decree! Gao Xian is being promoted to Far Subduing Generalissimo.
Rations and military equipment must be immediately supplied to his army.
I hope Generalissimo can successfully pacify the uprising of Shuobo.
Thank you for Your Imperial Majesty's graces.
Your Imperial Majesty is wise!
When I was still a prince,
I frequently told bold statements to my imperial brothers,
as if I could do anything.
I always felt that I could obtain the empire in front of me just by extending my hand.
But after I ascended to the throne,
I realized that I totally can't clearly see
how this empire looks like. I also couldn't clearly see
what position in this empire should an emperor be standing.
Tell me. Am I...
still the son of Heaven?
Of course, you are.
I dare not guess the intentions of Your Imperial Majesty,
but I know that you are the son of Heaven.
The reason that one is the son of Heaven
is not only because he has complied to the will of his citizens, but more because he has complied to the will of Heaven.
Since it is complying with the will of Heaven, Your Imperial Majesty is naturally standing above this empire.
No one can waver the position that the will of Heaven has bestowed you.
Zong Huan, let me be frank with you.
I only have one question for you.
Why did you stop investigating the case about the imperial civil examinees?
Does Minister Xi not know that this is an order from the emperor?
It was His Imperial Majesty who halted the investigation?
When did His Imperial Majesty make such a decree?
I did not know that there was a new decree.
Some of the decrees of His Imperial Majesty may be written in books,
some on his face, and some are even written on his heart.
Minister Xi, you should know that the war in the northwestern region is quite intense.
His Imperial Majesty has to rely on the power of Prime Minister Gao in the northwest.
What official position do we have?
Do you want to throw eggs on a stone, or seek for your own destruction?
Self-preservation. An ant is greedy to survive.
Perhaps a scholar's conscience no longer exists.
Xi Qingzhuo, as a scholar, my conscience is no less than yours.
Then, do you still remember the case of the exam candidates who were wronged and driven to death?
The oldest one who kept failing the exam
and finally died uncleared of a false charge in Bingzhou,
he was Old Master Mu, your first teacher.
How did you find out about this?
To tell you the truth. That night,
the bloodletter that appeared in my study room, a note was attached to it.
It listed in detail all the seven scholars' life history and all the names of their friends and relatives.
In the section of Old Master Mu,
I discovered your name.
That's why in the court that day, when the crown prince recommended you to investigate the case,
all the court ministers thought that you were Minister Gao's man.
So the case would be concluded without a conclusion. Only me...
I was still holding on to a glimmer of hope.
I imagined that you would look up to books of the sages with great respect.
And that you didn't forget to honor the teacher and respect his teaching and knew the meanings of righteousness and loyalty.
Too bad. How could the empty fame of a scholar
win against the official hat of the minister of the Ministry of Personnel?
It is exactly because I have once read all those books by sages
and spent so many years of hard work and arduous training in the political arena;
that's why I will not be like a pedantic old man like you,
who only knows to show off a moment of strength
and eventually cause the eternal loss of the last hope of exonerating those scholars.
You... You are...
What you?! Did I say anything wrong?!
Do you think that in investigating a case, one must openly wear a flag and beat the drums?
If everyone was as rash as you, so many innocent people would have died
even before the investigation of this case had finished.
I knew it! I knew it!
I wasn't wrong about you.
Okay already. Leave.
Are you mad at me?
I am apologizing to you now. Sorry.
How could I have so much idle time to be angry?
Do you not know that the people of Gao Manor have been keeping a watchful eye on me?
Oh...
If needed, I have to do an act for everyone to see.
I understand.
Minister Xi, may I trouble you to write down a list of names when you go back.
Send your most trusted aide to deliver it to me.
I will send people to follow that clue and immediately rush to Bingzhou
for a thorough investigation.
Okay already. Leave. Do you really want me to expel you out?
I'll go. I'll go.
Minister Xi, put on an act.
Put on an act!
You villain! You are such a coward!
Take care.
Stop!
[Gate Pass from the Ministry of Personnel]
- Where are you going?
- Bingzhou.
Let him pass!
Father, I heard earlier that Xi Qingzhuo went to look for Zong Huan,
yet he ended up being kicked out of there.
He was so mad that he kept cursing outside the manor of Zong Huan for an hour.
During the Shangyuan Festival, there will be so many people out in the streets.
Gu Jian might use this chance to take Xiaofeng out of the city.
I have already sent a lot of men to strictly guard each city gate.
If they are to go out of the city,
returning to Xi State is their only choice.
And this Bearing the Heaven Gate is a path they must take.
I need you to guard it.
I understand.
If they really appear, I will leave Gu Jian to you.
He must not fall into other people's hands.
As for Xiaofeng, I must take her back with me.
I will not let Gu Jian fool around again.
I know. Gu Jian is your disciple. You have always treated him like your own son.
His surname is Gu.Whether based on reason or affection,
I should leave him some dignity.
But if he does not know to mend his ways,
repeatedly doing what he wishes without restraint,
I fear that I do not have such good patience anymore.
You also should not keep being softhearted.
I will surely put the general situation above all.
I must go back now. I still have to enter the palace later.
Your Imperial Highness!
Your Imperial Highness, have you seen Mingyue?
Can you relay a message to her?
What message? Wishes for the holiday?
Mingyue is not an ordinary woman. For so many years, she was able to survive by herself.
At this critical moment, why must you disturb the state of her heart?
You must know that the more you care for her, the harder it is for her to endure palace life.
The hardest thing to do when it comes to familial love is to not mutually drag each other down.
I understand what you mean.
But no matter what, today is a reunion day.
As a father...
Revenge hasn't been sought yet, evil people are in power at the imperial court, my empire's lands are not peaceful,
there are unending problems both internally and externally. How could we still speak about reunions?
For us, the Shangyuan Festival
is just the same as every other day of the past.
Old Master!
Come in.
Crown Prince sent a secret message.
[...there must be an inside story regarding the uprising of Shuobo. Find evidence of the collusion between Shuobo and Gao Xian...]
Crown Prince is indeed very sensitive. Immediately give my command
to have people clearly investigate the background of Shuobo and Gao Xian.
Remember, hard evidence must be found.
Yes.
Gao Xian...
It's time for this game of yours of breeding bandits to make yourself eventually look good
to end its performance soon.
Your Imperial Highness has lost quite a bit of weight lately.
This belt is exactly one inch too long now.
Did Your Imperial Highness not sleep well last night?
No, I slept very well.
Even if you don't cherish your own body,
I do worry about it.
I will remember well how considerate and caring you are.
Let the servants do these things. There's no need to tire yourself out.
I have always helped you change into your clothes every time you came.
In addition, today is the Spring Lantern Festival.
Tonight, around 8:00 p.m., Your Imperial Highness, together with the emperor and the empress,
will be climbing up the city tower.
Therefore, I must personally help you put on your robe.
You worked hard.
Your Imperial Highness is becoming more and more polite to me.
People will think we are not familiar with each other.
Today is Shangyuan Festival. There's a cheerful atmosphere inside and outside of the palace.
Only the crown princess consort is still missing.
That really is making people worry.
She was supposed to accompany you to climb up the city gate today.
Crown Princess Consort is not here. She doesn't have the good fortune to enjoy the people's adoration.
You've only lived in the forest for a few days, but you can't bear to part with it now?
That's right. Even the best palace
can't compare to the relaxation I had with this forest you found.
The future is long. We will live this kind of lifestyle.
What? Looking down on me?
You think that I am used to life in the palace,
so I've forgotten how I was the boundless ninth princess of Xi State?
I wouldn't dare. Even the palace can't hold back that wild heart of yours.
A'Du, why are you nodding? When did you go on his side?
A'Du is the fairest one.
A'Du, you are my good sister. How could you be helping him?
Do the two of you have some kind of special relationship that I am not aware of?
Don't jest with A'Du anymore. Be careful that when A'Du gets angry,
you will be done for once her gold knife is unsheathed.
That's not possible. A'Du treats me the best.
She doesn't lie to me nor conceal the truth from me. She lets me win at leaf card games.
How can she pull a knife at me?
Let's head out while it's still early.
Go visit all the places you want to see.
Settle all the issues you need to settle.
I do need to say my farewell to this place.
Are there any clues to the whereabouts of the crown princess consort?
Imperial Father, I am too incapable. There is no progress.
I bumped into Prime Minister Gao a few days ago and asked for his advice.
According to him, the assassin that took the crown princess consort
might be related to the northwest territory. So, I followed his thought pattern,
but still did not have further progress.
I just fear that someone might use the opportunity when the northwest is unstable
to add dirty water into the situation.
Maybe, these past few days, the prime minister has been worrying about the Shuobo rebellion, so he couldn't spare the energy.
Crown Prince, you are still thinking too simply.
Pass on my verbal command. Tell Minister Wang Shu of the Court of Judicial Review
to re-interrogate all the important criminals locked up in Celestial Prison.
I don't believe that assassin really didn't leave any trace to be found.
In that case, I worry that will destabilize our court.
My plan is to let everyone know, especially the ones
who hold important position but do not restrain themselves,
that the might of the imperial family cannot be offended.
Imperial Father is wise!
Imperial Father, I have another small matter needing your advice.
What matter?
Now that the crown princess consort is missing,
who should I bring to climb up the city gate tonight?
Take Related Lady of Excellence Zhao. The Shuobo matter caused a big disruption in the northwest.
It's important to assuage the Zhao family's
forces in Danchi.
Yes, I understand.
Is Yongniang here?
Related Lady of Excellence, I heard from the lady-in-waiting of Bearing Graces Hall
that Yongniang received the crown prince's orders and went to retrieve the clothing.
She's probably going to be here soon.
Yongniang understands what's important. She won't get into trickery.
If she said she was going to retrieve the outfit, then she surely did.
Related Lady of Excellence, Yongniang is here.
Greetings to Related Lady of Excellence Zhao.
Yongniang, please stand.
Jin'er, hurry up and get the clothes from Yongniang. Be careful and not dirty them.
Yes.
My Lady, this is an auspicious gown worn by the crown princess consort when she wed into the Eastern Palace.
It was hand-sewn based on the crown princess consort's measurements.
I followed orders and brought it to Qingluan Hall today.
But after you are done with it, you have to return it to Bearing Graces Hall.
Since it belongs to Bearing Graces Hall, it also belongs to the Eastern Palace.
How could we talk about returning it or not?
It's only a piece of clothing.
My Lady is right. It's only a piece of clothing.
Yongniang, you are really loyal to the crown princess consort.
It's so touching. But you should save your loyalty
to show your mistress when she gets back.
It's my duty to be loyal to the crown princess consort.
I especially am an expert in teaching palace rules.
That's why I know the best about doing what's appropriate in one's position. Never going out of bounds.
You've brought the clothes here. As for the rules you talk about,
it's best to teach them to those who were born in the Western Border and do not understand etiquette.
I will take my leave.
The jeweled accessories look so ridiculously old. Immediately get someone to redo them for a new look.
And this waistline, alter it smaller to fit me.
♫ The night has yet to fade ♫
♫ The cold moonlight shines on the window ♫
♫ Matters of the past life ♫
♫ are carefully being considered ♫
♫ A long dream ♫
♫ Yet always gathering and separating into uncertainty ♫
♫ Watery eyes are wishing for your return ♫
♫ Wounds have frosted in my heart ♫
♫ Can't forget your image in my mind ♫
♫ Looking back to our first meeting ♫
♫ That first moment when we saw each other ♫
♫ Can't hold onto the fingertips that you've extended ♫
♫ Parting shattered the heart ♫♫
♫ Useless tears for the person isn't coming back ♫
♫ The River of Oblivion ♫
♫ Silently gazes unto the troubles of the mundane world ♫
♫ Time reverses ♫
♫ With a sip to forget love ♫
♫ If we meet for the first time again, who are we returning to ♫
♫ Fall goes and spring comes again ♫
♫ Dream and awakening are just in cycle ♫
♫ The night has yet to fade ♫
♫ The cold moonlight shines on the window ♫
♫ Matters of the past life ♫
♫ are carefully being considered ♫
♫ A long dream ♫
♫ Yet always gathering and separating into uncertainty ♫
♫ Watery eyes are wishing for your return ♫
♫ Parting shattered the heart ♫
♫ Useless tears for the person isn't coming back ♫
♫ The River of Oblivion ♫
♫ Silently gazes unto the troubles of the mundane world ♫
♫ Time reverses ♫
♫ With a sip to forget love ♫
♫ If we meet for the first time again, who are we returning to ♫
♫ Parting shattered the heart ♫
♫ Useless tears for the person isn't coming back ♫
♫ The River of Oblivion ♫
♫ Silently gazes unto the troubles of the mundane world ♫
♫ Time reverses ♫
♫ With a sip to forget love ♫
♫ If we meet for the first time again, who are we returning to ♫
♫ Fall goes and spring comes again ♫
♫ Dream and awakening are just in cycle ♫