Dreamy eyes.
An innocent face.
Smooth skin,
and lips that is always
ready to be kissed.
She is Azi Acosta.
In every scene,
every moan,
desire wraps around our entire body
whenever we watch her.
Hi… I’m Stephanie Raz.
And now, I’ll be with you
on a passionate trip
where you’ll feel
the body, emotions,
and allure of Azi Acosta
until the final moan.
We’ll take a sneak peak
at her movie scenes
you can never forget.
This is…
PASILIP NI AZI: The Steamiest Moments
of Azi Acosta.
Come, let’s take a look.
Having lots of money feels good!
It makes you want to
travel and go places.
You’ll never have
to worry about your fare.
And if we’re talking about
Azi’s steamiest scenes,
why go far?
Let’s start with the film where
she had her very first lead role…
Pamasahe.
And the buzz is…
this is very popular among seafarers.
Hmm... I wonder why!
Come,
let’s take another peek at
the scenes to find out why.
You know what?
I always hear them
doing it in the next room.
Since then,
I've been sneaking a peek at them
whenever they're going at it.
God, they were doing
all sorts of things
in different positions!
I used to be jealous of Shiony.
I said to myself,
it must be nice to have a man.
Shiony seems to enjoy it a lot
when my brother's
ramming into her.
I just bite my lips from envy.
This next steamy scene
you’re about to watch
comes with a view and is
definitely visually appealing!
She’s in the scene with Felix Roco.
I want you to do to me
what you do to Shiony.
What?
We knew it was wrong.
We were living in sin.
But what should never happen,
happened between us.
We were so attracted
to each other
until it got to a point
where we were
having sex a lot.
Especially since
Shiony wasn't around.
This next encounter will make you wet.
One of her scene partners
is the veteran actor
Mark Anthony Fernandez.
Come,
let’s watch them together and get soaked!
Sorry.
You're probably thinking
I took advantage of you.
I was just carried away
by your stories
and the cold weather.
No,
no need for that.
I felt it back on the bus.
I knew we'll end up here.
A man wouldn't approach
a girl like me
without an agenda.
Am I right?
Fess up.
I caught you looking.
You were peeking at my nips
while my baby sucked on them.
Do you like sex and games?
If yes,
then you’ll definitely enjoy
what I’m about to show you next.
In her movie Sex Games,
there are games that are intricate
yet sensual.
Are you ready to play with a
woman with no experience?
But once Shiela gives it her all,
she’s all in on the game
and she’ll drain every bit of your energy!
I love you, Shiela...
I love you too Alvin...
Some hearts lose because of lust.
In her movie Suki,
a stripper and a gigolo confess
their feelings to each other
on a night of seduction.
But first,
let’s take a peek at Eva
doing some pole dancing.
Sir Max!
Have a seat, Sir.
Have a seat.
Take a look at Eba.
She's so sexy, isn't she?
Tell me, Sir Max.
What do you need?
Once she's done.
Take her directly to
the VIP Room, okay?
You already know, Sir Max.
You're too generous.
After Eba's set.
Take her directly to the VIP Room.
Sir Max?
Oh yes! He's a generous tipper.
- I know, right?
- I got you.
Is it love
or maybe
you’re just lusting after each other?
In Pantasya ni Tami,
we’ll see a different kind of role-playing
the kind with costumes,
wigs, and sometimes props.
Most of the time, they imitate
fictional or anime characters.
They’re called cosplayers.
Let’s take a look at Tami
and her unforgettable fantasies!
Hold on, Ken.
Don’t worry, I’ll be very gentle.
The cosplay queen
who gives service using
only her body and camera
But behind the costumes…
is a woman searching for true love.
It feels so good, Ken.
[music fades]
It feels good to be the object of fantasy
but it feels even better when
someone loves you behind your mask.
Just like this hot and
passion-filled love scene
between Tami and Gelo,
played by Ali Asistio.
If beauty alone can’t
make someone love you,
what if
you try something else…
like
a love potion?
In the film Huwad,
Azi Acosta plays Romina
a wife who’s been cheated on…
but she didn’t play the martyr.
Instead,
she sought out a love potion.
Because for her,
if love won’t come naturally…
maybe it can be forced…
or
get intoxicated with lust.
Romina, come over here.
[heavy breathing]
[phone ringing]
Hello?
Everyone falls under Romina’s spell,
thirsty, burning with desire for her,
including women.
Her potion had a strange effect…
it drove everyone crazy for her.
The only problem?
It didn’t work on her husband…
but it did work on his mistress!
Romina! Romina stop it!
Lando! Get your hands off me!
Did you know how much
you two have hurt me?
My family is nearly ruined!
Romina, calm down.
Romina, stop it…
It’s not just me that you hurt me!
You hurt her too!
[sobbing]
Romina… Forgive me, please,
forgive me Romina…
Forgive me!
It’s not you who should be asking
for forgiveness, it should be him…
Lando… Is this the woman you love?
[heavy breathing]
What does she have
that I don’t?
Sue, you’re also mine now.
[moaning]
[panting]
Romina! Stop it! That’s enough!
Lando, let us be!
[moaning]
[heavy breathing]
In the next scenes,
there are no love involved
just purely transactional.
In the film Sugar Baby,
two women enter a world of luxury
in exchange of their bodies.
Azi is willing to do anything
for the right price,
alongside VMX crush Robb Guinto.
So, game? Me first.
Let's put it here.
Will it not spill?
It won't spill.
I'll put it in here.
Then, bite this one.
That's right.
It's my shot, okay?
You see, it's easy.
Now it's your turn.
You're still sweet.
Azi and Robb share an even
hotter scene in Sugar Baby.
Like this one…
You’ve always known
that even back then
you’re the one that I want.
I no longer know what I want.
Remember?
This was your favorite, right?
It’s truly satisfying to indulge
in money you’ve worked hard for…
especially when you’re with your friend.
Just like sex,
it’s even better when you have company.
But they say the feeling is something else
when there are three of you
Mara, you’re drunk.
I’ll be going.
No...
In Erotica Manila,
an old movie theater
becomes the gateway
to an unusual experience.
Azi plays the woman
who opens Gab’s eyes
not just to lust,
but to reality,
hotter than any film.
Let’s call it… Cinema Parausan.
What's this?
I'm trying something.
Didn't you say, not
'til after the screening?
Cinematic Experience.
- Hey! You two!
- What are you doing, huh?
- Hands up!
- Why? Wait!
So what?
We've done nothing wrong!
We're just here to watch
Celso Ad Castillo's opus!
Don't you know that "Isla"
is the greatest contribution
to Filipino Erotica?
Too bad—they got
caught in the theater.
But don’t worry,
you won’t be left hanging this time…
because they’re going all the way
to the climax.
Are you ready for the last
movie I’m going to show you?
Let’s watch how bold
and scorching Azi can get
in Call Me Alma.
Shit!
Whew… that was hot, right?
But admit it
with all her scenes,
you’re still left wanting more.
Because Azi…
isn’t just an actress.
She’s a fire you can’t help but play with,
even if you know you might get burned.
Until the next sneak peek…
I’m Stephanie Raz,
and this is…
Pasilip ni Azi.
The Steamiest Moments
of Azi Acosta.
Go cool yourself down for now.