=The Girl Inside Me=
=Episode 22=
What happened last night?
After you said that you wanted a bath,
Duke Dingjun was sent home
completely wasted.
Then the three of you
got even more hyped.
Your Highness, be careful.
Don't touch me, or I'll kill you.
Tell me how many stars there are.
One, two, three, four,
five, six...
So many.
Stars.
One thousand.
One hundred.
Tell me how many stars there are.
One thousand.
One hundred.
One thousand, right?
No, one thousand.
Why did you hit him?
Don't hold him. He's mine.
Don't hold him.
He's mine.
Mine.
Step aside.
He's mine.
Shut up, you're talking drunk.
Better keep it to yourself.
Rest assured, Your Highness.
I sealed Young Master Chu's
acupoints last night.
What about me and Xiaoxiao?
I forgot.
Flowers for sale.
Sweet and tasty pastries.
- Miss, take a look.
- Okay.
I'm out to look around.
Why are you following me?
The Sixth Lord could kill you
at any moment, you know?
I-I feel safe around you.
Look at this guy.
Why are they so strange?
Who are they?
Are we being too conspicuous?
Who cares as long as
the Sixth Lord's people
don't recognize you?
The Fairy Temple
outside the city is quite popular.
Those nobles would spend a fortune
just to be the first to offer incense.
Exactly.
Everyone started worshiping the fairy
after she descended.
What a commercial mindset.
How dare you commit fraud in my name?
Let me find out who you are.
Fairy Temple Registration Place.
We must get registered?
(Fairy Temple Registration Place)
Sir, we need to be registered?
Of course, the fairy and the master
are both very busy.
It's 100 taels per person
to get registered.
So expensive.
Go home if you don't have money.
Pay him. Let's find out who they are.
Okay.
Have some tea over there.
You'll be registered in a second.
Please enjoy your tea.
Thank you.
Fairy Temple.
Why are there two of you?
And there are two of you.
So dizzy.
We fell into his trap.
I'm afraid we're in serious trouble.
Nonsense. Chu.
Won't you do the introductions?
Good for you.
You have a fairy in your family.
My lord, this is between you and me.
Don't drag her into this.
Just come at me.
How can you say that? It hurts.
I sincerely admire your talent.
My lord, why don't you get to the point?
Alright, that little trick
you two pulled the other night
wasn't in my favor.
But I demand you two do it again.
As for my purpose,
I don't think you need
any further clarification.
Do your job and you'll get
all the wealth in the world
and all the prettiest partners.
What do you say?
Really?
Yeah.
But I'm not interested. How about you?
I have fantasized about it.
But not anymore.
You haven't figured it out.
Then I will give you some time
to think it over.
But you only have one day.
If you still can't figure it out,
Fei Teng, please help them.
With pleasure.
They both look exhausted.
Help them loosen up first.
Alright.
I pay my respects.
Did you find them?
Not yet.
How did they disappear without a trace?
We've dispatched the martial artists,
but there are no clues.
I suspect that it has something to do
with the Fairy Temple.
Look into it and keep an eye
on the Mansion of Lord Zhennan.
- Understood.
Xiaoxiao, I'm sorry.
I failed to protect you.
You think I need your protection?
Chu Xiaoran, you must live on.
The princess is waiting for you.
I don't know if we can get through this.
I don't want to lie to myself anymore.
Actually, the person I like is...
♪A strand of light
cast through my paper window♪
♪Like snow, buried deep in my heart♪
♪Who carved out your silhouette♪
♪Adding a stroke of heavy makeup♪
♪This love is hard to weigh or measure♪
♪Just like you, indescribable♪
♪Wordless, look at the dark-blue sky♪
♪In a moment of madness
at the cloud's edge♪
♪Travelers glare at the bright moon♪
♪People in the tower
have no clue about the world outside♪
♪Let this day be etched
in the painting of life♪
I've finally given away my first kiss.
Chu Xiaoran, don't overthink it.
That kiss was meant to
make up for a regret in my life.
I don't belong here. You know that.
♪The southwest wind blows,
scattering sparks cold as ice♪
♪Retreating deep
into the midst of longing♪
I told you this guy was trouble.
They have forbidden love.
Listen, I can agree to your terms.
But you must release him first.
Don't you know me?
I guarantee that as long as
you accomplish this task for me,
I'll release both you and your brother.
Do you think I'm a fool?
I'm the only one who can do this.
I'll watch you send him away.
Otherwise, I will
bite my tongue to kill myself.
Xiaoxiao.
Go ahead. Show me.
Alright, just kidding.
Don't...
Let's do it your way.
♪Preserve the fireworks for eternity♪
♪Is a lifetime enough to suffice♪
♪Turn the lens of time
for a retrospective glance♪
♪I am willing to stand by and wait♪
♪I spent half my life
in pursuit of freedom♪
♪Yet I was mocked
and urged to walk away♪
♪When I forget
what I've been seeking, can I still♪
♪Wait for time to reverse
and inscribe my heartache♪
♪Open the box of time
and turn the hourglass♪
♪Sing praises of my bravery,
steadfast through the years♪
♪The butterfly hiding within
is finally saved♪
♪The encounter in the fairy tale
turns out to be fictitious♪
♪A multitude of thoughts
arise in a moment♪
♪In the end, I let them
drift away on their own♪
♪Emotions are like a river flowing♪
♪How many withered flowers
have been greeted♪
♪Piecing together fragments of memory,
revisiting old places♪
♪Tracing the source of time♪
♪All the past is but a prelude,
for the sake of nostalgia only♪
♪A multitude of thoughts
arise in a moment♪
♪In the end, I let them
drift away on their own♪
♪Emotions are like a river flowing♪
♪How many withered flowers
have been greeted♪
♪Let thoughts be fickle
as time flows backward♪
♪Piecing together fragments of memory,
revisiting old places♪
♪Tracing the source of time♪
♪All the past is but a prelude,
for the sake of nostalgia only♪
♪All the past is but a prelude♪
♪For the sake of nostalgia only♪