[theme music playing]
GENIE, MAKE A WISH
[sighs, scoffs]
[whooshing]
[Ka-young sighs]
You were gone all night. Where did you go?
I distinctly remember saying
I'd go change--
[breath trembles]
What's wrong? What is it?
I was paid a visit just now…
[screams]
[Iblis] …by a boy who gave me
my memories back.
[breath shudders]
I caused you to--
[cries]
My arrogance resulted in…
I saw it all. Everything.
[Ka-young sighs]
We are living in the now.
That's in the past, all of that.
It doesn't matter anymore.
You can't bring back the dead
or take us to the future.
But the future is happening now.
It's moment to moment.
But always moving.
The past is closed off.
Don't think of before.
But just think of moving forward.
Even if we don't know how it'll end.
[sniffles] All right.
I can do that.
CHOI DA-JIN
ENTER PASSWORD
INCORRECT PASSWORD
You don't remember the password at all?
[laughs in disbelief]
- Okay, stop joking.
- It's not a joke.
It's driving me crazy too.
I honestly can't remember it.
That two-factor authentication bullshit.
Update the password that way.
I tried, but the verification texts
aren't coming and I'm not sure why.
[groans] Da-jin.
Da-jin, stop messing around, seriously!
I don't know what to tell you!
It's like my brain has
a huge hole in it or something!
- [sighs]
- What?
- Oh, damn it.
- A hole?
[typing]
- [error alert beeps]
- No way.
Second wish. You listening?
I wish she not remember anything!
Da-jin forgets everything!
She forgot everything.
The password counted in the wish?
[sighs]
What are we going to do?
[panting] Yeong-hyeon, I'm sorry.
I mean it. I don't know what happened.
Why I changed the password,
oh, it makes no sense, seriously!
Our wedding anniversary, our first date,
your birthday, the day you asked me
to marry you, it's none of those.
[crying]
Hang on.
So, your passwords
were all things like that?
How did I just forget? I'm going crazy.
I swear… [whimpers]
- Come on. [typing]
- [gasps softly]
- [error alert beeps]
- [typing]
[gloomy music playing]
INCORRECT PASSWORD
[crying]
[error alert beeps]
[whimpers]
Da-jin.
It'll be fine.
Your father…
will recover.
Hmm? What did you say?
Wait, where are you going?
- [Mi-ju sighs]
- [door opens]
Ka-young.
What's going on? What is all this?
What's happening?
That bastard dropped your name
to the cops.
- It's all right. It's all right.
- [sighs]
It's going to be all right.
Let's get out of here. You too, Min-ji.
We need to keep you hidden for now.
I know a place.
You're right. We can't let bastards
like him put us in even worse danger.
Hiding is a good idea.
We can discuss more once we're there.
Where is it? Nearby?
[pills rattle]
What about the wake for Heung-Rye…
[Ka-young] I'll make a contribution.
For now, just take this
and get some sleep.
I have to go for a while.
I have to do something to resolve this.
No matter what,
you have to stay here, Grandma.
- Okay?
- All right.
Promise me to be careful.
You're going with her, yes?
Mm-hmm. I am, Oh Pan-geum.
I'll stay with her the whole time.
- That thing I said I'd tell you later…
- Forget it.
Already figured it out.
She's Grandma, I know.
I'll consider this a housewarming.
She and I can make ourselves cozy.
[sighs] You've got a nice home in here,
more or less.
[Sade] Dinner delivery!
- [exhales]
- If you need anything, just tell him.
Sade, protect them with your life.
Yes, Master. I'm on it.
Jjajangmyeon, jjambbong,
- which one do you want?
- A genie, his beast,
and a lamp that looks like
a billionaire's penthouse.
Despite witnessing all of this magic,
I would still like to express
I still think we evolved from monkeys.
Hmm?
Yeah… That's, uh…
Uh, we can discuss that another time.
Why don't you get some rest for now?
Oh, you little…
- Kim Ha-neul, you found your toy, huh?
- Yeah.
See? You found it like I said,
because you had a proper look.
But you had to throw a tantrum,
cry and scream, didn't you?
So where was it? I swear,
we looked all over, up and down.
Ppoppi hid it. He told me where it was.
Come on, Ha-neul. You know Ppoppi
lives on a farm now, like we said.
It's true. Ppoppi whispered it
to me, remember?
In my ear.
- What's wrong?
- [pensive music plays]
[Chauffeur Kim sighs]
[Chauffeur Kim] In a past life, I was
a member of a reconnaissance unit.
I inherited a life-changing sum of money
from an anonymous donor,
someone I do not know.
But I have no recollection
of this happening.
In situations like these,
there are three options. The first one…
Turn it in.
The second option…
NEAT STACK SAFE
Hide it.
[sighs]
The third and final option…
[dog barking]
[panting]
You must have been abandoned.
- Would you like to come with me?
- [whimpers]
I have many others like you at my house.
Ah, but before that,
what should we call you?
Ppoppi.
Yes, Ppoppi sounds great.
[chuckles softly]
- [whimpers]
- Chauffeur Choi.
All right. Let's get going.
I chose the third option.
It's strange. Though I long for answers,
I feel I will be forever waiting for them.
The anonymous still have names.
I'm currently an abandoned dog detective.
My duty is to find those of you
who have abandoned your pets.
[door opens]
[Wahid] Have you still not made
your decision?
Well, that just won't do.
[choking]
I don't know why you're pushing off
the inevitable like this.
All you need to do right now is sing
the world to sleep this very minute!
[choking]
You better follow Father's orders
so Iblis can be tied up for good.
- [breathing heavily]
- [man continues choking]
- [beeps, chimes]
- [automated voice] Door opening.
[beeping]
[unlocks, chimes]
What the hell are you up to now,
you psycho?
All this cash is yours,
just let me buy your remaining wish.
If you don't, I'll set fire
to this entire bag of cash.
You do know that I will burn it
without hesitation.
And whatever you use your wish for,
I'll just undo it with mine,
so it's really in your best interest
to just let me use your wish.
So, I'm asking.
Take the cash, Gu Bo-gyeong.
How can I trust you?
What we need to establish
between me and you is not trust.
It's rules, because I know rules.
You give me your wish,
I give you this money.
That's it. This is our one rule.
[suspenseful music playing]
So I'm to wish for?
[bowls clattering]
[soft boom]
[sighs]
I'm ready for my final wish.
But tell that bitch, Ka-young,
I did exactly what she asked.
[breathing shakily]
[tense music playing]
[breathing heavily]
[whooshing]
[ominous music plays]
In your previous life, you sold out
hundreds in order to get into heaven.
And here you are once again, destroying
chances for others, Ms. Ki Ka-young.
That's rich coming from you.
You bullied a small child.
You made me use up my wish
so Iblis would suffer the consequences.
You're doing it in this life too.
Get lost.
All I did is state what happened.
What happened isn't the whole truth.
I hate to break it to you,
it doesn't matter what you do,
Iblis will perish by my hand.
I followed his orders,
I bowed down to mankind.
However, Iblis disobeyed his every word.
Not for one minute has Iblis ever followed
his orders obediently.
The fact that he still shows
that shaytan grace to this day
has to be so that I can complete my task.
It means that me slitting his throat
will be the thing that elevates me
to his right hand side.
[ominous music continues]
What the hell? It's like talking
to an engineering student.
Ugh, my arm hurts.
Look, Mr. Angel, whatever,
you're committing the sin of envy.
And what's worse?
You have an inferiority complex.
It's more complicated than that.
I act only for His--
Oh, shut up!
You will never be able to slit
Iblis' throat. Do you know why?
[tense music plays]
I will wish for something so very selfish.
I…
have never…
known what goodness is.
[tense music intensifies]
[music stops]
[bird cawing]
- [button clicks]
- [projector whirring]
[wistful music plays]
JOY
DESPAIR
LONGING
WAITING
MIN-JI'S EMOTIONS ARE SO EASY
RULE: NEVER SNEER AT PEOPLE LIKE THIS
[Ka-young] I knew you'd eventually
take a peek, you satan.
Switch it off when done.
You'll drive up the electricity bill.
[chuckles]
[door opens]
Did you meet Gu Bo-gyeong?
She hasn't forgotten yet.
She follow through? She make the wish?
Tell me now.
Yes, so did Ko Yeong-hyeon.
The kindness of humans… [chuckles softly]
is quite surprising.
They were not corrupt.
Really?
Hey, wake up. Ko Yeong-hyeon, get up.
- [groaning]
- Hurry, wake up!
- What happened? How did you know?
- Whoa, what's wrong?
Why are you-- Why are you crying?
What's wrong?
- What do you mean?
- You said, "It'll be fine."
- "Your father will recover."
- Huh?
Apparently,
my father's cancer is all gone.
They have no idea what happened.
- The doctor's saying it's a miracle.
- Really?
- Yes!
- Wow, that's wonderful!
Wait a minute.
Did I really say something like that?
When?
- [grunts]
- Thank you, Yeong-hyeon.
It feels like he recovered because of you.
- Like some form of magic.
- Okay.
- [cell phone vibrating]
- Someone's calling.
[gasps] Oh, my goodness.
Dad.
Yes, I was just telling him the good news.
He's thrilled.
What?
Uh, slow down. What messages?
You're getting texts all of a sudden?
Authentication messages
for YouTube account?
- They were being sent to you?
- Authentication?
Dad, you should be getting another message
right now. Read it out to me.
- Yeong-hyeon.
- Huh?
We can get our account back online again.
Views are up to six hundred thousand!
- Yes.
- Six hundred thousand? Wait.
Our video has nearly
six hundred thousand views total?
- [Da-jin chuckles]
- [gasps]
- Hey!
- Huh?
- Did you show them your breasts?
- What?
- Ugh, asshole!
- Hey! [groans]
- How dare you! How can you ask that?
- [yelping] I'm sorry.
So, that means I won?
I won in the end?
I'd say Gu Bo-gyeong's final wish
half counts.
So, I guess I could try to make my case
that you and I have tied. [chuckles]
I'm heading off.
Don't forget to track me down and save me.
Now?
Already?
Every fight has been won
by whoever strikes first.
Don't worry. I've never lost
against anybody but you.
- [gentle music plays]
- [sighs]
[crying softly]
[Ejllael] In a situation where
one of you two must be destroyed,
you still entertain the impossible hope
that you will both get to live, Iblis.
[Irem] As it stands now,
Iblis and Ms. Ki Ka-young
will almost certainly
try to save each other.
At the very least, Ms. Ki Ka-young will.
[sighs] They'll prevent me
from finishing this war.
[Irem] War?
[tense music plays]
- [knife slashes]
- [gagging]
[Shadi] Stop! All right.
I will sing the world to sleep.
And I will bind Iblis.
[exhales] Finally, today is the day.
Today? Has today finally come, Father?
I will be the one who tied down the genie.
My healing powers don't work
when this thread cuts me.
- [giggles maliciously]
- I can simply not hear his music.
- [grunts]
- [Shadi] Khalid!
[chuckles]
[Khalid] Right. Now, sing!
[whooshing]
Iblis has come of his own accord.
Sing, Father. I told you to sing now!
[metal thuds]
[dark music plays]
- [owl hoots]
- [birds squawking]
[hoots]
There's something you'll have to do
when that day comes.
That's all I expect you to do. Got it?
[hoots]
[dark music continues]
[Khalid in deep voice]
Finally, we meet again.
I have waited for you for 1,000 years.
You have finally made it here.
[in normal voice] I received something
of immense value today.
I'm very grateful.
[Shadi] Then,
will you grant me freedom, my son?
Yes, of course. However,
I shall first give freedom to myself.
- [gags]
- Shadi!
[yells]
[panting]
Do not forget my last request.
[Shadi gasps]
[Shadi exhales]
[Shadi] Up until this moment,
I've done everything I could, my brother.
[chimes]
- [tense music playing]
- [breathing heavily]
You do not have human empathy,
nor the generosity of a spirit.
Your demise by my hand…
is now guaranteed.
Are you angry?
You're being quite harsh on a deaf orphan.
What about the girl?
Has she been captured?
[breathing heavily]
[whirring]
[grunting]
It is time for me to take the lamp
once and for all.
So make your last wish.
Any resistance will bring harm
to those you love.
Your grandmother, your friend,
all the people in your village.
Wish the lamp over to me
and let's be done with it.
A zero-sum game, huh?
[sighs] Okay. You'll stop going on
about how we're connected.
Go off as much as you want,
you son of a bitch!
End quote.
What are you saying?
Give me your wish already!
[grunts]
What the hell? Where did she go?
That bitch used up her final wish
on this bullshit?
Find her. Track her down now!
Yes!
What do you want me to wish for?
When Ki Ka-young says, "Go off as much
as you want, you son of a bitch,"
wherever she may be,
take Ka-young immediately
to Iblis' location.
Use those precise words.
- You got all that?
- Yeah, I'm not an idiot.
[music building]
- [music stops]
- [Ka-young panting]
[grunting]
- [sighs]
- Damn, they use a lot of thread.
Well, that's what I've got.
- Don't know what to do now.
- That's okay, I'll take it from here.
We have the thread. I'll take it with me
and bring it to my brother's garden.
You two, follow me.
The rest, spread out! Find her!
[Iblis] He's half human, half spirit.
The thread is fatal for him too.
Let's see if I can carry it.
Carry it.
- [straining]
- [low whirring]
Don't worry about me, just go.
Go now. Get rid of him for good.
[exhales]
[tense music plays]
[owl hooting]
[muffled yelling]
- [all shouting]
- [Mi-ju] What is happening?
[Min-ji] Oh, I feel sick.
Someone must be carrying the lamp
right now.
[all yelp]
[panting]
What is this? I'll go out
and find out what's happening.
Who are you? A mythical beast?
[Sade pants]
Irem? What?
This is a gift from Ejllael.
From Ejllael?
This is it.
It's Iblis' lamp.
Irem. What are you doing?
I told you that one day
you would need to choose.
I serve only my master and no one else.
This is what your master ordered? No way!
That is not for mythical beasts to ask.
We do as we're told.
[Sade] Irem!
Hang on. How come I still see it?
They said it would evaporate
the minute her wishes were made.
She still has a wish left?
She deceived me.
[sighs] That bitch.
Go find her.
Whatever it takes. Go find her now!
- [men] Yes, ma'am!
- Stop!
I'll kill you all.
[growling]
[Ka-young] The day birds fall dead
from the sky, that is the day.
Please come save us.
[tense music plays]
- [yells]
- [Sade snarls]
[men yelping and screaming]
[screaming]
[growls]
[men yelping]
[metal clangs]
Huh?
[solemn music plays]
[whirring]
[grunts softly]
- [whooshes]
- [wind gusting]
You're not here to say hi, are you?
[sighs]
I'm a little busy at the moment.
[sighs] There isn't much time left
until Ka-young's last wish.
I thought I'd stall.
If you destroy that flower
before she makes it,
that ruins everything I've worked towards.
Your painting.
You asked why I bore out the eyes.
I saw their ambitions.
This, right here,
is the ambition of the angels.
Still fighting that 300-year war.
- Even now.
- You really thought the war had been won?
Where is the peace our battle won us?
You should've never removed that sword.
That sword brought calamity to us angels.
Nor should you
have ever met her again either.
Seeing as you've recovered your memories,
it should be clear how that ends. [scoffs]
I hope Ka-young's wish is a righteous one.
I will then slit your throat.
She'll go back to how she always was.
She'll forget you
and go back to her life of torment,
ostracized, denounced.
Because that is the appropriate fate
for a human who is loved by a satan.
Just as it was, it will be again.
I too hope her wish
is a noble wish, whatever it may be.
She may not know goodness,
but she saw to it that
she only made good choices.
I hope the rest of her life is peaceful.
Her memories will vanish.
She'll go back to her life,
rebuked for being a psychopath.
Her life indeed may be boring again…
[sighs]
…but she would still be righteous,
she'd still be worthy of love,
just as he intended.
That, right there,
is why I met her in this life.
So that the end of this war
would give heaven to Ki Ka-young.
And so you will…
bow to her.
[inhales sharply]
[grunts]
[both grunt]
[cell phone chimes]
CONVENIENCE STORE CLERK
FORMER MARINE, CLASS 1185
[cell phone chimes]
[sighs]
STRAWBERRY FARMER
WELTERWEIGHT CHAMPION
CAFE OWNER, NEW CIVVIE
ALL FORMER MARINES
CHEONGPUNG MARINES
PARK CHANG-SIK
[Chang-sik] Operation Cave Cleaning.
[dramatic music plays]
Whatever it takes!
If it doesn't work, make it work!
No stopping until it's done.
All right. Let's go!
- [dramatic music continues]
- [grunts]
[both grunting]
[Ejllael yells]
[Iblis grunts]
[thunder rumbling]
[Ejllael yells]
[both grunting]
[yells]
[groans] Shit!
- [cackles]
- [Iblis straining]
- [thunder rumbling]
- [panting]
Who are you? How did you get in here?
Are you another genie or whatever?
Sorry, I'm deaf.
Your granddaughter's outside,
waiting for you.
Ka-young is here?
Hang on. Who are you?
Where did you get that thread there?
- [men grunting]
- [growling]
[screaming]
[men screaming and grunting]
[screams]
Oh Pan-geum, do not let go
of my hand, got it?
What the hell are you saying
to each other? Don't speak at all.
I'm in charge!
[gasps]
Your bitch granddaughter made
my father angry,
so a few corpses
should return the favor nicely.
Which order should I lay them out in?
I guess the friend first,
and then relative second, no?
Kill her now.
[Mi-ju] Who are you people?
What's happening?
[growls]
- [snarling]
- [men scream]
- [Sade growls]
- [man screams]
- [Wahid] Father!
- [Khalid whimpering]
[gasps]
The day has come.
Not spring, but today.
- Grandma, you try to break it.
- [grunts]
Oh, whoa. It was easy before.
[Ejllael] When the flowers next bloom
in your front yard…
Oh, Lord.
[Ejllael] …you will die.
What is it?
Min-ji, tell Ka-young everything
I tell you now.
The exact words.
[breath trembles, sniffles]
Ka-young, you were the biggest blessing.
You're smarter than anyone.
You're beautiful.
You've never been a bad granddaughter.
Ka-young, don't you dare make the wrong
choice because of me, do you understand?
Tell her… Tell her this, okay?
Yes, I will, I promise.
But right now, let's run.
- [groaning]
- [growls]
[man yelps]
[yelps]
[grunts]
[growls, screams]
[bellows]
Seo I-deuk!
[Wahid] Kill her!
No, Min-ji!
[gunshot]
[sorrowful music plays]
Mm, odd for a man to have this.
[humming]
I made the flowers bloom in the front yard
with my own hands.
[gasps]
- [coughing]
- [cries out]
No, Grandma! No! No!
Mi-ju! No!
[crying] Mi-ju, please!
This can't be!
This is the wrong order!
I said to kill the other bitch first!
[Min-ji sobbing]
- [Min-ji] No!
- You bitch, what are you--
Spit it out. Spit it out right now!
[gulps]
- Open her stomach. Take the thread out!
- No, please, don't do that.
- I beg of you, please! Please!
- [exhales]
No! No!
[growls]
[man] No! [screaming]
[growls weakly]
[dramatic orchestral music plays]
Sade.
[grunts]
[straining]
[yelps, screams]
- [panting]
- [thunder rumbling]
[Ka-young panting]
[tense music plays]
Grandma?
- Grandma?
- Grandma!
It's all my fault! [sobbing]
[screams]
You can't, Grandma, no!
How could you do this?
I can bring her back
if she's breathing. The lamp.
- The lamp, where is it?
- You must spend your last wish on me.
This woman here
isn't breathing any longer.
You better obey,
or your little friend will die too.
[breathing heavily]
But first, we'll open her stomach
and take the thread out.
She swallowed it.
- [screams]
- [Min-ji] No!
- [sobbing]
- No! No!
No!
- [gunshot]
- [yelps]
[gasping]
Charge!
- Let's go!
- [all yelling]
[all grunting and yelling]
- Take those two to the cellar!
- [Ka-young] Grandma.
[all grunting]
Dr. Choi. Help me lift her. Pull her up.
[groans]
[Ejllael grunts]
[somber ethereal music playing]
[yelling] This is your once chance
to finish me off, so why don't you do it?
Just kill me! Do it already!
There is something you still have to do.
You must slit my throat.
[sighs]
- Move.
- [grunts]
[deep rumbling]
[Shadi] Please, my brother.
I walked all night,
found you, and tied you up
for this one reason.
End my son's life.
[yelps, grunts]
You are dead! I'll kill you right now!
Rub the lamp right now!
Make your final wish! Make me his master!
Wish that the lamp be mine!
Instead of doing that,
I'd rather just do this.
- [screams]
- You really are a psychopath.
- Wanna get stabbed?
- Do it. Do it!
Oh, yeah? Allow me to oblige!
- [choking]
- [breathing heavily]
[in deep voice] I saw it
a thousand years ago,
when you were dying,
Iblis revealed the lamp himself
so he might save you.
[continues choking]
As my owner, you must swear, though,
to use the first of your wishes
to save the life of this girl here.
[choking]
[breathing heavily]
[wind whistling]
It would be beautiful
if history were to repeat itself.
So, hurry up, Iblis.
[grunts]
[dramatic orchestral music plays]
- [grunts]
- [choking]
[yelling]
- [Khalid] No!
- [gasping]
- Father.
No!
[Wahid] Father!
[dramatic orchestral music continues]
[Irem screams]
[Irem whimpers]
[groaning]
[groans, pants]
The thing you've been striving for,
to finally end the war.
No.
What I strived for…
was to win.
[breathing sharply]
Father? [screaming] Father!
You bitch, I'll kill you! [grunts]
[gasping]
Are you okay? Are you hurt?
Grandma is… Grandma and Sade are…
[sorrowful music plays]
[rain pattering]
[siren wailing]
[EMT] The victim was
without pulse upon arrival.
Bullet wound through her chest.
- Call the Jeil Hospital ER.
- No.
Take her directly to the mortuary.
- She's been dead a while.
- I know.
But according to law, a morgue can't
take her until a doctor declares her dead.
- We also need to identify her.
- I know her.
And I can confirm her death.
Dentists can pronounce
an official death too.
Ms. Oh Pan-geum.
I pronounce her officially dead.
October 5th.
6:20 p.m.
Time of death.
[melancholy music playing]
[sobbing]
[Iblis] I will now also give sorrow to you
I will give you sorrow
Which is more precious than love
Other genie, what questions
did Oh Pan-geum ask the most
besides the weather?
[AI Genie] Ms. Oh Pan-geum searched
the following in order of frequency.
"Ways to heal my dear Ka-young's illness."
"How to fix a psychopath."
"Foods that are good for psychopaths."
[Iblis] On a blustery winter's night with
A few tangerines laid out on the street
KA-YOUNG, YOU'RE BEAUTIFUL TODAY AS ALWAYS
Sold by an old woman
Shivering with a lifetime of cold
FROM SORROW TO JOY
POETRY BY JEONG HO-SEUNG
To you, who was happy
To haggle the price of tangerines
I shall show you the equal face of sorrow
When I called to you from the shadows
- [crying]
- Please leave us.
We will wash and dress the deceased.
[Min-jae crying] Please, leave us.
[Iblis] Not once did you show me
An equal smile
OH PAN-GEUM
When someone huddled under a straw sack
Freezes to death
GRANDCHILD: KI KA-YOUNG
You did not so much as put
A single straw over them
For your indifferent love
For your tears
That seem incapable of flowing
It's painful.
[Iblis] I will now also give wait to you
Just deal with the pain for today.
You have to.
I thought I made all the right decisions.
Grandma is lying in a casket,
and now I'm miserable, so get off!
Miserable?
You're miserable because you don't like
that you made a bad decision?
It's not just you.
I lost Grandma. I was in love…
even though it was brief.
[sighs]
So you need to bear it too.
[Min-ji sniffles]
If I make a choice for someone,
everyone's unhappy afterwards.
[young Min-ji] Be my friend.
And what if I don't
wanna be friends with you?
- You and I are both negative ones.
- You have no other option.
So, we are friends from now on.
You're terrible at school.
So it appears I'm a negative one still.
Your mother offers this
to offset the costs.
[sighs]
[Iblis] I will stop the blizzard of snow
That fell on the world
You said you were going
somewhere nicer than Hawaii.
How have you returned to us like this?
[low chattering]
[Ka-young's aunt crying]
[Ka-young's aunt sobbing]
[Iblis] I will take the spring snow
That fell on the barley fields
And take them to visit the sorrow
Of the people shivering with cold
I will walk the snowy paths
No longer snowing, with you
[Ka-young's aunt bawling]
Oh, my gosh. She behaves like this
at her grandma's funeral?
Such a strange, strange girl.
Not even crying.
Do you have to act so strange today? Huh?
I knew from the start
Gyeong-seok should've held it!
[wailing]
Ma!
Mama! [wailing]
Mama!
[bawling]
[mourners murmuring]
[Iblis] We will talk
Of the power of sorrow
And walk all the way
To the sorrow of waiting
[sentimental music plays]