[theme music playing]
GENIE, MAKE A WISH
[exhales]
[mysterious music plays]
"Make sure we're punished right,
you and me." [laughs]
Full 20 years have passed since that day.
And no matter how long I wait,
this punishment won't arrive.
[Sade growls]
You should still be careful.
And watch what you say and do.
Ah, quiet, beast.
Why do I need to be careful?
I'm the all-powerful Genie, am I not?
[Sade] Man, this is so stressful.
[exhales]
[whooshes]
- [camel grunts]
- [Iblis] Hmm?
That smell of clay.
What? You're that…
Did you not die?
- Who are you?
- Huh?
You know the language of Goryeo.
Are you from Goryeo?
Do you not recall?
[sniffs] Definitely you.
You've been alive all this time?
I remember seeing you breathe
your last breath.
I saw it.
- [gasps]
- I recognize those marks, the bites.
- Wow, messy, wasn't it?
- You are rude.
No, just really curious.
The truth is I'm a genie.
We've met before, 20 years ago.
Your final wish was for me to be punished,
but I'm doing pretty well.
Anything?
Come try my dates.
Delicious dates!
- For sale!
- [whooshes]
[yelps, grunts]
[gasps] Oh.
Oh, no. [gasps]
My dates. [pants]
- [crunches]
- [past-life Ka-young gasps]
- [past-life Ka-young] Oh, no.
- Hey, look. Blood.
You take better care of your dates
than yourself.
Horrible thing to say.
I know you tripped me.
Are you going to set this right?
[past-life Ka-young sighs]
Ah, what to do now?
[pants]
Do I still try to corrupt her,
seeing as she's alive?
Oh, goodness. What a waste.
I asked how you were going
to set this right.
[playful music plays]
[coins jingling]
- [gasps]
- Will that do? Should cover it.
[Iblis scoffs, chuckles]
Here. You overpaid.
Enjoy your dates.
Delicious dates!
- Try out my dates!
- Come on, it's plain as day.
Tempting you will be too easy.
You're basically a lost cause.
That means we're almost there.
Try out my delicious dates!
- Try them!
- Wow, this is already fun.
- Where do you live?
- [man] Where is my money?
Someone took my money!
Here.
- Enjoy, my friend.
- [man] Thank you.
Hey, take a look at this.
I got lucky today.
Look, I got some dates for us.
Have some, all right?
Thank you.
[past-life Ka-young] Oh! Be careful.
Stay away, don't touch me!
You're scaring me.
[somber music plays]
Don't listen. Don't listen to that boy.
[sighs] It can't hurt me.
His words can't harm.
[indistinct chatter]
[gasps]
[Iblis] Hmm.
You live here?
[gasps]
What are you doing here? Leave!
I'll get kicked out if they notice you.
Don't worry,
I'm only visible to your eyes.
Also, no one's even looking at you.
[man] My wife bakes better bread
than this. Try some of hers…
- [indistinct chatter]
- [Iblis] You humans are quite shallow.
All it takes is being a tiny bit different
and you're an outcast. Tsk.
Don't disparage. They've given me shelter
and a way to make a living.
[sighs] So, get out of here already
before you're caught.
It's intriguing, that's all.
A human who used
all her wishes for others.
A human who dared to include me
in her last wish.
Huh?
Wow.
So that's how I was punished.
I seriously almost died of boredom
because I had no one to corrupt,
thanks to you.
You're still alive,
so no one can make wishes.
What are you saying? I told you,
I've never made any wishes before.
[sighs] Perfect. Refusing accountability.
Hiding in this foreign land,
with a foreigner's face.
You may appear steadfast,
but you will break eventually.
You'll be corrupt like all the rest.
Is it true? You're only visible
to my eyes, like you said?
Mmm-hmm.
It's one of my magical quirks.
So, why aren't you scared?
Most run for cover when they learn that.
You're a ji-ne, right?
We have them in Goryeo too.
The elders say they are spirits who
grant wishes for their owners with magic.
"Genie," not ji-ne.
Why'd you ask
if I'm only visible to your eyes?
It's a shame that only I can see you.
[chuckles softly] Well, it's just,
your smile is very endearing.
[chuckles softly]
[gentle music plays]
Uh…
"Endearing." That must be
the highest compliment in Goryeo.
[indistinct chatter]
[camel grunting]
Why are we here?
Why in the world do you think we're here?
- I can't travel on foot.
- And where are you traveling?
Back East, to Goryeo.
Are you looking for a camel?
I have excellent camels there.
Just stay here, don't get in the way.
- [past-life Ka-young cries]
- [thug grunts]
- [past-life Ka-young] No! My gold! No! No!
- [thugs grunting]
- [thug 2 grunts]
- [past-life Ka-young yelps, cries]
- [past-life Ka-young groans]
- [thugs laugh, grunt]
[thugs grunting]
[whimpering]
That's enough.
- [whimpers]
- [whooshing]
[groans]
[gasps]
[mysterious music plays]
[grunts, body thuds]
- [thug 1] It's Shaytan!
- [thug 2] Shaytan!
- [thug 1 whimpers]
- [thug 3] Shaytan!
[gasps, breath trembles]
Take it.
[spluttering] Shaytan.
It can't be. You… You're a monster.
[crying] You… you murdered him. Why?
He took your money.
It's my fault. [sniffles]
I know I was blinded by money.
I was greedy.
[sobs, sniffles]
I shouldn't have accepted all those coins
for my dates. I'm a bad person.
I want you to leave my sight.
Don't come back.
[crying]
- [comical music plays]
- [leaves rustling]
[wind gusts]
[funk music plays]
[Iblis grunting]
[fusion Arabic music plays]
[Iblis] Huh? Uh…
The money's been returned
to its original owner.
And that criminal deserved to die.
He hurt a lot of humans, not just you.
I'm sure that they…
would like it… maybe.
What else am I to do
when that's just my method?
You know what I am. A shaytan.
So, when are you heading to Goryeo?
You know, it would be faster
to go through the Gobi Desert.
I could take you.
You could?
- You know the way?
- Roughly. I once blocked the path there.
I can try to find out for real.
Really?
Then, I'll start saving for a camel again.
Thank you, for showing the way.
[chuckles softly]
[gentle music plays]
Why do you live like this anyway?
Don't you get angry?
I was given a second chance at life.
I don't remember dying, though.
These bite marks on my body
are surely connected to it.
I know that I was kept alive
for a reason, though.
And so, I should live with joy.
[chuckles softly]
[gentle music continues]
How foolish. Do you truly believe
there's a right kind of wish?
To gain something,
one has to lose something.
For a person to live, someone's life
must end. That's how it goes.
Sade!
[growling]
- [barking]
- [screaming]
[music fades]
[indistinct chatter]
[coughing]
[coughs]
Khalid.
I bought this from a stall selling linens.
He said this is good for coughs.
You must boil it and drink it,
then you'll be all better.
You take care of the children
and the elderly alike?
Stop that.
Your kind sells out the people
closest to them
and never shows a bit of gratitude.
Isn't that right?
After all, you're half-human
and half-spirit.
You know, his father sings like an angel.
Are you the spirit Shadi's son?
You are sick and weak because
you were cursed with a mortal body.
[suspenseful music plays]
Are you Iblis?
Could you cure this sickness?
You can do anything you desire, can't you?
You are the leader of spirits,
are you not?
I hate being weak.
This body is cursed. Please get me out.
This thread here can bind souls.
I will give it to you in exchange.
An enticing offer.
But I couldn't accept this request,
even if we are kin.
[Iblis] Let's go.
[groans softly]
- [Iblis grunts]
- [gasps, yelps]
- [groans]
- Hey, lie down if you're tired.
- Why are you forcing yourself awake?
- [sighs]
I said to warn me before
you just showed up like this.
How could I have been any clearer?
[sighs]
What are you staying up at night
to make anyway?
- Instead of resting.
- Hanbok.
I'm going to wear it
when we arrive at Goryeo.
But I have to work during the day.
It's so dark, how can you see like this?
Come on.
[captivating music plays]
[past-life Ka-young]
This is where you live?
Wow. It's like a palace.
You've clearly never seen a palace.
Hey. I'm from Gaegyeong.
There are tons of beautiful
and grand palaces there.
Even looking at them from the gates,
even seeing them from far away.
- Even the shape is… You know?
- So you've never been inside.
- Got real close up to one, one time.
- So what else is in your hometown?
[grunts] How different could it be
from here?
[past-life Ka-young] Mmm…
Goryeo has all four seasons.
In summer, it's lovely and warm.
And in autumn, the leaves change.
And in winter, white snow falls.
And when you see
the plum blossoms start to bloom,
spring's arrived.
And once the plum blossoms wither away,
then cherry blossoms grow in their place.
[chuckles softly]
The cherry blossoms are especially pretty.
[chuckles]
[romantic music plays]
[past-life Ka-young] In Goryeo,
we'd write out our wishes
and send them on boats down the streams.
We believed that if the boats reached
the ocean, they would come true.
Consider this the ocean at night.
Shall I send them out to sea?
Even further.
To the place where the land meets the sky.
Beyond Earth.
To Goryeo.
[romantic music continues]
[Iblis] What did you write
on those boats anyway?
[past-life Ka-young]
No need for you to know.
[Iblis scoffs]
It's almost like…
it's raining stars.
[gasps softly]
[romantic music continues]
PLEASE DO NOT LET THIS WANDERER STARVE
PLEASE DO NOT LET ANYONE FALL VICTIM
TO THIS WANDERER'S STRIKING LOOKS
PLEASE LET ME RETURN TO GORYEO
[all sobbing]
[dramatic choral music plays]
Ejllael! Ejllael has arrived
to take my soul.
[Ejllael] My sacred wings
shall guide you to the afterlife.
I shall go to the afterlife,
with you guiding the way.
Praise Ejllael!
- I'm in your sacred hands!
- Your soul is destined for--
Ouchy! Ow!
[man] My soul is destined
for ouchy, ow!
Ouchy! Ow!
[all wailing]
Hey, before you even take a feather
from my wings, first tell me what's--
What's wrong with you?
[people sobbing]
[Iblis] You, who came from Goryeo,
are enslaved.
Serves you right.
They say, in Goryeo,
there is a ji-ne who also wields magic.
I shall go up against it
once I get to Goryeo.
You wish upon stars.
She spent all her wishes on others.
Now, she makes wishes on mere stars.
To think she made wishes for my sake too.
To think that she was concerned for me,
making sure I was safe and comfortable.
[sweeping music plays]
[Ejllael] What could a mere
moment in time mean to an eternal life?
All that time, he was connected
to her final wish.
[weapon thuds]
He was more interested in that human
than any other.
He seemed far more excited
figuring out how to make her laugh
and what to feed her…
than he was in figuring out
his plan for spreading evil
and corrupting the world.
[sighs] I know.
[cries softly]
It's so tragic, Master.
[Irem sobbing]
[sighs]
Look, I'm over here complaining about
how much of a fool Iblis is.
But I can't complain
if you're just crying.
Apologies, I was too busy crying
to read your lips.
Could you please repeat that, sir?
[sighs]
- Watch me.
- Mmm.
Get out!
[sniffles] Mmm.
[sniffles, cries]
[past-life Ka-young gasps]
[sighs] Try to find some good clams.
Everything you find
is full of these stones.
[groans] Throw it away.
[Iblis chuckles]
[Iblis] Ooh, ow, hot! [sighs]
So, when will you be done
with your clothes? For Goryeo?
I'm having a hard time
finding the right cloth.
- Even so, it's nearly finished.
- Can't you just sew on the road?
Let's leave today.
Really? You mean that? We can go?
- What about your lamp, though?
- Hmm…
I'll just see if I can convince Him
to hurl it with all his might at Goryeo.
You, who are all-knowing,
and strong and great.
And benevolent and noble.
And also merciful, and of course,
wise and, uh, um…
Hmm, and…
- You're desperate and it shows.
- [both laughing]
[chiming]
- Oh? You…
- Hmm?
You're glowing.
A new master? But how?
I'm still tied to your final wish.
No one should be able to conjure me yet.
This is far too soon.
Couldn't this be a good thing
when you think about it?
You were bored without anyone to tempt
with wishes. Isn't that what you said?
[exhales] You're right.
Perfect. I'll just dash over quick.
[whooshes]
- [breathing heavily]
- [wind whooshing]
[man] Finally we meet, Iblis.
You have cursed me to live as
an oppressed Arab migrant for two decades.
[tense music plays]
- [grunts]
- [yelps]
[soft chiming]
[gusting]
- [rumbling]
- [men screaming]
Stop! Cast the bitch aside too!
[men screaming]
[Iblis] Huh, it seems I missed someone.
Please, I want to have more
than anybody else in the realm.
Listen carefully to my first wish.
I wish to have more than even
the wealthiest person in all of Arabia.
I knew you would ask for that.
Your wish has been fulfilled.
[inhales excitedly]
[dramatic music plays]
[people murmuring]
[whooshing]
- What's wrong?
- I have decided on my second wish, Genie.
Kill whoever has sneered at me
or dared to cause me any pain of any kind.
[past-life Ka-young] Shaytan.
It can't be. You… You're a monster.
[crying] You… you murdered him. Why?
[sighs]
Your second wish has been fulfilled.
[indistinct shouting]
[people wailing]
[foreboding music plays]
[past-life Ka-young] Dates for sale.
Delicious dates.
Come try these delicious dates. Come try.
Try them.
[sighs]
- [sighs heavily]
- [footsteps approaching]
[tense music plays]
Uh… Are… are you…
I got lucky today.
Look, I got some dates for us.
Have some, all right?
Thank you.
Yes. So you do know who I am.
Those dates you gave me
were very delicious.
As thanks, I shall now give you more
than you could possibly imagine.
Clothes, food, houses, servants, jewelry.
Anything you like.
All I want is what I can earn,
but only by my own effort.
I shall be leaving anyway.
I'm planning to return to my country.
[laughs]
You're leaving?
You're too good for my offer?
Now that I am up here,
looking down on you,
I see you're that same slave girl
I bought to feed to my animals.
And even so, you dare think
so highly of yourself?
[exhales angrily]
How does it look?
[Iblis gasps softly]
It's beautiful.
[chuckles softly]
I had finished it a while ago.
However, there was a chance
you wouldn't be able to leave yet.
Because of the wishes.
I don't know the way to Goryeo.
And anyway,
I wouldn't want to go without you.
- [chuckles softly]
- [chiming]
Oh.
Muttalib's final wish.
That means you'll be free after this.
We'll head out tonight.
- For Goryeo.
- Yes. Let's go.
I shall experience
the four seasons of Goryeo.
The bright red leaves, the snowfall,
the cherry and plum blossoms.
If you can't find me, call my name.
You may call me… [enunciating] Iblis.
Iblis.
It's very unique.
Is that good?
If so, yes, it is. [chuckles]
[chuckles softly]
- [gusting]
- [people exclaiming]
[chuckles smugly]
[people murmuring]
Well, then. What is your final wish?
It has dawned on me that I left something
very valuable behind in the desert.
Something so valuable that no amount
of money can possibly obtain it.
My final wish is for her
to submit to me fully.
I wish that this girl remain by my side
for the rest of her life.
[people gasping]
[chiming]
Your last wish has been fulfilled.
Now, I'd like to see this unique woman
that no amount of money may ever buy.
[tense music plays]
[indistinct chatter]
[dramatic music plays]
No, not her.
[soft chiming]
Why you?
[Muttalib] What are you doing here?
I see. You've come crawling back!
I knew no one could ever resist
all my riches.
- Bring her to me! Right now!
- [henchman yells]
[henchmen grunting]
[gasps]
[Muttalib screams]
[Muttalib] Shaytan's shown his face here!
[gasps, yelps]
That man is a shaytan! Seize him!
[gasping]
[pulsating]
[straining]
What is this thing?
Take this off me now! Take it off!
[yells]
[grunts, pants]
You refused my gift to you.
You were convinced the thread was useless.
It has a use, you see.
- A great use.
- [straining]
[Iblis grunts]
[past-life Ka-young whimpering]
[past-life Ka-young yelps]
[grunts]
[yelling]
[Iblis yelling]
Hunbish? Can it be?
[past-life Ka-young gasps]
You made it out alive!
[breathing heavily]
Was that the name of this boy? Hunbish?
[somber music plays]
[past-life Ka-young] Khalid.
[gasps] Are you Khalid?
[ring chiming]
How did you… How is this…
[people gasp]
Look! I've bound the Shaytan!
And this foreign woman, she loves him.
She loves the Shaytan!
What? You came for him?
You didn't come for me!
[grunts] Seize that girl!
[past-life Ka-young whimpering] No!
Let me go! [cries]
I wish that this girl remain by my side
for the rest of her life.
This was the wish. Your wish.
No. [yells]
[grunting]
- I'm coming! Don't worry, I'm coming.
- [crying]
If I can't have her, no one can!
[yells]
[gasps, screams]
No!
- [past-life Ka-young cries out]
- No!
- [Iblis yells]
- [groans]
[blood splatters]
[Iblis straining]
[strains] No.
- [somber music plays]
- [groaning]
[Iblis gasps]
- [past-life Ka-young gasping]
- No. No.
No. Please!
- [yells]
- [people grunting]
[gasping] In Goryeo…
- [coughs, gasps]
- No.
…everybody gets four lives.
Whichever life it is…
[gasping]
come and find me in one of them.
No, no. No, come on. Please.
Not yet. Hold on, I beg you.
Listen now, I am a Genie!
My lamp can grant any human three wishes.
I ask you to grab ahold of the lamp
and claim yourself as my owner.
You must swear, though,
to use the first of your wishes
to save the life of this girl here.
I beg you!
Please! I swear to fulfill
your next three wishes immediately after.
I beg any of you!
[indistinct chatter]
[people exclaiming, murmuring]
[people gasping]
Yes, I will do it, Genie.
I wish that I was
the richest man in Arabia.
Richer than Muttalib!
You…
[tense music plays]
All right, then.
Now, you must use your next wish
to save this girl here.
Do it.
Do it!
Mashallah! I'm so rich now!
- But it's not enough. It's not enough.
- [Iblis] No.
I need more. I need even more riches!
[crying] But, you can't. No.
[gusting]
This is your final wish.
Repeat this. "I wish to save this girl."
[people clamoring]
Do it now! You have to do it! [sobbing]
I wish for more gold, Genie.
Fill this city with
a bounty of gold! [laughs]
[sobbing]
[people clamoring]
No, no. [sobbing]
[groaning weakly]
[sobbing]
[weakly] I'm sorry…
for leaving you all alone.
[exhales]
No, no, no. No! [sobbing]
No! No! [sobbing]
[somber music plays]
[chiming]
[sobs] No.
[sobbing] No. No, no, no.
No, this can't… this can't.
She can't die, she can't die. No!
[Iblis wailing]
[melancholy music plays]
[sobbing]
[breathing heavily]
[dramatic music plays]
[flames roaring]
[ground rumbling]
[yells]
[Iblis grunts]
[Muttalib choking]
[coughing, chokes]
[panting]
[melancholy music plays]
[people clamoring and cheering]
[yells]
[yelling]
[dramatic music plays]
[gusting]
[men screaming]
[laughing]
[blade slices]
[Hunbish] Do you now see
how arrogant you were?
After so long,
that girl's…
final dying wish…
was granted.
[gentle music plays]
This was…
[exhales]
our punishment.
I have lived for so long,
suffering pain in this body.
It does seem, though, that this
eternal body finally released me.
Then, I became a wandering soul.
Until I met her and you.
The punishment has not yet ended.
The two of you are still bound
by three wishes in this life as well.
[breath trembles]
I know.
I caused that too.
[Hunbish] I now return to you,
this tragic and beautiful story,
as punishment
for granting me eternal life.
Born with no grasp of goodness
and being good anyway.
Her last wish, whatever it is,
please protect her.
I offer you my deepest apologies.
You were a noble child,
one of the finest I've known.
May your soul…
find solace.
[gentle music continues]
[sighs deeply]
[breath shuddering]
[sobbing]
[melancholy music plays]
[Iblis crying]
[tears dripping]
[breathing shakily]
[Iblis] Whatever the punishment,
I accept it.
I will take it willingly.
I yearn for it.
[Sade growling]
[Iblis] Impose whatever punishment
you see fit for my arrogance.
I yearn for it, crave it, plead for it.
Remove whatever possessions
you deem too good for me.
I only hope that…
just once.
Please, just once.
I hope to visit a life of hers.
I accept whatever punishment I am due.
Take what you will.
But, please.
Just once, whichever one of her lives
it may be.
Whatever the punishment, I will take it.
I accept my punishment willingly.
Impose whatever punishment
you see fit for my arrogance.
Remove whatever possessions
you deem too good for me.
I yearn for it.
[light chiming]
Wait a minute! Pan-geum is actually where?
She didn't fly anywhere. I'm telling you,
she didn't even go to Hawaii.
- What is she saying?
- [grandma 1] What?
[Heung-rye] Oh, Chang-sik!
You have to come to Pan-geum's house.
Get over here!
I'm telling you, it's crazy!
[winces]
- Everyone, follow me!
- [grandma 2] What is happening?
- [grandma 3] What's going on?
- [grandma 2] Oh, my goodness.
Where are we going?
What's all the hubbub?
[sighs]
[spoon clinking, tapping]
- [assistant 1] Hello, welcome.
- [assistant 2] Welcome.
Grand--
- Mi-ju.
- [sobs]
What is it? You're crying.
- Something wrong?
- [sobbing]
This wretched tooth.
It's a stabbing pain, I can't…
[sobbing]
I'll take a look.
[sighs]
[scoffs]
- [pots crashing]
- [Heung-rye] You evil witch!
- [Min-jae] Ms. Park!
- [yells]
Ms. Park, stop!
Thought you wouldn't be found out?
Oh Pan-geum! Show your face!
If you're so innocent,
show everyone what I saw!
[Bok-ja] Seongnim!
[Chang-sik] Oh, my goodness! Stop!
What pact with the devil
got you looking like that?
How did you get your youth back?
Tell me right now!
Tell us all what you've done!
- [Chang-sik] Ms. Park! She's not home!
- Hey! Get off me!
- Let me go! Get off!
- [Chang-sik] Please, just calm down!
[Min-jae grunts]
Let go! You'll see,
that bitch is playing us!
She bartered with the devil!
She became that young lady! Okay?
Hey! I'd like to be young again too!
- Do me next!
- [Min-jae] No one's getting young.
- Let go! Let go of me, you brat!
- [Jong-heon] It's dangerous.
- Ms. An, stand back. It's dangerous!
- [Bok-ja grunts]
Tell me. Is the Lord even there?
If He is real, He wouldn't let me be
so unhappy.
Why, Lord?
Why do I have to be old? [wails]
- [Chang-sik] Please try to calm down!
- [Heung-rye] When did I get so damn old?
- Oh, Lord!
- [groans]
[panting]
Wait. I know where she is.
- The field!
- [Min-jae] Where are you going?
- [Chang-sik] What now?
- [Min-jae] Ms. Park, stop!
- Please!
- [Chang-sik] Stop her!
- Oh. Don't get out.
- [Chang-sik] Calm down!
Stay and we'll sort this out!
- Let's go! I'll take care of it.
- [Chang-sik] Where's she running to?
I'm positive she's at the field.
- [Chang-sik] You'll hurt yourself!
- [Min-jae] Calm down!
- [Chang-sik] Calm down!
- [Heung-rye] After her!
[Bok-ja] Pan-geum is in Hawaii!
She's not in the onion field!
[Heung-rye] Shut up!
- [tires screech]
- [crashes]
[body thuds]
[all gasping]
[tense music plays]
[Bok-ja gasps]
Seong… Seong… Seongnim.
[gasping]
[breath trembling] Seongnim.
[Mi-ju gasps]
[Min-jae gasps]
You, you lunatic driver! Get out!
- Out of the car!
- [Jong-heon] Get the hell out.
- Get out!
- [Chang-sik] Out of the car, now!
- [Jong-heon] Get out! Hey!
Get out! Get--
[tense music continues]
Is this the station?
I've run someone over.
Ishrun. Remember the way to the house?
I think they're dead.
The location?
Ki Ka-young's property.
[tense music continues]
[Mi-ju gasps]
[dramatic rock fusion music plays]
[music ends]