(Christmas filled with excitement)
(The kids met each other for the first time.)
(And the First Impression Selection)
(Thank you for saying I lightened the mood!)
(Let's get along well!)
(I hope we become friends.)
(Choi Yu Bin chose Yoon Hoo.)
(Park Si Woo chose Yoon Hoo.)
(Yoon Hoo received 2 votes in the First Impression Selection.)
- I'll try my best. - Okay.
(Let's make it together.)
You and I have similar taste.
(We'll click really well.)
- We hit it off well. - Do we?
(But the latecomer arrived soon after.)
- What? - Finally.
(A good-looking latecomer appeared.)
- Gosh. - Oh, my.
(I feel bad for Yoon Hoo.)
(The daughters' hearts are racing,)
(and the sons are on guard.)
(How will the latecomer impact the kids?)
A new male resident appeared out of nowhere.
He turned things upside down...
the minute he joined the kids.
This kid also has a dad.
- Of course. - Yes.
Of course he has a dad.
And you all know the dad very well.
- It could be a mom. - True.
- We might know her well. - There won't be another mom.
- What? - There won't be another mom.
Be happy with me.
- No more moms. - Let's hope you're the only mom.
Right.
- Is he an athlete? - An athlete?
- For some reason. - Since he's tall?
That's plausible.
(While there are many guesses,)
(the latecomer's dad enters shyly.)
It's Tae Woong!
(The parents greet him happily.)
- It's been a while. - Have you been well?
- Tae Woong. - Hi.
No wonder the son was a looker.
The new resident's dad...
is actor You Tae Woong.
(A good-looker with defined features)
(The actor who left a lasting impression in "The Wild Days")
(Still handsome despite all the years)
The good-looking dad has a good-looking son.
- Exactly. - Right?
- The son is more handsome. - He got it from Tae Woong.
- Totally. - Right?
How tall is he?
Over 190cm, right?
He's 197cm.
- What? - Gosh.
- That's really tall. - He's 197cm?
He's as tall as Michael Jordan.
That's too tall.
Shouldn't the residents have a height limit?
I know, right?
Just look at the height difference.
- You're really tall. - Yes.
(Bewildered by the tall latecomer)
- What's your name? - I'm You Hee Dong.
- Hee Dong. - Hee Dong.
That's right.
(Handsome ever since he was a kid)
Gosh, what a looker.
He hasn't changed.
How charming.
(Grew up looking just like his dad)
- He's more handsome than his dad. - The air he gives off, right?
I'm a physical education major at Korea University.
I'm on the baseball team.
I'm a pitcher.
- So he does baseball. - He's even in the baseball team.
(Even on the baseball team?)
- He's a pitcher? - A pitcher.
- Remember Koo Ja Wook? - Koo Ja Wook of Samsung.
He's like Koo Ja Wook...
- of the Lions. - Totally.
The next-generation Koo Ja Wook.
My strength would be...
my sharp curveballs, which batters have a hard time hitting.
(His height is his weapon.)
I won the Excellent Pitcher Award for the first half of the year...
in the weekend league during high school senior year...
and have won it multiple times.
(Hee Dong pours his passion into baseball.)
(Do you often hear that you're handsome?)
Honestly,
I do.
When I went out to the hallway to switch classrooms in high school,
other students came rushing out to see me.
Saying it myself...
He's got everything.
(Saying it myself is a bit...)
Since I keep playing baseball,
there hasn't been much time to date.
Experiencing something new is very exciting.
I'd love to take photos with my girlfriend like my friends do...
and have a lovey-dovey relationship.
- He's got it all. - So young.
(Episode 2: A Restless Night)
- Nice to meet you. - Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
- Why do you have a flower with you? - I know, right?
He brought a flower with him.
(Everyone is curious.)
Hold on a minute.
(The new resident is to give the flower...)
(to the girl with the best first impression.)
Without talking to each other?
Without chitchatting?
He's choosing while everyone is there?
- Oh, dear. I feel bad for him. - That's a bit...
(Yoon Hoo, the popular guy with 2 First Impression votes,)
(has checked the text message.)
Interesting.
(Choosing the one who made the best first impression openly)
I have my hopes up a little.
To be frank, just a tiny bit.
My hopes went up by 0.1 percent. Just 0.1 percent.
Yu Bin is trying to look cute.
That's not a face...
- she makes at home. - Yu Bin is...
I guess you're not familiar with that face.
- It's new to me. - A new expression.
- A face you haven't seen at home. - No.
(While everyone is nervous)
Did everyone read the text message?
- Yes. - Yes.
Here.
(For the First Impression Selection, Hee Dong chooses...)
Thank you.
(Si Woo.)
The girl in front of him.
(Si Woo was chosen by three guys.)
- Gosh. - Goodness, Si Woo.
Hee Dong is very straightforward.
- Right? - She must have made...
a nice first impression.
Oh, dear.
(Why did you choose Si Woo?)
First of all,
she sat right across from me.
We made eye contact several times.
Her bright smile really did something to me.
She stood out the moment I looked at everyone.
It made me happy.
Yes, it did.
No girl would hate receiving flowers.
(Did it boost your interest in Hee Dong?)
Yes, of course.
(Meanwhile, Yu Bin was watching the whole situation.)
It was a bummer.
Either way, his looks were my ideal type,
which got me interested in him.
I'm sure I'll get a chance to talk to Hee Dong...
next time.
Thank you.
Oh, dear.
- How does it feel? - Sit over here.
No, don't.
- I'll switch seats with you. - No, it's okay.
- Really. - No, you should sit over there.
(Yu Bin changes seats.)
Is she switching seats?
Maybe Yu Bin wants to see him from the front...
by switching seats with Si Woo.
I know, right?
(Hee Dong and Si Woo sit closely, thanks to Yu Bin.)
(Glancing)
Did everyone have dinner?
- Yes. - Yes, what about you?
- I only had a little. - Is that so?
Is there anything you can't eat?
No, I eat anything and everything.
What kind of food do you like the most?
- Anything with rice, - Rice.
like bibimbap and rice bowls.
What about kimchi fried rice?
I like it.
I'll make it for you in a bit.
(Yu Bin makes a sudden move.)
- Hee Dong... - Is it Hee Dong?
Yoon Hoo got two votes...
- in the First Impression Selection. - Right.
Those were from Yu Bin and Si Woo.
- The two seem to waver. - Exactly.
Yoon Hoo is...
- Will he be okay? - Didn't you hear him earlier?
- What did he say again? - "Interesting."
"Things are interesting."
- He's enjoying it. - Right.
(Trying to stay calm)
The latecomer is a wild one.
He's too wild. Come on, Tae Woong.
A big, wild latecomer.
(Everyone is nervous about the big, wild latecomer.)
We've got a wild one.
Can we unpack our things now?
- Yes, shall we? - Let's go unpack.
(Si Woo and Eun Byul's room)
Oh, my. You received the flowers.
- You got a Christmas gift. - Right.
Gosh.
By the way, he's like 190cm tall.
- Right? - I've never seen someone...
as tall as him before.
- Like 190cm? - Maybe 196cm.
- Almost 200cm? - That's 200cm.
Exactly.
- I have to look up at him. - It was a surprise.
- Earlier, - Yes?
- when we sent the text message, - Yes.
- it was out of the blue. - Right?
We know nothing about each other.
- Exactly. - I just...
Did your first impression change after?
(Interested)
- No, it didn't. - Did it not?
That's how you should be.
- Of course. - Stay consistent.
- What about you? - Mine has changed.
- Really? - Yes.
- What? - It changed.
Si Woo's first impression has changed.
- My dear son. - She said Hoo was cute.
- Si Woo did. - It changed.
(Yoon Hoo and Jae Hyuk's room)
- He's super tall. I'm jealous. - Same here.
(Even they are talking about the latecomer.)
Hee Dong is such a looker.
Setting aside how handsome he is,
- it's his height. - I know.
Can't he give some of it to me?
Genetically speaking, I lucked out.
- That's totally true. - Yes.
He's taller than his dad.
I'll just blame my dad.
(Dumbfounded)
Jae Hyuk is holding it against his dad.
He blames everything he lacks on me.
(Jae Seung and Hee Dong's room)
This is the room we'll use together.
Are you good at making friends?
I get along with guys really quickly,
- Not with girls? - but I find it hard with girls.
I always hang out with my baseball teammates,
so I'm not the type to approach girls with confidence.
I wait for them to approach me.
I see.
They'd approach him for sure.
What a surprise.
He'll need some time with the girls.
- It'll be hard. - Yes.
He doesn't know much about girls' hearts.
(Hee Dong, who finds girls difficult,)
Excuse me.
- You'll have something, right? - Yes.
(only follows Jae Seung around.)
Go hang out with the girls,
not only with Jae Seung. Come on.
- Do you work out? - Yes.
I have to, even if just a little.
Everyone here works out.
(Yu Bin walks over to the two guys.)
Are you done unpacking?
- Yes. - I see.
(Turning)
Do you have a workout routine?
(Choi Yu Bin, Choi Jae Won's daughter)
What kind of workout do you like the most?
Just this and that.
(The conversation doesn't continue smoothly.)
Would you like to play board games?
(You Hee Dong, You Tae Woong's son)
Right now?
- How about it? - Okay.
- You know how to play it, right? - Yes.
Good.
Luckily, there was a game for three.
(With Yu Bin's help, the guys and girls finally hang out together.)
You guys play games, right?
I'm not forcing you, am I?
I play board games on my phone.
For real? Me too.
We might grow close after playing this game.
(Laughing)
Maybe not.
(The residents gather in the living room one at a time.)
(Hee Dong looks a lot more relaxed now.)
Hi.
I didn't know you were playing a game.
- Are you three playing? - Yes.
(Focused solely on the game)
(Park Si Woo, Park Nam Jung's daughter)
Time out.
She's being conscious of them a little.
- Of course. - "When will it end?"
- Something like that. - Right.
The end of the board game.
The end.
What should we do?
- Since he just arrived, - Yes?
- how about playing cards? - The one from earlier?
- Yes, Balance Game. - I'm in.
You give the question...
to the person you want the answer from.
- Gosh. - Oh, this looks interesting.
- Goodness. - Isn't it Truth or Dare?
- It's a sort of Truth or Dare, - I see.
but you get to ask the question to the person you want.
- You don't go in turns. - Okay.
Once you draw a card and read it,
you pass it to the person you want the answer from.
- That's right. - You get to know their feelings.
- Exactly. - I see.
Balance Game.
(Starting off with Jae Hyuk)
"I prefer to say 'I love you...'"
"as many times as possible..."
"or only when..."
"I really feel the love."
- Goodness. - Either say it countless times.
I'm sure he'll give it to Si Woo.
- He sure will. - Right?
(Jae Hyuk hands the card to Si Woo, his First Impression choice.)
- He's steadfast. - I told you.
- How competitive. - He lives up...
- to expectations. - Totally.
(Jae Hyuk is still curious about Si Woo.)
I prefer saying it...
only when I really feel the love.
"I want my partner to do this when things are tough."
"Ask me questions to figure it out."
"Figure out how I'm feeling without me having to explain."
- Okay. - This time...
- Who will this card go to? - Let's see.
- It matters. - Right.
- Who will get the card? - Who will get it?
(Thinking)
She should give it to Yoon Hoo.
- Hee Dong. - I bet she'll give it to Hee Dong.
Okay, Coach Shin Tae Yong.
(The person to receive Si Woo's card is...)
(Hee Dong.)
- It's Hee Dong. - Hee Dong right away.
- Poor Jae Hyuk. - How honest of her.
This is frustrating.
There's no reason for her not to give it to Hee Dong,
- who gave her flowers. - True.
(Si Woo passed the card to Hee Dong, maybe because of the flowers.)
Yoon Hoo is being forgotten.
I'm most likely the latter.
"I appreciate my partner more..."
"when they make me laugh..."
"or when they laugh when I'm being funny."
(Who will Hee Dong give the card to?)
(The person to receive Hee Dong's card is...)
(Yu Bin.)
- It went to Yu Bin. - But why?
- They played a game together. - He gave it to Yu Bin.
- True. - But the flowers went to Si Woo.
- Oh, dear. - Look at Si Woo.
Si Woo is sulking.
When they laugh when I'm being funny.
That makes me happier.
(The atmosphere has become strange.)
"When in a long-distance relationship,"
"I'm more moved..."
"when my partner can't visit often but says how much they miss me..."
"or when my partner visits without saying how much they miss me."
(Thinking)
(Who does Yu Bin want to know about?)
(Yu Bin's card...)
(goes to Hee Dong.)
Yu Bin, why did you change your mind from Hoo?
Goodness, it went to Hee Dong.
- This is bad. - Hoo versus Hee Dong.
This is nerve-racking.
(Even Yu Bin, after Si Woo, passed the card to Hee Dong.)
I like it when my partner puts it into action.
- A doer. - Same here.
- Is this a question for a couple? - It's a good one.
"Fried chicken should be plain or seasoned."
It's important.
True, the difference in taste.
I...
- Me? - Yes.
(Hee Dong passes the second card to Si Woo.)
She looks bright again.
- Si Woo... - Really.
Her expression changes when she gets and doesn't get the card.
- Right? - She can't hide her expression.
- No. - Nobody can.
My expression changes...
- with Si Woo's. - Of course.
I...
- Me? - Yes.
(When Hee Dong's card goes to Si Woo)
Right in front of her eyes...
The card was passed on right in front of her eyes.
- What was that? - Her expression was so honest.
Oh, no.
They'll probably get into a fight.
- Totally. - The daughters will.
I like plain fried chicken.
What about you?
Both are good.
- Half and half? - Half and half.
Was half and half even one of the options?
I asked Yu Bin a question,
and then Si Woo one.
It's the first day, so I don't know that much about them.
I want to get to know both of them.
That's good.
- You need to figure them out. - He's right.
At first, Hee Dong gave...
the bouquet of flowers to Si Woo.
- Then, they played games together. - With Yu Bin.
He played games with Yu Bin.
- Yu Bin is very... - She takes the initiative.
We've all seen it,
but she's been flirting with them.
- Flirting? - She's very proactive.
- It's all part of the process. - It is.
She might be strongly drawn to one guy after this.
Right.
There must be a lot on her mind.
Yes.
(Who will Hee Dong choose in the end?)
- You haven't had dinner, right? - No. Should we eat first?
(The children start cooking for Hee Dong, who's hungry.)
Can you cook?
- I can cook rabokki. - Wait.
Do you like rabokki? Should we cook that?
- Yes, let's make rabokki. - Just rabokki?
Without any meat?
I'll grill some meat.
I think we put too many fish cakes.
Excuse me.
There are too many fish cakes.
Sorry about that.
- You like fish cakes, right? - I do.
I put a lot on purpose...
because I knew you'd like them.
(Grinning)
- Do you like it soggy? - I do.
(Approaching)
He says yes to everything.
- He's a yes-man. - He is.
Do you like your noodles firm?
- I do. - She can't join them.
Really?
They were getting along really well.
Though he chose me at first,
I thought he could be more interested...
in Yu Bin.
Enjoy your food.
(Their dinner begins amidst a subtle tension.)
- Thank you for the food. - Thank you for the food.
You can eat first.
(Hee Dong)
(Yu Bin openly cared about Hee Dong.)
- She's offering him first. - She's totally into him!
- She is. - No one can eat first.
She's leading the dinner...
- at the head of the table. - Did Yu Bin make...
- a gesture at Hee Dong? - Yes.
Are there no rules against that?
- That's a little... - Si Woo is losing right now.
I mean, there should be some basic rules.
Right. She doesn't want anybody else to eat first.
What do you think?
It's good.
(Relieved)
Come to think of it,
my specialty wasn't kimchi fried rice.
- It was egg fried rice. - Egg fried rice.
- I'm good at egg fried rice. - With soy sauce and eggs.
But I only use eggs and rice.
- Tomorrow's breakfast? - Tomorrow's breakfast? Okay.
- The meat is good, isn't it? - It is.
What else should I ask?
(Glancing)
How do you feel?
Do you think you're settling in well?
- Not yet. - Not yet?
Have you ever drunk until you blacked out?
Well...
- Oh, once. - Once?
Alcohol tastes bad, doesn't it?
- It tastes so bad. - Right.
- Why are you drinking it, then? - For the vibe.
For the vibe.
That's true.
I feel like I'll feel even lonelier if I drink alone.
You come to enjoy that loneliness.
Jae Seung is being too pretentious.
I can't really see the resemblance with his dad.
He takes after her mom.
Jae Seung.
When you're in bitter love,
and you go home after a fight with your boyfriend,
listen to "It's Not Love If It Hurts Too Much."
That will make you cry so hard.
You should listen to it.
Songs these days can never recreate that old-fashioned vibe.
Really?
I wonder why people drink.
(And one person is interested in Jae Seung.)
(It's Eun Byul, who picked him for the First Impression Selection.)
Who's your favorite singer?
Do you like Kim Kwang Seok's songs?
I don't know any of his songs.
(She quietly gets up.)
I couldn't exactly jump in.
It looked like...
Jae Seung and Si Woo have been talking a lot.
They seemed close.
And I'm not the type to approach a guy first,
so I couldn't really express my interest...
or go up to talk to him.
Eun Byul is also interested in Jae Seung.
It's awkward to sit there...
- when the other two are talking. - Exactly.
She's very considerate.
She seems sincere.
(Meanwhile, Jae Hyuk started cooking meat.)
(When he washed dishes with Si Woo,)
(he promised to cook meat for her.)
So, he's doing it for Si Woo.
- He must be. - To show her.
I listen to songs like "Sunflower" and "Flower."
That's unexpected.
(Peeking)
I don't like getting too immersed.
You drink pretty well.
But when I'm sober...
Wait, what was that look?
- Si Woo! - He's a little mad.
Si Woo, you should have noticed him cooking meat.
Right.
I thought it was my chance to show off my charm,
so I cooked meat.
But I saw how much she was talking to Jae Seung.
It bothered me.
(The meat is all cooked.)
Awesome.
- He cut it really well. - It's presented so nicely.
I just cut it with a knife.
(Nom)
What do you think?
It's good.
(Moaning)
(Everyone's enjoying it, but Si Woo isn't eating it.)
You're not hungry, are you?
- Did you eat a lot? - Yes.
I'm not that hungry.
(Feeling bad)
Si Woo, he cooked it for you.
Right.
Try to open up.
(Si Woo, open up to him.)
(Oblivious to their mismatched feelings,)
(the first night wears on.)
(A text message arrives at that moment.)
Wait, what?
(The Attraction Selection will begin now.)
(Send a text with the name of the person...)
(who made your heart flutter today.)
The one who made my heart flutter right now?
I guess so.
It's time for the Attraction Selection.
- What's this? - Attraction?
All right.
This is getting direct.
It's different from the First Impression Selection.
- They've felt things now. - Things have progressed.
Exactly.
(What changes did Hee Dong bring?)
You're looking around too much.
(To the person that made their heart flutter,)
(they send a text with their feelings.)
You guys seem very cautious.
I suddenly feel...
(Smiling)
I sent mine.
(They've all replied to the text message.)
(Their feelings will be delivered one by one.)
(Nervous)
(Who will get the first message?)
- We have a text. - Who got it?
Who got the text?
(Let's go to a scenic spot and take pictures together.)
- Jae Seung! - Jae Seung?
- Jae Seung. - "Let's go to a scenic spot..."
"and take pictures together."
(Who sent this message?)
- I wonder who it is. - Who is it?
You're on a date...
and your partner asks, "Who did you pick last night?"
I can see that happening.
In the Attraction Selection,
the message read,
"Let's go to a scenic spot and take pictures together."
I'm guessing it's Si Woo.
(In the living room after they moved in)
I also like listening to music,
watching movies, and taking pictures.
I also like taking pictures.
- Do you? - Yes.
I thought so.
Do you also take portraits?
Not really?
- Just landscapes? - Yes, landscapes.
(Si Woo and Jae Seung had similar interests.)
(Is the message from Si Woo as he assumes?)
(Peeking)
I sent it...
to Jae Seung.
He mentioned landscapes...
and said that he liked taking photos.
(The one who remembered Jae Seung's photography...)
(was Eun Byul.)
I wrote that I also liked scenic spots...
and that we should go and take pictures together.
It was Eun Byul.
Eun Byul sent the message.
- That means... - Is he getting his hopes up?
Oh, no. What's wrong with his life?
Is he getting his hopes up for nothing?
- It's so sad. - This breaks my heart.
- It hurts! - Gosh.
- Goodness. - This is insane.
You threw away a great girl.
- You really... - He picked Si Woo at first.
- He did. - have bad taste in women.
- Goodness. - Eun Byul is a great girl,
but Jae Seung can't easily change his mind.
Jae Seung picked Si Woo...
for the First Impression Selection.
Do you think...
The ones with "Jae" in their names...
- always stick to their guns. - Really?
You're right.
Who will it be?
Si Woo?
(Who did Jae Seung pick?)
(I'll look forward to your egg fried rice.)
(Jae Seung picked Yu Bin.)
I picked Yu Bin.
- Jae Seung picked Yu Bin? - Jae Seung?
- But you stick to your guns. - Seriously?
- You were wrong. - That's sticking to his guns?
Jae Seung!
He changed his mind before midnight.
- But he sticks to his guns! - Jae Seung!
- What? - He's pretty fickle.
(The romanticist isn't romantic anymore.)
Hey, romanticist!
- What a mean guy. - He's very fickle.
He's been talking to Si Woo all day,
but he picked Yu Bin.
I think he was disappointed after talking to her.
Si Woo's father is also here,
so please watch your words.
- Well, we'll see how it goes. - Sure.
I want to apologize on his behalf.
Gosh.
(Why did you pick Yu Bin?)
She was sitting to my left...
when we were having drinks, and I've been...
talking to her.
I thought it might be nice...
to talk to her in private, so I picked her.
(Lee Jae Seung chose Choi Yu Bin.)
(Who will get the message next?)
(It was nice talking to you while doing the dishes.)
(I hope to get to know you better.)
- Si Woo also got one. - Si Woo got one too.
- Naturally. - Si Woo.
Who sent her the message?
(Who sent the message?)
- I wonder who it is. - Who will it be?
The moment I saw it, I knew...
it was Jae Hyuk.
I was certain about Si Woo in this selection.
I mentioned doing the dishes so that she'd know.
I was hoping...
she would see that I had feelings for her.
I was determined to work for it,
and I couldn't help but be straightforward.
(Jae Hyuk bravely told her his feelings.)
- He just goes forward. - He does.
- That's admirable. - Yes.
Jae Hyuk is truly manly.
Are you saying Jae Seung is girly?
When he's talking to himself...
- But I heard it. - He was talking to himself.
Your son just picked my daughter.
Are you sure you want to do this?
- Did Jae Seung do anything wrong? - He was...
- He was comforting me. - Was that it?
Okay, then.
(He calms down, thinking about his son.)
(Who did Si Woo choose?)
It felt like I wasn't so obvious with my feelings.
So, I tried to express them through the message.
But I'm not sure if he'll recognize me.
(Her First Impression Selection was Hoo.)
(Jae Hyuk continues to express his feelings for her.)
(And Hee Dong gave her flowers.)
(Who did Si Woo pick?)
(You must have been hungry. Enjoy the food!)
I sent my message to Hee Dong in the Attraction Selection.
(She chose Hee Dong.)
- All right. - He got one.
- "You must have been hungry." - That sounds cute.
"Enjoy the food!"
Poor Jae Hyuk. He really sticks to his guns.
Is Jae Hyuk being dumped again?
Oh, dear.
Hee Dong was really enjoying the food...
across the table.
He was eating as if he had starved for a few days.
So, I wrote, "You must have been hungry. Enjoy the food."
Was it, "You must have been hungry. Was it delicious?"
But she wrote it...
kind of cute.
The vibe told me it was Yu Bin.
- Oh, he thinks it's Yu Bin. - He's mistaken.
- Because Yu Bin was... - Right.
He thinks it's from Yu Bin.
- He could... - You're right!
- I can see... - He's really mistaken.
(He thinks Si Woo's message is from Yu Bin.)
(Who will be chosen next for the Attraction Selection?)
(Your steak was better, Hoo.)
- Oh, my son. - He's got one!
- He got a message. - Hoo got a message too.
"Your steak was better!"
Who wrote that?
He's still got it!
- He's still got it. - Who sent it?
But Jae Hyuk also cooked steak.
"Your steak was better, Hoo."
That was the message.
I thought it was Yu Bin.
I was really torn about whom to pick.
I feel close with and thankful...
for Hoo.
And my other favorite is Hee Dong.
We talked a lot...
while playing that board game.
And he has the looks that I'm attracted to.
I'm not sure how I feel.
I thought hard...
and sent it to Hoo.
(Yu Bin chose Hoo.)
Good.
He's been carrying my bags all day...
and cooked delicious food for me.
I feel really close.
We're on the same wavelength, and I feel comfortable around him.
So, I picked Hoo.
(Choi Yu Bin chose Yoon Hoo.)
(Who did Hoo pick, then?)
- I'm the same. Time passed, - Right.
and I felt fine.
(You made my day...)
(with your positivity and cheerful attitude!)
I picked Yu Bin.
Yu Bin got two messages!
(Impressed)
- She's the new star! - Yu Bin!
- She's earned it today. - She's becoming the new star.
(The parents with daughters are disappointed.)
I was able to express...
my feelings more, thanks to Yu Bin.
She was friendly at first,
so I was able to match that...
and expressed a lot of things.
She made my day...
happier.
I certainly want to get to know her more.
They chose each other for the First Impression Selection...
- and the Attraction Selection. - They did.
- That's nice. - Hoo and Yu Bin.
- Let's keep it this way. - Yes.
(The dads are satisfied with the outcome.)
I can talk more.
(Currently, Si Woo has 1 vote,)
(and Yu Bin has 2 votes.)
(Lastly, Hee Dong's choice remains.)
- No way! - No!
"Thanks for helping me loosen up."
Yu Bin got his message!
- She has three messages. - Three.
Goodness.
(Thanks for helping me loosen up.)
I thought it was a mistake.
I thought you were pulling a prank.
I thought, "What? Why do I have three messages?"
I picked Yu Bin for the Attraction Selection.
I was pretty nervous when I first got here.
But she approached me first suggesting we play a board game.
(Do you want to play a board game?)
I felt relaxed from that moment.
So, I wanted to thank her for that.
It doesn't feel real.
On one hand, I'm also worried.
Like, "How should I make up my mind?"
So, I have a lot on my mind.
But I had so much fun, and thank you for today.
I won't be able to forget this Christmas.
- Totally. - She's right.
- That's so nice. - She got a Christmas gift.
It's Yu Bin's landslide victory.
How did things change so fast?
- When I... - These two switched.
sent her to camp at first...
- Camp? This isn't a camp. - It's not.
Do you think this is...
- It's not... - What is this? A summer camp?
Don't call it a camp.
Do you think this is an English camp?
When Yu Bin first told me she'd come here,
- she's honestly not that pretty... - She's beautiful!
or tall.
I told her not to get her feelings hurt...
- and to enjoy the food, at least. - I see.
Now that this is happening,
- I can't... - You're tearing up.
(He gets emotional about the 3 unexpected votes.)
Si Woo got three votes in the First Impression Selection.
This is an honor for my whole family.
I can't believe how it turned out.
(Anxious)
Si Woo's dad is talking significantly less now.
He suddenly seems tired.
He's clearly less excited now.
I mean,
no one's looking at Si Woo right now, so...
- Exactly. - Yes.
He's feeling rushed.
I can tell.
Jae Won is the only one who can't stop smiling.
- This is... - It's amazing.
(And they receive another text message.)
(All feelings have been delivered.)
(The Attraction Selection ends.)
Yes.
(Followed by the First Impression Selection,)
(Eun Byul wasn't chosen by anyone in the Attraction Selection.)
I just feel frustrated.
I should be talking to everyone,
but I don't know why I'm overthinking it.
It's so hard to say something.
This is harder than I imagined.
It's only the first day.
Eun Byul has charms that become apparent with time.
- Of course. - You never know what'll happen.
- That's right. - It's only the first day.
- Her charms will come out. - They'll surely come out.
It'll be the first meeting.
(All feelings have been delivered. The Attraction Selection ends.)
(Jae Hyuk belatedly checks the text message.)
My goodness.
I just wanted to go home.
I received the text message in front of everyone,
so it was hard to school my face.
Gosh, there's no need to be disappointed.
Jae Hyuk, it's nothing.
- It's nothing. - He must be upset.
- As a dad, my heart aches. - My goodness.
- It does, right? - Yes.
I don't know why boys leave Eun Byul alone...
- when she's so beautiful. - Exactly.
I let go of all expectations.
I'm looking into multiple men...
so that I can set up a blind date for my daughter.
You're very upset, right?
Words can't describe this feeling.
- I see. - But my kid doesn't have any flair.
- No? - What you see...
is her authentic self.
In my opinion, she's pretty, nice, and beautiful...
as she is.
But only adults recognize...
- her true worth. - That's right.
- I agree. - Kids can't see it.
- It's frustrating. - There's Jae Seung.
Jae Seung?
For goodness' sake.
What?
Jae Seung will go to Eun Byul.
Right now... All right.
Coach Shin Tae Yong, are you okay?
My heart aches.
My heart aches even more...
- to see my kid's heart ache. - Right.
We entered this show to be happy, but...
- It hasn't ended yet! - But still,
that's the current reality.
- Only some people are happy. - Yes.
He's talking big since his kid received three votes.
- He's acting spoiled. - Yes.
With time, Jae Hyuk's charms will come out.
- Then things will change. - Things will change indeed.
- I believe in him. - Right.
(First Attraction Selection)
(Shin Jae Hyuk chose Park Si Woo.)
(Yoon Hoo, Lee Jae Seung, and You Hee Dong chose Choi Yu Bin.)
(1 vote, 3 votes, 0 votes)
(Park Si Woo chose You Hee Dong. Choi Yu Bin chose Yoon Hoo.)
(Cho Eun Byul chose Lee Jae Seung.)
(1 vote, 1 vote, 0 votes, 1 vote)
(The Attraction Selection with many twists ends.)
(Kids go back to their rooms.)
(Si Woo and Eun Byul's room)
- You're deep in thought. - Yes.
- Is it obvious? - Yes.
I... I don't know.
I don't know how the other person feels.
I see.
She's unsure.
- Hee Dong gave her flowers, - That's right.
but he didn't choose her for the Attraction Selection.
- She's like, "What's this?" - "What's this?"
- She's unsure. - She doesn't understand him.
Hee Dong is a bit...
Perhaps I'm overthinking it,
but I don't know what's going on in his mind.
It makes me curious about him.
I can't predict anything about him.
(Whom do you think Hee Dong chose?)
I think...
he sent a text message to Yu Bin.
The two of them seemed to get along very well.
They talked a lot too.
It's understandable.
He just arrived here,
so he'd want to get to know people.
I think it's understandable.
(Si Woo predicts that Hee Dong chose Yu Bin.)
- She has a hunch. - Did she observe them?
She's sharp.
(In the room of Si Woo who became thoughtful)
- What are you guys up to? - Yu Bin visited.
- Hey, that room is... - She couldn't read the room.
- She could've waited. - Come on in.
How is everything doing?
Compared to our very first meeting,
- you seem more relaxed. - Yes, I've adjusted.
- I see. - Thank goodness.
Can I...
- Can I ask you a question? - Okay.
- A question? - A question?
Is there someone you're interested in?
She asked that right away.
Already?
Is there?
- I'm not sure yet. - Really?
There isn't anyone I absolutely like.
But there are people I want to know better.
Things will feel very different when we have a 1-on-1 conversation.
But we haven't had a chance to do that.
I had ice cream with Yoon Hoo...
- earlier. - I see.
We talked in a relaxed manner...
like friends, so it was enjoyable.
I felt like I had already gained a friend.
The person you want to get to know...
and the person you want to befriend are different.
Did you send a text message to both?
To both?
The one you want to befriend...
and the one you want to get to know.
No, I...
only sent it to someone I wanted to befriend...
after some deliberation.
(Yu Bin chose someone she was comfortable around.)
(If you exclude Yoon Hoo, who is on your mind the most?)
For me, it's Hee Dong.
It's just a guess, but I feel like...
one of those text messages is from him.
So I want to talk to Hee Dong.
Yu Bin felt like she had already gained a friend.
Yes.
She wants Hoo as a friend...
and Hee Dong as a boyfriend.
(Does she want Hee Dong as a boyfriend?)
Isn't that it?
A friend versus...
- a boyfriend. - Yes.
What are you drinking?
I can't sleep.
Do you usually have trouble sleeping?
- A little bit. - A little bit?
You can sit at the front.
The furnace is still warm.
- He guided her to six next to him. - Just like that?
He told her to take the warm seat...
- next to his. - Gosh, that's...
- He's sweet. - My goodness.
He's better than his dad.
It's warm.
I could fall asleep in front of the furnace.
That sounds nice.
Please take my drowsiness.
(They joke around with ease.)
Do you know...
how to turn off the lights in the room?
What?
"Do you know how do turn off the lights?"
- Why did he come out? - Can't Jae Seung do it himself?
Can't Jae Seung turn off the lights?
Please turn off the lights.
Isn't this the switch? Why doesn't it work?
You can go back. We'll look for it.
- Good night. - Good night.
What are you doing?
Let's try this.
What is it?
You open the book to a page for a fortune reading.
Is it real? I thought it was a fake book.
Since it's past midnight,
we should do a fortune reading for today.
Go first.
When I checked earlier, it said that I had crossed the line.
- Did your fortune reading say that? - Yes.
The written words will give us our fortune for tomorrow.
Which one of you has nice handwriting?
(He shows up when the atmosphere turns romantic.)
- Do you? - No.
I don't have nice handwriting either.
(Sighing)
- Jae Seung, read the room! - For goodness' sake.
Why wouldn't the light go off?
(Hoo's dad finds it funny.)
Are you reading?
It gives you today's fortune.
I thought you were smart.
I can't believe it.
- I think he came to tease Hoo. - Good night.
You should sleep with the light turned on.
(Thus, everyone goes back to the room.)
- Get some rest. - Bye.
(Hoo goes back to his room feeling disappointed.)
(Suddenly, he goes back out.)
That was sudden.
- Gosh. - Gosh, you're too hurried.
Hoo, slow down.
(He passes the Photo Room...)
(and arrives at the Letter Room.)
Despite everything, I wanted to express my feelings...
as a tough guy.
- He wants to express his feelings. - That's right.
I guess he'll write a letter.
Hoo springs into action.
What should I do?
(Hesitant)
(After hesitation, he writes the first word.)
(Thinking)
(Writing)
Still, telling someone outright...
that I'm interested in her...
is my way.
(The writing paper is in tatters.)
(He takes out a new one.)
I just kept it simple.
Since we had just met,
a long letter would've been too much.
(Will the letter reach the recipient safely?)
(Meanwhile, Jae Hyuk's room)
(There's a letter on his bed.)
What? Did he receive a letter?
- What? - He isn't in the Letter Room.
(Someone left Jae Hyuk a letter.)
Why is there a letter?
(He finally smiles.)
- Jae Hyuk smiled. - He smiled.
- What? - It must be from a resident.
- Who sent it? - Did someone send a letter...
- before Yoon Hoo did? - That must be it.
It's express delivery.
- It's... - What is it?
(What's the letter he got via express delivery?)
"Go to bed first, Jae Hyuk!"
(It was written by his polite roommate.)
(Flustered)
(No one guessed the identity of the sender.)
- Gosh. - Is he a comedian?
Gosh, Jae Hyuk.
My son is so polite.
Jae Hyuk got disappointed again.
Gosh, my Jae Hyuk.
I had hopes when he smiled.
(The unforgettable Christmas passes.)
(The daughters wake up early.)
(Yu Bin finished getting ready and heads outside.)
(She goes up the stairs...)
(and arrives at the Letter Room.)
(She checks her mailbox for letters.)
(Smiling)
(Yu Bin's smile makes the dads happy.)
She likes it.
(Last night,)
(Yoon Hoo poured out his heart in the letter.)
(From the moment we met today, I thought you were a beauty.)
(Your cheerful and bubbly personality...)
(put me in a good mood today.)
(I want to get to know you better over a meal!)
"Over a meal."
Why does he sound so homely?
I like how innocent Hoo is.
The way he calls her a beauty puts a smile on my face.
(Her steps become light after reading the letter.)
(She reads it...)
(and reads it again.)
(She puts the letter at a place where she can see it.)
(Your cheerful and bubbly personality...)
(put me in a good mood today.)
(I want to get to know you better over a meal!)
Hoo wrote the letter at the perfect timing...
when Yu Bin was about to get swayed.
Nice timing.
What do you think of the letter?
It's nearly perfect.
- Perfect. - Yes.
- Seriously. - "Let's have a meal together."
My future son-in-law wrote a nice letter...
- to my daughter. - Your future son-in-law?
Isn't it too soon for that?
I could feel his innocence.
I think Hoo made a decisive move.
- He acted before the others. - Yes.
That's right. Dads with sons keep going,
"There'll be a hook."
- "He'll do something big later." - That's right.
But little strokes fell great oaks.
That's right.
Small things add up.
- Small things add up. - Yes.
Is that directed at Jae Hyuk and Jae Seung?
Yes. Hee Dong should take note too.
Hoo moved...
- a bit more quickly. - He's more forward.
Love is all about the speed.
That's right. The timing matters.
(Hoo and Jae Hyuk's room)
(The man who wrote the letter, Hoo is still asleep.)
(Jae Seung and Hee Dong's room)
(Tossing)
(Jae Seung is the first to wake up among men.)
(Halting)
- What? He got something. - He got something.
(Gift boxes are outside the door.)
(Lee Jae Seung, for the recipient only)
It's a gift box.
(What's inside the gift box?)
- What? He got something. - He got something.
(Gift boxes are outside the door.)
(Lee Jae Seung, for the recipient only)
It's a gift box.
(What's inside the special gift box?)
When I woke up and went out, I saw a present.
I wondered if it was a Christmas present.
I brought it inside the room feeling happy.
(Jae Seung opens the box.)
(First-come First-served Date)
(It's Dad's winning present for a date.)
Dad's winning present for a date.
"Deliver the present to the woman of your choice..."
"and ask her out on a date."
(They must deliver the present and ask women out on a date.)
"The dates will take place on a first-come, first-served basis."
"If your desired date has already matched with another,"
"you must ask out someone else."
- Yes. - They just need to act fast.
(Dads' presents for the First-come First-served Date)
But there are 4 men and 3 women.
- Yes. - Yes.
One man will be left at home.
- The sons shouldn't be sleeping. - I know.
- They should wake up. - They should call dibs.
- That's right. - Jae Seung should run.
The instructions told me to ask someone out on a date.
It was on a first-come, first-served basis.
- That's right. - I was a bit taken aback.
Inside the box was a present my dad had prepared...
so that I could hand it over as I asked someone out on a date.
Which present did his dad prepare?
I know.
(I hope it's something my daughter likes.)
It was a book of poems.
- A book of poems. - A book of poems?
- A book of poems? - A book of poems?
When I was young,
men gave a book of poems to women.
They read poems to women.
I guess your son was influenced.
There's a poem by Na Tae Ju,
- right? - Right.
"One becomes pretty with frequent meetings."
"One becomes lovely with a long relationship."
"You did." When I read such poems to women,
they became touched.
But parents with daughters are going,
- "Will a book of poems work?" - A book of poems?
They look unimpressed.
A book of poems.
- Kids these days won't get it. - No, they won't.
And while Jae Seung has a poker face,
he's a bit sentimental.
His sentimentality will come out when he reads poems.
He should find himself a girl...
- who can accept that. - That's right.
If a girl can't accept that, she won't be a good match.
I really hope it works out.
(He wraps it up hurriedly.)
I'm nervous. What should I do?
Who will like a book of poems?
A book of poems might lead to marriage.
(Shaking his head)
(Si Woo and Eun Byul's room)
(Women receive a text message.)
"Today, there'll be the first date..."
"that reflects men's preferences."
"Men will ask women out..."
"on a first-come, first-served basis."
"Women can't say no to a date."
They can't say no.
When I received a text message about the First-come First-served Date,
I hoped to get asked out first.
Men will ask women out on a date.
It gave me many thoughts...
and worries. Yes. That's my current state.
The day before,
I didn't get any votes for the Attraction Selection.
So I thought, "I won't go out on a date today."
Eun Byul is worried that no one will ask her out.
Eun Byul will get asked out.
- One man will stay home. - That's right.
(Dads with sons become nervous.)
(The sons are still asleep,)
(unaware of the First-come First-served Date.)
He even wrote a letter before he went to sleep.
It's first-come first-served basis, so he needs to hurry.
Is Jae Seung not going until he wakes up?
He should hurry.
(Jae Seung is the first to leave the room.)
If he's leaving now,
he could ask anyone out.
- That's Yu Bin's room. - Yu Bin.
- What? - What?
He's not going to Yu Bin's room.
(He heads to the men's room, not women's.)
How was your sleep?
Did you wake up to the sound of the door opening? I'm sorry.
I'm awake.
I was so bored.
Hey, now's not the time to be doing that.
- Hey. - He's bored?
You have a present in front.
Check it out.
Did something arrive?
Yes, a present.
- A present? - Yes.
Yours is in front of the door.
(Jae Seung spreads the news like a pigeon.)
It's first-come first-served, but he didn't leave first.
He could've just left first.
He's waking up his competitors.
How can he do that?
(Why did you tell everyone?)
Rather than knowing it...
and going to them myself,
I thought it'd be better if everyone knew.
(He prefers fair play.)
Jae Seung, what are you doing?
My goodness.
(Jae Hyuk takes the gift box in front of his room.)
(What date present did Tae Yong get?)
It was perfume.
(Perfume)
- Perfume. - Perfume.
Tae Yong gave perfume to his son.
- This is a nice gift. - I see.
Since Jae Hyuk plays sports,
he smells strongly of sweat.
I want him to smell refreshing...
when going on a date with a girl.
Isn't that supposed to be a gift, not for himself?
He can spray it on his date.
Everyone has different preferences...
- in perfume. - Is that so?
- Depending on the person... - His date will like it.
- Watch until the end. - Okay.
I think it's better than a poetry book.
- Why? - He must've bought a good one.
My dad likes perfume,
and so do I.
I think that's why he chose perfume.
I hope the person I'm asking out...
likes it.
What is he doing?
He finally got up.
(Yoon Hoo goes to check the gift box, still half-asleep.)
It's behind you, Hoo.
He's still not fully awake. What's wrong with him?
(Staggering)
Where is he going?
It's cold.
(He spots it.)
- He found it. - He saw it.
He's so funny.
- He's just like when he was young. - He really is.
(What present did Min Soo get?)
My father got...
a pair of gloves and earmuffs.
- Earmuffs. - Nice.
Gloves and earmuffs.
(The parents of daughters are satisfied with the present.)
That's pretty nice.
(Satisfied)
You're smart.
He was smart about it.
I thought my date would like it...
when she got it.
He might've used this method...
when he tried to appeal to women when he was my age.
- Even your son knows. - Did you do that?
I didn't do that.
- It's quite cold there. - Yes.
So I thought gloves and earmuffs would be nice.
You wanted your son to look good in their eyes.
Yes. But it's not about the physical warmness.
It's about how warm he is.
- Mentally. - How warm-hearted he is.
Convey your warm-heartedness.
Say something like that to your date.
That's what I'm hoping for.
Out of the three fathers,
that's the most likable present.
- Yes. - And they'll play the music.
(Satisfied)
(Hee Dong is checking his present box.)
(What date present did Tae Woong prepare?)
It was a necklace.
(A bear-shaped necklace)
(A necklace?)
- A necklace? - That's worldly.
(It's expensive.)
This is...
It's worldly.
It sure sets him apart.
The presents are getting more and more impactful.
- That's a strong one. - Yes.
Actually, very few ladies...
dislike accessories.
- That's true. - So...
I thought this could work well.
The poetry book is too weak.
The poetry book will be pushed aside.
When I saw it, I thought, "Dad really prepared this?"
I couldn't believe it.
I thought my dad was wittier...
than I took him to be.
I think it's a really good present.
My gosh.
(Which son will deliver the date present first?)
Have the rest done it already?
No, none of them are awake yet.
You should go quickly.
- Why isn't he doing it? - Why isn't he doing it?
I don't think anyone woke up.
- I think so too. - Right?
(They're waiting because they think the girls are still sleeping.)
I thought they could still be sleeping.
It felt a bit uncomfortable to be the first to do it.
More than worrying about...
the other guys asking them out first,
I didn't know what to say when giving them the present,
so I took some time to think about it.
(The sons are staying in the room due to their own reasons.)
They're so frustrating.
What is he doing? Goodness.
It was first-come first-served, so I should ask her out quickly.
But I thought she would prefer it if I looked decent.
So I washed quickly.
But it'll be too late once you wash up.
- Exactly. - Yes.
I'm so frustrated. What is he doing?
He's driving me insane.
(While the sons are deep in thought,)
(the girls have been long awake and are waiting for them.)
Did you ask anyone out?
- Not yet. - I see.
(Meanwhile, Yoon Hoo finishes washing.)
(Glancing)
- You all haven't? - No.
(Yoon Hoo runs without looking back.)
- Look at him. - He's running.
- Way to go, son! - Yoon Hoo.
Go!
(This is it.)
I haven't even dried my hair yet.
But since it's first-come first-served,
I thought I should hurry.
(Turning around)
- Dry your hair. - What?
That's it! Just say it! Spit it out!
Who is it, Hoo?
(Who is in Yoon Hoo's mind?)
I haven't even dried my hair yet.
But since it's first-come first-served,
I thought I should hurry.
(Turning around)
- Dry your hair. - What?
That's it! Just say it! Spit it out!
Who is it, Hoo?
(Which daughter will Hoo ask out?)
Hello.
Yu Bin, can I have a moment with you?
- Can you stir it once? - I'll keep an eye on it.
(Yoon Hoo chooses Yu Bin.)
- That's it! - He called Yu Bin.
That's it!
- That's my son. - He's so straightforward.
Nice. That's how a man should be.
- That's cheating. - Yes.
- A man... - He's disqualified.
- Yes? What... - Please go inside.
Me? Why...
Why am I in here?
- So nobody can snatch you away. - I see.
- "So nobody can snatch you away." - "So nobody can snatch you away."
(What he said makes her dad happy.)
That's it!
- That's cheating! - What a nice thing to say.
Women are deeply moved...
- when they hear stuff like this. - Of course.
- Yu Bin is moved now. - Yes, she is.
(In a rush, he wears Jae Hyuk's jacket.)
- Jae Hyuk's jacket? - What?
What is he doing?
- It isn't even his. - What is he doing?
(Knocking)
- Hello. - Hello.
They're my presents for you.
My gosh.
What are these for?
Go on a date with me.
Really? Sure.
Really? Sure, I'd like that.
Nobody asked you out yet, right?
No.
- Is this first-come first-served? - That's right.
- I see. Thank you. - No problem.
(Yu Bin is the first to be asked out by Yoon Hoo.)
The presents would keep me warm during the date,
so I liked it.
I felt very good.
She must be on cloud nine.
(Those left now are Hee Dong, Jae Seung,)
(and Jae Hyuk.)
- I think it's almost done. - Yes.
(Eun Byul and Si Woo are waiting for the guys to ask them out.)
This is bad.
We should be saying that. This is bad.
(Checking his face)
(After looking in the mirror, Jae Seung finally gets going.)
I have one person in mind.
Excuse me, Si Woo. Could I...
- speak with you for a moment? - Okay.
(The girl on Jae Seung's mind is Si Woo.)
Si Woo.
He's ever so consistent.
He wavered for a moment,
but he went back to being consistent.
(Wiping his nose)
- Please wait for a while. - Okay.
(He takes the poetry book with a fluttering heart.)
Well...
I'd like to ask you out on a date.
- Here. - Thank you.
(Jae Seung asks Si Woo out as he gives her the poetry book.)
(Feeling embarrassed, he runs away quickly.)
(Did you like Jae Seung's present?)
Jae Seung came to me first...
and gave me...
a collection of poems.
- Will she like it? - Does Si Woo like poetry?
Does she like it?
I really like the poem "Grass Flower..."
and I read it often.
I thought, "Is this coincidence?"
His dad chose it.
- And it worked. - She likes it.
(The poetry book captures Si Woo's heart.)
(Why did you ask Si Woo out on a date?)
I remember asking her...
if she would be okay with going on a date with me.
(During their first meeting)
I like taking pictures.
(They both like taking pictures.)
During the Attraction Selection,
I think the message I got was,
"Let's go to a scenic spot and take pictures together."
I thought that was from Si Woo.
It'd be nice to go on a date with her...
to a place with a nice view.
That's why he asked Si Woo out.
But Eun Byul sent that text.
The date will be tough.
He thought long and hard.
I think Jae Seung is a fool.
He's so dense.
- That can't be true. - He's so dense.
He's unaware of my daughter's feelings.
- The date will be rough. - Why?
Jae Seung thinks Si Woo sent him the text.
- Yes. - But once the truth comes out...
Yes.
It'll be...
They can become closer before they find out the truth.
- Yes. - You never know how it'll turn out.
(Meanwhile, Eun Byul is left alone in the kitchen.)
I voted for Jae Seung.
So I hoped...
to go on a 1-on-1 date with Jae Seung.
Oh, dear.
(Upset)
It's a pity,
but I think I have a lot of opportunities to talk with him.
Did you ask someone out?
- I did. - You did?
- I'll go now. - Do your best.
Are we supposed to go one by one...
when it's first-come first-served?
Shouldn't we fight to go first?
- That's right. - That's right.
I should go, but...
- Did you ask someone out? - Yes.
- You did? - Yes.
Really? Then I...
I didn't know you guys already did.
- Hee Dong. - You...
(Meanwhile, Jae Hyuk goes to ask a girl out.)
I had one person in mind to ask out on a date.
So I didn't need to think.
I wanted to ask Si Woo out.
During the Attraction Selection on the first day,
I chose Si Woo.
I want to go on a 1-on-1 date with her...
and get to know her better.
- Oh, dear. - He...
But Si Woo is already chosen, right?
- She is. - She is.
What was he doing just now?
Exactly.
He should act fast.
(Feeling bad for him)
I'll put it here.
Eggs again?
- Are you cooking eggs? - I'm boiling eggs.
Did someone ask you out already?
- Yes. - Someone did?
Really?
Gosh, Jae Hyuk.
Gosh, you jerk.
- Jae Hyuk. - Oh, Jae Hyuk.
Even the extra time is over.
Jae Hyuk is one step behind.
I feel bad for him.
Me too.
It's too bad.
Oh, well...
I see. Have fun.
Next time...
I regretted it.
I should've gone to her room and asked her out.
- Exactly. - Yes.
- He could've gone. - You should've acted fast.
He had the chance.
Why does he always regret belatedly?
Whose son is he?
Seriously.
This is frustrating.
(Knocking)
He went to Eun Byul.
- Hello. - Eun Byul.
Would you like to go on a date with me today?
Sure, sounds good.
And this is my present.
What is this?
It's perfume. Do you like perfume?
Yes, I do.
- Thank you. - Welcome.
- See you later. - See you.
- Bye. - Thank you.
Jae Hyuk chose me.
I think I was his second choice.
- She knows. - I'm sorry, Eun Byul.
Since she was with them.
Before he chose me,
Si Woo was in the kitchen.
"He must want to ask her out."
So I left the kitchen...
for them to talk in private.
So I thought he's interested in me...
second to Si Woo.
- That's sad. - Although...
I chose Jae Seung,
I wanted to know more about Jae Hyuk too.
So I was looking forward to it.
Thank you, Eun Byul.
- Thank you. - He's thanking her.
This breaks my heart.
I didn't feel this way even when I was on the World Cup.
- He... - This is hard to watch.
(Suffering mentally)
This is so hard.
This is harder than playing on the World Cup.
For me, this is harder than giving birth.
Giving a birth to another baby would be easier.
- This is so hard to watch. - The mother knows...
that her daughter was a second choice.
- Will Hee Dong stay in the dorm? - What about Hee Dong?
He still...
- Did you do it? - Yes.
(Shaking his head)
- I got a text. - You got a text?
"All the dates have been matched."
I see.
Were you asked out?
Then we're happy.
But doesn't that mean...
- one person is left out? - Exactly.
Can they not ask anyone out?
- It looks like it. - Really?
I put it inside.
(Si Woo seems troubled at the mention of Hee Dong.)
I was concerned.
I was concerned about him.
I even thought, "Did he not ask anyone out on purpose?"
He may be laid-back,
but this is an important moment.
I don't think he would've...
just done nothing.
"Why didn't he ask someone out?"
"Is he alone? Will he stay here alone?"
"What will he do when he's alone?"
I kept thinking about it.
(Si Woo actually wanted Hee Dong to ask her out.)
What will I do?
You didn't ask the new person out, right?
- No. - Then you'll probably go...
on a date with the new person.
- Someone new is joining? - A latecomer.
- Someone new is joining? - There's someone new?
The book.
I'll go use it.
(He opens the gift box again.)
(There's another piece of information.)
(A picture of a woman's back view)
(There's a new woman resident. If you want to ask her out...)
(on a date, write a letter on the back of the picture...)
(and put it in the postbox in front of the door.)
In the gift box...
is the information about the new woman resident,
only known to men.
- I see. - The daughters don't know about it.
- This is why he was so relaxed. - Then was Hee Dong...
waiting for this on purpose?
He could've been.
He has something to fall back on.
I guess so.
He's not the type to think that far.
Is he not?
He doesn't think that far.
- Is that a picture? - It's a picture.
- It's her picture. - Her picture?
- Really? - Yes.
- She has long hair. - She has long hair.
She appears to be a strong female latecomer.
I think she draws.
(Making the parents with daughters nervous)
Maybe she majors in arts.
(All four sons received her picture.)
(Did you consider the new resident...)
(when you requested a date?)
I wasn't torn.
I was interested in Yu Bin the most.
- Cool. - Cool.
He's certain.
When I saw it,
all I thought about was asking Si Woo to go on a date.
It didn't really impress me.
Men are firm.
First of all,
I don't tend to step forward.
I'm not certain about whom to choose yet.
When I saw the new resident's picture,
I thought she'd be okay.
(She'd be okay.)
Since I'm new, and so is she,
I thought we might get along.
- Now it makes sense. - Right.
(Requesting a date to the new woman)
(Writing his greeting carefully)
(How did Hee Dong greet her?)
(One is bothered.)
(While the other is excited.)
(Excited to send the postcard)
(What is the new woman like?)
Si Woo expects...
Hee Dong to be left alone.
- She's not expecting him... - Right.
- to see the new resident. - Right.
- Women don't know about her. - No.
Things are getting odd.
What if the new resident...
gets along with Hee Dong?
- Then Si Woo will feel betrayed. - Then...
- This is getting... - She'll be annoyed.
This is getting dangerous.
(Meanwhile, the new resident...)
(received Hee Dong's postcard.)
(Hello. Let's hang out together today.)
- "Hello." - "Let's hang out together today."
"Let's hang out together today."
(Hello. Let's hang out together today.)
Let me see.
(Even her lips are already so pretty.)
(Exclaiming)
She's pretty.
(A few hours later)
(Hee Dong waits for the new resident.)
(The new resident...)
(who excites Hee Dong)
- Hello. - Hello.
- Have a seat. - Yes. Hi.
- Nice to meet you. - Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
(Nice to meet you.)
My heart suddenly pounded.
It was a good idea...
to request the new resident a date.
(It was a good idea.)
I liked her so much.
(Who is the woman that got Hee Dong excited?)
(Finally, the first date)
(From the fire show...)
(to a fall)
(The parents are frustrated by their awful dates.)
I thought she was cute for trying hard.
(If I ask you to do something,)
(would you do it?)
(If you ask, I'll have to do it.)
(Do you want me to do it?)
(The unfaltering expression brings them close.)
(What are they doing?)
I like Hee Dong the most.
(The atmosphere changed after one day.)
It was so hard...
to see them together.