(The third day's Attraction Selection)
(Shin Jae Hyuk)
(Two of the girls' hearts headed to the same guy.)
(Si Woo chose Hee Dong.)
I'm a little confused.
Whether my feelings for Hoo are bigger...
than my feelings for Hee Dong.
(Last night, Yu Bin wavered.)
(The next day, it was the girls' 1st Choice Date.)
(The restaurant where...)
(Hee Dong, Jae Seung, and Yoon Hoo are waiting)
(Yu Bin has arrived to find her 1st choice.)
Hi.
(And another girl has come.)
(Si Woo came to Hee Dong, her Attraction Selection 1st choice.)
(How's the girls' 1st Choice Date going to be?)
(Episode 7: Confession)
(Park Si Woo and Choi Yu Bin are to leave with their 1st choice.)
The daughters will now go on a date with the guy they chose...
- as their first choice.
- Correct.
(Starting now, )
(the girls are going on a date with their 1st choice guy.)
(First, Si Woo's choice was...)
(Park Si Woo's Attraction Selection 1st choice was You Hee Dong.)
Going on a date with Si Woo made me happy.
I was over the moon.
- Yes, Si Woo.
- As we expected.
- Si Woo.
- She chose Hee Dong.
Even Hee Dong's first choice was Si Woo.
- Yes.
- Right?
(Si Woo and Hee Dong are each other's 1st choice.)
(Their date has finally come true.)
(Who was Yu Bin's Attraction Selection 1st choice?)
(Was it Yoon Hoo as always?)
(Or Hee Dong, who made her heart flutter?)
I can't even make a guess.
- Yu Bin...
- What will happen to Yu Bin?
- Exactly.
- Hoo is likely her choice.
- But who is it?
- It's 1 of the 3.
(Yu Bin's choice will decide the course of the date.)
(Is it a 1-on-1 date with Yoon Hoo?)
(Or is it a 2-on-1 date with Si Woo and Hee Dong?)
(Who did Yu Bin choose?)
(Choi Yu Bin's Attraction Selection 1st choice was You Hee Dong.)
Choi Yu Bin.
(Yu Bin's 1st choice was Hee Dong!)
Yu Bin's first choice...
- was You Hee Dong.
- That's it! They're equal now.
- Are they?
- Yes.
There's no need to feel bad, Hoo.
He's right. Unbelievable.
What was that about having ice cream last night?
The two chose each other...
- as their 2nd choice.
- They were each other's 2nd choice.
Is that how it works?
- Interesting.
- For real?
- The two got along really well.
- Yes.
Even their decisions were of one mind.
We're practically watching...
- "Love and War." - Totally.
The two chose each other...
- as their second choice.
- Exactly.
(Choi Yu Bin's Attraction Selection 1st choice was You Hee Dong.)
How did this happen?
(Yoon Hoo's mouth feels dry.)
(Glancing)
(It's bad news for Si Woo going on a date with Hee Dong.)
Goodness.
What about Si Woo? Is it a date together?
- Yes.
- Yes, together.
It's a 2-on-1 date.
- Si Woo doesn't get a 1-on-1 date.
- No.
Shall we leave?
This is fun.
"This is fun."
I was conscious of Hoo.
But I chose Hoo in the first...
three decisions we had to make.
(First Impression)
(Thanks for saying I lightened the mood.)
(Let's get along well!)
(Your steak was much better, Yoon Hoo.)
(Get up early tomorrow morning! You've got three chances!)
(Yu Bin kept choosing Yoon Hoo until the second day.)
I felt new emotions after a date with a new person.
Sending it to another person seemed like a good idea,
so that was what I did.
(Only yesterday, Yu Bin chose Hee Dong as her 1st choice.)
Either way, Hoo chose me as his second choice,
and I chose him as my second choice.
There's no need for either of us to feel guilty.
- The couple isn't final.
- Exactly.
It's natural to be interested in someone else.
- Of course.
- It's even now. The end.
I, personally, had no expectations.
But are you okay?
Yes. I'm not entirely sure how I feel.
We did talk last night.
But it was after the Attraction Selection.
It's best that we talk again.
"Something is wrong. Something's gone wrong."
Either way, my feelings are set in stone.
But, half out of courtesy...
and simply because...
she was the person I spent the most time with that day,
I chose Si Woo.
(He chose Si Woo, his date of the day.)
I thought Yu Bin chose Hee Dong for the same reason.
Or her feelings might have changed.
Those were what crossed my mind.
(Yoon Hoo is worried about Yu Bin's choice.)
Let's go back and work out.
- Shall we?
- Yes.
You two should grab a drink.
- Go ahead.
- Hoo.
At least Jae Seung won't feel lonely with Yoon Hoo.
I'm not sure...
- if that's any comfort.
- How did Hoo end up like that?
- Hoo used to be popular.
- Exactly.
(Meanwhile, Seo Yoon heads to Jae Hyuk, her 1st choice.)
(Jae Hyuk waits without knowing who it'll be.)
Back then, I was so nervous.
I don't know. Until that moment,
I was all excited.
But thinking we were about to meet again,
it made me all nervous.
There must be a reason she's nervous.
I'm curious.
(Why is Seo Yoon so nervous?)
(Before heading to her date)
We were on the same page about many things.
I was amused and such.
We kept teasing each other too.
I'm the type who prefers it that way.
Being comfortable together and all.
But do I have feelings for him as a friend...
or as a guy?
My head was a total mess.
Today helped me realize my feelings.
About Jae Hyuk?
Yes, when I was in the car,
I was so nervous.
Had I thought he was just a friend,
I wouldn't have felt like that. Right?
- You mean you, right?
- Yes.
I kept thinking over and over again.
We clicked well when talking,
and I had the most fun with him.
Up until this morning, I felt a little lost.
I'm going to stop thinking.
(Seo Yoon was confused about why yesterday's date was fun.)
When I waited...
and wasn't chosen,
I realized my feelings for him...
weren't for a friend.
Back when I was waiting for him.
Rather than not being chosen,
it was more about confirming my own feelings.
- Gosh.
- I see.
It's feelings of love.
(Seo Yoon realized her feelings for Jae Hyuk.)
She was able to confirm her own feelings.
Seo Yoon might start acting proactively.
- From now on.
- Cool.
- She's really cool.
- Yes.
(Unlike before, with butterflies in her stomach, )
(Seo Yoon heads over to meet Jae Hyuk.)
- Hey.
- Hi.
Would you like coffee or anything?
Yes, please.
I did think Seo Yoon might come.
I chose her as my first choice, as the date we had was great.
Seo Yoon had as much fun as I did,
so I thought she could've picked me as her first choice.
I'm really grateful.
Aren't you cold? Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
Would you like this?
Thank you.
What were you doing?
I was just here all along.
- Really?
- Yes.
With someone else.
- Right.
- He was hanging out with Eun Byul.
Thank you for coming.
- What did it say?
- Sorry?
What did the text say?
- Is it a secret?
- No.
(Eun Byul's 1st choice is Jae Hyuk.)
- She's here.
- Eun Byul is here.
The text doesn't matter right now.
- Eun Byul has returned.
- Eun Byul is here.
It's a 2-on-1 date here as well.
- Gosh.
- This is practically...
the rich get richer, and the poor get poorer.
Only the chosen are chosen again.
Hoo and Jae Seung are...
I believe Jae Hyuk must act wisely in this situation.
- Of course.
- Yes.
It's a good opportunity for Jae Hyuk,
- but also a pinch.
- Yes.
- He might lose both.
- Both might dump him.
- He might get dumped.
(Eun Byul is back.)
Hi.
- Hi.
Oh, dear.
I'll take a seat here.
Would you like something to drink?
- No, I'm fine.
- No?
- She already had one earlier.
- Goodness.
- In the same place.
- Exactly.
(The Girl's 1st Choice Date:)
(Woo Seo Yoon, Cho Eun Byul, and Shin Jae Hyuk)
(Restless)
It's...
Would you like to share it if I cut it?
I'm okay.
- Are you?
- Yes.
- Why?
- Dig in.
I had one earlier.
You did?
(Shaking)
(He accidentally drops the bread.)
I'll eat this piece.
(Flustered)
- He's nervous.
- That's cute.
(Seeing Jae Hyuk nervous is a first.)
(The girls find this situation funny.)
Oh, gosh.
I need digestive medicine.
Anyone would be at a loss.
- I might need one.
- This is awkward.
Can't we just relax?
Sure.
(Only awkward laughter)
(But here, it's much quieter.)
(Sighing)
- This is...
- They're interesting too.
There's going to be a scuffle.
I totally agree.
- Because of Hee Dong, - Yes?
They were conscious of each other and got on each other's nerves.
- Totally.
- Right?
I hope Yu Bin doesn't butt in too much.
- Is that what you hope for?
- I doubt it.
- Yes, quietly.
- You think she'll butt in?
My wish is that she only eats.
But from what we saw, she's going to be enthusiastic.
- Yu Bin...
- Yu Bin might take the lead.
That's what worries me the most.
- I have a bad feeling about it.
- She's bright and all.
- True.
- I mean Yu Bin.
No offense to the three parents,
but we're having a blast here.
(The Girl's 1st Choice Date:)
(Park Si Woo, Choi Yu Bin, and You Hee Dong)
I'm about to lose it.
This is tough.
It was a mix of bleakness, feeling lost, and awkwardness.
I guess it was more awkward...
because I didn't know what to say.
Let's just chat comfortably...
- and go back.
- Sure.
This awkward...
- We're hanging out, after all.
- Indeed.
The three of us are close.
This is my favorite mix.
- Do you mean that?
- Of course.
Are you going to tell other people that they're your favorite?
Well,
who knows?
(What?)
Gangneung...
I've always wanted to go to the ocean.
Not like this, though.
I've never been...
on a date with two people.
I was quite flustered by that.
Having to watch Yu Bin and Hee Dong in the same place...
was very difficult.
- Right.
- Naturally.
It must be upsetting.
Si Woo is serious about this,
and Yu Bin doesn't care if it works out or not.
He says his daughter is sincere.
Yes, she's sincere.
She is, indeed.
(Hoo and Jae Seung coming back home)
Oh, boy.
- These two...
- This is good.
I didn't think they'd show us these two.
Thank you!
We'll give you a peek.
That harmonica sound is so sad.
I'm already worried about tomorrow.
(Laughing awkwardly)
To be honest, I thought I'd be the only one left.
- Why?
- Because...
I thought you'd go with Yu Bin,
and Hee Dong would go with Si Woo.
It was really unexpected.
- It was.
- Totally.
- These two lonely men.
- It's such a sad song!
Jae Hyuk must be on a date with two women as well.
Right.
(Having mixed feelings)
Do you know who Seo Yoon is interested in?
Jae Hyuk.
- Eun Byul too?
- Yes.
I see.
I was slightly expecting Eun Byul...
to pick me, so it was disappointing.
But I can't do anything about how she feels.
They're getting really quiet.
(These two go back home with a lonesome air.)
A record bar?
(Park Si Woo, Choi Yu Bin, and You Hee Don at a LP bar)
(Hee Dong gets Si Woo's chair first.)
He pulls the chair out for Si Woo.
He also pulls the chair out for Yu Bin.
So, they're numbers 1 and 2?
Hee Dong will have to do a really good job here.
- He has a lot on his shoulders.
- This is uncomfortable.
(Son, good luck being tactful.)
Cheers?
- Cheers.
This is good.
What do you think?
Try mine using the brim.
It's really good.
(They naturally switch drinks.)
Good, right?
My drink is better.
Maybe you didn't stir it.
You know, there's syrup on the bottom.
- Try stirring it.
- Maybe I should.
(The two seem pretty close.)
Is yours any good?
Do you want to try it?
Maybe a little. I'll try a sip.
Do you want to try mine?
I don't really like peaches.
Really?
(I don't really like peaches.)
- Si Woo said, "No, thank you." - Si Woo just...
- That was...
- She said no.
That came from her heart.
(He tries Si Woo's cocktail as well.)
Is it good?
You don't like it.
(Glancing)
We'll probably reveal our ages today, right?
Do you want to know our age?
I'm dying to know.
We're all speaking to each other in the honorifics.
Why don't we drop the honorifics?
- Should we...
- Right now.
We're free to use the non-honorifics.
- Right. Regardless of our age...
- Yes.
We should drop the honorifics.
- Should we?
Yu Bin.
I'll continue to use the honorifics.
Si Woo.
- Si Woo.
- Yes?
We just agreed on it. You should join us.
I'm sorry.
I didn't want to drop the honorifics...
when there were three.
I wanted to speak calmly...
when I was alone with Hee Dong...
and naturally start using the non-honorifics.
You feel more comfortable with the non-honorifics.
It was the first time I went out with Hee Dong,
so it didn't feel right to drop the honorifics...
and feel comfortable with each other.
(Si Woo doesn't want to drop the honorifics just yet.)
We'll get even closer.
I guess so.
Si Woo...
Wait,
are you older or younger?
(What did she just say?)
Hey, Yu Bin.
Yes, ma'am.
"Yes, ma'am."
She was instantly intimidated.
(With subtle tension in the air...)
- Here's your food.
- Thank you.
- Should I scoop some for you?
- That's okay.
Who will he give it to first?
- You eat a lot, right?
- Yes.
I'll have some garlic.
- That's enough.
- Okay.
Give me some, kid.
- What?
- Me?
Yu Bin!
Do you want the chicken?
I think that's enough.
- You like it?
- What?
- I like it.
That's good.
We only agreed on using the non-honorifics.
Why the tone change?
Is that the tone we're using from now on?
Sorry.
And in ten minutes, you'll say,
"Please get in, Yu Bin."
You might.
They were constantly making jokes.
It felt like I was intruding two close friends.
It felt like I had to leave.
(Joking)
Would you like me to leave?
No.
She's getting on her nerves.
Now, this...
(Just then, Si Woo leaves?)
(Joking)
Would you like me to leave?
No.
She's getting on her nerves.
Now, this...
(Things are looking pretty tense.)
(Si Woo leaves them at that moment, )
(and these two are left alone.)
- Are you sad about going back?
- Yes, very sad.
- Should we also take a photo?
- Sure.
This could be our only chance.
There are lots of photo spots, though.
- Should I take one for you?
- No, thanks.
- In front of the mirror?
- Okay.
I'm not so good at this, so you should take it.
I'll try.
(The two take photos affectionately.)
It's not coming out so well. It's too dark here.
How should I take it?
I'll see how you do.
How should I do it? From this angle?
(She's serious about taking photos.)
I'll take one here, and you can take one next.
I'll act like I don't know you're taking a photo.
Okay. Pretend.
They feel totally comfortable with each other.
They're practically...
You really shouldn't leave while you're there.
- Exactly.
- As soon as you leave...
- You can't leave!
- You can't leave them alone.
That's why I said...
that they should pull an all-nighter.
I don't think Si Woo can come between them.
(I hope Si Woo doesn't see them like this.)
I'll act like I don't know you're taking a photo.
Okay. Pretend.
(Si Woo approaches them.)
Here comes Si Woo.
- Do I look okay now?
- It's a bit...
I'd love some feedback.
It's perfect right now.
You're pretty good at this.
(Si Woo returns only to find...)
My turn. You take a photo now.
Right.
(Hee Dong taking photos with Yu Bin)
Great.
- What? Okay.
- It's perfect.
Hang in there.
Hang in there, Si Woo.
I'm not even sure what's going on right now.
(This date makes even the dads confused.)
- This is so...
- I feel like Yu Bin can...
- survive anywhere she goes.
- I agree.
Anywhere in the world.
(She's incredibly sociable.)
- I just realized it.
- The whole world?
That's one of her charms.
It is, indeed.
Let's see how Si Woo deals with this.
(How will Si Woo overcome this crisis?)
- No one will be there, right?
- I bet.
(Back home at that moment)
Dad!
I want to go home.
Poor Hoo.
Hoo said he wanted to go home...
- for the first time on the show.
- I apologize, Hoo.
- I'll get changed.
- Okay.
- Let's work out.
- Sure.
- They'll exercise together.
- A workout.
(Hoo and Jae Seung on a workout date)
Looking good.
(Touching)
(The two men have an intimate date to forget about the sadness.)
- Feel it.
- These two...
That's good.
- Am I getting hot?
- Yes.
(Dad, what is love?)
(Can this much pain truly be called love?)
What?
- What is this editing?
- What?
Gosh. That's something.
So funny.
That's what most men do...
the day after a breakup.
You forget about it by going to the gym.
Yes, love isn't everything.
(After getting a pump, these two...)
How do you use this?
(A slim bike good for cardio)
Are they doing cardio next?
This must be the resistance level.
It's not bad.
(Lifting)
- That's good.
- Right?
A whole-body workout.
But this thing doesn't have a handle.
That's why you can also do arm workouts.
I think it helps me balance myself.
It requires more leg strength.
It certainly helps with my core strength.
(It's a good workout that helps distract them.)
This is good.
(One guy is panting especially loudly.)
(Shivering)
These may be too light.
Jae Seung might faint.
(He stops before fainting.)
Didn't you say Jae Seung was getting manual therapy?
I heard that Jae Seung had bad knees too.
(The patient is overworking himself.)
We get worried when he works out.
That's not important right now.
The emotional wounds are too deep.
It felt like...
love was already out of the picture,
so I decided to gain muscle.
He even forgot about the pain.
That's funny.
(The wounded men's night draws on.)
I pity these two.
It's nice, though.
(Woo Seo Yoon, Cho Eun Byul, and Shin Jae Hyuk, cocktail bar)
They went to a bar?
They also went to a bar.
What do people call this place? A cocktail bar?
- Yes.
- A cocktail bar?
- I think so.
- Right?
It's like a place mobsters would come to.
- They'd put a pistol on the table.
- Right.
They'll barge in and make a whole scene.
What do you think of my knife skills?
You're good.
- Does it look even?
- Even?
- Not that good?
Thanks for the food.
Seo Yoon is proactive, isn't she?
She just...
She plays along well.
It's really good.
Is that your favorite saying?
Did you practice it beforehand?
No, it really is good.
I'm only eating delicious food while I'm here.
It also reminds me of the squid yesterday.
- That was delicious.
- It was.
(The two continue to talk to each other.)
It looks like...
- Seo Yoon is leading it.
- Yes.
(Eun Byul can't seem to join them.)
(Glancing)
I don't know if I'm allowed to say this, but...
I actually...
enjoyed the dates with you two.
I'm thankful for both of you.
- I'm also thankful.
- So am I.
I'm also thankful.
It looks like a religious meeting.
They're all thankful.
- They give to each other...
- It's like...
and accept gratitude.
"Brothers and sisters."
(The vibe of the date is completely different from that of Hee Dong's.)
I was just curious.
You picked me.
Why...
I wonder why you did.
That's a tricky question.
How will they answer genuinely?
They might concern each others' feelings.
(An important question to figure out their feelings)
(Why they picked Jae Hyuk as their number-1 choice)
- The reason?
- Yes.
I just had...
the most fun with you.
That's why I picked you.
(Seo Yoon calmly tells him her feelings.)
I did tell you about this,
but...
I was absolutely tense on the first day,
and I could start speaking...
after the 1-on-1 date with you.
I was able to open up to others...
after our date.
I felt more comfortable, thanks to you.
Also,
I went to a roller rink for the first time.
And the sea squirts. I could try...
a bunch of new things that day.
I noticed...
a new side of myself.
I actually enjoy trying out new things.
I thought...
we were compatible in that sense.
This is embarrassing.
Thank you.
She's so eloquent.
That was pretty deep.
She spoke slowly,
yet she said everything that was on her mind.
Considering her personality,
- she wouldn't have gone that far.
- Right.
But given the situation, she might not have been able...
to tell him how she felt about him until the end.
- Right.
- She could have missed the chance,
so she confessed her honest feelings.
I used to think Eun Byul was mature.
But this helped me realize...
that she was also one of the kids these days.
She set her mind to go for him,
so she went for him.
- She expressed her feelings.
She knows how to do it in a polished manner.
- So Jae Hyuk can be less flustered.
- Yes.
Since she speaks calmly.
(Eun Byul's feelings would've reached Jae Hyuk.)
This is embarrassing.
Then...
If something new drops while we're on a date,
do we need to say goodbye?
Well, if that's how you think...
I'm joking.
There are many things I haven't experienced.
I'd never even been to a roller rink before.
I got to do that,
so I really had fun.
Eun Byul's story seems to have moved him more.
I spoke too shortly.
- Sorry, I spoke for too long.
- No.
I made it short...
because I was afraid the atmosphere would turn uncomfortable.
Eun Byul might feel bothered too,
so I kept it simple.
But later, I thought I should've spoken longer.
I regret a lot.
(Eun Byul's genuine confession made Seo Yoon nervous.)
Seo Yoon must've felt the shift in the air too.
Of course.
(Eun Byul's genuine confession made Seo Yoon nervous.)
(The night where one shares her sincere feelings...)
(and one is left with regrets)
(What changes will this date bring?)
Seo Yoon was being considerate of Eun Byul,
so she couldn't fully express...
her honest feelings for Jae Hyuk.
- Exactly. This...
- Yes.
Seo Yoon observes the situation calmly.
She needs to take the lead,
- but so far, she hasn't.
- Right.
- She's hesitating.
- Yes.
But after seeing Eun Byul express herself clearly,
she would find the right timing...
- to do something now.
- Yes.
She really must step up now.
- Exactly.
- Now's the time.
That's how Eun Byul was initially.
Yes.
(While Eun Byul expresses her feelings...)
(Jae Seung is lying down alone.)
Jae Seung.
Jae Seung, poor Jae Seung.
He's by himself.
(Jumping out of bed)
(He suddenly gets ready to go out.)
(He arrives at the Letter Room.)
- Yes, Jae Seung.
- Who is he writing to?
Isn't this his first time there?
- You're right.
- He's going to write a letter?
Jae Seung is mustering up his courage?
I came up to the room...
because I wanted to write some emotional words to Eun Byul.
(Touched)
Jae Seung.
Eun Byul just did something akin to confession.
Exactly.
- Eun Byul left.
- Oh, dear.
(Jae Seung is deep in thoughts.)
(After thinking long and hard, he writes the first word.)
(Winter)
- "Winter." - "Winter?"
"Love."
He's writing a letter.
(Love, )
(although I can't say that word)
"Love, although I can't say that word."
"Although I can't say that word."
(Hold on.)
- Like this, from afar - Like this, from afar
(Singing together)
- I could give you everything - I could give you everything
This is so sad.
Isn't that plagiarizing?
He just changed the title to "Winter."
The title of this song isn't "Winter."
It isn't.
(Embarrassed)
(Shaking his head)
(In the end, he crosses out the sentence.)
(He takes out a new piece of paper.)
(From winter...)
He added "night" to "winter."
The title was "Winter Night." The content...
("Winter Night" by Lee Jae Seung)
"Love, although I can't say that word,"
"on this cold day,"
"I stand here and wait only for you."
(Shaking his head)
(He folds the letter written with care...)
(and puts it in his pocket.)
(He walks down lonelily.)
- What?
- He put it in his pocket.
- You can't send it?
- Is he going to...
pass it to her himself?
(He opens the letter again.)
I wanted to write a poem,
so I wrote it in the form of poetry.
But I just couldn't get myself to send it to her,
so I took it with me.
(Throwing)
Is he going to burn it?
Goodness!
- Poor him.
- This...
He incinerated it?
Poor him.
Isn't he acting pitiful?
(Embarrassed)
I think Eun Byul has pretty much decided on her feelings.
When I burned that letter,
I took the moment to get over her too.
Now that I see it,
he's doing performance art.
Performance art.
He wrote a heartfelt letter...
and burned it. The whole process is art.
(The letter was a practice for a goodbye, not a confession.)
He's making me cry.
Jae Seung's heart must've felt like winter.
(In the end, Sung Mi sheds a tear.)
Life isn't that easy.
He's doing a breakup ritual on his own.
(Suddenly holding a breakup ritual after one date)
- My goodness.
- I mean...
It's okay Jae Seung, you still have time.
There are tomorrow and the day after tomorrow, punk.
Practice breaking up after doing something.
- You haven't done anything.
- He...
He didn't get to do anything.
He said he liked someone who liked him.
He needs to do something,
but he's doing nothing. What's happening?
Why are you asking me that?
I'm very frustrated as well.
Practice breaking up after you do something.
- Yes.
- You did nothing.
In this situation,
he wouldn't give up on Eun Byul...
and go for someone else, would he?
I don't think so.
He already burned his feelings.
"I won't love anymore."
He's even done a ritual.
Burning that put a full stop to it all.
(He's reached nirvana.)
(Meanwhile, another man who is at home)
(The person you love)
(I hope that's me)
(He's sublimating his pain by singing a breakup song medley.)
(He's not in his best condition as well.)
It must've been painful. He's very stressed.
This is hard.
It's hard.
(Yoon Hoo tosses and turns with mixed feelings.)
Actually, when we went on the date yesterday,
I thought it was a good chance to get to know many people.
But today,
it kept bothering me that Yu Bin went on a date.
That bothered me the most.
(The depth of his feelings has changed from yesterday.)
Actually, I did talk a bit with the others,
but I click the best with Yu Bin.
You made two mistakes. It's over.
No, you should grill this properly first.
Okay.
We had the best chemistry.
We call each other...
the relationship brought together by ice cream.
(You don't want to eat ice cream, do you?)
(Are you going to have it?)
(Nodding)
(Two of them have similar tastes...)
(and spent time of their own every evening.)
(Before he realized, Yoon Hoo has become attached to Yu Bin.)
Actually,
I don't regret just focusing on Yu Bin.
I definitely don't regret it.
My feelings have become firm.
"My feelings are firm toward you."
"I like you, Yu Bin." I should just say it.
That's all I had in mind.
- That's right.
- Yes.
- He's so mature.
He's cool.
He's so cool.
He's very thoughtful.
(Yoon Hoo's sincerity moves Yu Bin's dad.)
(As he waits for Yu Bin to come back, )
(he sings the song he sang for her on their date alone.)
(I can't do anything else but that)
(He misses someone...)
(and he lets go of someone.)
(The night is filled with waiting.)
(Park Si Woo, Choi Yu Bin, and Yoo Hee Dong at at LP bar)
Now that we dropped the honorifics, I can clearly tell your age.
Me too.
- I felt it so clearly.
- Okay.
It really feels like we're the same age.
Yes.
It could be because we're speaking casually now.
(Even now, only Yu Bin and Hee Dong are speaking casually.)
Isn't it better than being uncomfortable?
- I prefer speaking casually.
- Me too.
(Glancing)
Fine. Speak casually.
I did it.
I wondered how longer you'd speak formally.
- Finally.
- She agreed.
Hee Dong must've wanted this.
- And she should compromise.
- Yes.
- She changed her pace.
- Not too... Yes.
They should compromise.
- Would you like more bread?
- Give me one more shrimp.
- Thank you.
- One.
- Bread?
- What? No, it's okay.
- Do you want it?
- Here.
Thank you.
They're speaking comfortably now...
- after dropping the honorifics.
- Exactly.
They look a lot closer.
Which high school did you go to?
Seoul Arts High School?
- No.
- No?
I don't dance.
You're definitely a dancer.
Why do you think so?
You just look like one.
I have a knack for it.
I'll tell you next time.
Did you go to sleep right away yesterday?
- After I went back, - Yes.
I think I went to sleep right after washing my face...
and brushing my teeth.
Did you go to sleep right away?
I cleaned up first,
and when I was done with it, it was around 3am, I think?
(Yu Bin is left out of the conversation.)
I didn't know it flew so fast.
- Time?
- Yes.
Me too.
You acted like you'd go upstairs to write something yesterday.
So I went up because I got curious.
- You thought I'd write something?
- Yes, I thought you'd write again.
You were looking forward to it.
I'll write one today.
(Smiling)
Don't all the girls know?
I felt that Si Woo became very shy...
in front of the guy she has feelings for.
And Hee Dong showed so much romantic interest toward Si Woo.
I felt that tension in the air.
When I spoke with Hee Dong,
it felt more or less friendly.
Rather, the date I had with Hoo...
made my heart flutter.
(How can I sleep when I'm with such a beauty?)
(I'll protect you.)
(The date with Yoon Hoo made her heart flutter.)
I'd have enjoyed it more if I came here with Hoo.
And even as I ate,
"If I'd chosen Hoo as my first choice,"
"what kind of date would we be having now?"
I had that thought.
She didn't forget Hoo.
(Yu Bin kept thinking about Hoo.)
I told you. Now that they're apart...
- Yes.
- That's right.
- That's how they become solid.
- You need a moment like this too.
- Yes.
- Today...
made Hoo and Yu Bin grow closer.
Yes.
It's an important turning point...
- for them.
- Let us...
get along well.
My goodness.
- I'm sorry.
- "I'm sorry."
It's okay, same here.
I'll take a nap.
You two go ahead and talk.
(Tossing around)
They didn't have the chance to talk by themselves...
because of me.
So I told them to talk...
and pretended to sleep.
(Proud of her)
Yu Bin supports them.
You're so witty. That's my daughter.
- They're by themselves now.
- Yes.
(Si Woo and Hee Dong have the time of their own thanks to Yu Bin.)
(They keep giggling from just looking at each other.)
Do you normally not approach others first?
I've never approached.
Me neither.
- Really?
- Yes.
I'm serious.
Then the others always approached you first?
Normally, yes.
Were you always on the receiving end...
- of confessions?
- Me?
Yes.
But I always...
liked the other person first.
But I didn't say it.
I just liked them.
(Hesitating)
But...
I'll be very honest.
I tried my best for you in my own way.
I see.
(Feeling shy)
You know,
I felt that too.
But...
I feel shy to express it.
Why does it make you feel shy?
Hee Dong, what will you reply?
- Hee Dong.
- Why does it make him feel shy?
Say it and she'll fall over.
Yes.
(Hee Dong's reply is important.)
It seems that I tend to speak less when I'm with someone I like.
(It seems that I tend to speak less when I'm with someone I like.)
Same goes for me.
Si Woo.
- She must feel relieved now.
- She's smiling.
(Sighing in relief)
Honestly speaking...
(Hesitating)
It's a shame we couldn't go together.
(It's a shame we couldn't go on a date together.)
(Although Hee Dong feels shy, )
(he musters up the courage and expresses his feelings.)
(Hee Dong finally shows his true feelings.)
Didn't he practically confess?
Hee Dong had Si Woo on his mind.
I'm a bit moved.
But Yu Bin is listening in front.
She's only pretending to sleep.
She's blocking them out, considering everything.
- She really slept.
- Did she really sleep?
- She said she'd pretend to sleep.
- She must've really slept.
- She really slept.
She didn't pretend to.
You can sleep longer.
(Yu Bin pretends to sleep again.)
(Yu Bin, the queen of consideration)
Yu Bin.
That's right, sleep more. Good job.
(Good job, my daughter.)
(With a sweet nap, 8 of them all return.)
We're back.
- You're back.
- Where's Hoo?
- He's asleep.
- Really?
(Upon returning, Yu Bin looks for Hoo first.)
- She's looking for Hoo first.
- Yes.
Is he not eating jjajang ramyeon?
He probably will.
I asked to eat together,
but he said he'd wait for you.
(Pondering)
(After thinking hard, Yu Bin gets up from her seat.)
Hoo is asleep.
- Really?
- What should I do?
Is it bad if I wake him up?
- Shouldn't you wake him up, though?
- Exactly.
(Yu Bin is worried about Yoon Hoo's feelings.)
I'm off.
You're going?
- Really?
- Yes.
Good luck.
- She's going to Hoo.
- Yes.
Yes, go and see Hoo.
(With Si Woo cheering her on, Yu Bin goes to Yoon Hoo.)
Hoo.
Are you asleep?
Hoo, are you asleep?
(But Hoo is sleeping deeply.)
He sleeps deeply.
(He feels bad.)
(A bit later)
He's awake.
- Hello.
(Hoo finally wakes up.)
- It looks like you slept well.
- That's right.
(Things are still awkward between Hoo and Yu Bin.)
(At that moment, they receive a mysterious text.)
(Please reveal your age and profession now.)
"Please reveal your age and profession now."
- Finally.
Finally.
Whom they're attracted to might change.
- It might change.
- That's right.
Now that we need to do it...
- I know.
- It's a bit...
- We've been waiting for this.
- Seriously.
(The information that might change the flow will be revealed.)
To be honest, I was so curious...
about everyone's age.
I prefer an older man...
for mature personality.
I'm interested in something...
who leads me.
That's why I prefer an older man.
Why am I nervous about this?
Seriously.
We're nervous as well.
(How will the revealed information affect them?)
Shall we start with the guesses?
What? Yu Bin.
(Yu Bin goes first.)
Twenty.
She has to be 20.
- Twenty.
- Why?
You look young.
You're right. I'm 20.
I finished my second CSAT and entered university this year.
Yu Bin received good news regarding university.
She studied hard and got into two universities.
Between them, she decided to attend Sookmyung Women's University.
- Sookmyung Women's University.
- Yes.
It's a prestigious university.
- Buy us dinner.
- What?
Buy us dinner.
(He's happy thanks to his daughter.)
(Hoo is next.)
My guess is 20.
Twenty.
That's right.
(Hoo is a 20-year-old who was born in 2006.)
I'm 20.
I'm attending a university in the US.
I study economics.
(He's a business major at University of North Carolina.)
- Nice to meet you.
I expected Hoo's age.
Since we were the same age,
I felt closer to him.
Hearing about Yu Bin's age and profession...
made the atmosphere more relaxed.
Overall, the situation has improved.
I had that thought.
The two of them are the same age.
- Hoo is 20 too.
- He's 20.
They'll become closer.
(They'll feel more comfortable since they're the same age.)
Jae Seung.
My guess is 21.
I'm 20.
(Jae Seung is a 20-year-old who was born in 2006.)
What?
(My goodness)
(What?)
Is he 20?
He kept talking about poems and philosophical issues.
He talked about manual therapy.
(He didn't act like a 20-year-old.)
I didn't expect him to be 20...
because he behaved in a very mature way.
Twenty?
(Everyone is surprised about Jae Seung's age.)
No way.
As for my profession...
I used to b-boy and breakdance.
Really?
(Surprised)
(Everyone was curious about Jae Seung's identity.)
(He's a b-boy who breakdances.)
- Is that what he does?
- Look at that.
- My goodness.
- He should've shown that.
He's like an athlete.
Wasn't he a poet?
That must be why his knees are ruined.
He has a forward neck posture.
That explains why he gets manual therapy.
That's why he needs manual therapy.
(They finally solve the mystery of manual therapy.)
But because of my physical condition...
Because of my bad shoulders and knees,
I quit.
Now, I'm gaining experiences...
and hunting for a job.
Nice to meet you.
(Jae Seung's self-introduction was full of twists.)
- I had no idea.
- Seriously.
- Si Woo.
- I'm curious.
- Twenty-two.
- Twenty-one.
- Twenty-one?
Yes.
I'm 22.
(Si Woo is a 22-year-old who was born in 2004.)
I don't care about age.
It didn't seem like there was a big age gap between us,
so I didn't care.
(Hee Dong goes next.)
(Nervous)
Hee Dong, are you 29?
- Twenty-nine?
- Twenty-nine.
I'd be very thankful.
Twenty.
Twenty-one?
(Si Woo prefers an older man.)
(Si Woo is 22. How old is Hee Dong?)
I'm 20.
(Hee Dong is a 20-year-old who was born in 2006.)
He's younger.
(He's 2 years younger than Si Woo.)
- He's two years younger.
- He's younger.
It's an unexpected variable.
(An unexpected variable)
To be honest, I never thought about dating a younger man.
(Will Si Woo and Hee Dong's relationship falter?)
(Well...)
But I definitely think...
personality matters more than age.
If his personality is as I've expected,
it'll be okay even if he's younger than me.
(Si Woo is okay with a younger man.)
She corrected herself.
You can't have everything your way.
- You adjust yourself to the other.
- That's right.
(Si Woo and Hee Dong continue to like each other.)
What are your guesses about my age?
- Twenty-three.
- Twenty-two.
I think you're my age.
I'm 23.
(Seo Yoon is a 23-year-old who was born in 2003.)
To be honest, I don't care about age.
I'm good as long as the person gets along with me.
I graduated in May of last year.
It hasn't been long since I moved back to Korea.
Will you debut as a model now?
You should.
I'm studying a bit.
I majored in art.
It's true that I've studied art.
- That's incredible.
- Nice to meet you.
- Is it Jae Hyuk's turn?
- Jae Hyuk?
I'm curious about Jae Hyuk.
You look mature.
But even if you're on the older side,
you'd be under 25.
I'm...
twenty-five.
(Jae Hyuk is a 25-year-old who was born in 2001.)
I'm a soccer player.
That's incredible.
- That's cool.
- Seriously.
I've always had...
a thing for athletes.
Also, hearing about his age...
made me like Jae Hyuk...
even more.
I'm the most curious about this.
- Seriously.
- I'm the most curious about this.
- Who are you?
- Seriously.
- I have no idea.
- Who are you?
I work for an NGO...
that's related to international development.
Are you an office worker?
Yes, I am.
- What's your guess for my age?
- Twenty-three.
Twenty-three?
I was born in 2001, so I'm 25 years old.
- She's Jae Hyuk's age.
- They're the same age.
They're the same age.
(Jae Hyuk and Eun Byul are the same age.)
I was born in 2001, so I'm 25 years old.
I was very surprised when I heard about her age.
I didn't think anyone would be...
my age or older.
So I was surprised.
I thought Jae Hyuk was older than me.
I didn't expect him to be my age.
Was that why I felt so comfortable around him?
I had that thought.
"She's older than I imagined."
"She's very baby-faced." I had that thought.
In that stage of life, a five-year age gap is very big.
(Jae Seung and Eun Byul are 5 years apart.)
I told her that you could have pure love up to the age of 23.
(They say you can have pure love up to the age of 23.)
(Really?)
(He told a 25-year-old that the age of 23 was the limit.)
When I heard that Eun Byul was 25 years old,
I began to think that pure love...
could be possible at the age...
of 26 or 27.
(He adjusted the age limit for pure love.)
- He changed it right away.
- He changed his words.
He adjusted the age limit.
Jae Seung wanted to date an older woman.
That's right. He can talk to them more easily.
It's good for him.
I don't know how Sung Mi feels, but since I've watched Eun Byul...
I like Jae Seung too.
- Are you okay with a younger man?
- I like him too.
As long as he's healthy...
(Oh, my)
But his health...
(Everyone has finished revealing their age and profession.)
Now, I can talk with ease.
I know.
Shall I call you "Big brother?"
Big brother Jae Hyuk.
Big sister Eun Byul.
(They still feel awkward about using the new titles.)
In which month were you born...
again?
- He's checking the month.
- The month.
- June.
- June?
I was born in June too.
- How about the date?
- Second.
(Startled)
- Why?
- I was born on the fourth.
(Startled)
- Are they 2 days apart?
- They're 2 days apart.
You're the oldest in the group.
Only by two days.
My mom should've held out for two more days.
What?
I gained a friend.
(Fist bump)
(They bump their fists naturally.)
That did it naturally.
(Glancing over)
Aren't you guys going to eat anything?
- Shall we eat jjajang ramyeon?
- Shall we do that?
Let's do that.
My friend, let's go.
- Gosh, you're ridiculous.
- My friend, let's go.
Big sister.
(The atmosphere is more relaxed after revealing the age.)
Are you in charge of meat?
(They prepare for dinner in earnest.)
(Inching closer)
Do you still live in Canada?
Where is your workplace?
- Korea.
- Korea?
- What?
- I can't believe it!
Jae Hyuk's hand...
I'm so relieved...
- What?
- that I have a same-age friend.
Everyone thought I was 22 or 23 years old.
Ms. Eun Byul?
- "Ms. Eun Byul?" - Ms. Eun Byul?
What should I call you? Just Eun Byul?
It feels strange.
I'll just call you Jae Hyuk.
Eun Byul.
Eun Byul. My goodness.
(Their conversation continues on.)
(Seo Yoon listens to their conversation.)
I thought I was the oldest.
I became very wary.
They seemed close.
They seemed to like each other.
It seemed that way.
That's right. They became close after the age reveal.
- They became close.
- It's understandable.
- That's right.
(Jae Hyuk and Eun Byul became close after the age reveal.)
Can someone help me with this?
(Meanwhile, the two of them are cooking ramyeon.)
Will you do that? Okay.
- Is there a plate?
- My goodness.
- Is there...
- Why aren't we using a casual tone?
Is there a plate this big? Is there a lid?
Do you want to use a casual tone or a polite tone?
Do what's comfortable for you. I don't care either way.
I don't feel awkward.
- Really?
- Yes.
I thought you'd feel awkward.
What?
I thought you'd feel awkward because of the date earlier.
To be completely honest,
I was a bit surprised.
But I was relieved that I was your second choice.
If I weren't, we wouldn't have had a date today.
I thought a lot about how I'd explain it on my way back.
Let's talk as we eat ice cream later.
Will they eat again?
She felt Hoo's void at the cocktail bar.
- That's right.
- "There's no one like Hoo."
Upon a closer look, Hoo and Yu Bin look good together.
- They look good together.
- They look natural, right?
- I think so.
- They look good together.
(Will Hoo and Yu Bin end up together after the detour?)
(Jjajang ramyeon is complete.)
(He eats right away because he has been hungry.)
(Nodding)
(Thanks to Hoo and Yu Bin, they enjoy dinner today as well.)
- The meat is insane.
- The meat is so tasty.
- Thank you.
- Seriously.
It's so tasty.
It's the highest compliment.
(He eats jjajang ramyeon in earnest.)
After clearing up the misunderstanding,
- he got his appetite back.
- He gained a big appetite.
(Thanks to Hoo who ate voraciously)
The plate is empty.
(After the simple meal)
Thank you for the food.
(Si Woo and Seo Yoon set out to do the dishes.)
Finally.
(Tapping)
- What? What is it?
- Gosh.
You aren't very good at acting.
By the way,
how did you get out of work?
What? Work? I used my days off.
Did you use your precious days off for this?
(While Seo Yoon does the dishes)
- You used four days off.
- Yes.
You didn't use too many of them.
- But every day off is precious.
- That's right. I know that.
I know that.
(Seo Yoon listens to their conversation quietly.)
- Suddenly, Seo Yoon feels left out.
- Now...
- That's right. Seo Yoon is...
- She feels left out.
(Worried)
(After dinner, they gather in the living room one at a time.)
- We took so many photos.
- Seriously.
Let me take one.
(Seo Yoon takes a selfie.)
(Snapping a funny photo)
(They watch Seo Yoon.)
I won't show anyone else.
It's so shocking.
(Glancing over)
No!
- Come on.
- What's this?
- For goodness' sake.
- Seriously, what are you doing?
- I was so startled.
Seriously, what are you doing?
- Let's trade.
- I mean...
The one I saw earlier. This one.
- The one I took like this?
- No.
You looked like this.
Do you want it for real?
- Do you want it for real?
- Yes.
(Jae Hyuk receives Seo Yoon's photo.)
Unbelievable.
- Stop it.
- My goodness.
(The two of them seem pretty close.)
(She's wary of the relationship they have.)
- Now, Eun Byul is...
- My goodness.
She's shooting lasers out of her eyes.
Of course, she's wary.
It'd be strange if she weren't.
Eun Byul is so worried.
It's hard to know whom Jae Hyuk will choose.
(They can't read Jae Hyuk's mind.)
(As Eun Byul watches Jae Hyuk, )
(her heart becomes troubled.)
- I'll go upstairs.
- Okay.
- Which floor?
- Third floor.
Okay.
(Hoo and Yu Bin decide to talk as they promised earlier.)
- You aren't cold, are you?
- No.
(Neither one can start the conversation.)
Well,
I felt so uncomfortable after I left.
I expected it. I don't know if you did.
I think I know the reason why I became your second choice.
They're having...
- a serious talk.
- It's a serious talk.
(The two of them begin having a serious talk.)
Will Hoo get scolded again?
I think I know the reason why I became your second choice.
What do you think is the reason?
I assumed Si Woo became your first choice...
since you had a date with her.
I see.
I think... I think you're right. After all,
I had spent the entire day...
- with Si Woo.
- Right.
Seventy-five percent of the decision was out of politeness.
Okay.
And to be honest, I thought you'd do the same.
But I don't know what you're feeling for sure.
I was...
very disappointed after you left.
I felt that way...
because I thought receiving the news...
might shock you and hurt your feelings.
That was my thought.
He's very considerate.
- He's nice.
- He's cool.
He cleared the misunderstanding, looked back upon himself,
and consoled Yu Bin.
- He's cool.
- Yu Bin would understand.
Yes.
I raised him well.
(Yu Bin realizes how Hoo feels.)
I'd be lying if I said I wasn't shocked...
when I got the text.
But I wasn't disappointed because of it.
But you cared so much about me...
that you were worried I would've been hurt by it.
So I'm happy.
(I'm happy.)
Because I was also worried.
I thought you'd be heartbroken if you found out...
that you weren't my first choice.
I was rather worried about that.
(Yu Bin had the same worries.)
And as I said earlier,
if we had our date according to our choices,
I wouldn't have made that choice.
I see.
(Smiling)
(Tapping)
(Feeling shy after saying it)
Let me be frank.
My feelings didn't change at all.
(My feelings didn't change at all.)
If I were to put it bluntly,
you're the most...
You are...
I like you the most.
(I like you the most.)
I don't think that will change.
No.
I feel confident.
(Grinning)
I was excited.
Hoo tends to express himself directly.
So I don't feel anxious.
I'd have no regrets or worries...
about trying going on a date with other people.
I've decided to focus on Hoo.
(The two went back to each other.)
Good for them.
She stormed in with a huge announcement.
- Those words...
- That's right.
They had trouble.
They fought,
and they met again at the meal table.
Ground packs after a rain.
That's right.
I thought my son was an estrogen man.
- I realized he's a tough guy today.
- Right.
What more do you need to say...
than "I like you the most?"
If he stays with Yu Bin,
I can imagine their nice future together.
- Yes.
- Or am I getting too ahead?
- The future?
- Yes.
Whatever. You should treat us.
You need to set the date.
- I better throw the dates.
- Right.
- "Dates." - You need to hurry...
I don't think that will change.
No.
I feel confident.
(Yoon Hoo's confession moves her heart.)
(The two start smiling.)
- Why are you laughing?
- Just because.
Why are you laughing?
You got a problem?
(Feeling embarrassed, the two make jokes.)
I wanted to make jokes,
but it was awkward earlier.
I wouldn't have done it either.
(When the misunderstanding between them is resolved...)
They got something. That darn text.
(Everyone received a text.)
"From now on, regardless of your gender,"
"the first one person gets an endless night date ticket."
"Text the name of the person you'd like to go on a date with."
"The person who receives the request can't refuse it."
(A night date?)
- That's a good idea.
- Are they playing all night long?
Yes.
(They'll leave the place they're staying.)
"Leave the place they're staying?"
What's happening?
Maybe they're going to a different place.
Another place?
Oh, my gosh.
(Everything for two people is...)
(Everything for two people is ready.)
- What?
- Oh, my.
Even pajamas?
Are they matching pajamas?
What? Why are there matching pajamas?
(A chance to go on a date without a time limit)
That's not what it said.
Hold on.
That will change the game.
But... Gosh.
What's going on?
If there's no time limit, does that mean they can stay up all night?
- Yes, it could be two days.
- It's a night date.
Yes.
- You never know.
- It's a variable.
Are the surveillance cameras on?
- Probably.
What's going on?
- They have to be on.
- This will change everything.
This is unpredictable.
Only one team can...
go on this special night date.
I was thinking I must win the night date.
When I received the text,
I wanted to spend time with Jae Hyuk,
obviously.
The date today was a shame.
I had quite a lot of regrets.
From how I feel right now, I want to apply no matter what.
Eun Byul and Seo Yoon were...
charming in opposite ways.
(Jae Hyuk is torn.)
I'm not sure.
- Let's cooperate.
- Yes, that's the best.
Twenty one minutes.
- Oh, my gosh.
- Okay. She sent it.
(Only one team can go on a date.)
- Eun Byul needs it.
- She must send it.
- Seo Yoon also needs it.
- Press it.
- Hurry up and write it.
- Si Woo, you have to do it.
- Jae Seung.
- I think Yu Bin's faster.
This is tense.
Is it over?
(This person received the night date ticket.)
(Who won the night date ticket?)
(I think Jae Hyuk's 1st choice was Seo Yoon.)
(Right. Jae Hyuk told me.)
(Seo Yoon realizes she was Jae Hyuk's 1st choice.)
(The last date before the final selection)
(I'm not sure about Jae Hyuk's heart.)
(- Did you write it? - No, I didn't.)
(Why didn't you?)
(The relationship between the three is ambiguous.)
(Hee Dong and Si Woo finally go on a date.)
They're about to hold hands.
(Their kids become bold on their last date.)
Look at them.
Dramaday.me