Chimera
The characters, locations, incidents, religious sects, etc. in this drama are fiction and have no relation to reality.
Han Myeong University
Gosh, you came bright and  early.
Yes, there's a lot of work to be done today.
June 9, 1984, Macheon City
~ Episode 3 ~
Don't come, don't come!
Don't come! Please!
It's the water.
What?
It's the water!
Did you hear the story? They say the MO* of the crime was Chimera.   (*MO= method of committing a crime)
Then, someone was burnt alive?
What is "chimera"?
There was a series of explosions in Macheon in Gyeonggi Province thirty years ago.
Do you know?
Because of that, lots of people were fired.
That's worse than I thought.
So did Chief Bae step in crap? Right before his promotion?
Jeez.
(TV news) From what we know so far,
- He's here!
whether it was arson or murder
is not certain, but police are focusing on both possibilities
and we know they are investigating both.
Meanwhile, the whereabouts of Detective Cha, the first witness,
- Turn that off!
is still unknown.
An official at Jungsan Police Station ...
My gracious.
Who is Han Ju Seok?  He has 35 years of field experience.
Hey.  An incumbent detective and a superior police officer on top of that.  Does this make sense?
What were you all doing while things were going on like this?
Umm.  Because the impact on the public is so great,
for now, let's make an announcement about the incident ...
But reporters are not naive.  Talk about the chimera started immediately.
What do you mean chimera?  Who said that?
Yes, well, ... I think the word was mentioned because the pattern is similar.
It is the reporters' specialty to take pictures and attach labels to them.
No.  When did that case happen?
Why did you bring that up?  It's been a while since the culprit died.
Umm.  It's hard to say he was the culprit ...
The man died while being interrogated without even standing trial. So, well ...
No, he was the culprit. Yes. That's right.
An incumbent detective died.  And just two weeks before his retirement.
The culprit will be arrested within two weeks.
Set up an investigation headquarters immediately and mobilize all available personnel and resources.
Arrest everyone who has used a similar MO.
Until the bastard is apprehended,
don't even dream about sneaking home and changing your underwear! Understand?!
Stop.  Light.
Tweezer.
Who is he?
Go Gwang Su from the intelligence investigation team at headquarters.
He's exceptionally smart. He's both strong and fast.
Why hasn't he been promoted?
He's one of the stubborn ones.  He's not liked by his superiors and is indecisive.
Police Officer Personnel Card
Go Gwang Su.  Graduated 1997 Silla High School. National Police University.
- Are you from Silla High?
- Yes, I am.
- What class?
- The 48th.
If it's 48, ...
hey, we are twenty years apart.
It's 23 years because you are in the 25th class.
My, my, you are my hoobae  (junior) . Nice to meet you.
Sit, sit. Relax, relax.
Let's see.
Was your father a civil servant in Nam-do?
Yes.  He was in the Jeonnam provincial office.
Did he pass away already?
Yes, liver cirrhosis.
- Your family lives in the provinces and you're the only one that left home to study?  In Seoul?
- Yes.
Yes.  It doesn't matter where you're from. School is what's important.
I was in the Kendo club.  In Silla.
- Do you know it?
- Yes, I do.
- Were you at investigation headquarters from the start?
- No, I wasn't.
I was on a detective team during the Seonambu case.
Then, you've had a taste of it.
Yes.
I'm talking to my hoobae in front of me, but I feel like I'm dying.
What the hell is happening?
Do you know who is handling human relations for cops nowadays? It's the murderers.
A long time ago, there was a guy who broke out of prison.
Every time a top official encountered the case, he had to take off his uniform  (resign),  one after the other.
This case is especially generating a lot of talk.
It's a major crisis that a police officer was abducted and murdered.
The media keeps trying to connect it to a different case. They are trying to create a story.
So is this something we should prolong or not?
I will take care of it promptly.
Okay, Gwang Su.
Hoobaenim! You're the only one I can rely on in this situation.
Let's work together and get a good outcome.
You should also make a big hit, huh?
Yes.
- Put it there.
- Yes.
I'll take this too.
What is it, all of this?
Starting now, Violent Crime Team 2's data will all belong to the headquarters' special investigation team.
Please organize and transfer all the rest of the data on your personal computers by the end of today.
Yes.
Who are you?
The team leader of the investigation team. He's from the main office.
- What are you doing?  Introduce yourself.
- Violent Crimes Team 2.
- Yes.
As of today, you are all transferred.
You will work for the headquarters investigation team and provide support to the investigation.
Drop all the other cases you are working on, and direct leakage of the shared data will not be permitted.
That's it.  Do you have any questions?
According to whom?
- Seonbaenim.
- Detective Cha Jae Hwan?
Who said you can take the case as you want?
I heard you were at the scene at the time of the incident.
Write your statement about why you were at the scene with Han Ju Seok and the sequence of events after.
Describe everything you saw, heard, and know.
During the first meeting, do an official briefing without leaving out a single detail.
Shut up.  I won't turn over the case.
What?
I'm going to catch the bastard. I won't let him win.
Seonbae.
Cha Jae Hwan. Can you stop peeing and pooping?
They are here to clean up the mess you guys made!
So put everything down and go.
Hey, Cha Jae Hwan, don't overstep your boundary.
This bastard.  What are you glaring at?  Damn. What are you intending?
Detective Cha Jae Hwan.  You want to catch the culprit? Why?
Because it's agonizing?
Good.  I like that attitude.
You would have to feel guilty if you're a human.
Well.  Although it won't help with the investigation.
Get organized quickly. We don't have a lof time.
Why aren't you answering your calls? You made me come all the way here.
It was in the inside pocket.
I don't think it was Team Leader Han's. It seems like someone put it there.
It's up to you from here. This is all I can do.
Doctor.
I think the deceased old man was hiding something from me.
What the hell is this Chimera? What does he want...
Isn't there at least anything you know?
You knew him for 30 years.
I don't know.
It's true that I knew him for a long time.
What my wife said was right.
You don't even know the inside of the person with whom you live or have sexual relations.
When people are opened up, their internal organs are all the same. Isn't that right?
The only place where Buddha and the devil can live together
is inside the human stomach.
So, like I said, there was something you didn't know.
You didn't do anything wrong.
He's leaving us on a day when the weather is nice.
Rest in Peace Han Ju Seok
Move the case files to the data room.
Gun forward!
Fire one shot!
Water spilled, but it caught on fire?
So did the water burn?
From the sprinkler...
how many times do I have to say it?
It was probably not water. Maybe gasoline.
It was water.
Has that guy gone crazy?
He should say something that makes sense.
I don't think it's nonsense.
How do you know, man?
We worked together for so many years.
Seonbae, you should know this too!
Our Hyeong Jae Hwan is not  someone who would say something that didn't make sense.
It's always "our" Jae Hwan.
Are you in his fan club?
What did you say to the investigator?
- It's water.
- What?
I don't know about anything else, but only H2O,  the component of water was found in the pipe connected to the sprinkler.
Then why was there a fire?
I don't know. We've never had a fire like this before.
Isn't it only flammable materials such as gas that can cause a fire?
I heard it was oxygen in the last incident.
This time, it's a little different.
Gas and oxygen are heavier than air and will fall on the ground.
Then the soot spreads rapidly radially from the ignition point.
That's why a drop of ink on top of water in a dish spreads.
But this time it seems it rose straight up from the floor to the top.
Do not enter Police Line.
Investigation in progress
DIES IRAE
Dies Irae.
What does that mean?
It means the day of wrath in Latin.
It's the first verse of the chant about the final judgment.
It's used in the mass for the dead.
Judgment day?
Judgment day in the Bible has two meanings.
Resurrection for those who believe and death for those who don't.
That's crazy.
So monsters and the Bible. Just what does he want to say?
When judgment day comes, Archangel Michael appears.
He puts the human souls on scales and picks out the sinners, and drops them into the fire of hell.
If the culprit is a judge, just what sin is he talking about?
Do you have any ideas?
Are you okay?
About what?
Have you been sleeping well these days?
Of course.
Why? Are you worried?
No.
Yes. A little.
There is nothing bothering me.
Really?
So there's nothing wrong with you.
Thank you for what you did today.
If that's all, shall we head back?
It's pretty obvious when someone hasn't been sleeping well.
Even if it's not to me,
you should talk to someone about what is bothering you.
Who said anything was bothering me?
Don't treat me like a patient. Don't pretend you're a doctor.
Being a profiler doesn't mean you know everything about a person.
Even people who have lived together as a family their whole lives don't know everything about each other.
I've said everything I didn't want to talk about. But the other side hasn't done anything at all.
That's what people are like.
Not even knowing anything.
Much better.
You said that the team leader was the detective in charge of the Chimera case?
He never said anything like that to me.
Why did he hide it?
That silent old man.
What was there that he couldn't tell me? Even after 35 years, he couldn't trust me?
Isn't it just that he wanted to protect you?
You or someone else?
Protection. I couldn't do anything.
Investigator, I am...
Angry. I'm so angry I could go crazy.
If only I had been more careful,
if only I hadn't taken that one step. Or if I'd just called for backup at that moment.
It would have been enough for me to just stay still and make one phone call.
Why. Why, like an idiot couldn't I think of that...
Psychology and Crime
Criminal Psychology
Small World
Francis Bacon
Unsolved mysteries in
Unsolved mysteries in East Asia
(Chimera 1984, South Korea)
oxygen
water
chemistry
Repeat offender?
What. So, is this a serial killer?
A vehicle explosion occurred in Shinil-dong on the 13th. The victim was Son Wan Gi.
On the 18th, the Shinil-dong perpetrator's hideout exploded.
And on the 23rd, the incident in Macheon City occurred. The victim
was Han Ju Seok. These three cases have the same pattern.
But that criminal's methods are different.
The criminal left a signature at the crime scene.
What signature?
This is the lighter that was in Son Wan Gi's car.
And this.
What?
- It's the same
- The lighter was released in  Lumière, France in 1983.
It's otherwise known as the Chimera. Since it is a custom-made item, there are only a few people in Korea who own one.
Is it a designer item? Something expensive?
If it's real, it could even be worth one million.
What? This would be worth one million won?
Of course.
Where was the second one found?
It came from the pocket of the team leader who died in Macheon City.
Wait.
So this is from inside Son Wan Gi's car?
Then why isn't it on the inventory list?
I found it in Team Leader Han's house.
- What?
- About that...
It looks like he accidentally took it home.
But I'm certain that it came from the scene.
Evidence with a compromised chain of custody has no value. You can't take this to court.
Chain of custody: continuity of evidence management.
Are you just learning this now?
Can't you still take note of it for the investigation?
- What note?
- That this is the criminal's signature.
But what is this design?
The chimera.
The fire-breathing monster from Greek mythology.
In 1984, explosions with an unknown cause killed three people in a single month.
This is the so-called Chimera incident.
At that time, it was so brutal that it spawned ghost stories.
First, this is a picture of the scene where Son Wan Gi was murdered.
Look closely.
And second, this is a picture of the explosion at the criminal's hideout that was discovered while we were investigating Son Wan Gi's case.
And last. This is the third scene.
Not only this. But the victims, Son Wan Gi and Han Ju Seok were directly connected to the incident thirty-five years ago.
Connected?
The reporter for the Chimera case 35 years ago was Son Wan Gi.
And the lead investigator for the case was Han Ju Seok.
Check the message history for the messages that Team Leader Han received on the 18th.
Text outgoing/incoming history
However, the day of God's reckoning will appear like a thief.  On that day, the sky will echo with deafening sounds and substances will be engulfed in flames.
416 Shinil-dong,  Room 405
- Where are you? Why aren't you picking up?
- Independent action is prohibited.
Was that a setup to lure Team Leader Han?
Yes.
Because that failed, they went on to the third kidnapping operation.
So are you saying that the Chimera criminal from 35 years ago has reappeared?
So why kill a reporter and detective?
It's a grudge relationship.
Was the criminal arrested for the case 35 years ago released?
He died.
- Why?
- When?
He died by suicide. Thirty-five years ago.
- Really?
- Of course.
So are you saying that the criminal is a ghost?
- Really?
- Let's stop this here.
Don't be mistaken.
The case we are trying to solve right now happened a few days ago. We aren't trying to solve something from 35 years ago.
Right now, a police officer has been killed. It's a really sensitive matter. But you want to talk about Chimera right now?
How do you think this will turn out?
- Are you trying to protect yourself?
- What?
Do you get in trouble when things get bigger for you because you're tied to the past? Yes, I understand how it goes.
But Team Leader Han is a police officer and
we're family. We're family, but you're worried about the issue getting bigger?
Hey Jae Hwan, that's not what we're talking about right now!
Then what are we talking about!
This jerk is really!
We're not even hoping for your support.
We just want you to allow us to investigate this ourselves.
These fools must be crazy. Watch how you speak to us!
There is a suspect.
Clamp.
Dissect.
Hold it.
Hold it. Won't you get a hold of yourself?
Suction.
Jerome Edwards
- Is that all?
Please just take the search and seizure warrant.
At least, have the vehicle driving record released or let me get the phone records.
I have this now.
If you were the prosecutor, is this convincing?
He went to the same gambling house as Son Wan Gi.  Is that the only evidence?
Something will definitely come out if you investigate further.
What was your point of contact with Team Leader Han Ju Seok?
Aside from any grudge, was there any circumstance showing the two of them were even acquainted?
He kept saying he didn't know Son Wan Gi, which was a lie.
If he wasn't the culprit, why did he lie?
Witnesses lie too!
Fine.  Let's say this case is a repeat of the Chimera Case.
Then it makes even less sense.
Chimera is a 35-year-old case. So 35 years ago,
how old would your suspect, Lee Jung Yeop, have been?
An elementary school student at best.
Hey Cha Jae Hwan.  Stop obsessing over the Chimera case and think after subtracting it.
Be objective and take a step back.  Is it reasonable to connect Son Wan Gi and Han Ju Seok?
Connection?  There is none.  It's impossible to prove the MO from thirty-five years ago.
Team Leader Han was in his 35th year in the Violent Crimes Division.
There isn't even something to have  a grudge over.  Do you know there are dozens of suspects?
Hey, get a hold of yourself.
Police
Excuse me, but what is the matter?
I have something to ask Detective Cha.
Oh, Seonbae Jae Hwan? He left earl–
Detective Cha
- Well then, I'm off to work outside the office.
- Alright.
I didn't say anything.
Detective Cha. I was worried, you didn't even take your calls.
What are you doing?
I told you already. I came because I was worried.
You're not hurt?
What is it?  What will you eat after opening me up?
It's a feast for you
but we are in mourning right now.  This is a house of mourning.
Don't people like you have the bare minimum of manners?
Today I'm—
I'm not here as a reporter today, though.
What a great car. When will we ever drive something like this?
Stop talking about useless things and just look at this.
Hyeongnim, please straighten your face, okay?
People are going to mistake you for a car thief.
Hey, are you saying that because you're truly thinking about me?
Hey, then is anything because of me?  Yes?  I used to be the handsome one in Eulwang-ri. The handsome one. So don't talk about my face.
Yes, yes.  Please look at the angle.  Jeez.
Okay. The angle's good. Take out the card.
Thank you for your cooperation  We'll take the memory card for now...
DIES IRAE
Go slowly.
Why are you scared? You've been here before.
Try coming a hundred times to the scene where someone died.
Can you get used to this?
Seonbae, here. Should we start filming here?
No, the front might be better.
DIES IRAE.
Hyo Gyeong, didn't you hear a sound?
- What sound?
- I heard a sound.
- What sound are you saying you heard
- I really heard it.
Hey, shine the light over there.
You get scared so easily!
Why did you bring us to a place like this? Can we even use this footage?
Authorization after we gather the news.  Leave matters like that to me.
Seonbaenim please start filming from there, okay?
Seonbae. Here's the light.  Let's go, let's go.
Looks like you're coming back from somewhere
What is it?
You left work in the afternoon though.
Are you doing a background check on me now?
What can I do for you?
I was wondering
how you have been?
Please leave.
Seems like an invasion of privacy.
You must have been somewhere in the mountains.
Be careful.
Korea is smaller than you think.
You've got paint on you.
You should take it to the dry cleaners.
Here. It might be better here.
No.
Exit
Gasoline?
The reason for the fire at Team Leader Han's crime scene is gasoline?
It's true that water poured from the sprinklers, but that has nothing to do with the cause of the fire.
If you take a look at the chromatogram here, do you see the flames?
This is the component of gasoline. It appeared to be the highest.
Gasoline?
Yes. They said that gasoline caused the fire.
I couldn't smell anything similar to gas at the scene though.
Then what came out of the sprinklers? You said that was water.
They said the water pouring was a coincidence.
Does that make sense?
I saw it with my own eyes. The fire came from the water,
but no one believes me.
Even I, who saw it think it's absurd, so who will believe me?
Me.
I'm saying, I believe in chemistry.
Silver Nitrate. Magnesium.
This is FBI Profiler Eugene Hathaway.
She is an expert in explosive terrorism and is now dispatched to the Central Office.
So? Just what do you want to investigate that you even brought a terrorism expert?
The cause of the fire that occurred in Macheon city on the 23rd,
is this.
Silver Nitrate, Magnesium
Take a look at the chromatogram.
Gas. Water. Magnesium. Silver.
That examination has already been completed. The conclusion was that it was gasoline.
It was not gasoline. The samples were contaminated.
Contaminated?
That means it was mixed with something else. Are you saying the Crime Scene Forensic unit are fools?
The error occurred due to the distinctive factor of the scene being a construction site.
When crude oil extracts, such as paint or synthetic resin burn,
it appears similar to a flammable substance like gasoline.
The real cause is the rest of the ingredients.
Can you see the magnesium oxide here?
So you're saying the magnesium burnt, right?
To be exact, it combined with oxygen.
Some metals explode in response to water.
Lithium, Sodium, Potassium, Magnesium
Among these, magnesium belongs to a highly explosive metal group.
Magnesium is highly explosive and is quite dangerous.
There is a risk of explosion even if subjected to shock or an increase in humidity.
So, another substance is mixed in to stabilize it.
And that is silver nitrate.
Silver nitrate is highly toxic, so you have to be careful when handling it
so that it doesn't touch your skin.
Now I'm going to drop in some water.
When ions of silver nitrate are dissolved in water, nitric acid and magnesium bind to each other,
then it becomes magnesium nitrate.
Magnesium nitrate made like this reacts with water and explodes.
This is the magic of setting water on fire that Detective Cha witnessed.
Stop with that, my gosh.
But can this be used as evidence?
Isn't that all sold at industrial complexes?
Customs clearance is prohibited for ignitable substances such as magnesium.
The culprit obtained this in large quantities?
Is that possible?
Magnesium powder is a medicine
Silver nitrate is diluted and used as a disinfectant.
Obtaining them is possible
if the culprit is a doctor.
That is just circumstantial.
What?
A statement showing the culprit personally purchased those goods or video evidence.
We need those more right now. Isn't that so?
The black box video in front of Team Leader Han's house is out.
Hemorrhagic cerebral infarction
Team one, go to the office. Team two, go to the parking lot.
- Yes.
- Run.
Mr. Lee Jung Yeop.
Yes?
You are under arrest without a warrant for the two murders of Son Wan Gi and Han Ju Seok.
You have the right to remain silent and to an attorney.
You'll have to wait.
I have a patient in his 60s who takes care of his two granddaughters. Let me save him.
He has a hemorrhagic cerebral infarction.
It took an hour for him to be found, an hour to get to the hospital, and in three hours I won't be able to do anything.
What would you like to do?
Melatonin
Goodnight. Non-habitual sleep inducer.
Restful Sleep. Melatonin.
We looked around everywhere
but we can't find anything.
What do you mean there's nothing?
Bloodstains, chemicals,
well, at least the things we're looking for aren't in this house.
Did you find anything?
There was no rice but only medicine.
Medicine? What kind of medicines are these?
Sleep inducers.
This house doesn't seem like a place where someone is living.
- Why?
- There's no junk.
There's no sense of a lifestyle or preference.
It feels like a hotel room.
Seonbae, should we also take this?
What is that?
It looks like it's a painting.
Just leave it.
What's the matter?
It's nothing.
I said it's nothing.
What is it?
It's just a painting.
♫  Some people want to live  ♫
♫  But turn their back on me  ♫
♫  The time I lived with me  ♫
♫  Some people say to me  ♫
Chimera
Investigator, what's your strategy?
My strategy is to pressure him until he breaks.
I am ncredibly good at finding things that are strange.
If there's something you want to know, ask a proper question.
Why did you kill him? Why?!
There are two cases in a row with the same MO.
Lee Jung Yeop, you are more of a coward than I thought.
Even if the mutt I was taking care of died, I wouldn't do this!
Who is the culprit?
No, who's next?