Young Master Liang, come, come
Come on in
You're here
Who is this piano player
It's from our Miaoyinfang
Su Jin, the first musician
Why is she wearing a veil
Music Su was born blind
Introverted by nature
So I never show my true face to people
His Highness the Ninth Prince returned to court after victory
The Ninth Prince is invincible outside
I can't control it
His ninth prince concubine
But so is Su Fengyu
He actually committed adultery with his third emperor brother
It's so lascivious
Don't know
What does she look like in bed
You can go back first
Wait a minute
What's wrong, Su Leshi
You killed someone
He tarnishes other people's reputations so casually
Death is not regrettable
I am the most profitable leader of Miaoyinfang
Mom knows
What should be done
This king just came back
Your master will lose his breath
Stealing military information
Are you going to kill me
Your Royal Highness, the little one knows his mistake
Your Highness
Knowing mistakes
You have to accept punishment
This is the poisonous scorpion of the Miao border
Like to cannibalize human flesh
Put your hands inside
They will rush to gnaw
Until your hands turn to bones
Your Highness
Your Highness, please spare the young one's life
Your Highness Your Highness
I don't want to doubt my son either
But his face
Although it's exactly the same as before
But I always feel that
He seems to be a different person
Three years no see
Some changes are normal
Besides, Brother Jiu is in power now
Someone who wants his life
Not a few
He is more cautious
It's understandable
But
There is no one like a mother
Get to know your son better
If the mother feels that there is something wrong
Maybe
Is there really a problem
Why doesn't the mother put an eyeliner?
With Brother Nine
There used to be
But it's not very useful
Now he came back from victory
The house is heavily guarded
How do ordinary people get in
My son has a way
Princess Chaoyu chose in
The musicians at the celebration banquet of the ninth prince
If you can be elected
Will be able to soar up
Princess
These three are the twenty-four squares
The most famous musicians
Undress
Campaign for musician
Shouldn't you judge winning or losing by piano skills
Which so many words
If you don't take it off
Disqualify you from running
This is the dead Ninth Prince Concubine
And so on
What's your name
Blind girl
Su Jin
Like
Really like
She's not pretending to be blind, is she
You really can't see
The slave has been unable to see since childhood
For three years
The mother is the ninth brother
I picked countless noble ladies from famous families
All rejected by him
He said
The position of the ninth prince and concubine
Only for Su Fengyu
If you can get into his eyes
But it flew to the branch and became a phoenix
This servant is willing to listen to Your Highness's orders
Just
Ninth Prince
I can really like it
Is the servant a blind girl
Of course
Because
Your face
Your Highness
Drink
You say
Is she more beautiful
Or am I more beautiful
Needless to say
Just by you
Also worthy of mentioning her
Killed one yesterday
Another today
Your Highness
His Royal Highness has a high position
To get close to His Highness
These people really do not use anything
It shows that I have many enemies
Don't be jealous
Is mediocre
Your Highness
Princess Chaoyu
Invite you to the back garden tomorrow
He said he had a surprise for you
Chaoyu
I'm really looking forward to this royal sister
What kind of surprise will it bring me
Ninety-nine prince concubine
Bitch
How dare you have an affair with the Ninth Prince Concubine
Su Fengyu, the daughter of Su Family
Adultery and fornication with the third prince Jian Qingxun
General Su Lie's collaboration with the enemy and treason
The evidence is conclusive and the guilt is unforgivable
The whole Su family was beheaded
Dad
I'll find someone to save you
Run fast
A Yu