They say the earth is round,
but it's actually like a pyramid.
I am on the bottom...
"Where no one can see me... Invisible."
Do you like rabbits?
Do you?
I-I-I...
Why?
"I like it." It's such a simple thing to say.
I want to say it,
but the words never make it out.
It's always like that.
My parents were worried and took me to see a lot of doctors.
"Most outgrow it."
That was their diagnosis.
"Find a hobby," they said.
So my parents bought me a camera.
They took me all over
and said to take pictures of what I liked.
The truth is, no scenery
or anything I saw seemed beautiful to me.
Kazunari! It's time to get up!
I'm seventeen years old.
The spring before the beginning of my final year in high school.
My parents had to move on short notice because of work.
Since I had only a year of high school left,
they decided I should remain here
in my late grandfather's big house.
It's my first time alone.
Are you sure you'll manage all by yourself?
This experience will do him good.
Call us right away if you need anything, okay?
I'll be fine.
And be sure to get to school on time.
I will.
[Hira]
A new semester, a new class.
The day that begins with those dreadful introductions
which I'm hopelessly bad at.
A rubber ducky...
It should be in warm bathtub
or in a kiddy pool somewhere.
Rubber ducky isn't drifting in a filthy waterway by choice.
I'm in the same way.
I don't stutter because I want to.
[Hashimoto Nishi High School]
I'm Yoshida. Lately, I've been hooked on grilled fish. I know you all like it, too!
Doesn't this look yummy?
Please, let me make it through
this year without incidents.
Next! Number 13.
I'm Hira Kazunari...
Hey, Number 13. What's the matter?
Introduce yourself.
Hi-Hi-Hi-Hi...
Oh no!
We've got a rapper!
Funny!
This guy's funny!
- Hi-Hi...
- Oh, sorry!
Is he stupid?
It's over.
Where have you been?
Sleeping.
Introduce yourself.
I'm Kiyoi Sou.
It felt like being pulled by an ebbing tide.
The way I'm attracted by him,
I can't take off my eyes from him.
Anything to add? Hobbies?
Not really.
Hira.
Hira Kazunari!
You can sit now.
Yes.
Kiyoi Sou...
He was beautiful.
[Riku Hagiwara: Kazunari Hira]
♫ In love ♫
[Yusei Yagi: Sou Kiyoi]
♫ A bullish look ♫
♫ It's annoying ♫
♫ To chase after you ♫
[Akira Takano: Kazuki Koyama]
♫ Are in my pocket ♫
♫ I don't need an answer ♫
♫ Do you like me? ♫
[My Beautiful Man]
[Episode 1]
Kiyoi-kun!
One month had passed since the introduction day.
As I expected,
my classmates treat me like I don't exist.
But I'm okay with that.
I am invisible.
And that's okay.
Unlike me,
who tries to go unnoticed at the lowest tier,
Kiyoi is always the center of attention.
We crushed them thanks to you, Kiyoi.
- Your shot is money.
- You're the real deal!
Sneaky good!
Kiyoi-kun, are you free after school?
I'm busy.
What a shame... Momo-chan is cute.
What?
Check that baby face and big boobs.
You guys are annoying.
No one dared cross Kiyoi.
He was totally aloof
from everyone in class.
It was as if
he was born to be king.
K-Kiyo...
Is he asleep?
The king is attractive,
even when he's asleep.
So beautiful...
What were you doing?
Th-Th-Th...
Th-Thank you.
What?
D-D-During self introductions...
You came in late
and saved me.
Thanks to you,
people leave me alone.
So...
Thank you.
You're not making sense.
You're creepy.
I'm sorry.
Our monitors for chemistry lab will be Hira, Kiyoi, and...
Anyone else?
- Me! Me!
- Pick me, Sensei!
Pick me!
This is awful!
King Kiyoi and a peasant like me never interact.
Please protect me,
rubber ducky.
Become air.
No eye contact.
Are you done with that?
Here you go.
I am invisible.
I'm fine.
But Kiyoi doesn't like karaoke, so that's out.
- The diner, then.
- Evenings get crowded.
I hate lines.
Where then?
My sister is home, so my place is out.
- Your place?
- It's impossible.
Hey.
Hey!
You!
You stand in line.
- Good idea.
- Perfect.
Call us when you get a table.
B-B-B-But...
How do I contact you?
Whose... number is this?
What are you waiting for?
Get going, Stutz.
Go!
Go! Go! Go!
Why "Stutz"?
Because he always stu-stutters.
I'm just a gofer.
Just used.
But...
[Kiyoi Sou - 080-251-362]
I've started to accept it.
Thanks for holding the table, Stutz!
Do us this favor!
You idiots. I didn't do this for you guys.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
So how did that go, Kiyoi?
- What?
- Don't try to hide it.
You know...
You're in this contest, right?
- Awesome!
- Wow!
Contest?
You already made it to round two!
Someone else entered my name.
- Who?
- My cousin.
- Oh...
- You never know.
Round three is your photo
in a magazine and a popularity contest.
You're like a star, Kiyoi!
Badass!
- Awesome!
- Wow!
[Best 35]
[Vote for Sou Kiyoi]
Don't forget us when you become a celebrity!
Your cousin's serious.
I knew it!
Kiyoi is special.
It's for me, right?
Challenge.
Let me guess.
You like vanilla.
Yes.
My favorite is rum raisin.
It's my favorite.
For real!
Stutz. The usual. And three ice creams, too.
- How about you, Kiyoi?
- Ginger ale.
- And a ginger ale. Thanks.
- Thanks.
- Do you mean it?
- No!
Do it!
What's the matter with you guys?
Wipe that up quickly!
What?
Say, mind cleaning this up for us?
Help us out, Stutz. I'm sopping wet.
It's what you do, right, Stutz?
Do it.
Hey! What're you doing?
I-I was...
Hurry and get our drinks.
Yoshida!
Why're you calling him Stutz?
Well, but...
That's what you guys call him.
We do...
So?
You got a problem?
I'll clean it up.
Ginger ale!
Okay.
This is too much.
You're annoying.
Buy yourself an ice cream.
Quickly, go!
I'll go right now!
We'll be waiting!
Kiyoi couldn't stand the idea of waiting.
He crushed Yoshida for only that reason.
I have never seen anyone so selfish and strong.
I'm not wasting this on ice cream.
Okay. All clean.
I want to keep these near me forever.
I've never felt this way before.
A cruel and glorious imprint.
Beautiful like a spring storm.
Overwhelming in its power.
I could feel my view of the world changing.
Kiyoi?
I know what I'm doing is creepy.
But...
I was too curious.
Hi!
Are you here to watch a class?
Well, no...
Our dance school offers hip-hop, jazz...
A dance studio?
We just started K-pop too.
Would you like to try a class?
He was completely different from the Kiyoi I see at school.
I can't take my eyes off of him.
One, two, three... and hop!
Okay, take a break.
What?!
What the hell were you doing there?
I j-j-just...
h-happened to...
What a nuisance.
Just take your time.
I'll wait.
I was taking photos when...
I happened to see you.
Talking with you gets on my nerves.
I get it. I feel the same.
Ginger ale.
Oh... yes.
Here.
I thought you might be thirsty.
Don't tell anyone, okay?
What?
That I'm taking dance classes.
I see. So that's what he wanted to tell me.
He acted disinterested in the contest,
but actually, he was trying hard.
He doesn't want everyone to know.
I won't tell.
I'm alone at home and at school anyway.
Even at home?
My parents moved for work, so it's just me.
Oh, I see.
So you really are alone?
I won't tell, no matter what.
What if you were threatened with death?
I would die.
You're weird.
What the...?!
S-S-Sorry!
- I couldn't help it.
- Couldn't help it?!
Just...
So beautiful...
What?!
Don't ever take my photo again!
You are... annoying.
It was the first time I looked so directly at someone.
♫ That's why you don't see me ♫
♫ I go back to place I used to be ♫
♫ Isn't it my job to follow you? ♫
♫ It was for the best and forever ♫
I never understood the yearning I felt inside of me.
But now, I definitely know.
I like you.
I like you, Kiyoi.
♫ Can you let me kiss it? ♫
Will there ever be a day when I tell him how I feel?
♫ I'll embrace all your words like glass ♫
♫ Even if you're not a kind person ♫
No.
That day...
will never come.
♫ I'm so absorbed that no one can stop me ♫
[Next Episode]
Summer break.
It's our last summer of high school? it's now or never!
Let's invite the girls!
Kiyoi is... in my room.
Hearing a guy adding "kun" to my name makes my skin crawl.
Just call me Kiyoi.
Kiyoi is someone special, after all.
[This drama is fiction]