I can't see anything.
I can't see Ko Mi-nam!
I told you not to stay
where I can't see you!
-Who was that?
-What's going on?
Tae-gyung?
-Who was that?
-What's going on?
-Tae-gyung!
What's going on?
Look over here, please!
-Do the other members know about this?
-Please, over here!
-A word, please!
-Shin-woo!
She's my woman!
I had to keep her a secret until now.
This is the woman I love.
I do not wish to reveal my girlfriend.
Please, move aside so she can leave.
Tae-gyung, do you know
who Shin-woo's girlfriend is?
-Who is it?
-What's her name?
-A name!
That...
Was that...
Yes.
So he was a girl.
Hey! What the heck is going on?
Where did Shin-woo's girlfriend come from?
You know who she is, don't you?
How am I supposed to do damage control
for this? The premiere has to go on!
What was Ko Mi-nam thinking?
How do you know that it was her?
What?
Oh, so, I...
I'll talk to you later.
What do I say? What do I do?
Did he figure it out?
I could've ended her.
Why did you all have to appear!
-Shin-woo!
KO MI-NAM'S FIRST SINGLE ALBUM
MUSIC VIDEO PREMIERE
I'm sorry.
I'm actually
not a man.
I know you'll be very angry
if you see me now.
I can't ask you to forgive me for this...
Wow, what can I say?
This is all so sudden,
I don't know where to begin.
I wasn't prepared for a situation
like this, to be honest.
Should I be angry first?
But it'd be just as strange
to immediately say that it's all fine.
Mi-nam! You were a girl?
I can't believe this.
I understand.
Let me see you clearly. Lift up your head.
You really are a girl.
You really are pretty.
How did I not know this whole time?
I thought you were just clumsy,
but this is quite a feat you pulled off.
You were so good to me the whole time.
I'm so sorry that I completely fooled you.
We'll talk more later
about what exactly happened.
Anyhow. Ko Mi-nam!
I'm done treating you
like a little brother.
From this moment on,
we'll start over.
Shin-woo! Open the door!
-Shin-woo! A word, please!
-Tell us who she is!
As you can see, Ko Mi-nam is a woman.
I had known it before.
Sorry for keeping it a secret.
If you can't accept this
in any shape or form, speak up now.
I'll bear full responsibility
for Ko Mi-nam and not get you involved.
I've already jumped headfirst into it.
Shin-woo is in. What about you, Jermy?
Ko Mi-nam.
You were a girl this whole time.
A girl?
I'm sorry, Jermy.
Ko Mi-nam!
I had no idea...
Ko Mi-nam! You're a girl!
I'm so for this! I love it!
Ko Mi-nam!
Ko Mi-nam, I get it, I totally understand!
Am I dreaming? Is this real?
So I'll take that as a yes.
Now, to the situation at hand.
Ko Mi-nam.
Ko Mi-nam?
Forget it.
This is a dream. It has to be.
Right? Is it not? Is this real life?
Forget him too, he's lost it.
Shin-woo. Go get Mr. Ma and Ms. Wang.
Right? It's real, right?
Would Hwang Tae-gyung have figured out
that it was me who put her up to this?
Then he'll call us off immediately.
Ko Mi-nam is the one who's supposed
to be ruined, not me!
I don't want to end this...
-Excuse me!
-Look over here, please!
Excuse me! We cannot and will not
reveal Shin-woo's girlfriend!
Please return to the premiere!
-Just...
-No!
Hoon-i! What... is this
Shin-woo's girlfriend?
It's all right. I'll take her back home.
The kids are all in the dressing room,
you should start the premiere!
Right! Thanks!
I can't see! Slow down!
We're really all in the same boat now!
Ko Mi-nam.
We're all in the same boat now.
You told me that you came all the way
here so no one else will get hurt.
If that's what you really want,
stay until the end. As the man Ko Mi-nam.
Now, even if you want to stop,
we cannot let you.
We'll be accountable for you,
so be accountable for us as well.
Tae-gyung.
I look forward to it, Mi-nam.
Shin-woo.
You better take good care of me,
Ko Mi-nam.
Jermy...
Thank you so much. And I'm so sorry.
I'll make sure that I don't get caught.
Kang Shin-woo!
You...
You and I will talk after the premiere.
Mi-nam. Let's go.
We can call back the reporters.
Let's give them a great show!
-Let's go.
-Ko Mi-nam!
She's my woman!
Thank goodness we passed that hurdle.
It's all thanks to you.
It's broken.
I wasn't even paying attention
to the premiere.
Why would he bring her here
if he was so adamant in hiding her away?
Was this unplanned and unexpected?
Hold on a second.
Hwang Tae-gyung had been looking
for someone just before this happened.
-It's Hwang Tae-gyung!
-It's Tae-gyung!
-He's so handsome!
Hwang Tae-gyung? Who is he looking for?
We'll begin shortly.
This woman, who appeared out of nowhere.
Hwang Tae-gyung,
who was urgently looking for someone.
Perhaps there is a connection
between those two?
Kang Shin-woo's hidden lover.
Hwang Tae-gyung's hidden lover.
There has to be a connection.
Here they come!
The secret is hidden in there.
And I will find out what it is.
We won't take any more questions.
We are done for today.
I trust that you watched
the music video well?
Yes, I look forward
to your wonderfully-written articles!
Then today is a very great day!
Right?
Then I must have
a congratulatory party tonight!
Ko Mi-nam!
-Shin-woo.
-All right.
Before we do, there's another hurdle
we have to face.
What is it?
Honey...
It's a very scary hurdle. The Fake Hurdle.
Tae-gyung, I don't know
what this is all about...
Drop the act. I already know
that it was your doing.
Is that so? Figured it out, have you?
Do they all know too?
So they really forgave her
and they are okay with it?
What, do you think you're actually angels
because people call you that?
Ko Mi-nam.
You're so ridiculous,
you couldn't even pull that off?
But Hwang Tae-gyung.
You can't call this off. Ever.
Remember what I told you
when we started this.
The only one who can end this is me.
You agreed not to divulge anything
about Ko Mi-nam.
You broke the rules first.
Fine. I may have broken it first,
but if you want to keep my mouth shut,
you better keep up the act.
Hwang Tae-gyung,
keep pretending you're my lover.
Ko Mi-nam, keep pretending you're a guy.
You two keep pretending
you're a couple of angels.
Fine. You keep pretending
you're angelic, Fake Fairy.
Of course, I will.
Honey, I'll be going now.
Good night, everyone.
Tae-gyung. So you were
fake-dating Yoo He-i
to protect Ko Mi-nam?
Everything she just said
was actually the truth.
Tae-gyung, I--
All your apologies and gratitude,
I've heard them more than enough.
Tell them to Shin-woo and Jermy.
I didn't expect this either...
Please? Just one more time!
It will be just this one time,
Mr. Secretary!
I have to see Ms. Mo once more
and talk to her about the copyright thing!
-Just once!
-Fine. You may.
Oh, nice!
You'll be blessed, young man!
Ma'am?
Where could she be?
Oh, my! Look at all these bottles.
What a mess.
Wait, what is this?
My brother? And the twins!
She even has their picture.
Don't touch anything without permission.
I didn't touch anything.
Oh, I need to go pee.
Where's the bathroom?
Oh, this must be it.
I'm going to the bathroom so much lately.
Oh, I'm sorry! Excuse me!
Ms. Mo?
Oh, my goodness gracious! Ms. Mo! Hwa-ran!
Hey! In here! Ms. Mo! Hwa-ran! Oh my!
"Yellow Pants" Ko Mi-ja has rescued
a nationally beloved singer. Yes, indeed!
Who knows what could've happened
if it wasn't for me?
Oh, man, that was a real...
-Here you go.
-Oh, thank you.
Thank you for finding and helping Ms. Mo.
Please don't tell anyone else
about this incident.
Oh, of course!
You know, I'm such a big fan of hers.
Hope you get better soon!
I'll be off now.
Oh, by the way.
I was wondering, has Ms. Mo
ever received surgery for everything?
She has not.
I'll have to ask you to leave now.
She hasn't?
Really?
Then what's the surgery scar
on her belly for?
Did she have a C-section?
Did she? But she's not even married!
Oh, my!
Not even actual brothers
and sisters share a room!
Ko Mi-nam! Even if you may be comfortable
with Tae-gyung and don't see him as a guy,
you can't stay here anymore!
I'll move all your stuff
back to your room.
Sorry for imposing on you
for so long, Tae-gyung.
By that, do you mean
that you will no longer impose on me?
How could I? I'm not that shameless.
I'll take everything back with me.
Fine. So this doesn't even count as hers?
So cold-hearted! So disloyal! She just
throws it away after she's done with it!
She doesn't even know
that she has lost this.
I mean, it's in pieces.
She won't need this either.
Why did I even bring this back?
How could I bring Pig Rabbit with me?
I've even lost the hairpin...
Tae-gyung, you went through so much.
Thank you.
There's nothing for a party!
I'm pretty hungry.
Should we go out to eat?
Let's go to the market! I want to go
shopping with Ko Mi-nam, all chummy like!
Sure, let's take her grocery shopping.
Ko Mi-nam attracts accidents like
a magnet. You don't know what will happen.
Just leave her at home, that's safer.
Then you can stay home and be safe,
Tae-gyung. We'll take her with us.
Ko Mi-nam! Let's go to the market!
ALL-LOW PRICES!
Come this way.
I've never been to such a huge market
this late at night before.
Isn't it cool? There's no one here!
Vegetables!
Doesn't this look good?
Doesn't this one look tastier?
It's redder.
Maybe it is. But this one
smells really good too.
I'm not good at picking things out
by smell.
What else are you going to use
that pig nose for if you can't smell?
Ko Mi-nam. I'll make you a cup
of vegetable juice every morning too.
Let's have a glass together!
I'll blend it for you!
Really? I'd love that so much!
I'll blend these for you every morning.
I guess I'll get to see a rabbit blending
carrots every morning.
Ko Mi-nam! I like you so much!
What? What are you doing? Tae-gyung!
Jermy grew up in England so he
is used to being touchy and affectionate.
But you must never get used to it,
Ko Mi-nam.
-Yes, Tae-gyung.
-Tae-gyung!
Tae-gyung! Where are you?
Unzip this before you go!
Oh, this was our very first ad.
Do you remember this, guys?
Jermy, don't do it.
You'll ruin the fantasy. Don't do it.
Do you know how we shot this?
"Just one bite, and oh, my, it's so cold!"
And Tae-gyung wore icicles on his head
and Shin-woo was a snowman!
I want to see it too!
I'll show it to you when I get home.
Should we look for all the things
we shot ads for?
Let's go!
BIBIMYEON
Out of all the ads we shot,
this one was the best one.
Mix it, mix it, Bibimyeon
We didn't do it like that.
Wasn't it like this?
Jermy did it correctly.
We mixed it upwards and sideways.
Oh, that's right.
All right. We grabbed it like this and...
-Mix it, mix it, Bibimyeon
Why are we doing this here anyway?
"Angel Chocolate, melting her lips away."
So greasy.
I'm melting away.
I'd take Bibimyeon over this.
Why? You were so cool!
Ko Mi-nam!
-Strike!
-Ko Mi-nam!
-Catch!
-Mi-nam.
There you are.
And here we go!
Tae-gyung.
Ko Mi-nam. This beer is another
product we shot an ad for.
"Cheers!"
From ice cream bars to beer,
you really did a lot of ads!
If you think of all the ads we shot,
we really did get old, huh?
The kids who ate ice cream bars
became adults who drink beer.
But if another ice cream bar ad
comes in, I'll be great in it!
"It's so cold!"
Ko Mi-nam. Let's do it, the two of us.
Try it.
"It's so cold."
Ko Mi-nam! You're so cute!
Take me with you!
Cheers.
No sipping. In one.
They were just kids to me,
but they're all dating now,
without telling me...
They started as an idol boy group,
just kids, you know.
But they're all grown-ups now.
There aren't many idol groups
that have made it this far.
You can say that they've had a good run.
But! Mi-nam is here now,
they should go on and on, to success!
Right.
I just feel like they're hiding something
from me recently as well.
Pardon?
They're all grown now
and they are keeping secrets from me...
I'm going to the bathroom.
Now, what?
Nothing to it.
We hold out for a bit longer
and the real Mi-nam will come,
they switch, happy endings for everyone.
Then what about her? She's just going
back to where she was before?
That's what I had initially planned...
But Mi-nyeo's situation has changed
drastically, so I'm not sure anymore.
What situation?
She has realized...
what love is.
Where's Shin-woo and Jermy?
They went to get more beer.
Ko Mi-nam. You're carrying
something on your head.
Looks good on you.
On my head?
Why is this here?
Carrots are 3,000 won.
My hairpin was 3,000 won too...
I told you, it was 100,000 won,
not 3,000 won!
Tae-gyung. I lost the hairpin.
Again?
At least, you're aware that you lost it.
Did you see it? Where is it?
It was rolling on the floor in pieces
at the premiere venue.
It was? Oh no... What do I do?
What do you mean, what do you do?
It's useless now, just chuck it.
-I...
-Excuse me.
Are you okay? You almost fell.
Oh, thank you.
Be careful.
Tae-gyung! I brought more beer!
Let's go.
To me, it's the most precious thing.
I can't seem to sleep well
the past few days.
When did this start?
Was it since Ko Mi-nam left my room?
Maybe I'm not used to it yet?
Aunt Mi-ja? When did you get here?
I came back just now.
Everyone was sleeping
so I came back in quietly.
You surprised me.
Good night.
Mi-nam is sleeping well, right?
Ko Mi-nam is in your room now.
Mi-nam isn't in my room.
Wasn't he sleeping in your room?
I had so much soju, I'm so thirsty now.
-What the heck is this?
-Where has she gone this late at night?
Thank you so much.
It's something very important to me,
so I have to find it.
Just look for it quickly and leave.
Don't mention me if someone finds out.
Yes, sir. Thank you!
I'll leave as soon as I find it.
I can't find her anywhere.
Where did she go?
Wait. No way.
No. There's no way she would've
gone there to look for that.
Where could she have gone?
What did she say before?
What do you mean, what do you do?
It's useless now, just chuck it.
-I...
-Excuse me.
Are you okay?
I didn't get to hear the rest.
What could she have been trying to say?
What do you mean, what do you do?
It's useless now, just chuck it.
I...
Agree with you, Tae-gyung.
If it's useless,
you might as well throw it away.
It's only worth 3,000 won anyway!
There's no way Ko Mi-nam
can talk to me like that.
So that can't be it.
Then...
What do you mean, what do you do?
It's useless now, just chuck it.
I...
Couldn't find a chance to throw it away,
so thank goodness I lost it!
It would've been embarrassing to wear that
anywhere. It's worth 3,000 won anyway.
No, she didn't hate it that much.
She was so happy
when she got it back from Fake Fairy.
Then... Did she?
What do you mean, what do you do?
It's useless now, just chuck it.
I...
Can't throw it away like that.
That hairpin you gave me
is really precious to me.
I will find it. I have to.
If that's what she meant to say,
if she's over there looking for it now...
Why would she do that?
Is it okay... If I like you?
No. She likes Shin-woo...
There's no way she would've gone
at this hour to look for that.
Where could it be? He said
they didn't clean the place yet.
Oh, maybe someone picked it up?
There's no way. She's not here.
I'm just here to confirm the fact
that she is not here,
since I can't sleep anyway.
Why can't I find it?
Maybe it's under here.
Why am I all nervous over
something like Ko Mi-nam?
The lights are on.
The security guard said I couldn't
get caught by anyone.
What was I thinking?
INCOMING CALL
It's very late. Why are you calling?
Ms. Mo is very ill.
She has been looking for you.
Oh, I found it!
Why didn't I see this before?
Thank goodness.
I don't think I could live much longer.
I mean...
What's the point in living any longer?
There's nothing to look forward to.
Is that why you need something
to look back fondly upon?
If I say yes,
will you give me such a memory
so I could endure my boredom
and live a long life?
If I say no, you'll call me
for something like this again.
I'm going to grow more ill.
When I call you,
won't you come?
In order to prevent that,
I suppose I have to do it.
I'll make you that song.
I knew you would.
Because you're my son.
No mother
makes their son do something like this.
When that song is released,
I'll tell you everything.
What my love was like...
How big my love was...
I have to glue this on correctly.
I bet Tae-gyung is good
at stuff like this.
No. If Tae-gyung finds out that
I brought this back, he'll be suspicious!
He might find out my feelings for him.
Did it stick?
Oh no! Not you two!
You can't stick together!
Tae-gyung.
What are you doing?
Did you go somewhere?
I should ask you the same thing.
Where were you?
I was home. Why?
You were at home? Where?
Just, you know, here and there.
Anyway, I was home. I didn't go anywhere!
Yeah? I thought...
What are you doing?
Oh, something I consider precious broke
so I was gluing it back together.
Like what?
Oh, a cup! It's really precious to me
and it broke so I was gluing it back
but my fingers got stuck.
Don't worry about me!
You should go to sleep!
Did you soak it thoroughly?
Yes.
That tickles!
It's so cool, how it stuck together
like that! How could it stick like that?
Whose fingers are these?
Sorry.
It tickles!
I wonder why the adhesive
got on your fingers?
If it got on your mouth,
you wouldn't have been able to talk.
I'm sorry.
Tae-gyung. I got into trouble again,
didn't I?
This time is fine.
Thanks to these ridiculous fingers,
I got to concentrate and clear my mind.
Did something bad happen?
There's a person who is making me
do something unreasonable.
But I ended up agreeing to do it.
Because of you, because I had you,
I lost that precious thing.
I lost him because of you.
Let me at least remember him.
Help me.
Strangely enough, every time my mind
was cluttered because of that person,
you were always there somehow.
It helped a lot. You were quite useful.
Like today.
I'm glad to hear that my fingers
were useful!
If I had known, I should've just glued
all ten of them together!
All done!
Why do you do that all the time?
It's good for your health!
Do you have some kind of a secret?
I don't!
Fine then.
I feel sleepy now,
after all this chatting.
I'm going to bed.
The secret is my heart.
First Tae-gyung, now Shin-woo!
They're both dating now!
But we are true fans,
we have to congratulate Shin-woo too!
-Congratulations!
Shin-woo, I'm really sorry. You got
involved in this mess because of me.
Seriously though. Everyone has been
nagging me to tell them who she is.
It has to be hard. I know.
Moreover, the girl I like is going
through a hard time because of it.
I'm really sorry to her too.
Hasn't Shin-woo been acting the same way
even after he found out about her?
How would I know?
Whoa, whoa. Hold on!
What are you doing?
Why are you eavesdropping?
It's just for a bit.
You already have someone you like
but because of me... I'm sorry.
I should go to her now, even if it's late
and explain everything. Right?
Yes, you should!
Mi-nam. If it's needed, can you go
and explain it to her?
Yes, of course I will! It's all my fault.
As many times as you need me to!
Then I should set up a time
to explain everything.
You have to come with me, okay?
Yes! I will!
Tae-gyung.
I feel so bad for Mi-nam.
She has to go to the girl that the guy
she has a crush on likes
and say, "I'm nothing.
Kang Shin-woo likes you, not me."
She has to go and say that!
Like she'd go.
She just agreed to appease him.
She'll get out of it somehow.
She's a woman too, she has pride.
She wouldn't do such a thing.
Right? She wouldn't go there, right?
She likes him so much.
If she did end up going there,
her heart will be ripped
into a thousand pieces.
Mi-nam.
I don't think I can stay with you
for the time being.
I have some business to tend to,
but if you're with me,
it's a bit difficult.
Is that so? Then good thing
everything has worked out.
Have a restful stay
at your friend's house, Aunt Mi-ja.
Yes, sure. I'll be off now.
Mi-nam. Have you ever seen the singer
Mo Hwa-ran by any chance?
Ms. Mo?
I have. Why?
When? When you were young? With Mi-nyeo?
No, at the broadcasting company.
Right. Of course. That's what I thought.
She has visited your agency
before too, right?
Then I shouldn't stay here with you.
All right, Mi-nam. I'll be going!
Yes. Stay healthy, Aunt Mi-ja!
I will. You stay safe
and healthy too, okay?
I have to take care of the copyright issue
before Mi-nam finds out.
It would be so great if the kid
Mo Hwa-ran had secretly
was my Mi-nam!
I'd get hit by a flood of money!
PERSONAL DETAILS REPORT
The older brother, Mi-nam,
is currently in the States
but we haven't found him yet.
The younger sister, Mi-nyeo,
was at a convent which she left recently.
One is in the States
and one was at a convent?
Look for the girl first.
No, that's not it.
Doesn't she care about her heart
ripping into a thousand pieces?
Ko Mi-nam! Let's go for a walk
with Jolie when we get home.
I'll show you a water spring,
it's a hidden treasure!
Sure!
The weather is great, should we play
some badminton? Loser buys beer.
You're coming too?
Mi-nam. Do you not want me to go?
No, I want you to come.
"I want you to come." She's just digging
her own grave over there.
Ko Mi-nam. Don't think of playing
before you get all the songs down pat.
Don't leave my side
and memorize them all by today.
I've already got most of them memorized.
I don't have to stay by you all the time.
I was trying to help you,
but you'd refuse?
Yes. I refuse.
I'm going to play badminton.
Yes! Ko Mi-nam! Let's go together!
What about you, Tae-gyung?
It really is quiet up here.
Only grandmas and grandpas come here,
so they won't pay attention to us at all.
There's no wind either.
Right?
Smash!
Let's split the teams.
I'll be on Mi-nam's team.
Is that okay, Mi-nam?
I'm no good at this, is that okay?
It's fine.
Then I'm okay with it too.
Smash!
Later, it will be ripped into
a thousand pieces. So is it okay now?
Stupid Pig Rabbit.
One, two, three!
Ko Mi-nam? Step aside.
Shin-woo, you're on my team.
But that's too big of a gap
between the two teams' skills.
Then it's me and Mi-nam
and Shin-woo and Tae-gyung?
I'm fine with that.
If I'm on the same team as Mi-nam,
I'm for it.
Let's end this quickly.
Oh, my...
Hey!
Tae-gyung! It's just for fun!
What is this, the Olympics?
The game is almost over.
Mi-nam, try hitting this, okay?
See? Look how good Ko Mi-nam is
when you give it to her nicely!
You couldn't hit any of the ones
I sent over?
How are you even bad at that?
You're not good at anything.
The game is over, so let's go.
I'm good at other things! I'm good too!
Ko Mi-nam, you're amazing!
I think you'll get first place!
I may not be good at a lot of things,
but I have great endurance!
Where I grew up, I beat all the boys
and went first place in this!
I get that you're amazing,
so you can come down now.
I can keep going until I drop.
Does she want to appeal to him with that?
I'm tearing up, Pig Rabbit.
You're so good! So great. There.
Good enough? Now, come down.
I told you I can keep going,
so why are you butting in?
I'll show you that I can endure it
until the end!
Ko Mi-nam won't even come down
when Tae-gyung tells her to?
Should I try?
"It's so cold!"
Mix it, mix it, Bibimyeon
"I melt, on her lips."
I won't fall. I can keep going.
I will show you
that there is something I'm good at.
Tae-gyung's words have no effect,
Jermy's laughs won't do anything.
Should I give it a go, then?
Whatever you do, Shin-woo, I...
Shin-woo! That's cheating!
There were no rules against it.
Mi-nam, you lost to me.
Shin-woo, you really surprised me.
Don't pull jokes like that.
It wasn't a joke. We bet, remember?
I'm really competitive, you see.
Shin-woo! Don't scare Ko Mi-nam!
Ko Mi-nam.
You take Jolie with you.
Let's go.
Was that too surprising for her?
I have so many more surprises
in store for her.
That scared me.
Wait. Why do I have to be scared
because of Ko Mi-nam?
I'm honestly stressing myself out
over Mi-nam.
Why?
If you get down to it, Mi-nam is a girl.
But she's with Tae-gyung.
Why are you worried about that?
Do you think Tae-gyung would even
look at her when he has you?
Don't be silly.
To others, I may look like a shining star,
beloved by many,
but I'm just like any other girl.
I get jealous and I worry
over all the little things.
You're so delicate, He-i.
It'll be over soon.
Even if Mi-nam goes back to being a girl,
she may not leave.
She loves it here,
and everyone is so good to her.
Why would she want to go back
to where she's from?
He-i.
He told me not to tell anyone this, but...
Even Tae-gyung doesn't know.
What is it?
I'm only telling you because you
seem to be worrying way too much.
Mi-nam used to be at a convent.
She grew up at an orphanage
that was run by the convent
and naturally wanted to become a nun.
But she gave up everything
for her brother and she came here.
Then will she return to the convent?
I think that's the only place she has.
I'm sure she'll return there...
But don't let anyone know, okay?
Of course.
But if Tae-gyung and the others find out,
they'll be so shocked.
Why do I have to worry so much
about Ko Mi-nam?
It's Ko Mi-nam.
Jermy told me to bring this to you.
It's lime juice, your favorite.
Lime?
It's all your fault that I have to drink
this sour thing.
What? Why is this my fault?
That's a bit unfair, Tae-gyung.
Ko Mi-nam. Didn't you used to hold it in
and move on even if it was unfair?
I'm sorry. I'm holding it in.
I'll continue to hold it in well.
Then why didn't you hold it in back there?
With Shin-woo. You fell immediately.
I was caught by surprise, that's all!
Yes. It was so obvious.
Do you think that was it?
You wanting to be with him,
wanting to appeal to him,
your feelings are so obvious!
Tae-gyung! I told you that wasn't it.
You won't hold out for long.
Soon enough, Shin-woo will find out
and he has to apologize to you.
That all counts as being a nuisance
and causing trouble to the other party!
Is it that bad to like someone?
I don't want anything, I'm doing my best
to hide it. I can't even do that?
Like you have time for that right now?
If I were Shin-woo, I wouldn't like it!
Hey. Are you crying?
No! I can hold it in. I won't get caught!
I mean, it's a bit annoying,
but do you want me to help?
No. Don't help.
Don't meddle if it's so annoying to you.
Just act as if you don't know anything,
as you have been doing so far!
Fine! Let's see how long
you can hold it in, Ko Mi-nam!
Reverend Mother. My feelings,
my heart is nothing but a nuisance.
When I leave this place,
after holding on as long as I can...
I'll leave my star behind, safe and sound.
Please make sure no outsiders
come in after this time.
And please prepare everything
just as I asked.
Yes. We'll ensure your privacy.
When you stand here today,
you'll get to see the woman I love.
I hope you won't be too surprised.
You're going where?
I promised to meet up with Shin-woo.
There's someone I have to meet
and explain on behalf of Shin-woo.
Sister.
Do you have to go?
I should. If that's the only thing
I can do for him, I need to do it.
How can I stop her...
I'm the one who caused all this.
How can I stop her love?
I'm the biggest sinner!
I'm the sinner! I'm the one to blame!
Tae-gyung, we're in big trouble.
I'm busy. If it concerns Ko Mi-nam,
don't even bring it up.
No, it's an emergency.
I can't just stand by and watch.
Ko Mi-nam told me not to meddle
if it's so annoying. And I don't plan to.
Mi-nam went to Shin-woo.
All that denial, for what?
Did she go to confess or something?
She went to confess.
What?
Shin-woo asked her to come and explain
everything to his girlfriend.
And Ko Mi-nam just went?
Yes! She said she had to do everything
in her power
and she just left!
What an idiot!
Yes. I'm on my way.
I'll be right there, Shin-woo.
Sure, hurry. I'll be waiting.
Tae-gyung.
I...
I have to go! Tae-gyung,
please let go of me!
Tae-gyung, I have to go!
Why are you meddling?
Tae-gyung, why are you doing this?
Tae-gyung!
Tae-gyung! I have to go!
I'll be going now.
Do you even know where you're going?
You. I knew you were clumsy and out of it,
accident prone, unable to do things right,
and always causing trouble
and being a nuisance to others,
but have you no pride either?
When I look at you, you're so foolish,
and it annoys me so much!
So don't pay attention to me!
How can I, when you go around like this!
Why does it matter to you,
where I'm going right now?
It doesn't cause you any trouble, so why
are you meddling and being annoyed?
Because you're like an idiot
and it makes me mad!
Why do I have to be so mad because of you?
Why are you angry because of me?
Just ignore me, you're good at that!
Just don't look at whatever I'm doing!
You keep making me look!
You can't even see anything correctly!
You're so full of yourself,
you shine so brightly by yourself
that you can't even see anything
around you!
You can't see anything, you don't know
anything, so why are you doing this?
I'm doing my best to hold it in
so why are you getting mad at me!
Just leave me in the dark!
Who asked you to look at me?
Subtitle translation by Grace Kim