[Dawn is Breaking]
[Adapted from Fanqie Novel
"After the Obsessed State Preceptor's Takeover"]
[Episode 24]
[Jealousy]
But I'm different from most people.
My heart is on the right side.
If...
If we both die here,
will you regret it?
Will you
regret it
even for a moment?
I'll never let you die.
[Bishui Town]
[Yuelai Inn]
Come in.
What happened to you?
It's nothing.
Is there hot water?
I want to bathe.
Who's there?
Miss.
It's really you, miss!
Pei Che?
Miss, what happened to your eyes?
It's nothing,
just an eye condition.
Oh.
Miss, you're bleeding.
Don't worry, it's not my blood.
How did you end up here?
After you knocked me out that day,
I quickly came to my senses.
I decided to return to Dafeng
and reclaim what's rightfully mine.
But before that,
I had to ensure your safety.
I'm familiar with the terrain.
After leaving the Ghost Realm,
the first place to stop is Bishui Town,
so I came to meet you.
How about that, miss?
Aren't I smart?
It was just a casual move.
You didn't need to go this far.
To you, it was a casual move,
but I'll never forget it
for the rest of my life.
[Yuelai Inn]
Ow, it hurts!
You weren't this delicate
a few days ago.
Miss, be gentle. It hurts!
Miss, someone's in.
But really,
this person didn't even knock
before entering your room?
This young man saved my life.
If it weren't for him,
I wouldn't have made it out
of the Ghost Realm.
We've spent quite some time together.
I'm blind
and he can't talk,
so we've become more casual
with each other.
Sorry for making you feel awkward.
Alright.
A mute?
Huh.
Well then, the one who saved you
is also my savior.
Now that you're blind
and this mute young man
can't talk,
you might feel lonely.
But no worries.
I love talking to you, miss.
If you ever feel bored,
just come find me.
Ouch!
Miss, he's grabbing me!
Miss,
he's grabbing me too hard!
[Yuelai Inn]
You're lying to her.
You're not mute at all.
What happens between us couple
is none of your business.
Couple?
Miss never mentioned you before.
She did tell me
her family had long since perished.
If you're her husband,
you must be her late husband.
You're no ordinary slave.
What's your purpose
in getting close to her?
Miss saved my life.
I might scheme against the whole world,
but I'd never scheme against her.
If I find out you intend to harm her,
I'll take your life.
I'll say
the same to you.
You can't see.
I'll find someone to help you.
No need, I'm not used to that.
Stay outside the screen.
If I run into any trouble,
I'll call out.
Is that alright?
I'm afraid it's not appropriate.
I trust you.
If you really feel awkward,
you can get Pei Che from next door.
No need.
I'll help you.
♪The wind under the eaves♪
♪Gently taps on the wooden door♪
♪The candle flame flickers
as I sleep soundly♪
♪The night is at its peak♪
♪A thunderclap rolls♪
♪Stirring up old dreams again♪
♪Thoughts linger
on the warmth of the past♪
♪The sincerity of the past♪
♪Fireworks fall like rain♪
♪But soon they cool♪
♪I watch as you pass by♪
♪Not daring to ask♪
♪Like the moon, waxing and waning♪
♪How could it ask more?♪
♪You and I are like a small boat
on the river♪
♪Rising and falling with the waves♪
♪Speaking of love and hate♪
♪How can I distinguish them?♪
♪Longing for fate, praying sincerely♪
Are you still there?
Could you bring me
clean clothes
and put them on the screen?
♪Yet the previous ones
are still within them♪
♪Why do they remain silent?♪
♪Fireworks fall like rain♪
♪But soon they cool♪
♪I look, adding a few more strokes
to the word "love"♪
♪A new year's ring♪
♪The cicada's cry is close,
autumn leaves are near♪
♪Yet it's hard to recognize each other♪
♪I sigh, why are you and I♪
♪Rising and falling,
drifting in this way?♪
Dry your hair.
Got it.
I'm leaving now.
Get some rest.
♪A thousand mountains
bathed in the moonlight♪
You too.
♪Only now do I know
the years won't return♪
♪In youth, we spoke
of everlasting love too recklessly♪
♪Believing a heartfelt connection
would last♪
♪Later, the great dream of dawn
is no longer as it was♪
♪The passionate are the most sorrowful♪
♪He, with no time to spare, should be♪
♪Grass and trees, untouched by harm♪
♪Yet he ventured into the tumult
of the world, taking a journey♪
♪He's like the moon falling
into the dust, full of desolation♪
♪Thus, partings in life and death
became commonplace♪
♪Love, hate, joy, sorrow,
he dares not taste again♪
♪He's endured long years,
unable to let go of memories♪
Na Jinci,
this time,
are you lying to me?
♪The wind under the eaves♪
♪Gently taps on the wooden door♪
♪The candle flame flickers
as I sleep soundly♪
♪The night is at its peak♪
♪A thunderclap rolls♪
♪Stirring up old dreams again♪
♪Thoughts linger on the warmth
of the past♪
♪The sincerity of the past♪
♪Fireworks fall like rain♪
♪But soon they cool♪
♪I watch as you pass by♪
♪Not daring to ask♪
♪Like the moon, waxing and waning♪
♪How could it ask more?♪
♪You and I are like a small boat
on the river♪
♪Rising and falling with the waves♪
♪Speaking of love and hate♪
♪How can I distinguish them?♪
♪Longing for fate, praying sincerely♪
♪Yet the world does not acknowledge it♪
♪The night grows deep♪
♪Old dreams are stirred again♪
♪Yet the old people
are still within them♪
♪Why do they remain silent?♪
♪Fireworks fall like rain♪
♪But soon they cool♪
♪I look, adding a few more strokes
to the word "love"♪
♪A new year's ring♪
♪The cicada's cry is close
and autumn leaves are near♪
♪Yet it's hard to recognize each other♪
♪I sigh, why are you and I♪
♪Rising and falling,
drifting in this way?♪