[Dawn is Breaking]
[Adapted from Fanqie Novel]
["After the Obsessed State Preceptor's Takeover"]
[Episode 16]
[Cutting out The Baby]
♪The autumn wind stirs a ripple♪
♪Before the blossoms
could scent the earth♪
♪Snow falls on my hair,
I sing with no one to play the lute♪
♪Recalling the past
without a single note to mark♪
♪Sighing for the fate of all beings♪
♪Unable to seek the bond we once shared♪
Consort Li.
♪Leaving me with scars♪
♪Love and hate became fleeting years,
turning us into old acquaintances♪
♪The candlelight disturbs♪
♪Whispers by the western window
seem to lock a deep night♪
♪A dream too real♪
♪So I follow it all the way♪
♪Why does spring rush by?
The silent rain drenches a pair♪
♪Time flows by, not willing♪
♪Leaving traces of sorrow♪
♪The autumn wind stirs a ripple♪
♪Before the blossoms
could scent the earth♪
♪Snow falls on my hair,
I sing with no one to play the lute♪
♪Recalling the past
without a single note to mark♪
♪Sighing for the fate of all beings♪
♪Unable to seek the bond we once shared♪
♪How deep was the love♪
♪Leaving me with scars♪
♪Love and hate became fleeting years,
turning us into old acquaintances♪
♪The candlelight disturbs♪
♪Whispers by the western window
seem to lock a deep night♪
♪A dream too real♪
[Xie Tinghan and Jiang Mingyue
are to be wed in a harmonious union.]
[The wedding is scheduled
for the 3rd of the 11th lunar month.]
[We present a dowry of gold, jewels,
silk and dresses for you.]
[Marriage Proposal]
♪How deep was the love♪
♪Leaving me with scars♪
♪Love and hate became fleeting years,
turning us into old acquaintances♪
♪The candlelight disturbs♪
♪Whispers by the western window
seem to lock a deep night♪
♪A dream too real♪
♪So I follow it all the way♪
♪Why does spring rush by?
The silent rain drenches a pair♪
♪Time flows by, not willing♪
♪Leaving traces of sorrow♪
♪When the dream ends,
we finally become old acquaintances♪
My dear,
are you embroidering a fishing net?
Our family has been generals
for three generations.
It's normal I'm not good
at needlework, right?
Why are you doing it then?
Do you not have enough garments?
Spring is coming soon.
Next month is your birthday,
so I wanted to make you a spring outfit.
Let me do it.
Here, give it to me.
You can do this too?
I've been wandering since I was a child,
unlike someone
who can't do many things.
How did she even survive?
Are you mocking me?
How dare I?
Now that we're married,
you don't need to wander anymore.
I'll be with you through the seasons.
Alright.
My dear,
you were supposed to give me
a spring outfit.
Now I'm helping you make one.
How about this?
I'll teach you.
I'm so clumsy. I probably won't learn.
My dear, since you're so capable,
why don't you make me a spring outfit?
I'll choose the fabric.
I'll make you a spring outfit
every year from now on.
Miss!
Miss, bad news!
What is it?
News from the palace,
Miss Jiang...
Consort Li...
What about Yue?
Tell me quickly!
She's dead,
perished in a fire
with her baby.
That's impossible.
I'll enter the palace right now.
There's no need to go.
Come with me.
Yin,
you need to prepare yourself.
She may not hold on much longer.
What happened to Yue?
Tell me now!
The Moon Tower mysteriously caught fire.
Miss Jiang was so terrified
that she almost gave birth prematurely.
The poison in the baby
has invaded her body.
How did Yue's child
get poisoned?
The Emperor consumed too many elixirs
over the years and it accumulated.
Yin,
I'm sorry.
After Li Chi's fierce attack
on the Moon Pavilion,
the survivors all went into hiding,
so news from the palace
couldn't get out.
Does my brother know?
Yes.
Xiao Zhi went to find him.
Alright, I understand.
Yue.
Yin,
I'm sorry.
I've dragged you all down.
I'm the one who should apologize.
I shouldn't have listened to you
when you said those things.
I should've knocked you out
and taken you away.
I shouldn't have left you in the palace.
Those words I said that day
hurt you, didn't they?
Yin,
in fact,
there's something I've never told you.
Sometimes,
I'm really envious of you.
Envious that you have
the love of your parents
and the protection of your brother,
so you can be fearless.
Yue,
you don't have to be afraid
of anything either.
I promise,
from now on,
I won't let anyone bully you.
You need to live on.
Do you hear me?
You'll be fine, do you know that?
You've already done
enough for me.
It's my own fault for being too weak.
I thought
as long as...
as long as I
obeyed
and submitted,
they'd leave me alone.
I was wrong.
The more I submitted,
the more they become unscrupulous.
Yue.
Yue, does it hurt?
I've lived my life
cautiously,
never doing anything wrong.
And yet
I've ended up like this.
This is not the end.
Yue, listen to me.
My brother is on his way.
Just wait for him.
Wait for him.
Ms. Ruolan.
Ms. Ruolan,
I beg you, please help her!
Yin.
She's only 19.
Her life is just beginning.
Ms. Ruolan, I beg you, please help her!
The poison of Withering Summer
has already invaded her.
The child may survive,
but this girl's life is beyond saving.
Yue.
There'll be a cure, Yue.
Believe me.
There'll be a way to save both of you.
Do you remember?
We made a promise.
We'll go to Youzhou
to ride horses
and see the moon beyond the Great Wall.
Promise me,
don't die!
Na Jinci, please save her.
I beg you, save her!
Think of something.
Save her!
Yin,
calm down and listen to me.
I can use my inner strength
to keep her alive for a while
so that the baby can be delivered.
But the pain for her
will be extreme.
Yin.
Yin,
from childhood,
you've always protected me
and cared for me.
I've never lived for myself.
But now I have this child.
He's the continuation of my life.
Protect him for me.
Alright.
Help me.
Alright, Yue.
I promise you, Yue.
Yin.
Let me do it.
Yue,
Yue, I'm here.
Yue.
I'm here.
♪The wind under the eaves♪
I need to undo Miss Jiang's clothing.
Preceptor, please step aside.
♪The candle flame flickers
as I sleep soundly♪
♪The night is at its peak♪
Madam Xie, there's only a little time.
You must help Miss Jiang
deliver the baby.
How can Yue deliver the baby
in this state?
♪The sincerity of the past♪
Yin,
help me.
Help me.
I'll perform acupuncture
to relieve the pain.
You must extract the child.
Extract the child?
Do it!
♪Rising and falling with the waves♪
Help me!
There's no other way.
The more you delay,
the more she'll suffer.
♪Speaking of love and hate♪
I'm sorry.
♪Longing for fate, praying sincerely♪
♪Yet the world does not acknowledge it♪
♪The night grows deep♪
♪Old dreams are stirred again♪
♪The wind under the eaves♪
♪Gently taps on the wooden door♪
♪The candle flame flickers
as I sleep soundly♪
♪The night is at its peak♪
♪A thunderclap rolls♪
♪Stirring up old dreams again♪
♪Thoughts linger
on the warmth of the past♪
♪The sincerity of the past♪
♪Fireworks fall like rain♪
♪But soon they cool♪
♪I watch as you pass by♪
♪Not daring to ask♪
♪Like the moon, waxing and waning♪
♪How could it ask more?♪
♪You and I are like a small boat
on the river♪
♪Rising and falling with the waves♪
♪Speaking of love and hate♪
♪How can I distinguish them?♪
♪Longing for fate, praying sincerely♪
♪Yet the world does not acknowledge it♪
♪The night grows deep♪
♪Old dreams are stirred again♪
♪Yet the previous ones
are still within them♪
♪Why do they remain silent?♪
♪Fireworks fall like rain♪
♪But soon they cool♪
♪I look, adding a few more strokes
to the word "love"♪
♪A new year's ring♪
♪The cicada's cry is close,
autumn leaves are near♪
♪Yet it's hard to recognize each other♪
♪I sigh, why are you and I♪
♪Rising and falling,
drifting in this way?♪