[Dawn is Breaking]
[Adapted from Fanqie Novel]
["After the Obsessed State Preceptor's Takeover"]
[Episode 13]
[The Bait is Taken]
Madam Xie has been taken away.
I'm so sorry.
Punish me.
Who did it?
I took the initiative
to order the Jade Pavilion
to act in full force.
It's been confirmed
the Crown Prince abducted Madam Xie.
He's set up a trap
at the Crown Prince Mansion,
likely intending
to lure us in.
It's the Jade Pavilion's signal.
It's a trap.
Yin,
you're awake.
I never thought you'd stoop so low
by using an innocent beggar.
In strategy, there's no right or wrong,
only winning or losing.
This time,
you've lost.
You killed her?
You wouldn't spare a child?
She was just a beggar.
For a beggar to be killed
by the Crown Prince,
it's a fortune for her.
Crown Prince?
Are you worthy of the worship
and the position of the Crown Prince?
You're not even fit to be a human.
You're nothing but an animal!
Yin, you've changed for the worse.
I don't like you
like this.
Once you return to the Eastern Palace,
you must adhere to proper conduct.
You're dreaming.
What are you trying to do?
Of course,
to rekindle our old relationship
and rescue you
from Na Jinci.
You bit me!
You poisoned me.
It's my own fault for being blind
and deceived by a lunatic for so long.
Lunatic?
When it comes to that,
no one surpasses the Preceptor husband
of yours, Na Jinci.
Oh, right,
he's a true illegitimate child
and a monster plagued by poison.
Shut up!
What's wrong?
Just a few words about him
and you're already hurting?
Have you forgotten?
You and I were childhood sweethearts,
perfectly matched.
If not for him stealing you away,
we wouldn't have ended up like this.
We could've been happy together.
Happy together?
Your so-called happiness
is controlling me with poison,
making me live
in your lies and manipulation.
Let me tell you.
Even without him,
one day I'd have discovered the truth
and exposed your true nature!
Hahaha!
True nature?
What true nature?
Everything I did was for you.
Yin,
is it wrong for me to love you?
I want to be with you forever
and make you mine.
Is it wrong?
Forget it.
You're hoping Na Jinci will come
to save you, aren't you?
Good.
I'm waiting for him too.
When he arrives,
I'll make him watch as you and I
be happy together.
Then,
you'll kill him with your own hands.
Impossible!
What are you doing?
What are you planning to do?
Shh.
Don't be afraid, Yin.
Soon, we can
start anew.
Yin, you're awake.
You were scared just now, weren't you?
Where am I?
Who are you?
You...
You don't remember?
It's me, your Crown Prince.
Crown Prince?
It's all that villain
Dongfang Zui's fault!
Dongfang Zui?
You're the beloved daughter of Duke Xie.
We grew up together
as childhood sweethearts.
We got engaged at 15
and the seventh lunar month this year,
we had our wedding at the Yu Temple
on Liangwei Mountain.
I do have some memory of that.
So after the wedding, I've been living
in the Crown Prince's mansion?
Later,
you were kidnapped by a villain
named Dongfang Zui.
For six months,
I tried every possible way
and only last night did I
get the chance to rescue you.
That villain must have mistreated you,
causing you so much distress
that you lost your memory.
I'm the daughter of a duke
and you're the Crown Prince.
How could that villain
have kidnapped me?
That villain is ambitious.
Hiding behind the title of Preceptor,
he bullied the weak
and flattered the powerful
to deceive His Majesty.
He used the excuse of divine will
to forcibly marry you.
A few days ago,
you sought my help to escape
and jumped into a lake
in the deep of autumn.
I'm sorry,
but I can't remember anything.
It's alright.
Yin,
as long as you're still here,
as long as we're together,
it's OK if the past memories
are forgotten.
I'll do it myself.
[Crown Prince Mansion]
Yin,
you've become much colder towards me.
I'm sorry, Your Highness.
My memory hasn't fully returned,
so I'm not quite used to this.
You need to get used to it quickly.
You used to
call me Crown Prince.
What's that smell?
It might be the scent of plum blossoms.
I'm your husband.
You're the only Crown Princess
I'll ever have.
For this life and the next,
I'll cherish you,
love you
and protect you with all my heart.
Only I
can give you such happiness.
But as you said,
I was already promised to that villain.
How can I still be the Crown Princess?
I have sworn
in this life,
you'll be my only wife.
But...
But?
But you...
you were defiled by that villain.
You were so heartbroken,
washing your face with tears every day
and waiting for me to rescue you.
Yin,
I'm sorry.
I couldn't protect you.
I was defiled by the villain,
washing my face with tears every day
and waiting for you to save me?
I risked my life to save you,
but you...
but you refused to marry me
because you lost your virginity.
So, I had to let you stay
in the Crown Prince Mansion
as a concubine in name.
Yin,
don't worry.
I'll never despise you.
You shouldn't belittle yourself
because of this experience.
In my eyes,
even if the jade has a flaw,
it's still peerless in the world.
Don't be afraid,
Yin.
Try to accept me as you did before.
Love me.
Give me a child.
Become my rightful Crown Princess.
Assassin!
The bait is taken.
Who's there? Is that villain here?
Exactly.
If not him,
who would dare break into my mansion?
Don't be afraid, Yin.
I'm here.
I'll protect you.
If that villain humiliated me
in every possible way,
would I just sit there
crying every day
and waiting for someone to save me?
I'm too late.
He's coming for me.
Give me the dagger
so I can protect myself.
What nonsense!
You're a delicate girl.
Come on,
we'll fight our way out together.
You'll watch my back.
No way,
something's wrong.
My memory is gone,
but one's nature doesn't change.
If I truly loved the Crown Prince,
how could I be so caught up
in my virginity?
Kill him.
Show no mercy.
Let's go.
♪The wind under the eaves♪
♪Gently taps on the wooden door♪
♪The candle flame flickers
as I sleep soundly♪
♪The night is at its peak♪
♪A thunderclap rolls♪
♪Stirring up old dreams again♪
♪Thoughts linger
on the warmth of the past♪
♪The sincerity of the past♪
♪Fireworks fall like rain♪
♪But soon they cool♪
♪I watch as you pass by♪
♪Not daring to ask♪
♪Like the moon, waxing and waning♪
♪How could it ask more?♪
♪You and I are like a small boat
on the river♪
♪Rising and falling with the waves♪
♪Speaking of love and hate♪
♪How can I distinguish them?♪
♪Longing for fate, praying sincerely♪
♪Yet the world does not acknowledge it♪
♪The night grows deep♪
♪Old dreams are stirred again♪
♪Yet the previous ones
are still within them♪
♪Why do they remain silent?♪
♪Fireworks fall like rain♪
♪But soon they cool♪
♪I look, adding a few more strokes
to the word "love"♪
♪A new year's ring♪
♪The cicada's cry is close,
autumn leaves are near♪
♪Yet it's hard to recognize each other♪
♪I sigh, why are you and I♪
♪Rising and falling,
drifting in this way?♪