EPISODE 3
I wanted to come one last time
before they demolished this place.
Today's the day you and Mom died.
I'm sorry, Sang-yeon.
It took me…
fifteen years to come back here.
I'm sorry.
Look for a way to kill Bulgasal.
You'll recognize it. It's…
But Sang-yeon…
I don't remember what you said after that.
It must have been important.
Run.
This place is off-limits.
What are you doing here?
Right. I used to live here.
I heard it's being demolished,
so I stopped by.
Good night, then.
Can you show us your ID?
Pardon? Why do you want to see my ID?
We received a report
about a suspicious man here.
There was a theft case nearby too.
If you refuse, you will have
to accompany us to the station.
Sure.
"Park Hui-cheol." Born in…
In 1960?
I look younger than my age, right?
A lot of people tell me I look younger.
This is Patrol One.
Requesting a background check.
The name is Park Hui-cheol.
His date of birth is September 21, 1960.
His date of birth is…
I'm sorry. I mistook you for someone else.
Let's go.
To where?
Dogu-dong Intersection…
No. Wait.
Sir, drive me
to the front of Eunbaek Apartment.
To the front of Eunbaek Apartment?
Yes, but don't stop there.
Just keep driving.
There's something I want to check.
Where to now?
Dogu-dong Intersection…
Was it you?
The one who was here?
SI-HO
Hello?
Si-ho, where are you right now?
I just left work after my shift.
What is it?
Si-ho, can you hurry back home?
Something weird just happened to me.
What happened? Did you meet
weird people on the street again?
The ones who have been following you…
No. That's not it.
I think it was the guy from 15 years ago.
The power to break down a door…
It was the same as that night.
I think he was Bulgasal.
I haven't found a way to kill him yet.
Sang-un, let's talk about that
once I get home.
I need to take care of something.
What is it? What's wrong?
It's nothing serious.
Then come home now.
Si-ho, I want you to come home right now.
If he's really back,
we have to go somewhere else.
I can't come home tonight.
I'm having an important talk
with my boyfriend.
I'll call you later.
Make sure to lock up.
Hello?
Si-ho!
The person you are trying to reach--
I'm tired. And my feet hurt.
We have to hurry.
Where are we going?
Why do we have to leave home?
We can't live there anymore.
I miss Mom. And Sang-yeon too.
Where did they both go?
Mom and Sang-yeon…
We have to hurry. Let's go.
No, I'm not going!
Where did Mom and Sang-yeon go?
They're gone!
They're gone.
Mom and Sang-yeon aren't here anymore!
I brought some delicious apples
for you. Try some.
Gosh. Thank you.
They are my distant relatives.
Something happened, so I took them in.
Thank you for the apples.
-I hope you like them.
-Sure. Bye.
Si-ho.
You brought it, didn't you?
You brought that scary thing.
That's why Mom and Sang-yeon died.
No.
I didn't.
It's your fault.
It's all your fault!
Sang-yeon.
Why is he looking for me?
How can I kill Bulgasal?
What in the world…
is Bulgasal?
Hello, my good sir. You called again.
I haven't found the girl yet.
How many years has it been?
Isn't this your expertise?
Listen. I only have her photo and name.
That's all I have to go on with.
Right? This is tough for us too.
I went to the house she used to live in.
And someone had been there.
Gosh. Even so,
I doubt that it was Min Sang-un.
Get your men
to search the area just in case.
Well, to do that…
I'll need a bigger budget.
I'll give you the money, so just find her.
Really? Gosh, thank you…
Hello, you've reached
private investigator, Dachaja.
It's me.
-Did you find anything?
-Well…
It's not looking good.
We've been searching for two years but--
-I haven't even gone home for--
-Keep searching.
I will go after her.
And I will take revenge for my family.
Are you planning to find
the woman who will be reincarnated
as a human and kill her?
I will take her soul.
Just like she did to me.
I will turn her into Bulgasal
and put her away in a deep pit.
I will make her
live eternally as an immortal being
in darkness, despair, and solitude.
I will make her suffer
in pain for eternity.
That shall be my family's revenge.
And mine.
A young man with a dark hole.
He said he was after her soul.
That was when I realized
that I, alongside many others,
was after her soul.
I will not let you get away this time.
I will find you before those bastards do.
MAP
A STUDY ON SWORDS FROM JOSEON DYNASTY
Look for a way to kill Bulgasal.
How?
How do I look for it?
You'll recognize it. It's…
I need to go back
and put an end to this karma.
This is my final chance.
I need to find the sword
that can kill Bulgasal.
The same sword…
that killed me 600 years ago.
Where is it? Here.
MR. YOON, HANDLES ANTIQUE SWORDS
SAID HE WOULD CALL IF A SWORD CAME IN
The sword that can kill Bulgasal.
Sir.
Do I know you?
Goodness. You always seem
to know when to show up.
Sir, you received another sword
from the Joseon period, right?
Come on.
That's what you told me on the phone.
I didn't know I was talking to you.
Please, sir.
My goodness.
ENERGY DRINK
All right.
-Here.
-Gosh. Thank you.
You're not going to buy it,
but you always want to see
any new sword that comes in.
Exactly.
She's been checking swords
from every antique shop
in this alley for years.
I'm sorry.
But I really have to find something.
What is it?
A way to save my life.
I need that sword to save myself.
What? Goodness.
What a strange thing to say.
I just have a lot of interest
in ancient swords.
I bet you carried a sword
in your previous life.
-Right?
-Gosh. You're super smart.
I bet you're right. I must have wielded
my sword at bad guys in my previous life.
Goodness.
Look for a way to kill Bulgasal.
You'll recognize it.
No, it's not this one.
I don't know.
What is it? Is something wrong?
What? No.
Sir, please let me know
when you get another sword.
Gosh.
Thank you.
How on earth can I kill Bulgasal?
Your hands trembled
and you got goosebumps in the bus, right?
Yes. What was that about?
It means you recognize them as well.
You recognize those Monsters
from the past.
This won't be the last time you meet one.
Don't come after me.
-If you do--
-You.
How did you know I was watching you?
Can you sense people like me?
You can.
Come to think of it, you both knew
that I was watching you that day, right?
-What?
-Right?
Who are you?
How…
The smell of your soul.
Who are you?
You've been following me the whole time?
I've been looking for you
ever since we met that day
because I couldn't forget you.
Why are you Monsters
trying so hard to kill me?
Doesn't this get old for you?
Please.
Stop following me.
Trying to run away
from Bulgasal is tough already.
Hey.
You know,
I remember the smell of your soul.
You just wait. I'll find you again. Okay?
No.
You reincarnated Monsters
will never catch me.
I don't plan on dying
before I kill Bulgasal.
No, you'll die.
Many others are looking
for you besides me.
Is there a fan club I don't know about?
So where are they now?
Oh, my stomach.
Getting mixed up with
that weirdo is causing me trouble.
Hot! You startled me!
When did you get here?
My heart!
You get startled every single time.
Just give me what you found.
I asked you countless times
to let me know when you come.
You stink!
You should wash up. You reek of alcohol.
My nose is really sensitive.
Well, to get that information,
I had to drink with a cop all night.
I actually stopped by the sauna.
This is the suspect
of the missing person cases, right?
Yes. But…
I don't think he's one of the psychopaths
you're usually looking for.
He was a suspect
but was released recently.
He's the culprit.
He's the one
who killed those missing people.
How do you know something the cops don't?
It's not like you're a gifted shaman.
He's done it before.
He and the others were born to kill.
Hey.
Sir. I'm just really curious.
Why are you looking for these criminals?
Because…
we are looking for the same woman.
Hey.
Who are you?
It was you, wasn't it?
What?
A kid from my orphanage went missing.
I saw the kid get into a car,
and it had your plate number.
You took the kid, didn't you?
Right.
The cops told me something about that.
They said someone saw my plate number.
Was that you?
What did you do?
That poor kid has no parents
and was even bullied
at school because of that.
What's the problem then?
-What?
-That kid has no friends
or parents who would be worried.
So what's the problem?
The world will be fine without that kid.
No one is even looking for that brat.
Right?
Gosh.
You really are an asshole.
Right.
Did you come here alone?
You're one fearless kid.
I own this building.
No. I brought someone.
Hey! Over here!
I had to keep a low profile
because of the cops.
This all worked out.
What are you doing in my parking lot?
We need to talk. Get out of the car.
Are you a cop?
I already talked to them.
Well, I'm not a cop.
But I know that you killed
the missing people from this area
over the past few years.
Come on. What a day!
Who are you?
How did it feel when you killed that kid?
It was fun.
I see.
It was?
I'm just joking.
I was joking because
you were asking me a ridiculous question.
Right. I'm sure it was fun for you.
You were born to do that.
You just followed your instincts,
so it's not your fault.
It was wrong that you were born a human.
You were never human anyway.
What are you talking about?
You think I'm a joke? You crazy…
Have you seen this girl?
Did you kill her too?
Who…
are you?
What about her?
I don't know.
I don't know!
Where am I?
You may not remember me…
but we've met before.
A very long time ago.
Where did she go?
I killed her.
I've met people like you for so long
that I'm sick of you.
You Monsters from previous lives
were reincarnated as humans.
Yet, you still kill humans.
But all of you…
looked for this woman.
You were good at finding her.
I heard you could recognize
the smell of her soul.
But I, the owner of that soul,
cannot sense it.
It…
smells awful here.
It makes me sick.
You can smell it?
Was she here?
You…
You stabbed me again in the same spot.
Why are you doing this to me?
I didn't do anything to you.
This is the only thing I know how to do.
Kill Monsters.
What?
He's already back for the bowl? Come on.
-Hey.
-I think we can find her.
What?
Wait. Is that blood?
Oh, this? It's nothing.
No, that looks like something to me.
Gosh. What are you up to now?
Just a hobby.
What kind of hobby involves
blood splattering?
Wait. Did you go and see
the guy in the case file I gave you?
No, I didn't. I'm still looking for him.
Stop lying. I've been
a private investigator for 30 years.
All those bastards
I found for you went missing!
Really?
What a coincidence.
No, I can't do this anymore.
I'm done here.
This is way too dangerous.
You've been doing this for 15 years.
Don't make a scene now.
Yes. I've known you for 15 years.
But I know nothing about you.
Or what you do.
Besides, how did you make that much money?
I don't work now.
But I've done all kinds of things
in the past to make money.
How old are you?
How come you never age?
Exactly how old are you?
I never counted.
Any family members?
I had a family, but not anymore.
-Why not?
-Why do you care?
That's enough about me.
What? Gosh, this is so much.
I'm not the one you need to interrogate.
Focus on finding the girl.
She's at a nearby place
that uses a lot of detergent.
Detergent?
Dry cleaners, laundromats, hotels…
That's a big range.
Come on. Do your money's worth.
Other agencies have already started.
Gosh. You should have told me sooner.
By the way,
I have one more question
I've been wanting to ask.
Why have you been searching
for Min Sang-un for the past 15 years?
For atonement.
ATONEMENT: TO MAKE UP FOR ONE'S
SINS THROUGH OTHER MERITS
I've wronged my family.
And it's not 15 years.
It's been much longer than that.
Hey, where are you?
Why did you call?
I'm sure you know why I called.
I have a nice gig.
Do you want it, Detective Kwon?
No. I don't want it.
I'm on a stakeout, so I'm busy. Bye.
Goodness. All you ever do
is tail cheating couples.
You were a detective. How embarrassing.
It's so good.
These are the only requests I get.
So what?
-I love you.
-I love you too.
Gosh. Look at them having a blast.
How could they do that to their families?
It's because you're picky.
Take one of my cases.
I'll outsource it to you.
It pays very well.
I don't accept cases
from gangsters, drug dealers, or stalkers.
-You know, right?
-None of the above.
It's your specialty.
You just have to find someone.
-Get it!
-Yes!
-We got one!
ATTENTION: PLEASE KEEP NOISE TO A MINIMUM,
REFRAIN FROM EXCESSIVE DRINKING,
AND DO NOT DISTURB OTHERS.
Hey.
Come on. What are you doing?
Your feet stink. Put them back on!
My feet stink?
Come on.
I wore them for only three days.
So they still smell fresh.
INSTANT COFFEE
Can't you brew me real coffee?
I don't want chemicals in my coffee.
Are you kidding me?
As the kids these days say,
this is legit! Legit coffee!
Detective Kwon,
close down that small agency of yours.
Why don't you join me?
That sounds awful. Why would I do that?
And stop calling me Detective.
I quit years ago.
Right. Why did you quit?
It's so hard to become a cop these days.
I got kicked out
because of some case from 15 years ago.
What case?
Why do you want to know?
By the way, who do I need to find?
Well, you see…
This case is supposed to be top secret.
He's an old client of mine,
so I need to do it myself.
But you know about my health.
Gosh, you're dragging this out.
Just tell me already.
This photo…
What? Does she remind you of someone?
I think I might know her.
Do you remember the culprit's face?
Who is this girl?
This is an old photo.
You need to find a girl
who looks like the one in the photo.
Apparently, she looks exactly the same.
Who is the client?
That's confidential. Don't ask.
If he plans to hurt this girl…
Don't ask me that either. I don't know.
Seriously. Who is the client?
What's gotten into you today?
You never asked before.
I'll double your fee.
And I'll pay you under the table.
Can't you just tell me?
I'll close down my agency
and work here for a small salary.
Come on. I know you're lying. Forget it!
Tell me who the client is!
What's wrong with you?
Did you have too much to drink?
Call me if you remember anything.
Get well soon.
KWON HO-YEOL
Bulgasal.
What?
Bulgasal. Bulgasal is coming.
Where did you hear that?
Who told you that?
What's wrong, Ho-yeol?
He's coming to kill us.
He's still looking for me.
Are you sure it was Bulgasal?
Are you certain?
Ho-yeol.
Wake up.
Please wake up.
Bulgasal is here.
Bulgasal is coming.
Bulgasal is…
"Bulgasal is coming."
"Bulgasal is…"
WOO PHARMACY
Goodness, so many bandages…
Are you okay?
Shouldn't you go to a hospital?
I'm all right. This is nothing new to me.
FROM SEONGJIN POLICE STATION
NOTICE OF VIOLATION
By the way,
why have you been searching
for Min Sang-un for the past 15 years?
For atonement.
I've wronged my family.
What's this?
Hey.
Wake up.
Wake up!
Step back.
Stay away, you murderer!
It just healed, you punk.
You stabbed me in the same spot.
What…
Did I just stab you?
I thought you were that murderer. Oh, no.
What do I do?
Where are you going?
I'll call 911 right now. My phone…
Forget it. You don't need to call.
How could I not?
Where's my phone?
Sir.
Let me borrow your cell phone.
What are you doing?
Get away from me.
Here it is.
You're getting a call.
-Where's my phone?
-What is it?
You asked me to look into places
that use a lot of detergent.
So I sent someone
to detergent factories and to hotels.
But the thing is…
it will take
about three to four days to check.
No, that's too long.
We need to find her
before she finds out and runs.
Mister, you don't have time
to talk on the phone right now.
Look at all that blood.
Be quiet. Go away!
Call 911.
We have to call 911.
What is that? Are you in trouble?
No, I picked up a weird kid.
Me? Are you talking about me?
We have to call 911 right now.
You don't have time for this.
Tell me where to look. I'll go.
Text me the address.
What? Mister.
Don't tell me
you're going to drive in that state.
You could die.
I told you to forget it.
Don't come here again
unless you want to die.
What?
What…
MR. GU
What is it now? Just text me the address.
We'll look into the detergent factories.
But there are laundry plants
in the suburbs.
Do you want to check them out?
Where are they?
I'll text you the addresses.
The person you are trying
to reach is unavailable--
Hyeon-ju.
Hyeon-ju!
What's on your mind today?
You totally spaced out.
Oh, my younger sister
isn't answering her phone.
She hasn't been picking up
after meeting her boyfriend.
That's because she's a young girl in love!
My daughter won't answer my calls
when she's with her boyfriend.
-Gosh, give me that. I'll do it.
-What?
I'm fine.
-You have the late shift tonight, right?
-What?
How about I do it?
Can you?
If the boss finds out,
we'll get an earful.
The boss told us to quit
if we're not well.
Gosh. Then we don't have to tell.
It'll be our secret.
You should go home and rest up.
Gosh, I feel awful.
You help me out every time.
You're so considerate
for a girl of your age.
Gosh. My kids don't know
that I work my ass off for them.
They get so mad whenever I nag them a bit.
We must have been enemies
in our past lives.
I envy you.
What? What do you envy?
Bickering with your family like that.
Goodness, that's an odd reason to envy me.
You don't bicker with your family?
I can't fight with my sister.
I wronged her a lot.
-Hold on.
-Sure.
SI-HO
-Hello?
Hey, Si-ho.
Why didn't you answer my calls?
Well, I just had something to sort out.
Where are you?
Gosh, Si-ho. I was worried.
I'm at the laundry plant.
SPOTLESS LAUNDRY PLANT
I've never seen her.
She doesn't work here.
There's another
laundry plant nearby, right?
There's one beyond that vacant lot.
It's over that way.
There's something I need to tell you.
Well, I…
Hello? Sang-un?
Are you okay?
Is something wrong?
What? No.
I just got a weird feeling.
Are you there, Sang-un?
-Yes.
-Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I didn't get much sleep
so I'm feeling kind of down.
So you have something to say?
No. I'll tell you when I see you later.
I'm working late today.
I'll be home pretty late.
I know. I'll hang up now.
Okay. See you later.
Are you going home now?
Hey. Are you sure you'll be okay?
Can you stay here alone?
You bet I can. Go home now.
Thanks. Hold on a second.
Hey, it's me.
Yes, I'm on my way home.
What? You're going to wait
for me at the bus stop?
Gosh, you don't have to.
So much dust.
Who are you? I didn't hear you come in.
I just knocked.
I guess you didn't hear it.
I just wanted to ask you something.
Is there anyone who resembles her
among your employees?
I asked who you are.
I'm from an errand service center.
I got a request to find her.
I see. Is that an old photo?
I see. Yes, it's her. This is Hyeon-ju.
Does she work here?
But why are you looking for her?
She caused trouble, didn't she?
Why do you ask that?
I knew something was off
the moment I saw her.
She didn't want to sign a contract.
She just wanted to work.
I knew it. This girl…
Is she still at the plant?
No, she went home. It's late already.
What? She's working outside?
Hey! Why are you doing that outside?
Stop that. Finish the rest inside! Okay?
Who's that?
Her name is Hong Ji-suk.
She's working late tonight.
Gosh. She's always complaining
that she's not well but I can't fire her.
If you want to see Hyeon-ju,
come back tomorrow.
Can I get her address?
I can't just give out addresses
to strangers.
Wait. Let's see…
I texted you an address.
It might be Min Sang-un's home address,
so go and check now.
What? You found out where she works?
Did you see her?
Not yet. That's why I'm asking you
to go check the address.
Do it now.
It might be a fake one.
SANGYONG LAUNDRY
He should buy us a new one.
Thank you.
Thank you!
You're super strong, mister.
Two men struggle to lift that.
Thank you.
Wait.
Here. This is the only thing
I can offer you.
-Take one, please.
-I'm good.
Come on. Don't turn it down.
Take one. Please?
Wait. Are you hurt?
-It's nothing.
-No, that looks serious.
You should go to a hospital.
Should I call the boss?
-You seemed to know--
-No.
I'll take care of it.
Did you check?
There's no house there. It's an empty lot.
That was quick. You're already there?
No. I looked it up on a map online.
I'm using a satellite map.
I can check out any address
with just a few clicks on my computer.
Why would I waste gas on that?
No. I told you to check it in person.
I'm not an old dog
who can't learn new tricks!
Forget it. I'll go myself.
Come on. Don't turn it down.
Take one. Please?
SANGYONG LAUNDRY
I told you I'd find you again!
Listen carefully. You have to live.
Live in hiding, and don't trust anyone.
And look for a way to kill Bulgasal.
Hey.
How could this be?
Who the hell are you?
The smell of your soul…
It makes me sick.
The smell of your soul
makes me sick!
No. Don't go after him.
It's dangerous.
Are you all right?
You have a cut on your face.
Did he just do that to you?
Finally.
I finally found you.
Oh, no.
Shouldn't you go to a hospital?
I have spent a very long time
looking for you.
I desperately prayed
that we would meet again.
Well, thank you for helping me.
You helped me again.
I have never once forgotten
about taking revenge for my family
and the grudge I've held.
You have a cut on your face.
What did you just show me?
What exactly
are you?
Sang-un?
Is that you, Sang-un?
Who are you?
Are you okay?
Why are you here?
What's going on?
It is your fault.
Father!
You will cross paths one way or another.
Why did it have to be…
Either as enemies or as friends.
One of them has already found her.
The guy who lives here is really powerful.
Her soul will be ours!
Was he a Monster as well?
You're the one
who killed her family, aren't you?
Does that mean I'm not the only Bulgasal?
Subtitle translation by: Won-hyang Son