EPISODE 15
What is it? Are you still sad?
That we're leaving again
when we just came back?
A bit.
But it's okay
because we're together again.
I'll go to the hiding place
where Si-ho and I used to live.
No, not there.
Let's go back to the house
in the mountains.
That place is still safe.
And there's somewhere we need to go.
Do-yun.
-What are you doing?
-What?
Oh, these are Ms. Lee's clothes.
She must have left them here.
When she nagged us to make sure
we didn't leave anything behind.
Goodness.
Give them to me. I'll hold onto them.
Okay.
Do-yun, let's keep our chin up.
We have to stay on our toes now.
It's not the time to give up
and mope around.
What do you mean?
To be honest, I don't know what Hwal
and Sang-un are going to do.
I'm afraid they might go after Ok Eul-tae
because of what happened to Ms. Lee.
You still can't see with this eye?
No.
-It's not healing as fast as I thought.
-It's okay.
But I told the three of you to leave.
Why did you come back?
You could have just left me behind.
I told you.
I just couldn't leave you there.
I couldn't leave you on your own.
Even after hearing
that I asked Ok Eul-tae
to turn me into Bulgasal?
Do you think Ok Eul-tae is lying?
No.
I know it's true.
When a part of my memory came back,
I saw you and Ok Eul-tae together.
You looked like friends
rather than enemies.
But you still chose to stay by me?
As I told you before,
that doesn't matter now.
Any other memories?
I didn't have any flashbacks after that.
I think it was just temporary.
All done.
But didn't you say we had somewhere to go?
It's that mountain.
What happened there?
That's where the villagers believed
Bulgasal lived 600 years ago.
It all began on that mountain.
It's where I was born
and where I met you.
It's where my family died
and where I…
became Bulgasal.
I wanted to let you know
and wanted to come here one last time.
"One last time"?
Don't say things like that.
It will be.
Don't stop me anymore.
It's what Kim Hwa-yeon
and your twin sister wanted.
For Ok Eul-tae and I,
both Bulgasals, to die.
Wait. Then you brought me here
because you wanted me
to get my memories back
by looking at that mountain?
So that I would want you
and Ok Eul-tae to die together?
You once asked me why I liked you.
Other than my family,
I've never trusted or been worried
about someone the way I have with you.
So I thought I liked you.
But I was wrong.
What I feel right now goes beyond that.
There's something more.
What do you mean?
I don't think I can handle
not having you by my side.
If you're not there,
it'll feel as if half of me is gone.
And that terrifies me.
So I need to know why.
I know something happened between us
even before 600 years ago.
I can't let you die
before I find out what happened.
And…
you can't lose them again.
What are you talking about?
You called Si-ho Dan Sol.
And you always called Si-ho
and Do-yun your family.
They were…
your family in their past lives, right?
Yes. They were my family
who died 600 years ago because of me.
And you're still going to die?
When your family is right here?
That's all the more reason
why Ok Eul-tae and I must die.
Because I don't want to lose them again.
I don't want to live
in guilt or regret anymore.
After I die…
please look after my family.
You didn't tell us you'd go out.
We were just talking.
Is everything put away?
Yes. It didn't take that long.
Let's eat. We haven't had anything.
We only have instant noodles.
Sit with us, Hwal.
No, I'm good.
Please join us.
Sit with Si-ho and Do-yun.
Go ahead.
The noodles are going to get soggy.
Okay.
What?
They aren't soggy at all. Or even cooked.
Really?
Maybe I didn't cook them enough.
Sorry. I was distracted by my thoughts.
Seriously? You told me
to stay on my toes earlier.
Stay on your toes? What do you mean?
Oh, that? It's nothing.
But what about Detective Kwon?
Did he call you?
He should know we're here.
Oh, I called him earlier.
But he didn't pick up. I'll try again.
No, go ahead and eat. I'll call him.
TRUSTWORTHY POLICE, SAFE NATION
DAN HWAL
I'm not the one
who killed your father and your sister.
It was Hwal,
the man that's been
by your side all this time.
What are you doing here?
You bastard.
Are you really working for Ok Eul-tae?
Remember where we are.
People are watching.
So you care about what they think,
but not your conscience?
-Do you know what he's capable of?
-I do! That's why…
That's why I'm cooperating.
If I don't, he'll kill me right away.
It's better to work for him
and further my career at least.
You bastard.
Where's Ok Eul-tae?
Why do you ask? So you can go to him?
Do you have a death wish?
Get rid of Hwal or whatever his name was.
He's your enemy.
I'll take care of him myself.
-Tell me where Ok Eul-tae is.
-I can't tell you.
It will put my family in danger too.
Bye.
Hwal, we bought everything
they wanted, right?
Yes.
Give them to me.
Your wound hasn't healed yet.
Come on!
Don't you know
teenagers recover super fast?
Hey.
Hwal, can we stop by
that place before we go back?
-Where?
-There.
GALAXY PHOTO STUDIO
We have to wait for a bit.
What photo are you printing?
Oh, it's nothing much.
This one.
-Let's take a photo.
-A photo?
-A photo? Yes.
-Let's do that.
Sure. We never took a photo together.
Right.
-Okay.
-Everyone, look over here.
One, two, three!
Hwal, come on. Show us a smile.
-Okay.
-Goodness.
One, two, three.
Let's take one more. One, two, three.
That's nice.
I just wanted to print one out.
And I thought about printing
this one too, but I didn't.
Goodness. I'm so out of it today.
I forgot to ask how big
you wanted your photo to be.
What size do you want?
-The size?
-Yes.
Damn it.
I'm not sure.
The standard size will do.
Then I'll make it
a four-by-six-inch print. Okay?
By the way, how long
have you been living here?
What?
I was born and raised here.
Most of the residents here
have been here since birth.
But why do you ask?
-It's nothing.
-I see. Hold on.
Goodness. Where are you going?
Where have you been?
-I was looking for you to give you this.
-You shouldn't have.
-Don't worry about it.
-Thank you.
You called it here, didn't you?
It is your fault!
My father is dead because of you!
You're so pretty!
How does she get prettier by the day?
-I have no idea.
-I'm glad you don't take after your dad.
Hey, move.
Bulgasal came here for him.
He is going to get us all killed!
-We must kill him to save ourselves.
-Kill him.
What is it, Hwal? Do you know them?
Yes, I knew them
a long time ago in their past lives.
Gosh, really?
Awesome.
They still live here.
I guess people who cross paths once
continue to meet each other.
How pretty.
Then…
your family might be
somewhere together too.
Yes.
Were you close with those people?
No.
I used to hate them.
But if I think back on it now,
they were hurt because of my curse.
I'm the one to blame.
Wait up.
-What are you doing? Come on.
-Come on. Wait for me.
-What do you want to do?
-What are we doing?
-Hey. I found a place.
-What is it?
Let's go to the Internet cafe. Look.
-You want to go now?
-Let's go now.
-Let's play League of Legends.
-Okay.
-Let's go now.
Let's play for three hours.
Do you want to go back to school?
Well…
going to school was never my thing.
Your thing? Come on.
Go back to school once this is over.
-You should be studying.
-Fine.
Then can I commute to school
from your house?
I was wondering
if I could just live with you.
Never mind. I wasn't being serious.
No.
We should live together.
What? Really? You can't take it back.
Then what about Si-ho and Sang-un?
Oh, right.
Can Detective Kwon live with us too?
The more the merrier. Right?
You promised.
Si-ho!
Why did you buy so much stuff?
Give me some of that.
It's okay.
No way. How can we ask
a pregnant woman to carry bags?
-Give me that.
-I said I got it.
-Give it to me.
-I got it.
-Come on. Seriously?
-Gosh. Hey!
I said I got it!
-You could have given it to me. Oh, no.
-Gosh.
How are we going to eat this?
I'll eat them all.
And stop nagging too. Okay?
Let's head inside.
After I die, please look after my family.
What? How did you find me?
What are you doing here
on the street like a homeless man?
Let's talk. I looked for you all night.
What are you doing?
I thought you didn't drink.
The mayor has been missing
for several days.
I know. I saw it on the news.
What about that?
He's the one who told Captain Seo
to go to Hwal's house that day.
It seems he's been working for Ok Eul-tae.
Ok Eul-tae probably used him,
and something must have gone wrong.
So? What do you want from me?
Here.
What's this?
-This is--
-If I tell you where Ok Eul-tae is,
you can get rid of him, right?
I don't want to go missing like the mayor
after being used by Ok Eul-tae.
Are you sure about this?
I can't go with you.
So giving that to you is all I can do.
You know I'm a coward.
I have a young daughter too.
So that's all I can do for you.
Where is Ok Eul-tae?
We're almost there.
I'm not remembering anything.
I figured.
You didn't remember anything
at Kim Hwa-yeon's house either.
But that doesn't matter.
We didn't come here to help me remember.
We didn't?
We're here to end things where they began.
You'll become human again
and I'll become Bulgasal.
We should go back to our rightful places.
So you can die with Ok Eul-tae
in place of me when we do?
I'm not doing it for you.
I should have done this from the start.
I used to be Bulgasal,
so it's only fitting that I end this.
So you should go back to your family.
Don't think about dumping them onto me.
You were human and should have
never come in between Ok Eul-tae and me.
You used to be human,
so you can never beat Ok Eul-tae.
So let's go back to how things used to be.
Forget it. I told you
we aren't doing things your way.
Let's go back.
No.
You won't have a choice.
What are you doing?
If I stab my neck right now,
I'll just die.
To save me, you'll have to take my soul
and turn me into Bulgasal.
Hwal.
Thank you for everything.
Who said you could die?
You want to become Bulgasal?
Do you know what it's like?
I do. I watched you by your side
more closely than anyone.
I will become Bulgasal
and die with Ok Eul-tae.
It's not your problem now.
You've done enough by saving my life.
I can't let you go. I can't.
I can't do that.
For all my life I only thought about you.
You saved me from
the villagers when I was a kid.
I was sorry that you died for me,
so I only thought about you.
And because I hated you
for killing my family
and taking my soul,
I thought about you
and looked for you for 600 years.
Now that I know the truth,
I have no one to get revenge on or resent.
And I have no reason
to protect or kill anyone.
I could have moved on with my life.
But I lived with only thoughts of you.
So I can't let you go.
I can't let you die with Ok Eul-tae.
You told me that you didn't want me to die
because it would feel like
losing half of yourself.
But it's different for me.
It's not just half,
but all of me that will feel lost.
Because my whole life was
about finding you.
Sang-un.
What happened?
What did you guys do this time?
Hwal.
-I did it to myself.
-Why?
I wanted to give back his soul
and become Bulgasal.
Don't tell me
you were going to fight Ok Eul-tae
and sacrifice your life.
No. That will never happen.
I'll kill Ok Eul-tae myself.
Then you'll die too.
You said we'd be together yesterday.
You promised.
Were you secretly deciding
on who was going to die?
You still haven't learned
your lesson after Ms. Lee?
Have you thought about
the people who would be left behind?
Don't think about dying.
Come up with a way to live!
I can't believe you guys.
This is ridiculous.
You have to send Do-yun back to school
and be there when my baby comes.
Don't say that
you're sacrificing your life for us.
I don't want any of my family
to die anymore.
Please.
Can't we try to find a way
to survive this together?
Mr. Kwon.
What's going on here?
Did something happen?
It's nothing.
I found out where Ok Eul-tae is.
He's at the mountain where the well is?
Yes. Detective Ham told me.
It's a trap.
A trap?
He probably leaked it to you
on purpose through that detective.
I doubt that.
Detective Ham wants
to get away from Ok Eul-tae too.
Regardless of what his intention is,
Ok Eul-tae wants me to come to the well.
He wants to lock me up in the same well
I tried to put him in.
Si-ho says the food is ready.
Gosh. This looks great.
You two put a lot of effort into this.
I was hungover,
so I was craving some bean sprout soup.
I'll be giving birth in seven months.
Once I have the baby, I'll learn
butchery to run a shop like Ms. Lee.
I'll make deliveries to you once I do.
And my kids and I will guard the well
where Ok Eul-tae will be locked up.
I'll take over Ms. Lee's duties.
Wait, Si-ho.
It looks like you two came up
with a plan without us.
So I'm telling you what my plan is.
Here's what I need from you, Sang-un.
It's hard to raise a baby alone,
so I'll need your help.
I don't have a mother.
So you will assume that role.
You have to attend
my child's events at school.
Then I'll go back
to high school next year.
I'll commute from Hwal's place.
Teach me how to drive once I'm legal.
You promised me a car.
And we should go on a trip
once we lock up Ok Eul-tae.
And I also want…
Okay, I understand. You can stop now.
We'll find a way for both of us to live.
So you can stop now.
It's from Detective Ham.
I was an ex-cop,
so I'm the best shot here.
So I can shoot Ok Eul-tae from a distance.
I'll help too. Let me go with you.
No.
Right. You should stay with Si-ho.
Don't worry. It's three against one,
so we have a shot.
Outnumbering your enemy is
the best tactic in a fight.
How is it?
I can't taste anything.
You don't have to force yourself.
No.
It feels weird
not to eat anything at the table.
I want to practice.
We'll have a lot more
of these meals in the future now.
Let's eat.
We'll be back soon.
Yes, I know.
Of course, you will.
Detective Kwon.
Please protect them.
They're both willing
to give up their lives to protect us.
And you need to be careful too.
Don't lose your temper
and go after Ok Eul-tae recklessly.
Okay.
I'll do everything in my power
to send your sister back alive.
No! I want the three of you to come back!
And…
What else?
Buy hair dye on your way back.
You look old.
Once you come back, I'll dye your hair.
Gosh. Look at your beard.
Fine.
Why are you nagging me?
Bye.
Here.
Take it with you.
The weather is awfully nice.
And we'll have to fight Ok Eul-tae soon.
Right.
The three of us will be able
to go back home safely, right?
Yes. Everything will go as planned.
I'll make sure of it.
And…
once we lock Ok Eul-tae up in the well,
I have a favor to ask you.
I want to go back to being human.
Can I?
Of course.
What do you want to do
once you become human again?
I just want to live a normal life.
I want to pass the days
and die when I'm old.
Before my son.
You'll be able to.
Are you sure? You'll suffer a lot
when you become Bulgasal.
-You'll be lonely too.
-Well…
I'll be going back to who I was.
Living this life as a human brought me
a lot of pain and suffering too.
I lost my family
and was always chased
by Monsters and Ok Eul-tae.
But they won't chase me anymore.
And I'll be strong once I become Bulgasal.
So I like that I'll be able
to protect Si-ho and Do-yun.
I'll protect you
from reincarnated Monsters too.
And when I get sick of living as Bulgasal,
we can switch then.
You want to go down that path again
after everything we did?
Aren't you sick of it?
Not at all.
Bulgasal needs something
to look forward to.
In your next life, I'll come find you.
No matter how long it takes.
Let's not die.
I won't die. So you shouldn't die either.
Let's go back together.
We're okay.
Oh, right. Detective Kwon.
I'm reminding you just in case.
If Hwal's heart is wounded,
you must not shoot
Ok Eul-tae in the heart.
It might kill Hwal too.
Let me see if I understand correctly.
So to kill Bulgasal,
both Bulgasals' hearts must
be fatally wounded. Is that it?
Before one's heart recovers,
the other must be shot
in the heart, right?
Right. That's correct.
By the way,
you don't seem like your usual self.
I'm just nervous.
I have an important job today.
It's been my lifelong mission.
What should we do?
Should we all go in?
It's small and dark inside.
If we go in together,
Ok Eul-tae will kill us all.
I'll go in alone.
And then what?
I'll tire him out.
I was able to give him a heavy blow
because he let his guard down.
But not this time.
After he strikes me down,
he'll come out to kill you.
That's when you should shoot him.
If Ok Eul-tae is hurt and moves slowly,
I can get him from a distance.
If he's wounded and shot at the same time,
he won't be able to move.
And then…
it'll be your turn.
That's the poison Dueoksini had.
Okay. I'll handle this.
You have the most important job.
You have to shoot him and bring him down.
But don't shoot him in the heart.
Okay.
Don't worry.
I'll do everything to bring him down,
so that he doesn't come out here.
That's not my concern.
You just be careful.
Your family is waiting at home.
I've been waiting for you. Welcome.
The tables have turned.
Right. Last time,
you wanted to put me in the well.
But this time, I'll be putting you inside.
Let me see.
Have you changed since I last saw you?
You must have been very upset
that your family almost died.
You seem more okay than I thought.
I wished you would act more like Bulgasal.
I hoped you would kill
the detectives who took your family.
But killing one shaman wasn't enough.
You had an ill-fated relationship anyway.
You two never had any bond.
Your son, your wife,
and your father should have died.
No.
Killing her was enough.
I'm here, after all.
Right.
You did come even when you knew
you'd be buried here.
Did you want to fight me that badly?
No. I wanted to talk to you.
I'm sorry.
What?
Everything you said until now was true.
Sang-un has started
to regain her memories.
She told me that she saw you
saving me in your past life.
You killed my family 600 years ago
because you were trying
to turn me into Bulgasal again.
Everything you did was for me.
I shouldn't have blamed you.
Why all of a sudden?
Have you lost your mind?
Do you want a fresh start with me?
You think I will fall for your trick?
I'm not tricking you.
I'm saying I shouldn't have blamed
or resented you.
Everything was my fault.
You didn't do anything wrong.
I'm sorry that I couldn't do anything
when you tried to take care of me.
I'm sorry…
I couldn't fill that dark hole.
You're sorry?
Yes.
And…
I'm sorry that I plan
to lock you up in this well forever.
Even after everything…
Let's end this.
You said you were sorry.
You said…
you believed me now.
You said you knew
that I saved you 1,000 years ago.
But why are you doing this? Why?
Are you listening?
I'm exhausted.
I really need to end this fight with you.
Get locked up in this miserable well
and live an eternal life of suffering.
And regret…
that you betrayed me
and took Min Sang-un's side.
Before I put you away in the well,
I'll kill her in front of you.
What?
You should be
taking your revenge on Hwal, not me.
No!
What are you doing?
What are you doing, Detective Kwon?
I told you not to shoot him in the heart!
Bulgasal…
Both Bulgasals must die!
-What are you doing?
-Move.
Get off him.
-Why are you doing this?
-Both Bulgasals must die!
I will end it here.
Why? Why are you trying to kill Hwal too?
-Get off him!
-I can't!
He's not just Bulgasal.
It's Hwal.
He saved us multiple times.
If you don't, Dad will beat you again.
We should get rid of
Ok Eul-tae first. Please?
We have to poison him first.
Detective Kwon, you're bleeding…
How is he already…
He drank Hwal's blood,
so he must have recovered quickly.
I have to inject the poison right now!
I finally got you.
How long has it been
since I grabbed you like this?
Run away now!
Didn't you hear Hwal?
You have to live, Sang-un.
I'll go back with Hwal. So…
Detective Kwon!
That's enough.
You gave me no choice but to do this.
Run! Run away!
Hurry…
You won't be able to recover for years
if you don't drink human blood.
Then you won't be able to die or live.
Well, that doesn't matter now.
You can't go.
I won't let you go after Sang-un.
I won't let you.
Stop it, please.
What a miserable life you have.
You always end up
in the middle of all this.
Six hundred years ago,
a thousand years ago, and now too.
You still got dragged into all of this.
That's enough. Rest now.
And I'm always grateful to you.
Thank you
for bringing Hwal and Min Sang-un here.
I can't run away like this.
I won't leave alone.
I will finish Ok Eul-tae here.
And I'll go back home with you
and Detective Kwon.
We'll all go back to our family.
Let's go back home.
Hwal.
Hwal. Are you there?
A long time ago, when I was a kid,
Bulgasal killed my father.
My father was
a reincarnated Monster who killed people.
And my baby sister died
because of Bulgasal that day.
The day that she died…
has always stayed with me.
Even after all this time has gone by
and I've become an old man,
I could never let go of that day.
I couldn't
apologize enough to my sister.
The kid that day…
Why did you do that?
Why did you just leave us?
I get that you killed my father
because he was an evil man.
But you could have saved my sister.
You could have saved her.
You knew that we were hiding there.
Why didn't you help us?
I couldn't forgive you
when I found out you had left us there.
But I can't kill you now,
even if I waited
for this moment my whole life.
Because…
I've become attached to you.
I won't be able to face
my sister when I die.
Detective Kwon.
Hwal.
Were you awake?
Are you okay?
We don't have much time.
Ok Eul-tae went after Sang-un.
You have to save her.
I know that you don't drink human blood.
But can you make
an exception just this time?
No…
This is the only way
you can defeat Ok Eul-tae.
No, I can't.
I'll give you my blood.
No, not that.
It doesn't matter because I'll die anyway.
I'm sorry.
I ruined everything.
And…
tell Si-ho…
she can…
dye my hair some other time.
Detective Kwon.
Detective Kwon!
Father.
Let's go.
Come with me.
Be born as my real son in your next life.
I will protect you, my son.
Father.
The evil spirit
that fed off its father's blood
will rise up from the dark hole.
1,000 YEARS AGO
What have you done?
I despise you.
I truly despise you.
This will not kill me.
I will come back.
And when I do,
I will tear apart
the people who did this to me
and I will drink their blood.
And…
I will find you.
You…
are mine.
I shouldn't have
let you meet again in the first place.
I still have something left to do.
We will behead them.
And we will bury them deep underground
after chopping off their limbs.
I refuse to become human again.
I had no choice.
You'll go back to being
the Bulgasal you once were
and help me get rid of this dark hole.
Subtitle translation by: Won-hyang Son