I,
will personally send you off.
Don't be afraid, it'll be quick.
Finally dropped the act.
Why are you always here?
Come on, finish him.
Hurry, go!
No,
I... I...
Me.
Never thought my own uncle
would be so ruthless.
Sorry, Young Master Lin.
I was ignorant before.
It's fine, don't worry about it.
I'll protect you on this journey.
Night King City, I'm back!
By order of Lord Jun Wushang, the City Master,
the Aura Testing Array is now open.
Anyone with a score over one thousand
will receive ten thousand Luminous Pearls.
Over five thousand
will get twenty thousand Luminous Pearls.
Whoever can break Lord Jun Wushang's
record of one hundred thousand Aura Value
will be awarded a thousand acres of fertile land
and one hundred thousand Luminous Pearls.
I'll go.
Thank you for letting me try.
Impressive, really impressive!
Not bad!
Move aside, move aside!
Move!
Look at that.
So much aura!
Alright.
Amazing!
Impressive.
Really impressive.
S-sorry.
Sorry.
It's okay.
Did I say you could leave?
No.
Today,
I'll teach you a little lesson.
So you watch where you're going next time.
Beat him up!
Keep running!
You wanna run?
Try running!
Run, run!
Stop!
I told you to teach him a lesson.
Do you know what "little" means?
Brother,
Are you alright?
My men were a bit rough.
Here are some Luminous Pearls.
Take it as compensation for medical expenses.
Thank you.
In broad daylight,
you're robbing people?
Today,
I'm going to uphold justice!
Beat him up!
Hit him harder!
Grab it!
Do you know him?
He's memorable.
Why are you here?
Who is this kid?
Do you know him?
No, I don't.
Come with me.
Keep your hands to yourself.
Looking for trouble?
Young Master.
I'm in a good mood today.
I'll play with you.
How do you want to play?
See that Testing Array?
Go test yourself.
If your Aura Value is lower than mine,
you must die today.
What if it's higher than yours?
Then I'll
let you go.
It exploded!
The Aura Value is too low to register.
Hit him!
Stop!
Xiaoyue
Why are you here?
I'm just messing around with this bumpkin.
The testing array malfunctioned.
The previous test was invalid.
Xiaoyue
Why are you siding with this bumpkin?
You can call me Young Master.
Or Night Mingyue.
If you dare call me Xiaoyue again,
I'll break your legs.
There you go, getting angry again.
I'll treat you to a meal another day.
Aren't you leaving yet?
Get lost.
Thank you, Miss Ye, for helping me out.
Young master, do you know me?
We've met a few times, I think.
But you probably don't remember me.
May I ask your name, young master?
In a few days, your father Jun Wushang will come to see me.
You'll know then.
Let's go.
The array has never malfunctioned before.
Why did it happen this time?
This person's Aura Value
has already exceeded the array's limit.
What?
Send someone to follow him.
Find out his background.
Yes.
Sir,
Are you here to dine or stay?
To stay.
This way, please.
Come, eat, have some food.
What are you looking for?
A bunch of useless fools.
Please calm down, Young Master.
This person's identity
We've already investigated it.
His name is Lin Yue.
He came to Night King City this time
to attend the auction.
It seems
I'll have to handle this myself.
Sir, what would you like to eat?
What do you have here?
Here,
we have fine wine and great food, all for you.
Alright.
Please, have a seat.
Miss Ye, are you
trying to make friends with Young Master Lin?
If I remember correctly,
I don't think I've told you yet,
that my surname is Lin.
Young Master Lin's Aura Value test was impressive.
Of course I paid special attention.
Indeed.
I did look into some things.
So you had people follow me?
The good wine is here.
Young Master Lin,
I'll drink one as an apology.
I won't be drinking as punishment.
I was hoping
to have a few more drinks with you,
and talk about my troubles.
It seems
I won't get that chance.
You're the Young Master of Night King City,
with every luxury at your disposal.
What troubles could you possibly have?
In this vast Night King City,
I don't even have a friend to drink and confide in.
Tell me,
isn't that a kind of trouble?
Today,
I just wanted someone to drink with,
to ease my worries.
Young Master Lin,
surely you won't deny me this small favor,
will you?
Then I would be honored to oblige.
How are you so good at drinking?
Trying to get me drunk?
You're still too inexperienced.
Impossible.
Since I was a child,
I've treated wine like water.
I've never met a match.
You know,
I've been drinking for a hundred thousand years.
Who exactly are you?