ALL CHARACTERS
AND EVENTS ARE FICTITIOUS
CHILD ACTORS WERE FILMED
IN SAFE CONDITIONS
The guitar I mangled before.
I got you another just like it.
I know it'll be hard,
but could you forgive me, slowly?
I rearranged your room
the way I thought would work best.
I hope you'll like it.
I also received confirmation
from The Crown's agency.
The rest is up to you.
I'll do it.
I will.
No, I'll give it my all.
So that no one remembers
who I'm replacing.
I'll outshine Sa Gye.
I'll prove myself.
Good.
We're good now.
Everything is finally back
on the right track.
JO & JO ENTERTAINMENT: CEO JO
SANG-HEON ARTIST: SEO TAE-YANG
I truly welcome you as the new member
and leader of The Crown.
- Thank you.
- All in due time,
you'll greet the members
once the album is released.
It'll be kept under wraps from the media
for the time being.
That's fine by me.
Is the new song out today?
That's right.
It'll be dropped today exactly at noon.
That's in ten minutes.
It's good.
- The song's incredible.
- The Crown nailed it again.
It's amazing!
THE CROWN'S STILL GOING
FOR A REASON
I'll hold back my feelings to let you go
What the hell?
Bom, what's wrong?
- This…
- What?
This? What?
What is this song?
Oh, this song?
It's The Crown's new song
that dropped at noon today.
Isn't it great? I just love it.
You're still writing songs, right?
If you're selling,
I'm willing to offer top dollar.
What's with her?
…to let you go
But if that doesn't work
On the off chance
Say "I'll see you later"
Tell me it's never really bye, bye, bye
Can I ask how you came up with this song?
I felt down, so I went to the ocean.
I walked past a woman there,
and I saw myself in her.
Her eyes looked so sad,
but she kept her head held high,
making her seem even lonelier.
That's when the melody and the lyrics
of this song came to me.
Do you mind if I ask why you were sad?
Were you going through a breakup
with someone you loved?
Truth be told,
I had a crush on someone for a long time.
Someone as charming as you didn't have
your feelings reciprocated?
That's hard to believe.
It's that kind of bias
that makes me feel even lonelier.
But I'm over it now.
I feel like I've moved on
to a new chapter in my life.
I'm ready to experience
new love.
Why did The Crown release
your song as their own?
- Did you sell it to Ji-na?
- Of course, I didn't.
That song is about me and my mom.
Why would I sell it to anyone? Move.
I'll go with you.
Why? How is this your business?
I'm the only one
who knows the song is yours.
You can't do it alone. You don't know
what you're getting yourself into.
No one in there will believe you.
I don't trust you either.
So stay out of my business.
If you keep getting in my way,
I'll assume you sold off
my song to Jo Ji-na.
Like you said,
only the two of us knew this song.
You can't go in there.
Tell her it's Kim Bom.
This is urgent, and I must talk to her!
It's hard to say
when the interview will end.
You should make an appointment first.
Aren't you Kim Bom?
What brings you here?
Are you here to see me?
- Do you really not know why I'm here?
- Why else would I be asking?
Did something happen to Gye?
Fine.
If you're really clueless,
I'll say it right here.
Are you sure you don't mind
having reporters here?
I wouldn't mind,
but it's rude to keep a guest
standing in the hallway.
Shall we head inside?
Let's hear it, then.
Why did you barge in here
without an appointment?
When did you steal my song?
Why did you do this?
The lyrics and music
of The Crown's new single match mine.
What do you mean?
What are you saying I stole?
Don't act dumb.
You altered the chords
and the arrangement,
but even that…
It was too obvious.
Are you talking about
the song you sold to me?
No, not that!
Why do you keep playing dumb?
You obviously saw my songbook. When…
No way. On our retreat?
I'm off to the van.
- Are you having fun?
- Yes.
Why aren't you joining us out there?
It was then. I'm sure of it.
You looked through my songbook
that was in my backpack.
That's when the keychain fell off.
Ms. Kim,
don't you think you're being
a little delusional?
I don't even want to know
what song you're referring to,
but how are you so sure that you're
the only one
who can write a song like that?
There's no song that only you can write.
You're not exactly extraordinary.
How can you prove you wrote this song?
Show me if you can.
Why should I?
Because I know you stole it.
I can prove that it's my song.
Right here. It's all here in my songbook.
All the revisions I've made
over the years are all here.
Also…
This necklace is the proof of all that.
I'll request the song to be taken down.
And you'll have to give it your all
proving
you didn't steal my song.
See for yourself.
I also have a songbook.
Like you, I also spent years
revising my work.
The entire process is in there.
You're lying.
This can't be.
Bring me evidence that's irrefutable,
not just circumstantial.
Because an unbacked claim
is simply a delusion.
I answered your question,
so please leave now.
I've got better things to do
than handling losers' tantrums.
Can you see my visitor out?
Call security if you need to.
I'll sue you.
No lie can go unexposed,
and the law will hold you accountable.
I won't stop you
from getting into a dogfight.
However,
keep in mind that I already hold
the copyright to the song.
You're…
pure evil.
Let go of me. Let go!
Let go. Let go of me.
- This is unfair.
- Bom!
I didn't do anything wrong.
She's the one who stole my song.
I couldn't help but call the police.
The last thing we need is a scandal
on the day the song drops.
An explanation seems to be in order.
Was the song written by Kim Bom?
I wanted to dig us out
of the hole we were in.
I couldn't let my mistake
delay the release of the new song.
You call this digging us out of a hole?
Why'd you steal
from Kim Bom of all people?
Neither Kim Bom nor Sa Gye
will let this slide!
Why did you let us get involved
with those two again?
You should've discussed this with me.
Then things wouldn't have gotten this far!
I wanted your acknowledgement.
And I wanted that song for myself.
Things happened so fast,
and I was too afraid to confess.
Father, please help me this one time.
I'll do anything.
I can't go down like this.
If people find out I stole the song--
Shut up!
Listen to me.
From this moment on,
forget that you ever stole the song.
Don't ever mention it, even in your dream.
Do you hear me?
Ji-na, that song is yours. Okay?
You wrote it.
So defend it with your life.
If this gets out, you, me,
and Jo & Jo will all go down.
Bom, hey.
Are you all right?
Why are you here?
I was obviously worried.
Do you think I came here for fun?
Mind your own business and leave.
Do you and Sa Gye know each other?
Yes, I'm here as her guardian.
Guardian, my ass.
I don't know him at all.
I don't care about any of that.
Trespassing on private property
and vandalism.
It might not end with just a fine.
I'll make sure to give her an earful.
She hasn't been in her right mind
after a serious breakup.
- The jerk must work at Jo & Jo.
- Hey.
What is this crap?
I don't have the energy to deal with you,
so don't piss me off and leave.
- Go!
- But…
Will you just stay put?
It's actually time for her meds.
She's not usually this violent.
I'll make sure
she apologizes to those at Jo & Jo,
so could you give her a pass?
Are you insane? Why should I apologize?
I'll sue them
and request the song to be taken down.
Be quiet.
I'll make the guy who broke your heart
kneel before you.
Sounds good?
Did Jo & Jo put you up to this?
Did they threaten you to silence me?
- Don't get worked up.
- How can I not?
They stole my song.
Because you won't win
unless you stay cool-headed.
If you go after them without a plan,
they might…
bury you.
How could they bury me
when I'm not famous
and have nothing to lose?
It'll be their reputation
that takes the hit.
I'll continue to fight.
I won't let them have it.
- That's the song I wrote for my mom.
- That's why
you need to calm down.
Would you rather lose it in vain,
just like your mom?
What do you mean?
Well, I…
I mean, that's how important the song is.
Save the advice.
We mean nothing to each other now.
We could at least…
be friends.
I never considered you a friend.
I'm not saying you shouldn't fight.
I'm saying you should be smart.
I can't tell you about it just yet…
but there's a missing piece.
Just give me the benefit
of the doubt and trust me.
What is it that I don't know?
That your enemy
is more afraid of you
than you can imagine.
They're panicking,
desperate to hide something even worse.
I'll help you.
As long as you keep up the fight,
I'll be there by your side.
First, let's think about what we can do.
The members are still unaware
that you're joining the band.
For now, you'll use this locker.
You can use SAGYE's practice studio.
Just make sure no one sees you.
Sure. I got it.
SAGYE
THE CROWN FOREVER!
SAGYE, INO, KADI
Why do I feel like I'm being chased?
Why?
You told me
you liked Bom first.
But liking her first
doesn't mean she's yours.
Love isn't first come, first served.
You're wrong.
Time never betrays you.
I don't want to know why you did this.
What matters
is that I lost someone I cared about.
You're just like CEO Jo.
Shameless and evil.
EXPOSING THE UGLY TRUTH
OF JO & JO
UPLOAD COMPLETE
DELETED POST
BULLETIN BOARD
JO & JO STEALS
FROM A ROOKIE SONGWRITER
UPLOAD COMPLETE
JO & JO STEALS
FROM A ROOKIE SONGWRITER
DELETED POST
I can't post any negative post
about Jo & Jo.
So this is how far they'll go?
I'll hold back my feelings to let you go
But if that doesn't work
On the off chance
Say "I'll see you later"
See? The melody is identical.
It was plagiarized.
Well, I can't say for sure.
Is there proof?
This is my songbook.
You can see that the pages are worn out.
You can even see the date I noted.
Isn't this enough to file a lawsuit?
It is, right?
I guess you could file a lawsuit.
That's not what I want to hear!
You should say I can win this case.
I haven't won any cases yet, you see.
Anyway, the process
of proving song plagiarism
is time-consuming and tiring.
It's not worth the effort.
On top of that, the other party
has already copyrighted the song.
They fast-tracked it,
expecting this to happen.
Experts will recognize
that the song was plagiarized.
Please help me, sir.
First, please calm down.
Why don't we talk about
an irrefutable piece of evidence?
What can you present?
Why do I need to prove anything
when it's clearly mine?
One is soft and lyrical
while the other is hard rock.
How can it be plagiarism
when they have different styles?
They took my song
and arranged it with an intense rock beat.
The melody is identical.
How can you not see that?
You see…
I know music.
I was a musician myself.
What do you take me for?
Look. Lee Hong…
You know, the band that starts with an F.
Darn it.
Anyway, it'll be hard to win this case.
Jo & Jo will hire the best lawyer possible
and come at you.
How do you expect to win?
To be honest, I don't think
I could win.
Look how tiny my office is.
Take it and leave.
The person you called is unavailable.
Reporter Han, why couldn't I reach you?
I've been calling nonstop.
I'm sorry, but I can't help you.
You don’t know why I’m here.
Look, Jo & Jo has already spread the word.
That you'll come
at The Crown's new album, out of spite.
Leave it be. This won't change anything.
You'll only embarrass yourself.
You have it all wrong.
Don't believe what Mr. Jo says.
It's all lies.
Please. Please help me out.
- What's happening is unfair.
- Get a grip on yourself.
No reporter will help you.
All entertainment news outlets
are connected to Jo & Jo.
Jo & Jo owns half of their shares.
You won't get this advice anywhere else.
Take care of yourself.
Mr. Han, I'll wait for your call!
I trust you. You're the only remaining
reliable reporter!
Please call me!
Have you moved out of Kim Bom's house?
I have nothing to say to you.
Unless you're here to admit to the theft,
just keep moving.
Why are you doing this to me?
What do you mean I stole?
How can you accuse me
after only hearing Kim Bom's side?
It's a song I could've easily written.
So why do you think I couldn't have?
You couldn't have written it.
You can fool others, but not me.
Shouldn't you at least
give me the benefit of the doubt?
When you got into trouble
and got kicked out,
I begged my father on my knees.
So why won't you do anything for me?
You can kneel again…
in front of Bom.
It's not too late to ask for forgiveness.
Is that all you can say to me?
Do I…
Do I mean nothing to you?
I worked every day for six years
just to help you become a star.
I followed you everywhere,
from Europe to the US,
pouring my life into designing
your wardrobe and performances
at the expense of my own.
And this is how you repay me?
For Kim Bom, whom you only recently met,
you'll throw away our relationship?
You and Mr. Jo may have opened doors,
but I climbed to the top by myself.
I took every step alone.
What?
So why can't you do the same?
Does success have to come
at the cost of others?
Is that how you made it so far?
It's pathetic.
Tae-yang, are you aware
that you're addicted to caffeine?
Do you want to die while studying
all night? Please stop drinking those.
You need quality sleep.
Jeez, it looks tasty.
What's wrong with me today?
Breakfast is ready!
In five seconds, I'm clearing the table.
Goodness.
Seaweed soup. Just what I wanted.
Again, there isn't any meat.
Meat? In this weather, mussels are better.
I like my eggs over easy,
but you always fully cook the yolk.
Please keep that in mind.
Being picky, are we?
I cooked them thoroughly
since they had expired.
I was being considerate, okay?
Anyway, where is everyone else?
Beats me. What's taking Bom so long?
Ms. Kim, can I also have a perilla leaf?
Bom left ages ago.
Even though she makes very little,
she's incredibly busy.
It's not like her jobs pay well.
It's nicely seasoned, right?
- Totally.
- I know.
Did Bom get some sleep?
I'm not a watchdog. How would I know that?
The soup will get cold. Hurry downstairs!
Bae Gyu-ri!
Look at you dragging your feet.
Mom, were you in a heavy metal band?
A fangirl of Jeon In-kwon
and not Shin Seung-hun, right?
Would it kill you to speak more softly?
SAGYE!
What the heck? Why are you screaming?
When did you get back?
Do you have any idea how worried I was?
I thought you had dropped out of school
and left for good.
Goodness.
Don't you ever leave me again.
I was worried sick.
I couldn't sleep
and completely bombed my exams.
That isn't my fault.
- Let's eat.
- Sure.
How embarrassing.
Here for your stuff?
What do you mean?
What is this brat doing here?
When did you get here?
A while ago.
You brat. How dare you come back
like nothing ever happened?
This isn't a coin karaoke
that you can come and go as you please.
Get over here, you brat.
You…
You dodged that?
Like that'd stop me.
Why you… Get back here, you brat.
What's going on?
Why are you staying here?
Where's Tae-yang?
Unbelievable.
I'm gone for a few days,
and I come back to a new roommate?
You're one to talk!
You prick.
You quit the band
without so much as an explanation.
You have some nerve coming back.
The band broke up because of you.
Do you have any idea
the heartache you've caused?
You irresponsible jerk.
Just get lost!
Jin-gu, I know you're upset,
but at least give me a heads-up.
That was cowardly.
I see that punch wasn't enough.
Jin-gu, a punch from a trained drummer
could be deadly.
Are you kidding me?
I should beat the crap out of you.
Hello, Reporter Han.
Really?
Thank you so much.
I'll seriously owe you one.
I'll be on my way now.
Did you just smile?
Get back here!
SAGYE, run.
Stop, my ass!
I'm teaching him a lesson today.
Who are you to say that?
Don't you know who he is?
Take it out on me instead!
Hey.
You… Let go of me.
Let go while I'm asking nicely.
It's your fault!
Why won't you let SAGYE alone?
So why can't you do the same?
Does success have to come
at the cost of others?
Is that how you made it so far?
Why did you ask to see me?
Don't even think
about trying to pay me off.
No way I'm backing down
after that visit to the police station.
Of course. I didn't think you would.
I guess I can throw courtesy
out the window.
I came across an interesting video
in my dad's office this morning.
My dad must be deeply upset by all this.
It's understandable,
given that a mere 20-year-old
is making baseless accusations.
In two hours,
he will release this video to the press.
You probably know this,
but my dad is a man of his word.
Tell him to go ahead.
I'm not guilty of anything.
Did he catch me on video stealing,
like a certain someone?
Let's check it out together.
Only you can stop this video
from being released.
You're smart,
so I'll let you think it over.
Ms. Jo Ji-na,
is this who you are?
I can't just sit back
and let you come at me.
I have to do what it takes
to defend myself.
Don't you agree?
SA GYE
Promise me you won't
take issue with this song.
Just sign right here.
What if I won't?
Then, SAGYE will lose any chance
of making a comeback.
But if you sign this document,
I'll make sure this video stays buried.
You have my word.
My answer…
is no.
Don't you care about
what'll happen to Gye?
I thought you were close friends.
I'm disappointed.
The Sa Gye I know
would never resort to violence.
You should know that too.
If he went as far
as to destroy Mr. Jo's car,
Mr. Jo must have done
something terribly wrong.
Go ask your father
how he wronged Gye.
How's that for an answer?
We're good, Bom. I got the approval.
Reporter Han agreed to help us.
How?
Sometime this week,
he'll gather some reporters for us.
Isn't it great?
Mr. Han may seem cold,
but he's quite loyal.
He was more pissed off
about what they did to you.
You have your necklace and your songbook.
You also have me.
With the right counterattack,
you'll win your case.
- I'm hungry.
- What?
Sure. We should eat to fight properly.
What would you like to have?
They're all yours, so slow down.
I'm happy to treat you to all this,
but who runs up the bill at a cafe?
Now I feel better.
I'm good now. Bye.
Hey, where are you going?
We have to meet with Mr. Han.
I've let go of that song.
I won't sue them.
What are you talking about?
Why won't you sue?
I can write
other songs.
Jo Ji-na won't be able
to write any more good songs,
but I can.
- That's true, but--
- That's why I won't sue them.
I've had it with their dirty tricks.
And you…
Stay out of my sight.
How is that possible
when I'm back as your housemate?
Don't you get it?
I don't want to see you again.
I called you here because
our last memory together was the worst.
Remembering how you were that day
was enough to make me feel sick forever.
I thought this sweetness
would mask that bitterness.
Don't even come near my house.
Don't follow me out.
I can pack a mean punch.
Hey, Bom.
Bom!
Why won't you sue them?
I don't understand.
I don't want to. Why the fuss?
Are you stupid?
You wrote the song for your mom.
You kept it because it meant a lot.
So you should sing it.
Why let someone else do it?
That's right.
I wanted to sing that song. With you.
But who broke the promise?
It'll be sung by you and me.
You have to be the one to sing this.
Who else could sing it but me?
You abandoned me first.
And I don't think
I can sing this song anymore.
We're done.
Keep your promise
to erase that video of Gye.
From Kim Bom.
Ms. Jo.
It's been handled.
I think that dash cam video you gave me
scared her.
All right!
Here are the records
that The Crown has set.
The fastest single to break
into the World Chart's top ten,
the most-viewed
and highest-trending music video.
You did it all!
It's the most covered song as well.
Good job, Producer Jo.
Good work, everyone.
Raise your glasses.
Mr. Kang, join us.
We should celebrate together.
I can't hold my liquor, sir.
But I'll drink.
With our new single being a huge hit,
it's time I step up as the leader, Mr. Jo.
- You'll do what?
- I'll take over as the leader.
Are you already a bit tipsy?
SUNDER.
Do you think you're a big shot?
You think you can demand
the leader position from me?
That's not what I meant.
I'm sorry, sir.
I was going to save it for later,
but since we're on the topic,
I'll do it now.
Soon,
The Crown will get a new member.
And who's that?
I can't reveal that just yet
due to security reasons.
Just know that there's no one
more fitting for The Crown.
He will be the team's new leader.
Who could he be keeping under wraps?
- Are you off to smoke?
- Yes.
Isn't that Mr. Kang's wife?
Yes, I think that's her.
She must be here to pick him up.
Check out that fancy car.
It looks expensive.
Did he win the lottery?
Actually, I asked him
the same thing and he said
that CEO Jo gave it to him.
Did Mr. Jo own an SUV?
I thought he only drove sedans.
It wasn't exactly his.
I think it belonged
to either a friend or a relative.
It was set to be scrapped
due to water damage,
but Mr. Kang gave it to his wife instead.
- Water damage?
- Yes.
- It's chilly. Let's head inside.
- Sure.
Water damage?
Why aren't you picking up?
Gye, I just saw an SUV.
Apparently, CEO Jo gave it to Mr. Kang--
Did Auntie swing by?
THE LATE YU JEONG-AE
Mom.
It's me.
Your daughter, Bom-bom.
Mom,
you're still young and beautiful.
I'm glad.
Mom, did you miss me?
I missed you so much, Mom.
I wanted to come here every single day.
But I couldn't bring myself to.
It's still too painful…
to see your face.
Also, I'm sorry.
I…
I even lost the song I wrote for you.
I'm so pathetic, aren't I?
What's this?
- Auntie.
- Yes?
Did you go see Mom yesterday?
Me? No. Her birthday is still months away.
I'm so cold.
Am I coming down with something?
Someone went to see Mom yesterday.
Who could it have been?
Probably her friend.
I hear they do reunions there.
She was popular, you know.
- And those flowers?
- Didn't you bring them?
Goodness. Then it must have been
that brat Jin-gu.
He likely feels bad for freeloading.
But slabs of pork would've been better
than those flowers.
There's nothing to like about him.
Can you hang these to dry?
Bom-bom.
Mom?
What are you doing?
Isn't it obvious?
I've been cleaning. The house is a mess.
Also, shouldn't you keep the piano clean?
It was a gift.
You can't practice like this.
We're doing what here?
Heave-ho!
- Heave-ho!
- Hang those later and get the equipment.
SAGYE, Gyu-ri's here.
What took you so long?
You should've set everything up already.
Cut the chatter and give me a hand.
It's heavy.
- Hey, that's expensive.
- It just dropped.
What are you all doing?
Obviously, practice.
TWO SAGYE is back. Didn't SAGYE tell you?
The studio ban’s ending soon,
so we’ll practice here for now.
All right. Here's the sheet music.
Thanks.
What's your deal?
Why's it all so easy for you?
Who are you to reassemble the band
when you broke it up?
You said you're done with TWO SAGYE.
So what is all this?
Am I a joke to you? Is this all a game?
Why do you keep changing your mind
and irritating the hell out of me?
Put the instruments away.
I will never be in a band with you.
All right.
Don't join us if you're not up for it.
But can we at least perform this cover?
I found a song I like
for the first time in a while.
You can at least do that much.
Perform it yourselves
if you're that eager.
EXAM REGISTRATION SLIP
SEO TAE-YANG
Ta-da! I bet you didn't pack lunch.
I packed shrimp fried rice, your favorite,
and egg soup.
They'll stay warm until lunchtime,
so make sure to eat everything.
You shouldn't have bothered.
I was going to pick up some porridge.
You can't have that before an exam.
I made sure the eggs aren't lumpy,
so tackle all of those questions.
Our Hanju University High School
should produce the top-ranking student.
That reminds me. The exam slip.
Do you have it?
You don't?
Of course, I have it.
Just a second.
Here. I prayed for you.
SEO TAE-YANG, DON'T FRET!
KIM BOM IS PRAYING FOR YOU HARD!
Victory! I wish you good luck
on your CSAT!
I'll get going.
Tae-yang, good luck on your exam.
Get the correct answer,
whether you know it or not.
Let's get you to Hanju Med School!
Go, Seo Tae-yang!
KIM BOM
Bom, are you doing well?
Could we perhaps meet up?
There's something I should tell you.
TWO SAGYE BANNED
FROM USING THEIR STUDIO
I'll hold back my feelings to let you go
But if that doesn't work
On the off chance
I'll hold back my feelings to let you go
But if that doesn't work
On the off chance
Girl, you shake up my world
Even without words, you know how I feel
You appear before my eyes
Without you, my nights will be lonely
I find new things to do
Meet friends at every chance
Talk about meaningless things
But why is it still this hard?
I added a rap section
to your original song.
Let's upload this as a cover song.
That darn song is being played
everywhere you go.
Will you keep avoiding it?
It's your song, isn't it?
You said only losers backed out
without a fight.
This is the hottest song right now,
so our cover will get a lot of views.
Even Jo & Jo will promote it.
That won't make it mine again.
- It'll be just one of many cover songs.
- Yours will be different.
Let's prove together that the original
stands in a league of its own.
You have me. What is there to fear?
What if…
you change your mind again?
What if you give up and run again?
That…
will never happen.
I'll never run away again.
I swear on these very eyes.
Were your eyes always this beautiful?
Both eyes shining like the stars.
Hey. You made me rush the cover,
so I recorded it only with a guitar.
I bet the audio quality was lousy.
No.
It's good.
Really?
Nice! Does that mean you approve?
That was my audition.
You acknowledge my talent, right?
When did you write the rap?
Writing the rap was a breeze,
thanks to the inspiring original song.
Come on. Let's go practice.
The others are waiting.
I'll hold back my feelings to let you go
But if that doesn't work
On the off chance
Mr. Kwon Hyeok-gi is here?
Yes, it's an emergency, sir.
He is asking you to perform the surgery.
Right. I just received a call
from the president's office.
Performing surgery on the floor leader
of the ruling party should be my priority.
Prep the OR immediately.
Kim Bok-rye's surgery is scheduled
for 3 p.m. today.
She's elderly and lives alone,
so the social welfare division
has specifically asked you to operate.
Push it to tomorrow.
You can't, sir.
Considering her age, her deteriorating
liver condition is a serious concern.
Time is of the essence.
Life and death is up
to the patient's will.
If her time has come,
we won't be able to change it.
- I'll operate on Mr. Kwon.
- But--
Make sure to schedule
the post-op briefing.
I'll be handling that myself too.
Get on it.
What in the world?
Is this a dumpster or what?
Are you kidding me?
Would it kill them
to clean up after eating?
This won't do the job. My gosh.
So much for washing these for him.
Why are they like this
when they haven't been worn?
I can already see
how this place will be without me.
It's basically a pigpen.
Goodness.
If it weren't for this, Sa Gye,
you'd only be getting the bare minimum.
My gosh.
I don't know why this makes my heart
skip a beat every time I see it.
In my early days,
my heart fluttered for Shin Seung-hun.
But now, it skips a beat
for a suitcase full of cash.
Goodness me.
Aren't these Jin-gu's?
Unbelievable.
I told him to put dirty clothes
in the laundry basket!
He's a freeloader, and yet
he's the most high-maintenance.
Goodness.
It's so worn out it's got holes.
This is basically a rag.
He's nothing but a homeless bum.
Just my luck.
Unbelievable.
All that stress has turned my hair gray.
How upsetting.
Ms. Kim, are there any snacks?
We're rehearsing on the rooftop.
Can't you see I'm busy dyeing my hair?
Drink tap water.
- Why are you dyeing it at home?
- To save money.
I'm low on cash because of a freeloader
who doesn't pay rent.
Ask Gye to help you out.
I heard his mom was a hairdresser,
so a dye job will be a piece of cake.
I'm not like you, you know.
Of course, the freeloader knows
exactly what to take advantage of.
Unbelievable.
Wait. What's that around your neck?
A rag, of course.
It looks familiar.
Jin-gu, Bom's back! Hurry on up!
Sure, I'll be right there!
I know I recognize it.
Oh, right! I've set aside clothes
for dry cleaning, so don't touch them.
They can't be washed with water.
Who gets clothes with holes dry cleaned?
That's why you're so poor!
Bom! I've landed a role in the band.
Ta-da. Clever, right?
SAGYE recommended it.
Gyu-ri, could you be a maracas prodigy?
The way you play with the beat
is ingenious!
All right. Let's give it a shot.
Hold on. What about Tae-yang?
TWO SAGYE is missing a SAGYE.
Exactly. What's he up to?
That's why I'm telling you to let him go.
Let him swim in a larger pond.
We'll perform…
without Tae-yang.
It'll be just us.
Why? He doesn't want to?
He thinks he's better than everyone.
Focus, guys.
Shall we?
Let's go!
TWO SAGYE…
doesn't have a future.
It ends here.
I hope you get to do what you want.
Don't waste your time with me.
Tae-yang.
Is this your answer?
Was it so wrong of me
to tell you I like you?
Was it too much for you to deal with?
Was disbanding TWO SAGYE all a show
to drive me out of the band?
It's a misunderstanding.
It's not what you think.
You should've just been honest with me
and told me to leave the band.
If you had,
it wouldn't have been this miserable.
Please hear me out.
I meant to break up the band.
- But--
- I don't get you at all.
How can you welcome Gye with a smile
after what he did?
Do you have no self-respect?
You must be so into him
to be this understanding.
I can't seem to catch a break with you,
but he gets away with everything.
I'm sorry…
I couldn't reciprocate your feelings.
That's why…
I couldn't hold onto you.
Don't apologize.
It's actually for the best.
I won't have to feel bad either.
Regardless of how I start my career…
You won't care, right?
If it's your choice,
it must be the right choice.
TWO SAGYE and I were never a good fit.
If I could,
I'd wipe it from my memory.
You didn't tell Gye anything, did you?
I didn't. You told me not to, sir.
But why can't I tell him?
What?
You know how suspicious he can be.
There's no point in giving him ammunition.
Which SUV is Gye looking for?
It wasn't even yours,
so who wanted it scrapped?
How long have you worked for me?
Six years, sir.
In those six years,
you would've learned how the world works.
Gye and I are like brothers.
We grew up in the same neighborhood,
our mothers are close,
and we don't keep secrets from each other.
Is that so?
I envy that friendship.
I'll keep it short, then.
Which mountain will it be?
Pick one to hike up.
The day is short,
so don't get stranded halfway up
and end up torn apart by a wild animal.
I'll now start the presentation
introducing The Crown's new member.
Girl, you shake up my world
Even without words, you know how I feel
The time that we had
You appear before my eyes
Without you, my nights will be lonely
I find new things to do
Meet friends at every chance
Talk about meaningless things
But why is it still this hard?
I think about you every day
I hold back as much as I can
If we're meant to be, we'll meet again
I'll hold back my feelings to let you go
But if that doesn't work
On the off chance
We're going to film it now.
The video will go up at midnight.
That's too sudden.
You never said we'd be filming it today.
Hanju University High School's finals
start tomorrow.
If we're too loud at night,
the mothers will murder us.
I'll need 11 mm falsies to be
camera-ready.
These are only 9 mm.
We absolutely can't do this.
I'm in. Cover videos should look
as natural as possible.
I'm in too.
My wardrobe today…
couldn't be more natural.
I honestly can't agree.
All my clothes were ruined,
so Ms. Kim lent me some of hers to wear.
They suit you nicely.
How generous of my mom.
Hang in there, Jin-gu.
Right.
Put these on.
We'll rock it
in these matching bucket hats.
What the hell?
This covers my face completely.
Why wear this?
I don't want to either.
As the face of this team, I refuse.
My hair is my best feature!
We'll reveal our faces when our video gets
over three million views.
Three million?
- Are you kidding me?
- That'll never happen.
Who'll listen to our song
if we show Gye's face?
The entire nation will be
too busy hating us.
Are you good with that?
Hear me out.
We'll blow people's minds
with our cover song,
then reveal that it's Gye.
It'd be annoying to get chewed out
before a fair assessment.
My fans will still recognize my voice,
even if my face is covered.
You need to fool them.
Switch up your singing style.
Forget what you learned at Jo & Jo
and sing however you want.
Belt out notes if you want
and even try growling.
Can't you do it?
Okay. Sure!
It'll be done in a single take.
You can't mess up, so focus.
- Got it.
- We'll nail it at first attempt!
- Yes!
- Let's do it!
Roopretelcham.
Girl, you shake up my world
Even without words, you know how I feel
The time that we had
You appear before my eyes
Without you, my nights will be lonely
I find new things to do
Meet friends at every chance
Talk about meaningless things
But why is it still this hard?
I think about you every day
I hold back as much as I can
If we're meant to be, we'll meet again
I'll hold back my feelings to let you go
But if that doesn't work
On the off chance
I hear time will do the work
It'll help me forget about you
Only until then will I give it my all
I'll hold out, even if it's just for a day
At exactly 10 a.m., public TV channels,
general TV stations, cable networks,
and other media outlets
will introduce you as breaking news.
The members will find out simultaneously.
The CS department is paralyzed
from the rumor about a new member.
Global fans must be stirred up too.
The timing couldn't be better.
The Crown's new song
just topped the charts.
We'll be the center of attention
and have the most viral videos.
It's almost 10 a.m.
Let's head to the conference room.
Right. Let's go.
Guys, come quick!
The Crown is announcing its new member.
- What?
- Who is it?
Let me see his face. Who is it?
THE CROWN NEW MEMBER REVEAL
COUNTDOWN
THE CROWN'S NEW LEADER REVEALED
ON DECEMBER 1ST, 10 A.M.
I'll hold back my feelings to let you go
But if that doesn't work
On the off chance
If you don't want to get hurt,
leave the agency on your own terms.
I'm always down for a fight with you.
- Bom, did you know about this?
- It's not our place to meddle.
Make me a more successful artist
than Sa Gye.
TWO SAGYE is finally making its debut.
I have something to say to you.
This is cheating.
You have no fear, do you?
You let Sa Gye get the better of you.
I can't let him sink and drown.
I'm set on taking down
the shady Jo & Jo Entertainment.
I'll get it done.
Don't. This is Tae-yang's choice.
She's letting it slide for your sake.
Because she's kind to a fault!
Do you know Bom that well?
More than I do?
Subtitle translation by: Hyelim Park