Music
rows.
By¿¦ le?
Let's introduce ourselves as the Committee of The Nationaloni
and the Sang dużrisei
to end this discussions
everyone on your pedestal
And love song.
Can a
I've been keeping my mouth shut for years.
I have nothing to say.
But you don't have to be so reckless.
You know very well what kind of person Liang Juren is.
Working with him is like fighting a fire.
I'll give you a little bit of the sauce.
Liang Juren is really good at playing hard to get.
I didn't expect that the Green Scent Committee gave him a position as a member.
If you have a wife who is willing to pay for her family's funeral,
you'll climb faster than her.
You're faster than her.
Hello, Director Li.
Director Lin and the committee members are all here.
Director Lin.
Please don't kill him.
This is the chief of the Green Scent Committee,
the chief of the Green Scent Committee,
and the chief of the Green Scent Committee.
Director An Jing,
it's a great honor to meet you.
Brother,
my name is Kanegane.
I've been working with Taiko for a long time.
He often talked about you when he was a chief of staff.
I didn't expect to meet you here.
Would you like to talk a little?
I'll talk about the past with only you and Li.
Please.
Mr. Komizu,
since there is a translator by the chief of staff,
you don't have to follow me.
Okay, Director Li.
Thank you.
I will help you.
Cheers.
Let's talk.
When did Brother Liang call me out?
I saw it just now.
I didn't let you in.
What does it mean?
It means you have a different mind.
I'm used to it.
I'm the chief.
It's strange that Director An Jing
suddenly came here.
It seems that Director An Jing is the chief of staff of the Green Scent Committee.
In fact,
he is here to investigate the secret and secret secrets
of the people in the space.
Li Yue Se is the spy.
Brother Liang,
you are going to kill Mr. Li.
But as far as I know,
An Jing Zhong and Du Yue Si are old friends.
Will he give them a chance?
Don't talk about you.
I said we were friends.
Let me tell you this.
Du Yue Si is good friends with An Jing Zhong.
But he has always been in the middle of the conflict between the Eastern Yuan Temple and the Eastern Tiao Sect.
Moreover,
he has been the ambassador of the camp for so many years.
His family business is all in London.
Once he fights with the British and the Americans,
he is the first one to be hurt.
Moreover, he has been in bed for a year.
It's important to wake up.
So,
is the Eastern Yuan Temple family
a life-saving or a death-saving family to Li Yue Se?
What do you think?
Please give me your advice.
This is a letter from the British.
I have written the content for you.
With your identity and your statement,
the British and British people know Li Yue Se and have a secret relationship.
You need to write the letter.
But if I am here to ask you,
I will be the first one to be hurt.
If you sign the letter,
Mr. Li will be dead.
I want to ask you.
You always think for him.
But have you ever thought for him?
Has he ever thought for you?
If Li Yue Se has always been the head of the secret research institute,
will he keep you under his control?
Do you think so?
As long as you sign the letter,
the general will sign it for you on the letter.
By then, you will be the secret inspector of the Green House Committee.
The Left Palace is your tree.
Don't say a secret code.
All your talents
will not be seen.
The secret inspector of the Green House Committee
What did An Jing say to you?
The Green House Committee has adopted the secret code designed by her.
And the one you designed has been returned by Nanjing.
Do you know?
She said that you gave the Japanese a very secret code behind my back.
It seems that your new protector is very powerful.
But I still want to remind you.
Even if the Green House Committee uses your secret code,
we will not give up.
I'd better remind you again.
Don't trust Liang Jing Yuan too much.
I understand.
The secret inspector of the Green House Committee
Now, use numbers 1 to 10 to express your strength.
You don't feel anything at all.
You have a very strong sense.
Let's start.
How about it?
Or
I understand.
How about this?
Less than 100 meters away.
He has to walk for 10 minutes at the travel price.
It's been so long.
Why can't he recover?
I can feel the wound on Sen-san's spine.
But the recovery of the spinal nerve is slower than usual.
However,
it is a miracle that he got off the bed in her spinal nerve state.
let's encourage him to strengthen his recovery training.
Take your time.
Then, I'm going to go.
Goodbye.
I'll send them off.
Take your time.
Is it really that important who is in charge of the top floor?
It's only your mother's risk.
Don't worry about me.
I'll find out the result.
I have a way out.
How's it going on your side?
The password plan the organization gave me has been handed over to Nanjing.
In a few days, the Qingxiao Committee will formally use our password.
But I still feel a little bit unstable.
It's always good to be cautious.
But remember, don't put too much pressure on yourself.
Our top floor is the base of the base.
The Chinese and Chinese troops of the Kuomintang have all been drawn into the important scope of this Qingxiao.
Only by mastering the password of the Qingxiao Committee's secret power station
can we understand the work of the Uyghur Qingxiao.
In my understanding of Guoyangshan,
he will not give up.
After the war in Banan, the Uyghur was already a general.
For the past half a year, your efforts to fight the Uyghur army
and the civil war between Liang and Guoyangshan have suffered a lot.
But they have also accumulated a lot of experience.
These two people are very rich.
It's not easy to form an alliance.
So I guess they will have the next move soon.
We can't sit and wait.
We must send someone to kick Guoyangshan out.
The organization sent a secret expert to support me.
When can I come in?
The background investigation of the research institute
is now under the responsibility of the head of the institute.
It's very strict.
We have prepared for several months.
The identity and disguise of the expert has just been solved these days.
After you go back, find a chance to request
to send a new secret agent.
He will find a way to get to you.
It's time to say goodbye.
Slow down.
Be careful.
Tell Xiao,
the replacement of the key to the reception of the Uyghur People's Committee
has been completed.
The expert we have assigned to him
can enter the secret agent at any time.
Okay.
But what should you do?
You alone...
I will go.
If the information is correct,
the suspect is the first target
of the heart and brain blood vessels.
The patient living in the upper floor
has this kind of acupoint to wake him up.
He must be an important figure in the Japanese military.
I suspect
it's the Uyghur people.
But
the Japanese military's senior
has heart and brain blood vessels.
Not only him.
Why do you suspect him?
The Uyghur people are the Uyghur people.
Now the relationship between Japan and the Uyghur people is so tense.
In this situation,
do you dare to use the Uyghur people?
Besides the Uyghur people
who have been working in the Western-style East Garden for years,
who else will?
But based on the information we received
some time ago,
this job
is still in the hands of the Japanese people.
The Uyghur people
are still in the hands of the Japanese people.
Ding Yi mentioned
that they received a private radio
from the secret station.
Do you remember?
Yes.
Ding Yi told us the frequency
and the time of the radio.
It's a good thing.
Actually, this is the private radio of Zuo Zuo Mu.
But
it doesn't matter who lives upstairs.
Zuo Zuo Mu
is the representative of the Shaozhuang Sect
and the representative of the Eastern Garden.
He is the heir of the four families.
After the work of the other party's
is completed,
I believe the secret message of the radio
will tell us
who the patient
who lives on the top floor is.
Who is it?
I have to sign the contract
to be the chief executive?
You can write the contract as a secret agent.
Sign the contract?
That idiot wants to sign it.
What can he do?
Lin, the board of directors has been established.
When will we move there?
I don't know.
You don't know?
The committee of the
Qingjiang Committee is a false name.
Am I reading a newspaper?
I'm reading the future.
The future?
The house has been replaced.
But you are all
as bad as the tofu.
You have to take charge.
You are so old.
We have to fight for this.
What do you want?
It's done.
Don't touch me.
Don't cry.
Do I want to be an official?
I'm trying to find
a sense of security for us.
But you know
what's going on now.
We are both
trying to survive in the gap.
People
have their own difficulties.
They get over it
and become more and more cheerful.
What do you want?
The chief executive called me
to send a new secretary to Li Yunsi.
Do you know?
Is this news accurate?
He just called.
That's great.
Don't say it.
You can't tell me about it.
I know.
Secretary Gu.
You have to get
the new secretary in.
And post his
report in our office.
The chief executive
has to be in charge
of the new secretary.
The personnel is never
an official.
It's not just about the official.
I want the head of the department.
I have to show
everyone in our office.
What are you going to do?
Give me a leg.
A leg?
I'll write it in English.
Last month, the foreign affairs
negotiations with the UK and the US were very bad.
So the Japanese have hired
a special person to investigate
the intelligence agency of the new government.
Li Yuese
has a deep connection with the UK and the US.
So once the war begins,
he will be fired.
Ding Yi is a
county man.
He is there to cover you.
Once the cover is broken,
he will be fired.
As long as you are still in the research institute,
you are there.
I am going to use the Japanese
to investigate the intelligence agency of the UK and the US.
I will report to Li Yuese
and the UK and the US
to the state.
Then Ding Yi will be fired.
And I will stay
and carry out the mission.
Liang Jinyuan has been
pulling you down.
He hates Li Yuese.
You can sign
the letter he gave you
and hand it over to him.
I will
but I will write
this letter myself.
I understand what you mean.
You just want to
get hold of the letter
and get Ding Yi out alive.
But who is Liang Jinyuan?
He can't guess it.
To save Ding Yi,
Liang Jinyuan
lost his trust in you.
Hu Yangshan,
I advise you to focus on the big picture.
Don't be emotional.
I will.
An, I understand what you mean.
But you have to know
that Ding Yi is
a big trouble to us.
So if we push him too hard,
it will affect our next action.
So I have my plans.
You just
report to me
as I want.
Mr. Li,
you are going home.
Mr. Gu,
it's you.
congratulations.
Mr. Li,
it's you.
Congratulations.
Mr. Li,
I see.
Mr. Gu,
congratulations.
Congratulations.
You are so good.
See you tomorrow.
Congratulations.
Mr. Gu,
you are transferred to the Green House Committee.
Congratulations.
You are transferred to the Green House Committee.
You are transferred to my position.
I really underestimated you.
I thought he was just a fake.
I didn't expect
that he really had some power.
But I'm curious about
his future with his wife.
And you,
what did you do?
The new secretary that the Red Cross recruited for you
should be here tomorrow.
I will work with him as soon as possible.
From now on,
we will separate.
I won't change.
You want to replace the Green House Committee?
I won't let you go.
Thank you.
Please come with us.
I'm sorry.
Gu Ruoyuan.
This way.
Please come with us.
Yes.
Mr. Qiao Benpailang,
the team leader of the password development team.
The key password of our committee
is his design.
His design?
Yes.
But as far as I know,
Nanjing
uses Mr. Li Yuese's password.
I don't know
the specific reason.
But we always use the password of Qiao Benpailang.
The password of the team leader.
Your office is here.
The team leader of the team development team
hasn't arrived yet.
I'll introduce him to you when he arrives.
The team development team?
Yes.
Gu Ruoyuan, didn't you just say
you have something to give to Mr. Suo.
No hurry.
Mr. Suo,
this is the daily work plan.
Is Mr. Liang here?
Mr. Liang hasn't arrived yet.
What's the matter?
Nothing.
Please go ahead.
You дыis here.
I told you he didn't.
I told you he doesn't.
You had better be careful.
Chen Ren
Wait.
Mr. Liang.
Just call me Liang.
I'm going to see Mr. Liang.
There are some things I don't understand.
I want to ask Mr. Liang to explain to me.
Say it.
Why does the Qingjiang Committee use Qiao Ben's password?
And why am I arranged into the Phe Clan?
Your promise to me is as disappointing as ever.
I'm sorry.
The Phe Clan
Zuo Zoumu has handed the letter you wrote to the Anqing Zhong family.
He was very angry after reading it.
Let me tell you.
Li Yuese will die this time.
As long as he is dead this time,
you will be the director of the password research institute.
Why do you care about a mere password specialist?
What do you say?
I know what you're thinking.
Your letter of resignation
is not evidence that Li Yuese has been secretly working for Yingmei.
It's not important.
What's important is this letter of resignation.
It's Li Yuese's suicide note.
Mr. Li.
I'm sure you know this.
All the statements here are recorded.
The general is in the military.
It's a disaster.
According to Japanese military intelligence,
he is dead.
What do you mean?
Do you think Zuo Zoumu has a big circle
just to get rid of a blind man?
Of course not.
You have a message that you have the right to own the secret code design business of the new government.
Is it the order of the Toen case?
He wants to use Li Yuese
to get the hat of the Toen family from the Toen family.
It's a nonsense.
This is all Zixun's doing.
I don't know anything.
Once this is done,
no one will ever fight against the Toen family again.
In the last Chuei era,
your father and his classmates were frequently involved in the Toen case.
What kind of British did you meet in the Toen family?
Daguang is the ambassador of the Toen family appointed by His Majesty.
He has always been loyal to His Majesty.
He has never had any contact with any English-born people other than work.
Moreover, he invited people to his home in private.
Mr. Anjing, you can suspect me,
but you should never suspect Daguang.
Brother, you should be glad
that you have this knife to prove your loyalty.
You should keep your eyes on the long term.
So I want to thank you for your advice
and for bringing me out of this political whirlpool.
Dad,
don't forget that we are friends.
Why do you say that?
I and Mr. Zuo really admire you.
There are so many talented people like you.
Don't let anyone down.
Mr. Li,
while we investigate the case thoroughly,
we will stop the work at the secret research institute
and wait for the judgment to be made.
The secret research institute
《花蜜蜂》
火一支毒物 破碎的拉脫這溫度
紅透過眼光 搖曳那微弱的一盞烏中
花 捧起爪路 俊烈的身距化成泥土
能 天邊日出 第一綠光輝替我起舞
家 隔著迷霧 沒有方向也沒有退路
在眼下痛哭 假的戲真的人說不清楚
風 去往何處 搖晃著誰的窗 低聲的訴
心 傻傻坐下 或是你或是我在干擾
他在守望 茫茫遠夜上
一瞬風光 一軍跌的傷
他在守望 陰影裡流浪
夜色落幕 回舟也是天涼
他在守望 茫茫遠夜上
淚水風光 一軍跌的傷
他在守望 陰影裡流浪
夜色落幕 回舟也是天涼
詞曲 李宗盛