shooters and
Mr. Li,
the ship tickets to Hong Kong are ready for sale tomorrow.
I'm sorry.
There are too many people who want to buy the tickets.
I'm late.
It's okay.
Mr. Li,
you're leaving?
Yes.
Actually,
I'm here to say goodbye to you.
This last glass of wine...
Thank you.
is our
last glass of wine.
Why?
Actually,
I don't have to leave.
But what's the point of staying?
My password has been leaked.
Mr. Li,
do you know what you just said?
Everyone in Jiangcheng must not leave.
Mr. Li,
where did you get the password?
The British.
Is it Mr. William?
Why did they tell you?
William and I have been friends for many years.
He didn't like me being?
So he told me.
Actually, Mr. Wu,
I didn't want to say this today.
But I think,
as a brother,
I have to give you an advice.
Change my password as soon as possible.
In case of leaking.
How do they know?
There are too many people in the trap.
It's not impossible to leak the password.
Impossible?
We have a very high security level.
The security of the security team
has never been solved.
If you have leaked the password,
I can't help but suspect you.
Yes!
Wu Tian,
you are insulting me.
This password is my life-long wish.
Why would I leak it?
It's my honor.
It's your trap.
You broke my heart.
For your sake,
I have to ask you and Zai Jiang
to talk to the trap.
Yes!
Yes, sir!
Take him away!
Wait!
Woo
We lost the alcohol tip.
Thank you.
Here,
as a thanks to your hard work.
I swear in the name of my adoptive father,
I never did anything wrong
to betray the Empire of Japan.
The Eastern Plains is under the Great Wall.
The Eastern Plains?
That's the side of the Heavenly Emperor.
You have such a dangerous background.
You didn't tell me.
I didn't tell you.
I never heard of it.
What does the Eastern Plains have to do with it?
Chief Wu Tian.
Do you really think that if there is no such relationship,
I would come to Shanghai
and help you work?
What kind of identity does my adoptive father have?
Do I have to inform you
about my adoptive father?
I will tell you these things.
I will verify it.
Verify it?
I am here to save the seven princes and mission
of the Eastern Plains.
I came here to work for you.
Now,
you suspect my loyalty.
This is not only a humiliation to me,
but also a humiliation to my adoptive father.
Mr. Li.
I don't need you to
insult the Eastern Plains.
Okay.
Don't you want to verify it?
No problem.
I will give you a chance to verify it.
Now,
send a message
to blow up
the Chinese troops around Shanghai.
If the enemy's military camp
doesn't react,
we will all be happy.
You will not lose anything.
On the contrary,
if it is confirmed
that my password has been leaked,
you still have time to make up for it.
Otherwise,
all the losses in the future of the Great Japanese Empire
will be on your head.
át
Captain.
His greater good is busy in the law firm.
Today,
he is going to move out of Eastern Plains.
He has no face to sit back
over the absurdities.
clockwise
lan tastes.
and blown out your lips,
and then stock it up with words 一
because your house is也,
and people call me the ''Mirror'',
and fool the way you think I am,
with that one chance,
there must be another meaning.
You guys gonna get out of here and get laid,
or we will go to C Doll,
to hell?
If the dollar
Here.
You're a good actor.
How can you make the audience believe
that you're acting?
Jiaxi Acupuncture.
You're a student.
Be careful, Chief Wu Tian.
Okay.
Are you okay?
Let's go.
Take her out.
Yes.
Let's go.
Our men will be waiting for us under the window.
Jiaxi Acupuncture.
Mother!
What happened?
Mr. Li, I'm sorry.
I didn't protect you.
Chief Wu Tian.
What are you doing?
Call an ambulance.
Chief.
It seems like a military operation.
And...
We found this one.
It's a military operation.
Chief Wu Tian.
There's no evidence.
This service officer
was sent by the military to assassinate Mr. Li.
Mr. Li did his best
to serve the Japanese Empire.
Chief Wu Tian,
don't you believe in Mr. Li?
It's really a small accident.
Call an ambulance.
Chief Wu Tian.
Mr. Li is a friend of the Japanese Empire.
He almost died in the hands of the anti-Japanese.
If anything happens to him today,
who can take the responsibility?
Chief.
What you found here
is my responsibility.
Wait here.
Hey.
Take care of this guy.
Chief.
Tell Chief Aota.
Chief Aota.
I have a favor to ask.
Please.
Chief Aota.
I have a favor to ask.
Please.
Chief Aota.
I have a favor to ask.
Please.
Chief Aota.
I have a favor to ask.
Please.
Chief Aota.
I have a favor to ask.
Please.
Chief Aota.
I have a favor to ask.
Yes, this is Bakuda.
Chief Takeda has ordered the Air Force No. 1 and No. 3
to take off.
Unfortunately,
the People's Army 405 has taken off at 8 o'clock.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
I've been working for you
for thousands of years
and I've been suspected
by you three times.
Today,
I'm in such a mess.
I'm blind.
Yes.
Mr. Li is right.
What we did was wrong.
We have to prove that we suspect everyone.
Mr. Li.
I'll send you to the hospital.
You can go back to work.
Yes.
Yes, this is Kobayashi.
Chief.
What?
The air force warning was also issued
from the headquarters of the Communist Party.
Yes.
Get on the ambulance quickly.
Mr. Li, there is a step.
I ask you to take care of Lisa.
Yes.
Please.
Thank you.
Yes.
Please.
Thank you.
Did you arrange
tonight's event in advance?
Why didn't you tell me in advance?
I'm afraid that Wu Tian won't believe you.
So I arranged this.
If I'm honest,
Wu Tian won't believe you.
We did this
for your own good.
For my own good?
You let Lao Gu die?
Kobayashi, you don't believe me.
Why did you let me do this?
Now it's okay.
You don't trust me.
That's why you killed Lao Gu.
Kobayashi, are you still human?
Do you think I would let
Lao Gu die?
You are a soldier.
But he is my family.
I can't stop him from going to the battlefield.
But who would let his family
to send him to death?
No.
This is absolutely not right.
I said, don't persuade me.
Master,
you are not suitable.
I will go.
You go?
Is your leg suitable?
Don't hesitate.
This is the best way.
Don't forget,
I'm not only a soldier,
but also a soldier of the Gu family.
If your identity is exposed,
Ding will die.
He needs you more.
I will go.
Master Gu,
how about this?
After we talk,
I will put you in the window.
Then I will push you down.
Our people will come to pick you up.
When they get to you,
I will send you to your mother's ship.
I will go to the ship.
I will come to you.
Today's plan is
after Uncle Gu's death,
Ding will jump off the second floor.
Those who are in front of him
will send him to the dock
and leave immediately.
We have already discussed this.
But why didn't he do anything?
He promised me.
But Ding, I tell you,
tonight's plan,
we never thought of letting you die.
I promised you,
if there is danger,
I will stand in front of you.
I will never lie to you.
ас
One, two, three, jump!
Come here!
Get away...
I'm sorry.
Look at him. Look at him.
Slow down.
Come on.
Is Gu
my comrade?
Comrade Xiao,
Wu Tian is a man of many words.
Ding Yi's combat experience is not rich enough.
I'm afraid that
if Ding Yi can't convince Wu Tian,
I decided to leave a good hand for him.
I need to kill Li Yueze at the banquet.
I can make the Japanese believe in Li Yueze's loyalty.
Only then will they not doubt Ding Yi's words.
I know this is a dead end.
But Li Yueze's secret is not out for a day.
Thousands of miles of land will be destroyed.
I've been a
husband and wife for years
with Gu Zhengze.
Now it's a dead end.
If I can make the most of it
when the country is in danger,
I will die in Wuhan.
Please forgive my late-battle report.
Ding Yi
is a good boy.
Let me
see him off again.
My dear comrades,
goodbye.
This is the cherry tree
that I brought from Kyoto.
The cherry trees in Japan
are very beautiful
and beautiful.
The cherry trees in Japan
are very beautiful
and beautiful.
The cherry trees in Japan
are very beautiful
and beautiful.
But the cherry trees in Japan
are not suitable for China.
I don't think so.
But if you grow them properly,
the cherry trees in Japan
will be able to bloom in China.
Takeda Kenjiro
came to say goodbye
to Colonel Sasaki.
Takeda Kenjiro
did you do something wrong?
I found the code of Ryuesawa
in my own room.
I will take responsibility
for the failure of the information battle.
I see.
The information battle
was developed by a team
that handled the information
and the information.
But it was all wasted.
I am very sorry.
I was incompetent.
I will take the blame
and make amends.
Takeda Kenjiro
Bushido's spirit looks great,
but
even if you die,
you can't take it back.
It's easy to die.
What you should do
is to live and atone for your sins.
I was worried
that Ryuesawa
had a problem with his money.
But he said
he was a good son of the late Emperor.
And he also has a picture
of the late Emperor
holding him when he was young.
We can easily question
the reason for his death.
His father
was a math teacher
of the late Emperor.
When the Emperor recommended him,
he had already been tested.
I wonder if he is a good son.
If you say so,
I will say so.
If you can't do it,
let other people do it.
In China,
there is no emperor
like the Emperor of Japan.
Each person acts on his own.
Each person has his own secrets.
Each person has his own way of thinking.
To get along with them,
you need skills.
You have to have the will and the will.
You need to be able to
use your friends in China.
So you are asking the Chinese
to find out about the Chinese?
There is a Chinese saying
called the zhó shán guán fú dō.
Zhó shán guán fú dō.
If you change the password,
you will be safe.
Yes, I am safe.
Have you eaten?
I will order some breakfast.
Don't bother.
We don't know the relationship
between Dongyuan Temple and Li Yue Se.
It won't take long
before they will take the boat.
So I arranged
to send you to Hong Kong
by tonight's boat.
There are people
who will pick you up at Wanwang Lake.
You will meet in Hong Kong.
That's all?
The show is over.
Everyone is gone.
Why? Are you unhappy?
I am not unhappy.
I am happy.
Maybe there is
a bigger stage waiting for me.
Here, this is your passport.
Take it.
The money is in the box.
It should be enough for you to relax for a while.
I wish you can play your favorite role
on the new stage.
What are you doing?
I am going to the stage.
I have to say goodbye to everyone.
The organization has agreed
to let the people of the troupe leave first.
I have already told everyone
that tomorrow, in the name of the show,
they will go to the countryside
to take a break.
They will come back
after the show is over.
Where are you going?
I am going to the troupe
to talk to Miss Xian.
We have achieved great success this time.
The Japanese and the military
must have been watching us.
Before we get caught in trouble,
we will leave after the show tonight.
Let's go.
Bi Yu,
I understand your feelings.
After all, you created this troupe.
You don't want to see it destroyed in your hands.
But,
since we agreed to help Ding Yi,
you should have this psychological preparation.
Besides,
as long as we protect these members,
one day,
we will form a new troupe.
The foreigners are here.
The street is getting more and more dangerous.
There is our base near Kunshan.
It should be able to guarantee everyone's safety.
You go to Ding Yi
and tell him to leave with the troupe.
Also,
Hong Yu's application for membership
can also improve the popularity.
Okay.
Yu Yun!
You are...
so popular.
Is Miss Xian Bingbing here?
Who is this woman?
Ye Ying.
Ye Ying?
I know.
She is the wife of Liang Jiyuan, the commander of Suzhou.
Chief,
the Crown Prince...
The other day,
the wife of Liang Jiyuan,
the commander of Suzhou,
Ye Ying,
told us that
our information was already leaked.
Did she tell you anything about that information?
She told us that
the same information was leaked from the British.
I took her to the dance hall
where the chairman of William's company was present
and told the Japanese
that the information was leaked.
I heard that
the information that Li Yunse designed for the Japanese
was already leaked to the British.
Really?
So I was thinking,
if you could tell the Chairman Wang
about this information,
maybe your Liang Jiyuan would come back.
That's a good idea!
Many years ago, I saved Liang Jiyuan's life.
But he didn't know my real identity.
Now that I look at it,
he might be sent to the Special Forces headquarters.
Maybe it's a good chance
to get Ye Ying's information.
Shen Wei was also close to the British.
That night,
after the DUSR went to Chaoshan District,
everything started to go wrong.
I should have investigated him sooner.
But do you think
we should allow the DUSR
to investigate her?
We should let the people of the department
investigate Chaoshan District.
Including Shen Wei himself.
Wait.
Liang Jiyuan
was probably
trying to get into the role of the new government.
If he can make this clear,
tell Ye Ying
that he will give her the right to be satisfied.
Yes.
Miss Jiang, the guests are here.
Mr. Xia.
Mrs. Liang is here.
You brought so many gifts.
It's my duty.
You're a big star.
You're still playing the game?
It's not over yet.
You're a big family.
You don't understand the game?
It's my first time to come to the forum.
It's interesting.
And you guys
are really good.
What's so happy about?
Come in and talk.
Sit.
I'll do it.
Thank you.
Remember the Japanese password?
I didn't believe it when I told the Japanese.
I said,
our password
is very high-level.
It's impossible to leak.
You're out of your mind.
But
how did you know
such a secret from the British?
Look at what you said.
It's like our two families are selling drugs.
You have to ask our ancestral secret recipe.
Is it appropriate?
That's what Mr. Liang said.
But we're very regular.
The Japanese said
it was from the British.
I didn't mention a word about you.
There's another thing today.
Look, I've been away from Shanghai for so long.
What's the trend in Shanghai now?
I don't know.
Are you free today?
Go for a ride with me.
Not today.
Look at my big table.
I can't even finish it.
I'm also planning to do it.
It's not a day's difference.
Okay.
Next time,
I'll have a good time with you next time.
Next time, no.
I'm going back to Shanghai.
You're going back to Shanghai?
Congratulations, Liang.
The Chinese newspaper is selling the newspaper.
Please contact me immediately.
The news is on.
Yes.
The Chaosheng Group.
Yes, there is such a place.
Don't worry, Tai Jun.
As long as you have the money,
it's easy.
Come together now.
Yes.
Get ready to go.
You're the best.
Is there something wrong with these guys?
They're so fast.
Hurry up.
Brother Huang.
Poor brother Huang.
I won't leave you again.
I want you to leave him.
I don't want you to be together.
You're so unfilial.
No.
Let go of me.
Get in.
Dad.
Stop.
Don't move.
What's going on?
What are you doing?
Director, you're acting again.
Brother.
You're all so naughty.
You're so rude.
We're rehearsing.
Don't make trouble.
Kill them.
Don't let them die.
Someone reported to the police.
Someone is hiding in the police station.
Search every corner and take them away.
Stop.
Dad.
Hongyu.
What should we do?
Dad.
Hongyu.
Listen to me.
The organization has arranged it.
You go to Kunshan by train tomorrow morning.
Go to the boss of the miracle pharmacy.
Tell him to send someone to pick us up.
Dad, what about you?
Don't mind us.
Let's go.
Come on.
Be careful.
Remember, miracle pharmacy.
What are you doing?
Take them away.
Yes.
Go.
Okay.
The pain in the eyes
The one who is pretending to be serious can't say it clearly
Where is the wind going
Whose window is shaking
The sound of the lock
The heart is thinking
It's either you or me
He is watching
In the vast night
Tears are floating
A bunch of broken wounds
He is looking
Wandering in the shadow
The night falls
Looking back at the world
The one who is pretending to be serious can't say it clearly
Where is the wind going
Whose window is shaking
The sound of the lock
The heart is thinking
It's either you or me
He is looking
Wandering in the shadow
The night falls
The heart is thinking
It's either you or me
He is watching
In the vast night