The Long Ballad
Episode 16
Gu Yangshan.
He has been working at the SID in Chongqing and the US for the past few years.
After he returned to Shanghai,
he did not participate in the real cleaning and cleaning of the property.
The Gu family is now in a difficult position.
Meng Mingyi is a famous traitor.
I'm afraid the Gu family can't handle this.
We should wait for the news from the organization.
There's no time to wait.
The SID wakes up at noon every day.
And Miss Meng is on the list of the group's wake-up calls.
Now, except for Gu Yangshan,
we all have no way to get Miss Meng out of the hands of the SID in one day.
Miss Meng saved my life several times.
I can't just watch her die like this.
But Gu Yangshan was so embarrassed when he left.
Are you sure he will see you?
I believe him.
Gu Yangshan
How is it going, mom?
Young Master,
the SID just came to say that they had been to the Meng family.
But there's no one there.
He's going to the SID to check
if Miss Meng has been arrested.
If you have any news, tell me right away.
And
a man with sunglasses is looking for you.
He said his surname is Ding.
He heard that Master was sick.
He asked me to give this to you.
He left.
Okay, mom, I got it. You can go ahead.
Gu Yangshan
Where's Chief Cao?
He just went out.
How is Commander Gu?
He's fine.
Chief Dai and Chief Mao Fu
are very concerned about Commander Gu's health.
They all said they were going to visit the east gate.
I'm afraid I'll bother Commander Gu.
Tell them to call me as soon as they see you.
It's not a good thing.
I want to ask you.
What's going on with this list?
The country knows its enemies.
We have to kill them.
Is there a problem?
No problem.
If it's really a traitor, he should be killed.
But Meng Jie is a public official who did this.
Why did he appear on this list?
Gu Yangshan
You forgot.
The senior officials have already decided.
Our assassination operation has failed.
A failed operation is not a public official.
As the son of Commander Gu
you've been a great man for so many years.
Why are you still a public official?
Isn't it because you have a great influence
during your work in Shanghai?
Now Commander Gu has retired.
You must not investigate his relationship with the traitors.
Besides
his father died.
It's of no value to you.
Why do you want to be your own future for him?
It must be valuable
to live.
Otherwise
why did you think everyone
didn't save me
and care about Liang Jinyuan?
Where did you get this?
It looks like a candy bite.
You dug it out yourself?
You never listen to me.
You should ask Commander Cao
about these books and paintings.
You know
I'm not interested in these things.
I'm sorry.
Long time no see.
I meant to see you.
In front of me.
You were in this room.
As soon as you came in
you wanted to fight me.
Yes.
But these five years
you've changed a lot.
You haven't changed at all
these five years.
Really?
Here you are.
I'll do it in a few days.
I'll keep the position
of the groom for you.
Come on.
You finally got what you wanted.
Congratulations.
But before the wedding
you have to save Miss Meng first.
Saving Miss Meng
is your party's idea, right?
No.
It's my wife's idea.
She said Miss Meng is our benefactor.
So she has to be there on the wedding day.
All right.
Don't lie to me.
Your people have been in touch with me these years.
I can tell if you're acting.
Besides, the list of stars of the Sujian Security Council
will not be public.
So if no one reports to you
how can you know the time?
Don't ask me
who provided me with the information.
Even if you wear a headscarf
and tie me to the ten yellow fish outside the Meixin Theater,
I won't tell you a word.
All right.
But no matter who it is,
thank him for me.
Actually, I know why you went to the orphanage to find me.
But the Gu family now
is not as good as before.
I just went to Shanghai station
and bumped into a soft nail.
So it's not as easy as I thought to save Miss Meng.
But you have a way out, right?
Yes.
But I need your help.
Of course.
I saw a light-colored bottle of Tang Yue Yao in Mr. Cao's office today.
It's worth a lot.
And I happened to see this bottle in Meng's house many years ago.
Today it suddenly appeared in Shanghai station.
It must be Mr. Cao's name for cleaning up the miscarriage.
He's going to report to the police and take the blame.
I'm sorry.
If there is one, there will be a second and a third.
Mr. Cao.
But the security of the warehouse of the miscarriage committee
is managed by the Commander of the Shanghai Command.
Liu Changdong, who is currently working as the commander,
is my father's old uncle.
I'll let him get the evidence.
So next, it's up to you.
What do you need us to do?
Report it.
I know that your party's emergency services are very influential in Shanghai.
Now is the critical moment for the formal two parties to negotiate.
The Chief of Staff is about to kill Ji Jinghou.
So once he knows the evidence of the miscarriage committee and Su Jian Committee's joint corruption,
he will be able to force the criminal to re-examine.
Do you know what you're talking about?
I know.
We still have 12 hours.
The Meteorological Bureau should be on the way to send the photos.
I'll have to trouble you to give the photos to your superior later.
And ask them to send the photos to the newspaper.
So, at six in the morning,
I think these photos will spread across the streets of Shanghai.
If nothing goes wrong, I guess at around ten o'clock,
someone will call the Chief of Staff in Shanghai.
I've always seen your party's work.
I think you can do it.
If you let them know you're doing this,
it's treason.
I'm sorry.
But the ones who betrayed the three-democracy first
were them.
I was wrong just now.
You've changed over the past five years.
And you've changed a lot.
I don't care about my father's will to leave.
I can finally walk the same path as you.
I've always been on the wrong path.
If I don't turn around,
I'll die alone in the desert of life.
No one will shed tears for me.
I'm sorry.
Father!
My daughter.
Call me Father now!
When I was helping a Japanese,
so many of my fellow men
died in the desert of life.
They were all killed.
I'm sorry.
Father!
I've helped a Chinese.
I've helped a Japanese.
Father, you went to ask Brother Shi.
You went to find Brother Shi.
He helped me.
I didn't lie to you.
You helped a Japanese.
I helped a Japanese.
I was in the front line, bleeding.
You were still with your father.
I was still with my father.
You were still with your brother.
You were still in the house of San Yang.
That's what a Japanese is.
What am I?
No!
You're mistaken.
I'm really helping them.
I'm helping a man named Li Yue Sen.
I'm helping him to cover up.
He has a wife named Xian Biyun.
They are all Japanese.
I didn't lie to you.
Li Yue Sen and Xian Biyun are communists.
If that's true,
you're not only foreign,
but also a communist.
I didn't.
Girl.
Girl, don't say it.
I'm sorry.
I've caused you trouble.
Dad.
Dad!
Stop!
What are you doing, Gu Yaoshan?
Dad!
You killed her father
in front of her.
Do you have any humanity?
Foreign traitors,
pig dogs,
do you still want to find a place?
Shoot!
Brother,
don't move.
Gu Yaoshan,
do you want to stop the law?
I'm telling you,
Mengjie, I have to take her away today.
Then try it.
Come on.
Shoot.
You try it too.
Chief Lu.
We just received
the special order from the chief.
He asked us to review these orders
in public.
To stop all the cases,
we immediately stop the execution.
It's okay.
These days,
you are the one who always has to suffer.
I will help you with the preparation
of the material to be sent to the court.
Get in the car.
I'm going to fight him déadeole Frost Dragon Hurts
F bu
No!
Mengjie
Let me go
Luo, look at this
Two days ago
We just checked the Meng family's property
Today, these red items
say that we are loyal and honest
And you said that Su Jian
and Wei Yan Gui
beat Zhongliang into traitors
just to take away
their property
Isn't that ridiculous?
I'm going to check this newspaper
What's the use of checking it now?
They have solid evidence
Take a good look at the photos
We wanted to show our faces
but we didn't expect to show our asses
Aren't you ashamed?
We are not going to show our real property
We are going to show our real property
How did they get the photos
of the property committee?
Vice-President, we are in Shanghai
When will the mayor of Shanghai
take the responsibility
and give us a beating?
And the Communist Party
doesn't know about it?
I don't understand
How did you find me?
Report
Come in
Deputy Chief
We sent people to follow Meng Ni
and we got the photos
Please have a look
But they are very cautious
Our people
are lost
It's really him
We got it
Yes
I guessed it right
The person who did this
is not only the Communist Party
but also a thief
How is it?
I only got the medicine
after taking the medicine
I just fell asleep
The best psychiatrist
is in Chaosheng Group now
I'll get him back right away
You were just passing by
Luo Han will not be afraid
And I guess
Chaosheng Group is not necessarily safe
How about this
You take Miss Xian and these doctors
to our house
No one dare to search the
Imperial Museum until now
No, these doctors
are very sensitive
We can't give you any trouble
When you helped me
I was afraid of trouble
It's different
We were barefoot
But now
you are in your home
We can't let your family take the risk
Right
It's different
But now we are on the same path
Tomorrow
I will send my father to London
to see a doctor
By then
I won't have any trouble
It's settled
Listen to me
Tonight I will let the Meteorological Bureau cover you
Okay
Then do as you say
Wait for me
to send Bi Yun and these doctors
back to Shanghai safely
Why do you have to come back?
I have to go
This is my task
To send all the doctors
back to Shanghai safely
But now
There are still some people
who can't be found
I can't leave
Dingyi, you should know
You are more dangerous than these people
Luo Hai has killed Hu Yan
If he finds you
He wants to kill you
He doesn't need to wait for him to go to the city
That's why I need your help
Call me when necessary
You must do it
I must
You are just a moth
You haven't changed for five years
You used to help Miss Xian without my knowledge
Now you are helping me without Miss Xian's knowledge
Does Miss Xian know?
I can't let her know
Don't tell her
Or she will be angry
and will kill herself
It's annoying
I want to know
How to deal with you after knowing your plan
By the way
Do you remember
When we were in Sanyang
On my birthday
We took a picture together
Yes
Today is such a happy day
Let's take a picture together
To remember
Miss Xian
Stand in the middle
Just leave me a part
I will take care of you
The Chinese Communist Party is going to be defeated
On September 30th
The Nationalist Party Han De
issued a warrant
to arrest all members of the Communist Party
and execute them all
The Nationalist Party Han De
I have to
close the camera
in advance
Clean up the mess
Don't let them know we are here
We will leave after we finish the cleaning
The New Year's Eve
Come on
Father
London is often rainy
I prepared more clothes for you
The doctor has contacted the authorities
and ordered them to Wang Ma
Don't worry
You really don't want to go
I will go with me
Yangshan has something to do
We haven't done it yet
We will go to London after we finish
This is the property of our Gu family
The anti-Japanese army used it
and now it's back
I think you are not even
a member of the government
You don't need it
I will give it to the government with my own hands
The New Year's Eve
I will invite you to come home
for tea tomorrow
Father
Is this because I saved Miss Meng?
Liang Hongzhi's house
is for the White Dragon
Chen Gongbo's house is for Dean Song
Luo Hongyi's property
is for Gu Zhutong
Even your Juntongju Shanghai Station
is now
an old and desolate property
If you want to live on the other's land
you have to follow the rules
I will come
Father
You told me since I was a child
My grandfather and my uncles
were defeated in the Great Revolution
for the sake of China
My uncles
were defeated in the Northern France
for the sake of China
and for the sake of unification
and for peace
for the sake of the anti-Japanese
and for the sake of the anti-Japanese
Our family has been
passionate about the Three Jewels
not for the sake of these rules
Then what are you going to do?
Father
I think
someone should stand up
and create a new rule
I think
I should stand up
It seems that you have been in Shanghai
for a long time
and you have made good friends
The Three Jewels
are the path I want you to take
But now it seems
you have your own path
Father
Your friend
He is here
They are very cautious
They have left our eyes
shortly after we got off the car
But from the map
the two stations they got off
are very close
They are very close
I have buried people around
I can wait for them to show up
This is
Nanyang Road
Gu's Mansion
Take your people away
and follow me to search Gu's Mansion
Gu's Mansion?
Yes
Inform Deputy Chief Mao
to tell him
I have got new evidence
The Communist Party
is hiding in Gu's Mansion
and ask him to issue a search warrant
But
There is no evidence
The
investigation is in his hands
If we can't find him
the consequences
will be my responsibility
Anyway
I can't let Ding Yi and Gu Yanshan go
Ok
It's settled
Miss Xie
Please don't talk
I have contacted all of them
Liu Jinzhi will drive
the police car
to come here tonight
After you finish the meeting
no one will stop you
Thank you
Don't say that
I should thank you
Dr. Lin
has finished the interview
with Mengjie
He said he was shocked
and was very emotional
and he couldn't say
he was separated from his family
But
we need to confirm it
before we know it
Well
I haven't asked you
how Gu Silin is doing
before I came
Gan'ai
told me
that my father had a
long-standing illness
and he refused to go to the hospital
I'm sorry
My father's life
was a revolution
but he ended up
living a life of
exile
What about you?
What's your plan?
I miss you
Ding Yi has missed you
He knew you were back in Chongqing
and was studying the code of the
Because he was lucky
and you took him
to the right path
I believe if I was in his position
I would have made
the same choice
It's a pity
I fixed the camera
Let's go
Sit
It's the same as before
I have to follow you
I want to see
who can run away
today
OK
Come
Look here
Smile
One, two, three
What the hell?
What a bad camera
I've been fixing it for a long time
I fixed it
How to use it?
No, no, no
I'm telling you
I'm collecting the camera
not for taking pictures
Young Master
What's wrong?
Something happened
They said they were going to search for Gu's
What are you doing?
Don't move
Who are you?
Let's do this
You take the guest in and wait
I'll deal with it
Be careful
You go in too
This is my house
I can't let them in
You go in first
Young Master, you take them in first
Since they are here
They are Gu's guests
Gu family
doesn't have the principle
to push guests out
Let Quan handle the outside
You follow me
Go
Long Han
Why did you bring so many people to my house?
Sorry to bother you
I have something to do
What?
I suspect you are hiding traitors
Director Mao has been approved by the committee
He ordered me to search all Gu's properties
Including Gu's Palace
You mean our family
is hiding traitors?
And you have been approved by the committee
to search our house
What about the approval?
What about the search certificate?
I know you are the deputy director
You have a job
It's normal
I can let you lock up our house
But you can only enter our house
If they want to enter
You have to think about the consequences
I'll decide the consequences
Go
Yes
You are so rude
Let me go
Sorry
I thought I would kill you
Who wants to try?
You are traitors
after you shoot us
You can't search our house
Take out your guns
I tell you
If anyone shoots you
You will be hurt
Who?
Young master
Master said
Please let me in
Master
Commander Gu
Sorry
Young master
Since you have a job
Let me search
I have no shame
I have no one to see
I will listen to the party's trial
Yes
I have no one to see
I will listen to the party's trial
Yes
Then I'll let you go
Go
Yes
Close all documents
Take them back
Yes
Yangshan
We are fine here
Take me to the yard
Yes
When you I'm turning blind
Looking
Nights long trash
White smoke
And the wounds flat
Looking
And the streetlights
coming and falling
Looking back, it's still dawn
Lying in the watch
In the vast night
Tears are floating
A wound that has fallen
Lying in the watch
Wandering in the shadow
The night is dark
Looking back, it's still dawn
Lying in the watch