Your Highness.
Your Highness!
Lord Gongsun
has sent a message—
at tonight's royal family banquet,
he has
arranged for a poisoner.
The poison is
Death Powder,
mixed with
Heart-Severing Grass,
and
Thunder God Vine,
and arsenic,
and...
What was it again?
Yes.
Anyway,
he'll be dead for sure!
Even God himself couldn't save him!
Feng Mochen, oh, Feng Mochen.
What a pity.
Working so hard every day.
The more I sleep, the more tired and weak I become!
I must be dreaming again...
There's no way I'm really inside this body!
I need to wake up now!
Wake up now! Wake up!
Stop!
I don't need your concern.
I don't care about you.
I just care that if this handsome body of mine gets scarred,
I won't know what to do.
You demon!
What sorcery have you cast?
Change us back immediately!
Are you...
having a fit?
I'm casting a spell.
Why isn't anything happening?
You think just waving your hands around
will make things appear?
How could that be possible?
I get it now.
You're in my physical body,
so you have my cultivation and technique.
I'm in your physical body,
so I've gained your...
dull-wittedness.
So that means...
I can control wind and rain now?
Mm.
Cool!
♪ A fox demon's body,
but a human soul within ♪
♪ When spells go awry,
heaven and earth tremble ♪
♪ The left hand summons clouds,
while the right commands rain ♪
♪ Unstoppable power,
overturning the ocean's reign ♪
♪ Chant in haste, shout with force ♪
♪ When spells falter,
time and space twist off course ♪
♪ The Nine-tailed Fox is confused,
while Xiangjiu laughs ♪
♪ All creatures gather for a wild dance ♪
♪ Magic rises ♪
♪ But spirals out of control ♪
♪ Randomly summoning things from the sky
leaves the Nine-tailed Fox speechless ♪
♪ Time and space twist off course ♪
♪ You should be more careful ♪
♪ Even Heaven does not know ♪
♪ What will fall next ♪
What is this?
This is...
Looks like
you're not all-knowing after all.
How could I not know this?
This is...
a fish tank.
It's a fish tank?
The fishing rod.
Really impressive.
Impressive.
No, no, don't!
Casting spells requires unity of mind and intent.
You're a mortal after all.
Reckless spellcasting will severely damage your vital energy.
If things go wrong,
it could be fatal.
That serious?
I'll find a way
to switch us back as soon as possible.
If you want your body back,
first hand over my dad!
Your dad?
My dad secretly entered the palace to meet the Emperor two years ago.
After that, there was no news of him.
He just disappeared.
I heard
that some palace maids disappeared from Fucang Palace.
You must be behind that.
So what if it was me?
And what if it wasn't?
If I die,
your powers disappear with me.
Hand over my dad now!
You dare threaten me?
I am openly
and blatantly threatening you.
And what if I refuse?
That powerful?
You!
Are you having fun?
Yeah.
Hand over my dad now!
When did your dad enter the palace to meet the Emperor?
If he entered Ganquan Palace,
there must be a record in the Ganquan Register.
I found the date.
But you tore out the two pages around that date ages ago.
You just wanted to secretly erase
the traces of my dad meeting the Emperor.
Where did Xiangjiu go?
How could she disappear for no reason?
Could it be...
that wily fox took her?
Third Uncle!
Third Uncle,
get up.
Time to work.
His Majesty and the others will arrive soon!
Hurry up.
My dear nephew,
can't you do the work without me?
No.
Third Uncle,
the Chief assigned this task to both of us.
How can I manage it all by myself?
The Chief is so old now.
He doesn't have much time left.
Who do you think the chief steward position will go to in the future?
I'm your third uncle.
Would I compete against you?
If you want the position,
shouldn't you prove yourself?
If the Chief finds out
that you managed the royal family banquet alone,
wouldn't he
see you in a new light?
When that time comes,
the chief steward position...
will be none other than yours.
Third Uncle,
your words
are like a revelation!
Well then,
I'll do all the work myself.
You can just show up later, for appearances.
I'm off!
Where on earth did Xiangjiu go?
You sly old fox.
I don't trust you one bit!
Hand over my dad now!
Aren't you afraid
I'll eat you?
You wouldn't dare.
Watch it.
You're using my body!
It's dislocated.
Bear with it.
Master!
It's time for the royal family banquet!
Mao Jin, you may leave first.
I'll be there shortly.
Insolent!
You reckless maid, who do you think you are?
How dare you order me around as if you were my master?
No manners!
This is outrageous!
Look carefully.
Can't you recognize me?
Master.
Who is she?
She won't even look at me properly!
You pride yourself on being a loyal dog,
yet you can't even recognize your own master?
Xiangjiu loved apples when she was little.
Third Uncle,
you mustn't.
These are for the royal family banquet.
Look,
there are five apples here,
representing the five blessings.
Taking one away would break the blessing.
What do you know?
I'm doing this for your own good.
His Majesty likes things to be auspicious.
Four apples mean "all wishes fulfilled."
When His Majesty sees this, he will surely
reward you generously.
"All wishes fulfilled."
That actually makes sense.
When Xiangjiu sees this,
she'll be very happy.
I...
-Greetings, Princess Ningshuang.
Attendant Bai, you're quite bold,
even daring to steal fruit from the royal family banquet.
This servant wouldn't dare.
This servant
only noticed there was
a wormhole in this fruit.
I was worried it would displease His Majesty,
so I took it.
Where is the wormhole?
It's right...
Darn it,
what a coincidence.
Your Highness's arrow went right through the wormhole!
Your Highness's archery is truly exceptional—
like Li Guang of our time,
Hou Yi reincarnated!
Having a princess like you
is truly our kingdom's great fortune
and a blessing for all citizens!
Yes, indeed!
Our kingdom's fortune!
The citizens' blessing!
Right?
-Our kingdom's fortune.
-The citizens' blessing.
Attendant Bai,
don't think you can distract me with flattery.
This fruit
was carefully selected by the palace servants.
If you say there's a wormhole on it,
then I'll find those servants
and punish them.
Your Highness,
every year, the palace is extremely busy preparing for the royal family banquet.
It's hard work for them.
Even if there are some mistakes,
they're understandable.
Madam Chen, you're so considerate of us servants.
It's truly a blessing for us.
So you're making veiled accusations,
implying that I'm not considerate of you?
Your Highness is overthinking this.
This servant wouldn't dare.
Attendant Bai, then
you're saying I'm paranoid.
Your Highness,
please forgive this servant for my poor choice of words.
Please have an apple
and calm down.
Outrageous.
Father!
Father.
Who!
Who's so blind
as to throw apples around?
Lord Gongsun!
How could you insult Her Highness Princess Ningshuang?
Ning...
What a great throw!
So it was Your Highness who threw it.
I must say,
after that apple hit me,
I
suddenly felt refreshed
and full of energy.
Thank you, Your Highness.
This is a family banquet.
Lord Gongsun,
why are you here?
Don't tell me Father
has adopted you as his son.
It was His Majesty
who ordered me to attend the banquet with my son.
Your son
is entering the palace for the first time, right?
Yes.
Tell your son
that the palace is heavily guarded—
he must not wander around carelessly,
lest he stumble into forbidden areas
and lose his head.
This minister will remember.
Ningshuang!
How can you speak like that to an important court official?
Greetings to Your Highnesses the Crown Prince and the Princess Consort.
Your Highness,
quickly greet His Highness and Her Highness.
So many people are greeting them already.
One less greeting from me
won't hurt them.
Madam Chen,
forget it.
Let her be.
My sister
has been spoiled by Father since childhood.
It's not Her Highness's fault.
It's all this old servant's failing.
Madam Chen, don't say that.
Ningshuang didn't grow up by Mother's side.
Thanks to you, her wet nurse, for taking such good care of her.
Your Highness is too kind.
This is all this old servant's blessing.
Ningshuang,
it doesn't matter how you treat me.
But when Lord Feng arrives,
you should restrain yourself.
Lord Feng won't indulge you as we do.
I don't know what methods he used
to make Father trust him so much.
You're afraid of him,
but I'm not.
When he arrives,
I'll show him who's boss.
I'd like to see what he can do to me.
How could this happen?
What should we do now?
Mas...
Master.
I want my dad.
Where have you been hiding my dad?
Why are you asking my master
where your dad is?
He took my dad.
My master doesn't need another dad.
Why would he capture yours?
Then why did he tear out these two pages from the Ganquan Register?
My master treasures books above all else.
He would never tear them carelessly.
Moreover, the Ganquan Register
documents the Emperor's...
Give it to me!
The Ganquan Register documents
the Emperor's summons of his ministers to Ganquan Palace.
How could anyone tear it up at will?
There is indeed a strange fragrance on this book.
Master.
I only smell ink.
Impossible.
Your sense of smell is even better than mine.
How could you not smell it?
Useless people say useless things.
Worthless things just yap.
Of course, a book only smells of ink.
What other scent could there be?
There really is a fragrance.
You can smell it?
It's very obvious.
Different from your scent.
I told you, it couldn't have been my master's doing!
Looks like...
you've even acquired my sense of smell.
That's right.
Foxes have keen senses of smell.
But why can you smell it too?
Focus your attention
and direct your intention toward him.
I'm not telling you to strain your eyes.
It's about your mind.
Clear your mind of distractions.
Unite your thoughts and intent.
You're a mutt!
I'm a dog.
I'm a
Chinese Pastoral Dog!
What's the difference between a mutt and a dog?
They're definitely different!
Would you dare call the Lord Howling Celestial Dog a mutt?
My dad's disappearance
really has nothing to do with you?
If you waste your energy on me,
you'll never find your father.
In that case,
I'll have to go ask the Emperor myself
what exactly happened that day.
It's useless.
The Emperor's memory is very poor now.
He forgets even what just happened,
let alone something from two years ago.
What am I supposed to do now?
Mao Jin,
do you know who has this scent?
This scent...
does seem familiar.
I think I've smelled it in the palace before.
Who was it?
I can't
remember clearly.
No.
You have to remember.
There are so many people in the palace.
How am I supposed to find them?
Don't worry.
Only a handful of people in the palace are qualified to burn incense.
Right!
Usually, only those of high status burn incense!
Oh.
Tonight's the royal family banquet.
Everyone of rank in the palace will be there.
This is a good opportunity.
I'll know once I take a sniff.
Your manners and behavior
don't resemble mine at all.
Aren't you afraid of being exposed?
Doesn't seem so hard to me.
Why hasn't Lord Feng arrived yet?
How long do we have to wait?
What's the rush?
Mochen must be bathing and changing his clothes before coming.
That alone shows
how seriously he takes this family banquet.
Let's wait a bit longer.
Ningshuang.
-Greetings, Your Grace.
See?
I told you.
I wouldn't show any flaws.
Let's hope so.
You must always remember
you are the supreme Lord Feng above all others.
Such a nag.
Relax.
Nothing will go wrong.
Heaven-Mandated
Celestial Emperor
of Supreme Purity
and Ultimate...
He's not finished yet!
-Greetings, Your Grace.
Xiangjiu.
Let's go.
Mochen,
what's wrong with you?
What's...
What's wrong?
What are you doing?
I need to go back quickly,
or something bad will happen.
If you go back, that's when something bad will happen.
Let's go!
Bai Yu!
Lord Feng, you
seem rather unusual tonight.
Unusual,
very unusual.
His Majesty loves...
turtle soup!
It makes your skin glow,
lengthens your life,
and even helps you
sire more children!
Then I'll accept your good wishes.
May I have a few more sons.
Father.
Is Lord Feng usually like this?
He seems like a completely different person tonight.
Please, everyone, take your seats.
All the nobles are here.
So who exactly tore out those two pages from the Ganquan Register?
Mochen,
please take your seat too.
I need to find a way
to smell them.
Lord Feng,
could it be that you feel apologetic
for arriving late today?
Ningshuang,
watch your manners.
What?
Did I say something wrong?
I've got it!
That's right!
Indeed!
Princess Ningshuang is absolutely right!
I'm late.
I should indeed apologize.
Your Majesty,
may I propose a toast to everyone in turn
to express my apologies?
Very well, very well.
Mochen, it's rare for you to want to socialize with everyone.
I'd
be delighted.
Let go of me!
Bai Yu!
What are you doing?
It's all my fault.
I got you into this.
What are you talking about?
There are some things you may not know.
If I tell you,
I'm afraid it'll scare you.
Feng Mochen captured you
to get to me.
What?
See?
You're scared, aren't you?
He must know about our relationship.
So he's using you to threaten me.
What...
are we?
We were betrothed as children.
You're my Xiangjiu,
and I'm your Yu.
We were betrothed as children?
Bai Yu,
this engagement
is off.
Why?
I...
Xiangjiu.
How could you have such poor taste?
What's so good
about Feng Mochen?
He's plain-looking
and incredibly ugly!
Compared to me...
we're worlds apart.
What do you even see in him?
Plain-looking...
and incredibly ugly?
Of course.
Bai Yu!
Among all the men
I've ever seen,
Lord Feng's appearance
is unmatched.
His beauty
is rare in this world!
To be by his side
is the lifelong dream of countless women!
How could someone like you...
with such rat-eyed, shifty features, ever compare?
From now on,
don't mention yourself in the same breath as him,
lest you tarnish his name.
This is outrageous.
Calling me ugly?
What a sheltered brat.
Trash.
Could Xiangjiu
have been bewitched by Feng Mochen
and lost her senses?
Impossible.
No normal woman would leave me.
Could it be
that she knows about my feud with that wily fox
and doesn't want me trapped in hatred
or facing any danger,
so she's saying that on purpose?
I will never let that wily fox hurt you.
For you,
I'm willing to submit myself to him.
Is it really worth it,
just for me?
Yu,
you don't know how precious you are in this world.
You're handsome and dashing,
unrivaled under heaven.
You're gentle and considerate,
attentive to every detail,
and absolutely adorable.
You're funny...
Don't say any more.
I have so many merits.
You can't list them all.
Mm.
Yu.
Xiangjiu.
Yu!
Xiangjiu!
That's right.
It must be so.
A man
should never let his beloved woman get hurt.
Feng Mochen,
just you wait.
I'll destroy you with my own hands!
Then I'll first
toast to the Crown Prince and the Princess Consort.
To show my closeness,
I'll go over to drink with them.
Yes, yes, yes.
Fuying,
you should learn more from Lord Feng.
Look how good he is at getting close to people.
Yes, Father.
I'll keep it in mind.
I can tell
from the smell of this baijiu.
This is sauce-aroma baijiu!
Lord Feng...
You know your baijiu.
Come on, cheers.
Come on,
let's have another cup.
I'll drink...
the light-aroma type.
Cheers.
The Crown Prince smells so nice.
It's not him.
Come on,
Your Highness the Princess Consort.
Not her either.
Lord Feng, do you want to
whisper something to my consort?
You misunderstood.
It's...
It's like this.
I've recently been studying a technique
known as Scent Divination.
It's about
smelling a person's scent
to predict their fate.
Oh?
Such a technique exists?
Yes,
it's that magical!
Well then, Lord Feng,
tell us about the fortunes of the Crown Prince and his wife.
They're both
destined for wealth and honor.
Destined for wealth and honor!
Then...
smell Lord Gongsun and his son too.
Your Majesty,
there's
no need to smell us, right?
We're just enjoying ourselves.
It's all for fun.
Don't take it seriously.
I have to smell you.
Come on.
It's just for fun.
Let me smell you.
Ginseng, deer antler,
curculigo,
epimedium,
cynomorium,
cistanche,
more deer antler,
astragalus seeds,
morinda root,
and dodder seeds.
My goodness!
This old man
is taking way too many tonics.
Lord Gongsun...
Do take care not to overexert yourself.
Lord Feng, what do you mean by that?
I mean,
Lord Gongsun's body is...
robust.
This scent is so familiar.
I think I just smelled it.
It's not him.
Lord Feng, you're behaving like a dog.
Ningshuang,
watch your words.
This is the scent.
Why are their scents
so similar?
Could they possibly...
I wonder if that girl
will cause any trouble.
One Bam,
you went to relieve yourself
and were gone the whole day.
Did you fall into the latrine and eat your fill before coming back?
Was it tasty?
Are you full now,
huh?
How dare you!
One Bam,
you've grown quite bold!
I'll beat you to death today!
My hand...
My hand!
What a weak body.
One Bam,
you dare to mess with me?
I'll deal with you properly when we get back to the Imperial Servants Bureau!
Go!
Let go of me!
I'll teach you a lesson today!
Let go!
Mochen,
are you alright?
I'm not feeling very well.
Look at you,
you went to the latrine for a whole day!
You had me
searching everywhere for you!
I'll make you pay for this today!
I'll finish you off!
Damn One Bam?
One Bam?
I didn't...
I didn't even touch you.
Stop trying to frame me.
It's her.
Something happened to her.
One Bam?
Summon the royal physician now!
No need.
The old fox's body must have gone wrong.
I can't let anyone discover this.
I need to find him quickly.
But...
I haven't smelled Princess Ningshuang and the others yet.
Forget it.
There will be another chance.
Your Majesty,
I'm feeling unwell
and would like to take my leave
to rest.
Chief Steward Sun,
find someone to escort him back immediately.
Take good care of him.
There must not be the slightest mistake!
Yes, Your Majesty.
Attendant Bai!
Go follow His Grace now!
Yes.
Wily fox,
heaven truly has eyes.
This time, I'll settle things with you once and for all.
Old Fox,
where are you?
There really is a fragrance.
It's that scent.
Feng Mochen,
you never thought you'd end up like this, did you?
You've committed too many sins.
Even Heaven can't bear to watch anymore!
Yu...
Pah!
Disgusting.
How dare you call me "Yu"?
Help me chase...
You want me to help you chase after Huo Xiangjiu?
Dream on!
A truly loving couple
will never be easily separated!
Huo...
Huo Xiang...
jiu...
Your filthy mouth
doesn't deserve to speak such a sacred name!
Feng Mochen...
The thousand-year feud between my Bai Clan of Bronze County and you
ends here today!
Ancestors of the Bai Clan of Bronze County above,
I, Bai Yu, the 30th generation disciple,
am here to vanquish evil and protect our way!
By Heavenly Thunder, Earthly Fire,
Five Elements, and Six Harmonies—
vanquish evil and subdue demons!
Follow my command!