Your Grace, you've honored
my Ningshuang Palace with your presence.
What is it for?
Well...
You...
I...
I happened
to be passing by.
Your Grace, are you trying to seduce
Madam Chen?
Princess Ningshuang,
you have quite a sense of humor.
I'll take my leave now.
It's you!
What did you say?
Nothing.
Goodbye.
Don't move!
Well, One Bam,
now that you've caught
Attendant Bai's favor,
I wouldn't dare to treat you poorly.
So many!
These
are for you.
I don't like eating these things.
Do you have chicken?
Either drumsticks or chicken wings
will do.
Finish these buckets,
and you'll get everything you want.
Buckets?
Who could possibly eat buckets?
What I mean is
that you should finish
these chili peppers.
I don't like eating chili peppers.
Pure Suit, Triple Dragons,
make sure One Bam eats her peppers!
-Yes.
I've said
I don't like eating chili...
Will you eat them or not?
Lady Zhao,
please stop hitting Xiangjiu.
I'll eat those for her.
This is none of your business!
You're a Sichuan girl.
Making you eat peppers
is practically doing you a favor!
Get lost!
Boss,
let me try talking to her.
Xiangjiu,
if you don't want to eat them,
just apologize to Lady Zhao.
Come here.
Just apologize to Lady Zhao.
I'll take you to the Imperial Kitchen
for some delicacies later.
Guard Mao, who's by His Grace's side,
sent me to taste dishes for His Grace.
I can eat any dish
prepared for His Grace as I please.
Aren't you afraid
of getting caught by His Grace?
There's nothing to be afraid of.
I'd venture to guess
that His Grace must be an idiot.
Will you eat them or not?
What are you dawdling here for?
Someone come here!
Lady Zhao.
Take her away!
Please let me eat them for Xiangjiu.
Both of you, let me go!
Will you eat them or not?
Eat!
Take more!
There's no way
you can survive these chili peppers!
Eat!
That's it.
This is the exact scent.
It's the same as the one
on Princess Ningshuang.
Why did she tear out these two pages?
Since she did it in secret,
asking her directly
would only make her deny it.
Is there a spell
that could make her tell the truth?
I'll go find the Old Fox.
He'll surely have a way.
Just walking over there like this
is not impressive enough.
I've got it!
What's going on?
The Old Fox said I need to focus my mind
when casting spells.
I'll give it a try.
I'll teach you a lesson,
One Bam!
Eat!
Hurry up!
What...
What is it?
Which bastard dares...
Your Grace.
Your Grace, spare me!
My mouth!
Who did this?
Triple Dragons,
should we go break up the fight?
That's Lord Feng!
But Lady Zhao is our supervisor,
after all.
It doesn't seem right
to just stand by and do nothing.
That's true.
Then...
-Your Grace, please don't be angry!
I was such a beauty.
Look what you've done to my face!
Don't touch me!
This is my body!
Why can't I touch it?
It hurts.
Okay, okay.
I won't touch you.
Let me tell you something important.
I've found out
that the scent on Princess Ningshuang
is similar to the one
on the Ganquan Register.
Since Princess Ningshuang
was the one who tore out the pages
from the Ganquan Register,
then if I go ask her outright like this,
she definitely won't tell me the reason.
Do you have any spell
that can make people tell the truth?
You're a nine-tailed fox!
You can even shapeshift into a human form!
How come you don't have a spell
that can make people
tell the truth?
Are you an idiot?
Of course I'm not.
See?
Making people tell the truth
is harder than shapeshifting
into a human.
Besides,
didn't I already tell you these things?
First,
magic must never be casually shown
to others.
Second,
you're just a mortal.
Once I cast a spell,
it will definitely harm your body.
If you could help me find my father,
I wouldn't have
to go through all this trouble.
Let's go.
Come back with me
and figure something out.
I'm not leaving!
You've actually grown fond
of staying here?
I'm going
to have my revenge.
Why are you being so petty?
Didn't we just
get our revenge?
Not enough.
Far from enough.
For centuries,
I have never suffered
such great humiliation.
If I don't get even,
how can I hold my head up...
in this world?
Fine, have it your way.
I don't care anymore.
Wait.
You should be careful too.
Something might come for you at night.
You!
I advise you not to make
such an expression with my face!
You'd better take care of yourself.
Don't wear my body out.
You!
-Farewell, Your Grace.
Le Ning!
Come stay with me at Fucang Palace.
Your Grace!
This...
This is not appropriate.
What's wrong with it?
Didn't we often...
Never mind.
Listen to me.
From now on,
stay away from that Huo Xiangjiu.
She is no longer
the kind and clever Little Xiangjiu
you once knew.
Your Grace,
Xiangjiu and I are as close as sisters.
I don't understand why you're trying
to drive a wedge between us.
Could it be
that you also want
to be Xiangjiu's good friend, Your Grace?
Forget it.
This isn't something
I can easily explain to you.
Listen up, all of you!
From now on,
no one is allowed to bully Le Ning.
Anyone who disobeys...
will face immediate execution.
-Yes.
Fine, fine.
The Old Fox won't come with me.
I'll just figure something out myself.
Off I go!
-Le Ning.
What's your relationship
with His Grace?
He seems to really like you.
What exactly is going on between you two?
-Come on, tell us!
I...
For the failure,
just pay with your life.
It's no big deal.
Lord Gongsun,
didn't you say this would be a sure thing?
How is Lord Feng still alive and well?
Gao Wei!
How dare you speak to Lord Gongsun
like that?
Lord Gongsun
was also acting for my benefit.
Your Highness,
I was blinded by my ambition
for personal credit.
hoping to help you ascend
to the throne sooner.
I never imagined
that Lord Feng would be so fortunate.
Your Highness, I hope
you can forgive me.
Lord Gongsun,
please don't say that.
You are a pillar of our state.
How could I
ever punish you?
Your Highness,
you are so benevolent...
A father's debt
should be repaid by his son.
Guards!
Your Highness!
I only have this one son!
Your Highness,
please have mercy!
Even if I have no merits, for the sake
of my years of hard work in your service,
please spare my son's life,
Your Highness.
Hard work is just hard work.
If hard work counted as merit,
then every constable in this state
would be considered a hero.
Your Highness,
if you could spare my son's life,
I am
willing to be your loyal servant!
There's no need for that,
Lord Gongsun.
Your son
is to marry Princess Ningshuang.
How dare I let you be my servant?
I wouldn't dare anymore.
I would never dare again.
I wouldn't dare to covet the marriage
alliance with Princess Ningshuang again!
Your Highness!
Lord Gongsun,
your family came from humble origins.
Your current position is hard-won.
You must cherish it.
You must always hold gratitude
in your heart
and repay kindness with action.
Your Highness, without your favor,
I couldn't have become who I am today.
Lord Gongsun,
it is good that you know it.
A low-born wretch
will always be a low-born wretch.
If one day they dare
to dream of a noble's status,
that is overstepping!
They will lose their life!
Gao Wei, how insolent you are!
Sorry that I spoke out of turn.
Enough.
As long as you behave obediently,
which master
would bear to kill an obedient servant?
From now on,
Your Highness, I will follow your lead
with unwavering loyalty.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Your son is no longer a young boy.
How can he ever grow
if he stays by your side?
Transfer him to the palace.
Make him a palace guard
right by my side.
That way, I may also entrust him
with greater responsibilities.
Thank you for your kindness,
Your Highness.
However, my son has stayed
by my side since childhood.
He is simple-minded and dull.
If he were to enter the palace,
I fear he might cause offense...
Lord Gongsun,
What a great opportunity it is
that His Highness
transfers your son to the palace!
Why do you keep declining?
How ungrateful you are!
That is not what I meant.
Then why not express your gratitude
at once?
Thank you,
Your Highness.
You...
Thank you, Your Highness.
Matters concerning Lord Feng
must not be rushed.
At the family feast,
I noticed a new maid by his side.
Let's bribe her.
She is close to him.
She can act far more easily
than we ever could.
Your Highness,
you're truly thoughtful.
I'll do it immediately.
That won't be necessary.
This time,
I'll handle it personally.
Your Highness.
Your Highness,
dinner is ready.
Lord Gongsun,
please stay for the meal as well.
Thank you for your kindness,
Your Highness.
We still have official business
to attend to,
so we won't
take up any more of your time.
Your Highness,
I'll take my leave.
Lord Gongsun,
please.
How many times have I told you?
Do not disturb me
when I'm discussing official matters.
Let's go.
Why do you never listen?
Prince Fuying wanted to transfer you
to the palace,
just to keep you firmly under his control.
And you
actually agreed!
Did we even have the option to refuse?
If you hadn't been helping the tyrant
do evil all this time,
how could our lives have become so fraught
with fear and dread?
You insolent fool!
You absolute idiot!
Have you ever thought about this?
All other princes are stationed
in their own states.
Only Prince Fuying stays
by the His Majesty's side.
If we don't pledge allegiance to him,
how can our Gongsun family
rise to greater heights?
So what?
I don't care at all.
You...
You're truly stupid!
What did I teach you since you were a boy?
Each generation must be more ruthless
than the last.
But you...
How did I end up with a son
as ambitionless and soft as you?
And there's another thing.
Don't tell me I'm right.
You want to stay in the palace,
just because of that woman!
If Prince Fuying learns
about your past with her,
our Gongsun family will be finished!
Also,
try not to mention Lord Feng
in front of Prince Fuying.
You...
Did you hear me?
Where is the secret manual?
Where is...
the secret manual?
It's here.
Please don't pass out just yet, okay?
Your Grace.
-Ah!
A demon!
Ah!
You should push it.
Thank you.
What a coincidence.
Bye.
What on earth
did I do to you?
We have no grudge against each other.
What kind of demon are you?
Why are you following me?
You're not Lord Feng.
What do you mean?
Lord Feng wouldn't be afraid of me.
But you look exactly like Lord Feng.
Wait.
I think I've seen you somewhere before.
Give me a hand.
So it's you!
What do you mean?
Do we know each other?
Once,
when I was in the outhouse,
you helped me.
I'm sorry.
I don't remember anything.
Why is this happening?
I have no idea either.
Where is Lord Feng now?
Can you take me to him?
This is what you get
for staying behind to seek revenge?
It's all because
your body
is too weak.
What is she?
A flower spirit.
A flower spirit?
Flowers can become spirits too?
All things can become spirits.
Then can shit become a spirit?
It can help flowers become spirits.
What are you two talking about?
Your physical form is already gone.
Now only your soul remains.
I don't even remember what I am anymore.
I only remember
I wandered the palace day after day.
One day, I saw Lord Feng by chance.
After watching him secretly for days,
I noticed he and I seemed
to be of the same kind.
So I wanted to ask you, Lord Feng,
to free me from this endless torment.
But never did I expect
that Lord Feng and this young lady
had swapped souls.
Since her body is already gone,
why does her soul still remain?
It won't last long.
A soul cannot survive
once separated from the body.
It must be
that there are still unresolved regrets.
What regrets do you have?
I only remember my name is Ru.
As for the rest,
I remember nothing.
Your Grace,
please help me uncover the truth.
Please help her.
Your soul won't last long.
Soon it will vanish completely.
What does it matter whether you can
settle your regrets or not?
Of course it matters.
Even with only one day left,
if there's still an unfulfilled wish,
one should do their best to fulfill it.
Only then
can they finally be at peace.
I never meddle in others' affairs.
You may leave.
Your Grace, without your help,
I'm afraid
I'll have to vanish into nothing
with my regrets.
Old Fox!
You're so cold-blooded!
Ru!
Don't leave.
Don't worry.
He won't help you,
but I will.
Really?
Thank you so much.
May I ask
your name?
My name is Huo Xiangjiu.
You can call me Xiangjiu.
Miss Xiangjiu,
I'll await your good news.
Huo Xiangjiu...
As a noble gentleman among flowers,
it is like a refined guest from Sanxiang.
Blessed with the peerless fragrance,
it bears the virtuous spirit.
She's quite pretty,
but her singing is awful.
It was you who promised to help her.
It had nothing to do with me.
You're not really going to sleep
in this pigsty, are you?
You're so terrible
at getting along with people.
None of your business!
Come back to Fucang Palace with me.
Why?
I absolutely will not allow my body
to sleep in a place like this!
I think
you're
afraid.
Afraid?
I'm afraid?
You're afraid.
I am afraid?
You are afraid!
I'm not afraid of demons.
I'm now the supreme Lord Feng!
You think I'm afraid...
Why did I pass out again?
Your body really isn't very good.
It's your mere mortal soul
that can't handle my powerful body.
Why don't you put a bed in the room?
Have you ever seen a fox
sleeping in a bed?
Then aren't you cold sleeping
on the block of ice?
How ignorant.
This is thousand-year-old ice.
It can suppress
the innate fire
generated by my cultivation.
No wonder you're so hot-tempered.
But putting my body on this ice
will easily cause rheumatism.
I really miss
my nine-colored tail now.
Well,
why did Princess Ningshuang
tear out those two pages
from the Ganquan Register?
Could it really be her
who captured my father?
If you're so eager to find your father,
why bother
with someone else's trivial matters?
That flower spirit
will soon
vanish into nothing.
Why waste your efforts on what's futile?
There are no trivial matters
in this world.
So-called trivial matters
are just
hardships that haven't yet fallen
upon oneself.
But then,
you'll delay your search for your father.
My father said
that one shouldn't ignore
others' suffering
just because they're in a hurry
to reach their own destination.
Do you know
why humans are stronger than animals?
Because we know how to help each other,
how to understand each other,
and how to love.
Love, you understand?
Love me?
The way you broke up my sentence
changed the meaning.
It's...
It's not "love you."
It's "love, you understand?"
Forget it.
You're not even human.
It's pointless explaining it to you.
In my life,
if only I could meet someone
who would love me for a lifetime.
Wouldn't it be better
if it were for every lifetime?
You really don't understand love at all.
Getting love that lasts a lifetime
is already a rare blessing.
If that's the case,
if one could experience love
that lasts every lifetime,
wouldn't that be the greatest blessing
in the world?
Every lifetime?
That's something
I wouldn't even dare to dream of.
Since it's just a dream,
why not be a bit bolder?
By the way,
is it possible that my father
has some secret business to take care of,
so he's hiding,
not wanting me to know?
It's possible.
Yeah,
I think so too.
Xiangjiu!
I've learned the soul-swapping technique!
Yu!
How dare you hit me!
Xiangjiu,
I'm sorry
that I hit the wrong person.
Hurry up and swap back!
I'm going crazy dealing with you two!
Xiangjiu...
Let's begin.
Ancestors
of the Bai Clan of Bronze County,
I, Bai Yu, the 30th generation descendant
of the clan,
will perform
the soul-swapping technique here.
Heavenly Thunder!
Earthly Fire!
Five Elements!
Six Harmonies!
Commence the soul exchange!
Follow my command!
Why am I still in Huo Xiangjiu's body?
Bai Yu,
your soul-swapping technique
didn't work at all.
Yu,
why am I in your body?
Why am I in the wily fox's body?
You two...
I'm Huo Xiangjiu.
I'm Bai Yu.
Yu!
I'm so sorry.
It's my first time
performing the soul-swapping technique.
I'm not very skilled at it yet.
Let's try it again.
Totally worthless, just as I thought!
Heavenly Thunder!
Earthly Fire!
Five Elements! Six Harmonies!
Commence the soul exchange!
Follow my command!
Why am I back
in the wily fox's body again?
Why am I in Bai Yu's body?
Xiangjiu,
I'm in your body.
I never thought
that I would embrace you
in this way.
Don't move!
I'll break your arms if you try anything!
Do you actually know how to perform
the soul-swapping technique?
The current situation
clearly proves that I do!
Then could you just get it right
for once?
Calm down!
Everything is under control.
Yu,
make our souls return to our own bodies!
Let's try it again!
Heavenly Thunder!
Earthly Fire!
Five Elements! Six Harmonies!
Commence the soul exchange!
Follow my command!
Xiangjiu,
is it really you?
It's me!
I'm back!
Old Fox!
Old Fox...
I'm Bai Yu.
Then you two...
Every soul back to the right body counts.
Old Fox,
it's our turn now.
Xiangjiu,
you go back first,
in case we mess things up again.
Okay.
Good luck!
Xiangjiu,
I'll go find you soon.
For the first time, I'm admiring
my own appearance so directly.
Truly majestic and imposing,
valiant and extraordinary,
curvaceous and shapely,
dashing and stylish,
and drop-dead gorgeous!
You wily fox,
being able to enjoy such a fabulous figure
is the greatest honor
of your life!
Please remember this moment forever!
Stop babbling.
Just do it.
You're right.
If this drags on any longer,
you'll end up occupying my body.
What a rotten deal for me.
Heavenly Thunder!
Earthly Fire!
Five Elements! Six Harmonies!
Commence the soul exchange!
Follow my command!
It didn't work.
Master,
it's me.
You stupid dog,
why did you suddenly show up
in the middle of this?
What was that in my mind just now?
How bizarre.
You're Huo Xiangjiu, aren't you?
No.
You are Huo Xiangjiu!
Prince Fuying
asked you to go to the Eastern Palace.
wants to see me?
I'm quite busy today.
Perhaps another day.
Prince Fuying's order
is not something you can refuse.