SUBTITLES BY Babel Fansub
Subbers: Archanfel, Toki
Lu Zhaozhao's Assassination Notes
Episode 20
Nannan.
Here you are.
Were the one who sent me
to kill Huangfu Yi?
What are you talking about, Nannan?
The red spots.
My memories serve me well.
So your family's poison is the Cloud-nine Powder.
How did you know that?
You sent someone to poison me.
Nannan.
I have no idea what you are talking about.
How could I poison you?
Wait.
You are poisoned by the Cloud-nine Powder?
When did it happen?
A while ago,
I was forced to take that drug
and threatened to kill Huangfu Yi.
I have just learned
that its producer has red spots on the wrist
and
few people
could make such a worm poison.
I can't think of
anyone else who would do that but you.
It was him.
What the hell do you want?
It's pointless to know the reason.
Sister is dead,
so I will make the Huangfus pay for it.
I will make Huangfu Yi experience
the feeling of watching his love
die in front of him
helplessly.
Nannan.
It's hard to explain
to you in a short time.
Anyway,
the Cloud-nine Powder is an extraordinary poison
and its cure...
What's wrong?
Your eyes...
It's fine.
Where were we?
Right.
The Cloud-nine Powder.
Yes,
I poisoned you.
I asked servants to look for an assassin
but I didn't expect that they found you.
You disappointed me so much at first,
to think
you surprised me a lot afterward.
What's the matter with you?
Why are you different?
You just...
You just need to follow my order
because nobody can save you
except me.
What do you mean?
Not all worm poison have cures.
As the worst worm poison of all,
the Powder's cure is pretty unusual.
You're lucky
to experience it.
I don't get it.
Why are you doing this?
To revenge.
To make Huangfu Yi suffer.
He deserves this.
Do you get it?
Have you heard about a woman
who hanged herself at his home?
It was my sister.
Sister Fu Han?
How could it be her?
The murderers
shall pay with their lives.
It's time to make the Huangfus pay.
What happened then?
Why did sister Fu Han...
Enough.
Well,
you don't believe me?
Right,
you think
all the Huangfus are good people, right?
Those hypocritical
and stupid men!
Instead of colluding with them,
why don't you
marry me?
Maybe I will detoxify you
when I feel happy.
What happened to brother Yu?
Why was he suddenly different?
Why did he ask me to marry him?
Shameless.
How could you poison Nannan with the Powder?
You know
there are only two antidotes.
One is the one poisoned
consummates with the poisoner
and the other is...
Shut up.
Isn't the first way better?
So you may be with your Nannan.
I'm not the one she loves,
I won't push her.
Don't be so hypocritical.
You'd better face your lust.
You don't get it.
I will never push Nannan.
I'm warning you
that if you tell someone
the second antidote,
I promise
that your Nannan will die earlier.
Don't you hurt her.
Her safety is my bottom line.
Nannan.
You'd better get out of my way.
All my enemies
will end up miserably.
So the wedding is fixed.
The bride-price will be sent to the Lus' home later.
All right.
Though there were misunderstandings between us,
given the wedding is approaching,
we shall make up.
Since my Zhaozhao
has gained the favor of master Huangfu,
I'm glad for her as her father.
So the wedding feast and the bride-price...
The wedding feast?
The bride-price?
Zhaozhao.
Come here.
Right in time.
Your marriage to master Huangfu
has been settled.
Look at her.
Did I say something wrong?
Zhaozhao.
Why did you ignore me?
YoYo English Channel    YouTube