SUBTITLES BY Babel Fansub
Subbers: Archanfel, Toki
Lu Zhaozhao's Assassination Notes
Episode 16
Huangfu Yi.
I'm sorry.
Mister Luo Bai.
You seem to be worried.
Something happened at the Huangfus' mansion?
Nothing.
Maybe
you should stay at the academy for a while.
I'm good.
I have a room at Water-cloud Dream.
It occurs to me
that I need an assistant,
would you like to help me?
An assistant?
I don't think I'm a good fit.
I've looked for one for so long
and can't find anyone suitable.
Besides,
won't it
cost you much to stay in a hotel?
Right.
All right then.
Eat something, nephew.
You can't hold up if you don't eat.
Aunt.
I'm fine.
About Riyue...
Aunt,
I have to handle many things at the bank.
So why don't you go to rest?
Mister.
The paintings are sorted out.
Thank you.
Mister,
something is wrong with your eyes?
I'm fine.
An old problem.
Mister,
don't underestimate the ailment.
All right.
Nannan.
How do you know my pet name?
Isn't it obvious?
You are...
Same red spots as when I was a kid.
You are Fu Yu.
Brother Yu.
You finally recognized me.
Why did you change your name?
By the way,
where is sister Fu Han?
Let me
explain it to you later.
You shall call me Luo Bai
when there are other people.
My sister
is no longer in this world.
When
I was mistreated by the mistress,
it was you and Fu Han who saved me.
I would have been eaten
by the beasts in the mountains
without you.
I  knew you were Nannan,
but I didn't know
that you were from the Lus.
Nannan is my pet name.
I went to look for you afterward,
but you moved away.
I wanted to repay you when I found you,
to think sister Fu Han...
She will rest in peace
since you've come to see her.
Lu Zhaozhao.
So you are Lu Yao's daughter.
How dare you deceive
my talented,
righteous
and handsome Mister Huangfu
as well as me?
Lu Zhaozhao!
I'm sorry.
You should apologize.
To think I helped you to chase Huangfu.
Lady Linglong came here
and I led her to your room.
Should you have any difficulties,
just tell her.
Thank you,
Lin Yizhi.
I'm not taking you as my friend,
I'm just doing this for Huangfu
though I don't think you are a bad person.
Just go.
Thank you.
Aunt.
Sit.
I never investigated you
because I believed that you're a good girl.
I'm sorry, Aunt.
Don't say that.
You are not supposed to apologize
to me.
The notebook...
I get it.
I've read the last part
which records
your affection and sincerity
to my nephew.
We've been living together for a while,
so I have faith in your personality.
Nannan.
Brother Yu.
I didn't see you just now,
so
I put it on your table.
You are going back?
Is it because
you can't leave him?
YoYo English Channel    YouTube