What's going on with all of you? Huh?
Wee and Grandfather are all smiley.
And what are you two signaling
each other about?
It's nothing, Dad.
-Just eat.
-Eat.
Eat up.
-Please eat up.
-Yes.
So you'll grow faster. One more.
I'm your father.
Well, well, well…
You're so in sync.
What are you on about, Chu?
Duh. You went for the same plate.
You wanted the same food.
If that's not being in sync,
what would you call it?
Hey.
-Eat.
-Yes.
How's it going?
How's what going?
Yeesh! Don't play dumb.
This thing with Wee. How's it going?
What's the matter?
I'm into Wee.
I fell for him.
Doesn't this mean I'm betraying Ms. Wad?
Jeez! Great-Great-Grandfather.
Just accept it.
Our family has been looking
for Ms. Wad for 100 years.
Have you found her?
Finding Wee makes
all the pieces fit, right?
Or him being a man still bothers you?
But it's still troubling.
Don't forget
that doctor's still pursuing Wee.
He's a doctor,
respectable, highly educated.
He knew Wee from before.
They understand each other
and they share interests.
While I'm…
just a grumbling old man. I can't compete.
Wow. Who would have thought
I'd get to see this version of you?
Typically you're like,
"Chu, you're a child.
Don't talk back to your elders.
Hey, if you don't listen
and mess up later,
I'll chew you out even worse."
See?
Even you think I'm a grumbling old man.
All right. Great-Great-Grandfather,
I know you grumble because you care.
You're taking care
of everyone in our family.
Despite your grumbling,
you're very reliable.
So when it comes to you and Wee,
I want you to be happy.
So don't worry. I'll help you!
Ok?
I have to count on
my great-great-grandchild.
I'm a lousy great-great-grandfather.
You're an asshole for ditching me.
I won't go accompany you anywhere again.
Ton, hello?
I'm not done yelling at you. Ton!
Wee!
Come on.
Wee! Is there something wrong?
I got two amusement park tickets for free.
I was gonna go with Ton tomorrow
but he ditched me.
Eh?
Oh… What a coincidence.
He just told me yesterday
he wanted to go to an amusement park.
I never said that.
He's old so he's forgetful.
Great-Great-Grandfather,
this is your chance
to hang out and get to know each other.
Yeah, right.
I vented to Chu yesterday
I wanted to go out and have fun.
What a coincidence.
If that's the case,
you should go with Wee.
Take him out.
He's over 100 years old.
Broaden his horizons.
San!
San! Come on!
Hey.
Look.
Dinosaurs.
OPENING CELEBRATION, MAKING PERFUME
FREE! TODAY ONLY
What do you think about this?
Smells great.
I like it.
Uh, you like it?
Then I'll let you have it.
I'd rather you didn't.
I prefer it on you.
CT SUPERMARKET
Holy! For real?
San's got moves.
See? Something good
came out of me ditching you.
Don't change the subject.
Thanks to you, I'm stressed out.
Stressed out about what?
Oh. The stone you're planning to steal?
I'm being serious.
Give up.
Even without the stone,
I'm still not the one he's waiting for.
DOCTOR THIRD
Wow.
So you married to undo bad luck.
Yes, Third.
Then I have a chance, right?
A chance to do what?
You know I'm into you, right?
Since high school.
But I messed up by waiting
for too long to tell you.
Then you were gone.
Third.
But I'm back now. Let me take care of you.
I promise I won't leave again.
Wee?
Wee.
-What do you think? You're hooked?
-So delicious.
I know another shop.
I'll take you there next time.
-Ok?
-You got it.
Get home safe.
Text me when you're home.
-You got it. Get home safe.
-Bye-bye.
Doctor, don't you get it?
What do you want?
I can't believe it. Someone like you?
What are you saying?
Wee told me you two
got married to undo bad luck.
So I asked to date him.
What did Wee say?
I promise
I won't break your heart.
Give me a chance, Wee.
Thank you, Third.
But I…
I'm too late again, aren't I?
Mr. San?
Congrats.
I wish you two happiness.
That won't happen, Third.
Between me and San,
the best I'll ever get
is that excuse of a wedding.
San already loves someone else.
Someday he'll go back
to the person he's been waiting for.
If you love someone else
and don't want Wee, then let him go.
What if I don't?
How do you really feel about Wee?
Are you a dog in the manger?
I'm into him.
I never thought I'd ever be.
Next thing I knew, I already were.
If you're into him, tell him.
He's gonna be thrilled.
But if you ever break his heart,
I'll take him from you.
Don't worry about that.
I suggest you get out
of my and Wee's lives.
This sucks.
I don't know why I feel like
I lost to you before.
Now I lose to you again.
Wee. Please open the door for me.
I wanna talk to you.
Wee.
I know you're in there.
I wanna talk to you.
I talked to Doctor Third.
I know you're not sure about me.
I'm into you.
I'm really into you.
I wanna be with you.
I wanna take care of you.
I know you've always been alone.
You've had a hard life.
But will you give me
a chance to be in your life?
I will take care of you.
I won't break your heart.
I will make you happy every day.
Wee.
San?
Eh?
What are you doing?
Wee.
I wanna talk to you.
Can I take a rain check?
I'm having a headache.
Wee.
I wanna talk to you.
Let's talk later. I'm late.
Something wrong, Great-Great-Grandfather?
Are you sure your plan will work?
Jeez, trust me.
Follow my plan and you'll win Wee's heart.
I'm an expert on love.
Despite my appearance, I've helped
many friends get into relationships.
If you're so good,
why haven't you found anyone?
Goodness.
Don't say I haven't found anyone.
I'm single by choice.
I gotta go, Ton. Stock the shelves for me.
San, why are you dressed up?
Go take a shower.
And dress up.
You're going out with me.
Where are you taking me?
Never mind that. You'll find out.
Go make yourself handsome. Come on.
Come on.
Give me the most handsome version.
Go on.
The owner's renting my building
so I asked them a small favor.
It's good.
Wee.
This one's good too.
It's my favorite.
What, San?
Dance?
No way. I can't dance.
Come on. I'll teach you.
Wee.
I wanted to tell you
-I…
-Don't say it.
Why not?
You're something else.
I was trying to avoid you.
Wee.
I talked to Doctor Third.
I know you're not sure about me.
I'm into you.
I'm really into you.
Wee.
San?
I wanna talk to you.
Can I take a rain check?
I'm having a headache.
You heard everything that night?
San,
you're not into me.
You're just lonely
and I happened to come by.
What gave you that idea, Wee?
You said it yourself.
I'm untidy, filthy,
loud, rowdy,
cunning, foul-mouthed,
and completely shameless.
How could you fall
for someone that horrible?
I was biased at the time
so I only saw your bad traits.
Actually,
you're lighthearted,
kind,
care about people around you
and have mental strength.
Whatever hardship you face,
you can still smile.
These things I just listed
didn't make me fall for you.
But I love everything
that you are.
Both your good traits
and bad traits.
Are you sure?
I am.
Even though you already heard it,
I'm gonna say it again before you.
Give me a chance to be in your life.
I will take care of you.
I won't break your heart.
I will make you happy every day.
Yikes. Old-fashioned lines.
You really are an over-100-year-old man.
What's your answer?
This is Ms. Wad,
Duke Phichitphusit's daughter.
Aren't you in a hurry
to catch your criminal?
Yes, ma'am.
You're safe now.
Mister?
How are you feeling?
Did I wake you?
It's ok.
Wee?
San.
This ring
is yours.
-Chu, back off.
-Jeez, Grandpa, Mom.
-I'm gonna look for Grandfather.
-I said he'd be right soon.
He's been gone a long time. This won't do.
-Jeez, give him time.
-No. Let me go.
-You're overreacting.
-Wee, Grandfather, you're back.
Goodness, I was worried sick.
I was gonna look for you
but Chu stopped me.
I told you they'd be back soon.
You just didn't believe me.
-What if they weren't?
-Well, are they back?
Give it a rest.
Where were you two last night anyway?
I crashed at Ton's last night.
I ran into San at the gate just now.
Wait.
We spent the night together.
Spent the night? You mean slept together?
That's what I meant.
The two of us are married.
It's normal to sleep together.
Rat, Chu.
-Yes?
Help Wee move his stuff into my room.
Sure thing.
You got it, Great-Great-Grandfather.
-That's what I'm talking about.
-Good job.
Your breath smells great.
Of course.
Let me smell it again.
San.
What are you doing? I'm late.
I love this scent.
I'm gonna go to work.
Wait.
Kiss me first.
Bye.
Oh, what the heck?
San.
Thank you.
BAO GONG SHRINE
The investigator we hired
found where Ms. Wad's
descendants live in Chiang Rai.
But nobody's home.
So I'm gonna send them
a sketch of Ms. Wad to ask around.
No need, Tao.
Eh? Why not?
I'm convinced now
Wee is Ms. Wad. There's no one else.
Huh?
But Wee's a man.
Is that ok with you?
It is.
It's actually more than ok.
You can say it's wonderful.
Huh?
Goddess, why is
the Five-Colored Stone like this?
What's going on?
You're in a good mood today.
Nothing's going on, Grandma.
Oh, right. San's gonna come by
to pay you his respects today.
He has an errand to run first.
San?
The guy you said
married you undo bad luck?
So why would he pay me his respects?
Eh? Or…
Nothing, Grandma.
He just wanted to pay you his respects.
San happens to be a respectful person,
deferential to old people.
I'm not old yet.
Sure, pretty lady.
Eh?
Hello, ma'am.
Something wrong, Grandma?
No.
Hello, Doctor?
Sure, I'll be right down.
I'll be right back. The doctor wants me.
Ma'am,
please let me know if you need help.
It's strange.
You look just like my friend.
No!
-What the hell? Let go!
-You're gonna get it.
Let go!
Thank you very much, Mister. Thank you.
You're safe now.
Thank you very much for saving Chaem.
Thank him, come on.
Thank you again, Mister.
THAI STEAMED PORK DUMPLINGS
Mr. Handsome!
Here. My mom sent me to give you this.
Thank you, braided girl.
My name is Chaem.
So…
Why are you renting this house?
You work nearby?
No.
I heard someone who looks
like my friend just moved here.
So I came here.
In case I run into her.
Braided girl?
You're her?
San.
-Braided girl.
-San.
Is this really you?
HOSPITAL
So your San is my Mr. Handsome.
Yes.
What I told you
might sound a little fantastic,
but it's all true, Grandma.
You were so mean
for leaving without saying goodbye.
I'm sorry about that.
Back then I heard about
someone who looked like Ms. Wad,
so I went to look for her.
But it wasn't her.
When I got back, you were gone.
It's amazing.
I've gotten to see
my first love before I die.
What do you think, Wee?
You always thought
I exaggerated about Mr. Handsome.
Look at him. Is he handsome?
He's so-so, Grandma.
Oh, San.
The Ms. Wad you were looking for,
have you found her?
BAO GONG SHRINE
GODDESS NU WA
Ms. Wad?
You… Your name is San, right?
You really exist.
Please give San back to me, Wee.
It's none of your business.
Great-great-grandfather!
This Five-Colored Stone will let us know
who is the real Ms. Wad.
Why are you doing this?
Subtitle translation by: Chonnikarn Ounob