♪The evening breeze
gently stirs the stars♪
♪Like you quietly entering my heart♪
♪I wish for time and you to pause♪
♪In this beautiful moment,
only you and I♪
♪Moonlight accompanies
the silhouette of the stars♪
♪Like a romantic encounter♪
♪I want to hold your hand
and cross through dreams♪
♪Together, let's search for
the most beautiful scenery♪
♪I want to embark on
an adventure of love with you♪
♪To fulfill the wishes buried
deep in my heart with you♪
♪Your appearance warms up every day♪
♪I just want to be by your side forever♪
♪Next to you♪
[Mr. Insomnia Waiting for Love]
[Watch on www.kisskh.co]
[Episode 17]
Yanxu.
Why are you here?
You're not picking up my calls,
so I came here to find you.
I'm worried about you.
I'm fine.
What happened to your hand?
Tell me what happened.
You're not picking up my calls
or responding to my messages.
Also,
what is going on with
you and that real estate girl?
We're not acting.
Have I done something wrong?
Or
is there some misunderstanding?
There is not misunderstanding.
I think my father is right.
I'm the executive officer of a company.
You are useless to
my future development.
We are together because of our illness.
But what about the future?
What about us after we are cured?
There's no value to
both of us when that time comes.
Our treatment is almost finished.
I
have also met someone during this time
who is the most suitable for me.
Answer me this.
Is this what
you really think?
Look at me!
Yes.
Song Yanxu,
it seems like I am wrong about you.
Did you have to go that far?
Since you've already decided to help me,
then stop with all the nonsense.
This jerk!
How dare he say such things.
He even said
if I can't fall asleep
then I can go to find him after
his fiancé falls asleep.
What?
This jerk!
I'll kill him!
You…
Why aren't you stopping me?
It's bad to be impulsive.
Entong,
I have a new treatment plan
for you and Yanxu.
Let's meet up to talk about
it if you are available.
You are not
thinking about going, right?
He's breaking up with you
and you're thinking about helping
him treat his insomnia?
It's not for him.
It's for myself.
[Café]
Why are your eye so red?
Is it because of that trending topic?
You saw it too, Doctor.
I don't know what happened
between the two of you,
but up until now,
Song Yanxu's heart rate towards
you has not changed.
If you get what I mean.
Really?
I'm just talking about the data,
you have to deal with the
relationship problems yourselves.
Now let's talk
about your dream.
Okay.
Remember the drowning incident
we talked about
last time Yanxu and I were hypnotized?
Of course.
But the hypnosis failed halfway
through the treatment.
That's true.
But I had another dream last night.
I was able to see
things a lot clearer this time.
And
it felt so real,
like it really happened.
In this case, there are generally
two possibilities.
One possibility is that it's been too
long so the memory is forgotten.
Simply put,
most of us
don't remember what our
kindergarten teachers look like.
And the other possibility
is that something happened
which caused both of you
to forget the incident.
And this memory is being pulled
back into your increased conscious mind
with time and your reunion
with each other.
It seems that
our insomnia
has a lot to do with this memory.
That's right.
If we can fully recall this memory,
then your insomnia can be cured.
So I need to do another
deep hypnosis session
with you and Song Yanxu.
Maybe we'll discover something new.
All right.
[Kerwin Group]
Xiao Meng, Xiao Xia,
please let me in.
I really have to talk Mr. Song.
Entong, we want to help you
but Mr. Song specially requested us
to not let you enter yesterday.
Not let me enter?
Entong, you're here.
Ye Zi, I have to talk to Yanxu,
but they won't let me in.
How about this? I'll take you inside.
Come with me.
It's fine.
I asked Assistant Li just now.
He said Mr. Song has a
meeting this morning.
He should be here soon.
Why are your eyes so puffy?
Did you cry?
You saw that trending topic
about Mr. Song, right?
I need to talk to him
about something else.
It has nothing to do
with the trending topic.
Don't you understand?
He just wants to break up with you.
Do you know something?
Here is a hearsay.
The daughter of Shuntu Real
Estate is also my friend.
She's a misogamist.
What do you mean?
It seems like you still don't know.
No wonder you came looking
for Yanxu so shamelessly.
Ms. Xu,
you've crossed the line.
You're Ye Zi, right?
You violated company rules
and brought irrelevant
personnel into the company.
Your year-end bonus is fully deducted.
As for you,
since Yanxu doesn't want
to hurt your feelings
then I'll play the bad cop.
Come with me.
Don't worry.
Entong?
Mr. Song,
I just saw
Ms. Xu took Entong to her office.
Tongtong!
Tongtong.
What's wrong?
Why are your eyes red?
Are you sick?
Mom,
is this all true?
Did I get Yanxu's mother
killed 15 years ago?
[Tragic Accident of the
President Song's Wife]
Tongtong,
hear me out.
This was actually…
So
the reason you wouldn't
let me be with Yanxu
is because you figured out who he is
that day when we met with his dad?
Song Yanxu
promised me yesterday that
he wouldn't tell Tongtong about this.
He didn't!
You guys went to find him?
Why did you do that?
He's already suffered
so much knowing this!
Why would you do this to him?
Why?
Tongtong!
I've already told her about it.
What?
Why would you tell Entong about this?
Even if I didn't,
she would have known about it sooner or later.
Besides,
why does she get to go around unbothered
when Yanxu is suffering?
But what you did makes
both of them suffer,
did you know that?
Chi Zuo,
you should be thanking me.
Now it is the perfect timing
for you to pursue Lu Entong.
Mansu,
if you really like someone then
you wouldn't hurt him
or the people he loves.
Tongtong.
I thought you wanted
to stay away from me.
Tongtong,
don't be like this.
I don't blame you.
I hate that you don't blame me.
You will only blame yourself
for not stopping me,
for not holding on
to your mother's hand,
for not stopping her to
save another person,
right?
But this is exactly why
I hate myself even more.
I would rather you hate me.
Xu Mansu was right.
If it wasn't for me,
you wouldn't have lost
your mother at a young age
or be in a bad relationship
with your father.
I only bring you misfortune.
I don't deserve to be with you.
Song Yanxu.
Let's break up.
♪I think I will understand♪
♪I won't rely on anyone anymore♪
♪You can only exist in my memories♪
♪Drawing the one who loved me♪
♪But I can't touch your love♪
♪Everything that should
come has arrived♪
♪This ending is harder
to guess than the truth♪
♪Hard to guess♪
♪I think I will understand♪
♪I won't rely on anyone anymore♪
♪You can only exist in my memories♪
♪Drawing the one who loved me♪
♪This separation is so absurd♪
♪No farewell words♪
♪The one who is weak in love is not me♪
♪It's you♪
Yanxu.
The tide is rising. Come up.
Yanxu!
The tide is rising!
Get out of the water.
It was just here!
Why is it gone now?
Song Yanxu!
Are you trying to
get yourself killed?
Get up!
It was just right here.
Get out!
Do you hear me?
Right here.
Why is it gone?
Have you lost your mind?
Stop looking for it!
It was right here.
Just right here.
Song Yanxu!
It was right here!
Stop looking.
No.
It was right here!
Please!
Don't be like this!
Was it washed away by the waves?
What should I do?
What happened?
Why is it gone?
Why?
Tongtong.
Tell me
what you're thinking.
I'm worried about you
not speaking at all.
Mom,
I feel terrible.
I don't want to break up with him,
but
I'm afraid he'll think
about what happened
in the past when he sees me.
This will make him feel even worse.
I don't want him to have an even worse
relationship with his
father because of me.
That's why
our Tongtong
has always been a
kind-hearted child.
I don't believe
it was you who did it.
Mom.
Can you tell me
what happened then?
You were five
that year.
There's an artificial lake nearby
the music academy where you
learned to play the cello.
♪You left without saying goodbye,
how great is my sin?♪
♪I thought you deliberately
joked with me♪
♪Later, how heroic was my extinction?♪
♪How pitifully kind?♪
♪No luck to embrace
and reconcile with you♪
♪Such a gentlemanly behavior♪
♪Only then can I live up
to my poor acting skills♪
♪The knot between us is unsolvable♪
♪Just like day and night♪
♪On the deserted streets♪
♪Freezing the air♪
♪I stand in the middle of the road,
intercepting like a wild one♪
♪When everyone misunderstands
how wicked I am♪
♪Since I left your sight♪
♪My decline has become
increasingly intense♪
♪I really want to thank you in person♪
♪I stand in the middle of the road,
intercepting like a wild one♪
♪When passing cars timidly compromise♪
♪I know there will definitely be
misinterpretations♪
♪How can normal people
be indifferent to everything?♪
♪Even the moon has chosen to extinguish♪
[Li Che]
[Kerwin]
Mr. Song,
today is the inspection day
for phase one of Banana 3.
The board is all here.
I'll go pick you up right now.
Okay.
[Facial Cleanser]
Tongtong, come down to eat.
Coming.
You didn't sleep again last night?
This tastes pretty good.
No, I was talking about…
What?
No.
Nothing.
Eat well.
Eat more.
Okay.
[Kerwin]
What's with this change in style?
Mix and match?
I know about you and Lu Entong.
Don't be too sad.
Let's work hard
to develop Banana 3,
and then cure your insomnia.
What style?
I guess you
didn't hear a single thing I said.
Tongtong.
It's only been a few days
and you've lost so much weight.
I'm fine.
I'll gain it all back through eating.
That's true.
How about this?
After we finish the movie
let's go have a big meal.
I'll go get the tickets.
Then, I'll get the snacks.
Okay.
I want a bucket of
popcorn and two cokes.
Okay.
Chi Zuo.
Tongtong's all good.
Don't worry.
Tongtong,
is this enough?
Shall I give you more?
Yanxu
why are you selling popcorn?
And you're so skilled at it.
Tongtong.
Tongtong!
What's wrong?
Nothing.
We have everything now.
Let's go watch the movie.
Okay.
♪Trying to break free♪
♪Pretending to be
more carefree than you♪
♪Simply close my eyes♪
♪Not looking at the me of the past♪
♪Until it's hard to distinguish♪
♪Loving you is like a game♪
♪Deceiving time♪
♪Can't deceive myself♪
♪I think I will understand♪
♪Won't rely on anyone anymore♪
♪Can only exist in memories♪
♪Drawing the one who loved me - you♪
♪This farewell is too much of a farce♪
♪No words for parting♪
♪The person who is weak
in love isn't me♪
♪It's you♪
♪The person who is weak
in love isn't me♪
♪It's you♪