(Ministry of Culture, Sports and Tourism
and the Korea Creative Content Agency)
Recent disappearances have been reported
in and around Guam City.
It's been reported that over ten people
have been confirmed missing.
- How am I supposed to pay you back...
- Police suspect violent crime,
- if I don't make any money?
- not just disappearances...
Hey, you think this is all on me?
That's on you for lending it to me.
Whatever. Sue me!
Goodness, you just can't stop talking.
Gosh, just hang up!
Darn, it's all soaked.
Aren't you Hong Jae Gwang?
Who on earth are you?
I said, "Who are you?"
My gosh.
What's going on?
(Police SWAT team)
We'll search for the missing victims
as soon as the suspect is in custody.
Turning left, entering the approach route.
All agents, move out!
Begin the operation.
(Yeonpung Inn)
Hey, Prosecutor Cha.
Why did you come all the way in here?
You promised you'd just watch.
It's dangerous. All right?
Don't be difficult.
Please go back outside.
This isn't even your case, Prosecutor Cha.
Goodness.
- Police! Don't move!
- Don't move!
Are you Lee Woo Gyeom?
A pleasure.
Prosecutor Cha Yi Yeon.
But we have a problem.
You're here much earlier than I expected.
Could you give me five more minutes?
I'm still treating a patient.
Would you like to see?
- What are you doing? Don't move.
- No, I'll be done in a second.
I said, "Don't move!"
All right. I'll stay perfectly still.
Drop what's in your hand
and cooperate with us.
Arrest him.
You have the right to remain silent
and to an attorney,
anything you say from this point on
will be used as evidence.
Get the forensics team in here
and tend to the victim.
- Check for any other victims.
- Yes, sir.
Prosecutor Cha.
Don't let anyone else
operate on the patient.
What was that?
If my surgical methods get mixed up
with another's,
they'll never recover.
What are you talking about?
You wouldn't understand
even if I explained it now.
I'm telling you, don't let them get
any other treatment.
You went to great lengths to find him.
You can't have him dying on us.
(Yeonpung Inn)
Multiple bodies found scattered.
One surviving victim, condition unknown.
- Requesting support from a rescue team.
- I told you, he's not a victim.
I repeat.
Requesting immediate support
from the rescue team!
(The Killer’s House)
- Here he comes.
- He's here.
Don't come too close.
- Let us through!
- Is it true a large settlement was paid?
Why are you denying the use of a weapon
during the assault?
Did you even give the victim
a proper apology?
I've cooperated fully
with the police investigation.
I apologize for the concern I've caused.
Jeffrey, please give us a statement
on the situation!
Excuse me. One moment, everyone!
This case has been closed
with no charges filed.
That's enough, all right?
But the CCTV footage confirms the assault,
doesn't it?
Please have some faith
in the police investigation.
- We're coming through. Make way!
- Jeffrey, do you admit to using a weapon?
Hey, kill the music.
Please have some faith
in the police investigation.
Gosh, you were so impressive.
You're a total lifesaver.
No, really. I had faith in you
from the very beginning.
You only got away with it
because it's your first offense.
Assault, drugs.
One little spark, and this all
blows up in your face. Got it?
Yes, that's what I'm paying you
the big bucks for.
That's what you're paying for?
Am I your friend?
Sir.
(Park Min Seo: Medical bill payment)
(Guardian Park Han Jun,
please come to the admin office)
(Jaeil Hospital)
I just stopped by
the administration office.
Have you still not heard from him?
No, not yet.
You must have been going through a lot.
Mr. Park,
I can get my hands on
the treatment for Batten disease.
But the procedures for getting it
are extremely strict.
Since it's a treatment for
a rare genetic disorder,
you're aware the bidding costs are high,
aren't you?
I know. I'll get the money,
no matter what it takes.
I should tell you upfront.
You have to be prepared
for the side effects.
What do you mean, side effects?
You didn't know?
Didn't you say your wife is a doctor?
I haven't told her yet.
Just a moment.
Would you take a look at this?
It's a treatment for genetic disorders
being developed by a domestic company.
It has also shown a positive response
in patients with Batten disease.
It also recently passed clinical trials
on children.
Now, it's still in the approval phase,
but if you were to invest
in this early project,
you won't have to get on the waiting list,
and I'll do what I can
to get you the medication quickly.
How's our Min Seo doing?
She might look fine,
but her motor skills have worsened.
And she keeps forgetting things
that happened just yesterday.
- What? Dad!
- Hey, Min Seo.
The phone you have dialed
is currently switched off.
You will be redirected to their voicemail
after the beep.
- Call charges may apply...
- Darn you...
(Please, I'm begging you, call me.)
(Moon Se Guk, Serom Biotech)
(Happy Citizens, A Just Prosecution)
- Are you coming straight from the scene?
- Yes.
(Prosecutor Cha Yi Yeon)
Good work out there, Prosecutor Cha.
The detectives did the hard work.
Ours is just beginning.
These are the documents for approval,
right?
- Yes. But are you leaving already?
- I need to be on it from the very start.
And please clip any articles from tonight
so I can review them in the morning.
Got it.
Looks like things will be hectic again
for a while.
But don't you think the case will be
reassigned anyway?
Come on. Have you forgotten?
Any case she sets her sights on is ours.
With her background
as the youngest daughter of Sejin Group,
why does she make things
so hard for herself?
I'm sure being passed over for promotion
was a big blow.
What's the big deal?
She won't be a prosecutor forever.
She could just coast for a while,
get a boost from her father,
and land a cushy job as chief counsel
on the Sejin Group's legal team.
I'd say it's 1 of 2 things.
She doesn't want to
tarnish her father's name.
What's that supposed to mean?
All conglomerate heirs are
put on the elite track.
Parents are always sizing each other up
in the center of attention.
The comparisons must be brutal.
So what's the second reason?
I guess it's just her nature.
She's someone who wants to right wrongs.
I didn't mishear back at the crime scene,
did I?
That guy, Lee Woo Gyeom,
he knew your name.
And?
Do you two happen to know each other?
Detective Gong, expand the search area
at the scene for now.
- Yes, ma'am.
- I'll ask Lee Woo Gyeom myself.
Hello.
We'll be seeing a lot of each other,
so let's skip the pleasantries.
How did you know who I was?
I've seen you in an article before.
- I have a pretty good memory.
- That's good.
Because I have
quite a few questions for you.
Back at the crime scene,
you told me you were
treating the victim, correct?
Yes. He was a terminal cancer patient.
By the time he came to me,
the cancer had already spread quite a bit.
So I...
Let's save that story for later.
What?
But you're the one who asked.
I was just confirming whether or not
you intended to kill him.
All right, then.
Let's go through this step-by-step.
What was all that stuff
in the refrigerator?
You already saw what was in there.
I'm asking you why you did it.
I want a clear explanation.
It's for research purposes.
Research.
The dismembered bodies.
What kind of research?
You're asking because you're
actually curious, right?
- Why do you ask?
- The detectives didn't believe me.
I'll have to hear it to judge, won't I?
What was the research?
I was developing a cure
for incurable diseases.
Incurable diseases?
A cure that can overcome any disease.
That's the kind of cure I was making.
But to see if the cure actually works,
- I needed a living human body.
- So, like a clinical trial?
Yes. So I conducted experiments on people.
Did you kill them during the experiments,
or...
did you experiment on them
after you killed them?
Since they died
after I administered the cure...
No, that's not it.
I think I administered the cure
after I killed them.
It really depends on the situation.
It's case-by-case.
Fine.
That's for the autopsy to determine.
How many victims are there?
Prosecutor Cha.
How long are you going to keep asking
these pointless questions?
I'm telling you I was developing a cure.
Aren't you curious about that?
In an investigation,
the first step is to establish
the scale of the crime.
Now, tell me.
The DNA analysis suggests
there are more victims.
Where are these people?
I'm sure they're around somewhere.
Did you kill them?
Come on, Prosecutor Cha.
- You can't just keep demanding answers.
- I'm asking you, did you kill them?
- It's the same as not killing them.
- Lee Woo Gyeom!
We found more than five dismembered bodies
at the scene.
And...
they are the bodies
of the missing victims, aren't they?
Here, take a look at this.
(17-17)
You know the answer, right?
Just tell me what you see.
Stop wasting my time. What's your point?
You're the one wasting time.
If we can't get on the same page,
how can this investigation get anywhere?
- Zero.
- Exactly.
I killed 17 people,
but in return, I saved the world.
So in the end, the death toll is zero.
It's as if I didn't kill a single person.
(Police)
Yes, Prosecutor Cha.
- We found them.
- Lee Woo Gyeom has 17 victims.
What? Seventeen victims?
At the crime scene of Lee Woo Gyeom,
who was arrested yesterday,
seven bodies have been discovered
out of a total of seventeen victims.
Police are determining the time of death
and identify the bodies...
Good.
- Min Seo.
- Dad,
Where have you been?
Here you go.
Let me know when you're heading out.
Okay.
So, Min Seo...
You love dolls that much?
- Yes.
- I know you love your dolls,
but it's also good to go outside...
- and play with your friends.
- But I don't have any friends.
I was only at school for a week.
I know.
It's okay, Dad.
Min Seo,
once you're all better,
you're going to make so many friends.
Dad will send you to middle school,
high school, and...
I'll even send you abroad to study.
- Really?
- Of course I mean it.
Pinky promise? Promise.
- Dad.
- Yes?
Can't we all...
live together again...
like we used to?
Of course.
Of course we will.
(Reporter Jo Woo Cheol, Daehan Ilbo News)
Well, look who it is.
Long time no see.
(It's not too late for the Prosecution...)
(to stop the false charges and listen.)
Reporter Jo.
Well, hey!
- How long has it been?
- It's been way too long.
- Have a seat.
- No, please, you have a seat.
- Here, I haven't touched this one.
- No, it's fine.
I had something on the way.
So, Reporter Jo.
Why did you suddenly leave the paper
when you were doing so well?
Don't get me started.
Remember last year when I clashed
with the Prosecution?
Well, after that, I lost all my sources,
got hit with a lawsuit, and was terrified.
I still have to support my wife, right?
So I just started my own thing.
So, how's it working out for you?
Well, it's a relief not having to
walk on eggshells around the higher-ups,
but the money's just not there.
I've been following the Jeffrey case.
He's a famous producer, isn't he?
I never imagined you'd be the one
to take his case.
A man's got to feed his family.
So here I am.
So, Mr. Park.
How about you and I...
work on something
that'll help us both get by?
A case?
You've seen the news
about Lee Woo Gyeom, right?
The serial killer who murdered 17 people?
He wants to hire you.
The retainer has nine zeroes.
Man, for that kind of money,
he could hire a big-name law firm.
He'd have a much better shot
with them than with me.
We can't have that.
I'm the one connecting you to him,
so I need to get my finder's fee.
Just kidding.
Apparently, Lee Woo Gyeom has a reason...
why it absolutely has to be you.
And what reason is that?
He said you'd know what it's about
if I mentioned Moon Se Guk.
I can get you the treatment
for Batten disease.
It's just that the procedure
is incredibly complicated.
He knows Moon Se Guk?
Yes. I heard it
from Lee Woo Gyeom himself.
How in the world does he know Moon Se Guk?
He said Moon Se Guk
was one of his victims.
He killed him? Lee Woo Gyeom did?
- Sir, did you call for a driver? Sir.
- Seriously.
But why would Lee Woo Gyeom
kill Moon Se Guk?
He wouldn't tell me the details.
Damn it.
Arrange a meeting for me with him.
Section Chief Bang, get all the case files
on Lee Woo Gyeom from Detective Gong.
But I heard they'll pick which department
gets that case after the meeting today.
Exactly. And after that meeting,
it's going to be ours.
What was that?
I told you yesterday
I was going to land this case.
I meant that I understood.
Manager Lee, schedule an interrogation
with Lee Woo Gyeom for this afternoon.
Yes, right away.
- Prosecutor Cha.
- Yes?
He has a meeting scheduled
with his attorney this afternoon.
His attorney?
Yes, come on in.
I was just heading out. Let's go.
I need to talk to you before the meeting.
All right, have a seat.
About the Lee Woo Gyeom case...
Please assign it to me.
What's the big rush?
I did all the legwork
to bring this case in myself.
I spent my whole paycheck schmoozing
the detectives at Guam Police Station.
Give me a break.
Since when you worry about money?
I know you missed the promotion,
and that's why
you're acting like this, but...
Prosecutor Cha, don't focus on cases,
but your peer reviews.
Those reviews aren't because
I did something wrong.
I know. They're all just jealous.
Some crazy kid just walks away
from her dad's perfectly good company,
rejects a match with a conglomerate heir,
and doesn't care what her superiors think.
You live your life saying
whatever is on your mind.
How could they not be jealous?
That's exactly why I should take it.
I have no conflicts, so I would be clean.
No.
If only for the media attention,
it has to be someone with
Prosecutor Kim's experience.
Even with Park Han Jun
as the defense attorney?
What?
- Park Han Jun? From the CIU?
- You know the one.
He won landmark unfair labor,
harassment, and injury cases...
for the first time in Korea.
He'd eat Prosecutor Kim for lunch.
Wait, why would Park Han Jun
even take this case?
What, is he that desperate for money?
That's not the point.
Director Oh, this is a serial murder case.
If we can't get the death penalty,
whoever prosecutes will be crucified.
No one is going to want to touch it.
Don't just play hot potato with the case
until it blows up in our faces.
Let me take the case.
Listen, you can't take on a case like this
out of some misguided sense of justice.
Are my peer reviews going to be
any different next year?
Not unless I solve a major case myself...
There's no other way, is there?
But what if our department...
had the prosecutor who finally took down
Park Han Jun?
Then you, the director who mentored me.
Wouldn't you be setting off fireworks
instead of a bomb?
Please, assign me the case.
(1 Ha 3, 1941)
This is Attorney Park Han Jun.
And this is Mr. Lee Woo Gyeom.
A pleasure.
To give you a brief summary of the case...
You killed Moon Se Guk?
Aren't you supposed to be
the composed one here?
You're very impatient.
Comes with the territory.
You hesitate, you get stabbed in the back.
Lee Woo Gyeom.
Did you really...
kill Moon Se Guk?
Yes, I did. Why?
Then...
The cure.
The cure that Moon Se Guk had...
- What did you do with it?
- What are you talking about?
All I did was kill him.
What?
But the fact that
you're looking for a cure...
It must mean someone you know is very ill.
- Don't play games with me...
- Is it a family member?
Seeing how desperate you are...
Could it be the daughter
you had so late in life?
You're more naive than I thought.
No wonder you got scammed
out of 2 million dollars.
You...
What was your relationship
with Moon Se Guk?
Tell me exactly what you know. And...
Where is the cure that Moon Se Guk had?
I'm telling you, there's no such thing.
He said he completed the clinical trials.
He was clear.
It has to exist.
Attorney Park.
There is no cure for Batten disease.
Especially for someone like Min Seo,
who's already showing early symptoms.
Death within a few years
is the only possible outcome.
Mr. Park.
Why don't we all sit down?
Attorney Park.
There's no need to get so worked up.
Let's have a real conversation.
Moon Se Guk may have lied to you,
but I, for one,
can cure Min Seo's disease.
But...
How do you...
even know my daughter's name?
Since you came all this way today,
I'll give you a retainer
of one million dollars.
And if you get me out of here,
- I'll give you another million dollars.
- Lee Woo Gyeom.
Didn't I tell you to stop playing games?
You're a lawyer.
Is being scammed all you've ever known?
I have the money, if not the cure.
You don't believe me?
Reporter Jo.
He's for real, Attorney Park.
No need to be so grateful.
It's the money
you got scammed out of anyway.
Let's just say I believe you.
But what if I just take the money...
and refuse to represent you?
I doubt that's going to happen.
Once you meet the people I've cured,
you'll be the one coming to me.
Lee Woo Gyeom.
What makes you so confident?
They all had incurable diseases,
and I'm the one who cured them.
(Taesan Bank deposit: 1 million dollars,
From Lee Woo Gyeom)
A million dollars in one go. I'm jealous.
I should've studied harder in school.
Reporter Jo.
What's the deal between
you and Lee Woo Gyeom?
I already told you.
I make the introduction,
and I get a commission.
I think it was about a week
before he was arrested.
Lee Woo Gyeom contacted me directly.
A week before he was arrested?
I thought he was crazy at first,
of course.
But he claimed he was curing people
of incurable diseases...
and told me to go find his patients.
And there was survivor,
right there in front of me.
And then, the money hit my account.
I figured, "This is meant to be,"
and I just went with it.
- You saw this for yourself, Reporter Jo?
- Yes. I'm the one who found them.
That's why I ended up writing the article.
Is that right?
All right.
First, let's go meet this survivor.
(Guam Police Station)
It looks like most of the evidence
from the scene will be admissible.
The forensics lab called this morning.
They found a common substance
in all the victims' bodies.
Apparently, it's very similar
to a compound...
from a new drug just developed in the US.
It's just strange that Lee Woo Gyeom
seems to have used it first.
The guy must've been brilliant.
He was top of his class in med school.
But then, the car accident happened,
and it was all over just like that.
He was in a vegetative state for 3 years,
you said?
That's right.
He only had two family members,
and his mother passed away
while he was in that state.
So he was left with no next of kin.
And this...
This is the victims' profiles.
I think you should take a look at these.
(Summary of victims' criminal records)
They all have criminal records?
Yes.
(Guam Medical Center)
In that case...
What kind of treatment was it?
Did he explain that to you?
He did, but what would I know
about any of that?
Then what made you decide
to go through with it?
My husband was in so much pain.
I just told him to do whatever he wanted.
Excuse me, do you know anyone else
who got the treatment before your husband?
Yes. I was referred by Sang Woo's Mom.
We used to work together.
She said her son was cured
of incurable polio.
In that case,
could I get her contact information?
There's the owner of the hair salon
right next door to where I used to work.
She and Sang Woo's mom have been friends
for a long time.
You can probably find out from her
if you go there.
(Lee Woo Gyeom: Murderer or Savior?)
Have you met any other survivors
besides him?
Besides Lee Chang Se who I just met,
it's all just been hearsay.
What? So you wrote this article...
without even meeting them?
A guy's got to eat.
An article's merit is measured in clicks,
isn't it?
There was a time...
when you were all about social justice
and fighting the Prosecution.
Now it looks like all you're fighting
is your own conscience.
Gosh, that's a great line.
You should comment that on the article.
I bet it would go viral.
- Goodness.
- Sure. I'll comment that it's all lies.
Come on. The other one sounded better.
You should post that one, word for word.
Cut the crap and tell me already.
Besides the victims
whose dismembered bodies turned up,
the other ten...
- Where did you dump their bodies?
- If you look at it from another angle,
that's not what's important
here at all.
You killed 17 people.
You should see it as me saving them,
not killing them.
Is that really what's important to you?
Not the fact that all your victims
had criminal records?
You figured that out sooner
than I expected.
So at trial, you were planning on saying,
"I only killed bad guys."
"Please let me off the hook?" Is that it?
Please. That's so childish.
I have some self-respect.
Stop posturing. This is vigilantism.
You really think that's going to hold up
in court?
Prosecutor Cha.
I saved patients with incurable diseases.
Their deaths were a necessary sacrifice
to save others.
So when exactly were you going to ask me
about that?
Even if you saved 100 or 1,000 people,
killing someone means you're a murderer,
doesn't it?
Isn't that simpler math than 17 minus 17?
Are we done here?
Sit down.
You don't get up before I do.
If you wanted to be treated like a human,
you should've acted like one.
Don't get cocky,
you murdering son of a gun.
I apologize.
Such a self-righteous ass.
- What was that?
- Nothing.
Forget it.
You don't have to tell me
where you dumped them.
I've already identified all the victims,
and I have more than enough to indict you.
I couldn't care less
about your so-called "cure."
You can go ahead
and run your mouth in court.
You're just taking your bad mood out on me
because it's hot.
If you insist on being this stubborn,
you're the one walking away with nothing.
We have to find those dump sites,
no matter what.
What? You're saying
Lee Woo Gyeom won't cooperate?
He's just trying to play games with us.
If we just let him
spoon-feed us the answers,
it'll be humiliating.
But Prosecutor Cha,
if you could persuade him,
we could find the victims much sooner...
Persuade him?
I ought to be chewing him out.
We'll find them on our own,
and then we'll indict him.
- Got it?
- Yes, ma'am. Understood.
I'll expand the search parameters
and get started.
I think we've checked everything here.
- Let's move on to the next alley.
- You guys check that way.
We'll go this way.
Excuse me, ma'am.
We'd like to ask you a few questions.
We're from the Guam Police Station.
- Do you have CCTV?
- Are any cameras installed?
At our shop...
By any chance,
could we check your CCTV footage?
- May we see your CCTV footage?
- One moment.
Just a moment.
(Bora Hair Salon)
Why are you looking for Sang Woo's Mom?
I heard that
Sang Woo made a full recovery.
- Really?
- Yes.
No way, how did that happen?
So, that's why...
Her home address...
or her new phone number...
Do you happen to have it?
She only told me she'd contact me
once she got settled.
She didn't give me any other details.
Sang Woo's Mom had it really tough
when she was here.
The money she made for his medical fees.
It was nowhere near enough.
And she couldn't look after Sang Woo
while she was at work, you know.
Look, what about places Sang Woo's Mom
or Sang Woo used to frequent?
Or someone who was like family to them,
like you?
Seriously, anything at all.
Please just tell us.
I don't know if this will help. Hold on.
Sang Woo really loved to draw, you know.
Here it is, right here.
Take a look at this.
He was so talented, wasn't he?
- Over there.
- That way.
Haven't seen them.
Do you...
No, I haven't seen them.
The serial murder suspect
and a former medical student.
We're here at the scene where police
are searching for more of his victims.
Public outcry is growing
over the massive police mobilization.
They say it's a waste of manpower,
all based on the suspect's single word.
- Reporter Jo.
- Yes?
The victims.
Do you have any of them identified?
The police aren't releasing any names yet.
In that case, I need you to...
do some digging on your own.
Okay, I'll do that.
You've had a long day, Prosecutor Cha.
- Welcome back.
- Lee Woo Gyeom's psych eval results.
- They're in?
- Yes.
(Guam Central Dist. Prosecutors' Office)
(Polygraph Test Results)
Mr. Lee Woo Gyeom.
Is it true that you murdered people?
Yes.
Is it false that you treated people
and saved their lives?
No.
(First Trial: No deception indicated,
Second Trial: No deception indicated)
Are you sure
this test was administered correctly?
Yes. They said his responses were normal.
They even ran a different test pattern,
and the results were still the same.
And the funny thing is,
they said he was happy that he passed.
Why are you still just searching?
Lee Woo Gyeom is using the location
of the bodies as a bargaining chip.
Just play along and wrap this up.
If I do that, he'll lead me
by the nose for the entire trial.
The public is in an uproar
because we can't find the victims.
I understand.
I'll think it over.
This isn't a confession.
You've written your own heroic epic.
Depending on
whether you believe me or not...
That's what changes the genre.
Whatever the genre, the ending
to this story is the death penalty.
Fine.
- Since we're on the subject, tell me.
- Tell me what?
You said you treated people.
So tell me all about it.
Are you serious?
Want to start with the cure?
Actually, no.
Start with how you made it.
Are you going to tell me or not?
The cure...
It all began with a dying potted plant.
I poured some leftover liquid
from my research into the pot,
and when I checked on it the next day,
the dead flower had come back to life.
That's the cure?
Yes.
Go on.
Next, I took that cure,
and put it in a fish tank.
My dead goldfish came back to life.
Then there was a cat with an injured leg.
It recovered so well that...
it was jumping high again in no time.
At this point, aren't you curious too?
If it works on humans.
That's when you started killing people?
I told you, it wasn't murder.
It was research.
- How long did you plan to keep this up?
- But the thing is...
Humans are definitely a lot harder.
How long...
did you plan on going around
killing people?
Seventeen people.
That was it.
Why?
Because the experiment was a success.
Who was the last victim?
Hong Jae Gwang.
Are you sure about that?
Yes.
You'll understand
when you see him for yourself.
It's a little complicated
to explain in words.
(Guam District Prosecutors' Office)
Okay.
Why didn't you resist arrest?
You could've gotten away.
I was planning to turn myself in
after treating my patient,
Lee Chang Se, anyway.
Turn yourself in?
I was just waiting for the right moment
to prove my abilities.
You didn't catch me.
Why do you insist on proving it,
specifically through a trial?
Because that's the most official,
indisputable way.
That's how I can be forgiven for my sins.
Not forgiveness. Condemnation.
We'll see about that.
Okay.
All right.
I've heard enough about the history
of your so-called cure.
Now,
it's your turn to help me out.
Where did you dump the remaining victims?
On the mid-slope of Mount Cheonggye,
facing the river,
at the 100-meter mark.
Be more thorough!
- Bring it here.
- Yes, sir.
- Let's go.
- All right.
I heard there's something called
a plea bargain in trials.
- Yes.
- Well, I don't want a lighter sentence.
I want to make a different kind of deal.
First, I'll need you...
to help me so that
I can prove my abilities in court.
(Liked by 99_guswn and others)
Okay, thank you.
Attorney Park.
No matter how much I dig,
I'm coming up empty.
I'm thinking,
since Sang Woo's leg was injured,
maybe he just drew those pictures
at home by himself?
We have to find him.
Right.
- Hello?
- Mr. Park? Hi, it's the hair salon.
Right.
So this is the place.
Is anyone here?
You're going to demonstrate your abilities
in court?
Because I've been indulging you,
you're getting pretty cocky, aren't you?
Aren't you the one who's excited,
Prosecutor Cha?
Thrilled this case will make your career,
aren't you?
Or is it thanks to your powerful father
that you think you're above it all?
This punk.
You've really crossed the line today.
- Mom.
- Yes, sweetie?
Hey! Bring me a shovel!
I found it!
Over here! I found it!
- Get a shovel over here!
- We found it!
- Right here!
- Hey, get the gear over here now!
- Over here! We found it!
- We found it!
- On my way!
- I said it's over here.
- Yes, coming!
- Here! Over here!
- Hey, hurry up!
I found it! It's here, right here!
I think it's Hong Jae Gwang.
The body's been completely drained
of blood.
You'll see for yourself once you check.
It's complicated to explain in words,
you see.
Moon Se Guk lied,
but as for me,
I can cure Min Seo's illness.
Every single one of them...
was treated by me.
Now it's your turn to cross the line,
Prosecutor Cha.
Come over to my side.
I will personally show you in court.
How I can save a life...
without so much as a scalpel.
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)