BAD GUYS
[Episode 1]
Look at you doing interviews. You made it.
No, not at all.
Take care.
Wait. Here.
Right.
Hello, I'm Gun-wook Nam from Homicide
Team Two, at Dobok Police Station.
I'm 34 years old.
I'm in charge of almost all of
the major cases in Dobok-dong.
Over a half a year ago,
a series of incidents have happened
in the Southeastern Seoul.
The culprit picked any woman
on the street on a rainy day.
We uncovered his criminal patterns,
and now we're on a stakeout.
It looks like a serial murder case.
Aren't you afraid?
Have you ever felt this way?
I may not be able to see my family again,
even though I'm looking
at their faces right now.
Look over there.
Isn't that a knife?
Damn it.
When you become a detective
you encounter those criminals
who you need to catch
even if it costs your life.
He's not a just petty criminal.
My son's face I'm seeing now...
My wife's face...
I may not be able to see them again.
Stop, you bastard!
Me and my co-workers,
cannot risk our lives while on duty.
If we die,
who will protect our family?
Who will?
Detective Nam!
People are shocked over
the news of Detective Nam's Murder.
He worked at Dobok Police Station
and was murdered while chasing a culprit.
He was always eager to catch criminals
and had a strong sense
of responsibility to keep the public safe.
Many people from all walks of life
mourned his death.
They also called for countermeasures
against violent criminals
who have developed
more intellectual offenses...
Grandpa.
Min-joon.
Do not
follow in your father's footsteps.
Understood?
Yes.
Gu-tak Oh.
Where is he now?
Why are you looking
for that Mad Dog all of a sudden?
BAD GUYS
EPISODE 1
We learned a lesson from the murder case
of a Dobok police officer.
We, the police, are too naive
and predictable
to cope with the crimes
of antisocial and psychopathic killers.
A hundred thousand police officers
choose their job
not to serve 50 million citizens,
but to obtain their own job security.
They're no different from the rest
of the 50 million citizens.
Unfortunately, this is
the reality of Korean police.
Then, what should we do?
You're saying you can't catch those
violent criminals
with your current forces, right?
What kind of a backup plan do you have?
We should stop our ordinary citizens
from suffering from violent crimes.
You're right.
You have a point.
Please share your plan,
if you have any, Inspector Yoo.
A plan...
Speaking of a plan...
Hey, what are you up to these days?
You should go easy on the alcohol.
You're not young anymore.
You must take care of your health.
You should say that to your wife, not me.
Why did you want to see me?
You...
Don't you want to get reinstated?
Why are you looking for Mad Dog
out of the blue?
You know my son, Gun-wook.
What about him?
Did his wife run away?
Other kids always insist
they don't want to follow
in their father's footsteps.
But my Gun-wook was different.
"Like my father,
I want to become a great police officer."
A few days ago,
he died.
He was stabbed to death.
He died earlier than me.
How can this happen...
So, you want to release a mad dog like me
and make me fetch Gun-wook's killer.
Is that it?
Fetch one
that's still fresh and alive.
Then, what?
You want to skin him on your own?
You...
If you handle this case well enough,
I'll help you work off the anger
and grudge buried deep inside you.
Beating up an innocent guy is violence.
But beating up a bad guy is
justice.
I heard Gu-tak Oh's nickname is Mad Dog.
He considers brutality
and violence essential for investigation.
Whenever he believes
the suspect is an evil culprit,
regardless of his rank and power,
regardless of whose side he is on,
Gu-tak Oh bares his teeth
and tears him apart.
That's why he's called Mad Dog.
Some police officers
took bribes from gangs,
but they had to quit their job
when Detective Oh tracked them down.
He's not a boy at puberty.
He can take care of his own business.
Just sit tight. It won't take long.
If you handle this case well enough,
I'll help you work off the anger
and grudge buried deep inside you.
What?
-What?
-No, nothing.
No! Why are you doing this?
Beating up an innocent guy is violence.
But beating up a bad guy is
justice.
What? What's wrong?
No, nothing.
Why are you doing this?
No!
Do I have to beat you up?
Son of a bitch!
Who are you, you bastard?
Detective Oh, please stop.
You may kill him for real.
All right.
Let's prepare three more mad dogs.
When Dongbang gang conquered Seoul
two years ago,
how many days do you think it took?
Twenty five days.
One district per day.
They conquered all the way
from Guro to Nowon district.
This guy led the gang.
Ong-chul Park.
As soon as Dongbang Gang dominated Seoul,
he got caught and was sentenced
to 28 years in prison.
He's now a prisoner
in Daejeon penitentiary.
Who is it?
What?
Who painted your face black and blue?
How is he doing?
Is he likely to regenerate himself?
Regenerate himself?
Are you daydreaming?
Son of a bitch!
Go!
Should I approve him?
Let me hear about the rest of them first.
Who is next?
Tae-soo Jung.
A hit man.
Tae-soo Jung is a hit man.
No one knows who, why, where
or how he kills.
His background is also unknown.
Then, how come he got caught?
-In one murder case...
-He turned himself in.
Wearing a shirt stained
with the victim's blood,
he walked into the police station
and turned himself in.
What a crazy bastard.
He was sentenced to 22 years.
He's now imprisoned in
Jeonjoo penitentiary.
Who is the last one?
You must be very familiar with him.
The culprit of the Hwayeondong
incident two years ago.
Jung-moon Lee?
He had an IQ of 165
when he was 12 years old.
He was the youngest member
of Mensa in Korea.
He also earned the youngest title
of Ph.D. in philosophy and math.
Which of his titles
do you think is most shocking?
The youngest serial killer.
From December 2011 to August 2012,
he killed 15 people in total.
But when I investigated the crime scene,
no fingerprints, no single hair strand,
and of course, no footprints.
To put it in a nutshell,
there's no trace of Jung-moon Lee
at the murder scene at all.
Oh, there's only one thing.
The victim's body.
-Is he a psychopath?
-You know PCL-R?
It's a psychopath test.
He scored 38 out of 40 points.
Why should we choose these people?
No, I should rather say these beasts.
Ong-chul Park's power,
Tae-soo Jung's technique,
and Jung-moon Lee's intelligence.
If we can make use of all these three,
no criminals can escape from us.
Beasts enjoy socializing with others.
They will obey my orders.
I think this is too risky.
You also said on TV that we can't catch
those violent criminals effectively
with our current forces, right?
But I never implied we should take
this kind of measure.
In order to catch beasts,
setting other beasts free is...
Get one of them for me.
What?
You think it's gross?
It looks gross.
So, you don't even want to touch it.
Since you don't want to touch it,
you can't put it on a hook.
Is that right?
I'm not sure what you're trying to say.
Without this bait, we can't catch fish.
I'll take care of everything.
Let's just give it a try.
PRISONER TRANSPORT
MINISTRY OF JUSTICE
Where am I going?
Aren't I supposed to be transferred?
Are you mute?
You should answer when I'm asking, punk!
I memorized your face. You are so dead.
Why are you drinking without any snack?
Chief told me that you're the fishhook,
and Ong-chul Park, Tae-soo Jung,
Jung-moon Lee are worms.
He explained a simple thing in a hard way.
It probably means you should put
the worms on a hook well
in order to catch fish.
Let's work hard together.
What handshake? That's embarrassing.
Forget about it.
What are you doing now?
Are you trying to take a nap?
Then, what else?
Should I play with you until they arrive?
Wake me up when they get here.
Also, don't even expect me
to use honorifics with you,
just because you're higher in rank.
When those punks with higher ranks tried
to boss me around,
I showed them who's boss.
Change.
Why are you giving me civilian clothes?
Are you trying
to make me look like a civilian,
so you can bury me somewhere in secret?
Hey, you bastard. I'm asking you
why you gave me these clothes!
It's your day off.
What kind of a day off?
Am I a soldier or something?
Just change your clothes, okay?
I just asked out of curiosity.
Why are you so annoyed?
Don't be annoying to me.
Even without you,
my life is already annoying enough.
If you don't mind,
let's both keep smiling.
Okay, then. I'll change my clothes.
PRISONER TRANSPORT
MINISTRY OF JUSTICE
Who are you?
I asked you first, you little boy.
Don't raise your hand at me.
You may get killed.
You...
Look here. I raised my hands.
What can you do?
Do you want to get beaten up?
-How dare you...
-Stop.
Well, who are you, Miss?
I'm not a Miss. I'm Mi-young Yoo.
I'm a police inspector.
Both of you will be under my supervision.
I guess the other one is running late.
Let's start first.
Please follow me.
Is she being confident or rude?
Is she kidding me?
Gosh.
Please make yourselves at home.
Shall we begin?
What you see here are the case materials
regarding the serial murders
in Southeastern Seoul since last December.
The number of victims is eight so far.
Please take your time
to read the materials.
Why are you showing them to us?
Why do you think I am?
Because we want you
to catch the serial killer.
Oh, dear. I almost bursted into laughter.
Are you kidding me, Miss?
Do you think your life is so boring?
Everything looks easy
because you're high in rank, right?
Hey, gangster. Sit down
if you don't want to get hurt.
Come here, so I can understand.
Let her finish first.
Stop acting stupid.
Why does this son of a bitch
keep talking to me?
What are you babbling on about?
Your breath stinks!
Stop it!
Stop what?
It's just getting interesting.
Please continue.
While you continue, please listen.
I was told that if any of you
catch that serial killer,
you will have a five-year reduction
in sentence.
You were going to tell them this, right?
Then, you could have just spit it out.
They pretend not to listen,
but they actually do.
Isn't it right?
Still, not everyone can get
his sentence reduced.
Only the one who catches the culprit.
If Ong-chul Park catches the culprit,
nothing for Tae-soo Jung.
You know, we're living
in a competitive capitalist society.
Please understand. Any further questions?
No questions?
Then, you can continue with
what you were doing.
Who are you, mister?
Come on, I told you to continue with
what you were doing.
I'll deal with you later.
Who is this guy?
He's Detective Gu-tak Oh,
who will also supervise you.
I see, he's a detective.
Mister, what are you planning
to do with us again?
-Are you suffering from dementia?
-Dementia?
That sounds great.
It's such a torture
to live your daily life
remembering every detail so clearly.
-Is what he said true?
-Yes.
You're going to legally release us
until we catch that punk?
Yes, correct.
Of course there are some conditions.
What conditions?
Alcohol, women and driving are banned.
Violence and weapons are also banned.
Banned, banned, banned.
Technically everything is banned.
But you know what? Just do everything.
How can a human survive
without drinking alcohol?
Detective Oh.
But there's one thing
that you should agree upon.
Even if you feel humiliated.
Inspector Yoo.
What is this? Is this a watch?
We should be punctual, right?
You're degrading me.
You don't like a digital watch?
-It's a digital ankle bracelet.
-A digital ankle bracelet?
The one that sex offenders wear?
This can't be. How dare you...
If anyone sees this on me,
they'll think I'm a rapist.
You're in no position to be picky.
You mean, we criminals are not allowed
to decline an unjust offer?
Seriously, you're driving me crazy.
I can't accept that, either.
We also need human rights.
"Condemn the sin,
but not the sinner."
The sinner is the one
who committed the sin.
How would it be possible
not to condemn the sinner?
Tae-soo Jung, your sin is murder.
That's why you're condemned.
Ong-chul Park, your sin is
violence, kidnapping, confinement
and so on.
That's why you're condemned.
You should claim human rights and what not
when you're released later.
At this moment,
even if I fed you burnt rice,
you should eat it up, feeling thankful,
unless you want to starve yourself.
The way you talk is quite irritating.
Mister!
Mister, what are you?
I'm using honorifics
and treating you quite well
which, by the way, I'm not cut out for.
But, if you behave like this,
you'll be in trouble.
Do you want to die?
Ong-chul Park, you son of a bitch.
If you can't bite, don't dare to bark.
You may end up getting bitten and dead.
Seriously...
Who the hell are you people?
Stop here.
Okay.
Detective Oh.
Officer.
What?
Hurry up.
Come on, seriously...
That's what happened.
Gosh, seems like you had a hard time.
Didn't he take any money from you?
-No.
-You're not hurt, right?
My well-being doesn't matter much.
I'm sorry that punk got away...
-Your shoulder looks seriously hurt.
-I'm ashamed.
You should get treatment
as soon as possible.
-I'm fine.
-No, you're not.
You look hurt. Why don't you take a look?
If you leave your injury untreated,
you'll suffer from aftereffects.
The wound here. Is it because of a blow?
Yes, probably.
If you take a blow,
you usually don't get a cut,
but your skin pops open.
Why did you get a cut?
You said he hit you with the toilet lid.
Then, why is your head intact?
Is your head
made of diamond?
You punk. How much salary do you receive?
Three or four million won
a month based on your experience?
Jin-sook's mom, who lives downstairs,
runs a corner shop.
Jong-min's dad, who lives upstairs,
runs a laundry shop.
Hae-nam's uncle, who lives next door,
runs an Internet cafe.
They all pay taxes.
Your salary comes from the taxes they pay.
If you're living off their money,
eating, drinking, and buying your clothes,
you should not lie, at least.
Isn't that common courtesy
for our citizens?
I didn't lie.
Your whole body is telling a lie,
but your damn mouth in denying it?
Which one is wrong, then?
-His mouth is wrong.
-I know.
His mouth is wrong.
Then all I need to do
is get rid of his mouth.
I can catch him
only if you tell me the truth,
How did Jung-moon Lee escape?
This guy says he's going
to confess everything.
He's going to tell.
All of a sudden, he started to beat me up.
I had no other choice.
When did I beat you up?
I was just playing with you.
Oh, here's your cap.
Now tell us.
How did Jung-moon escape?
He said he wanted to go to the restroom,
so we stopped here.
-I'll go buy some cigarettes.
-Okay.
Do your business.
Number two? Come on.
We don't have much time. Hurry up.
Scream.
What?
Scream out.
Are you okay? Where did he go?
The key.
It's been exactly two hours
since Jung-moon Lee took flight.
He could be anywhere in this country.
If we don't catch him right now,
we'll be in trouble.
We didn't agree to join you yet.
Why are you giving us orders?
That pissing me off.
We?
What? Are you're in or not?
How long were you sentenced?
Twenty eight years.
You don't want to waste
your whole life in jail, right?
Then, catch Jung-moon Lee
even if it means risking your life.
Is your offer still valid?
We'll reduce four years
for the one who catches him.
Okay, I got it.
Still, it's way too embarrassing
to wear this.
Give it to me.
If I wear this,
can I legally beat up people?
As long as you don't kill them.
I can't guarantee that.
Consider this as a warm-up
before it gets real.
Can you catch Jung-moon Lee?
Thanks for the sentence reduction.
I'm pretty sure
that Jung-moon Lee went looking
for this girl, Yu-jin Yang.
She could be his last victim.
She gave a critical testimony against him,
resulting in his life sentence.
She is the one that Jung-moon Lee loved.
Wait for me.
Is this Jung-moon Lee?
Why? Does he look familiar?
So, where is this girl now?
I don't know.
As soon as Jung-moon Lee's sentence
was confirmed, she disappeared.
But I know someone
who may know her whereabouts.
KOREA TAE KWON DO
Hey, you should finish within an hour.
Can you do that?
I'll take care of everything.
You just handle the aftermath.
Things tend to end up messy
when I get involved.
Are you sure Jung-moon Lee
is really looking for Yu-jin Yang?
How come you know so much about his case?
Is there anything
that you're hiding from me?
Ong-chul Park and Tae-soo Jung.
Can we trust them?
In order to live
like a decent human being,
what do you think is the most essential?
Desperation.
It's hard to find someone
as desperate as them.
Trust them.
Are you sure they're ready
to become a decent human being?
If you break the ankle bracelet,
you can run away.
Need some help?
We're live in such a small country.
Even if I run away, I can't go far.
I'll solve this case
and receive a sentence reduction.
Me? Or you?
Me.
We're closed today.
What the hell?
Where is Sung-beom Ma? I need to see him.
Gosh, you're drinking in daytime.
What are you staring at?
The girl who worked here two years ago.
Her name is Yang...
What's her name again?
Yu-jin Yang.
Oh, right. Yu-jin Yang. Where is she?
Are you the police?
I don't like the police, either.
-Me?
-No, me.
We came to find someone.
You know Yu-jin Yang, right?
Mr. Ma said you took her away.
You were going to sell her off
because she owed you.
Hey.
Who are you?
I won't ask you again.
Where is Yu-jin Yang?
Fifty-two minutes.
She was sold off far, far away.
I'm not sure at how much she was traded.
You know, she's like Chun-hyang
from the fairytale.
No, was that Sim-cheong?
The one who had to trade herself for rice.
So where? Where is she now?
BUSAN STATION
To Yeonsan-dong.
Hey, is this Baljjong?
This is Ong-chul, you know.
Ong-chul Park, you silly boy.
Who's Ong-chul Kim?
You're right.
No, I'm not discharged from prison yet.
I'm still in prison. Right. In prison.
But it's kind of hard
to explain my situation.
You're still living in Busan, right?
Are you still familiar with hostess girls?
Oh, you found her?
Write it down.
Room 203, Hana apartment, Yeonsan-dong.
Her phone number, hurry!
Who is it?
Here it is.
I'm here to read the gas meter.
Gas?
INCOMING CALL
Hello.
-Is this Ms. Yu-jin Yang?
-Yes.
I'm Inspector Mi-young Yoo
from Seoul Metro Police Agency.
You know Jung-moon Lee, right?
Jung-moon Lee is...
Hello? Ms. Yang?
Jung-moon Lee is coming to you now.
Are you listening?
Ms. Yang? Hello?
It's been a long time.
Hello? Ms. Yang?
Hello?
Ms. Yang!
How...
How did you know?
How did you know I was here?
Do you
feel sorry for me?
Why?
Should I?
Why should I feel sorry for you?
The detective
who was in charge of my case
told me that you feel sorry for me.
Why?
Why are you feeling sorry for me?
I don't feel sorry for you at all.
Don't you remember? You tried to kill me.
Why should I feel sorry for someone
who tried to kill me?
I have...
no memory...
of trying to kill you.
KOREA TAE KWON DO
HANA APARTMENT
It must be that building.
Who will catch him first?
It's not you.
If it's not me, it won't be you either.
-Shall we move?
-Let's go.
You punk.
Let me catch that bastard, huh?
-Go for it!
-Goodness.
What the hell are you doing?
Jung-moon Lee?
Did you get your face tanned?
He looks quite tanned.
Did I
really try to kill you?
What about those countless people
that you've killed?
Do you remember killing them?
You killed all of them, right?
What? You killed them!
These are all the people
you've killed, you bastard.
I'm telling you one more time.
I really...
don't remember anything.
I didn't kill them.
That's why you're crazy, you psychopath!
Trust me.
I didn't kill anyone, Yu-jin.
Yes, you did.
I saw your face...
that time.
I sensed everything.
Yu-jin.
Happy is dead.
You know what, Yu-jin?
I'm so sad.
You told me that
ever since you saw your parents die,
you often don't remember things
that even happened an hour ago.
Your doctor also said that
it might be caused by the shock.
While you had no memory
of what you were doing,
you were on a killing spree, you know?
-No.
-Yes. I'm right.
You're the one who killed them.
You're the one who tried to kill me.
You! Jung-moon Lee!
Aren't you the one
who killed your own parents?
You killed them
but pretended not to remember it.
I didn't kill them.
That son of a bitch
confused Hana studio apartment
with Hana apartment.
Keep running!
Damn it.
I will kill him.
It's because I got a cramp in my leg.
Remember this clearly.
Never forget
that you killed me.
Do you understand?
-Here it is.
-Wait.
Right.
Let's die together.
Jung-moon!
Where are you?
I'm looking for you!
You should answer me,
you bastard.
What are you doing now?
What if the hostage dies
while we're waiting to arrest the suspect?
We need to save the hostage first.
Hey buddy.
There you are.
What? Are you going to kill her?
If you try to kill her,
you'll be in big trouble.
If you get shot,
it will hurt you pretty badly.
Do you want to the hard way
or the easy way?
Okay, then.
The hard way it is.
Detective Oh!
Ong-chul, that's Jung-moon Lee.
Are you okay?
What the...
My car!
Nice to meet you, Jung-moon.
Don't hold a grudge against me
because of the shot earlier.
The situation was bad.
I had to pull the trigger.
Jung-moon.
Don't attempt to pump out water
in a flooded area.
You'd better swim instead.
You're more likely to survive that way.
Get more details from that Inspector Yoo.
If you want to be a part of our team,
join us at the pub.
I insisted we should send
you back to jail.
But Detective Oh said we need you.
I don't know why.
So, let me ask you again.
Don't you want to live
like a decent human being?
I was running frantically.
Then, that bastard fell from the sky.
Right in front of me.
He fell from the sky,
like Jack and the Beansprout.
-Jack and the Beanstalk.
-Beanstalk?
Are you sure? Beanstalk?
-I'm sure it's the beansprout.
-It's the beanstalk.
How ignorant you are.
You're so uneducated.
Seriously.
Are you already finished?
Sit.
I hope you can catch
the criminal next time.
Of course.
You must feel great.
What? Are you leaving me out
because I'm a woman?
Let's work hard.
From now on, we're on the same team.
Teamwork?
I don't expect such a thing from you.
Care for teammates?
That's bullshit.
What I want from you is only one thing.
Those villains who refuse
to live like a decent human being,
attack and rip them to pieces like dogs.
Don't you know why we,
mad dogs, are scary?
Once bitten by us, they'll die.
Let's drink.
Let's drink today.
From tomorrow, we should find
and knock down that beast,
who's been killing so many women around.
Got it?
Let's do that.
Why did you accept this project?
Ong-chul Park, Tae-soo Jung,
and Jung-moon Lee.
Why did you pick those three?
I did some research
before I started to work with you,
and I found something interesting.
They all went to jail
around the same time.
Ong-chul Park in June 2012,
Tae-soo Jung in July 2012,
and Jung-moon Lee in September 2012.
And one more thing.
You were suspended from your job
in August 2012.
-Do you have any connection...
-I told you not to be authoritative!
Subtitles by Netflix
Translated by You-jeong Kim
Does that woman matter that much?
-Are you okay?
-You killed me.
And the woman saved me.
What is the reason
the culprit murder people?
Smell of blood.
Help me! My mom...
This is not the first time, is it?
If I want to beat his record,
I need to kill as many
as possible at once.
Rainy days, smell of blood,
and compulsive crimes.
He's targeting the survivors
from the hidden murder cases.
What is this a funeral?
Why is everyone so gloomy?
Aren't you going to catch him?
Blood. He'll beat the record
if he kills one more.
And we have one survivor left.
You should protect her on your own.
Stop trying to hide yourself out of fear.
I wish I could.
Where did he go?
I'll definitely catch that culprit.
Ripped and resynced by
gabbyu @ Subscene