Are you okay, Noonim?
Don't you have to go to a hospital?
My friend is a doctor. Should I call him? He lives in the next building.
I'm okay now.
I get surprised easily and have an indigestion problem.
Mainly because of somebody.
I'm sorry. I should've not brought the dumplings.
- Did you bring these dumplings?
- Yes.
Of course, she gets choked on it because she doesn't like dumplings!
What are you talking about it? I love dumplings.
Oh, did you?
Look at him. He doesn't even know what his wife likes.
But still, I'll ask my friend just in case.
Hello? It's me. Can you talk right now?
Oh, I was wondering, what should I do if somebody gets food stuck in their throat?
- They don't have any other symptoms, but--
- Yes, aunt! It's me!
Can I talk to you right now?
Yes, James! What's going on?
Yes! There's somebody who had food stuck in their throat. Should we go to an emergency room, doctor?
Oh, that happened to whom?
Ah, to my old friend.
Oh. Are they okay now?
Oh, yes. That' a relief.
Then, just let them drink some warm water and relax.
Jjung-a!
If any other symptoms come up, call me.
- Yes!
- Who is it?
- Ah, it's Mr. Eems.
- Yeah?
He said his friend had something stuck in their throat.
- His old friend?
- Yes.
- Who would that be?
- I don't know.
Noonim, my friend said, since you're breathing fine, so it's okay--
Drink some warm water and relax. That's what Man Jung said.
Why did you even call Man Jung?
- Who would that be?
- Oh!
I'll go to the door.
Hello, grandfa--
Wow.
Hello, ajussi.
Hello, kid.
You finally recognize me properly.
Also, could you call me an uncle, not an ajussi?
Call me, uncle Eems.
- Yes...
- Ba Wi, come inside!
I guess he came here to find his dad!
- Did you come here because your dad wasn't coming back?
- Did you come here to find me, Ba Wi?
My friend said to call him if you have any unusual symptoms in 30 minutes. He said he'll run right here.
Thank you so much. You're very kind!
My dad is always kind!
He said he was very popular with girls!
That's right, dad?
- This boy!
- Is that so? I think so, too!
- Yes?
- Grandfather... no, ajussi... no, uncle Eems!
- Yes!
- That's a toupee, right?
Ba Wi...
I dyed my hair because of you, you little boy!
Woo Jung Hoo looks pretty good after dying his hair!
By the way, why did you come here today?
Ah, I heard that you met up with Soon Jung.
Did she run to you already and told about it?
She didn't run to me.
But Jae Hee said to me as well that it's utterly ridiculous.
It's too salty!
Is it? It was good!
Man Jung said you shouldn't eat yet.
By the way, what the hell was that?
I heard that you go against the children's marriage because I and Soon Jung needs to be together?
No, I didn't go against their marriage!
I said we should postpone the wedding until Chae Woon becomes the legal daughter of Jung Won!
Even though Chae Woon becomes the legal daughter of Jung Won, she's still Soon Jung's daughter as well.
How can you think of such ridiculous thoughts with a person who's going to be our in-law?
I was thinking of your future.
There's still a long time to live from now on!
Are you going to get older by yourself lonely?
Then, what about you? Aren't you going to be in the same situation as me--
- Ah!
- Ah?
That's why you did that. You felt bad to start a new life first, so you wanted to get me someone before.
How can you think about it that way!
You don't know my sincerity.
What kind of sincerity is that? It's just a delusion.
A delusion?
The first love that you dreamed of came in front of you! As a single!
If you married your first love, then you would've not become the stubborn, stingy person you're now.
You didn't want to, but I made you marry me, so this tragedy happened!
Did I say something wrong?
Sure.
I guess it can be like that.
Because of my bad temper, I made you who never had to suffer, suffer.
I pestered you so much, so you got the indigestion issue.
At least you admit that.
So, it was because I thought about your future, and your new start, purely on a friendship level.
I get it.
Thank you.
Okay. I'll start my new life first.
And you should start a new life with that good-looking, tall guy across the hall.
Why are you keep trying to make me involved with professor Son?
What about you? You had been trying to involve me with Soon Jung the whole time!
Anyway.
Either we are starting a new life separately or whatever, let's focus on Jae Hee getting married first.
Then, I'll get going.
Ah.
How is your indigestion?
I'm fine now.
That's good to hear.
Wait.
You know that I have a therapy session tomorrow, right?
The doctor said I should come with you. Can you make it?
I don't know.
I don't know the two who will start new lives separately needs to go to a therapy session together.
That's true. Well, you can leave.
Why is he acting like that when I said I'm going to help him start his new life?
My goodness!
When did he eat all of the dumplings?
He doesn't even like dumplings!
Is it like when I ate all of the egg buns that Soon Jung made?
Since you're helping me, the work is getting done faster!
There are so many things to do!
I hope this goes well, so you can pay off all of your debt.
You said you still have a lot of debt even after you sold your studio, right?
Yes. I'm still paying off my best!
I heard from Chief Yoo that your debt is because you were losing money for your contractors.
I can't turn away from people going through trouble.
But because I sold that place, I moved into the Samgwang villa, so I met you!
That's true.
I wish I can make enough money to get our own place.
Yes. A small and pretty house.
That day has to come as soon as possible! But why did my mom said we should wait for what?
I think she has a plan in her mind for your father.
I was thinking about this in the office today.
I thought about what it would be like in your mother's position. And then, that just popped in my head.
I guess my mom is a unique person.
- Do you want some coffee?
- Sounds good.
I'll make some in decaf.
Ah, you should enjoy the scent first. Like this.
Did you hear anything from Park Pil Hong yet?
Ah...
In fact, I ran into him earlier today.
He came by to pick his stuff up.
You should've called me!
I got his phone number.
Also, I got his promise to keep in touch.
Give me his number. I'm going to meet up with him.
Moong-i.
Why don't you give him some time?
He said he wants to be a good father for you.
Do you trust his words?
I don't trust that! I'm never going to trust him!
If he were a trust-worthy person, then he would've not deceived us in the first place!
But I still want to trust him.
Let's not push him too hard and see what he does.
But what if he makes another trouble?
Why don't we give him a shot? He's your father.
Let's do it that way, shall we?
Your phone is ringing a lot.
This time it's aunt Man Jung?
I guess everyone's gathered right now.
And I think aunt Man Jung had no choice but to call me.
I guess you didn't have a good relationship with Bit Chae Woon's aunt?
I was in a good relationship with everybody.
Ah, besides with Woo Jae Hee.
What about with Bit Chae Woon? Did you have a good relationship with her?
It wasn't good nor bad.
Is it decided to fail the full-time position transition of Bit Chae Woon?
Yes.
I think she'll leave the company soon.
With her personality, it'll be strange if she doesn't leave.
I bet she must get so annoyed.
She doesn't get recognized in the company, and she doesn't get accepted as a daughter to my mom.
That's good. It's going according to the plan.
Are you really happy about it?
What?
I don't think you're truly pleased about it.
Then?
You look empty.
I think Seo Ah, you're actually not a person who hates and attack other people.
Did you just call me by my name?
Now you're crossing the line.
If you get warm affection all the time,
you'll be a brighter, warmer, and sweet person than anybody else.
To make you into that kind of person,
I'll love you a lot, Seo Ah.
Jae Hee's mom! Jae Hee's mom!
Is she going to be okay now?
Ah, really...
We're strangers now. I should be nice.
Yes?
Her voice sounds fine.
What was that?
She's really fine now.
Ah, really!
Young lady Min Jae.
She still loves the president.
How can I make her realize the president's feeling?
Ah! That's right.
I guess Chae Woon came home!
Oh, Chae Woon!
You came home late tonight!
- I was helping Jae Hee's work a bit.
- Oh. It's cold outside, right?
Where's Mr. Woo?
He's going to stay overnight at the office. He has a very important contract tomorrow.
Oh. He's working really hard.
Earlier today, Mr. Woo's mother came by here.
Ah, really?
She's against our marriage, right?
No, she's not against it,
but she has a different reason that she needs to think about it.
Then, it was true that...
What? What are you talking about it?
I heard about you and James from Jae Hee today.
My goodness! Chae Woon!
It's nothing like that!
Are you sure?
It's nothing like that! There's nothing.
But you don't sound like it.
Chae Woon! My goodness.
I'm going to see the CEO soon, and talk about your wedding.
- That sounds good, right?
- Yes, sure.
- You should wash and come out! I'll prepare for your dinner.
- Okay...
- Hey, I recommend the pink one!
- Okay.
It can be not enough, so we should ask about this...
- The red one is pretty, too!
- My god!
What are you guys doing? What is this unusual scene right now?
Unni, are you coming home now?
- Unni, you're home!
- Hey, noona!
Lee Hae Deun, did you do it well earlier today?
Yes. I'm going to work for the online business team from tomorrow!
I was so surprised to hear that younger noona got head-hunted to the big noona's workplace!
I was so surprised as well!
It's not getting head-hunted, but it's just a contract position.
It can work out after doing the work! Congratulations my sister!
I'm happy for you, unni!
- Thank you.
- Congrats!
But what are you guys looking at?
Ah, Lee Ra Hoon is thinking of taking over a second-hand food truck.
Even it's second-hand, it's going to be expensive!
We're getting it from a person we met through our boss, and it came out 40% cheaper than usual.
40% cheaper?
It's that one.
It's a street food franchise.
Just with this, it looks okay.
Right? I think so, too!
Tomorrow we're going to meet up with the person who takes care of the franchise.
- Just two of you?
- Yes.
So, I talked about this with Ba Reun,
and if it's okay with you, it would be great if you can come with us tomorrow.
We're a bit worried to just decide by ourselves.
- But she's busy.
- Right. I mean, if it's possible.
Even though I'm busy, I should come with you guys because this is so important!
- What? Really?
- Unni!
- Noona, thank you so much!
- Thank you!
- Did you tell about this to mom?
- I'm going to tell her in the morning.
- Oh, Lee Ra Hoon, now you're a business owner!
- Call me an owner.
I'm proud of you!
But it has to work out well.
With unni's help, it'll go great!
That's right! And we should work hard as well.
- Fighting!
- Business owner! You should get us something!
- Of course! Tell me everything that you want.
- I want a nice bag.
Then, what can I do because I'm your daughter?
What is possible because I'm your daughter?
Was being your daughter meant I have to give up so many things like now?
- Young lady, you came home late tonight.
- Yes.
Thank you for your work.
- Seo Ah, you came home so late.
- Mom!
Mom, your daughter is home now.
Did you drink again?
I just drank a little bit in a good mood.
- Good night, mom.
- Did you...
drink with Hwang Na Ro?
Yes.
Seo Ah.
I really don't like that you go out for a drink with Hwang Na Ro like this.
What do you like about me, anyway?
Are you really going to have a relationship with Hwang Na Ro?
Please don't do that, Seo Ah!
Why can't I date him?
Is it because his background is not good?
It's not about his background, but his human nature is the problem!
What's wrong with his human nature?
What do you know about him to say such a thing?
Isn't it enough if he likes me unconditionally and treats me well no matter what?
I can't be with Jae Hee oppa, and now I can't be with Hwang Na Ro!
Why are you being like this to me, mom?
Because I think you're like this because you got angry with Jae Hee!
- You're being irrational!
- I'm not doing this in anger at the moment.
I'm in love with Hwang Na Ro.
What?
I think it's not like you don't like Hwang Na Ro,
but you don't trust what I do.
If Bit Chae Woon liked him,
you would've acted differently.
Seo Ah!
If you don't like me that much,
then you should bring your biological daughter and live with her.
I'll leave this house!
Or maybe you should leave the house.
How can you say such a thing?
Do you really don't know how many things I gave up because of you?
I announced that Chae Woon is not my daughter and let her leave this house. You saw all of those!
And how can you say such a thing to me!
That's what I'm saying!
So!
You should bring your real daughter and have a happy life together.
Ah, it's so strange.
What about it?
I mean, Na Ro didn't eat together with us that often,
but it feels empty after knowing that he actually left.
Right, uncle?
I wonder if he's eating well.
He'll be fine! Don't worry about him too much.
Then, is the downstair's room empty now?
- Yes.
- Oh?
If that room is empty, then Cha Ba Reun! You should take that room.
That's right!
Can I just keep using the room together with you?
- Why?
- Because I got attached to you!
What?
Don't get attached to me!
Ah! That's right! She shouldn't move to the downstair's room.
If she moves downstair's, then she would hang out with Ra Hoon over there in secret.
- No, we wouldn't do that!
- No!
A strong denial is suspicious!
No! It's not like that...
Wow! This meat! Noonim!
- Having a meat dish in the morning is so indulgent!
- Right. It's the best breakfast ever!
Have as much as you want!
- Mr. Woo, have a lot!
- Yes, mother!
Wait a second.
Son-in-law Woo.
Oh, with wasabi?
Wow! It goes well together!
Right? It's a good combination, right?
I learned this when I was working in a restaurant!
- Uncle!
- Yes?
- Thank you!
- No, no!
- No, no.
- Okay, I get it. You should have it first.
Yes, thank you.
It's spicy!
I was going to give it to the uncle, but you took it! Why are you mad at me!
Were you trying to pull a prank?
Mr. Woo! I heard you have an important contract to make today.
Ah, yes.
It'll go well since you worked hard for it.
Thank you.
Today is an important day for everybody! Including Lee Ra Hoon.
Ra Hoon as well?
I'm going to take over a second-hand food truck today.
40% cheaper than usual.
Oh! That's great news, Ra Hoon!
I'm happy for you!
I'm going with him today for the contract.
He's going to meet the person from the head-quarter.
Oh, really?
If you can go with them, it's great.
Oh! Our Ra Hoon is now a business owner!
- Yes, I'm an owner now!
- I have to be nice to you!
I'm going to work with our Ba... with Ba Reun.
Owner Lee Ra Hoon, congratulations! Owner Ba Reun, congratulations!
Ra Hoon, congrats! Ba Reun, congrats to you, too!
Thank you so much! We'll work our best.
Hey, Chae Woon. Isn't it time for your company to announce the transition to the full-time position?
Ah, yes. But don't have your hopes high.
The other intern that I'm competing with is very good as well.
What are you talking about it! He wouldn't be better than you.
- If you don't become full-time this time--
- Hey, Chae Woon! You'll get it, so don't worry about it!
Noonim! Shouldn't we blow your lucky flower petal at this point?
Oh, about that...
Why? Did we already use all of them?
No, it's not like that.
I think that flower petal is not working anymore.
Last time, when Chae Woon's contest time, it didn't really work as well.
It eventually worked out!
Let's do something else!
Yes! That petal lost its power. It has been around a long time! It totally lost its power.
Yes, everybody. Thank you for waiting. Then let's do Hwak Se's "Samgwang, Samgwang, fighting."
Everybody, gather here, please!
Okay. I hope Mr. Woo's important contract goes well,
and Ra Hoon taking over the food truck goes well as well!
Yes, and our Bit Chae's work goes well as well!
I hope all of us do well!
Let's do this. Samgwang, Samgwang, fighting!
- Hello!
- Good morning!
Hello!
Yes.
I can't make Seo Yeon get unfair treatment anymore.
If I don't get the full-time position this time, I really think there's something going on.
Why do you think like that? You might have a lower score than her.
No, I don't think so.
I checked it, and we have a similar evaluation score.
Well, isn't that because you got many important projects at the end of the term?
It seemed like Director Jang is helping you a lot.
Anyway, you know that rumor is still going around!
The rumor that Bit Chae Woon is the daughter of the CEO?
They said it's not true!
No, it's really suspicious.
Don't you think that's the reason why Bit Chae Woon and Director isn't getting along with each other?
Are you saying they're competing with each other because they're sisters?
I guess that can be a possibility.
Bit Chae Woon, good morning.
Are you going to quit the company right away?
Aren't you going to quit the job if you don't get a full-time position?
It's a bit shameless to stay around in our company without having a decent position.
Thank you for worrying about me, director.
She's arrogant until the end...
I looked through your data throughout the time.
You're definitely better in skill-wise than Kim Dae Won.
I'm proud of you.
Thank you.
So...
I'm going to pick you.
The reason why I called you in today
is I wanted to apologize to you about yesterday.
No, I'm the one who should apologize.
I regretted it.
But if you pick me this time, you'll suffer from a lot of misunderstanding and speculation again.
I think so as well.
But instead, you can do great job to cover up all those speculations, right?
I think my individual data is better than Kim Dae Won,
but he will have a better overall evaluation.
That's how the evaluation program is structured.
I thought about this a lot.
But don't choose me, CEO.
Even if you choose me, I'll turn it down.
Then, are you going to quit and leave like you said yesterday?
I'm not going to leave.
I'm going to start again from the bottom and make the way up.
Also, I'm going to go to school as well.
If you think that way, why don't you go to study abroad?
I want to do study abroad someday, but not now.
I still have a lot to learn in the field,
and I want to get married as well.
Oh, the personnel appointment is up now.
Congratulations!
I told you so, Dae Won! I knew you'd get it.
- Congratulations!
- Thank you!
Congratulations, Dae Won! I'm happy for you.
Thank you, Bit Chae Woon.
I'm sorry.
Why are you being sorry? Congratulations.
- You should get us something!
- Yes!
- I knew you'd get it.
- Thank you!
If you want to stay in the company as a contract position,
your work will be different from now on.
It means it's going to be hard. Will that be okay with you?
I'm sorry!
I'll help you.
It's fine.
Why is Makjang not coming here?
Hello, Mr. Makjang? Where are you?
I'm a bit sick right now.
You're lying! You just don't want to come here.
I'm really sick...
The office is too cold.
Ah, cold...
It's freezing! Why is it so cold in here?
Mr. Makjang!
Mr. Makjang! Mr. Makjang!
- I'm so cold...
- Why did you not turn on the heater? Is the heater not working?
- I couldn't pay for it, so the gas is not coming in anymore.
- What?
- Why didn't you turn this on at least?
- That's broken.
How much didn't you pay for the gas to stop?
You had been paying me the whole time.
I was paying your paycheck instead of the gas.
Oh, no! Let's go to the hospital now!
- Don't take off my blanket.
- But we should go to the hospital!
- Put my blanket back on.
- Stand up! Ah!
You're very pretty.
Do you have a headache?
I don't have a headache. I said it wrong. You're not pretty. Give my blanket back.
I guess you're very sick.
You're not pretty...
It's just a common cold.
- I got surprised.
- Why is it so cold in here? That's why he caught a cold!
- Thank you for coming here, aunt.
- Your welcome.
Let's go for now.
- Where?
- Where are we going?
We should go somewhere warm. You'll be sick even more if you stay in this cold room!
Where do you live?
I'm not going to tell you where I live.
- His home is far away, somewhere in a rural village.
- Oh.
He looks like a city boy.
- Aunt.
- Yes?
I'm very dizzy right now, so I can't stand up.
Right. If you're dizzy, then you can't stand up.
Then, there's no choice. I'll piggyback him until the taxi stop.
Hae Deun, grab his legs. In three, grab his legs up.
- You want me to hold him up?
- Yes. I'm going to piggyback him.
- Okay, pull him up in three!
- I don't think this is a good idea.
- I can carry you.
- It's not a good idea, aunt!
One, two, three!
Oh, no! I'm so sorry! Oh, no!
- Oh, my god! Mr. Makjang!
- Help me...
Wait!
You don't look like a person who's sorry.
What? Ttak Bae, I'm not a person who does that kind of a small business!
Please help me with this, hyung! Think as a part-time job.
You're the best at talking! I'll pay you a lot.
How much are you going to pay me?
You bastard, you should pay me more than that!
Koala! Are you on the way to make the contract?
Yes. I'm about to go inside.
I called you to wish you good luck.
Thank you. Did you meet up with Ra Hoon for the food truck?
I'm on my way there.
Ah, if it weren't for this contract, I would've come with you.
It's okay. You can come by and see it later. Then, good luck with your work!
I might not be able to call you right away. I have to go around multiple departments for a briefing.
I get it. Let's eat something delicious tonight.
Sounds great.
Moong-i, I love you.
I love you, too, Koala!
I'm so nervous, Ra Hoon.
Don't be nervous.
- You're so frozen right now.
- What?
I'm not frozen! I'm fine! My goodness...
You're cute.
Don't be nervous!
- I'm not nervous.
- Let's take a picture!
- A picture?
- It's the historic first day of our business.
Sure.
Oh! Excuse me.
Are you the chief Ko from PH Food?
Yes, that's me.
Hello! It's nice to meet you.
- Hello.
- It's very nice to meet you.
It's so good to meet you.
Why don't we have a seat?
Yes, sure.
We read the headquarters guide book thoroughly.
And we have a couple of things to ask you.
- First of all, the food truck's menu--
- Wait.
Don't do this.
I'm sorry?
This is not a good thing. Don't do this work.
What are you talking about it? We looked up, and it looked nice.
The company where provides the menu is a famous place as well.
No. This is bait! Anyway, don't take over this one, and find another place.
Chief Ko, didn't you come from the headquarter?
I'm sorry. I should go.
Oh! I'm sorry, guys.
- Noona.
- Hello--
Park Pil Hong.
I'm sorry!
Park Pil Hong!
- Big noona!
- Unni!
Park Pil Hong! Wait!
Don't follow me! You might fall!
We should talk!
Seo Yeon!
You were going to scam on my brother, weren't you?
The food truck and the company, those are all lies, aren't they?
I didn't know it's going to be your brother!
Also, I just came out here because an acquaintance asked me to help him.
But I recognized your brother, and told him not to take this!
If it weren't my brother,
then were you going to scam the person?
Why are you doing this kind of work?
Do you know how much my brother was happy about this opportunity?
That money!
Do you know how hard he saved that money?
- That's why I told him, honestly! Don't do this!
- If it weren't for my brother, you would've scam the person!
All those money that people saved really difficultly, you were going to take all of it!
Well, I'm not the person who's taking that money directly. I was just here to explain the business.
- Because I'm good at communicating, so I'm pretty famous in this field.
- Park Pil Hong!
Did you live like this the whole life?
Were you like this before as well, so that's why you made my mom sick, and you went to jail?
Why?
Why did you finally show up before me?
In this terrible form! Why?
Seo Yeon.
I'm sorry.
I have a plan.
Even though I lived a life full of regret, but I remorse about it.
- I'll get back on my feet as soon as possible, so I can be your proud father--
- Stop right there.
Please get away from my sight.
I don't need a dad.
I don't have a father.
So...
Please go far away to where I can't even hear about you.
Please...
Please, I want you to do that.
Seo Yeon..!
Really! There's a big misunderstanding between us.
Okay, Seo Yeon. I'll never come back in front of you in this horrible form.
I have an important plan, so I should get going.
Where are you--
Where are you going?
Are you going somewhere else to scam other people?
You should put some ointment on your knee, okay?
My goodness!
You're not going to make any trouble, right?
Park Pil Hong!
- Big noona.
- Unni!
What's going on?
Who was that guy?
Is he really a scammer?
Unni! Did you get hurt here?
Oh, no...
I guess Woo Jung Hoo is not coming.
Jung Min Jae!
They said we should come here 10 minutes before the session.
I'm sorry. There's heavy traffic.
You fall easily! You shouldn't run.
Let's go inside.
I didn't know they had a space like this.
Be careful!
Welcome.
This room is a bit different, right?
Yes! I only met you in your office.
Today is a day we just talk comfortably.
I don't have that much time right now.
It wouldn't take that long.
- Did you bring your emotionally attached objects?
- Ah, yes.
This is it.
That's so cute!
What about you, Mr. Woo Jung Hoo?
Yes...
That's great! Who wants to talk about it first?
Why don't you go first? You said you're busy.
S-Sure.
Then, you should go to the next room and fill out the questionnaire.
Yes.
You look good in that outfit!
This is another room that I've never been to.
Take your time and fill this out, please.
Ah, yes.
Oh, wait. I did this before--
When was the happiest moment in your life, Mr. Woo Jung Hoo?
Well...
I bet it was when you made tons of money.
When the sales have gone up dramatically,
or is it going to be when you pay off all of your debt?
Ah, when you first went to see the movie with your first love, Soon Jung?
The happiest time in my life was when my wife had our Jae Hee, I mean when she gave birth to our son.
His mother and father liked it that we had a son.
My wife was in labor for more than 18 hours.
But I couldn't be with her because of my company's work.
I couldn't focus at work at all,
but I'm the person in charge, so I couldn't get out of it.
What if something happens to her?
I thought I was losing my mind.
After working until dawn, I ran to the hospital,
but she wasn't in the labor room.
I thought something happened to her.
I was terrified.
But then,
I went to the hospital room...
She was drinking kelp soup in a huge bowl and smiling.
I was really happy at that moment.
She's alive!
Since she's eating well, she's fine.
At that time, I was really...
I was really happy.
Yes. It must have been a happy time.
Then, can I ask, what do you regret the most?
If it's a tough question for you to answer, then you don't have to talk about it.
I bet it would've been the time when he started a business with a friend that he trusted.
He got fooled by his friend, lost a lot of money, and was chased by debt collectors.
If it's uncomfortable for you to answer, then you can talk about it next time.
My wife...
and my son, I wasn't nice to them.
I was a cranky, stubborn, and stingy guy to them.
I took care of my parents, my siblings, and even my relatives.
I paid for all of their living expenses and tuition,
but I always told my wife to save electricity and water.
I said to her that "you don't know that money is precious because you don't go out and make money!"
I see.
Can I ask you why you did that?
In this whole world,
I thought she was the one whom I can take for granted.
I thought I could walk all over her.
Actually, it was really hard for me to make money to support my parents
and take care of my younger siblings.
Sometimes I hated it,
but I had to bear with it.
Everyone was looking at me because I'm the oldest son.
I pretended to be okay when I'm outside,
but I poured out all the annoyance and frustration from outside on her.
Because I thought it was okay for me to do that to her.
Because I knew it well that my wife loves me so much.
So I thought I could treat her like that.
I didn't know...
that was growing into a wound in her heart.
I really didn't know about that...
Did it go well?
Of course!
- How about you?
- It was fine.
Your eyes got red.
I sneezed a bit hard.
Do you want to go somewhere and have Soondae soup with me..?
I have a plan.
Oh, right. I have to go to the jokbal place for my part-time job.
Then, why don't we say bye here, Jung Min Jae?
Okay, you should go, Woo Jung Hoo.
Yes, then.
What's the point of realizing it now?
It's all over now.
Yes, Soon Jung!
Soon Jung! Welcome to my place.
How have you been?
Your place is wonderful!
That's really nice.
- Take this, please.
- Thank you! It's very pretty!
How can your taste for choosing flowers so similar to your daughter?
Are you talking about Chae Woon? She has a similar taste to me.
Soon Jung. You're here to persuade me, aren't you?
That you and Woo Jung Hoo has nothing in between.
You already knew about it.
Why don't you read this?
Oh, this is... How can I..?
This is my diary that I wrote a long time ago.
Did you still keep your old diaries?
This is a precious one! I didn't know you kept a diary.
Well, you wanted to be a writer, so it's not surprising, I guess.
But why do you want me to read this..?
It's a bit embarrassing,
but I thought it might help you to understand the situation at that time.
It's too embarrassing for me to show you the whole entries, but...
Why don't you read this part?
Oh, my. Is it really okay for me to read this?
Yes, it's okay.
Oh, my...
Today's a very sorrowful day.
It's because I realized Jung Hoo oppa's real feeling.
Actually, I...
Actually...
I like Min Jae.
I guess you must be surprised.
Whenever I'm around Min Jae, we are always fighting.
I'm trying to be nice to her, but somehow it doesn't work like that.
Jung Hoo oppa had feelings for Young lady Min Jae.
I had no clue.
I really didn't know about it at all.
I can't believe there was someone else in Jung Hoo oppa's heart
who was the only consolation in my life.
It's very sorrowful.
What should I do with this sorrow?
Soon Jung, I didn't know about this.
Has your misunderstanding been cleared up a bit now?
But then, why did he treat me like that?
Soon Jung, you would have been upset at this time.
Yes, I was upset at that time because I had a crush on him.
But now it's all a good memory.
When I see both of you from the side,
I can tell that you both have feelings for each other still.
Oh, no. It's not like that! That's not true!
- Please, have some tea.
- Yes.
What a strange thing.
Be careful, be careful!
- Careful!
- Let's lie down right here.
I'm sorry, I must have been heavy to carry.
- Thank you, uncle!
- It's nothing!
By the way, I guess you are really sick! Your whole body is burning like a campfire.
He took some medicine, so it'll go down soon. Why don't you lie down and have some rest?
Yes, thank you so much.
Don't worry about it. I guess he can't lie down because we're around! Let's go outside. Have some rest!
Have some rest.
Where are you going?
- What's wrong?
- Don't go!
Let's go back up to the bed!
Are you okay?
- What's wrong?
- Don't go. Stay here.
Why don't you lie down first?
Are you okay? Did you eat something?
I didn't eat anything yet.
How can't you haven't eaten yet? I'll make you some porridge.
It feels like your fever went down a little bit.
I guess you're worried about me a lot. You're so cute!
Why is he laughing?
Did he lose his mind because of a high fever?
Yes, I think I'm a bit off right now.
Are you okay?
I'm not okay.
- Can you see it in the front?
- I can see with my eyes.
- Hwak Se.
- Yes?
It was hard, right? Thank you.
It was nothing! I'm very strong, you know.
Because of that, I came home with you, so I'm happy.
I'm happy, too.
I guess noonim went to work.
Then, Jjung-a, why don't we kiss in the meantime?
- Hae Deun will come inside soon.
- Don't worry about it.
I'll look around like this.
What should I do? How am I going to get out of this room?
I can't hide it anymore.
- Forget about it. Let's tell everything.
- Wait, wait!
Why, all of a sudden?
What? Why not?
- Let's just tell them now!
- No, wait!
At least, when I pass the audition for the radio singing contest, can we tell them then?
- No, what's the difference? Let's just tell them now.
- Wait, wait!
I just want to have anything to make noonim feel secure about you dating me.
Thank you, Jjung--!
Man Jung...
Why did you two come out from that room?
Unni.
Yes?
- We...
- Wait!
We are in a relationship.
What?
We are dating.
I'm sorry, Mr. Woo.
We decided to change our subcontractor.
The contract will proceed smoothly.
Is the company you were going to sign a contract with was Woo Jae Hee construction company?
Yes. Didn't you know about that?
I thought you intervene this because his company is very small.
I feel bad for Mr. Woo. He worked really hard.
But I can't do much because I got told to do it from the top.
What? You didn't get the contract?
How come?
We were sure to get it!
It was. But it got changed at the last minute.
The company's management changed its contract at the very last minute.
This is driving me crazy...
I thought it would be a done deal, so the material company already brought all of the materials in!
What should we do with all the construction workers that we signed the contracts?
What should we do with all those debts that we pushed it until now?
Yes, president.
I'm sorry.
We didn't know this will happen as well.
Yes, hyungnim! I just heard about it as well.
I didn't expect this to come.
Mr. Woo! I heard you couldn't get the contract!
What are you going to do with the delayed construction cost?
President, I will fix that for you!
How are you going to fix that! Huh?
Mr. Woo, we know that you're suffering, too, but how are you going to fix it!
I'll take responsibility and fix it all. I'm so sorry.
What should we do now!
I'm so sorry.
Hey, Woo Jae Hee!
This bastard, you were here.
What are you doing now?
I took care of everything in the name of Park Pil Hong.
I guess Jae Hee will struggle for some time.
He should've not offended our princess!
But Jae Hee oppa will get through this well, right?
I was just going to make him scared a little bit, but the problem is
that he's business partner Yoo Do Hyun, even used private loans in secret to Woo Jae Hee.
Is that so?
This might be complicated.
Why is he still not texting me?
The person you're trying to reach is unavailable now...
Jae Hee...
Hello...
You did this, didn't you?
What is going on!
Please, don't misunderstand me.
I just got some information, so I wanted to tell you.
Your father, Park Pil Hong, made Woo Jae Hee couldn't get the contract.
He got a bribe and stole the blueprint.
And he worked as a broker in between.
Why would Park Pil Hong do that?
Why would Park Pil Hong screw Jae Hee!
You know about it.
He does anything if you give him money.
He doesn't even care about his child in front of money, that old man.
I'll see if there's any way I can help.
What do you mean you're going to help?
You're all the same people!
I hope you can pull yourself together, Bit Chae Woon.
Hwang Na Ro... Hwang Na Ro...
Hwang Na Ro!!
Jae Hee.
Jae Hee. Are you okay?
Did you get hurt?
What happened? Who did this to you?
Chae Woon.
I'm fine.
I'm sorry...
I'm really sorry...
When the memories are fading
I stand on the street where we walked together
I'm trying to erase it again and again
But I can still hear you breathing on my ear
Did you forget? Did you forget about me?
I'm still waiting for you
My love is crying
My heart is filled with tears
I'm trying to erase it again and again, but I keep thinking of your face
Unni, can you just tell me your honest feeling?
I don't like you two dating. Bring someone who's a doctor like you!
Can't I say that as your sister?
Man Jung! Man Jung!
Please help Jae Hee. I'm your granddaughter as well.
Please take some pity on me, grandmother.
Seo Ah, please help me.
- You should convince the Chairwoman and make this right.
- Jae Hee.
There's no reason for the Chairwoman to ruin your work.
- I didn't do it!
- If it's not you, then why would the company related to the Chairwoman intervene in the contract?
I'm sorry, Jae Hee.
If you didn't meet me, you didn't have to go through this.
It's fine! Mr. Woo is a wealthy family's son!
I'm ashamed that you are my father.
I have someone to report.