- Jae...
Jae...
Im...
Se?
James?
The patient...
isn't entirely alert yet.
We'll keep an eye on him for now.
Yes.
Then, I'll get going now.
I paid for the hospital bill.
You'll have to stay longer.
If he doesn't gain consciousness,
we'll have to report this to the police.
We'll need the witness testimony.
My goodness.
It's so weird.
Why...
do I keep thinking of him?
It's a gift.
To be a good writer,
you have to know Korean well.
Gosh...
He can't be.
He has a different name, too.
LX...
Oh, you didn't know about it?
It is our CEO's brand.
And she's the director of the company.
Hi, Chae Woon.
Mom, where are you?
Well...
I'm at...
I'm at work.
I'm at Yeonhuidong madam's house.
Why?
Well...
I saw you still in bed this
morning when I left.
It was bothering me.
I told you I'm doing fine.
Aren't you at work right now?
Get back to work.
Mom, you're really okay, right?
Yeah.
All right then.
Mom, I love you!
Chae Woon.
Yeah?
Well...
you know the company
you're working for?
Yeah, what about my workplace?
Would it be...
- okay if you quit that job?
- Hello?
Mom?
Oh, no.
I love you, too, my daughter.
I know.
Okay, I'm hanging up.
You looked much better then.
Geez, I look the same.
Dae Won, I'm done.
Okay.
Kim Dae Won as a baby.
Isn't he so cute?
Whoa.
- I see your face there.
- Totally the same.
- And this is you, Choi Hyo Jung?
- Yes.
Gosh, your pudgy cheeks are so cute.
- You look exactly the same.
- Na Ro.
Show us your baby picture, Na Ro.
I don't have any.
Gosh, how can you not have any?
And you're the only son.
Let us see it.
It's true, though.
Then why don't you look at mine?
Yes, I wanted to see it.
Wait a minute. Where was it?
Here it is.
So cute!
Your cheeks are so pudgy.
- You look exactly the same.
- Totally the same.
I look much better now.
Anything exciting?
Hello.
- Hello.
- What is it?
Your baby picture, Bit Chae Woon?
Gosh, you were adorable.
Director.
Could you take a look at this?
Shall we get back to work?
Ah, yes.
As for this...
I'm totally adjusting to the workplace.
Of course, Samgwang Villa, too.
Lee Bit Chae Woon?
Who am I?
She's falling for me already.
Okay. Hang up then.
- Hey, get him!
- Get him!
Stop right there! Get him!
Stop right there!
Hey, man!
Stop! Hey!
Oh, my.
Are you awake?
Let me get the doctor.
Please save me.
You're alive.
You are alive.
You're okay.
Please lie down.
Those guys are chasing me.
Gosh.
By chance, are they creditors?
Please help me.
Help me.
Please save me.
You still need to be treated.
Let's get up...
Ahjussi!
Gosh.
Excuse me!
Ahjussi!
My gosh.
Where did he go already?
Ahjussi!
My goodness.
Oh, my!
Ahjussi!
Mr. James!
Aigoo.
Ahjussi!
Mr. James!
Wait.
My gosh.
Aigoo...
Gosh, wait.
No one is chasing after you.
Walk slowly.
You're not even well.
Your number.
Please give me a phone number.
I'll call your family.
Well...
don't you remember the number?
Of course, everyone saves
their contacts on their phone.
But still, think carefully.
You must remember
your wife's number.
This won't work.
I'll call the police station.
No, you can't.
No.
They'll take me away.
Is he on the run because of his debt?
Are you hungry?
Gosh.
What should I do? Where is
a restaurant around here?
Let me see.
Well...
the growling was coming from you.
No, it didn't.
My goodness.
I guess so.
These are the only shoes I can find.
Please wear these for now.
Thank you.
Thank you. Enjoy.
Take your time eating.
- Take your time.
- Thank you.
Thank you. I appreciate it.
I guess he's all right,
seeing how well he's eating.
I knew someone who used to make
delicious noodles a long time ago.
Your wife?
Excuse me?
Well...
you still don't remember...
your wife's phone number?
Yes.
It's so weird.
Why is my head blank?
I can't remember anything at all.
He looks so much like him.
So...
you said you're James, right?
Pardon?
Earlier, you said your name is...
James.
Yes.
Did I say that?
Are you from overseas?
No.
Am I from overseas?
Then what is your Korean name?
Oh, yes...
My Korean name...
I can't remember.
By chance...
you're not Woo Jung Hoo...
are you?
Oh Jung Hoo?
You must not be.
Well...
Please eat.
Eat and...
let me know if you want more.
Please eat.
Yes.
Thank you for this food.
Well, what should I have for dessert?
Please give me some ice cream.
There is no more ice cream.
Eating again when we're full already?
I'll eat this.
I'm gonna eat it.
Aigoo.
Why are you acting so fragile?
I know you can crack it in half.
What does being fragile
have to do with this?
Give it to me.
Gosh, so cool.
Na Ro oppa, you're so strong.
Hae Deun, doing this has nothing
to do with one's strength.
You said it does.
What's with this...
This is all about the method.
Geez, I haven't washed my hands.
Do it.
Eat what he cut already.
Why break more?
I'll eat them. Do it.
To do that,
you have to do this, like this.
Like this...
Geez.
Geez, you lack technique.
Do you have bear claws?
Whoa!
Oh, my!
Geez, man. Why are
you cutting so many?
We'll all share them.
Wow, you split it so nicely.
Wow, the line is so crisp and perfect.
Na Ro, you're so delicate.
He's the best.
Let's compete in something else.
Whoa, challenging me?
May the best man win.
Now, now. Let's be fair and square.
You can't cheat. Are you ready?
Are you ready?
Then sit down.
All right.
Start!
Oh, you know this.
Let me see. Over here?
Over here. There.
Go, Na Ro oppa!
Go, Jae Hee hyung!
- Go, Na Ro oppa!
- Go, Jae Hee hyung!
- Na Ro oppa, go!
- Go, my hyung!
Go, my hyung!
- Don't do that.
- Hyung, hyung.
Turn and kick.
Okay!
What are you guys doing?
- Hyung!
- Wow, look at them!
- Playing a game?
- Go, Na Ro oppa!
Go, Na Ro oppa!
Turn him around right here.
- Turn, turn.
- Kick him.
Then push him on the back.
Wait, wait, wait!
Wait. You're not as strong as him.
Na Ro, let's make a winning move.
Your winning move.
Does that work?
I'm telling you it works.
I was a champion in this
before. Listen to me. Do it.
Do it. Begin.
Ready, begin.
- Okay.
- How can you teach him?
Go, go!
All right!
I won!
Hyungnim, what's up with this?
You said you were a champion!
- I was a champion.
- When?
Back in elementary school.
Come here.
Let's do it.
I don't want to play you.
Do it with me.
- Let's play with me.
- That's even worse.
Forget it. Have fun!
Hwak Se, stop right there!
He ran away.
Young man, play me this time.
Play me this time.
Na Ro, play with me.
When did you do that?
Will you really be okay?
Yes, well...
A friend lives in this area.
I'll go to his house.
Please go.
Well...
this is all the cash I have.
You never know.
Gosh, no thank you.
I'm fine.
Please...
Then, take care.
Thank you.
Who am I?
This face...
seems unfamiliar...
and familiar...
I'm handsome, though.
Wait.
My name is Jae...
Jae...
Oh, that ahjumma said it was James.
Am I really from overseas?
Gosh.
Why can't I remember anything?
Mr. James.
Please be honest with me.
You're not feeling well, right?
No.
Please go.
Your bus will leave.
I can't leave you like this.
They say destiny can form
from one encounter.
How can I leave you
like this, James?
Even though I say I'll take you to
the police station, you say no.
You seem to be on the run...
Actually...
It's blank up here.
Pardon?
I can't...
remember anything.
What should I do?
Oh, my.
Yes, Noonim.
You're still working late?
Should I pick you up?
What?
So...
I don't know what to do.
Noonim, still...
you don't know what kind of person
he is. Why are you with him?
Hurry up and come home.
I don't think he's a bad man.
Then...
does a bad man put a sign that
says, "I'm bad" on his forehead?
Well, the way I see it...
I think he's in dire straits.
Let's help him out, Hwak Se.
Let's think together what is
the best thing to do.
Geez, Noonim. Seriously.
♫  A night without anyone
to lean on or to talk to  ♫
Excuse me.
You shouldn't stay here like this.
Young man.
- Look.
- Leave me alone!
♫  Everybody looks happy except me  ♫
♫  Is the good day will ever come  ♫
I used to be like that, too.
Hello?
Hwak Se.
Yes, yes, Noonim.
Noonim, where are you right now?
♫  Youth these days are
having a hard time  ♫
Mr. Woo.
Mr. Woo, are you sleeping?
Mr. Woo...
Jae Hee hyung just left saying
something urgent came up at his office.
Oh, really?
I can't find him when I need him.
Did he take his car?
Probably so.
Geez, this is nuts.
Seriously.
It's noisy. Why are you so chatty?
Don't say anything to
Man Jung or my kids.
They'll worry.
Uncle!
Where are you going? To sing?
What's wrong with him?
Sing what? He got fired
from all the bars.
Is he going on a date?
A date, my foot.
This is becoming a habit for you.
Bringing me in for emergencies.
I'm sorry.
They're asking for it by
tomorrow morning suddenly.
What can I do? Here.
So why don't you
hire an engineer?
Do you think I'm not
hiring one on purpose?
I just can't find a good person.
True.
Who'd want to work under
a cheapskate boss?
What? A cheapskate?
How am I a cheapskate?
You just wait.
"You just wait."
Yeah, Mom.
♫  I'm so curious  ♫
♫  The taste when you bite
into it for the first time  ♫
You called me a lot.
Mom, where are you?
At home. At Jung Min Jae's home.
♫  The taste of summer that I love  ♫
I've been busy all day.
I was all over the place.
I was worried since
I couldn't get ahold of you.
♫  The seven colors of the rainbow  ♫
I told you not to worry about me.
♫  It colors your world  ♫
It's Jung Won!
- Jae Hee, hang up. Goodnight!
- Hello? Mom? Mom?
Welcome, my friend!
♫  It's what I like the most  ♫
- Hey, you...
- Isn't this great?
This is the house
I've been longing for.
Gosh, it's so loud.
- Jung Min Jae.
- Yeah?
What are you doing at night?
What else?
I'm enjoying myself.
Oh, I was starting to get hungry.
My friend, you're so sensible.
It must be so good.
Delicious...
What's with her?
Did your mother say
she's doing all right?
Oh, yes.
Well...
She sounds good. She sounds energetic.
But why do you look so uneasy, Koala?
What?
Well, no. I'm fine.
If you feel uneasy,
check on her tomorrow.
Geez, she'll get upset saying I don't
trust her and went to see her.
Sons don't know
how moms feel at all.
She may say that, but she'll
be so happy to see you.
How can you not know
anything at all?
Yeah, right. What did
you say earlier?
A cheapskate?
How am I a cheapskate?
Oh...
you remember. Amazing.
Cheap, cheap, cheapskate.
Do you want to see a magic trick?
- Yeah, sure.
- Okay.
Look at this.
This...
seals the Headbutt.
What's this?
- What? Am I a zombie?
- A zombie...
It looks good on you.
Come here.
Ta-da!
On the other cheek.
Over here, too.
Ta-da!
I'm holding back only
because you're helping me.
Put this on, too.
That looks good.
Wouldn't it be too noisy?
That's why I moved
into the first floor.
The second-floor unit is empty.
Let's get it!
♫  What if we're finished?  ♫
♫  My heart will break,
but I'll have to ignore it  ♫
♫  It would hurt less
than breaking up  ♫
♫  I never thought you'd leave me  ♫
♫  I never thought you'd abandon me  ♫
♫  I can't easily forget
our deep affection  ♫
♫  It's too late, I'm already
your woman  ♫
♫  Don't say that I'm vicious  ♫
Sing with me!
♫  Take care of me
because I love you  ♫
Aigoo, be careful.
Aigoo, I'm sorry.
My legs are weak.
Noonim!
Hi, Hwak Se.
Wait.
It's okay.
He's a younger brother
who lives with me.
Noonim...
Give me a moment. Come.
Excuse me.
Why?
What?
Shouldn't we take him
to the police station?
Gosh.
I told you.
I think his creditors
are chasing him.
Inadvertently, I've been
through that myself.
You know that well.
Just until he regains his health,
let's help him out.
But what if he's not someone
who is in dire straits,
but what if he's a weirdo?
What if he's into crime or...
there are people who are serial...
My gosh! Hwak Se!
I don't think he's like that.
Noonim, how would
you know that?
I'm not sure.
I just...
feel that way.
Gosh, that feeling again.
I get so nervous whenever you
move based on that feeling.
Come in. Watch your head.
Geez.
Be careful.
- Be careful.
- I'm sorry.
Be careful.
Gosh, I guess you
can't see in the dark.
I'm sorry.
Gosh, no. It's okay.
Wait, wait a minute.
About me...
staying here...
I'd like to keep it
a secret from others.
I'm so nervous.
Yes, that'd be nice, but...
our Samgwang Villa isn't
set up to keep a secret.
Is that so?
Well, then...
I'll get going now.
- Oh, my.
- Goodbye.
- Yes, be careful going home.
- Gosh.
Mr. James.
Aigoo, you've come all this way.
Where do you think you're going?
I got it.
Don't worry.
We'll keep it a secret.
- Noonim...
- Hwak Se.
- Lead the way.
- Okay.
Let's go in.
Come in.
Be careful.
- I'm sorry.
- Please be careful.
I'll take him to my room, Noonim.
- Let's go.
- Thanks, Hwak Se.
Be careful going upstairs
and get some rest.
- Okay. Thank you.
- Yes.
Yes.
Wow, so detailed
about stuff like this.
Please go up and rest.
Thank you.
Aigoo, seriously.
- Are you okay?
- I'm sorry. Sorry.
Here are the stairs.
Be careful.
- Unni!
- Aigoo!
- Unni, come here.
- Man Jung.
You didn't sleep yet?
What happened, Unni?
Why didn't you answer your
phone? I was worried.
Aigoo.
You didn't tell my kids, did you?
You told me not to.
Why did you go to
brother-in-law's grave?
Just because.
Aigoo, I'm so tired.
Hey, let's talk tomorrow. Goodnight.
- Ahjumma!
- Mom!
You're back. Why so late?
Mom, did you just get home?
Why are you working so late?
Well, it just worked out that way.
Where did you two go?
Something urgent
came up at my office.
I reviewed his floor plans.
I see.
Gosh, you worked so hard.
Did you help him with work or
go on a date this evening?
- Auntie!
- Listen to you.
- Go to your rooms.
- Okay.
Go to sleep, too.
Unni, goodnight.
- Good job, Mom.
- Goodnight.
Sure.
- What's wrong with mom?
- Your mom?
I don't know what's up with her.
Your reactions are over the top.
Mr. Woo, pay Bit Chae Woon overtime.
Ah, yes, Auntie.
Don't you worry.
You two are the same
at times like this.
Geez.
Goodnight.
Is he home?
Hey.
Are you home?
Hey!
I'm home.
Where did you go this late at night?
- None of your business.
- "None of your business."
You were going to say that, huh?
Where did you go?
Well...
I went to see someone.
Man Jung, goodnight.
So, who? Who did you see?
Did he really go on a date?
Who cares if he did?
What do I care?
Geez, don't be like that. Just...
take the bed. You're injured.
No, how can I?
I'll just sleep on the floor.
Gosh, James. I'd be uncomfortable.
Please sleep on the bed.
- No thanks.
- Hyungnim!
Geez, what's with today?
Yeah, what? I'm changing.
I missed several of
your calls earlier.
Was something the matter?
Oh, that? Everything is fine.
Go to sleep.
Yes, Hyungnim. Goodnight.
What's this?
Geez, where did he go?
Look at this dirt.
Mr. Woo, seriously...
You disappear when I need you,
and I'm the one who is suffering.
James.
It's okay now.
It's the young man next door.
He's not a bad guy.
He has a legit job, too.
James.
Geez, what a scaredy-cat.
Excuse me...
Look at this ahjussi.
He seems to be in quite a bind...
yet he seems so innocent.
So innocent.
Geez, this is nuts.
♫  On the day, even the
hope gets shaken  ♫
♫  Like the star that's shining
like a jewel in the night sky  ♫
I've been busy all day.
I was all over the place.
♫  The shining day will come  ♫
Aigoo, Mommy...
♫  I'm comforting myself  ♫
♫  This tearfully lonely night  ♫
♫  Love is so difficult  ♫
♫  Life is so hard  ♫
Gosh...
I have enough on my plate.
And now that ahjussi, too.
♫  Well, just living with
that in my heart  ♫
Mom?
Oh, hi.
Gosh.
Mom, why do you get
startled so easily lately?
Should you go for a physical?
Gosh, no.
It's okay. I did it in the spring.
Why?
When I talked to you
this afternoon,
I remembered you started to say
something about my work and stopped.
What is it?
It's nothing.
I was wondering...
if it would be okay...
if you quit your current job.
Huh?
Why?
Before you get much older,
I thought it'd be good for
you to study abroad.
I have some savings.
With that...
If I do a good job at the company,
I can go to the US to study.
What if you don't get it?
If I don't get it by any chance,
I'll just keep working here.
They said I could stay
as a contractor.
I really like my company.
You like it?
Yeah.
I think I'll get along
with Jang Seo Ah,
and the CEO completely
fell for my charm.
Gosh, I'm joking.
Anyway, I'll work really hard here,
and I'll go to the US to study.
I'll get the full-time
position for sure.
So, don't worry, Mom. Okay?
All right.
This is different.
Whoa, this is nuts.
This is somewhat of
a familiar sound.
Geez.
Wow, I must be getting
used to Auntie's snoring.
Human beings sure have
a remarkable ability to adapt.
Aigoo.
My goodness...
I couldn't sleep last night, either.
Gosh, how nice is this, though.
I get to stay in bed at this hour.
Gosh, I'm so happy.
Friend, did you sleep well?
I said, I'd clean up
with you before I left.
You kept pushing me to leave.
Sorry.
How do you feel?
I cleaned up the house
already and am exercising.
I'm feeling very good.
Thanks, my friend.
I don't think she's feeling "very good."
♫  Even if I'm reborn
a thousand more times   ♫
♫  There will not be
another person like you  ♫
♫  The person who warmed
up my sad life  ♫
♫  I'm grateful for that person  ♫
♫  For that person  ♫
Is it leaking?
♫   My heart could hurt indefinitely  ♫
♫   Even if I cannot tell
you that I love you  ♫
I bought some macarons for you.
Why did you come again?
I was at a construction site nearby.
Mom, did you cry?
No, I didn't.
I slept all this time and yawned.
Gosh, what do I do? It's a mess.
Wait. Mom.
Mom...
It's nothing serious.
I'm just a bit depressed.
Did you go to a hospital?
Of course. I'm free at last.
I'll take care of my body and
my heart. I'll live boldly.
Geez, why are you sick? Come on.
I wrapped up half a century
of personal history.
It won't be too easy.
But I'll become strong. Okay?
Be sure you work with me, okay?
Of course.
It's your uncle.
We're supposed to meet.
Uncle? Why?
For business.
I'll live diligently.
Hi, Min Suk.
I took lunch over to
James hyungnim.
- You did?
- Yes.
Good job.
- But...
- Yes?
does he seem like
he's hurting anywhere?
I think he's fine.
Noonim, I've been looking through
the police station missing person's site.
But I don't see anything reported
about James hyungnim.
- Really?
- Yes.
In my opinion,
either he has no family,
or his family has turned
their backs on him.
Gosh, no way.
Noonim, how long are you
thinking of having Eems hyung?
What do you mean, how long?
Gosh.
Hey, you didn't go to work yet?
I'm working afternoon today.
What the heck?
You two are acting very
strange right now.
Look at you. What do
you mean strange?
Gosh. Seriously.
You're acting strange.
Very strange.
Is something there?
Who am I?
Why can't I remember anything?
Why...
You haven't eaten yet.
I have no appetite.
I see. Then...
try this.
You'll get your appetite
back right away.
I don't feel like...
It's good, huh?
I knew it.
Okay, eat a lot with this.
So that you'll become healthy,
and you'll get your memory
back when you get healthy.
Whoa...
This is very good.
I feel like I've tasted this before.
Really?
Maybe your wife makes good
geotjori, too, Eems hyungnim.
Hyungnim, eat more. Here, eat.
As for this launch showcase,
I'd like to have Kim Dae Won and
Bit Chae Woon to be in charge.
It will be part of your evaluation
for the full-time position.
So, please work hard.
Bit Chae Woon...
Are you confident?
Yes. I'll work hard.
Where is Hwang Na Ro?
He was in the reference room.
It might not be the same person,
but the shoes are the same.
Portugal?
How unique.
- I'm sorry. Are you all right?
- Yes.
- I'm sorry.
- I'll do it.
Ms. Goo.
Did the design team
start the meeting?
Yes, CEO.
Hello.
I'm Hwang Na Ro, a contractor
for the design team.
He's working on the Spain project.
Oh, really?
Thank you in advance.
Sure.
- Here's another one.
- Yes.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
Those are cute sneakers.
What brand is it?
These?
I'm not sure. What were they?
No, it's okay.
I thought I saw them somewhere.
Carry on.
Thank you!
Where would you see them?
They don't sell them here.
Five, six, seven, eight.
One, two, three, four.
- Five, six, seven, eight.
- Do it strong!
One, two, three, four.
Five, six, seven, eight.
- One, two, three, four.
- Do it again!
Is this a school play or something?
Five, six, seven, eight.
One, two, three, four.
- Gosh, you can't do it like that.
- One, two, three, four.
One, two, three, four.
Five, six, seven, eight.
- One, two, three, four.
- Yes?
- Five, six, seven, eight.
- Ms. Lee Hae Deun?
Is this spam?
- I'm not buying.
- Hello.
I'm Manager Joo Man Dae
from Production Million Big.
Excuse me?
One, two, three, four.
Five, six, seven, eight.
- One, two, three, four.
- Hello?
- Five, six, seven, eight.
- Yes!
Hi...
♫  The yellow cafe I see over there  ♫
♫  I'm meeting her for
the third time today  ♫
♫  I'm running toward that place  ♫
Why do I keep...
♫  500 meters before I see you  ♫
Don't disappear from my sight.
Because I like you.
♫  How should I say it?  ♫
What am I doing? What?
What are you doing, Lee Ra Hoon?
I've done all kinds of stupid things.
♫  Is the cloud in the
sky cotton candy?  ♫
Geez.
♫  Should I try jumping into it?  ♫
- It's this house.
- I see.
- Good luck.
- Thanks.
♫  I'll be bold  ♫
- Hello.
- Yes, hello...
Who are you...
Ahjussi.
Geez, I said there is
no room available.
I beg you. I want to
eat delicious food.
No, it won't work.
Sorry.
I can share a room.
Please look into it for me, please?
- Please.
- Geez, I told you.
There is no room.
- Ahjussi.
- Hurry up and leave.
Sorry, sorry.
- Please.
- Leave now.
Noona, will you be okay?
If you run our company
store branch,
you can bump into Jung Hoo.
It's okay. It's not like
we're enemies.
I want to do this line of work.
I prepared for a long time.
Is Woo Jung Hoo doing well?
Huh?
Yeah, of course.
What a relief. Let's go in.
This bed is a popular item.
I see.
I'll show you other products.
- As you can see, do this...
- Oh, my.
and put it around your waist.
There are various products.
You can't reach Jung Hoo yet?
Yes.
President told me not to contact
him while he's on vacation.
I'll wait and see.
Yes.
This is weird.
- James.
- Yes.
Do you feel better with
some fresh air?
Yes. It's nice.
Drink this.
I ground some nuts in milk.
Thank you.
It tastes wonderful.
Do you like it?
James.
Do you still not remember
anything at all?
Yes.
Except for being
chased by creditors.
My apologies.
No need to apologize.
It's not like you don't
remember on purpose.
Just relax.
Thank you.
You've done a great
job with flowers.
I really love the flowers.
I see.
- Then stay and enjoy.
- Okay.
Thank you.
Aigoo, too bad.
Wait...
Do you have something to say?
Well...
No matter how much
I think about it,
you're so similar to him.
- Are you sure...
- Geez, I'm sure it won't work.
Please be careful!
Are you okay?
Aigoo, Noonim.
I'm glad you're home.
Who is this...
I mean...
this student really wants to
move into our Samgwang Villa.
He says he's willing to share a room.
Hello. I'm Kim Joon Woo.
Yes, hello.
But what can I do...
No room.
See? No room.
It's not a creditor.
Where was the room?
This isn't it.
Is it this room's tenant?
He's handsome.
Hello.
I got a call from Jung Min Jae.
She said her son
would pay me a visit.
I see.
How is my mom's condition?
It's not that serious.
Don't worry too much.
What Jung Min Jae needs
the most right now
is the family's constant
attention and love.
The family...
Whoa...
Is this your first time
at our agency?
Yes. I did see your
company website.
It's so nice here.
I have to go up soon,
so I'll get to the point.
I'd like to scout you
for a girl group that we're
producing, Hae Deun.
What do you think?
Excuse me?
There are lots of frauds
in this industry.
So just in case you're suspicious,
I called you over to our agency.
Over here.
Aren't you going to say hi?
Hello.
I told them so many times,
yet they're not courteous.
Oh, it's them.
Once you approve, you'll
get to work with them.
Without an audition?
We'd be so grateful if
a gem like you would join us.
What audition?
They work very hard, but...
we don't have a center who's
got the moves and looks.
It'd be perfect
if you'd be the center.
Me?
Center?
Room share?
Share my room?
Geez, that student was
totally begging me.
I asked Na Ro and Mr. Woo,
but they both said no.
- Even if I want to do it, I just...
- Wait...
Not Ra Hoon, Hwak Se.
He's splitting upstairs and
downstairs with Hae Deun.
How can we put a
young man up in the attic?
If we assign new rooms...
Aigoo, no way.
He needs to focus on his studies.
Gosh.
Gosh, what's this?
Gosh, your feet stink.
- Go and wash your feet.
- My feet...
- Okay.
- Geez.
- My gosh!
- They stink.
I'd like to scout you
for a girl group that
we're producing, Hae Deun.
What do you think?
Of course.
They say every cloud
has a silver line.
Not "line." It's "lining."
There's a light at
the end of the tunnel.
Geez, so ignorant.
Hey, you're home early.
Aren't you seeing
Cha Ba Reun today?
I'm not.
Hey, wait.
A daebak incident.
Really?
Really.
It's not a scam?
My gosh.
Look. Production Million Big.
Manager Joo Man Dae.
I asked around through my
friends. He's a manager there.
I even went to the agency earlier.
Really?
- Daebak. Wait.
- Hey!
I still haven't told them I didn't
make the Trot Girls audition.
I'll reveal it after I sign the contract.
You zip it until then.
Hey, Lee Hae Deun.
I'm so happy for you.
When I heard that you
didn't pass the audition,
I was so sad...
Hey. Are you crying?
Hey.
It's a lie.
A lie, lie, lie.
I'm starving.
I ate dinner earlier.
Why am I hungry again?
Right?
Since we're hungry,
- let's have snack time.
- Sounds great!
Let's play a game for the snacks.
How about Snakes and Ladders?
Great. Draw lots?
Draw lots? Let's do it.
Then I'll write it out.
Is it kimchi dumplings?
- Write out the names and...
- Then I'll fold the papers...
All right, thank you
for working late.
Work after eating some snacks.
- Whoa, thank you!
- Thank you!
So great.
How should we
arrange the VIP seats?
For now, place Mr. Joo
and Ms. Park to the back.
It's delicious!
- So good!
- I was craving this.
CEO, do you like this
type of food?
Of course.
I love tteokboki and dumplings.
I didn't think you'd like that.
You seem like you'd
only like steaks.
It's so tasty.
I'm sorry. Go ahead.
Geez, that's no fun.
Should we do rock-paper-scissors?
- Oh, then...
- Sounds like fun.
- Right?
- Whoever wins three rounds.
- Okay.
- Good? All right.
- Let's do it.
Rock-paper-scissors!
Oh, my gosh!
One win.
CEO, you're the best.
Don't let your guard down.
I'll go.
Rock-paper-scissors!
It's a practice.
No, no, wait.
Rock-paper-scissors!
Okay, then.
I have to win one more round.
- Last chance.
- Yes.
- I'll go. Rock-paper...
- Wait a minute!
Wait. Wait a minute.
Then, I'll do it, too.
- Geez.
- No way.
Okay, okay.
I see it.
Rock-paper-scissors!
This is mine.
Okay.
You want it?
Thank you.
Me-rong.
You're so mean.
Everything is so tasty.
Yes, thank you.
- Dumplings are the best.
- Director.
Come and join us.
Director Jang, come in.
Did the meeting go well?
Yes, we'll meet once
more next week.
Good job.
Oh, no. What do we do?
We ate by ourselves.
We already ate dinner on our way.
Good job, everyone.
Thank you.
Bit Chae Woon.
Did you organize the styling files?
Yes, I finished it.
If you're finished,
bring it to my office.
- Let's review together.
- Yes, got it.
CEO, I'll get back first.
Come in.
I brought you the file.
Have a seat.
How far did the
afternoon meeting go?
We talked about the
upcoming event.
I posted it on the team site.
You did?
Our design team family from
some twenty years ago.
Oh, my gosh, look at the cuties.
Bit Chae Woon,
why don't you post yours?
You were so cute.
So embarrassing.
I'll keep it for myself.
Oh, no. Baby Bit Chae Woon
was the best.
Post yours since we
posted ours, Chae Woon.
That's right. Post it.
Bit Chae Woon.
You must've been
adorable as a baby.
Yes, I guess I was.
Let me see it.
Here you go.
It's cute.
You look different, though.
Thank you.
It's the same kid.
Are you sure...
this is you, Bit Chae Woon?
Yes.
I guess I must look
so different, huh?
I'm sorry.
Excuse me for a moment.
Director Jang, I'll go home first...
Is something wrong?
Mom.
Yeah?
Who...
is this child?
You...
had this?
Who is it?
Director, please go to
the reference room...
♫  You don't need to force love  ♫
♫  Like passing time,
you can't stop the heart  ♫
♫  We're drawn to each
other like the magnets  ♫
♫  So that we can fill in
a hole in our heart  ♫
Do I get to perform
internationally, too?
- Just sign here, right?
- Wait.
You have to deposit
your training fee first.
Just succeed.
This will be chump change.
Hold it.
Geez, come on, carry some weight.
Gosh! Oh, my goodness!
My goodness!
Aigoo, I don't know if I should
continue to live in this house.
Aunt, how can I live
seeing stuff like this?
- Aunt!
- Oh, my gosh!
The model can't make it?
She went to the ER
for a stomachache.
- I just got a call.
- What should I do?
Bit Chae Woon.
♫  You became the meaning  ♫
♫  The one who taught me love  ♫