It's so lovely here. Don't you think?
What's with you?
Hey, you still haven't
memorized the move yet?
How do you do it?
- Look. Like this.
- How? Like this?
- Am I doing it right?
- No, not like that.
No?
How do I do it then?
- Jung Won.
- Hi, Min Jae.
- Hello.
- Hi, you're here.
Hello, In-law.
It's a wonderful day.
Yes, it really is a wonderful day.
- The weather is lovely, too.
- Yes.
Oh, go ahead and talk.
- Okay.
- All right then.
Soon Jung, no...
In-law.
Did you have a nice dream last night?
Gosh, I'm not sure. I couldn't sleep at all.
You, too? Me, too.
I was tossing and turning,
and it was already morning.
I don't think my makeup went on well.
You look so beautiful, In-law.
- Really?
- Yes.
This place is cozier than
I thought. Don't you think?
Yes. I think they picked a good place.
But still, there are lots of places
that are better than here.
Mom.
- You came.
- Hello.
Thank you for coming.
Chairwoman, hello.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
- See you.
- Thank you. Thank you.
Mom!
Chae Woon!
My gosh.
Gosh, you're so beautiful.
- Aigoo, so beautiful.
- You look so pretty.
Gosh, you're so beautiful.
Are you very nervous?
Yeah. A little bit.
Chae Woon...
I was so happy because you
became my daughter.
Thank you, Chae Woon.
Aigoo, my daughter.
Mom, you look so pretty, too.
Aigoo, my Chae Woon looks
like an angel today.
Gosh, so pretty.
My Seo Yeon is so pretty.
Please be seated.
Next, we'll have today's stars.
The bride and groom will enter.
Please welcome them
with lots of applause.
That will make them so happy.
All right...
Bride and groom, enter.
♫  I can see your heart even
when you don't speak  ♫
♫  I can see it in your eyes  ♫
Beautiful!
♫  Whether you're happy or sad  ♫
- You look beautiful!
- Yay!
♫  I can see your heart even
when you don't speak  ♫
♫  I can feel it when I touch you  ♫
♫  Your heart that I feel
at the tip of my fingers  ♫
- Hey, hey, hey!
- Hyung!
Geez!
I like you.
I like you. I'm totally into you.
I really like you. I like you!
♫  You're like the sunshine that
shines on me through the fog  ♫
♫  You welcome me while
walking a distance  ♫
♫  You're like a tree to me   ♫
♫  My all  ♫
I'm sorry.
♫  My love  ♫
♫  You're the only one I can
give you my whole heart  ♫
Everyone...
Thank you so much for coming
to our wedding in this cold weather.
Everyone, I'm finally getting married.
I'm so happy.
So handsome!
♫  I will give you love  ♫
Be happy!
♫  You're like the sunshine that
shines on me through the fog  ♫
Mom, who raised me so well...
Thankfully, I have two mothers.
Mothers, thank you so much.
♫  My all  ♫
♫  My love  ♫
Father and Mother.
Thank you for raising Jae Hee so well.
Sure. Thank you.
Mothers, thank you so much.
Mom.
Dad.
Thank you.
♫  My love  ♫
♫  You're the only one I can
give you my whole heart  ♫
Everyone.
We'll live happily ever after!
♫  You're the only one I can
give you my perfect love  ♫
Congratulations on your wedding.
Yes.
♫   The best!  ♫
♫   Honey, baby, sweetie, darling, good!  ♫
♫   It's good! It's very, very good   ♫
♫   I totally fell for you   ♫
♫   It's perfect! You're truly perfect   ♫
♫   It's a destiny like a present   ♫
So cool!
Oppa!
♫   The pretty face with a big big smile   ♫
We love you, Kim Hwak Se!
♫   It makes this man's heart to flutter   ♫
My Seo Yeon...
You struggled so much because of me...
Be happy, Seo Yeon.
♫  It's very, very good   ♫
Thank you, everyone.
With this energy, we'll have the bride
and groom walk down the aisle.
♫  I love you, I like you  ♫
♫  I only trust you  ♫
♫  As we change as the time passes  ♫
What, me?
♫  In my eyes, to me  ♫
♫  You only sparkle to me  ♫
I'll throw it, Auntie. One, two, three!
Here!
♫  Be my star forever as always  ♫
♫  I love you, I like you  ♫
- What?
- What in the world?
We'll take a group photo.
Please get closer.
♫  Be my star forever as always  ♫
All right.
One, two, three.
One more time.
♫  I love you  ♫
Aigoo! I'm so tired.
- Aigoo...
- Good job, everyone.
Gosh, I'm tired.
I found out for the first time how
pretty Chae Woon noona is.
Of course, she's pretty.
Aigoo, I knew from way before.
Chae Woon is pretty because
she takes after my Jjung-a.
That's right.
- Auntie.
- Huh?
Aren't you happy that you
caught the bouquet?
Gosh, well, rather than happy...
- What do I do with this?
- Aigoo...
What else? You caught it,
so you should get married.
Guys, don't you have to get married
within six months if you catch this?
- Yes, of course!
- Of course!
- Go where?
- Must we go for it?
- Go to the military?
- What?
What's with this for me?
A stem. Do I have to get married, too?
Hey, you have a boyfriend, huh?
Be honest.
What are you talking about, Auntie?
- What?
- You're so funny.
- Joon Ah.
- Yes?
It was tiring today, huh?
Gosh, no, ma'am. I came out
for some water.
Wait. Your face is bright red.
Did you get sunburn? What's wrong?
- What? Me?
- Yeah, you're red.
- What are you saying?
- You're flushed.
- Wait a minute.
- Nothing.
Gosh, you scared me.
- Oh, wait. Thank you.
- Thank you.
What's with those two?
Did you meet for the first time today?
Everyone, you all worked so hard today.
Everyone, go to your own rooms now.
- Get some rest.
- Unni, you went through a lot.
- Right. Good job.
- Everyone, good job!
Let's get some rest. Disperse!
Gosh...
Aigoo...
My gosh.
My Chae Woon left for good now.
You didn't have to drive me home.
Today is a special day.
So it's a special treatment.
Have some tea then.
I noticed how handsome
my Jae Hee was earlier.
Of course, he takes after me.
- Chae Woon was pretty, too.
- Aigoo.
My legs.
Of course, Bit Chae Woon
was pretty, too.
But my Jae Hee looked better.
You only see your son, huh?
But...
I wonder if Park Pil Hong came.
I don't think I saw him.
Chae Woon's father?
You've never met
Park Pil Hong, have you?
Well? I don't know what he looks like.
Right.
You couldn't make it to
Jung Won's wedding.
Because you had to work.
You couldn't make it to
her housewarming, either.
I guess so.
It looks like...
all you did was work so hard
all your life. Isn't that right?
Wouldn't it be uncomfortable living
with your son and daughter-in-law?
Well, it won't be comfortable
all the time, but
we'll have some fun as well.
Oh, wait.
Aigoo.
Here.
What is this?
Another manual?
These are quick breakfast recipes.
Don't just wait for them to
make food for you.
Look at this and make breakfast
a couple of times a week.
I don't think I can do this.
Gosh, even if you don't think
you can't, you should try.
You were able to sit and wait
because I took it from you.
You can't do that with
your daughter-in-law. Okay?
You can read it easily, huh?
So you could read it easily.
Practice them while they're
away on their honeymoon.
You have to do this to be loved
by your daughter-in-law.
True.
The tall guy living across from her is a
master homemaker who makes dumplings.
Yes, I could do this, too.
All right, Jung Min Jae.
Aigoo...
Gosh...
Gosh, I knew you'd be here, Mom.
- Mom!
- Why are you guys here?
We thought you'd be lonely.
Mom, you have Ra Hoon and me.
Gosh, I know.
I have you guys.
I'm not lonely at all.
Ra Hoon and I will be
better to you. Right?
Yeah, of course! I'll be so
good to you, Mom.
Aigoo.
Gosh, I'm touched even
hearing those words.
I'm tearing up.
Aigoo, my Hae Deun.
Here, you, too.
Aigoo, thank you.
What will my mom do once
I go to the military, too?
Aigoo...
Ra Hoon, why do you look so down?
Aigoo, you're feeling sad, my son.
- Since your older sister is out of the house.
- Oh, no...
Gosh, Lee Ra Hoon.
You sure are the youngest.
Let go. You're dead.
- Were you sad?
- I'll use my strength on you.
♫  When you look at me
with your warm gaze  ♫
♫  My weary heart melts away  ♫
♫  Without any reason  ♫
Am I dreaming?
You're not dreaming.
I'm not.
I think there is such
a thing as destiny.
Why?
The first time I saw you
at the construction site,
you didn't feel like a stranger.
- You seemed so familiar.
- You, too, Moong-i?
The moment I butt your head,
I came to. As if you
crashed into my heart.
Finally, my destiny...
I thought I finally met my destiny.
Gosh, that's too...
What do you mean?
♫  You make me fill up my whole
day with the thoughts of you.  ♫
Did you arrive okay, Chae Woon?
Yes, Mother.
Jung Won, no...
Did you call your mothers?
I'm about to.
You should've called them first.
I'll call Dad.
Okay. Chae Woon, have a good time and...
have a relaxing time.
Okay. Thank you.
I'll let you talk to Jae Hee.
Wait, Chae Woon.
I felt terrible about last time.
I shouldn't have
brought up Park Pil Hong.
I'm so sorry.
No, Mother.
What?
I'm still so childish
even though I'm older.
I regretted it a lot.
I'm really sorry.
It's okay. I'm really fine, Mother.
At Father's company?
Yeah.
The business division made a formal offer
for me to work on a project for a year.
Father must've ordered them, huh?
Probably.
Dad helped me out with
my company a lot recently.
I think I should help him, too.
But I'm worried that my relationship with
him would worsen while working on the project.
The project is one thing, but...
don't you think Father suggested it
because he wants to work with you?
Father reached out to you first.
Why don't you muster up the courage?
Should I?
I finally feel like
we're starting out together.
Our adventure.
Gosh, we went through tough
adventures all this time.
You had some tough times, Moong-i.
I did.
But the future adventures
are different, though.
It's a heart-fluttering, happy adventure.
I'm sure we'll face some
difficulties, but
I'm not afraid at all.
Thanks to this.
Moong-i.
Let's live delightfully.
Let's grow old gracefully...
and let's be happy for a very long time.
Okay.
I'll be your good friend and a good wife.
I'll be your dependable husband.
I love you, Chae Woon.
Thank you so much for
becoming my wife.
marrying me, too.
I love you, Jae Hee.
Please look over here.
Are you sure Director Jang Seo Ah
didn't order you the job
with an intention?
Director Jang Seo Ah has nothing
to do with construction affiliates
personally nor for business.
And she did not interfere with
Woo Jae Hee's contract intentionally.
Don't be scared.
It will be okay.
Drink this tea.
It was rough, huh?
I was scared until I got
to the police station.
But I feel more relieved now.
Thank you.
I got over a hurdle thanks to you, Na Ro.
Let's resolve one thing at a time together.
Gosh, it looks delicious!
Taste it.
Put it there.
- I'll wipe here.
- Over here.
It's really good.
I'm going to do this.
Go away.
What's that?
Is Bit Chae here already?
I don't think so.
- Come on.
- I'm trying.
- Why are you trying to be close to me?
- Joon Ah.
Move.
- You were here, too, Joon Ah.
- Mom.
My gosh, Unni!
Oh, my.
CEO, what are you doing here?
They said they're going
over to your house.
I talked to Chae Woon.
She said to meet everyone
here altogether.
I see.
Gosh, why did you bring
so much stuff, Unni?
Aigoo, it's nothing.
Take these. They must be heavy.
Thank you for bringing them.
- Aigoo.
- Oh, my goodness.
Aigoo...
- Thank you.
- My goodness.
Hae Deun.
Hi.
Hello, CEO.
Hae Deun, you've been acting
strangely since last time.
Pardon?
You're so nice to me all of a sudden.
- I know.
- She's so wild.
Yeah. I mean, you're awkwardly
gentle right now.
I'm gentle, to begin with.
What? She's not awkward at all.
Actually, I'm enforcing manners
with Director Lee.
Our company policy is to be gentle.
Aigoo, aigoo.
You should try harder.
Soon Jung, how can I help you?
What should I do?
Gosh, no. Just have a seat.
- No, I want to help out.
- Ra Hoon.
- Get some tea.
- No, no.
Don't get me any tea. I'm not a guest.
Mother, we need to peel these, right?
Yeah, Ba Reun.
Oh, Soon Jung, I'll peel garlic.
Aigoo, gosh.
Hae Deun, should we peel
garlic together?
Me, me?
Go ahead.
Sure. I mean...
- Let's peel them together.
- Unni, do you know how?
- Do you know how?
- I'll work hard at it.
I haven't done kitchen work in a while.
I'm not doing this well.
You can't dig into the
garlic clove like that.
Look. Just peel the skin like this.
I see. Like this?
Gosh, you're so bad at this, CEO.
Peel the skin gently like this.
Don't use your nails. Do it like this.
Like this.
Hae Deun, you're so good at this.
- Do it all then.
- Gosh, you can't leave like this.
We have to peel all these.
Hurry. Let's do it.
Peel the skin like this.
Don't scratch it with your nails.
Gosh, my eyes sting.
CEO, your hands are so slow.
So funny.
Your hands are golden, I meant.
I'll peel them all, CEO. Go over there.
No, I'll peel them.
You're so good.
Mother, we're here!
Seo Yeon is here.
Oh, my.
Sorry, Hae Deun.
Whoa, back from honeymoon.
Did you have fun?
Hey!
Whoa, looking good.
Unni, Brother-in-law.
I heard you were here, Mother.
So we came straight here.
Yeah, it's so lovely to celebrate
with everyone gathered here.
I know.
Mothers, we'll bow.
Aigoo, so pretty.
- Unni is so pretty.
- Right?
Did you have fun on your honeymoon?
Yes.
Did you have a nice dream?
A dream?
Well, not sure. Did you dream?
Soon Jung.
Go ahead.
Yeah?
All you have to do is be happy.
Right?
Jae Hee, love Chae Woon a lot.
Yes. I'll love her very much.
Chae Woon, be good to Jae Hee as well.
Always don't lose your first love.
Yes. I'll do that, Mom.
Okay. Now that you're back
from your honeymoon,
you're stepping out first as a married couple,
Woo Jae Hee and Lee Bit Chae Woon...
Gosh, it's so weird to
call them "a married couple."
Hae Deun, I forgot what
I was going to say.
All right. To wish them happiness
and joy for the couple.
For the happiness of
our Samgwang Villa family
and first steps for the newlywed.
Cheers!
Wait, wait a minute.
On a happy day like today, shouldn't
we hear a song from our newlyweds?
- Hey, what are you saying?
- Sounds good!
Sounds great.
I want to hear you sing, Jae Hee.
You, too, Chae Woon.
Mother, I can't sing at all.
- No, no.
- Sing a song!
- Eat, eat!
If you can't sing, you can't get married.
But you're married.
One more time still.
All right, all right.
Then we'll sing a song.
Let's go.
So cool.
Good, good.
Okay, okay.
I can't do that.
We can't wait!
One, two, three, four.
♫   It's good! It's good! It's good!  ♫
♫   It's very, very good   ♫
♫   It's perfect! It's perfect! It's perfect!    ♫
♫   You're the perfect one   ♫
♫   When you ask for love, it's okay!  ♫
♫   Okay!  ♫
♫   Even when you whine, it's okay!   ♫
♫  ♫   You're very, very good!   ♫  ♫
Gosh, I can't believe you're driving us.
On top of that, you told us
to sit in the back.
Yeah, Mom. We're so uncomfortable.
No.
I wanted to drive you, my Seo Yeon.
- Jae Hee.
- Yes.
I leave Seo Yeon to your care.
Yes, Mother. Don't you worry.
Mom...
My daughter...
My Seo Yeon, you have
to be happy, okay?
Yes, Mom.
Mom and Dad, we'll bow.
We'll bow.
Aigoo...
Gosh, you're so pretty, my Chae Woon.
Thank you.
I'm sure your two mothers had
wonderful things to say.
Let's get along in the future,
Ms. Chae Woon.
What do you mean, "Ms." Chae Woon?
My daughter-in-law.
Chae Woon.
Thank you in advance, Father and Mother.
If it's uncomfortable living
with your father-in-law
or if you have any complaints,
report them to me.
- "Report"?
- Okay?
Okay.
Mom, can I report them to you, too?
I won't accept your complaints.
Why not?
All right.
We should take you to
your newlywed room.
Whoa!
Gosh, did you do all this by yourself?
Father...
It's so nice, Father.
Father, you must've worked
so hard to prepare this room.
Didn't you hurt your shoulder trying to
put those balloons up there?
I did hurt it. Look...
Over here?
I'm just kidding.
It's okay.
Aigoo...
My goodness... whoa...
When did you do all this?
Wow...
Don't come out.
Mom, be careful going home.
Goodbye, Mother.
Bye, Jung Min Jae.
Bye.
Oh? Geez...
Geez...
Wait.
- What are you doing?
- The recipes I gave you...
Did you do your homework?
No, I didn't.
What in the world?
I told you to practice while
they were on their honeymoon.
You really didn't do it?
Do you think I have that much time?
Whatever.
I don't care whether you become
a disliked father-in-law or not.
Don't you become a disliked
mother-in-law, Jung Min Jae.
Don't you worry. I'll work on it.
I'm leaving.
I won't walk you out.
What?
Goodbye.
Bye.
It's so weird.
I'm so happy that the kids
are happily married.
But why does she look more lonely?
Aigoo...
I should've been good to her.
♫  You are just like a giving tree  ♫
♫  Even if you give me everything  ♫
Woo Jung Hoo...
Why does he look so lonely
even though he's smiling?
Gosh, I'm lonely, too.
Life is lonely for everyone.
So lonely...
♫  You've always been there for me  ♫
♫  You always said, "I'm so happy"  ♫
♫  You always said, "If I like you, I like it, too"  ♫
Why did you show up in front of me?
Why must you be so pathetic? Why?
♫  The only thing I need is you  ♫
♫  You always said, "I'm so happy"  ♫
♫  You always said, "If I like you, I like it, too"  ♫
♫  I don't want much from you anymore  ♫
♫  The only thing I need is you  ♫
Seo Yeon must be back
from the honeymoon.
Be happy, Seo Yeon.
♫  The only thing I need is
you right by my side  ♫
♫  Just like a giving tree  ♫
♫  Even if you give me everything  ♫
♫  It's never good enough for you  ♫
Moong-i...
Let's sleep five more minutes.
Five minutes.
Ten minutes.
Breakfast?
Oh, no...
Ow, Moong-i...
It hurts.
Let's hurry.
What's this smell?
It smells so savory...
D... Dad...
Father...
Good morning.
Why did you come down so early?
Are you making breakfast?
We were going to do it.
It's our first day. I wanted to prepare it.
It's a welcome breakfast.
Gosh, Father...
But I can't guarantee the taste.
Father...
We'll make breakfast tomorrow.
I'm sorry.
Dad, I'm so shocked.
Don't be too sorry, Chae Woon.
We live together now.
We should share stuff like this.
I even made our schedule.
Here.
Look at this.
When did you come up with this?
Does "babes" here refer to us?
That's right.
My daughter-in-law.
Since you're her husband,
you're kiddo, too.
Father, you're listed more often.
You're at a disadvantage, Father.
What?
Then I'll switch it next month.
- How about it?
- But still...
Dad, you might get sick doing this.
Hurry up and make money
so that you can move out.
Before I get sick.
Gosh, we should make money quickly.
Okay, eat. It will get cold.
Okay. Thank you.
Father, it's delicious.
Huh?
Wait.
It's unexpectedly good.
Dad, it's really good.
Gosh, I'm so relieved.
I'm glad I practiced.
You practiced?
Just a little bit.
Because Min Jae was nagging
me so much about it.
- Eat. Eat a lot.
- Thank you for this food.
All right...
Dad.
I'll work on your company project.
Will you?
If I talked to you about it,
I thought you'd say,
"I don't want any favors from you!"
I reached out to you officially
through our business division.
Geez, I wouldn't have said that.
Come on, man.
You're pretending not to be like
that with Chae Woon here.
But...
it will be tough to handle two jobs
with your own office.
Will you be okay?
Well, I'll have to work hard
to pay off my debt.
I'll work hard, Dad.
Okay. Do a good job.
- Fighting.
- Eat.
Yes.
It's good.
I guess I'm talented at cooking.
Yeah, you're good.
More than anything, be sure the
construction is done safely and on time.
Yes, will do.
Oh, Jae Hee, welcome!
Did you have a nice time
on your honeymoon?
Yes, Director. Thank you in advance.
Of course.
Wow, I look forward to
your work, Jae Hee.
Welcome, Mr. Woo Jae Hee.
I look forward to working with you.
Thank you in advance.
Yes, Eems hyung.
Everything is ready.
Thanks to you, we're doing well today.
- What's going on?
- I know.
What is all this?
Okay. No, no, sit down.
Eat comfortably.
It's my treat. Enjoy.
You are, President?
Yes.
But why would you treat us?
My son got married.
So it's on me.
Enjoy.
It's warm and delicious.
Okay, eat, eat.
Gosh, it's spicy. It relieves my stress.
Thank you, President.
Yes, enjoy.
It's melting in my mouth.
Why don't you join us, President?
Should I do that?
Then excuse me.
Go ahead and eat.
- It's good.
- You love your son so much.
You're so awesome, President.
Aigoo, thank you.
Both of them are being
investigated, right?
I'm not sure about that.
What's going to happen now?
Hello.
Hi, Bit Chae Woon. Did you have
a lovely honeymoon?
Yes, thanks to you.
Thank you.
Bit Chae Woon, you got prettier.
I know.
Come on now.
Thanks for going around the
branches on your first day back.
No problem.
But you know...
I heard that the police investigated
Director Jang Seo Ah and Chief Hwang Na Ro.
Pardon?
I guess you didn't know, Bit Chae Woon.
They're not at a meeting as we speak.
They're actually at their
second interrogation.
Yeah, I heard Chairwoman Lee Choon Suk
is being summoned, too.
I'm sorry, Grandma. It's all my fault.
I'm glad you know it's your fault.
I tried to stop you so badly.
Aigoo...
- Gosh. Aigoo.
- Chairwoman.
- Grandma!
Grandma?
Seo Ah, how is the Chairwoman?
Go in.
See for yourself.
Thankfully, she's conscious.
She needs to rest for a while.
Lucky you.
Now that Grandma and I are both
in this current predicament.
Must you say it like that in this situation?
- Seo Yeon...
- Mom...
She just fell asleep.
She turned a corner.
I feel like I did this to her.
I feel so bad.
Don't think like that.
Thanks to you...
she made the right decision.
Right.
But still, she'll be investigated
without being detained.
What a relief that is.
She said she'll pay enough
for compensation.
Don't worry too much about
Jae Hee's company.
Okay.
We're meeting Jae Hee oppa now?
I don't want to.
Seo Ah.
We must meet Woo Jae Hee.
We'll meet and apologize to him.
We have to check on damages suffered
by the subcontractors and take care of them.
I don't want to. Why should I?
Do you still have feelings
for Woo Jae Hee?
If it's not that,
listen to me.
We went in for a police investigation
along with the Chairwoman.
I heard from my subcontractors.
I wanted to know about
the subcontractors' damages.
I'll visit each one of them to
apologize and pay for damages.
Why?
You sure change your words fast.
I should move quickly on this.
We weren't trying to destroy subcontractors
who had nothing to do with this.
We'll compensate them plentifully.
Fine. Apologizing quickly
and compensation?
Sounds good. However...
your crime doesn't disappear
just because you do this.
The wounds don't disappear.
For them as well as for Chae Woon.
I had no idea...
things would get this bad.
I really hated you, Oppa.
You were so heartless,
and I hated you for it.
I couldn't see things clearly.
Is that why you asked for help from
Hwang Na Ro and the Chairwoman?
And you helped Seo Ah
when you knew about this.
But now you're busy trying
to clean up the mess.
No matter what happens to others, you're
fine as long as you kiss up to Seo Ah?
Woo Jae Hee...
We didn't intercept the contract illegally.
A more solid company had jumped
in the middle of the deal.
Why did you involve Park Pil Hong in this?
Park Pil Hong kept
pestering the Chairwoman.
He was asking her for some work.
That's why she asked him to do that.
You weren't trying to put everything on
Park Pil Hong and put him
away in prison?
That's not it.
Hey, Hwang Na Ro.
What should I do?
I can't believe anything you say,
no matter what.
Woo Jae Hee...
Oppa.
Na Ro is genuine.
Believe him.
- For my sake.
- So...
I'm worried that Hwang Na Ro is
with you for your sake.
I'll apologize.
Oppa...
I'm sorry.
But don't think negatively of Na Ro.
I love him.
Looks good.
I'm glad that it ended there for Seo Ah.
Yeah, I'm glad.
But I think she needs to go in
a few more times for interrogation.
There still are lots of things
to take care of.
I went to see Grandma earlier.
She seemed to be having
a tough time as well.
She needs to be hospitalized
a little longer.
Mr. Makjang!
What are you doing?
Mom, cheer up. Call me if
something comes up.
I have to get back to work.
Okay. Good day.
He must be close to Hae Deun.
- Come on.
- I'm trying.
- Why are you trying to be close to me?
- Joon Ah.
- Come on.
- Move.
Smile bigger.
Change up the pose. Nice.
So pretty! So pretty.
They're not in focus here.
- Sorry. Let's take a break.
- Okay.
Lee Ra Hoon, aren't you
going to work today?
Huh?
I'm off today.
Then you should've stayed home.
Why are you here?
Cha Ba Reun, he's so attached to you.
I asked him to wait for me.
So we could leave together.
This is a workplace. You think you're
waiting for a study session to end?
Hey, Ra Hoon, this is bad.
We have to take them over again.
- This will take a while.
- Really?
Yeah.
It's okay.
Hey, Lee Ra Hoon!
Are you going to leave?
Since you've waited this long,
why don't you wait a little longer?
I don't know when
you'll be done, though.
That's why I told you
not to come today.
When did you say not to come?
You said to come if I have time
and go see a movie afterward.
Hey, that's because you want to
hang around me all the time lately.
Even today, you said you're not
going to work at the food truck.
I just mentioned that you should come.
I had no idea you'd dart over like this.
"Dart over?"
You "just mentioned it"?
Whoa, I must be bugging you now.
I guess I'm just a sticky leech to you.
Well? A little bit, I guess.
You keep following me around lately.
I think you're obsessed with me.
I have my reasons.
It's not like I'll get to see you
all the time in the future.
What are you talking about?
Nothing.
I'll go ahead, Cha Ba Reun.
Hey, Lee Ra Hoon.
Gosh, what's wrong with him lately?
I knew it when I saw those
two hang around together.
Isn't it too much, though?
Who knows...
Hello.
Chae Woon, that branch manager
is handsome, huh?
I was so surprised today
when I saw him.
The staff knows that I went in
for interrogations, huh?
I think so.
Seo Ah, I told you it's something
we have to go through anyway.
Don't let them see you shaken.
He used Lee Hae Deun as a model?
Look at these people.
Seo Ah.
What the heck?
Ba Reun said she'll see
Ra Hoon out and come back.
What's taking her so long?
Let them be alone.
So we could have
a good time by ourselves.
What in the world...
Hae Deun.
Do this. Like Jesus.
- Do this.
- Like this?
Hug me for a minute like that.
- My gosh, what?
- Hug me for a minute.
- Just a minute.
- What's this?
- Whoa! It's so cute!
- Isn't it cute?
- This is...
- Did you buy this for me?
Isn't it so cute? Adorable, huh?
Gosh, so adorable.
So cute. You look the same.
I was walking by and noticed that
the bunny looked just like you.
- That's why I bought it for you.
- What in the world?
- Hug me for a minute.
- What if people see us?
Who's going to look? People are...
- Hug me.
- No...
Thirty seconds.
- Thirty seconds.
- No.
Fine. Twenty seconds.
Yay!
- Hug me, hug me.
- Jang Joon Ah.
What?
What do you mean?
Why do you barge in
without saying anything?
"You"?
What brings you here, Director?
Jang Joon Ah.
Did you submit this as a finished product?
Yes, I submitted it as my final.
The concept and styling are
totally messed up.
Did you do the styling for this one?
- Yes.
- See?
You got a ridiculous product because
you hired someone without any basics.
I don't think it's that
ridiculous, though. Right?
Director.
I worked on it based on
the design team's feedback.
I don't think it's ridiculous.
And the company asked
me to come work here.
Good, good, good job.
Had I been involved from the beginning,
I would've never selected you,
Lee Hae Deun.
What do you want me to do about it?
I'm already here.
Hire a professional model
and start over.
Hey.
- Hey, hey.
- Jang Seo Ah!
"Jang Seo Ah"?
Aren't you thoughtless here?
Hold yourself back.
- What?
- You could dislike it as a director.
But to rip up the work that someone
worked so hard on is substandard.
Substandard?
It looks like you're in a foul mood
and are taking it out on us.
But still, this is wrong!
- Hey!
- What?
What are you two doing?
People will come in.
You know that the police interrogated me.
So you think I'm easy, too?
What are you talking about?
- Hey, Seo Ah...
- How rude are you?
You and Bit Chae Woon are the same!
You just found that out?
My unni and I could go bonkers.
What?
I see. I guess this is how you
mistreated my sister, too.
It's a miracle that Bit Chae Woon
still lets you live. She's a saint!
- Hae Deun, please...
- Oppa!
Fire her right away!
Fine! Fire me! Go ahead!
Geez, what are you two doing?
This is nuts. Seriously.
Geez, this is nuts.
Director.
I'll apologize sincerely. Sorry.
I just have to do it over, right?
And you shouldn't tell me to
fire my employee...
Director Lee. Hae Deun...
Gosh, I'm about to go crazy
because of you, Seo Ah.
Hey, what are you doing?
What's with this?
Seo Ah, I realize you're on edge
after the police interrogation.
But this isn't right.
What the heck is this?
Let's calm down. Please?
Director Lee, geez...
Lee Hae Deun.
Lee Hae Deun!
Director, did something happen?
How could two sisters be so same?
Tell Lee Hae Deun to get out now.
What's going on?
Was there trouble between
you and Hae Deun?
Hae Deun doesn't insist
on things without reason.
Are you siding with her
because she's your sister?
This is your workplace.
Seo Ah, I know you're having
a hard time right now.
But you shouldn't take it out
on people like this.
Let go.
Fine.
I could be siding with Hae Deun
because she's my sister.
But if you were in a similar situation,
I'd side with you.
Because we're sisters.
What did Hae Deun do wrong?
Tell me. I'll talk to her. Please?
I heard from the CEO.
That you're trying to resolve things.
I think it's very brave and
you're doing the right thing.
I want to help you if I could, Seo Ah.
Did you have a nice honeymoon?
Yes.
Where do you guys live?
I'm living with my father.
Aigoo, at the father-in-law's house.
It must be uncomfortable for Seo Yeon.
I'm sure it's not that uncomfortable.
She's close to my father.
Really?
No matter how close they are,
he's still her in-law.
Pardon?
Why did you want to meet me?
What kind of work are you
doing these days?
I'm not doing anything bad. I cut ties
with Chairwoman Lee Choon Suk, too.
I'm not saying you might be
into anything bad.
If you're not doing anything,
come out and work at my site.
Are you looking after
your father-in-law?
Because you're Chae Woon's father.
Chae Woon wouldn't like this, but
I want to look after you.
Thank you for saying that, but
the construction work doesn't suit me.
Then what kind of work
are you going to do?
- At this rate...
- So...
I found something that
totally suits me.
What is it?
I'll let you know when
the deal goes through.
You're not doing something terrible like
getting paid to do things, are you?
No, no.
Would I do things like that after
seeing what you went through?
And...
this is small, but it's my wedding gift.
I made it with loving care in every stitch.
I'm giving you a gift that I made myself
- but once I make tons of money...
- No, no.
This stuffed animal. It's perfect.
Don't think about getting something
for us by making lots of money.
Geez, you don't trust me at all.
I'm sad.
Geez, Father. What is he trying to do?
Moong-i.
Are you busy, hubby?
I'm swamped, but
I was thinking about
my lovely wife Moong-i.
What's going on?
Just because. I wanted
to hear your voice.
I have to go somewhere today.
Do you want to go with me later?
Where?
Hae Deun. Hae Deun...
Why are you walking so fast?
You don't look it, but you're so fast.
You didn't go out to dinner?
I heard the design team was eating
together for working late.
How can I go there
without you, Hae Deun?
Wait. Talk to me for a minute.
The police interrogated Director Jang?
Yes. She went in voluntarily
and was questioned.
For ruining Jae Hee's contract?
That's right.
Seo Ah is on edge lately
because of that.
You know her temper.
She's trying to keep her temper in
check but tends to burst on whomever.
But she still shouldn't
take it out on me.
I'm not her emotional trash can.
I know. I know.
People with weak mental
power do that.
They behave contrary to their feelings.
Seo Ah was always so anxious,
even as a child.
I feel so sorry for her
as her older brother.
I regret it a lot, thinking that
I should've been nicer to her.
That's why I probably sided
with her earlier.
You were hurt, huh?
Yes.
I'm really sorry, Hae Deun.
I'm really sorry.
In some ways, I think you're
really close to me.
So I guess I did that inadvertently.
I must've thought that you'd
understand how I feel.
Can't you understand me
a little bit? Just a little bit?
I'm having a hard time these days
because of Seo Ah. I'm so drained.
So please be just
a little bit understanding.
Koala! Did you wait long?
Gosh, why call me Koala?
I'm your hubby now.
What should I call you?
How about be traditional
and call me "honey"?
Geez, nah. It's weird.
It's weird? How about "honey-buns"?
Gosh, I get goosebumps.
You're "Koala-honey-buns," so...
How about "Ko-bong"?
Ko-bong.
Ko-bong? No way. Never mind.
Just call me Koala.
Why? It's nice. Ko-bong.
Ko-bong, Ko-bong, Ko-bong.
Ko-bong.
Father looks busy.
It's a busy time.
Wow, Father will be so touched when
he finds out we came to take him home.
Let's go and help him.
No. I think he has about 30 minutes left.
Should we go to Samgwang Villa
and see Mother?
Should we?
I'm so sad and having a hard time.
I wonder if I wasted my life.
I feel like it's all my fault.
Why is that your fault?
All right. I'll try to be understanding.
You'll try to be understanding?
Are you less angry now?
Hae Deun, be a little understanding...
I'm sorry. Please forgive me
this once, Hae Deun.
- Don't do that again.
- I won't do it again. I promise.
I promise. I'll be on your side
no matter what.
- Really.
- Really. I'll be on your side.
Do you forgive me then?
- I'll see about that.
- Give me a kiss.
Put a stamp on it to seal the deal.
Once. Hurry. Someone will see us.
What the heck?
Unni.
Hey.
Joon... Joon Ah...
You guys...
You must be shocked.
Hae Deun. Hae Deun, it's okay.
Come here.
It's okay.
I mean...
- Holding hands?
- Oh, hands!
We were just holding our hands.
Were you together?
Congrats on your wedding.
Congrats.
Oh, what?
Run! Run! Run!
- Run!
- Lee Hae Deun!
Hey!
Come here! Jang Joon Ah!
Get them!
♫   Honey, baby, sweetie, darling, good!  ♫
♫   It's good! It's very, very good   ♫
♫   I totally fell for you   ♫
♫   It's perfect! You're truly perfect   ♫
♫   It's a destiny like a present   ♫
♫   The pretty face with a big big smile   ♫
Am I not your senior now, Unni? Right?
Lee Hae Deun!
Do what? Remarry?
That's right. I'll start anew.
You begin your new life, too.
Oh, my gosh!
Excuse me. Is there a jokbal
place around here?
- By chance, are you Eun Ji?
- Hwak Se oppa?
Hwak Se oppa!
It's my first time holding
Seo Yeon's hand.
Take good care of my Seo Yeon.
He must've been in the
same prison with Park Pil Hong.
Mother.
It's not true, is it?
There was some misunderstanding, right?
Jae Hee.
Why open your store here?
Samgwang Villa is right there.
Jae Hee?
What brings you here?
Hello. I'm Lee Dong Chool,
and I opened up this tailor shop today.
♫   The best!  ♫
♫   Honey, baby, sweetie, darling, good!  ♫