Chae Woon.
Yeah?
Yeah...
You weren't sleeping?
Yeah.
You weren't sleeping, Auntie?
Did Mr. Woo go somewhere?
Well...
Yeah, he had to go to a site early.
He left.
It looks like he went somewhere far.
Yeah, a bit.
He said he has to stay there for a while.
Why did you cry?
Because he went far away?
I didn't cry.
There's a trace of tears on your face.
My gosh.
- What could it be?
- Stop lying.
Why weren't you sleeping?
Geez...
Chae Woon...
Anyway, cheer up. I'm going to bed now.
Okay.
- Is something wrong?
- Nothing's wrong.
Chae Woon.
Hi, Mom.
Whoa!
Did you iron this?
I couldn't find it to wear. Of course.
Thank you.
With this shirt...
should I tie my hair up?
Let me see.
No? Put it down?
I'll do that.
Aigoo.
Mom.
Mr. Woo and you didn't argue
or anything, right?
No.
Jae Hee wants to focus on work
for now and think things through.
Same with me.
Right.
You both need more time, I guess.
Some time to endure, right?
Yeah. I think so.
But still...
don't try to put on
a bold face all the time.
Even an elastic band will break
if you pull too hard.
Let it be known to me
when you're struggling
and discuss it with me.
Okay?
Okay, Mom.
My gosh. You two must
really love each other.
Dad, I'm leaving for
a construction site in Incheon.
I'll focus on work there and take care
of my company problems.
♫  When you look at me with your warm gaze  ♫
Thank you for helping me out.
I'll work hard and pay you back.
I'm sorry for my harsh words.
Oh, yeah.
I'll call Mom and ease her mind.
Please look out for her,
so she doesn't become anxious.
Stay healthy.
Love, Jae Hee.
♫  Meeting like a fate, and stopped time  ♫
Geez, this guy.
He is hell-bent.
♫  I'm in love, I'm in love  ♫
♫  I guess love changes everything  ♫
♫  You make me fill up my whole day
with the thoughts of you  ♫
Koala!
I'll savor this moment.
What in the world?
♫  With you  ♫
Joon Ah.
Mother, I love you.
What's going on this early
in the morning?
Mom, I have to confess
something again.
- Again?
- Yes.
- Can you sit for a moment?
- Oppa!
Hi, Seo Ah. Good morning.
Thank you.
Well...
I'm working at your company
these days, Mom.
What?
You know your online photography team?
I'm working with them.
Oppa, since when?
It's only been a few days. Be quiet.
Did you shut down your
online shopping mall then?
No, no. I didn't shut it down.
The online photography
team saw my mall
and suggested that we work together.
They said that we have good taste, and
they like our styling sensibilities.
Really?
I guess your shopping mall
must be pretty good then.
Our online photography
team is quite particular.
Rather than liking our shopping mall,
my stylist is pretty good.
Gosh.
Look at this guy. Because there's
an event at work today,
he's afraid that we'll bump into
each other. That's why you're here.
Right?
Mom, that's not it. Really.
You know the day I went to
you see you at your office?
I went there to tell you this that day.
But because of that Mr. Sideburn.
Is that his name?
No. Hwang... Hwang Na Ro?
Because of him, I totally forgot.
If I do bump into you at work,
just treat me like a professional at work.
Hey, you too, Seo Ah.
Of course, we will.
The employees might start talking.
Oh, yeah.
Oppa.
What do you think of Na Ro
after meeting him?
What do you mean?
Na Ro? That guy?
Well? I don't know.
To me, he's...
Forget it if you'll say you
don't like him. Don't say it.
Geez, unbelievable.
Seo Ah, you just asked me.
Then you should hear me out.
Will you only hear what you want to hear?
Are you a dictator or something?
What are you looking at?
I'm talking to you.
Thank you.
Hello, CEO.
Hello. We meet again.
What brings you here this morning?
Na Ro is here to pick me up.
What?
What the heck...
Do you come by every morning
to pick up Seo Ah like this?
I'm Director Jang Seo Ah's assistant.
Gosh, this is unbelievable.
Hey, Jang Seo Ah.
Even Mom goes to work alone.
What the heck are you doing?
Do you have a hard time
walking or something?
Are you a baby?
Oppa, we'll go ahead if
you're done talking.
What are you saying? Are you a baby?
We're done talking?
CEO, we'll see you at work.
See you at work, Mom.
You, too, Oppa.
Hey, what? Jang Seo Ah, stop. Hey.
Hey, hey. One, two.
- This one.
- Okay.
Dae Won, is this the one?
Yes.
Bit Chae Woon, take this one, too.
Okay, I'll get it.
Chae Woon, check on the
speaker's schedule again.
Okay, will do.
- It's okay. Please rush.
- I'm sorry.
Let's wrap this up today.
Unni!
Fighting!
Gosh, I feel so bad for my sister.
What's going on with Bit Chae Woon?
What? You're Mr. Woo's friend,
and you don't know?
What?
I guess Mr. Woo's construction
contract didn't work out.
So I heard he's hit hard.
Is that right? I had no idea.
So he went to another location to
work to make up for his loss.
He's separated from my sister.
So how do you think my sister feels?
But in my opinion,
I think this is all Jang Seo Ah's fault.
That CEO Kim Jung Won's daughter.
I heard that vixen used to like Mr. Woo.
You must know since you're his friend.
I know a little bit about it.
Oh, then you must know Jang Seo Ah.
That obsessive, rude wench.
I do know a little bit about her.
Anyway...
I think that Jang Seo Ah
played a trick on him.
Did I go too far?
No. I don't know about that.
Anyway, I hate both CEO Kim Jung Won
and Jang Seo Ah. Hate them.
Director Lee, Director Lee.
We need one more model.
I'm supposed to be the model.
No, not that. We have too many
outfits. We need one more model.
- What should we do?
- Really?
Let me call the models who
used to model for my mall.
They're not...
Why won't they answer?
The customer is not answering the phone.
They're avoiding my call on purpose.
They don't think I'll pay them.
- What do we do?
- Oh, trust me with this.
What? Who? Who?
Ba Reun, are you almost ready?
Yeah, I'm coming.
Hurry, hurry.
It's too cold outside.
What the heck?
How could you be so cute?
Are you a polar bear or something?
It's Hae Deun unni.
Hi, Unni.
Model?
Right now?
You said to model, right?
Could she do a good job?
Has she ever modeled?
Let's record some poses
to show Ba Reun.
Looks good.
Gosh, so pretty.
Looking great.
Great. So pretty. That's good.
Good. Look at it.
Let's look.
As for your hand gestures,
do it a little less.
- What a great recording.
- Your expression is excellent here.
- It's a work of art.
- What the heck?
Aren't you Bit Chae Won's sister?
Hello.
Jang Seo Ah. That rude wench.
Lee Hae Deun is working as a contractor
for the online photography team.
Is that so?
- How about my oppa...
- Hey, hey...
Oh, not hey.
Gosh, I'm speechless. I misspoke.
I'm sorry. We work together. Hello.
I heard they selected a talented stylist.
Did they pick just anybody?
By chance, did you get hired
through Bit Chae Woon?
It's not just anybody.
You'll find out when you
talk to Chief Yoon.
The online photography team
contacted our shopping mall first.
You're so clueless.
Why do you speak so bluntly?
Yes, hello.
We're not just anybody.
Our stylist has an incredible sensibility.
Should I show you our work?
Chief Yoon spoke very
highly of Lee Hae Deun.
She doesn't have much
experience as a stylist,
but she's very talented.
Well, we'll have to see about that.
Her contract isn't that long, right?
I'll check.
Hi, Unni.
Bit Chae Woon.
Gosh, seriously.
How can you carry them like this?
You're pressing this down.
That's the point here.
Why are you so thoughtless?
If I don't carry them like this,
this side gets flat.
I checked out everything.
Gosh, she would've put them away
while talking like that.
Lee Hae Deun.
- What did you just say?
- I mean...
you must be bored, Director.
You're picking on my sister
when she hasn't done anything.
No, wait. I'm the director here.
- She was talking to me. I'm the director.
- What are you talking about?
What the heck? It's so annoying.
They're all clinging to our company.
Director.
Clinging on?
How about you? Are you clinging here
because you're the CEO's daughter?
What?
You're not, right?
We're not, either.
We proved our abilities
and were hired fairly.
We're working hard.
I believe that's not something
you should say as a director.
Hey, Bit Chae Woon.
Director, lots of people are
watching. Let's go.
So you won't see me anymore, right?
Fine. Let's break up. Let's end it.
Have a nice life, Kim Hwak Se.
♫  Don't cry  ♫
♫  I can understand you now  ♫
Hwak Se, where are you?
I miss you so much.
Please answer my call.
Or just text me, Hwak Se.
♫  Don't think of me as a child forever  ♫
Gosh, this is so annoying.
♫  I'm going toward you slowly  ♫
♫  Take one step toward me for me  ♫
♫  Don't say anything  ♫
Hwak Se, you do what you want to do.
I'll do whatever you say.
I was so happy all this time.
I was incredibly happy.
Because of you, Hwak Se.
Because you loved me so much.
That's all there is to it.
Be sure to keep seeing a doctor
wherever you are.
So you could continue to sing.
You love to sing.
Hwak Se, you're the coolest
when you sing.
Jjung-a...
♫  I'm going toward you slowly  ♫
♫  Take one step toward me for me  ♫
♫  Don't say anything  ♫
♫  What will you need? You have me  ♫
♫  I feel bad for having
nothing to give you  ♫
♫  Don't you cry, I love you  ♫
♫  Even your tears  ♫
Aigoo, aigoo...
Oh, there's a big hole.
Let me see.
Hello?
Hi, Seok Ho.
It's me, Soon Jung noona.
How have you been?
By chance...
have you talked to Hwak Se lately?
I'm sorry. We're not open yet.
Hwak Se.
Noonim.
What's this, Hwak Se?
You got me so worried.
Noonim...
How did you find out that I'm here?
Did you think I'd never find you?
I called everyone about you today
that I couldn't even go to work.
What will you do now?
I'm sorry, Noonim.
I just...
couldn't face you, Noonim.
And it pained me to see
Man Jung so upset.
So it looks like...
you're extremely selfish in one sense.
What?
You couldn't face me...
and it pained you to see Man Jung.
You ran away because
you couldn't stand it.
I'm disappointed in you, Hwak Se.
I hoped that you'd plead with me.
That you love Man Jung and
that you'll make her happy.
Or argue with me confidently.
"Can't you believe in me?
Does our love seem that
ridiculous to you?"
For me to do that, I felt...
so bad for you, Noonim.
If you had just...
slapped me across the face
or slap me in the back,
I would've felt less sorry.
I mean...
"I didn't raise my Man Jung so hard
to give her to a guy like you.
How dare someone like you...
- my wonderful Man Jung..."
- Gosh, you're so foolish!
That's right.
I could've said that.
If I'm just Man Jung's older sister,
I could say that a thousand times over.
But I'm also Kim Hwak Se's older sister.
To see Hwak Se, looking so intimidated
in front of the woman he loves,
really offended me.
Noonim...
How did I raise her? How about you?
How did we come to know each other?
You were so pitiful living
in the streets like that,
and I brought you home and turned you
into a wonderful little brother.
Such a special relationship is
about to be ruined overnight.
How could I not be cautious?
Gosh.
So...
when will you take
the rest of your stuff?
Noonim.
After you left the house on a whim,
did you think you could come back
to Samgwang Villa on a whim?
Does Samgwang Villa seem
that easy to you?
I heard you're preparing
for a radio singing contest.
Man Jung told me before.
Yes.
Make sure you make it.
Don't even think about coming
back before you make the cut.
You said you love Man Jung.
You know that Man Jung fell
for you watching you sing.
What can't you do for your love?
If you really love her,
can't you pluck a star in the sky?
Geez.
Here are some side dishes
and bellflower tea.
Eat it if you want or whatever.
I'm leaving!
Noonim.
Noonim...
Gosh, why aren't they here yet?
- Oh, Noona!
- Unni!
What took you so long?
I was so worried.
There was so much traffic.
- Sorry, Unni.
- Let's hurry up!
Hurry.
And now...
let's bring out a lady and
conduct a lesson.
Yes.
Please hold it.
Hold the driver flat for a backswing
and swing with your elbow
close to your body.
Nice. Good.
Okay, the same way.
Hold it.
Again. Hold the driver flat
on the backswing
and bring your right elbow
close to your body
and swing all the way.
Whoa.
Wow, you look great, Ba Reun.
You're good at modeling.
Thank you.
Hey, Cha Ba Reun. You know this is
all thanks to my styling, right?
Thank me.
Okay.
The way I see it,
my Ba Reun is talented.
- Aigoo.
- So I was thinking...
How about work as a model
every now and then?
Sounds great! We have to hire
more models anyway.
Really?
I always wanted to work as a model.
Really? That's great!
Whoa, Cha Ba Reun,
you're a model now.
- Good job today, everyone.
- Unni!
Good job to you, too.
Ba Reun, you looked great.
Thank you, Unni.
It was a lot of work today, huh?
Great styling.
I didn't do much.
My stylist is the talented one.
Gosh, Chae Woon, You were great, too.
You were flying all over
the place carrying heavy stuff.
Gosh, you were cool.
I'm pretty strong.
Whoa, I think I know
why Jae Hee is so into you.
Jae Hee likes strong women.
He loves a woman who knows
how to butt her head.
Gosh, really?
But now I look at you, you look
like my mom, Moong-i.
- My beauty?
- Your strength.
I heard Jae Hee is struggling because
the contract he was
working on fell through.
I heard from Hae Deun.
Yes.
He'll overcome it.
Yeah, of course. He'll overcome it.
Well...
Jae Hee's panic attacks...
Did you know about it, too?
You know about it, too, Chae Woon.
We had a really close friend
back in high school.
His name is Beom Jin.
During high school, Beom Jin's
father's business failed.
And his family was suffering financially.
Jae Hee saw all that and...
I guess he felt bad that
he asked his father to help them.
He pleaded with him for days, but
Jae Hee's father didn't help him.
I heard through the grapevine that
Beom Jin's father's health deteriorated
and passed away soon after.
After Jae Hee heard that,
he blamed himself.
He was so tormented and
shed tears. Gosh, really.
I saw him struggle
back then. Seriously.
Jae Hee struggled a lot then.
Did his panic attacks resurface again?
He was fine for a while.
Yes.
I think so.
Gosh, he must be having
a real hard time.
I should visit Jae Hee.
He's at a site in Incheon, right?
He sent me a text earlier.
Would you like to go with me?
I have to work late.
You're working late?
What do you mean you're working late?
Why are you working nonstop?
Don't you go on dates with Jae Hee?
You should stay together,
especially at times like this.
Are you two having some problems?
No.
We should get back to work.
We've been away too long. Right?
Yeah, sure.
Hello?
By chance, have you found
anything on Hwang Na Ro?
Nothing shows that Hwang Na Ro
was involved in the contract issue.
All right.
Come in.
The fact that I'm working on
the smart clothing project...
Did you hear that from Director Jang?
Yes.
So I researched the industry
trend relevant to this project
and future direction.
It's a thorough analysis.
If you entrust me with this project,
- in the future...
- Good job.
But unless I've asked you,
I don't like anyone touching
my project like this.
My apologies.
Hwang Na Ro.
You must be getting involved in this
with your future with Seo Ah in mind.
I'll tell you this once and for all.
As Seo Ah's mother,
I will not accept you, Hwang Na Ro.
So, don't approach me
this way again. Understand?
I'll keep that in mind.
But...
Director Jang Seo Ah is...
leading the company proactively lately.
She's less obsessed over
Woo Jae Hee as well.
I may be out of line saying
this to you, but
ever since Director Jang
became close to me,
I believe she's changing for the better.
I'll work hard and continue
to assist the director.
Chae Woon.
- Have a seat.
- Okay.
- Have some.
I didn't come to say anything special.
I just thought you'd feel down today.
I heard Jae Hee went to
a site in Incheon.
He snuck into my house
early in the morning.
Oh, really?
It's not like he's Santa.
He came, took out the trash,
and left me a letter.
I heard that you helped out Jae Hee.
Thank you.
Geez, don't mention it.
You must feel down being
apart from Jae Hee.
- Gosh...
- Oh, no.
Gosh, it's all wrinkled.
But it's clean.
Thank you.
- Wipe your tears.
- Okay.
After having lived some years,
you realize a person's depth
when facing a hard time.
Someone you thought was strong
turns out that he's as flimsy as paper.
And someone who
seemed weak and fragile
turns out he's dependable and strong.
Chae Woon, you're deep and strong.
I'm sure you'll overcome this just fine.
Holding onto Jae Hee's hands tightly.
That's how Jae Hee will
overcome this as well.
Yes, I'll do that, Father.
Thank you. Thanks.
Do Hyun.
The company that intercepted your
contract is CEO Kim's subsidiary?
Oh, my gosh.
Then it really is Seo Ah?
My goodness.
You must be so upset over what
happened to Jae Hee oppa.
I contacted everyone and
tried to do something.
I'm sorry I couldn't be of any help.
Seo Ah...
Yes?
By chance...
was it you?
What do you mean?
I mean, did you...
get angry at Jae Hee and
took it out on him?
I asked Chief Yoo, Jae Hee's partner.
The company that intercepted
the contract is your subsidiary.
No, Mother.
That's a coincidence.
Even if they're our subsidiary company,
there's no way for me to know
everything they do.
I'm sad that you're
suspicious of me, Mother.
No, I'm not saying this
to make you sad.
You know, I'm straight forward.
No matter how much I think about it,
you're the most suspicious person.
- Really, it's not you?
- Mother!
Oh, my. Seo Ah.
Did you just yell at me?
If you want to figure out
who is in the wrong,
it's totally Bit Chae Woon's fault.
What about Bit Chae Woon?
Do you know who caused all this trouble
for Jae Hee oppa's project?
It's Park Pil Hong.
It's Bit Chae Woon's birth father.
Oh, my. Why bring up
Park Pil Hong now?
How could that moron ruin
Jae Hee's project?
From what I hear,
Park Pil Hong has been trying to
hit it big using Bit Chae Woon.
He's been circling Bit Chae Woon.
And when a competitor
offered him money,
he jumped for it and ruined
Jae Hee's contract.
My gosh.
He did that knowing that Jae Hee is
his daughter's boyfriend?
He'll do...
anything for money,
whether it's his daughter or not.
That ahjussi still lives like that?
Then...
that man back then was...
Oh, my gosh!
Oh, my.
Ever since then, he's been...
Oh, my goodness.
- My gosh.
- On top of that,
he found out that Bit Chae Woon's
fiancé's family is wealthy,
and he's very happy about it.
Because there's plenty for
him to rip off.
Rip us off?
Oh, my gosh!
What do I do...
Oh, my gosh.
Hello, Mother.
Hi, Bit Chae Woon.
I just came back from meeting Father.
Woo Jung Hoo? Why...
I guess...
he was worried about a lot of things.
Oh, it must be about Jae Hee.
He was never like that before.
Would you like some tea?
No, no.
I have a doctor's appointment
today. Next time.
Then I'll walk you out.
No, no. That's too burdensome for me.
Get back to work. I'll go.
Bit Chae Woon, you know...
Nothing. Good day.
Yes, be careful, Mother.
Gosh, I totally forgot about that.
That Bit Chae Woon has
a troublemaker birth father.
If my Jae Hee marries her, he'll suffer.
He'll have a troublemaker
father-in-law and two mothers-in-law.
Park Pil Hong.
Thanks to Woo Jae Hee's testimony,
we'll let you go with lack of evidence.
But remember we'll be watching you.
Geez.
I feel bad for Mr. Woo.
Geez, it's one thing to be sorry.
The customer is not
answering the phone.
You'll be connected to
the voicemail after the beep.
That's right.
Chairwoman Choon Suk
feels ashamed, too.
She can't answer my call.
Then I'll have to counterattack.
What now?
Seo Ah asked you for
a favor about this, right?
To ruin Jae Hee and Seo Yeon, right?
Please tell me honestly.
Tell you honestly about what?
The subsidiary company must've
done it to take the contract.
Are you sure?
I'm sure.
I know nothing about it.
You're going to insist on it then.
What's this then?
Mother-in-law, you're too much.
Why won't you tell me
where Seo Yeon is?
I'm Seo Yeon's dad.
Watching you ruin my daughter's life...
I can't stand it anymore.
I'll give you the money
you love so much.
Take it and leave.
I'll tell Jung Won that Seo Yeon died.
After Seo Yeon's funeral, get lost
to somewhere far away.
Got that?
Park Pil Hong, that jerk!
So...
he sent this to you?
Step down.
What?
Step down?
Step down from
the chairwoman position
and go back to the States.
Kim Jung Won.
Are you saying you'll push me out?
I helped you in every way I can for
you to get to your position.
You didn't help me exactly.
Because of your greed,
I overcame several crises thus far.
You abandoned Seo Yeon
without my knowledge,
and you acted as if you had no idea.
You even blackmailed Soon Jung,
who raised my daughter.
Chairwoman Lee Choon Suk.
I can't tolerate you any longer.
Please step down.
What?
Hey. You...
Rather than getting dismissed in
a shareholders' meeting,
I think it would look better...
if you step down on your own.
What?
What did you say?
Hey!
I said to keep the meeting short.
Why do they talk so much? Geez.
You and I must have a deep tie.
We keep running into
each other wherever we go.
I know.
Isn't this amazing?
Seriously.
Ms. Jung Min Jae.
Yes.
All right then.
Have a nice session, Noonim.
Okay.
What? What the?
Woo Jung Hoo, why are you hiding?
Why isn't that guy leaving?
Oh, my. You didn't leave, Professor?
Yes.
By chance, did you wait for me?
I felt so lonely going home
after my therapy sessions.
It looked like you came alone, too.
Thank you.
After my wife passed away,
I struggled with depression.
But I'm much better now.
But I come in every
six months for a session.
And I bump into you here, Noonim.
So we ran into each other like this
when you come in every six months?
That's why I said we have a deep tie.
When I first met my wife,
we kept bumping into
each other by accident.
That's right.
If you're meant to be, you keep
running into each other.
- Ow!
- Ouch!
What? Jung Min Jae?
Why do you keep following me around?
I'm not following you, Oppa.
Yuck! I keep bumping into
you wherever I go!
Wait...
- Geez, so cold.
- Hey, you're here.
Hey, I heard you're struggling.
Let's talk.
Hey, there are tea, coffee,
even cup ramens.
Yet you give me water?
Hey, Jae Hee.
I'm really sorry.
It's Seo Ah, and my grandma's doing.
Did you hear that?
I pretty much heard it.
Are you having problems with
Chae Woon because of that?
No, it's not like that.
Did Chae Woon say that?
No, no.
No, it's just me. That's just how I felt.
Is Chae Woon doing okay?
I'm not sure if you'd say
that she's doing well.
She's so worried about you, man.
I think she's putting all her
worrying energy into her work.
When I see her at work,
gosh, she's working
endlessly without a break.
I asked her to come here with me.
But she said no, saying she's busy.
That's when I felt that something is
going on with you and Chae Woon.
What happened? Just tell me.
It's not like that.
We don't want to show
our struggles to each other.
"We don't want to show our
struggles to each other."
Is that how you say that?
Whoa, I guess my friend
really is in love.
Hey, man. You two should be together,
especially at times like this.
Anyway, you two are so tough.
- Hey, Joon Ah.
- What?
How are Seo Ah and
Hwang Na Ro doing?
Hey, that's right. I came to
ask you about Hwang Na Ro.
What's up with that guy Hwang Na Ro?
He's stuck to Seo Ah. It looks like
they're about to get married.
I get so nervous watching
them together.
Really?
You can't let them get close.
Hwang Na Ro, that guy wants
to become successful.
He's doing that by sticking
to the CEO and Seo Ah.
Hwang Na Ro is involved
in losing my contract.
Really?
Right? I have a bad feeling
about that guy.
Hey, whatever.
Let's talk about that later.
Do you remember
Beom Jin from high school?
Do you stay in touch with him?
- Beom Jin?
- Yeah.
No, why?
Just because.
Can't I just ask?
You don't stay in touch?
I don't.
I have to go. I have lots of work to do.
I'll leave for now. I'll call you.
Good night. Come again.
You said you're smart.
Why do you act as if
you have amnesia
whenever I bring up
my friend Beom Jin?
I begged you.
I pleaded with you, asking you to
help my friend Beom Jin's family.
You ignored me.
And then Beom Jin's
father passed away.
That Jae Hee,
he has no idea how I feel.
Should I have told him the truth?
Gosh, no, no.
Why bother with excuses now?
Ms. Lee.
Mr. Woo.
Did you go somewhere?
Yes.
To see Hwak Se.
Where is Hwak Se right now?
He didn't even tell me and left.
He's working at a friend's cafe.
Actually...
I found out that Hwak Se
and Man Jung are dating.
Oh, I see.
By chance, did you know?
Actually...
Hwak Se was so worried about that.
He felt so bad for you.
I see.
Hwak Se... He's so kind
and soft-hearted.
I went to see him and
said some harsh words.
I feel so uneasy about it, though.
Gosh, Hwak Se must be so hurt.
Why?
You might feel uneasy, but
not Hwak Se.
Because he found out how
much you care for him now.
The way I see it...
I think you're the soft-hearted one.
Me?
Gosh. Oh, no.
After living through tough times,
I'm so glad to know that
you're still so graceful.
Since you see me in
such a positive light,
it comforts me.
Woo Jung Hoo must be so miffed.
He didn't even come to therapy.
We're friends. So I should apologize.
- See?
- Oh, yes.
I think it'd be nice if you're nice to her.
My goodness.
That's right.
They may not be lovers,
but they could be good friends.
Good friends who connect.
Hwak Se or Man Jung...
They're in love with each other.
What can you do?
A true friend helps another
friend smile like that.
- What is it?
- Oh, no.
Woo Jung Hoo's smile.
It's still the same.
He only smiles at Soon Jung.
This could be a workout. If you do this...
you could exercise your elbows.
Is your heater still broken
at your officetel?
Yeah, it's still broken.
Then how about you move into
Samgwang Villa for a while?
I'll ask my mom.
But that could be impolite.
Well, forget it if you don't want to.
I didn't say I didn't want to.
I'll think about it positively.
Yeah, right.
Before I move in, I have to tell her
CEO Kim Jung Won is my mom.
- Wait, Director Lee.
- Huh?
I meant to tell you this.
My mom is actually...
Yeah, you said your mom runs
a clothing store, right?
Yeah, it is a clothing store. Right.
Where are you going?
- To the restroom.
- What?
I'm trying to talk to you.
Why go to the restroom now?
I know. I want to go all of a sudden.
I have to tell you something.
Hurry back.
What the heck?
Why isn't this opening?
It must be broken.
It's stuck again?
That door was stuck earlier,
and I had a hard time.
- Do it like this.
- What do I do?
It's not opening.
It locks by itself.
People are confused about this.
- You have to use force.
- What?
How can you pull it out?
I said you can't use force
for stuff like this.
- I said that.
- How did you pull it out?
It just came off.
Put it back.
Look at this...
- Director Lee.
- Yes?
Well...
I think...
I think I... you.
What did you say?
Come again? What did you say?
I like you, Director Lee.
Don't you like me, too?
Well...
I don't. Who says?
You don't?
You really don't? I thought...
All this time, I thought
you liked me, too.
Geez, well...
Well...
Are you crying?
Are you really crying?
How can you cry over this?
I like you, too. Why are you crying?
I'm not crying.
What did you just say?
Huh?
I never said such a thing.
What?
- I never said such a thing.
- What? Didn't you say you like me?
I never said that.
I like you a lot, Director Lee.
♫  Now we are going to like each other  ♫
Why are you closing your eyes?
Why do you close your eyes?
To do what?
Geez.
♫  When the time that has been
passed comes back  ♫
♫  Now we are going to...  ♫
Seo Ah.
I thought you'd need some
food and some things.
I was about to order something.
No. I wanted to choose them myself.
- This and...
- Whoa.
Isn't it pretty?
Thanks.
This really makes me feel at home.
At home?
At home.
I've never done stuff like this.
Me, neither.
Housekeepers always did this for me.
But it's fun to do stuff like this.
When I see that,
you and I have some common grounds.
Although we grew up in
entirely different environments.
I parked it on level two of
underground parking.
Ride it.
Is it okay for me to accept this?
Just accept it.
I have something to give you as well.
What does this mean?
It means I love you, Seo Ah.
I'm sorry, it's not a nice ring.
I love you, Seo Ah.
Really?
Do you really love me?
Don't feel anxious anymore.
And don't be lonely, either.
As Seo Ah's mother,
I will not accept you, Hwang Na Ro.
Mother, you're home.
You're late, Unni.
Are you busy?
Yeah. I have a conference.
Why?
Just because.
Unni, I might move to Cheonju.
I got an offer from a general hospital.
I've waited for their offer,
and I'll move if the terms are good.
Sure.
If the terms are good.
You'll never call me, huh?
He read all my texts,
and he's ignoring me.
If I ever date another man,
I'm a moron.
See if I do.
I'll never date another man.
Ever again.
I shouldn't be waiting for him
like this at my age.
- Never in my life...
- Auntie?
Who are you talking to?
What? I wasn't talking.
You were talking like this.
No. Aren't you hungry?
Do you want to eat ramen?
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
Hey, let's make some spicy ramen.
With some dumplings.
Mix it up. How about it?
Doesn't it sound good? Huh?
Here you go. Enjoy.
- Thank you.
- Have a good time.
- Very, very... Yes!
- Excuse me.
Give us menus and...
- another bottle of beer.
- All right.
Thank you.
♫  Very, very  ♫
♫  How was your day today?  ♫
♫  I really thought I'd be okay  ♫
♫  Even when I'm with my friends
and rely on my drinks  ♫
♫  I keep thinking of you  ♫
Woo Jae Hee.
Why are you struggling like this
being apart from Bit Chae Woon?
♫  Wherever you may be  ♫
I'm doing it for Chae Woon.
If Chae Woon is by my side,
she'll struggle because of me.
It's right that we stay apart like this.
♫  Could it be you?  ♫
♫  Would it really be okay
even if I think of you?  ♫
Hey, Chief Yoo.
♫  Am I the only one holding on?  ♫
That's what I'm willing to do.
♫  I couldn't tell you this  ♫
But why do I miss her so much?
Geez...
I miss her so much.
♫  Is it a goodbye?  ♫
Geez, seriously.
Geez...
What were you doing there
together for so long?
Anyway, he's so nosy.
♫  Did you forget?
Did you forget about me?  ♫
Are you jealous?
You're jealous. Jealous.
You're mine, though.
♫  My heart is opening arms to you  ♫
♫  I'm barely going through today  ♫
♫  When the memories are fading  ♫
♫  I stand on the street where
we walked together  ♫
♫  I'm trying to erase it again and again  ♫
♫  But I can still hear you
breathing on my ear  ♫
♫  Did you forget?
Did you forget about me?   ♫
♫  I'm still waiting for you  ♫
Jae Hee, are you doing well?
I'm very busy and working so hard.
I'm working hard so I won't have
a minute to think about you.
♫  I'm trying to erase it again and again  ♫
I'm extremely busy.
I'm busy without a minute to breathe.
All right.
Even though I'm so busy,
I miss you from time to time, Jae Hee.
I miss you.
♫  I'm trying to erase it again and again  ♫
Over there.
Let's go.
♫  I'm trying to erase it again and again  ♫
♫  But I keep thinking of your face  ♫
Here you go.
Did you do all this last night?
Yes.
Bit Chae Woon, aren't you
working too hard lately?
You might get sick at that rate.
No, I'm perfectly fine.
You did a good job.
We can use this for
the design team report.
Thank you.
I'll go to the branches then.
- Okay. Good day.
- Okay.
Jae Hee.
Jae Hee!
♫  I say my goodbyes to you every night  ♫
♫  I erased you from
my drunkenness last night  ♫
♫  The way you spoke and
the way you looked at me  ♫
♫  No matter how much I erase you,
I keep remembering you  ♫
♫  I got emotional late at night  ♫
♫  I stepped outside the house
in a few days  ♫
Where did you go?
You left your things with us.
Oh, my. Joon Ah,
what are you doing here?
Mom...
Mom?
Son Ba Wi, let's play at your house.
Your house is empty.
My mom is home.
- Ba Wi, what's going on?
- Mom!
Are you Ba Wi's mom?
Dad, ahjumma was my mom for the day.
Put anything fishy on Hwang Na Ro.
Grandma, how could you say that?
Let's just get married.
I want to live with you soon, Seo Ah.
What's going on with Chae Woon?
She fainted?
Seo Yeon?
CEO, the executives are all
gathered in the conference room.
Hwak Se is going to be on
a radio singing contest today.
I'd like to dedicate this song
to Lee Man Jung.
♫  My memory is...  ♫