Go home with me.
My baby...
Let's go home.
Go home with me.
- CEO!
- Young Lady!
CEO...
Oh, my!
Aigoo, come.
Unni! The umbrella.
Gosh, it's pouring.
Why are you getting wet?
Let's go inside.
You're all wet...
No, I should go.
I'm sorry for showing up
all of a sudden.
Bit Chae Woon...
I just thought of you out of the blue.
Young Lady.
Chae Woon...
Wait, I'll drive you home.
I have my car over there.
Oh, okay...
Here.
Thanks.
Don't get wet, Mom.
Unni, the umbrella.
- Mom, you'll catch a cold. Come.
- Yeah, go in.
- Go in, Mom.
- Let's go inside.
- Mom.
- Mom, let's go in.
Where is your car?
I'll call a taxi.
- Mom.
- Hae Deun!
Let her be.
Come here.
Leave your mom alone.
CEO was a bit strange, huh?
Did she have a drink?
I guess she missed her daughter.
Even though she knows
she shouldn't...
her feet automatically...
lead her this way.
Whoa, psychological analysis.
Gosh, it got cold.
CEO...
must want to take
Chae Woon noona home.
Right, Auntie? Right, Noona?
Is that something she can do
just because she wants to?
Unni told us she'd never go.
What do you think you
would've done?
She'd go right away.
Auntie!
That's not true.
Hae Deun wouldn't leave
because of me.
Let's go...
Go home with me.
My baby...
Yes...
I should let her go.
No matter Chae Woon
says she won't go...
I should let her go even
if she says no.
I should let my Chae Woon go...
I should let Chae Woon go...
Do you have any illnesses?
No, I don't.
I'm sorry about last time.
I was too rude.
No.
I'll hold it.
I'm sorry...
for showing up suddenly.
♫  I wish it'd be like that now  ♫
♫  Heal your draining heart
sitting in the shade  ♫
♫  The precious things are
right next to you  ♫
♫  I wish you'd say so to the one
who is about to leave  ♫
Aigoo...
Dummy.
♫  I knew I'd be back  ♫
♫  This familiar place,
a place I can rest  ♫
Dummy!
Didn't you know how stupid I am?
♫  A place I can sleep comfortably  ♫
♫  Overcoming those days
when I wanted to hide  ♫
♫  How did you feel then?  ♫
♫  I want to fly high and
embrace the stars  ♫
Aigoo, my unni...
♫  Did I forget everything
that is precious?  ♫
♫  I wish it'd be like that now  ♫
♫  Heal your draining heart
sitting in the shade  ♫
♫  The precious things are
right next to you  ♫
♫  I wish you'd say so to the one
who is about to leave  ♫
♫  I wish it'd be like that now  ♫
♫  Heal your draining heart
sitting in the shade  ♫
♫  The precious things are
right next to you  ♫
♫  I wish you'd say so to the one
who is about to leave  ♫
Geez, anyway...
James and Jae Hee are late.
What did they say earlier
when they called?
He said that James ahjussi
would go to his therapy
and take a drive.
I'll call him again.
Anyway, Jae Hee is...
so good to S-jussi.
It doesn't suit him.
What's "S-jussi"?
Jame ahjussi. I'll just call him
S-jussi from now on.
Then for Hwak Se ahjussi,
you're Se-jussi.
No, I'm not.
I'm Hwak-ppa.
Hwak Se oppa!
- Yeah, I'm an oppa.
- The customer is not...
answering the phone.
Jae Hee hyung isn't answering.
Really?
How come Na Ro oppa
isn't home yet?
He said he was closeby.
I know.
He said he was closeby,
so put some cheese on his.
The cheese must be
hardened by now.
Geez.
A**hole.
You're pretty gutsy.
Going deep into the fish tank.
That's my charm. You know that.
Right.
It's your charm.
But this is wrong.
How dare you barge into my territory
and coiled up like a snake?
That's not it, Hyungnim.
I happened to find a room to rent...
and it turned out that way.
This is your plan.
Move into Samgwang Villa
and my daughter Seo Yeon...
No, it's Bit Chae Woon now.
You want to entice her
since you look all right.
And you'll become Kim Jung Won's
son-in-law, ta-da.
You want to make that entrance
and live a good life. Right?
Geez, all he has left is
his quick wit.
Punk, how dare you want
to be my son-in-law?
Son-in-law?
Ouch...
Did anyone say they'd acknowledge
you as Bit Chae Woon's father?
Do you think CEO Kim Jung Won
will sit back, Hyungnim?
I guess you don't get it since
you've been put away for so long.
The situation isn't
like that right now.
In any case.
Get lost within the next 24 hours.
If you don't pack up and move out
of Samgwang Villa tomorrow,
I'll just...
Today, I just tickled you a little bit.
Just know that.
Mom.
Did she go home okay?
Yeah.
I grabbed a taxi for her.
You did well.
CEO...
must've missed you a lot.
Mom.
I'm sorry for throwing a fit earlier.
Are you sorry?
Aigoo, you're all wet.
But...
don't iron all those things again.
I get so scared that
you might tell me to go.
I won't.
Go wash up and go to bed.
Okay. Rest.
Mom...
do you know an ahjumma
named Byun Mi Ja?
Byun Mi Ja?
Who is that?
Yeah...
She's the sister of one of the
engineers I work with at the site.
She said she used to
be your neighbor.
So I was wondering if you knew her.
Get some rest.
Okay. Go rest.
Byun Mi Ja?
She said they were close.
Mom doesn't know her?
Hey, you're driving me crazy.
Sit down.
I can't sit still.
- Unni!
- Noona.
Why?
Is something wrong?
No.
I thought you'd just
leave with the CEO.
Hey. Like this?
In my slippers?
No, when I saw you follow the CEO...
I felt like you were leaving
for good like that.
Hey.
Idiots.
I told you that I'd never leave.
But still...
since she's your birth mom...
We don't know how that feels.
If she's your birth mom,
wouldn't it feel like
being pulled by a magnet,
and shouldn't you leave?
Aigoo, aigoo!
Hey. What do you mean
you don't know?
My mom is right over there.
When Mom goes somewhere,
do you guys feel like
going like magnets?
Why overreact?
Ra Hoon, go upstairs.
Goodnight.
Clean up your things.
Okay.
What's with you, Lee Ra Hoon?
Don't disappear, Chae Woon noona.
Go.
I'm going.
- Wash your feet!
- Okay.
Let's clean up.
Unni, don't go anywhere.
Hey, just finished up cleaning.
These clothes are all yours.
Thanks.
Mom.
Where did you go?
Mr. Kim said he dropped
you off somewhere.
I couldn't reach you.
Where did you get
rained on like this?
What happened?
You'll catch a cold.
Start a bath for me.
Yes, CEO.
Mom.
Did you go and meet
Bit Chae Woon?
Did you?
Seo Ah.
Yes?
Who is Lee Bit Chae Woon?
Who is it?
It's her.
Lee Bit Chae Woon...
It's her, Mom.
The girl who bullied me in middle
school and quit school.
It's her.
I thought you'd leave.
I thought you'd leave since
you're not my real mom.
No.
Mom.
Should I ask Dr. Lee to come over?
I think you have a fever.
What do I do...
No, I'm okay.
I want to be alone.
Mom...
- I'll do it.
- Over here.
Gosh.
Bit Chae Woon...
She's taking everyone from me.
She's...
taking everyone from me.
Red...
All right. Let me see...
Oppa, when are you
coming back to Korea?
I miss you so much.
Gosh, Seo Ah. Why does
she keep doing this?
Are things not working
out with Woo Jae Hee?
Then she should just give up.
Aigoo, seriously.
Whatever.
Hello?
What, hello?
You were waiting for my call, huh?
I wasn't.
Geez.
You were staring at my number,
and you were wondering
if you should call or not.
Where are you right now?
I'm out with James to
get some fresh air.
It was cold and rainy today.
Get fresh air?
Well, so...
The oldest daughter?
I'll talk to you at home.
Bye.
Wait...
What the heck?
So...
are you feeling better?
Yeah.
Maybe it's the good IV.
I feel better now.
Do you know how scared I was?
I'm sorry, Yoo Jae Hee.
It's okay.
Actually, it was my fault.
- Hang tight.
- What?
Sorry, Mom!
That ahjussi I saw when
I went there with Seo Ah...
That was Jae Hee's dad.
Our competitors are developing
many products these days.
Mom, what? It's raining.
Woo Jae Hee, this guy...
Just because I'm
seeing a therapist,
he's hiding something
from me. I'm sure.
If I pester him,
he'll be busy trying to
sneak out of it.
That slippery Woo Jae Hee.
But you're still my son, man.
You got that, punk?
What could it be?
This uneasy feeling.
Me, too.
I feel very uneasy about something.
It's cold. Button up.
♫  It's a slap, slap, slap  ♫
♫  No, you're the one  ♫
Geez...
Why aren't Jae Hee and
James home yet?
Geez...
Hey!
I'm not scared.
Koala...
Why isn't he home yet?
Gosh.
This makes me look bad.
Na Ro.
What happened?
I ran into a friend on my way home,
and we went to ride bikes.
I fell.
You should go to the hospital.
It's okay.
Goodnight, Bit Chae Woon.
Gosh.
Ow...
Yes.
I brought some medicine.
Thanks.
I'll get it.
Sit down over here.
Ow...
This isn't from falling.
You got beat up.
Did you get into a fight?
No.
Give me your hand.
I'll do it.
You can't move that hand.
I'll just do this hand.
Let me see.
I didn't touch yet.
I see...
Sorry.
Yoo Jae Hee.
You went through a lot
today because of me.
Yes, I sure did.
Come on.
Ouch, be gentle. Be gentle.
- I'm being gentle.
- What are you doing?
What are you two doing?
So close together!
Cunning Penguin.
Aigoo.
He got hurt. See, there's
the emergency kit.
I'm treating him.
Cunning Penguin,
how did this happen?
I fell. I'm okay.
Fall? Right...
You got beat up somewhere.
Right?
It looks that way, huh?
Did you take medicine?
No. I'll be fine if I put this on.
I got some medicine today.
- I'll share it with you.
- Geez.
You can't share medicine like that.
You have different symptoms.
I see.
What medicine?
Were you at a hospital?
Are you very ill?
Well...
He's such a party-pooper.
You're really okay, right?
Yes.
I feel better thanks to
expensive medicine.
Thanks, Yoo Jae Hee.
What's wrong?
You'll be fine.
You should be fine since you took
expensive medicine at the ER.
Geez, I feel like...
someone said I got
expensive medicine.
Go to sleep.
Are you going out?
I'm going to work out.
Nah.
For real. I exercise at night.
Goodnight.
Nah...
It's true.
No way...
♫  Now we are going to
like each other  ♫
Moong!
♫  Now we are going
to like each other  ♫
My goodness...
Gosh, you should be careful.
Do you like me that much?
What are you saying?
I can't see well in the dark.
You should've just dropped
off the medicine.
Why were you with him
for so long in there?
Anyway, you're so nosy.
Are you jealous?
What jealousy?
You are.
I think so.
You're mine.
♫  Even those precious
days might pass  ♫
Finally, it's our alone time.
I had quite a day today.
Me, too.
Did something happen?
How about you, Koala?
Is James doing okay?
He got scared a bit.
I hope James gets
his memory back.
I feel sorry for him.
Well, actually...
- James is...
- Oh.
When I skipped out on work that day,
I ran into your mother.
At a batting cage.
Your feet apart, stick out
your butt like this.
Hold the bat like this.
Put 1,000 won in there.
Ah, okay.
- Really?
- Yeah.
How did you know she was my mom?
Oh, at the work event last time...
Seo Ah told me.
Oh, I see.
But your mom is so cool.
It was like this back then.
She was teaching me
standing like this.
She had such a cool pose.
She swung like this.
She was powerful, too.
Bang! Her swing was awesome.
Her strength was... bang!
She's so strong.
When I see you,
your actions are so grand.
So over the top.
Now that I see you,
you look like my mom.
How so?
I see.
My beauty?
Your strength.
She is strong.
♫  We will make a beautiful love  ♫
Did you have fun?
Yeah.
Isn't my mom pretty?
Yeah, she's really pretty.
But she couldn't hit the ball.
Really?
Get lost within the next 24 hours.
If you don't pack up and move out
of Samgwang Villa tomorrow,
I'll just...
Today, I just tickled you a little bit.
Just know that.
That's not enough?
- Ttak Bae.
- Yes.
Don't do this, Hyungnim.
I don't like to get beat up.
It hurts.
Hyungnim, if you keep doing this,
I'll spill everything.
What?
That you...
abandoned your daughter
a long time ago.
To get your hands on some fortune.
S***.
Do you think Seo Yeon
will believe that?
Do you think she'd believe you?
Why wouldn't she believe...
what her beloved boyfriend says?
Hyungnim.
You know, I...
like Bit Chae Woon
with pure intentions.
I'm different from you from ages ago.
Please bless our love.
I'll be good.
Bit Chae Woon.
Can't you just like me?
If you liked me,
even if you're not worth
a bundle of money,
I would've let it go.
Had I known this would happen,
maybe I should've been her friend.
Don't come close!
This is real! My cross!
My cross!
What do I do?
He always wakes up when
I need to go to the bathroom.
What's this?
A ghost! Here is my cross!
- With my cross...
- What are you doing?
- What?
- What, what the heck?
Oh, my! Oh, my gosh!
- You're crazy.
- The ghost...
- You're crazy!
- It's because of the ghost.
- Hey, how dare you!
- No!
You!
Manager, let me apply for
this trainee position in France.
Please give me one last chance.
Please?
It's not as easy as you think.
You have to go to France
and get trained for
two years. It's tough.
It doesn't mean you'll
make it in the end.
It's okay even if I don't make it.
Just one last chance, please.
I really worked hard all this time.
Let me discuss it with the CEO.
Thank you!
Live or die, Lee Hae Deun.
This is your last challenge.
50,000 won!
You said you'd send me 50,000 won.
I still haven't received it.
Did I say that?
I forgot.
Give it to me now.
Sure, okay.
Let me see.
I don't have any cash.
I said to send it to me here.
I don't do any phone banking
or internet banking.
Whoa, then did you mean
you'd send it from the bank?
Yes. That's right.
Let me make a suggestion.
If you sit for 50 minutes again today,
I'll add 50,000 won. I'll give you
a total of 100,000 won. Okay?
You look like you're very angry.
All right. 130,000.
120,000 won.
Deal.
Let's go.
Mr. Makjang... no...
Mr. Mark Jang.
Your contract happens to
be up with our academy.
Let's part ways now.
The end. Okay?
Bye.
Wait...
How about my 50,000 won?
- Let's go to the bank together.
- Wait!
Wait. Ouch.
Ow, my elbow. My arm broke.
- My arm...
- You don't have money.
Thank you. I'll be back again.
I'll stay in touch.
I didn't suggest that
you sell your shoes.
Don't blame me.
Why would I blame you?
I was getting tired of
that design anyway.
But still, I know this place well.
She gave you a good price.
- Really? I'm so grateful.
- Gosh.
Give me my money.
My money.
What? Money?
I should pay you.
One, two, three...
Five. Here.
Four.
Four. Yup.
You don't fall for it.
All done. Have a good day.
What good day? Hey.
What's your name?
Gosh, they all do this.
Why?
I'm afraid you'd sign up
for my class in the future.
They can't seem to forget me,
so they google me and
come looking for me.
No worries. I know your name.
I'll be sure to avoid you.
- Mr. Makjang.
- What?
Not makjang.
- It's Mark Jang.
- I know.
It's not daenjang,
gochujang, ssamjang...
it's Mr. Makjang. Bye.
Daenjang, gochujang, ssamjang?
Is she trying to be funny?
She's so funny. So funny.
Gosh, seriously.
Mom...
do you know an ahjumma
named Byun Mi Ja?
They must've grown up so nicely...
despite the fact that one
of them was stolen.
Mother.
Hi, Mr. Woo.
Gosh, for the construction
in Hwak Se's room?
Yes.
My gosh. You're working so hard
when you're busy already.
Let's have some snacks.
All right.
Give me one.
Thanks.
Byun Mi Ja?
Who's that?
The customer is not
answering the phone.
You won't answer, huh?
Ahjumma, I can't reach you.
I'd like to discuss something
important with you.
Please give me a call.
Look at her.
It's true. She is
Park Pil Hong's daughter.
Let's see how long you avoid me.
All right. Let's get back to work.
- Okay.
- Yes!
Let's go.
You didn't get one.
Thank you.
Let's do it.
I'm still working on
Hwak Se's room ceiling.
You miss me, huh?
Nope.
Mr. Woo.
- Aigoo.
- You worked hard.
- Aigoo...
- Drink it.
Thank you, Mother.
My gosh, Mr. Woo.
Did you just call me "mother"?
Yes.
Because you're my Moong-i's mother.
It makes me so happy to
hear you call me "mother."
In any case,
Na Ro refuses to eat lunch.
I wonder if he has bad flu.
Cunning Penguin didn't go to work?
Oh, Na Ro didn't go to work?
Yeah, I guess...
He won't open the door for me, either.
S***...
Geez!
How did you get in here?
How else? I got the key
from Mother and opened it.
So what? We're both men.
I heard you didn't eat breakfast.
I'm not interested.
What's going on?
You should tell us,
so we can help you or not.
Geez, mind your business.
Oh-ho?
Did you come into my room before?
It's my first time.
This is all my first time.
I came in worried,
yet you're suspicious of me.
Here.
Eat.
So, are you two dating?
Are you dating Bit Chae Woon?
Can't you feel it already?
Why pretend not to know
when you're so quick?
How about Jang Seo Ah?
Nothing is going on
with Jang Seo Ah?
You're testing me, too?
No.
Nothing is going on with Seo Ah.
I'm sure you feel it, too.
Accept it, Cunning Penguin.
Accept it and...
let's be friends. Okay?
I don't want to.
Geez, Hwang Na Ro...
Hey.
You don't have any friends, right?
Even if you did,
you only know people who ignore you
when you're down and out, right?
What good is your bed?
You sleep like this
on the floor so pathetically.
Aigoo, poor penguin.
Eat a lot. Don't be picky.
And...
here is your dessert.
I have to go on a diet.
You have it.
Geez.
- Hae Deun, you're home early.
- Hello.
I'm leaving again. I got some money,
so I bought clothes. I wanted to try it on.
Oh, really?
Didn't Na Ro oppa go to work?
He has the flu.
I see.
You know...
I saw something strange.
- Something strange?
- Yeah.
Was it you, Lee Hae Deun?
You were in my room?
What, Noonim?
Bit Chae Woon?
Yeah.
She keeps calling me...
and texted me to meet her.
You told me to give her
my phone number, so I did.
Maybe I shouldn't have.
You did fine.
Ignore her calls and
drag it out for now.
Your job is to delay Bit Chae Woon
from moving into her
birth mom's house.
Got that?
I got it.
Hwang Na Ro is struggling big time.
Please shake up Bit Chae Woon.
What?
Am I making it sound too difficult?
Seduce Bit Chae Woon.
From what I see,
I think you're interested in her.
Be more aggressive and pursue her.
Well?
Longer Bit Chae Woon can delay
her move into her birth mom's house,
it'd benefit Jang Seo Ah.
Hwang Na Ro.
I just got this information.
Chairwoman Lee Choon Seok
is in Korea.
Kim Jung Won and
Jang Seo Ah don't know yet.
Grandma Lee Choon Seok...
I heard she adores Jang Seo Ah.
Of course.
Okay.
Nice.
The customer is not
answering the phone.
You'll be connected to the voicemail.
Why don't you answer
my calls, Mom?
I think you're avoiding
my calls on purpose.
Please call me.
Back then...
why did you lie to me?
Saying that my Seo Yeon died.
If you keep avoiding my calls,
I'll come to you.
I know you're in Korea.
Please call me.
Hi, Min Jae.
Jung Won.
I said you didn't have to come.
Why did you come?
You never answered my calls.
No matter how busy you are,
you always call me back.
Yet I heard nothing from you.
How can I not worry?
Why do you look so bad?
Are you sick? Is something wrong?
No, I'm just busy with work.
By chance...
did Seo Yeon's dad come out?
Who cares whether he's out or not?
It has nothing to do with me.
Then what is it?
Gosh, why is everyone
doing this to me?
You're all busy hiding things.
To be honest...
I want to open up
everything to you, Min Jae.
What is it?
What's wrong with your mom?
I can't tell you just yet...
There really is something.
If you say it's still a secret...
I can't help it.
Mother.
- Jae Hee has a girlfriend?
- Yes.
How can he do that to me?
But you know...
you two...
weren't really together officially.
Isn't it up to Jae Hee to
decide whom he'll like?
Seo Ah.
When it comes to these things,
you need someone to set things
straight for you even though it hurts.
When it comes to a man and a woman
relationship, no means no.
You may be sad if you think
of me as Jae Hee's mom.
But think of me as
a sunbae in life.
Then I'm right.
But...
who's Jae Hee's girlfriend?
Mother.
You know Soon Jung ahjumma?
Yeah, of course, I do.
It's her daughter.
He's dating that ahjumma's daughter.
What?
Jae Hee oppa lives in
Soon Jung ahjumma's villa.
I think they got close while living there.
Is that the case?
Jae Hee, this punk...
He didn't tell me anything even though
he was living in Soon Jung's house.
On top of that,
Soon Jung's daughter...
This neighborhood is weird.
There's something here.
Mom said not to tell her.
I couldn't help it.
Jae Hee oppa does
whatever his mom says.
It's better that Mother knows.
Young lady.
You didn't eat lunch yet, right?
Eat some jokbal.
Isn't Uncle Hwak Se here?
He went to an interview for his gig.
Hwak Se is a singer.
I see.
Sit here and wait.
I'll bring it out real quick.
Excuse me.
Yes?
You're a girl.
Do you know where
Samgwang Villa is around here?
Well...
Why?
I'm looking for someone.
Looking for someone?
By chance...
James ahjussi's debt collector?
But...
why do you ask why when
I'm asking for directions?
Go over that way.
Thanks.
Did you wait long?
- Aigoo.
- Why?
Why, why?
Why, why, why?
Why? What's going on?
An ahjumma was looking
for Samgwang Villa just now.
She said she's looking
for someone.
But you said you're running
away from debt collectors.
For now, I told her
the wrong direction.
Hide in here.
Thanks.
Where is Samgwang Villa?
Oh, my!
- Hello.
- Hi!
I'm so glad to run into you here.
Yes, me, too.
What brings you here?
I'm here to meet my son.
You're... well...
your name is?
I'm Lee Bit Chae Woon.
Lee Bit Chae Woon?
Oh, my. What a pretty name.
I'm Jung Min Jae.
Yes.
What are you doing here,
Lee Bit Chae Woon?
Oh, I live around here.
I have to tell her Koala
lives in my house.
Then by chance, do you know
where Samgwang Villa is?
I asked a student over there,
but I think she told me wrong.
Oh, well...
actually, I also...
- Woo Jae Hee.
- Mom!
Mom, what are you doing here?
Hey.
I heard you're dating the daughter
of the villa you live in.
Did Seo Ah tell you?
Let me see her face.
- Let's go.
- Mom.
Hold on. So...
Let's go.
It was nice to see you.
Mom.
To tell you what's going on...
I'll introduce myself.
What?
Mom, I'll introduce you
to my girlfriend.
Lee Bit Chae Woon.
What?
Then you're Soon Jung's daughter?
Hwak Se.
Hi, Noonim.
How did your interview go?
Hwak Se.
It's okay.
For now...
heal your throat first.
And take your time. Okay?
Yes, Noonim.
- Noonim.
- Yeah?
I'm not down.
Aigoo.
Of course not.
- Hwak Se.
- Are you going to work?
- Yeah.
- Okay, go ahead.
- Okay.
- Yes.
Bye.
Long time no see, Lee Soon Jung.
Could we talk for a moment?
Well...
this is the house.
Gosh, I came empty-handed.
- I should buy something.
- Gosh, no.
Next time.
Let's go inside.
- Shall we?
- Yes.
Geez...
Yoo Jae Hee.
Go! Go!
Go back inside! Hurry!
Why?
Yoo Jae Hee.
Someone came looking
for me earlier...
Let's talk later. Go back inside.
- Why?
- My mom is here.
I'm afraid...
she'll find out about us acting
during the executives' meeting.
Then I'll go.
Go. Hurry up and go.
Geez, my heart.
Gosh, Noonim just left.
It would've been nice
for her to say hello.
I'll call my mom.
No, no.
You said she went to work.
I'll see her next time.
Okay.
Have some tea.
I want to see Jae Hee's room first.
Wait, what about my room?
You don't have to see my room.
It's really messy.
Don't you think I know
how messy you are?
Koa...
I'll take you up to Mr. Woo's room.
- Thanks.
- Wait...
Jae Hee, where is James hyung?
At the store...
James?
Yes.
James hyung...
He lives with us here.
He's very close to Jae Hee.
They share the room.
Why are they sharing a room?
Oh, he used to share my room...
but there's construction going on
in my room. So he's with Jae Hee.
They'll share only until
the construction is finished.
I see.
Geez, it's almost time for
Eems hyung to stop by here.
That hyung is so...
Yes, look around.
What?
I don't like you.
That stings.
Why?
Wait, wait, wait!
Wait a minute.
Let me clean up a little bit.
Why is he freaking out so much?
Okay. Yes.
Come in.
Oh, my.
Look at you sweating.
Aigoo, you're still so scatterbrained.
- Geez.
- You scared me.
My underwear.
Look at me.
It took me long enough to
visit my son's place.
Gosh, well...
It's all the same. Nothing to see here.
Let's go downstairs
and have some tea.
Hold on!
This smell...
is Woo Jung Hoo's odor.
What are you doing?
Prisoner Park Pil Hong was released.
Your request for a visit
has been canceled.
Park Pil Hong...
was released?
I don't know how to
express my gratitude.
Thank you, Soon Jung,
for raising Seo Yeon...
Oh, it's Bit Chae Woon now.
Bit Chae Woon is all grown up now.
Did you meet my Chae Woon?
Gosh, I'd be too ashamed.
I saw her from afar.
From afar.
♫  Riding on it...  ♫
By chance, you're not going to...
appear as Chae Woon's
father now, are you?
Why can't I?
Bit Chae Woon is my child.
How can you cut off blood ties?
Blood ties?
After doing that, how can you now...
say you're Chae Woon's father?
Do you think Young Lady
Jung Won will do nothing?
What...
did I do?
What?
Geez, I guess I got dumber these days.
I can't remember.
Don't ever come around
this neighborhood.
Don't come around Chae Woon, either.
If you...
hang around this neighborhood, I'll...
You'll...
What?
I'll kill you.
Lee Soon Jung, you got gutsy.
Soon Jung.
Do you think I'd sit back
until you do that?
Anyway, thanks.
For keeping Chae Woon close.
Right.
It's right for me to get
close to my daughter
and send her to Jung Won.
Aigoo.
It hurts, Ms. Soon Jung.
Do whatever you want.
I'm not scared of you at all now.
I'll never sit back, either.
Soon Jung.
Do you think I'd sit back
until you do that?
I have to protect my Chae Woon.
I have to protect Chae Woon.
I'll protect my Chae Woon.
I'll protect her.
Mom!
Chae Woon.
I thought you went to work.
- Go in.
- Huh?
Oh, yeah.
- Mom, earlier...
- Chae Woon.
Yeah?
You...
You, go.
What?
You...
go to your birth mom.
Mom, again?
If you don't go,
I'll turn myself in.
Turn yourself in?
What do you mean?
And say I was...
the kidnapper.
What did you say?
I...
I... I stoled you.
I stoled you.
Mom.
♫  You don't need to force love  ♫
♫  Like passing time,
you can't stop the heart  ♫
Woo Jung Hoo was there.
Then, my job is...
Mom!
Your dad has amnesia?
Mom, Mom, Mom!
To me, Bit Chae Woon and
you're both same daughters.
We're the same?
Do you really think so?
Chairwoman is here.
Did you really confirm
Seo Yeon's body?
Let's take a risk.
Hello.
What did you want to
discuss with me?
Ms. Byun Mi Ja?
Why are you so stunned?
Hwang Na Ro revealed everything.
She says she left her cellphone.
Chairwoman?
- Yes?
- Don't you get it?
What's the point of trying to
send Seo Yeon to our house now?
Park Pil Hong.
She's that scumbag's seed.
♫  The rain called you is
making me wet  ♫