Oh, no. My goodness. Seo Yeon.
Oh, no...
My gosh...
My goodness.
Seo Yeon.
Okay.
Oh, my!
Oh, no!
Aigoo.
Aigoo, my goodness.
She must've pulled
an all-nighter again.
Gosh.
My gosh.
Aigoo...
My gosh!
Yeobudong by 7 a.m.,
Samseongdong by 10 a.m.
At 11 a.m...
Why are there so many stops?
Escape.
For sure.
All right...
Smells nice.
Chae Woon will faint.
Mom, I'm leaving!
Oh, you have to eat breakfast.
- I have to go now.
- No! Chae Woon!
Hey, Bit Chae Woon!
I'm sorry, Mom! Love you!
Ms. Lee.
- Going to work already?
- Good morning, Uncle.
Did you have lots of customers?
I worked three gigs like
a medley all night long.
- We'll talk details tonight.
- Okay.
Oh, sorry.
- Uncle!
- Chae Woon!
Wait a minute.
Take a bite before you go.
It's beef radish soup.
It's your favorite.
- It's a killer.
- Right?
Wait, the meat.
Noonim, it's hot!
No, no, it's okay.
My hand is fine.
I'm off!
Wait, this, too.
Hot, hot!
Wait a minute. This, too.
You have to blow this into the air.
It's an important day for you.
- Okay.
- Wow, your lucky petal.
This is valuable.
Please let my Chae Woon
make it today.
I'm really late. I'm going.
Good luck today.
Fighting, my daughter!
You know what today is, right?
Come home early tonight!
Good luck with what, Noonim?
Today is the deadline
for the final submission.
Oh, that design competition?
She gets to go to Paris
if she wins?
Gosh, New York.
Not Paris.
New York! Not Paris.
♫  You can tell me why  ♫
♫  Oh, no, please don't tell me why  ♫
♫  I couldn't forget you  ♫
♫  In the warmth of your glance  ♫
♫  Those cruel eyes  ♫
♫  Your warm hands  ♫
Room 304.
Yes?
When will you pay for your room?
You're behind since last week.
Have I not paid you yet?
This won't work if you'll be this way.
I gave you a 20% discount
for a long-term stay.
I'm sorry. I'll pay you tonight.
My apologies.
How is it living in a motel?
Totally trying to get used to it.
Wow, you're so...
You put your house
into your business
- and you're living in a motel?
- Hey.
Our company is upward bound.
I should invest in it boldly.
When it's high time, I'll go for it.
Geez, go for it, man.
Good for you, man.
With that in mind,
let's work today as well.
- Okay!
- "Fighting" on the count of three.
One, two, three!
Geez, that guy...
Wait for me.
We have to finish all that
over there today, huh?
Sir!
You can't tear this down.
It's dangerous.
I'm following the blueprint.
What's wrong?
What in the world...
Where is the blueprint?
- Where is it?
- What's going on?
Hello.
I'm Lee, in charge of
the interior decoration.
He's trying to tear this down.
I was part of the plumbing job
here three years ago.
Hyungnim, let's rush.
We have to finish this today.
We took out the water pipes
from the second floor then
and buried along this wall and
connected them down to the drain.
No.
- Please wait.
- Look.
- Are you the interior designer?
- Yes.
- If you tear this down...
- Then...
Please wrap up the decoration
work on the second floor.
What a sloppy mess.
Come on!
Look here.
If you tear that down,
you'll flood this area.
The pipes are all connected
from the second floor
to the drains by the entrance.
- Mr. Yu!
- Huh?
Bring me the blueprint.
It's in your pocket.
Okay!
From what I'm hearing,
it sounds like you've picked up
a few things in the field.
Take a look.
This isn't right.
- What the heck? This isn't it.
- Ms. Lee.
This has been revised four times.
This is the latest version. Here.
Do you see that?
I see.
Right.
This is wrong.
Look at this.
We're in this area right here.
But it's not indicated in the blueprint.
This blueprint is off.
Well, did you study architecture?
Are you my hoobae?
You're my hoobae, and you're
trying to impress me...
I didn't attend university, and
I'm telling you based
on my experience.
I've worked in this field
for almost ten years.
Based on my experience...
Ms. Lee, I'm very angry
with your company.
The owner of this place
called various people
to collaborate and that upset me,
but I'm holding it in.
But seeing how the wall finish is...
I'm just so furious.
The previous person did that.
- I joined as of yesterday.
- In any case...
let's focus on our own tasks.
Don't throw a hissy fit and stick
your nose in my business.
A hissy fit?
I think you'll be throwing a hissy fit.
You strictly go by the book
and are so frustrating.
What did you say?
I clearly warned you.
I don't care if you regret this later.
Excuse me.
What's with her? Hey, you!
What the heck was that?
Mr. Woo, we have to go.
Okay.
Tear this part down
and put it with this.
Connect this and that area.
I think so, too.
What? What?
Hey, come down. What are
you doing right now?
Yes, give me a moment.
Excuse me.
Please turn off the water
valves upstairs.
Okay, got it, Ms. Lee.
Geez, come on. Come down.
Come down!
Geez!
Mr. Woo.
I think she's right.
Hey, what's going on here?
The building owner said he
changed all the pipes recently.
He lied.
Geez, he's trying to
save some money.
Okay.
Done.
I happened to have some sockets.
But this is a quick fix.
You have to change
the pipe quickly.
Good thing we did this
before tearing down the wall.
Did you hear that?
- Let's change them.
- Okay.
Mr. Woo.
I told you I've been
around in this field.
Why can't he believe me?
So much mistrust.
Mr. Woo!
Hey, hey...
Hey! Wake up!
- Wake up!
- Hyung!
Geez!
Wake up!
I know I'm pretty.
Stop staring.
Gosh, so tiring.
The men's room is over there.
You're pretty.
Thanks.
I pick you today.
That's too bad. I'm not
picking you today.
I think you'll pick me once
you know who I am.
Come. I'll tell you.
Let go of me!
Oh-ho, you're strong.
So cool.
- How much do you want?
- What?
How much does it
take to date you?
You came here for money,
didn't you?
Hey, I didn't come here
for the money.
I came because my friend's
blind date fell through.
Give me a break.
I know girls like you very well.
Just because of your pretty face,
you try to snag
a rich guy somehow.
I'll give you.
I'll give you money.
Gosh, what nonsense is this?
Why not? Huh?
This is me.
How dare you refuse me?
I refuse you because
you're this way.
So what if you have
tons of money?
Totally unattractive,
sucky manners, and no self-esteem.
Take your pick elsewhere.
Darn it.
Gosh, I said, don't!
Get her!
You'd better stop.
S***.
Look over there!
Geez.
Get her!
Gosh!
Let go!
Hey, Lee Ra Hoon!
Who the hell are you?
You want to know?
I'm her husband.
- Hey!
- You were married?
Run.
- A gold digger!
- Get her!
You're dead.
What do we do now?
You trust me, right?
- No.
- Darn it, just trust me.
Geez. Hey!
My gosh.
Did it dry?
Whatever!
What in the world?
This is expensive.
I rescued you out of the den of evil.
How ungrateful of you!
Hey.
How did you know that I was here?
There's nothing I don't
know about you.
Don't you know you're playing
in the palm of my hands?
- How did you know?
- I saw it on SNS.
You and your friends.
You guys talked about some party
here with rich people for days.
I've been checking up on everything
you were saying with your friends.
I've been nervous ever since!
So what? That's because...
Ji Min said her blind
date fell through,
so I had no choice
but to come out.
You come to a place
like this just for that?
Do you meet anyone who's rich?
Hey, who cares if I meet them?
I don't have to date them.
You think you can control that?
That guy...
He's number one on the
blacklist in your field.
- Really?
- "Really..."
Geez.
What a Cinderella virus carrier.
What do I do with you?
I don't have the Cinderella virus.
Then what is it?
Just learning the attitude.
What attitude?
It's none of your business.
Gosh...
If you were my sister, I'd just...
I'd just...
You're wrinkling my pretty face.
Hey! I have to get to work.
I took a half-day off.
Take this home.
She's going to fall.
Hey, you'll fall!
I'm sorry. There were too many
patients at the hospital...
I had to wait...
Yeah, right. The showcase is today.
♫  I'll approach you and
speak to you shyly  ♫
♫  The door to the future that
only you can make  ♫
♫  I'll memorize the spell
to open your heart  ♫
♫  Mysterious  ♫
♫  Look at me, hold my hand  ♫
♫  I'll give you my heart that
I've been saving for someone  ♫
♫  I'll approach you and embrace you  ♫
♫  Feel the dance  ♫
♫  You and I together  ♫
♫  Shout as loud as you can  ♫
♫  Don't be afraid of losing me  ♫
♫  I've come to an unknown place  ♫
♫  I only see his world  ♫
♫  My heart thumps
when I think of you  ♫
♫  My heart is trembling  ♫
♫  Every moment of meeting you  ♫
♫  Pretty space where
you can feel me  ♫
Hae Deun, what are
you doing here?
You came in late
taking the morning off.
I'm sorry. I'll get to work.
Go now.
Please take a look.
Thank you.
Ma'am, take a look at this.
Thanks.
Ma'am, we have some cauliflower
that's sold only on
the first floor of our mall.
Please take a look.
Oh, my.
You look so cute.
Give me some of this.
I'll help you.
- One more, please.
- Okay.
- My daughter likes it.
- Sure.
Cauliflower?
Ma'am.
Are you done shopping already?
Since I come here every day,
there's nothing to see.
It's my daughter's birthday today.
The quality is good here for these.
I'm sorry. These are
my personal items.
It's okay.
You should feed her
good things on her birthday.
Buy everything you want.
It's my treat.
No, ma'am.
I bought everything
I needed yesterday.
Here you are.
Please take a look
over here, ma'am.
Sweet potatoes.
They're organic and very delicious.
- Ahjumma!
- Yes.
She's my boss.
I work for her.
- Give them to me.
- Okay.
Anyway, I shouldn't go
around with you.
Everyone always thinks
you're the madam.
Gosh, no, ma'am.
They think you and I are friends.
Because you look so
young and beautiful.
If they find out you're
much older than me,
they'll all faint.
I'm going to the ladies' room.
Okay.
See you, ma'am.
My son.
Where are you? At school?
Huh?
Yeah.
It's my break.
I was wondering what kind of gift
(sounds like fish) I should get you.
Do you need anything, Mom?
Fish?
(Short for birthday gift)
I bought some fish already.
Your favorite cutlassfish.
Not that kind of fish.
Your birthday gift.
Oh, gosh.
It's okay.
What birthday gift?
My son...
got into the elite Seohan University.
That's worth ten years of gifts.
You can't do no wrong, as you say.
Hello?
Ra Hoon.
Yeah, Mom, my class is
starting. I have to go.
Oh, okay.
- I'm working, too.
- Okay.
- Did you see?
- I did. So funny.
- The facial expression.
- It was so funny.
Please...
It'd be so nice if I'm a student here.
My goodness...
I wonder if Chae Woon
submitted her work okay.
Aigoo. No, no.
She must be busy.
Let's call her later.
Gosh...
I have 30 minutes left
until the deadline.
Gosh, Bit Chae Woon...
Why did I meddle?
Wait.
I didn't see you.
Geez.
No, no...
No...
I'm sorry, Director.
Someone jumped in front of us.
Just a moment.
- Are you okay?
- Yes, I'm fine.
- I'll take you to the hospital.
- No, I'm fine.
I'm sorry.
Bit Chae Woon?
It's Bit Chae Woon.
I'll take care of this, Director.
Okay.
Yes, CEO.
Director Jang, did you leave?
Just now.
I'm sorry.
My meeting with Sejin
ended a bit late.
You can't be late.
The kids will be waiting.
- I just got here.
- CEO!
Ahjumma!
How have you been?
Gosh, Hae Rin grew so much.
Why?
Come on!
Wait a minute!
Excuse me.
Where are you going?
To submit this.
- It's over.
- Wait...
- You can't go in.
- Why not?
Give me a moment!
Excuse me...
Wait.
Just a moment!
My portfolio.
For the final round.
So, did you submit it?
Yeah, I just turned it in.
Gosh, I almost missed it.
You should've rushed it.
I wanted to, but...
I had so much going on today.
Too many things were going wrong.
I bumped into an annoying guy.
- Hey, hey, hey!
- Hyung!
He looked like a crushed koala.
Really?
Look at the sky and spit.
Hurry.
Darn it.
Spit, take that!
Good job.
Now, you'll only have good luck.
They say if the mountain is deep,
the valley is tall.
It's the opposite.
If the mountain is high,
the valley is deep.
Oh.
Yeah, right, right.
Aigoo, tomato or to-mah-to.
To-mah-to or tomato.
Hurry home. We'll have
our birthday party.
I'm off work, too. I just got home.
Well, I have to stop by another site.
Okay, make me lots
of good food, Mom.
Yeah.
Get the grand prize.
I must.
Please...
Fresh vegetables are here.
We also have fresh fruits.
Oh, my.
- Unni!
- Oh, my gosh!
My goodness, Man Jung!
- Unni!
- The doctor!
The doctor!
What brings you here?
You're busy.
How about the
Jeju Island hospital?
- I...
- Yeah?
I had a conference in Seoul,
so I stopped by.
Gosh...
Hey, girl.
You came because it's
my birthday, huh?
Of course! I came here
for your birthday.
- You're so thoughtful.
- Unni...
Aigoo, my goodness.
Aigoo.
You miss me more
since you live far away, huh?
- Right, I miss you so much.
- Aigoo...
- I'm glad you came.
- Unni...
Man Jung, go inside.
Aigoo, all right.
Go inside.
I have to go and buy
something. I'll be back.
Here.
- Go inside?
- Yeah.
I thought of you this morning
while making plum juice.
Gosh, and you came.
I'm glad you came.
- Go inside.
- Go now.
No, go inside.
- Go inside.
- Go on.
Hurry up and go inside.
Go inside and...
Aigoo, so heavy.
Why do you have so much stuff?
Go inside, drink some
juice, and rest.
I'll be right back.
Gosh...
Unni.
Where are you going?
- Go in.
- Okay.
Oh, my God! My God...
Gosh!
He startled me.
Gosh...
Geez, that Kim Hwak Se.
He hasn't moved out.
Why isn't he moving out?
♫  Did you see? Did you see?
Did you see?  ♫
♫  Did you see me
with another woman?  ♫
♫  Trust this man  ♫
♫  You always doubt me  ♫
♫  You always get miffed at me  ♫
♫  Why is it so difficult?  ♫
♫  Why are you complaining now?  ♫
Excuse me? How old?
129 years old.
I'm 56. My oldest daughter is 27,
my second daughter is 24,
and my youngest is 22.
We all have the same birthday.
Really? How neat.
Isn't it fascinating?
I think so, too.
Here you go.
Catch me if you can!
Aigoo, so cute.
So cute.
Gosh, they're so pretty.
Right?
The kids are most
adorable at that age.
I know.
Gosh.
My kids were like that
at some point.
Chatting away and yelling.
Gosh, when did they
grow up so fast?
Well, the kids grow up
fast once they're born.
How many children do you have?
I have three.
Two daughters and a son.
They're all grown up now.
Gosh, that's perfect.
You must be so happy.
Yes, I'm happy.
How about you, ahjumma?
Three kids.
You must've struggled
so much, raising them alone.
Without their father.
Do you know me?
Of course, I do.
You worked in an
orphanage a long time ago.
Down south.
Don't you know me?
I worked there, too.
Is that so?
But who are you again?
I'm disappointed.
By chance...
- did you work in the kitchen...
- How are your kids?
Yes, they're well.
- But I can't seem to recall...
- I'm glad they're well.
They must've grown up so nicely...
despite the fact that one
of them was stolen.
Excuse me?
Isn't that right?
I know about your family very well.
Who are you, ahjumma?
What are you saying...
Who are you exactly?
Aren't you Ms. Kim Bok Hui?
From Haenam.
From Happy Orphanage.
No, I'm not.
I never lived there before.
Oh, no. I must be mistaken.
I'm so sorry.
Gosh.
You don't even know anything.
Why do you speak as if
you know everything?
My gosh.
Where did she go?
Who was that ahjumma?
Gosh...
What a strange woman.
That was so offensive.
No way.
Wow...
Whoa...
Let's try it.
Kids wait for the day
you come to visit us.
- Oh, my. Really?
- Yes.
- Is that true?
I want to see you every
day, ahjumma.
Gosh, thank you!
Gyeol, she's not "ahjumma."
She's CEO.
No, ma'am.
It's okay. I love it when
I'm called ahjumma.
Take this!
Watch out!
CEO!
Hae Rin!
Did you get hurt, Hae Rin?
Are you all right?
You must've been
so scared, my baby.
It was scary, huh? It's okay.
It's okay now.
CEO!
Are you okay?
Oh, no, CEO...
I'm okay.
Gosh, my Hae Rin.
You've turned into a snowman.
So pretty!
What have you all been doing
that CEO had to go
through that?
My apologies, Director.
It happened so suddenly.
If it happened so suddenly,
how could the CEO be
faster than all of you?
Director Jang, what's going on?
It's nothing, CEO.
Gosh, our Director Jang
is overreacting again.
My people didn't do
anything wrong.
CEO.
How did your meeting
with Sejin go?
It went well.
I'll brief you on our way back.
Go on home. Good job.
You should've changed inside.
It must be uncomfortable.
Why bother?
Kids were so excited that
I turned into a snowman.
Ms. Kim and Mr. Goo.
They're all slacking off.
Gosh. So...
were you upset again,
my daughter?
- Are you my mom now?
- Gosh.
"My people didn't do anything wrong."
You always ostracize me.
Gosh, you're so cute!
Even how you get
miffed so easily...
reminds me so much
of Kim Jung Won.
Well, it's because I'm
Kim Jung Won's daughter.
♫  I guess I'm still young  ♫
♫  I must be  ♫
♫  Oh, my gosh!  ♫
♫  Why do I miss you
out of the blue?  ♫
♫  Oh, my gosh!  ♫
♫  Why do I feel sad
out of the blue?  ♫
♫  On the hill with colors of fall  ♫
♫  I came to pick some wildflowers  ♫
Mr. Woo will arrive soon.
Let's set the table.
How do I look?
Hello.
When did you clean up
by the front door?
Today...
I swept around 5 p.m.
this evening.
This was in front of my front door.
I'm sorry, sir.
How could this be...
You sweep.
We should sweep
our own house entrance.
Our house is ours to keep up.
My apologies, sir!
I'm sorry!
She should do the work
she's getting paid for.
How much do you pay her?
She gets enough.
What?
She gets 5% less than
the market price.
She's very good at the job.
I'm worried she might quit.
Fire her, and you do it.
Honey...
This is my final warning.
If I spot another thing, I'll fire her.
- Aigoo.
- Gosh.
Here.
There's a hole on the heel.
Sew it up.
How is Jae Hee?
He must be busy.
What a pain in the neck.
Jae Hee!
I couldn't answer your call earlier.
Is something the matter?
I just wanted to hear
my son's voice.
Dad must be home already.
You're whispering.
He came home early today.
What did he pick
a fight with today?
It's all the same.
Isn't Seo Ah's father's memorial
around this time of the year?
It's today. I'll stop by later.
Yes.
You should go on a day like this.
Their son is out of the country.
My underwear!
Yes.
Hey, hang up. Hang up.
Mom...
Geez.
My forehead...
The 23rd.
Hey, Lee Ra Hoon!
It hurts! It hurts! I give up! Give up!
Are you really my sister?
- It really hurts!
- Are you my brother?
I always get you, but
you keep provoking me.
Provoke?
I was going to hug you.
My dear sister.
Did you go around like this again?
- Come on!
- What now?
Would a man approach you
when you look like this?
I don't need a man.
Hey, galbijim.
Plus japchae, beef pancakes.
And fish jeon.
- Go, go, go!
- Let's go!
Let's go!
Gosh, I just love your family.
For everyone in the family to
have the same birthday?
This is totally newsworthy.
Right?
Gosh. That's what I'm talking about.
The lady of the house
where I work at said
three siblings who share
the same birthday were on TV.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Some doctor said on that show
that this is extremely rare.
While walking down the street,
you get hit by a meteorite.
He says the chances are
even lower than that.
Oh, I see.
The rock...
No, a meteorite.
- Oh, a meteorite.
- We're home!
- Kids are home!
Kids are home.
You're home.
Auntie!
Ra Hoon!
How have you been, my nephew?
My hoobae from Seohan University.
- All right.
- Chae Woon.
You went through a lot today, huh?
Look at your clothes.
- Hurry up and wash up.
- Okay.
Hey, Bit Chae Woon.
You should greet me
when you see me.
Can't you see me?
- Hello.
- Hi.
What?
Gosh, I was going to go
on a diet starting today!
Auntie!
Auntie, I missed you!
Me, too. Me, too.
My Hae Deun.
So adorable.
There's a call. Quiet!
- Ms. Noh in the States.
- Oh, yeah?
Hold it for me.
Hello, ma'am.
How are you?
Gosh.
I can't believe you remember
our kids' birthday.
Gosh, yes. Thank you.
Yes.
Of course, I remember.
You let us manage the villa
instead of paying rent.
I'm so grateful for just that.
Yes.
We're getting ready to move out.
Yes, ma'am.
Thank you. Goodnight.
Mom.
Unni, do we have to
move out of here?
Gosh, no...
- When?
- Really?
- Whoa.
- No, no...
- Next spring?
- Yeah.
Ms. Noh is coming back
to Korea for good next fall.
Before then,
I guess she'll demolish everything
and build a new building.
Then we'll have to move out.
- Where should we go?
- Gosh.
I'm sure things will work out.
- Don't worry.
- Mom...
Why are you telling me that now?
How can I tell you...
all that when you're focusing
on your competition?
Gosh, japchae will get soggy.
Hwak Se, help me out.
Yes, Noonim.
Everyone heard, right?
Let's get ready.
Ready for what?
Hey, Chae Woon.
- We're still okay.
- What do you mean...
We have to save up as
much as we can to move.
Our apartment we're renting out?
Because we have to give
them the security deposit?
Yeah. Well...
Mom, did you tell the tenants
that we're moving in?
Yeah. Of course.
That place is so small.
The semi-basement and
the upstairs room
didn't rent out, right?
Yeah, well, I did list
them for rent.
A few people stopped by to look,
but no one is interested.
You guys, ask around.
You. Ask around if there
is anyone in your major
who's looking to rent.
- We should save every penny.
- Okay, Noona.
Wow, I should get ready, too.
Where should I go?
If Unni leaves to study overseas,
what do we do then?
Aigoo, seriously.
It'd be great if she leaves to study.
It's for her own good.
What's with you?
Chae Woon, don't worry.
We'll be fine on our own.
Gosh, let's forget about
everything for now.
Let's get ready
for the birthday party.
- Let's go, Hwak Se.
- Okay.
- Let's get ready.
- Move it.
All right.
♫  Happy birthday to you  ♫
I want to blow out the candles.
Wait, wait, wait.
♫  Happy birthday dear...  ♫
It's going off.
- Me, me, me!
- Me!
You do it, Mom.
Me?
Okay, now...
♫  Happy birthday dear
Bit Chae Woon  ♫
♫  Ra Hoon, Hae Deun  ♫
♫  And you, Mom  ♫
♫  Happy birthday to you  ♫
Let's blow them out.
One, two, three!
Congrats!
Happy birthday!
Gosh, there are
so many candles.
Happy birthday...
♫  Happy birthday to you  ♫
Gosh, so noisy.
Today is Jang Eun Ho...
Brother Francesco's memorial service.
We'll pray together for...
his peaceful rest.
Jesus said this.
I want to send it to
Joon Ah oppa.
My pretty mommy.
Jae Hee.
Hello.
God Almighty says...
Face the front.
At that point,
the narrow path leads to...
Whoa, that could've been bad.
You almost lost out
on studying abroad.
Your dad helped her.
My unni thinks her husband
takes care of everything.
Of course.
Will you go to the States as
soon as they announce?
Yeah.
Probably.
You leave right away based
on the schedule.
Gosh, stop jumping the gun.
It hasn't even been announced.
It's not guaranteed that Unni
will win the competition.
She was one of
the finalists last year.
I'm sure she'll make it this year.
Hae Deun is right.
Let's stop jumping the gun.
Yes, yes.
Always be careful what you say.
Okay, now, now.
You can stop jumping the gun,
but hop for the kimchi noodles.
- Here you go.
- Gosh, Uncle!
It's my favorite kimchi noodles.
This is my birthday gift to you.
I don't really like noodles.
Yes, don't eat if you don't like it.
Uncle, it's super good.
You know, I make good noodles.
You know, how you cook
the noodle is crucial.
- How do you do it?
- Okay...
When the noodles
are boiling in the water,
you dump the whole
thing in the strainer.
And hit it with cold water.
Then they will go into a shock
and say, "Gosh, it's so cold.
Turn off the AC."
You say, "No, wake up!"
The point is to shock the noodles.
Eat, eat.
Why? Work again?
Yeah.
Aigoo. The workday is over.
They don't let her rest.
Gosh.
Hello?
Is this Bit Chae Woon?
I'm Manager Oh Byung Wook
from Hanmaeum Adoption Agency.
Yes, hello.
Someone stopped
by our agency today.
She wants to meet you,
Bit Chae Woon.
She thinks you're her
biological daughter.
Isn't it good?
Did she see the blog I posted?
Gosh, what are they talking about?
Her soup is getting cold.
- Then I'll go and scold them...
- Gosh, Hwak Se...
We didn't get to eat our birthday
miyukguk, thanks to Unni.
Your miyukguk is daebak.
The competition is still a test.
- Eat my noodles.
- I'll make you a pot of miyukguk.
- I have to heat this up again.
- Unni.
I'll do it.
You will?
Yes, see you tomorrow.
If she wins the competition and
leaves, I'll take her room.
Who was it?
My work.
Hey.
Are you still looking for
your birth parents?
Unni has no idea, huh?
That you're desperately seeking
your birth parents, huh?
Where will you go?
Let's talk later.
This is why they say you
shouldn't take in a human.
So what if she sacrificed
her life to raise you?
Every chance you get,
you're looking for your birth
parents. So ungrateful.
How about you, Auntie?
What's the point of Mom
sacrificing to support you?
You always get ripped off
and try to live off of her.
What did you just say?
You lost everything again, huh?
That Dr. Song or whatever.
You gave him everything as if
he's the best man in the world.
He pushed you around again, right?
What did I tell you?
- I told you to watch out...
- Hey!
You scared me.
Be quiet.
- What did you just say?
- What's going on, you guys?
Why are you fighting again?
Man Jung, I asked you
to get hot soup.
Unni.
This girl is ridiculous.
She saw me earlier, yet
she won't acknowledge me.
She treats me like crap.
Man Jung.
Chae Woon had a rough day today.
- You let it go.
- Unni.
Is she the only one
having a rough day?
I'm having a rough day, too!
Unni, do you know who
she just talked to?
Right now, she's...
I'll reveal it, too.
You lost the apartment.
We have no place to move to.
What is it Chae Woon?
What phone call?
Did something happen on a site?
No.
Sorry, Auntie.
I went through quite a bit today.
I guess I was sensitive.
Gosh. Aigoo.
Yes, yes. Man Jung.
Let it go.
It's our birthday.
And we're encouraging
Chae Woon for the competition.
You let it go.
Let's do that, okay?
Auntie, let it go.
You know Unni could be super rude.
Lee Hae Deun, you...
Aigoo.
Aigoo, why are we acting
like this on a happy day?
Okay, stop now. Let's go sit down.
Unni, sorry. All right.
I'll bring the soup.
Go.
- Let it go.
- Okay.
All right?
Let's go, Chae Woon.
Let's go.
Auntie...
Yeah, we're fine.
Things are fine
at the company, too.
I miss you, my son.
Not again, Mom.
Jang Joon Ah,
did you get married over there?
Why don't you come back?
Yes.
- Get back to work.
- Take care, Oppa.
I'll call you.
I'll call you again.
CEO, you're not crying, are you?
My heart breaks for you.
Thanks for coming today.
Don't mention it.
My mother asked me to
be like your son
until Joon Ah comes back to Korea.
Is your mother well?
Yes, of course.
I'll go ahead.
Let's have dinner together.
No, I have work stuff
to take care of.
You two enjoy dinner.
Mom, drive carefully!
- I'm leaving.
- Be careful going home.
Bye.
Score! This is great!
From this moment on,
you're mine.
Come on, Jang Seo Ah.
Check our manners and distance.
No, I don't want to.
We promised last time.
- Who am I?
- You're mine.
Who am I?
Who?
- This won't do. I'm leaving.
- Wait!
You're Joon Ah oppa's friend.
Am I a man or a woman to you?
A man or a woman?
You're just an oppa.
That's right.
Seo Ah, this is how I can see
you without expectations.
I'm hungry. What do
you want to eat?
Well, whatever you want.
I really love high-calorie food.
Can you handle it, Seo Ah?
- I can eat everything.
- Okay.
You can't say, "Gosh, I gained 2 kg!"
and regret it in the morning.
Let's go.
I'm hungry.
What are we eating?
She called after seeing
the post and the photo
you posted on the blog
a long time ago.
She said you resemble
the daughter she lost.
There's a record that says
I grew up in an orphanage
ever since I was two years old.
I lived in the orphanage
until I was five years old.
When the orphanage
director got married,
I got adopted into her family
and have lived with them ever since.
If you want, after going through
a confirmation process,
we can set up a meeting with you.
Could she be the one this time?
This is why...
they say you shouldn't
take in a human.
My daughter.
You went through a lot today.
Mom, you weren't sleeping yet?
I'm sleeping.
How can you talk
while you're sleeping?
Because I'm a mom.
When my daughter
comes into my room,
I speak in my sleep.
What a lie.
It's not a lie.
My mom smells good.
Chae Woon.
Actually...
I know.
That your auntie...
lost our apartment.
Mom, you knew?
But I won't tell her for now.
Your auntie must be
so upset about it.
Since it happened again.
A person's heart is
the most important.
It shouldn't get hurt.
It's just money.
So, don't say anything
to her about it.
Gosh...
Well, I'm sure things
will work out.
I wish things would work out
with your auntie and Dr. Song.
You did well.
Sorry, Mom.
Eun Ho.
How are you doing?
It's already been over
ten years since you left.
We're all doing well...
so don't worry.
I'm fine as long as you're okay.
If you ever...
run into our Seo Yeon there,
see how she's doing.
No...
This is too shameless of me.
Right?
Sorry.
I miss you, Seo Yeon.
This is the last time. For real.
If she's not it, that's it.
I won't look for her anymore.
Hi, Mom.
Are you busy?
Yeah, a little bit.
I'm shopping for your jacket.
Why? I have one already.
I was washing your jacket
this morning,
and that white stuff
won't come out easily.
Besides, you have only two jackets.
I'm unsure about the size,
so I'll try it on.
Take a look. I'll send you pictures.
Looks nice.
Okay.
Yeah.
Did you see?
What number?
I'll buy one later.
Today is the last day of the sale.
What number? Hurry.
I have to get back to work.
What number?
Number two.
Okay. Good day.
She says number two.
My daughter sure has
a great taste.
It may not look that great on me,
but my daughter is tall and slim.
It will look great on her.
This is really my last time.
Thanks to your support, CEO...
many children are meeting
wonderful adoptive parents.
It's all thanks to you
and your staff's help.
I ask for your support
in the future.
Thank you.
CEO.
Give it to me.
Thank you. I can't lose this...
Bit Chae Woon, welcome.
Hello, manager.
She's over there.
Hello.
This is Lee Bit Chae Woon.
- This is...
- Hyo Jung!
Hyo Jung!
My baby...
My goodness...
How did you live all this time?
How did you live away
from home?
My gosh...
Let me see...
I bought it! My daughter's
cute jacket.
CEO?
Is something wrong?
No.
I just feel...
a little strange.
For some reason...
I'm sad.
Gosh, this is cute, too.
Gosh...
This is so cute.
This will look great
on Chae Woon.
Why don't you buy this, too?
If I buy this one, too,
my daughter will scold me.
Mom.
I'm sorry.
♫  You don't need to force love  ♫
♫  Like passing time,
you can't stop the heart  ♫
♫  You're drawn to each
other like the magnets  ♫
♫  You part ways leaving
a hole in your heart  ♫
She must've grown up well.
Even though you stole one of them.
Driver, stop please!
The design competition.
I got the grand prize.
- Daebak! Daebak!
- Noona, you're the best!
Old people should step down?
That's what that means!
- Is that Hyo Jung?
- Why are you Hyo Jung?
The test results are already out?
What are you doing over there?
When you get out,
find Lee Soon Jung.
She's the bundle of money.
Lee Bit Chae Woon?
It's a unique name, huh?
Revoke my prize?
♫  Like a bird drenched...  ♫