Is this true?
Is that why...
I was working late...
and ran into the CEO.
I can't believe an article like this posted.
Someone must be playing a joke.
Since it's an anonymous blog.
It just got deleted.
See? It's a joke.
Did someone take it out on Bit Chae Woon
for messing up at the event today?
Why are you looking at me?
I didn't do anything.
I have to organize new items.
I'll go to storage.
All right.
Yes, Executive Director.
I think someone posted it as a joke.
I'm sorry for causing concern.
Please speak with Director Hong
and tell her to rest easy.
Okay.
Yes, Director Jang.
It's nothing serious.
We have had stunts like
this pulled before.
Sister-in-law is doing well, right?
Please tell her I said hi.
Okay.
I was leaving, then turned
around out of shock.
Who posted such an article?
Isn't it someone who
knows about our family?
We deleted the post and
uploaded an explanation.
It's nothing serious. Don't worry, Mom.
What do you mean it's not serious?
Don't you know a small
crack brings down a dam?
Gosh. I have a bad feeling about this.
Because of that Seo Yeon or
Bit Chae Woon or whatever...
I think something huge will
happen to our family.
CEO! On the internet...
Chairwoman, you're back.
Did you see our blog?
What's going on online?
There were two posts
about the article
that was posted on the company blog.
- I asked them to delete them.
- What?
Aigoo, gosh.
What are we going to do? What now?
Ms. Goo!
Yes, CEO.
Find out where the post came from.
We're checking right now.
What does the IT Team say?
They still haven't found the employee
who posted that blog post?
No.
It came through an external
server. They can't find it.
The IP that deleted the post came
from another location, too.
Gosh, all right.
You can leave.
Aigoo.
Someone is totally determined.
Someone is totally determined
to ruin our family.
Yes, uncle.
It's nothing serious.
Of course. It's nonsense.
Director Jang just talked
to me on the phone.
Director Jang?
Wait.
Your brother-in-law?
See?
They're coming at you in droves
as if they were waiting for it.
What do we do now?
Please, Mom!
Why are you irritated with me?
I'm sorry.
This isn't going to work.
- Make Bit Chae Woon leave.
- Mom.
Chairwoman, how could she do that?
She's Mom's long lost daughter.
For now, send her far away
like New York or Paris.
Study abroad or training.
There are lots of reasons.
Until your position
in the company is firm,
- tell her to stay out for a few years.
- Mom...
You'd better come to your senses.
Everything you've struggled
to build all this time.
Do you want to lose it because
of that Bit Chae Woon?
Why do you keep saying I'll lose it?
Do you think I'll stand back
while that happens?
Do you know how I've come this far?
That's what I'm saying.
Then...
the CCTV didn't work
at that time frame?
Yes.
Of all places, just the prep room
and its surroundings?
It looks that way.
Of course.
No one can find out who
hid the clothes.
What?
Nothing.
Have a good day. Thank you.
It has to be someone inside.
Hwang Na Ro?
Jang Seo Ah?
Chae Woon, you had a tough day, huh?
I enjoyed the event earlier.
I couldn't say bye because I rushed out.
My Chae Woon was so cool.
I know you were worried.
Hi, Mom. Did you get home okay?
Hi. I just got home.
It was a tough day today, huh?
It wasn't that bad.
I made a mistake at the end...
But I got lots of compliments
for positive responses.
Really?
Mom, you were worried seeing
me get nervous earlier, huh?
That happens a lot when
you're working at events.
Everyone understood.
I see. I'm glad...
that everyone understood.
Chae Woon.
James...
I mean...
Mr. Woo's father is here.
Oh, really?
As for my dad getting his memory back,
I won't tell Samgwang people for now.
Tell Jae Hee's father that I said hello.
Chae Woon says hello.
I see.
Chae Woon, you take care, too.
Chae Woon.
Have a good day.
Okay, Mom.
Oh, Chae Woon.
Nothing's the matter, for real, right?
Yeah, everything is fine.
Okay.
- I'll hang up.
- Bye.
Chae Woon went to her
birth mom's house, right?
I heard Hae Deun and Ra Hoon talk.
You must feel very empty
since Chae Woon went to that house.
No.
It's a good thing.
She went back to her birth mom.
My Chae Woon...
will struggle for now...
but she'll prevail.
Yes, she will.
Chae Woon is bold.
She'll overcome it well.
Ms. Lee.
By chance, is something the matter?
By chance, is someone bothering you?
I was wondering if something
like that was going on.
Aigoo, aigoo...
Gosh, it's not my place and
asked you such a thing.
It's okay.
Thank you for your concern.
It may be out of line,
but you tend to take
everything on alone.
When I think that
you must be struggling
with something,
but Samgwang Villa family
or I say something,
you take it all in with a smile.
You continue to endure alone.
I was worried that you'd damage
your health at that rate.
I just...
feel like...
I'm still so dumb...
at this age.
I'm so fearful, too.
Actually...
I should reveal something honestly,
but I can't bring myself to do that.
How come?
Is there a reason
why you can't reveal it?
Or is someone scaring you
so you can't reveal?
No.
I'm not...
scared of that at all.
But my daughter...
My Chae Woon...
When I consider how shocked
and hurt she will be...
So I'll keep my mouth shut
decided to hold it in
all inside.
But that is so tough to do.
I feel like I'm committing another
type of sin by doing so.
My gosh.
Why am I such a stupid person?
No.
It's not like that at all. Never.
Who is stupid in this world?
Just because you're kinder,
gentler, and more fragile
than others, they think you're foolish.
That's not true.
That's really not true.
Gosh, I can't believe I told you all this.
- Let me get more ginger tea...
- Ms. Lee.
I don't know the details, but...
why don't you have courage?
I don't know what it's about,
but I don't think
Chae Woon will be hurt
as much as you think.
Chae Woon is just as strong as you.
Just think you're doing it
for Chae Woon,
and why don't you
muster up the courage?
Gosh.
Gosh...
I was out of line.
Gosh, I spoke out of my place.
Gosh, I'm sorry.
Mr. Woo...
you were always a very warm person.
When I faced difficulties or struggles,
you always comforted me.
I did?
What do you mean...
Did I do that?
You can't come in today?
We can't help it. Rest up.
What's going on, Eems hyung?
Eems hyung!
- Eems hyung!
- Hwak Se!
Eems hyung!
No wonder.
I felt like coming home.
Eems hyung, do you know
how much I missed you?
Me, too. Me, too, Hwak Se!
But...
how have you been?
What's the use in
dressing up like this?
I heard you didn't get
your memory back.
- Aigoo. What will you do now?
- Hwak Se.
- Is something the matter?
- What?
Oh, the part-timer at work...
He's not feeling well,
so he can't come in today.
- It's trouble.
- Yeah, that's bad.
It's one of the busiest days.
What?
Yeah, right?
Yeah, right.
Whoa!
Hwak Se!
Hwak Se.
James... I mean, Mr. Woo...
He just stopped by.
- Eems hyung, you said you're fine.
- Yes.
Don't worry.
I finished all my work.
But still.
If your wife and Mr. Woo find out,
they'd worry.
I'll tell Jae Hee.
- Let's go.
- Aigoo, don't worry, Noonim.
Look how happy Eems hyung is.
I'll take care of Eems hyung.
Okay, Hwak Se. Take care of him.
Okay, don't worry, Noonim.
- Let's go, Eems hyung.
- Let's go.
My goodness.
My phone.
Hi, Soon Jung.
Did you get home okay?
Yes, did you get home okay?
Well, I'm here to see Jae Hee.
Jae Hee's dad?
Yes.
So...
he's at the jokbal place
he used to work at.
I didn't know what I should do.
What kind of mood was he in?
Well, he met Hwak Se
and seemed very happy.
That's good then.
It's fine as long as he's happy.
That's what his doctor said, too.
Don't worry.
Okay.
I'll call you again
if anything happens.
Thank you.
But Soon Jung.
I told you.
Jung Hoo and I got divorced.
Of course, I'll take care
of him as a friend.
But don't think that I'm his wife
and feel burdened.
Just consider me his friend.
Okay.
I understand what you're saying.
But still, since you're his close friend,
I'll discuss it with you
if this happens again.
Thank you, Soon Jung.
I guess Jung Woo was happy
while he stayed at Samgwang Villa.
Where is this?
Hwang Na Ro, that jerk.
He sure plays dirty.
Hey, man. Is this how you work?
Did you already switch
to Jang Seo Ah?
Oh-ho? Look at this guy.
Hwang Na Ro, is this
how you'll interfere?
My Seo Yeon needs to be
accepted there quickly.
Excuse me.
I'm here to see Mr. Woo Jae Hee.
I'm his mom.
Jung Min Jae is Mr. Woo's mom?
By chance, do you know where he is?
Over there? Where?
Ahjussi...
Are you okay?
Wait. Hold on.
My gosh. I'm so sorry.
Who put this here? It's dangerous.
Jae Hee!
Hold on.
Are you here to see Jae Hee?
Yes.
By chance, are you his older sister?
What?
Hello, I'm Son Jung Hoo,
Jae Hee's sunbae.
- Son Jung...
- Son Jung Hoo.
Hoo, as in hoo-hoo-hoo.
Jung Hoo.
He's Jung Hoo, too.
- Excuse me?
- Oh, nothing.
- Professor, you're here.
- Hi, Jae Hee.
Did you two meet?
He's my college professor.
He used to be my sunbae
and became a professor.
Hello, I'm Jae Hee's mom.
You're Jae Hee's mother?
Is that right?
I thought you were his older sister.
Oh, my gosh...
Really?
Mom, you must be so happy.
But Mom, what brings you here?
I came by Jung Won's office
and stopped by since
you're in the area.
You two talk first.
- I'll wait over there.
- Okay.
Excuse me.
Interior trend seminar?
Yeah.
I'm the chief researcher
at the company.
I was wondering if you can do a presentation
for our upcoming interior seminar.
Of course, I will.
I'm still lacking, but I'll do my best.
I knew I could count on you.
Thanks, Jae Hee.
Hey...
is she really your mother?
Well, no. She's actually my older sister.
Nah...
He looks very familiar.
- I wanted to see his face.
- I'll do my best to prep.
Please do.
- I'm off.
- All right.
It's been so long since
I last saw Min Jae.
Wait.
That family has some money, too.
Wow.
Seo Yeon was sure born into money.
So, that professor is your sunbae?
Right. He's my sunbae and a teacher.
He's like a mentor to me.
But how can his name
be Jung Hoo, too?
He has the same name as your father.
It's not a common name, either.
I know.
But it's so neat.
Professor Son thought
you were my older sister.
Aigoo, I feel great for some reason.
You just found out?
Even now, people see me
from the back
and say, "Hey, student!"
Mom, I love everything about you,
but you always go too far.
Come back, Mom.
I'm coming back.
Hey, hey.
I got a call from Soon Jung.
She says your dad is at Samgwang Villa.
Why? Did he lose his memory again?
No, it's not that.
Hello.
What?
Jung Hoo, where did you go?
I got so scared because you
disappeared all of a sudden.
Why get scared?
I gave my instructions to
Mr. Seo on tasks.
Where are you right now?
Here?
With a vendor.
What?
Why didn't you take Mr. Seo
with you to meet a vendor?
I'm busy. Hang up.
Hwak Se!
Aigoo, Eems hyung, come on.
- Here.
- Aigoo, good job.
Here is the next delivery.
- Two this time?
- Yes.
Since you're back at our store,
you brought high sales with you.
Right? It makes me so happy, too.
I'll be back.
Wait, no, no.
Okay.
Aigoo, don't be too jumpy.
Walk slowly.
Here comes Bit Chae Woon.
Bit Chae Woon, did you fall?
I was looking for some
stuff in the storage.
Look for what? I thought you
were organizing new items.
The outfits I had prepared
for the styling class.
I looked to see where
they were hidden.
Bit Chae Woon, do you
think you were framed?
Unbelievable.
Who would hide that in there?
It's not like a psycho did it.
I know.
It wasn't there as expected.
Interestingly, the CCTV wasn't
working only in that area.
CCTV... really?
Okay, I came to explain the post
that posted a little bit ago.
I'm sure you read the announcement.
I want to say that the rumor that
the CEO and Bit Chae Woon
are somehow related is not true
at all once again.
The reason Bit Chae Woon
was in charge of the event
was because she performed
very highly thus far.
Of course,
I will ask her to be accountable
for the mistake she made
at the event.
All right, everyone, thank you for
your hard work at the event.
Director.
I'd like to meet with you.
Come to my office.
What is it about?
Is it about the post on the blog?
I think you gave them
the reason for it.
If you had led the styling
class perfectly,
I don't think a post framing you like
that wouldn't have come up.
Do you think so?
I thought it wasn't framing
because of my mistake
but a trap trying to get me.
The disappearance of
the outfits I prepared
- for the styling class...
- Wait.
I thought it was in line with
the post that was on the blog.
So what you're saying is that...
someone planned it purposely?
And you came to see me
to ask, "Isn't this your doing,
Jang Seo Ah?"
The photo on the blog
was possible because
it was an insider.
And the reason CCTV didn't work
means someone who can control
all the system in the
company was helping.
Bit Chae Woon.
Were you investigating
that all this time?
That's why you look
like a dirty mouse?
How could you think that?
I'm a director of this company.
I worry about the company
more than anyone else.
How dare you say such a thing?
So?
What do you really want to say?
I wanted to let you know that
I'm fully aware of such intentions.
What intention?
Your intention to get rid of me.
- Hey!
- Director Jang!
Bit Chae Woon.
What I heard was over the top.
About what had happened today,
you're not remorseful at all?
You put Director Jang and me
in confusion all-day,
and you try to blame Director Jang?
Wait.
What's with your clothes?
To find the proof that I framed her,
it looks like she searched
all over the building today.
What?
It's my fault that I showed
my flaws at the event.
But there were definitely
unsettling aspects to it.
So?
Are you saying I did that?
You're really...
Did you see that, Mom?
That's how she is.
She acts calm and quiet,
- yet she throws you under the bus!
- Director Jang, we're at work.
Call me, "CEO."
Okay.
Let's say Director Jang did that.
If we supposed that,
what will you do, Bit Chae Woon?
Hm?
There's nothing I can do.
I'll just take the punches
and fall into the trap she dug.
However, I'm falling into her trap,
knowing she set it.
If I keep falling, I can build a tolerance.
That I won't fall over just
because she tramples on me.
I came here to say this.
Hey.
You get out.
Get out!
- Get out!
- Calm down, Director Jang!
You can leave, Bit Chae Woon.
Leave now.
Calm down.
You clearly understand
it's your fault, right?
You can leave, Bit Chae Woon.
Leave now.
I still...
can't protect you.
I'm sorry, Chae Woon.
So I wanted to discuss it
with you again.
I'm so happy about going
to France as a trainee.
I wanted to know if
I really have potential.
I've been thinking a lot.
Actually...
I put you as a candidate
since you pleaded.
But when you get there,
you'll have to help out
with other tasks.
Just like what I've been doing here,
getting the costumes, cleaning,
chores like that?
When you work hard like that,
you can get another chance.
When I work hard?
Didn't I work hard here?
Gosh, so I was an odd one out again?
No...
This is still a good chance.
Yes.
Wait, wait a minute.
Wait a minute. I'm on my way.
I'll do it if I can't find a model.
I'm a man.
Mr. Makjang.
I told you we're meant to be.
Wait. I'll call you back.
Hae Deun, come with me.
I'm glad I ran into you.
Where?
A part-time job.
English class again?
No, not an English class.
Something else.
I'll pay you 70,000 won per hour.
- 10,000 won?
- Did I push too high?
10,000 won, okay. Let's go.
Wait!
- A shopping mall?
- Yes.
It's a small business I'm running.
Mr. Makjang, weren't you
an English teacher?
That's a side job.
This is my dream job.
Don't you know full well
since you have your dream?
I think you can understand
me very well.
What a line, huh?
Anyway, my part-time model ran away.
Please work with me just
for the day, Hae Deun.
Gosh.
But I don't want to model. I didn't
put that much makeup on today.
Why? You look great.
You look so natural.
Anyway, the natural look is
our store concept.
It's okay. You look great right now.
No, I don't want to do it.
Wait.
The photographer is
waiting right now.
You can't say that...
I paid him a lot to hire him.
I rented this cafe for a limited time.
Hae Deun, please let me
ask you a favor this once.
Just this once. Really.
Oh, this...
This... what?
It worked. I loosened it.
Did you see that? This...
You remember, right?
I said we're meant to be.
Please rescue me just this once.
This checker pattern
looks great on you.
Try it on. Looks great.
Let's go. Let's go. It's okay.
Hello, I'm sorry we're late.
- Why do you make me wait?
- I'm sorry. Let's get going.
Sit here. You look pretty.
You look like an idol. Great, great.
Great. That's right.
You look great.
Right.
Great.
Your expression.
You can wear this next.
No.
Okay. One more time. One, two.
Gosh, great.
Looks good.
Are you a model?
No, it's my first time.
You have talent, Hae Deun.
- You look good now. Let's go again.
- Okay.
One, two.
Look to the side and smile.
Again.
Hello, dry cleaning owner.
Mr. James.
Whoa, Dad is totally James.
Of course, James is James.
Auntie, you're home early.
I heard James came by.
I wanted to see him.
I even canceled my dinner plans.
You're home early, Mr. Woo.
I have to go out again.
I heard my dad came here,
and I was worried.
Wow, Mr. Woo...
You're such a scary person.
When he's your father,
how can you deceive us
as if he's a stranger?
There's a family story behind it.
I'm so sorry, Auntie.
It's okay.
What family doesn't have a story?
I understand.
So are you going out on
a date with Bit Chae?
Yes.
Is Bit Chae doing well?
Yes, she's doing very well.
Be good to Bit Chae.
I have never seen her
relying on anyone before.
But she does rely on you a bit, right?
Gosh, of course.
I'm a very broad-minded Koala...
Oh, you're Koala?
You two call each other that?
Gosh, that's how you two are.
Why did Jae Hee come
home so early?
What's wrong with him?
I know.
Auntie, I'll get going.
All right.
Bye, Koala.
Yes.
Yes, Moong-i.
Dinner? Sounds good.
Yes. Right now?
Phew.
Gosh.
He must be on his way
to see Chae Woon.
Aigoo.
Here you go. Enjoy.
Thank you.
♫  I love you  ♫
♫  I like you  ♫
♫  I only trust you  ♫
Jung, you're home early.
Well, you know.
You said Jame was here,
so I came home to say hi.
What the heck?
You didn't come home early
to see me quickly?
Well...
that is a part of a reason
a little bit, too.
"A part of a reason a little bit"?
That's the only reason.
Isn't that right?
- Isn't that right?
- No, no, no.
No, no...
Scared me.
Why are you standing so close?
You're ridiculous.
I had to tell him something.
James, you're here.
How have you been?
I heard you came,
so I wanted to say hi.
I came home even canceling
my dinner plans.
Nah.
What?
Ba Reun, I'm saying this just in
case there's a misunderstanding.
My Jung...
Aunt Man Jung and I usually...
tend to push each other...
and we throw punches, left, right,
hook, straight, to the side.
Nah...
Student, you're a young student.
How can you be so rude
when an elder is speaking?
James, come in later.
- Okay?
- Yes, Auntie.
Take care.
- See you later.
- Bye.
Eems hyung.
You can go home now.
The night part-timer is here.
Hwak Se, congrats.
Eems hyung, congrats on what?
I'll keep it a secret.
Me, too.
Gosh. Nah...
No...
Please have dinner with us.
No, I'll eat at home.
All you did was work all day.
No, I had so much fun.
Ms. Lee.
What I had mentioned earlier.
Please consider it.
I hope you'll muster up the courage.
Okay.
Thank you.
James ahjussi!
Hae Deun. Ra Hoon.
I was sad thinking that I'd miss you.
It's good to see you.
You left without saying bye. I'm sad.
I'm sorry, Hae Deun.
James ahjussi, I missed you so much.
Me, too, Ra Hoon.
Ra Hoon.
You can't call him "James" anymore.
No.
Just call me James, at least here.
- All right then.
- Good-bye.
Do you know your way home?
Don't worry. I know my way home.
Bye.
- Bye.
- Be careful going home.
Yes, yes.
Mom, I guess he hasn't
gotten his memory back yet.
I guess not.
It's so nice to see him.
It's been a while.
James ahjussi looks healthier, too.
Right?
Doesn't he look like
a different person in a suit?
♫  My love  ♫
I'll carry this.
♫  You're my only one  ♫
How is your depression, Mom?
I'm taking medication and
have therapy sessions.
I'm getting better.
I thought...
Min Jae would live happily
ever after the divorce.
She has depression?
♫  You shine down on
me with comfort  ♫
♫  You're like sunshine to me  ♫
I wonder...
how she's doing today.
You've improved a lot, Jung Min Jae.
At this rate, you'll
overcome depression.
♫  My love  ♫
I wonder how Woo Jung Hoo is doing.
♫  Only you can give me perfect love  ♫
♫  You're my only one  ♫
Moong-i.
Why did you...
come suddenly while I was yawning?
I know.
Why do you yawn all the time?
Let me see you.
Did your mouth rip?
Stand up.
Where are we going?
Unbelievable.
Was it Cunning Penguin?
Hwang Na Ro?
It's the day I went to your
office basement parking lot.
Yeah.
Then was it Seo Ah, by chance?
Or two them together?
There's no proof.
I can't jump to conclusions.
Anyway, it has to be someone
who wants to drive you out,
causing the problem with this.
Also, the outfits disappearing
from the styling class.
If it's Hwang Na Ro's doing,
I won't stand back.
You must be so upset, Moong-i.
Yeah, a little bit.
Then...
you got dirty from looking
through the storage?
Gosh, they wouldn't hide it
inside the building.
Right?
I thought that, too, but just in case.
I had to do something.
I was too angry to sit back.
You did well.
I even confronted Seo Ah.
I'm glad you did.
Am I very dirty?
Yes, very.
It's okay.
You're cuter when you're dirty like that.
You really look like a puppy. A pup.
Finally, you smile.
I have to be by your side, Moong-i.
What if you didn't see me tonight?
You'd be sitting there
on the street and crying.
I don't cry on the street.
Earlier, it was just that
I was thinking of seeing you...
So you were thinking of meeting me...
When I thought of seeing you...
You let your guard down.
Right?
I think the CEO is in
a bind because of me.
My heart is heavy.
You must be.
About this mishap, and I'm sure
Seo Ah will keep doing that.
Why?
This thought just occurred to me.
It's a calm and peaceful lake.
And I flow in
and create all kinds of ripple,
making everyone suffer.
CEO, Koala,
and including Seo Ah.
What kind of nonsense is that?
Who's suffering now?
You're having the hardest time.
You were childlike,
bright, and cute.
One day, you got swept
by a strange tornado.
But it will pass soon.
The tornado won't last forever.
The tornado will tire out.
Right? The tornado will tire out, right?
Moong-i.
My life is...
divided into before and after I met you.
Isn't that too grandioso?
Listen.
I was very grim as a child.
I fought with Dad all the time.
After I left home,
I failed two businesses.
I lost a studio that I used to live in.
It was really tough.
I'd laugh on the outside,
but thought, "What's going on?
Why am I struggling so much?"
It was a bit tough.
One day...
as I buttheaded a super strong woman,
I came to my senses.
That's how I got to know you
and living is so fun to me ever since.
When I open my eyes in
the morning, I think of you first.
And you're looking down
on me from the ceiling.
Smiling like this.
And I'd look up like this
and laugh, "Ha, ha."
"Ha, ha, ha."
Yeah.
I laugh because I'm happy
and because it's so neat.
So...
don't say weird stuff like
you're bothering everyone.
Okay?
You're not answering me.
You got that, Moong-i?
Don't laugh so sadly like that.
I can't sleep tonight then.
Laugh big like this.
You have such a cute smile.
♫  Life is so hard  ♫
It's so neat that someone's smile can
make me so happy.
♫  Well, just living with
that in my heart  ♫
Maybe I should've given in
and eaten there.
You did refuse,
but I sent a few side dishes I made.
Geez.
What's going on?
"What's going on?"
I was wondering if you ate dinner.
I ate a long time ago.
Look at the time.
I think you're eating now.
What do you mean?
Don't assume.
Did you go home right after work?
Of course, I did.
But Jung Min Jae.
Why are you checking up
on my personal life?
Aren't we strangers?
We are strangers.
But you just got your memory back,
and you live alone.
I'm calling just to check.
Don't think of me as your ex-wife.
Just think of me as your old friend.
What friend?
- Between a man and a woman.
- A man and woman?
Do I even look like a woman to you?
And you're a man?
Oh, my gosh!
- Aigoo.
- Why are you laughing?
Then are you a man?
Am I a woman?
Do you like the side
dishes I sent you?
Don't know. I haven't eaten them yet.
Be sure to turn on the heater
in your room before you go to bed.
There's a draft in the room.
It gets cold early in the morning.
I'll take care of it, Jung Min Jae.
You do that, Woo Jung Hoo.
I'm hanging up.
Gosh, what terrible manner.
I feel sorry for him, so I try to be nice.
But after talking to him for
a minute, I lose my temper.
Gosh, gosh.
Jung Min Jae, why did you call him?
He's living a good life.
Oh, my. What's wrong with me?
Oh, my.
Gosh, what do I do?
What is it that you're
dragging this out?
Lee Hae Deun!
- You're breaking all the dishes, right?
- No, I'm not.
I didn't break any.
Ra Hoon.
What's wrong?
Is something wrong?
Mom.
Mom, actually...
Mom, I...
Mom, I'm actually...
You don't have to say it.
Mom.
Did you know?
That I don't attend Seohan University?
What? What's this?
My gosh. What is all this?
Mom, I'm sorry for lying about
being a Seohan University student.
Mom. Mom, I'm really sorry.
I'm really sorry.
You must've felt so uneasy
every single day.
Mom...
I wanted to study really hard...
and make you happy...
by going to a good university.
I'm sorry. I'm a fool.
Gosh.
Ra Hoon.
Why are you a fool?
Because you didn't get
into a good college?
That's just a good college,
according to other people.
I just...
cheered you on since you had a goal.
I never thought that you have to
attend a good university.
My Ra Hoon...
had a dream and living diligently.
It was so wonderful for me to see.
All right.
Let me hug you, Ra Hoon.
Don't cry.
My gosh.
Ra Hoon.
If something comes up again,
don't hide from me.
- Okay?
- Yes.
It's tough on you.
- Okay?
- Yes, I will.
Okay.
Just tell me. You can just talk to me.
Gosh, don't cry.
It's okay. It's okay.
Gosh, you're a baby.
You're a baby crying like this.
Don't cry.
We can talk at home.
Why did you ask me to come out?
It was you, right?
What?
Wasn't this your piece of work?
You also hid the clothes
for her styling class.
What the hell?
- Did you open up a PI agency?
- Hwang Na Ro.
I told you to stay put if
you're not going to leave.
I did stay put.
Why would I do such a thing?
It's a hassle.
Because you and
Bit Chae Woon are dating?
Out of jealousy? Hey.
Don't be delusional.
I wasn't into Bit Chae Woon that much.
Didn't you find another target?
Jang Seo Ah.
Did Seo Ah tell you to do this?
Or you did this to
capture Seo Ah's heart.
Isn't that right?
Hey, you laugh?
Why?
I can't find another target?
It's none of your business what I do.
Nothing is going on with
you and Jang Seo Ah.
- You a**...
- Hey, a**hole.
Look out for your good.
Don't meddle in my business.
This jerk!
Dang it.
This jerk...
Hey, Hwang Na Ro.
I'm warning you.
If you do anything suspicious,
I won't let it go.
If you don't let it go, then what?
Will you put me away in jail?
You don't have any proof.
How could such an evil bastard...
It hurts.
I still don't want to move
out of here, though.
What I heard was over the top.
And you try to blame Director Jang?
Why don't you muster up the courage?
I don't think Chae Woon will be hurt
as much as you think.
Courage.
Should I muster up the courage
and tell her everything?
That everything happened
because of the Chairwoman.
But my Chae Woon will get hurt again.
Did you have someone post this?
Anyway, we're all about to go down
because of you, Soon Jung.
Even with this, you insist
you won't leave?
If you'll stand your ground foolishly,
take Bit Chae Woon back.
You can leave, Bit Chae Woon.
Leave now.
I hurt Chae Woon again...
My gosh.
Seo Yeon is crying her heart out,
and you're her mom.
Aigoo, aigoo, Seo Yeon...
Aigoo, Seo Yeon.
Aigoo...
Gosh. Don't cry. Don't cry.
Aigoo, Seo Yeon.
Soon Jung, come in.
Young Lady Jung Won.
Long time no see.
Hey, Soon Jung.
Calm her down somehow.
Aigoo. Here.
Gosh, all the helpers quit.
We have no one to take care of the baby.
And Jung Won is in that state
with depression or something.
And who knows what kind
of trouble Pil Hong is up to.
I can't even reach him.
Oh, my.
Look at her.
She's smiling since you're holding her.
My gosh.
Hey, Soon Jung.
You said you're not working at
the factory since it's Sunday, right?
Yes, ma'am.
Then please take care of the baby today.
As you can see, the mom is in that state.
I'm so nervous.
- Okay, I'll do that.
- All right.
Gosh.
Aigoo, my Seo Yeon is smiling.
Aigoo.
Aigoo, so pretty.
Young Lady.
Please get stronger for
Seo Yeon's sake.
I'm exhausted.
My Seo Yeon...
I don't even know how
I'm going to raise her.
I'm too exhausted.
CEO.
Seo Yeon.
You asked me why...
I had lost you back then, right?
You asked me what I was
doing when I lost you.
CEO.
Actually...
it was my fault.
I should have...
protected you no matter what.
It's all my fault.
I'm sorry, Seo Yeon.
I'm sorry.
Seo Yeon is so pretty.
Aigoo.
Aigoo, so pretty.
♫  I'm in love, I'm in love  ♫
♫  I'm in love with you  ♫
♫  Stay with me forever  ♫
♫  It makes me fill up my whole day
with the thoughts of you  ♫
♫  Just like that...  ♫
I won't tell Chae Woon.
Did Seo Ah send out the post?
It was you who posted an article
saying I'm CEO's daughter.
Jung, shall we go on a date today?
I said I'd treat you to everything
including a movie.
Ra Hoon.
I'm sorry.
Jung Won is looking for me?
Ms. Goo, give me a cup of coffee.
- Jung Won, long time no see.
- How did you get in here?
- Ms. Lee.
- Mr. Woo.
Long time no see. I'm Jung Won's
friend Min Jae's husband.
Mr. Woo, you remember?