I tried so hard to escape
from that dreadful fate.
I can't let her stay there anymore.
If anyone
finds out
that she's Hong Gyeong-rae's daughter...
I always wondered
why I had to dress as a boy,
run and hide.
Ra-on.
But now I understand
how you must have felt.
You could not tell me
because Father was infamous, right?
You did not want me to live as the
daughter of a traitor
responsible for the death of thousands.
Do not hate your father
too much.
He only did that to make this
a better place...
for you.
You should have kept it a secret
from me until the end.
No.
You should have told me sooner.
Ra-on.
I am so sorry.
I'm sorry.
Mom.
Let me go.
Ra-on.
I'll be back before you know it. Please?
Ra-on, please, I can't let you.
Please don't go.
He is waiting for me.
Without knowing anything...
JAHYEONDANG
Did you wait for long, Your Highness?
I promised myself not to smile
when I see you again.
I was worried because
you didn't show up on time.
Why?
Will you punish me again?
You seem to be expecting it.
I will forgive you
since you have returned safely.
How is it
that no one else is in sight?
By chance,
has Hun-nam left you with all the work?
I asked to take on the work.
You already have enough on your plate.
I requested to work night shifts
of the Crown Prince's palace
for the next few days as well.
I wasn't there by your side
while you were ill in bed.
I was told to watch out for women
who were filled with jealousy.
If you want me so badly...
you can have me.
Your Highness.
I have one request.
What is it?
Would you allow me
to be right by your side all day long?
Yes.
To rest on your shoulders,
to fall asleep on your lap--
As you wish.
I will plead that you look at me
instead of your books.
It is now my turn.
Are you prepared?
Pardon?
What is it?
You do not have to make requests.
I will grant
all your wishes.
I cannot believe that it happened
undetected by dozens of guards.
This awful and devastating event
has left us speechless.
If I told you
I felt more awful and devastated
over your presence even
after your dismissal,
what would you say?
He loyally took your place
while you were ill.
It is also considered disloyal
for disobeying the orders
of his dismissal and probation.
I may have been ordered for dismissal,
I had to deal with unexpected threats
in the palace.
How could I simply turn my head away
from the issue?
It is true.
He was royally granted his return
for his loyal service.
I beg your understanding.
Your Highness,
please show your understanding.
-Please show your understanding.
After the alarm drums
and the palace guards' arrival,
only the bodies of nine attackers
remained at site.
Nine bodies...
Yes, Your Highness.
All we needed was to catch one alive,
and we could have interrogated him
to uncover the truth.
I apologize.
They could not have breached the walls
without anyone knowing.
There must have been an insider.
We must find
the rest of them.
Yes, Your Highness.
Eunuch Hong.
How do you deal with
the discomfort of your injured hand?
The look on your face
seems more uncomfortable.
Pardon?
You must have been frightened
the other day.
I'm all right.
I didn't get hurt or anything.
How is His Highness doing?
I'm all right.
As you can see.
At some point
it started to get harder to
treat you as I did before.
Maybe it's because I am
the only legitimate son of the Kim family.
I think that is one of the reasons.
However,
I felt sorry to see you block the sword
with your bare hands...
which was aimed at me.
Perhaps, I was making it
all too complicated.
I felt indebted to you.
May I think
I repaid you a little bit?
From now on,
I won't wait, be considerate,
nor ask for your favor anymore.
I don't intend to stop you.
Only after you try enough,
you will be able to give up.
Please listen carefully, Your Highness.
These books on the left need to be dried,
these books on the right are damaged,
and I sorted out the books that
need to be written anew.
Do I have to know that?
You don't have to do it in one go.
You're overexerting yourself.
Whether in one go or slowly,
I need to do it anyway.
Your Highness.
Shall I write down the story I told you
when you couldn't sleep?
It's okay.
Whenever I want to hear that story,
I can call you over.
You are right.
Ra-on.
Your Highness.
I'd like to stay like this
for a moment.
You may stay like that
for as long as you want.
I heard His Highness started
to tend state affairs again.
Yes, My Lady.
You know, Eunuch Hong.
His Highness didn't accept my heart
after all.
So I decided not to show my feelings
to stay beside him.
Are you going to hide your feelings
to stay beside him?
In that case,
although I can't be the one
who he cares for,
but the one who can be of help to him.
Won't it be too difficult for you?
I have a feeling that it will be.
But
he might be able to accept
my love someday.
I look pathetic, don't I?
No, you don't.
Please take good care of him.
He needs
someone like you.
I feel like you are my friend now.
When I feel upset again,
can I call you over and chat with you?
I think I should get going.
In the hope of bumping into him,
I walked around the garden for too long,
so my legs hurt so much now.
My lady...
Where did you go without saying...
What brings you here?
My apologies.
As I have something to tell you,
I got some help from my friend.
Are you feeling better, Your Highness?
I am okay.
I'm feeling much better.
Last time,
you said that you have someone else
in your heart.
I thought a lot about that.
You have someone in your heart,
but you strongly refuse to get married.
Does that mean she is
someone you can't marry?
What do you want to say?
I want to be
your nest.
You can't refuse to get married forever.
If you can't avoid getting married,
how about placing someone
who can be of help
to His Majesty and you in that position?
Do you mean you are
the one who can be of help?
Yes.
In order to start soaring
with your great ambitions,
please use my family and me.
What is it, sir?
Why do you look at me that way?
You look like you are angry.
I really am angry
at myself who has always been
one step behind.
But this time,
I think I should not be one step behind.
Not because of myself,
but because of you.
I don't understand what you mean.
You need to get out of here.
You should leave
the Crown Prince too.
I can't
love you at all though.
I am not such a pathetic woman
who begs love
from a man who has someone else
in his heart.
Then,
why do you want to get married to me
despite this poor treatment?
For the future of my family.
Your family may prosper,
but you will become extremely lonely.
It doesn't matter.
It is just business
for the benefit of both parties.
I am not telling you to come to me.
I just want to help you
to be safe as soon as possible.
I will be leaving.
So please, pretend you don't know.
The more you know about me,
the more it is of danger to you.
Eunuch Hong.
What do you mean by that?
-Are you--
-I believe I just told you
to pretend you don't know.
It is easier said than done.
I must get going now, sir.
There is an emergency.
The one who escaped from the palace
has been arrested and
is being transported
to the Royal Investigation Bureau.
If the truth is revealed
in the courtyard...
What are you talking about?
I asked what you were talking about.
Premier Kim, we sent ten assassins
to the Crown Prince's palace.
However, only nine bodies remained.
Are you telling me that the one
who escaped has been arrested
and is in transport?
Yes, Your Lordship.
So this is not the doing of
the Baekwoon Group?
No, Your Highness.
They are named after their white masks,
and known for writing the character Woon
in their messages.
Which is why they are named
the Baekwoon Group.
I am aware.
Of course.
However, the masks are not meant to cover.
But rather to raise awareness.
To raise awareness?
That is why with every case,
marks are left representing their purpose.
How?
Like this.
WOON
No marks were found at
the Crown Prince's palace?
No, marks were not found.
Only that they attempted in
your assassination.
Your Highness, this is Byeong-yeon.
You must come with me right away.
What is the reason
for your attempted murder
of the Crown Prince?
Please spare my life.
I was only doing what I was told.
Who ordered this act of treason?
Resume the torture.
Stop immediately.
The judge is to stop the torture
and inquire once again.
Stop.
I will ask again.
Who ordered this act of treason?
Will you able to repeat this
in front of the Crown Prince?
Can I trust you?
If I do as you ask...
Yes.
This is the only way for
you and your family
to survive.
The Baekwoon Group...
Is there an insider from that night
who opened the gates
and allowed your entry?
Yes, there is.
Tell me.
There is a Baekwoon Group spy
within the palace.
Hong Gyeong-rae may be dead.
But his daughter,
possessing the same thought and values,
is here in this palace.
I heard she's planning a rebellion again.
Who is that?
It is...
Premier Kim!
He has just confessed
as a traitor to this country.
He may be a criminal,
but you have no right to execute
without the King's orders.
I had to step in due to Your Majesty's
and Your Highness's hesitation.
Executing my subject in front
of me, the Crown Prince,
is also an act of treason.
Did you not know?
If my act threatens my position as
the Premier,
you can take my life with the sword.
Your Highness, please have mercy.
-Your Highness, please have mercy.
If any group threatens the subjects,
or puts this country at risk,
it must be dealt with immediately.
That is exactly why
I cannot sheath this sword.
-Your Highness, please have mercy.
Your Highness.
Let go.
EUNUCH TRAINING INSTITUTE
Have you heard?
What?
The invader of the palace confessed...
and is apparently an act of
Hong Gyeong-rae remnants.
Did something happen at the palace?
Keep quiet and finish your meal.
I'll beat you to a pulp.
That threat message was not
just a happening.
There is a rumor...
that the daughter of Hong Gyeong-rae
is in the palace as a spy
and opened the gates for the invasion.
How dare you!
That is nonsense.
We will finish our meals.
-Are you sure?
-Of course I am.
This is me.
"I could say
I have a lover or maybe not.
Jeong Deok-ho."
Jeong Deok-ho?
Master Jeong?
Yes, you are right.
You did it again?
Jeong Deok-ho is...
me.
Are you Master Jeong?
Yes, Your Highness.
But the one you loved
is Wol-hui.
My goodness.
What do you mean?
This is ridiculous.
The one I...
The one I love is--
How dare you touch me?
I mean the one I love
-is--
-Let go of me!
It is...
Hey!
It is you.
It is you
whom I am in love with.
We found the man Chil-seong
contacted right before he died.
If we meet him,
we'll be able to confirm what information
he found out that day.
About the girl named Hong Ra-on.
is said to be in the palace now.
Yun-seong.
Yes?
What did you say Grandfather?
I told you to pay a visit to the Queen
before she delivers a child.
Okay, I will.
How did it go?
She gave birth to a baby just now,
and it is a boy.
Gag him or something
so that his cry won't be heard.
Yes, Your Highness.
Okay.
Go ahead and kick me.
Resent me and hate me as much as you want.
My goodness.
Your...
Your Highness, Official of Ministry
of Rites is here to meet you.
Welcome.
Are you okay?
Yes, I am.
What brought you
all the way here?
My grandfather wanted me to
visit you before your delivery.
Premier Kim,
is it true that you killed the criminal
while the Crown Prince
was questioning him?
Yes, Your Majesty.
That kind of absurd behavior
is not like you.
My apologies, My Majesty.
However,
as I was busy finding out
if what the criminal said was true,
I couldn't tell you about it in advance.
You mean you found out if there was
a spy in the palace indeed?
Yes.
What the criminal said was true.
And we found out who it was.
HONG RA-ON
"Hong Ra-on?"
Is this
Hong Gyeong-rae's daughter then?
Yes.
All we have to do now is find her.
They are very well aware
of the power
that the name Hong Gyeong-rae itself has
although there is just the name.
Then,
what are you going to do with Hong Ra-on?
In the name of Baekwoon Group,
I will protect her.
It is too late to wait for her decision.
-Are you going to abduct her or something?
-We can't
leave her in danger like that anymore.
Tomorrow,
I will take her to the headquarters
in secret.
When the day breaks,
a massive search will begin.
If she really is the spy
Baekwoon Group planted,
she won't be the only one.
If we keep investigating all those
who are relevant,
the palace will become bloody
for quite a while.
We should find Hong Ra-on first
and seize her.
If we hold her,
she will be of use to us.
Of course she will.
There is no doubt about it.
Were you waiting for me?
I want to ask you for a favor.
You do?
-What kind of--
-It's about her.
About Eunuch Hong?
Last time,
you saved her
against Premier Kim's will.
Please take her out of the palace.
To a place no one knows
without anyone knowing.
Can you?
When you're sitting over there,
how can I fall asleep?
You already have such sleepy eyes.
I said you don't need to
stay up all night.
I just want to look at your face
all night.
You can look at me tomorrow
as much as you want.
What you always see
and always do
sometimes
seem very precious all of a sudden.
When you think it is the last time,
you get to feel that way.
Pardon?
Yes, that is right.
All the things you thought trivial
because it happened everyday
suddenly mean a lot
if you think it is the last time.
All right then.
Okay.
Come here
to see my face.
Your Highness.
If I was...
born into a noble family
then came to you,
would you have taken me in with love?
Of course I would have.
Then
Your Highness.
If I had not
dressed up as an aristocrat that day
and went to Mongmyeoksan,
would we have been
destined to meet at all?
That is obvious as well.
I told you.
We have been destined
go around in circles
and still meet each other in the end.
Then
your Highness.
If one day,
you found out I was
the daughter of a traitor,
would you not regret
meeting me?
Would you
ever think back
and reminisce about this moment
at least once?
Ra-on.
Eunuch Hong.
Is anyone there?
Yes, Your Highness.
Have you awakened already?
Where has Eunuch Hong gone?
I have not seen him since early morning.
Your Highness. I'm glad you're here.
Why is the palace in such disorder?
Have you not heard
about the royal command?
What royal command?
Tell me the details.
There is a search for the traitors.
Have you not heard from before?
Daughter of Hong Gyeong-rae
is within the palace as a spy
from the Baekwoon Group.
They finally found
the detailed information.
What?
So they are searching among
the younger palace servants first?
Yes, Your Highness.
I understand.
You can continue with your business.
Of course.
One moment.
What is the given information?
Has the montage been released?
No montage has been revealed.
Only that she is around the age of 18,
and resided in Pyeongan-do
before the riot.
Her real name given by Hong Gyeong-rae
is Hong Ra-on.
We have called for all servants
around the age of 18...
Just now...
What did you say?
That we have called for
all servants who are 18.
No.
The name.
Do you mean Hong Ra-on?
Her name as a child was Hong Ra-on.
Of course, she would be using
a different name now.
If you will excuse me.
My Lady, what should I call you?
I'm Hong Ra-on, Your Highness.
Ra-on.