[National Radio Station]
I'm sorry, Wei.
for causing you trouble.
Don't apologize to me.
Can you tell me
what happened?
Stop!
Where did you go, little girl?
Don't worry about anything.
Go!
Get off.
Thank you.
What?
Did something happen?
They're in trouble.
What do you mean?
I'm the producer of Happy Birthday.
I was stepping on the food center.
I found a restaurant using expired ingredients
with an expired ingredient.
So I filmed it.
I think I've seen this show before.
So you're the director.
Excuse me.
It's one of the directors. It's nothing.
Hello.
Put it down at the intersection ahead.
Okay.
Okay?
No problem.
Okay.
XiangY 45831.
Be careful.
Okay.
Chief Editor.
I don't know your name yet.
You don't need to know your name.
Thank you.
Bye.
Chief Editor.
It's you.
How have you been?
It's amazing.
How did you know I work here?
It's not hard to find
It's not hard, right?
What's the matter?
Last time,
you took my ride.
You didn't even pay for gas.
Right?
I won't figure it out when I go back.
You're a great editor.
how can you treat a loyal citizen like this?
I'm really sorry.
I'll transfer it to you.
I'm just kidding.
Although I'm driving a black car,
You thought
I really drive a black car.
Let's have dinner.
Turn around.
Turn. Let's do it together.
Together.
Turn around.
Later,
just like all couples in love.
every day
every day.
I once thought
I had true love.
XiangY 45831.
Be careful.
Why is your tie crooked?
I'll pick you up after work.
Let's go.
By the way,
You
always skip breakfast.
It's bad for your stomach.
Let's go upstairs.
Let's go.
Okay.
Don't be too tired.
Drive carefully.
Okay.
Bye.
I'll pick you up.
Done.
Here.
Happy birthday.
Are you happy?
Yes.
Can I ask you to do something?
What is it?
Give me your phone.
Honey.
Happy birthday.
Thank you, honey.
Lili.
Are you really not going to sing with us?
Yes.
I'm not going.
It's my boyfriend's birthday today.
I have to keep him company.
He's so inhumane.
Okay, we're leaving.
Have fun later.
Okay, bye.
Bye.
Shameless bitch!
This is what happens when you seduce someone's husband.
I'm warning you.
Stay away from Zhou Group.
If there is a next time,
it won't be as easy as splashing mud at you.
Are you cold?
No.
What should we buy in the mall?
A birthday cake.
Birthday cake?
Do you still want your birthday gift?
Zhou Zcheng.
You're married
and have a wife and child, right?
Lili,
I didn't mean to hide it from you.
So it's true.
Why did you lie to me?
Let me explain.
Actually my relationship with her
between us.
I just...
Dad.
I thought we were going to buy a birthday cake.
Who are you talking to?
This prank call.
We won't listen. Hang it up.
It's your bad luck to meet a scumbag.
It's not your fault.
Thank you, Wei.
I know.
cyber violence is not good.
The company
will try their best to help you.
But the key is yourself.
You have to show us the evidence
to promote public opinion
and let the public know the truth.
I called him, but he didn't answer.
Where is he now?
Did you contact him later?
He's in his hometown.
How about this?
I'll go back to my hometown
and tell him face to face.
No matter what it takes,
I will get the evidence
to prove my innocence.
Normally,
when the scandal comes out,
On the first day, the netizens are celebrating.
The traffic increased.
The next day,
[The netizens start to calm down.]
[Looking forward to the twist.]
On the third day,
if we still can't get evidence,
it means the rumor is true.
the reputation of the mistress
can't be cleared.
So,
I'll give you three days at most.
PR is also efficient.
Okay?
Mr Chen.
About the sauce purple,
was deliberately exposed online.
It's not decided yet.
Do you have proof that
she's not a mistress?
A mistress?
is too sensitive now.
The netizens are all over the internet.
I won't take the risk.
As long as you can delete
from this project,
Contract.
Let's go as usual.
It's not appropriate.
It's not fair to Jangja.
She's just
who has only 300,000 fans.
Is that necessary?
Mr. Ai,
I
take responsibility for the company.
If you insist on
in this project,
I'm afraid
we can't continue our cooperation.
Mr. Chen,
How about this?
Give me three days.
Just three days.
In three days,
in three days.
Is this okay?
Okay.
This is the greatest respect
for Mr. Ai Wei.
Thank you.
Why are you here?
I came to see you.
Me?
Lili.
We've broken up.
Why are you looking for me?
You should have seen the rumors online.
They said I was a mistress.
Can you clarify it for me?
When we are together,
when we were together.
I didn't know you were married.
Are you kidding me?
You want me
to report myself?
You're too naive.
You deceived my feelings.
Isn't it too much to clarify it for me?
Let me tell you.
You can find anyone who splashed mud at you.
It has nothing to do with me.
Zhou Jicheng.
I won't leave if you don't help me.
Are you crazy?
Just stay here.
Zhou Zcheng.
I don't want to disturb your life.
But
can you help me
please help me.
Just admit that
you were in a hidden marriage.
It won't affect you.
But it's important to me.
Lili.
I know it's hard for you to break up.
It's hard for me too.
But you can't change the truth.
You know I have a family.
You
seduced me.
How did it become
I hid my marriage
to deceive you?
You...
I'm sorry. I got a little excited.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
You can say anything.
As long as you're happy.
Really.
As long as you're happy,
But you have to know
our love and ours
is over.
As an adult,
Stop pestering me.
Take care.
Moving and pulling goods to us. Professional organization.
Move and pull goods to us.
Come to us.
Lili.
I didn't know you were coming back today.
We've had dinner.
This dish...
I heat it up for you again.
Make do with it.
It's good.
Thank you.
Well,
It's been half a year.
Who is so bad and dug it out?
How could you twist the truth?
How annoying.
It's a big tree.
I'm famous now.
Find some marketing accounts to hype up.
I heard that someone is receiving money
to dig up scandals.
Yes.
You know what?
In our industry,
in our industry.
Such a filthy thing.
That's normal?
Seriously.
Look.
When you eat fish,
there must be fish bones.
The bigger the fish is,
the bigger the thorns.
It's because I'm popular, right?
Who else would do that to me?
Many of my classmates know you.
Really?
Lili,
What are you going to do next?
I'm here to see Zhou Zcheng.
and ask him to clarify it for me.
The company will clarify it for me.
Can he make it public?
If he refuses,
I can always think of a way.
There are always more ways than difficulties.
Right?
Yes.
Lili.
Have you
to Luo?
Did he misunderstand you?
I made it clear.
Just make it clear.
so that there won't be any misunderstanding
and affect your relationship.
Don't worry.
The food at home tastes better.
Eat more.
Eat up.
There's going to be a twist.
Ladies and gentlemen,
please give us some time.
OK?
Then we've missed such a good topic.
Of course we will clarify it.
How about this?
After this,
after this.
Okay, I agree.
Okay.
Thank you, mentors.
Vivi.
Don't you worry that
Aren't you worried that she's lying to you?
What if she's really a mistress?
I trust her.
Thank you.
Missy.
You deserve it.
That's right.
People like him should be sentenced.
Seriously.
No way
In this era,
in this era?
What are you thinking?
Yeah.
What era is there a mistress?
Isn't it nice to find a man?
You're so young.
Can't you be a good girl?
Who is she?
He looks good.
What did he do?
I know.
I think she did it on purpose.
Is it fun?
Is it only exciting to be a mistress?
We brought you up
to make you a mistress?
You're embarrassing women.
Exactly.
Those who ruin other's family deserve to die.
How are you doing?
Have you found the evidence?
No.
I found Zhou Jicheng.
He doesn't want to clarify it for me.
I have to go to Zhongtian Culture tomorrow
to ask their leader
to see if there is any new breakthrough.
Do me a favor.
What is it?
In the drawer on the right side of my desk,
on my desk.
Send it to me.
I want to see
if there's any useful information inside.
Don't worry.
Thank you.
I'll send you the address.
Bye.
Fresh juice is ready
What are you doing?
Are you speaking for your classmates?
Yes.
I've clarified it for her.
Look at these netizens.
They don't believe it.
She even said I'm a marketing account to get her attention.
You did everything you could.
They can say whatever they want.
Just ignore them.
But look.
Look.
This one
received a lot of attention.
Many people asked me
what brand my clothes are.
Look at this.
Someone asked me what color my lipstick was.
I received over 700 likes this night.
Over 800 comments.
That's a lot.
Of course.
So many people have good taste.
Great.
Xiao.
Why did you buy so many things again?
I'm going to be a dressing blogger.
So,
buy some clothes and bags
for matching.
Are you serious?
Of course.
You saw it just now.
I have so many supporters.
It means I'm still
a potential dressing blogger.
Since
you went to your reunion last time,
and became a blogger.
Why?
What do you mean why?
Why can't I?
Because you have three minutes of passion.
You are interested in this
and then that.
In the end,
in the end.
What do you mean?
My husband supports everything other's wife does.
I didn't ask you to spend money or help you.
Why are you so mean to me?
I'm not.
I'm afraid you'll be shocked.
Because you're not suitable.
What do you mean?
Do you think
I'm not suitable for anything?
That's not what I meant.
I mean...
Stop messing around.
Stay at home.
and do nothing.
I can support you.
Let me ask you.
Do you support me?
You're really not suitable.
If you don't support me, someone will support me.
Aunt.
What's wrong?
Did you fight with Jintian again?
Yes.
Why?
I told him I wanted to be a dressing blogger.
He said I was not suitable.
and he keeps giving me cold water.
Why do you suddenly want to do this?
I've always liked it.
What kind of dressing do I usually wear?
I'm quite interested in cosmetics.
I might as well be a dressing blogger.
Aunt.
How about
ask your company to run it for me?
I think
Jintian is right.
You're not suitable.
Why?
I know you well.
Why don't you support me?
Be good.
I have a phone conference.
Let's play outside.
Go.
I saw it.
Uncle.
Xiao.
How's your hand?
Just so so.
Take your medicine.
Physiotherapy, rehabilitation.
Don't worry.
With the advanced medical skills,
It will definitely be cured.
By the way, uncle,
let me tell you.
I went to visit my aunt that day.
We were shocked when we knew about this.
But luckily, the hospital said
you were not in danger.
Do you know
When the show was about to start,
she looked calm on the surface.
But her hands are trembling all over her body.
Really?
Yes.
She was so nervous after cutting the phone.
We were so scared.
Wait a minute.
I'll get you something to drink.
Is bubble water okay?
Sure, uncle.
Thank you, uncle.
What did you mean just now?
After she answered the phone,
she went to the hospital
to the hospital.
No.
I have to go.
I have something to do. I'll talk to you later.
What's wrong?
Tell me.
What happened?
What do you mean?
Xiao told me everything.
On the day of my accident,
you received a call from the hospital first.
But you're still doing the live stream.
I spent five minutes
to finish the live stream.
and rushed to the hospital immediately.
I didn't expect
But you didn't get to the hospital immediately.
Do you know
If it weren't for you,
hadn't come to sign,
My hand won't be delayed.
I won't be able to recover until today.
I rushed to the hospital right after the live stream.
I didn't expect such serious traffic to happen.
I couldn't control myself.
All right.
If you insist,
Is there a minute
have you ever
even for a minute?
I thought of how I felt
his hand was broken.
what does it mean to him?
I know you're having a hard time.
But I really didn't expect
this would happen.
After my live stream,
Enough.
You only care about yourself.
Only your fans' fame and status.
Is there anything more important than that?
It's not like that.
Why not?
That's it.
I was wondering
you've been so gentle to me at home.
and caring?
I thought it was true.
Turns out it's all fake.
You're nice to me
just to make you feel better.
Vivi.
I finally see you clearly today.
You're too selfish.
Mr Luo.
Do you remember me?
It's you.
Long time no see.
Hello.
Here's the thing.
I came to you
to ask you for a favor.
When Zhoucheng was with me,
he was already married.
You should know that.
Can you
say something fair for me?
I'm sorry.
I can't help you.
Mr Luo.
This incident has ruined
and career.
The netizens are calling me a mistress.
But I'm the one who was cheated.
I'm a victim.
Please help me.
Jiang Li.
Why are you here again?
Mr Luo.
I'll
I'll take care of it.
Go ahead.
Mr Luo.
Zhou Zcheng.
Are you done?
You lied to my feelings
and made me a mistress for no reason.
I found someone to clear my name.
What's wrong with me?
Jiang Li.
I'm warning you.
I don't have time to talk to you now.
Leave now.
If you don't leave,
I'll call security.
Call security.
I won't leave.
Let go.
Okay.
Looking for help?
Who are you?
You don't need to know who I am.
I punched her for her.
Okay.
I'll remember you.
I remember you.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Why are you here?
You haven't told me why you're here.
Well...
My company sent me to Changde for market research.
I'm here to give you a phone.
to save money for delivery.
to do market research in Chang De.
Of course.
I can send it to you myself.
You wish.
If you feel bad,
pay me the travel expenses.
Okay, no problem.
What's wrong?
Does the content in the phone work?
Nothing useful.
It's over. There's only one day left.
There's no progress.
Don't worry.
I'll help you.
Just do your work.
I'll figure it out.
I've been here for days.
I'm not worried about the city investigation.
How about this?
Think about it.
Who else knows about this?
can come out and clarify it for you?
except the person involved.
who knows the truth.
They don't want to get involved.
Well...
Joo Ji Sung's wife.
Does she know?
Probably.
She's hostile to me.
Anyway,
she's a family.
Even if she was deceived by Zhou Jicheng,
she won't testify for me.
Let me tell you.
In probability,
probability
Only zero.
to the closed area.
There's no negative number.
Even if it's one in a million,
it's still possible.
AVRI
Are you happy today?
Yes.
I'll take you to play next time, okay?
It's you.
What are you doing?
Can we talk alone?
What do you want?
To clear up the misunderstanding.
Jeong-il.
Can you wait for me upstairs?
There's no misunderstanding between us.
Don't you know
Zhoucheng cheated others
to cheat others?
What?
Do you think Joo Jae-sung is secretly married?
Are you kidding me?
I'm sorry for hurting you.
But he really fooled us.
You seduced my husband.
Now you're going to blame him.
Shame on you!
I'm telling the truth. I have a clear conscience.
You criticized me before.
I just want you to know the truth
and clear my name.
Alright.
I'm warning you.
Don't appear in my life again.
What should I do?
Don't worry.
She must be brainwashed by Zhoucheng.
Our priority now
is to find a way to let her know the truth.
Wei,
Have you seen the news about Wei Wei?
Yes.
It's so fake. It's obviously a pose.
It's just a couple.
Lu Li's best show.
It's less than half a month before we get the investment fund.
Lu Li obviously wants to take his last gamble.
Should we spend money
to remove the trending topic?
it'll be a real relationship.
and put them in trouble.
Wait for Myeongja.
When she clarifies,
we can cooperate with Mei Duo.
After we get the plan with her,
the investment fund
Lu Li will be completely out.
There's only this little time.
Do you think this will work?
Hello?
How is it going over there?
Not yet.
Hurry up.
Otherwise, it will be confirmed.
I'll be quick.
Wait for her.
Mr. Ai,
You just promoted a newcomer.
You got skinned so soon.
I'm a bit unlucky.
You're happy.
She'll prove her innocence.
She's a mistress.
The people online hate the most
is this kind of people.
Can she prove her innocence?
Although you don't like
the CP in my hand.
But at least
we can win.
It's too early
is still too early.
Okay.
Let's wait and see.
Zhou Zongcheng.
Jiang Li.
What's wrong with you?
You keep pestering me.
What do you want?
I want to talk to you alone.
Again?
Where are you hiding the recorder?
Even if you leave today,
I'll stick to you like Ha Ram.
You know my temper.
This is the last time I'm looking for you.
There's no recording.
Today's conversation is only between you and me.
Okay.
Go ahead.
Lu Li went to Meoduo's headquarters with his team.
It's not time yet.
It's not the appointed time yet.
Mr. Chen won't choose to leave light.
They must have a plan.
The scandal between Wei Wei and Zhang Zi Hyun
It's getting more and more popular.
If we don't do it today,
the light will be incorporated and replaced.
One thousand and one night is all your effort.
It's too risky for you to take the risk.
Jjangja.
Chen Haofeng.
Yu Feifei.
Singer of Ten Songs.
Young Uhan
Li.
Spider man.
Guest Bing
Class B.
Excuse me.
Zhao Liang.
Li Nan.
Wang Jia.
Ge Yu.
Ma Simbo.
Chen Dayue.
Zheng Tian Ye.
Liang Youbin.
Kwok Man-yun.
Li Na.
Cheng Cong.
Yao Qi Zheng.
Xin Yubo.
Director.
Team B director.
Team B.
Executive director.
Vice director.
Set up.
Assistant Coordinator.
Remember.
Director assistant.
Team B.
Project Manager.
and actors.
Actor selection director.
Actor assistant director.
Vice director.
Photographer.
Photographer assistant
Focuser.
and the plane.
Mobile team leader.
Mobile assistant.
Lighting guidance.
Lighting Daisuke.
[Follower]
Side shot.
Executive Producer.
Director.
Director of Drama.
Live Producer.
Office producer.
An external assistant.
Producer assistant.
Car Supervisor.
Life assistant.
Manager of the field.
Director...
Art guidance.
Execute art.
Sub-art.
The layout
Arts for the play.
Fair design.
Live art.
Fair art.
Props team leader.
Vice-captain of the props.
Props purchase.
Focus on the scene.
Set-up monitor.
Props.
Production of props
Production of props oil.
Props coordination.
styling instructor.
Makeup instructor.
Costume team leader.
Costume assistant.
Team B's fashion focus.
tailor.
Makeup team leader.
Makeup assistant.
Hair styling assistant.
The focus of the hairstyle.
Recording assistant.
The recording team leader.
DIT data management.
DIT Project Director.
LED materials collection.
LED project summary.
[JCB1]
Editor.
The post-production editing.
Project Director.
Set-up art team leader.
Scene set, art team leader.
Scene art.
Liu, Jiang, Li Linfei.
Project Manager.
Project Producer.
Project assistant.
DI Procedure.
Color maker.
subtitles.
Digital engineer.
Visual Director.
Division effect.
Late-stage sound coordination.
Visual effect producer.
Producer.
Producer director.
Digital grapher.
Synthesis Director.
Administrative support.
Voice Production Director.
Voice guidance.
ADR recorder.
Effect production.
Foley director.
Foley.
A dubber?
Music Director.
Project manager.
"Despicable".
Chae-qi Wu.
Pass the music.
"A Little Courage".
Marcel.
White.
Pass the music.
Di Wei.
Wu Caiqi.
Zhi Shuang.
Liu Chuan Bo.
Bai.
Yu Zilu.
Pass the music.
Wu Caiqi.
Xiao Chase Lee.
Liu Chuan Bo.
One in a billion.
Bai.
Yang Rui Jia.
Yu Zilu.
Wu Chaiqi.
Yang Rui Jia.
Xiao, Chase Lee.
Chu Sanjin.
Feng Shi.
Liu Chuan Bo.
Wu Caiqi.
I Want To Be With You.
Wu Chaiqi.
Xiao Chase Lee.
The 100 kinds of anger of neighbors
"Qianmeng Mark".
Xiao Chase Lee.
Salt Seabreeze.