(Moonlit Reunion)
(Episode 22)
(Chang Ming)
Sect Leader.
Zhu Yu.
Shuang Jiang had told us all about your experience
in the Arcane Appraisal Bureau.
After your trip to Chang'an,
not only did you help your bureau solve mysterious cases
and capture demons,
but you also found the Demon City.
You didn't let us down.
I appreciate your effort.
So, the Demon City does exist within Chang'an, huh?
Indeed. But I was only able to remain there briefly.
I still have no way to enter the Demon City yet.
You've already done a lot by yourself.
At least we can prove that the info we've received was true.
But I hear that Chang'an is rife with rumors
related to bat demons and ink tigers.
The Demon City is filled with heinous demons indeed.
It seems that our journey down the mountain
is imminent.
Sect Leader, you're right.
We need to leave our sect and vanquish the demons.
I've prepared many anti-demon arrays.
That's right. We can't allow them to run amok again.
Let's descend the mountain and vanquish them now.
That's right.
Everyone.
The incident with the ink tigers has nothing to do with the Demon City.
It was caused by men.
Men?
Zhu Yu, what are you saying?
How could such man-made incidents summon demons?
It was caused by men.
Zhu Yu, what do you mean?
Someone cultivated demonic arts.
He commanded ink demons to summon lesser demons to gain a profit.
I encountered him.
Seniors, the sect decides
whether you guys will descend the mountain or not.
I shouldn't interfere.
However, the Demon City isn't behind the incident with the ink tigers.
Demonic arts?
Since there are no demons running amok in Chang'an,
should we still descend the mountain?
It seems like there's no rush.
I can use this time to prepare more arrays just in case anything happens.
Sect Leader, what do you think?
You're right.
It's impossible for us to annihilate the Demon City in one day.
Naturally, we have to plan this through.
All right. We shall set this aside for now.
Since Zhu Yu has returned,
I have one more thing to discuss with you all.
Zhu Yu is Master's favorite disciple.
He's naturally gifted and skilled in arcane arts.
And now, he knows the Demon City better than any of us.
I wish to promote him to Head Administrator
so that he can assist me in managing Changxi Palace.
Him?
Is he even worthy?
Do not speak such nonsense.
Sect Leader, I'm still inexperienced.
Please rescind your order and appoint another candidate.
Zhu Yu, you have concerns. I understand that.
- But I...   - Sect Leader.
Actually, I came back for two reasons.
Firstly, it's to explain the incident with the ink tigers.
Secondly, I came back
to receive my punishment.
Receive punishment?
What punishment?
Master taught me and raised me up.
In the future, if Changxi Palace needs any help, I'll do my best to help.
I won't forget about my mission all these years as well.
However,
when I was living in Chang'an,
I fell for someone.
I had feelings for another person.
Seniors, please grant me my wish.
Please allow me to kick myself out of the sect and marry her.
I wish to be with her forever.
(Master, if you were still around,)
(I wonder if you would be disappointed to see the current me.)
Young boy, did you desire it?
- What do you want to do with it?   - I'll eat it.
What did you say? Did you say you want to eat it?
It's been so long since I had meat.
But you captured it first.
I suppose it's yours.
Young boy.
Although you're young, you do behave like a gentleman.
Since we've met each other, I suppose fate has led us here.
I'll give you some guidance today.
Brilliant spirit, revealed! All evils shall be vanquished!
Look. This isn't a wild chicken.
This is a pheasant spirit that has committed countless evils.
You're quite bold, aren't you?
It seems you have great potential.
Are you hungry?
Why didn't you have your fill?
My parents died.
I'm living in the manor alone.
Another orphan, huh?
Is there no one else in the manor?
There is.
But...
But no one cared about you.
If that's the case, wouldn't it be better for you to follow me?
Consider my proposal.
Be my disciple, and I'll prepare roasted pheasant for you.
Be your disciple? What's your occupation?
You're quite the cautious kid, huh?
I'm Si Qing, a Celestial Master of Changxi Palace.
What does Changxi Palace do?
It's a great place.
We exorcise demons, capture spirits, and dispel misfortunes.
It's a place for doing good deeds.
Master.
(I've failed you, Master.)
(Although I intend to practice the way of our sect,)
(I went against the sect rules as I'd fallen for someone.)
Master, what are you eating?
Zhu Yu, I was thinking that you would come back at this time
after your sword practice at Shuiqin.
This is Beggar's Chicken. It's piping hot.
Here.
Zhu Yu, eat up.
What's wrong?
I came across this the other day while reading.
It states that cultivators must restrain their desires for food and drink.
Strange. You were a cute boy before this.
But why are you getting more and more dull?
I know you're pure and have few desires.
And, you're a talented cultivator.
But you're too obsessed with sticking to the book and rules.
What about this?
I'll give you a lesson.
Let me ask you this. What is the Way?
According to the books, there's the Way of Heaven,
the Way of Earth, and the Way of Man.
Those are the three natural Ways.
One attains the Way only by not contending, not seizing,
remaining tranquil, and having a mind free of attachments.
If so, why do you cultivate the Way yourself?
You don't even know why you're cultivating the Way, huh?
The methods of your cultivation are, in truth, nothing but nonsense.
Everyone has their own Way to attain.
Take me as an example.
I crave roasted chicken every day.
But will that affect me from managing Changxi Palace? It won't.
It won't impede me from slaying demons as well.
So,
Master, what do you think I should do to attain the Way?
That'll depend on yourself.
There's no need to rush.
To attain the Way, you must first cultivate the mind.
The Way follows nature, as one acts in accordance with one's heart.
As for your Way, you can take your time looking for it
after finishing this roasted chicken.
Eat up.
It's delicious, isn't it?
Thank you, Master.
You should eat.
I still have some left.
Zhu Yu.
You've never left Changxi Palace ever since you came here as a child.
It's only human for you to be bewitched by the splendor of Chang'an.
If you're willing to turn over a new leaf,
I'll treat it as if nothing had happened.
One's feelings emanate from the heart.
How can I change it?
Since I've already fallen for her,
if I admit fault against my conscience today,
when I have to face a life-or-death situation,
you would never believe
that I would seek not to protect myself
and abandon righteousness for survival.
You still haven't repented even though you've knelt here for days.
If that's the case, as the Sect Leader,
there's no way I can defend you again.
According to the rules of Changxi Palace,
if one wishes to leave the sect,
one has to enter the White Night Array
and be punished by the White Night Birds.
After that, they shall be unrelated to the sect.
Thank you, Sect Leader.
He's a traitor. We should've annulled his cultivation.
Sect Leader, why are you still trying to defend him?
He's Master's favorite disciple. I've nurtured him as well.
Who would've expected him to do such a thing?
Since I'm the Sect Leader, I cannot practice favoritism.
Sect Leader, you've already given him a chance.
Now, he's bewitched by an outsider. That's ridiculous.
It'll be impossible to uphold proper conduct if you practice favoritism.
Are you sure Zhu Yu can do it?
Changxi Palace has always been fair and just.
Now, Zhu Yu had confessed to his crime and insisted on leaving.
No one can side with him.
But Brother Ming is...
Indeed. If other people were to have the same thought,
they would've been cast into the White Night Array immediately.
Brother Ming actually gave him a few days
so that he could reflect upon his actions.
But the sect rules must be obeyed.
Is Zhu Yu going to...
Don't worry. The White Night Array won't kill him.
But he'll definitely suffer.
I’ve heard that being pierced by the White Night Birds is excruciating.
A century ago, another disciple also wanted to leave the sect.
After going through the punishment, his injuries never healed.
In the end, he took his own life because of the pain.
This...
Tomorrow, once Zhu Yu steps into the array,
the White Night Birds will come. They're sentient.
Brother Lu Yang, do you have any other questions?
No, I don't.
You've explained everything there is to it.
If so, let's head back.
Okay.
Cat Lord is going to get married!
Do you guys know this? Cat Lord is going to get married!
- She's going to get married?   - To whom?
I heard that she's going to be married to a mortal.
A mortal?
Even Cat Lord is going to get married.
When will you marry me?
Cat Lord, I heard that you were granted a marriage in the Mortal Realm.
Is that true?
Strange.
You guys spend your days in the Demon City.
Where did you receive such news from the Mortal Realm?
The walls have ears, you know?
I've already heard about it. You just need to answer my question.
So what if it's true? So what if it isn't?
I'm the one getting married here.
What has this got to do with you all?
Naturally, your marriage is related to the Demon Market.
No Cat Lord has gotten married to a mortal since ancient times.
Indeed.
Your marriage to a mortal is inappropriate.
You mustn't do it.
Tell me, then. What's inappropriate about it?
Which line in this demon law states
that the Cat Lord cannot marry?
This has never been done since the founding of the Demon City.
Does that mean I cannot do it?
My lord, ever since you assumed the position of Cat Lord,
you've always gone against everyone else.
You always wish to blaze a new trail.
But there's no way every attempt can yield a good result.
Elder Jin Men, look at what you're saying.
It's as if you've been holding a grudge against Cat Lord for a long time.
Indeed.
I was rude just now.
Since none of you have any objections,
- I shall...   - My lord.
I object.
Do you not care about my opinions?
Lord Shu.
I'll bear the responsibility for my own decisions.
Even if it's the wrong decision, I'll take charge of it.
No one can decide my fate for me.
Lord Shu, perhaps you should clarify where you stand.
If so, after your marriage, will the Demon City...
Everyone, don't worry.
The Demon City must not be spoken of to mortals. That is the rule.
It'll be the same.
I am willing to experience what others go through
to truly feel it for myself.
(Duke Wu's Residence)
Zhen.
Zhen, is that you?
Zhen!
I heard you.
What? You think you're seeing a ghost this early in the day?
So, you know that it's early morning as well, huh?
You're actually reading instead of sleeping?
And, it's an indecent...
Wait. It's actually a decent one.
This is my personal experience.
One has to read in order to lead a good life.
Why are you sighing?
What's Mei Zhu Yu's true intention?
He said he had to return to Quzhou. But why hasn't he returned yet?
Could it be that he’s deceiving you and pretending
to be courteous while hiding his true intentions?
In reality, he ran away and he's never coming back.
Pretending to be courteous and hiding one's true intention?
That's your usual trick.
- Me?   - Did you forget
how you used to deal with those who asked for your hand?
Zhen.
It's not that I'm not confident in you.
But you see...
Even the master said
those who commit too many misdeeds will face retribution.
They'll be struck by lightning!
Father, can't you be optimistic about me for once?
He'll return.
He said he would return in ten days.
But today's already the 12th day.
He's right.
It's already the 12th day.
Zhu Yu?
Zhu Yu.
It’s all my fault. I was confined for so long.
Only now am I being released.
After I was released, I heard about you.
I was so flustered.
I heard that you haven't eaten anything since you started kneeling.
Therefore, I brought you some buns. You should have some.
No need for that.
Zhu Yu, are you sure you want to leave the sect?
Since I've broken my vow, I must make a choice.
Moreover, she's still waiting for me.
What's so good about that vixen?
Is she truly worth all the sacrifices you've made?
She is.
She's worth it.
I don't understand at all.
I was just like you once.
I once thought that the purpose of my life was to uncover past events
and to slay demons.
For the past 18 years,
this thought presses upon my heart every single moment.
Apart from this obsession,
I find no joy in this world,
nor any expectations.
I once thought that I would lead a life like this until death.
Until I met her.
Do you know the scene when I first saw her?
That day,
I returned to Chang'an.
The way she looked on horseback,
I could never forget about it.
After that, she started pestering me.
When I was alone,
I once thought to myself
that it might be fate.
Zhu Yu, all these years, I felt like
we weren't truly close even though we looked close.
I feel that you were aloof and indifferent.
I...
I never expected you to fret over such an affair.
How dare I speak of being aloof when I haven't experienced the world yet?
With her existence,
it made me think that the worldly realm wasn't as bad as I thought.
Besides reminiscing about the past,
I finally longed for the future.
I started to have desires.
Therefore, I think she's worth all of my sacrifices.
I can't allow my beloved
to stay in Chang'an as it's dangerous.
I have to head back and protect her.
I mustn't let what happened 18 years ago repeat itself.
According to the sect rules,
if one wishes to leave the sect, one has to enter the White Night Array
and be punished by the White Night Birds.
After that, they may leave.
Zhu Yu, no weapons are allowed
in the White Night Array.
What the heck is this array?
Zhu Yu, are you sure you can withstand this?
Physical pain
means nothing to me.
Brother Ming, there are too many birds.
All these birds will pierce through his body? How can he endure that?
The White Night Array has been activated.
No one can stop it.
Zhu Yu!
It's finally over.
What's going on?
I've never seen a second punishment before? Did something go wrong?
Mind your words. It's an array filled with divine birds.
They do not commit mistakes.
This is strange. I suppose it's the wrath of Heaven.
Zhu Yu has fainted!
Zhu Yu, wake up!
They can't punish him for the third time.
Zhu Yu will die from this!
Yeah. Twice is already harsh enough.
How could they punish him again?
You have ten days.
(With a righteous heart and pure intent, all obstacles can be overcome!)
Is that the Changxi Truncheon?
Boss, why are you doing the rounds together with me today?
Shu has taken leave. Now, you have to manage the Ruyi Pavilion
and his bookstore as well.
It's tough on you.
As your boss, I feel sorry for you.
My home is too chaotic. I don't want to stay home.
Is the duke still worried about Mr. Mei's promise of return?
Say, why hasn't he returned yet?
Could he be in trouble?
With his capabilities, I don't think he'll be in trouble.
But what if he doesn't want to return of his own accord?
Boss, are you sure you can remain composed?
What else do you think I should do?
Cause a ruckus?
It seems Cat Lord has truly fallen for him.
Come and place your bets.
Place your bets!
It's been so many days.
Commissioner Mei hasn't returned yet.
In my opinion, it's obvious enough.
I'm sure he ran away from the marriage.
We're veterans, you know?
We know that the best.
- Indeed.   - Don't you agree?
My bet is that he ran away from marriage.
I'll bet on this.
That gambling house has started a new round of betting.
They're betting on whether Mr. Mei will return for the marriage or not.
Let's go and place our bets too.
If he doesn't return, at least we'll make a fortune.
We won't incur any losses.
Boss?
He has definitely run away from marriage.
Here comes a young lady. Come.
(Run Away From Marriage)
(Will Return)
Lady, don't hesitate.
It's been over ten days since Mr. Mei's departure.
I'm sure he doesn't want to marry her.
Of course that's the case.
Bet on this.
Bet on this. You'll surely win.
What's wrong?
Lady, do you think Mr. Mei will return?
I just hope that he'll return as soon as possible.
I want him to return early.
He won't.
She'll definitely lose.
She'll lose all of her money.
Come.
This is my bet!
Zhu Yu!
Zhu Yu, wake up.
This is...
It's harrowing indeed.
I've only heard of them before. Today's my first time seeing these birds.
Zhu Yu.
Be gentle.
He's still alive?
How is that possible?
From now on, you're no longer a member of Changxi Palace.
Seniors, thank you for taking care of me all these years.
May all of you be safe and joyful.
May you all lead a life with no worries.
Zhu Yu.
It's a harsh punishment.
Why don't you rest here for a few days before leaving?
That won't do.
Since he's no longer a member, he cannot rest and recuperate here.
No need for that.
I made a promise with someone from Chang'an.
I'm in a hurry to head back.
I won't rest and recuperate here.
Fine.
But before you leave,
there's one last thing you must do.
You have to leave the Changxi Truncheon behind.
Indeed. Master has left that behind for you.
But he left it behind
for his disciple at Changxi Palace.
It's not for someone who has abandoned his sect
because of a woman, Mei Zhu Yu.
Indeed. Changxi Truncheon belongs to Changxi Palace.
You have to leave it behind.
Is the chicken ready?
Master, I haven't finished my homework yet.
Do you think I'm asking you to do it for free?
Of course there's something in it for you.
Roast the chicken.
What's in it for me?
I'll trade my artifact for a roasted chicken.
Master, this truncheon belongs to you.
You should take it. How could you give it to me?
I'm old now. I have to make arrangements for the future.
But Master...
It's just a joke.
My internal injury hasn't fully recovered
ever since my battle with that demon three months ago.
I assume it's because of my age.
I'm giving the Changxi Truncheon to you as a form of entrustment.
From now on, I'll entrust the demon-slaying duties to you.
Master, even if you wish to entrust this artifact to someone,
it shouldn't be me.
Brother Ming is the official successor.
That has nothing to do with the Changxi Truncheon.
It's just an artifact.
We merely use them to slay demons.
Moreover, your senior is diligent and upright.
He won't mind it.
The duties of a Celestial Master should never be dictated by a truncheon.
I hope even more that you take it to explore the world
and experience the bonds and affairs of the Mortal Realm.
Here, take it.
Give it a try.
It hasn't acknowledged you as its new owner yet.
You must communicate with it wholeheartedly.
Not bad.
Not bad at all.
Now, it's truly yours.
I know.
Changxi Truncheon is a keepsake of Master's.
You can't bear to part with it.
But it belongs to Changxi Palace after all.
You have to look at the bigger picture.