(Moonlit Reunion)
(Episode 23)
I know.
Changxi Truncheon is a keepsake of Master's.
You can't bear to part with it.
But it belongs to Changxi Palace after all.
You have to look at the bigger picture.
Brother Chang Ming, you...
You're just pouring salt on his wound.
I wish to leave the sect, and I'll accept any punishment for that.
That doesn't mean I'm going to cast away my duties as a Celestial Master.
Slaying demons
and getting rid of evil are still my goals in life.
It's just that there's someone I need to protect now.
Zhu Yu...
Zhu Yu, don't worry.
Master said that Brother Chang Ming is hardworking and upright.
I'm sure he's the most suitable wielder of Changxi Truncheon.
If so, I'll entrust it to you, Sect Leader.
There's one more thing. Although you're leaving the sect,
you grew up here after all.
You need to make a vow before leaving.
Once you leave this gate,
you're not to mention a single word about Changxi Palace.
All right.
I hereby swear
that I won't tell anyone about Changxi Palace.
If not, you'll lose your loved ones and come to a bad end.
If not,
I'll lose my loved ones and come to a bad end.
Congratulations on getting what you want.
The matter is over.
You may go now.
I'll see him off.
No need for that.
Shuang Jiang, you should head back.
I'll see him off.
But you...
Right now, he's no match for you.
Don't worry. I'm just chasing him away.
I won't take his life.
You can have this horse.
Hurry and return to Chang'an.
Brother Xiao Mu, apart from cultivation, your only interests are horses.
Why would you grant me your favorite steed?
I just want you to leave quickly and never come back.
You and I were distant since young.
Why did you help me out when I was in the White Night Array?
I don't know why you joined Changxi Palace.
I joined it to cultivate my skills.
Since it's a place of cultivation, no blood must be shed there.
Thank you.
Zhu Yu, why are you standing there?
Master, I have something to ask you.
Ask away.
Master, you gave all nine of my seniors a Daoist name.
I'm the only one using my real name.
I heard from Brother Lu Yang that I was different from them.
I'm not considered one of your official disciples.
Therefore, I'm not an official member of Changxi Palace.
Master, is that true?
About that...
Seems like it's true.
Master, why didn't you give me a Daoist name?
Zhu Yu, don't misunderstand me.
I didn't give you a Daoist name because I made a divination.
I know that you'll leave our sect eventually.
Master, don't you intend to make me stay?
Changxi Palace cannot keep you here.
You have an obsession that you haven't gotten over.
That means you have unfinished business.
What I can do is to lend you a hand in overcoming your obstacles.
You have to return to the origin to finish your unfinished business.
In this world, everyone has desires.
What your seniors desire is here.
But your desire isn't.
It seems that certain matters and certain people
are finally about to surface.
Benefactor! It's actually you!
You're finally willing to see me again.
Benefactor, please help me.
How can I help you?
Please teach me your spells.
I still have my left eye and all of my limbs.
Benefactor, I can still practice the suppression technique.
I can help you accomplish many things.
You couldn't even complete the menial task I assigned.
Now, you want me to teach you?
That's a total waste of my time.
I've already released the ink demons into Chang'an and completed your task.
But there were unexpected occurrences.
I've already tried my best. Benefactor, please try to understand me.
But what I want is to stir up rumors in Chang'an about a demon uprising.
I need a proper excuse to bring my men to Chang'an.
But I've already accomplished the task as per your instructions.
It's all because you provoked that fellow outside Chang'an.
That's why he disobeyed my order and kept an eye on you in Chang'an.
Pei Ji Ya, you ruined my plan. How dare you still come to me?
- I... - What a fool.
You're truly useless.
Benefactor!
You can't just burn your bridges!
Mr. Pei, you can't blame me for this.
You can only blame yourself for this.
You couldn't even complete such a menial task.
I'm already generous enough to allow you to live.
Now, you're half-blind, and you no longer have dark magic.
Scram. Never come to me again.
This won't do!
Sect Leader Chang Ming, you promised that you would help me to be stronger.
If you don't help me out,
I'll head to Changxi Palace and find the other Celestial Masters.
By then, if I blurt out something I wasn't supposed to,
your position as the sect leader will...
Fine. Since you want to die,
I can only take it as if I've never saved you before.
Hey! You're a Celestial Master!
I've given you plenty of benefits as well!
So what?
Useless fool.
It's you?
Mr. Pei, long time no see.
You were the one who killed Wu and Zhen!
That kind of trash is not even worthy of calling her name.
I knew that you would find the person who taught you dark magic.
I never expected you
to wait here for days
without even being able to see him.
Forget about you. Even if I was anxious for you.
You planned everything in advance, huh?
What exactly do you want?
I don't want anything.
Since I've found the mastermind, it's pointless to keep you alive.
Naturally, I'll get rid of you.
Are you going to kill me?
Just look at you.
I think your current expression fits you better.
No matter how pretentious you were,
did you think your cousin had spared you one more glance?
No wonder you were anxious when we were by Lin'an River.
If you're interested in Zhen, you should target Mei Zhu Yu.
I'm not your rival.
Even if you kill me, you won't be able to obtain her.
I'm not trying to kill you because I fancy her.
It's because you were bold enough to drug her at Ruyi Pavilion.
I won't allow such despicable men to appear in front of her again.
What are you laughing at?
Initially, I thought that it was already hilarious enough
to see a weak mortal like me lose everything
after devoting all of my efforts.
I never expected to see someone more laughable than me.
What do you mean?
Although you're powerful, you still couldn't win Zhen's heart.
Your only choice is to vent out your anger on weaklings like us.
You're no better than me.
I may be laughable, but you're ridiculous yourself.
I was laughing at myself and you.
How dare you put yourself at the same level as me?
I was born a cripple. I didn't have an expertise either.
Even if I live, I'll only be a laughingstock. That's pointless.
Forget it.
It is said that a dying person's words should be kind.
I have a piece of advice for you.
A piece of advice?
What is it?
Naturally, it's for you not to imitate me.
There's nothing wrong with struggling to make a living.
But if you're too cunning and greedy,
you'll bite off more than you can chew.
You'll lose your body, conscience, your beloved,
and yourself.
You think you've won. But in reality, you're worse than I.
Such nonsense!
In your current state, Zhen will never fall for you.
She'll hate you instead.
Shut up!
If the afterlife does exist,
I hope I won't be born a cripple.
I hope I won't be afflicted with ailments
or need to suffer.
Ji Ya, you've been aiming for some time. You didn't make a single attempt.
Just do it.
Let me aim for a little longer.
Ji Ya, it's just a game. You don't need to worry so much.
Why don't we consider this as my loss?
No way. Pitch-pot is what I'm best at.
You just picked this up not long ago.
I have to defeat you.
Fine, then.
Ji Ya, you're too competitive and prideful.
That'll wear you out, you know?
Why must we win all the time?
Now that I think about it,
Zhen is right.
It's pretty nice to lead a simple life.
I'm different from you. So what if I obtain her body?
What I desire is her entire being.
We shall be together forever.
(Ruyi Pavilion)
Before this, Cat Lord wanted the best products from Yuzhen Parlour.
Now, she doesn't even want to pick one when I've delivered them here.
These are the trendiest and best products I have currently.
Mr. Mei did delay his return too long.
Seems like Kitty has to head to Quzhou now.
That was an excellent drinking session.
Beauty...
Lady Wu Zhen?
What a coincidence.
I've heard about it. Commissioner Mei has run away, huh?
If I must say, you should've said yes to me back then.
I do appreciate delicate beauties like you, you know?
I heard that Mr. Mei has run away from his marriage.
He didn't show up for half a month.
I wonder if he's afraid of Princess Qing He.
If we compare them, I suppose Young Marquis is better.
I like that.
Lady Wu, why don't we rekindle our old flame?
Sure. Young Marquis, do you want me to kick you again?
Who's that? Let me go!
Young Marquis.
Isn't that Mr. Mei?
That's right. That's Commissioner Mei of the Arcane Appraisal Bureau.
Everyone, it's my fault for returning late to Chang'an.
I don't mind what you guys say about me.
But I won't allow it if anyone tries to bully Lady Wu Zhen.
How dare you offend me? Aren't you afraid...
Not at all.
If you're unsatisfied,
you may present a petition to His Majesty and let the world decide.
I only know
that all husbands in the world will protect their wives.
Wife, huh?
They're indeed getting married.
Seems like they have a great relationship.
Lady Wu.
Something occurred on my way back.
That's why I was late. I...
Lady Wu?
Young Marquis, this is...
Have you lost your mind?
I need to tell you something.
Young Master, you're back.
Wen Hua, go out and buy some stuff.
I already bought everything we needed. We lack nothing.
Understood. I'll buy extra.
I won't interrupt you two.
I was in a hurry just now. Are you hurt?
Sorry. I'm late.
Do you have a partner in Quzhou?
What?
It doesn't take that long to return to Quzhou.
Perhaps you have a partner in Quzhou
and you went back to give her an account.
But she refused to accept it and wouldn't allow you to return.
Are you writing a story here?
It sounds logical. Everything makes sense, you know?
I swear, you're the only woman I love.
Really?
If so, why are you only back now?
I miscalculated the journey. That's why I was delayed.
I'm sorry.
Come with me.
Is this your parents' spirit tablet?
When my mother was 16, she fell into the water while traveling.
Luckily, my father rescued her.
They fell in love, but their family didn't acknowledge their relationship.
They thought Father was just a normal merchant.
I heard that from Si more or less.
After that, my mother eloped with my father.
Thus, the Mei Residence was born.
They had me as well.
The three of us led an ordinary life.
Until 18 years ago.
My parents died during the Divine Fire Chaos.
The Mei family sent me to Quzhou.
I never expected to go hungry in summer
and suffer the cold under thin quilts in winter.
After that, even if I was fortunate enough to be taken in by Master,
even if I'd witnessed the bustling Chang'an,
I still had no desires
in this world.
Mei Zhu Yu.
I once thought that I would stay distant from the worldly realm forever.
Until I encountered you.
You were the one who dragged me into it.
You're an excellent lady.
How am I excellent?
You're the bravest,
most determined,
and most outstanding lady I've met.
You're even more outstanding than most of the men I've encountered.
I think I'm not good enough for you.
I have a cold personality. People hate me as well.
But now that I'm lucky to make your acquaintance,
Father and Mother shall be our witnesses.
I'm truly sincere in asking for your hand.
I'm willing to pledge a lifetime with you as we grow old together.
Wu Zhen, will you marry me?
Didn't Sister and Brother-in-law already grant us a marriage?
Why are you still asking me this?
It's because your will is much more important than the imperial decree.
You are all alone with no family to rely on
while I'm reckless and unruly.
Both of us are "outstanding" in our own ways.
Doesn't that make us a match made in heaven?
From now on, with me by your side,
you may continue to live with ease,
unrestrained,
heedless of convention,
while following your heart.
You're still as free as ever.
But there's one thing. Perhaps you're taking this one day at a time.
But I can't.
You were the one who provoked me first.
You caused me to have desires and long for love.
Even if, one day,
you lost your interest in me,
even if you are annoyed
and are bored by my presence,
you cannot abandon me.
If not...
If not, what?
Life is short.
I will never let you go.
My cousin and Lady Wu Zhen are getting closer and closer.
Indeed. He's an excellent groom.
She'd better not scare him away.
Sister, seems like you're going to be an aunt in the near future.
Me too.
When it comes to children, one must start with at least a pair.
If it's a boy, he must inherit your family's graceful air.
If it's a girl, she must inherit our family's valiant air.
But they say that daughters take after their fathers
while sons resemble their mothers.
If
They give birth to sons who take after Zhen...
Did you two summon me just to talk about this?
Giving birth to and raising children are very important, you know?
Zhen, you're getting married soon.
You can't afford to act willfully anymore.
In my opinion, it's too early to talk about kids.
Why don't we decide if we should grant them a huge manor?
Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, you have to look at the bigger picture.
My father and sister lack nothing.
Why should we grant them a manor when they haven't rendered any merits?
Fine.
She's getting harder and harder to serve.
However, Mr. Mei's residence could be better...
Mr. Mei, would you mind if you were to live at Duke Wu's Residence?
People will gossip about him and say that he's a live-in husband.
I don't mind. It's fine as long as she's happy.
I don't care about what other people say about me.
But I do.
There are only the two of us. Why should we live in a huge manor?
And, people might badmouth us because of it too.
I think the Mei Residence is good enough.
She's the hardest one to serve among us.
Lady Wu Zhen is a princess after all. Of course she's delicate.
Zhu Yu, you'll have to be more understanding.
There's no need for that.
She's a great woman.
In my opinion, we should pick an auspicious date early
and hold their wedding.
We shouldn't let them wait any longer.
Mr. Mei.
Why don't we admire the view at the Imperial Garden together?
Go now.
Aren't you going to join them?
I don't think I'll be joining them.
I'm sure nothing bad will happen.
Do you know why I brought you out here?
Your Majesty, it's because you're worried about Lady Wu Zhen.
Mr. Mei,
Zhen had a narrow escape from death before.
Your Majesty, are you referring to the incident 18 years ago?
Look at the tiny butterflies.
- Look! They sell candy figures! - There?
I want a candy figure.
- Okay. - Take a look.
Mister, one candy figure, please.
All right. Please pick one.
Run!
Divine fire?
Why is it happening during winter?
Lady Wu Zhen?
Lady Wu Zhen!
Father!
Sister!
That's right. She was born with a weak constitution.
She had a close shave
on New Year's Eve 18 years ago.
She was lucky enough to be blessed by the heavens.
That's how she was able to recover.
Although her health improved gradually,
she had a complete change of personality.
People say that she's willful and unruly.
But in my eyes, she's always hiding something beneath the surface.
Even Father and I couldn't figure it out.
Do you think there are unresolved issues in her heart?
I don't know.
All these years, she has always returned late.
She always had a worried look on her face.
Sometimes, she even came back injured.
But she told us nothing at all.
I know I'm strict with her.
In reality, I just want her to lead a better life.
Your Majesty, Wu Zhen and I are deeply in love.
I believe that she's not unruly and willful,
unlike what other people think of her.
She's kind, intelligent, and decisive.
She's the most radiant person I've ever seen.
I'm truly fortunate to be able to stay by her side.
Excellent.
Since this is the marriage she wants,
Father and I can finally rest at ease.
Our mother passed away at an early age.
Our father has a childish personality.
It's inconvenient for me to do anything
within the deep confines of the palace.
Mr. Mei, she's my only sister.
From now on, I'll entrust her to you.
I hope you can resolve her worries for her.
I hope you'll lead a safe and peaceful life with her.
I will never let her down, even in death.
It's getting late. You should look for Zhen.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Father, you can rest at ease now, right?
(Duke Wu's Residence)
What is this?
Is it food?
It's your betrothal gift, a goose.
Excellent!
Sinister Lord Infant, thank you for remembering me.
I've served you once after all.
Now that I think about it, I shouldn't have refused your goodwill.
I promised that I would locate your core, restore your body,
and rebuild our great empire.
How is it?
In two more hours, we can rebuild Chang'an
after the demonic fire has been extinguished.
The Mortal Realm and the Demon Realm will be merged.
The Mortal Realm will be rebuilt.
Naturally, you shall be our ruler.
I'll surely eradicate Chang'an.
By then, you can take over the world all you want.
She's the only one I desire.
Zhen, you're the only one I desire.
All those around you, they are unnecessary.
So filthy.
Elder Gray, how have you been?
Don't be scared.
I'm here to negotiate a deal with you.
The Bai Sect has never been good at handling affairs.
I merely need to lift a finger to obtain your demonic core.
What do you think?
Will you break free from the plight of ordinary rats and work for me?
Lord Shu.