(Moonlit Reunion)
(Episode 34)
It looks like Mei Si's horse carriage.
It really is.
Si!
Is it you, Si?
Is Mei Si inside?
I think it's your friend?
Lady Liu, I...
Coming.
Huang Da Zhuang?
What are you doing?
Mei Si.
Something is wrong with you.
Nothing.
What is wrong with me?
It's early in the morning and you are dressed sloppily.
Is there someone inside?
No.
No one is inside.
We grew up together.
I know you well.
You must be hiding something since you look like this.
Come on. Tell me.
Who is inside?
No one. I told you there's no one inside.
You rejected Lady Liu's marriage.
Who else can you go out with?
Is it
a girl from the brothel?
Stop saying nonsense. Can you not embarrass me in public?
Fine. I'm saying nonsense.
Now that Miss Zhen and Commissioner Mei
is traveling south,
I'll be in charge of you.
After all, Zhen isn't here.
I can't let you go on the wrong path.
Let me see who it is.
Huang Da Zhuang. Mr. Huang.
There's no one inside.
There's no one inside?
- What are we doing in Chang'an?   - Catching thieves!
- What should we do if we see a suspicious vehicle?   - Investigate!
See?
I can't help you.
Show me.
Stop. I said there's no one inside.
- Show me.   - There's no one inside.
- Are you sure? Let me see.   - No!
Why are you arguing over something trivial?
There's really no one?
I told you there's no one inside.
Open the curtains and show him.
No one wants to see it.
Let's go!
Where is she?
My hand is tired. Is that enough?
You left too quickly.
What? Should I stay in the carriage
and let them badmouth me?
Cat Lord is married.
Since you like Mei Si,
why are you pushing him away
and not telling him your feelings?
Nonsense!
Who told you that I like him?
Tell me. Who told you that?
Ling Xiao.
I'll deal with him in a couple of days.
Are you addicted to becoming Mei Si's lobbyist?
Have you become a matchmaker?
I've been treated with respect
by that fool.
It's only normal for me to be considerate
before I leave.
Leave?
Where are you going?
I didn't want to tell you so soon.
I will soon
transform into a dragon and ascend to Heaven.
Congratulations.
I don't miss much here
except that fool, Mei Si.
I hope he can fulfill his wish.
You want him to fulfill his wish.
What does it have to do with me?
Come with me.
Let me show you something.
Mei Si is not around.
Come.
Come in.
Right. We can use the door.
You've spent too much time with Mei Si.
What is he doing?
That fool has been doing this recently.
I don't know where he found this method.
He said eating raw chicken hearts
for 49 days would turn him into a demon.
In a few days,
he ate all of them
but I almost threw up watching him.
What is this in the cup?
Take a guess.
He said smelling it often
and getting used to the smell of chicken blood,
would make it easier to eat the chicken hearts.
Also,
two days ago,
it was a full moon night.
He insisted I bite his neck.
He said he would turn into a demon after that.
Is that written in your "Compendium of Demons"?
Don't let him buy random books from peddlers.
- Did you bite him?   - Of course, not.
It was so unhygienic.
Later, he wanted to bite me instead.
He wanted a drop of my blood.
I ended up being chased by him the whole night.
- Did you let him bite you?   - I beat him up.
In my opinion,
you should deal with him.
He might not look intelligent
but I don't think he should behave like a fool.
I will
soon become a dragon.
I have something to request of you.
Clear your name in Demon City?
That's not important.
I want to beg you
to come back and meet him often
if you are not too busy in Demon City.
Meeting him once
makes him happier.
Mortals have a short lifespan.
I think
it's not that easy
to be happy in life.
Everything you say is for his sake
yet you say you are not his lobbyist.
I just have
one friend.
I can only leave him in your care.
Enough. I'll be leaving.
Well,
I'll use the door.
(Mei Residence)
Who touched my paintings?
Who touched my chicken hearts and chicken blood?
I know you are worried about Boss
but the Serpent Lord is right.
Mr. Mei has been treating Boss well.
Nothing will go wrong.
I didn't know how you felt about the Boss previously.
We've been working together for so long.
If you had told me sooner,
I could help you put in a good word.
I wasn't teasing you.
Go back.
He is just as pretentious as always.
You don't know what's good for you!
Elder Gray, it has become a habit for you
to come here.
However, I remember no one can enter this place
without an invitation.
It's too troublesome for me.
Every demon in Demon City thinks I'm dead.
If I walk around outside all day,
it's bad for you
if someone finds out, Lord Shu.
Why don't you
send me away from Demon City
so I can help you from the outside?
I am trapped in Demon City
and you want me to release a cunning geezer like you.
If you are going to hurt Zhen,
I'm afraid no one can stop you.
Lord Shu, how can you say that?
You revived me.
I will never move on my own
and make plans myself.
Is that so?
Why do you need this demon core then?
Who are you trying to hurt?
Wu Zi Shu.
You are the Sinister Fiend Infant's confidant.
It's fine even if you are not as ambitious
as your master
but you are always hesitating
for a half-demon.
If the Sinister Fiend Infant
finds out how incompetent you are,
he will regret it so much.
Elder Gray, you described me as an awful one
but where were you 18 years ago?
When you were around
during the Demon City attack,
it would be a success.
It seems like you still don't know the Sinister Fiend Infant
as much as I know him despite the years you've served him.
He wasn't trying to attack Demon City
but to reclaim it.
The creator of Chang'an Demon City
is the Sinister Fiend Infant.
What?
You really don't know this?
I've been alive for a millennium.
Back then, this place wasn't called Chang'an.
I was a rat spirit in the mountains.
Demons like us were living a good life in the mountains.
Life was good.
However, those darned mortals
started a war
for their selfish desire
and turned this place into a raging battlefield.
My mountain
was completely ruined.
Without these darned mortals,
we wouldn't need to hide,
live cautiously and gather in nests
just to protect ourselves.
The Sinister Fiend Infant
created the barrier
and established the Demon City.
He wanted to strengthen the demons and overturn the mortals.
Unfortunately,
The first two lords were despicable.
They controlled Demon City
and took it for themselves.
They drove the Sinister Fiend out
and contributed nothing
just like emperors of the mortal realm.
They only wanted to pass down Demon City's authority to their descendants.
No wonder you treat Cat Lord and Serpent Lord without respect.
This is the reason why.
That's right.
They are nothing
in my opinion.
I've waited a millennium.
I've always waited,
hoped,
and remembered.
Until 18 years ago,
the Sinister Fiend finally returned.
You are right.
If I left Demon City that day,
he would never lose to the former Cat Lord.
You are really useless
as his confidant.
Let me tell you.
I'm fine with serving someone
but my master must be worth serving.
For the sake of humans,
the demons have to seal ourselves off
and be trapped here
without knowing anything about the mortal realm.
Someone as foolish as they
have no right to rule Demon City!
This place is supposed to be ours!
I don't give a care about Cat Lords or Serpent Lords.
I must revive the Sinister Fiend Infant
and help him create a new Chang'an that prioritizes demons.
A Chang'an where demons will not be equals to mere mortals!
Brother Lu Yang.
This is my wife, Wu Zhen.
This is my fifth martial brother in Changxi Palace, Lu Yang.
He is the best in Changxi Palace when it comes to medicine.
Greetings, Brother Lu Yang.
Soon.
Greetings, Sister-in-law.
You are not guarding the waterfall.
It seems like Shuang Jiang hasn't been stealing your fish recently.
Yes.
That's unlike him.
What has he been doing recently?
Got it.
Let's go.
He is busy.
Don't you have any serious wishes?
Serious?
(Get rich)
Get rich.
You're checking the ledger. Why are you spacing out?
Brother Chi Hua, why are you here?
Zhu Yu is back.
Brother Mei is back?
You're scaring me.
Brother Mei!
Is this Zhu Yu's wife?
Not only that. She's also Demon City's Cat Lord.
To be exact,
She's Demon City's Cat Lord who has lost her memory.
Having a demon inside Changxi Palace.
Doesn't it feel strange?
Enough.
Something serious happened to our former sect leader.
Let's not find fault with others.
She's a guest, after all.
Lian Fu.
Why are you hiding so far away?
I...
I'm not hiding.
You're not hiding?
Why are you standing over there then?
Come here!
You...
Brother Lian Fu, what are you doing?
No. What are you afraid of?
Are you afraid of her?
She is pretty. What's so scary about her?
I think none of you know her well.
It's all right. She also doesn't know herself well right now.
In that case,
she can stay here for a few days.
Changxi Palace has many books.
Perhaps there is a cure.
Thank you.
- Well...   - Zhu Yu used to be a member of Changxi Palace.
We won't stand by and do nothing.
- No...   - Lady Wu Zhen might be a demon
but there are kind demons too.
Don't you know that?
I know, but...
Lady Wu Zhen is a good person.
Even if her memory returns, she won't harm us.
I just have one thing to ask!
Are they going to
stay in one or two rooms?
Since she is staying in your old room,
you can stay with Shuang Jiang for now.
It's only separated by a wall.
It's convenient if something happens.
Thank you.
Don't be so polite. We are a family after all.
However, it is a crude room.
Bring more daily necessities
so Wu Zhen can stay comfortably.
Which of you is going?
Me! I'll go.
Has Lian Fu changed a lot?
Yes.
He has been like this since he came back.
He has become so hardworking.
He is probably worried that we might take revenge on him
because he was close to Chang Ming.
You won't.
Yes. If he isn't guilty,
we wouldn't think of that.
Whatever.
The position of sect leader is vacant now.
Many duties have been separated among us.
It's easier with him helping us.
Shuang Jiang has started managing the accounts after he came back.
So,
you are Changxi Palace's Celestial Master
and I am Chang'an Demon City's Cat Lord?
That's really interesting.
Unfortunately, I don't remember anything.
Do I know any demonic spells?
Try it.
It's so fun.
This is bad.
What is this?
It's probably an array left behind by Brother Chi Hua
when he was practicing.
Here you go.
(How did she...)
What are you doing?
I'm calling you.
I didn't expect it to work.
It's late. Why are you still awake?
The bed is too hard.
I'll get something to pad the bed for you.
I just want to have a chat with you.
Did you sleep here back then?
Is that ugly thing yours?
The ugly doll that's staring at me.
I won against Brother Xiao Mu once.
Master made this clay doll for me
as a reward.
Now that I look at it closely, it's quite cute.
I was thinking about
what you looked like when you were a child
and what you would do.
When I was young?
I practiced martial arts, studied, and slept.
That's really pitiful.
It must be boring.
Is it?
Actually, a boring life isn't pitiful.
I think
having a wish
that cannot be fulfilled
is the most pitiful.
You created Heaven, Earth and the Three Realms.
People worship you.
Now, the ruler of the universe should change hands.
(What did)
(the Satanic Fiend wrote on my body back then?)
I'm sure everyone is awake at this time.
Zhu Yu had a habit of waking up early since young.
Shuang Jiang has also been studying early
since he returned from Chang'an.
I think he should also be awake.
Good morning.
Did I arrange for you
to stay in this room yesterday?
No.
Good morning.
This morning, Lu Yang found many fruits
from the mountains.
They are in the front yard.
Sister-in-law, you may try them.
I think they suit you.
Sure. I couldn't
take a good look at Changxi Palace yesterday anyway.
Changxi Palace is boring.
There's no fun to be had.
However, it is quiet
and might be different perhaps.
You may walk around the place, Lady Wu Zhen.
Zhu Yu and Sister-in-law
can't separate from each other for even one night.
Enough of the nonsense.
I discussed it with Chi Hua.
Lu Yang excels in medicine.
He will try to think of something.
Many books are stored in the archive.
You can have a look
and see if you can find anything.
Brother Mei, you wake up so early.
I didn't notice.
They were right.
Life in Changxi Palace
is indeed boring
and doesn't have much fun.
The sword guides the Three Celestial Lights,
the will guards Heaven and Earth!
(However, it's special.)
I didn't expect
Demon City's Cat Lord to behave like this after losing her memory.
Even if she has lost her memory,
she is still the same.
If she hadn't lost her memory,
she probably wouldn't have stayed by your side
after what happened in Chang'an.
Right now,
I just want her to live well.
Zhu Yu, it's a pity.
The sect leader hasn't been elected
and you are the most suitable candidate.
No.
I'm not.
Once something happens in this world,
traces will be left.
How can the slate be wiped
for me to start all over again?
Since the day I chose to leave this place,
I could no longer return to Changxi Palace.
I'm in charge of the archives now.
I'll leave the key in your care.
You may enter this place as you wish.
Even the secret chamber's key is there.
If nothing works,
you may open the secret chamber and we'll turn a blind eye to it.
Thank you.
I still don't get it.
With your talent,
is it really worth it to sacrifice everything for a woman?
It is.
Well,
do you want to reconsider?
Is it really worth it?
Mr. Mei.
Having fun?
Yes.
Not really.
You won't lose against them.
I don't remember.
I think you won't lose against them, right?
No need. You won't lose against them. There's no need to prove it.
Come back.
What a coincidence.
I was just passing by.
Do you believe it?
What did you do?
I... I'm not doing anything.
Does Lady Liu
think my way of becoming a demon is too foolish
so she wouldn't see me?
I don't think so. You did many foolish things.
She wouldn't wait until now to treat you so coldly.
If you don't know why,
just ask her.
Of course, I want to find her.
But she's in Demon City and I can't enter.
That's exactly why I'm here to give you some information.
Lady Liu
left Demon City an hour ago
and went to Yuzhen Parlour.
You don't have to thank me
for what I just told you.
However, the most important thing today
is to tell you...
I'm here to tell you
that I'm going to turn into a dragon
tonight.
This batch has just been acquired from Annan.
They are a little different from previous batches.
What do you think
of the smell for this batch?
It's decent.
All right.
I'll return to Demon City if there's nothing else.
I'll send you off.
Manager,
I heard Fourth Master Mei's horse carriage is rushing here.
He is quite well-informed.
I'll use the back door.
Wait.
Fourth Master Mei, aren't you at the front door?
My horse carriage is in the front door.
After so many years,
I've known Lady Liu quite well.
Why are you looking for me?
Lady Liu,
I'm here to ask you
what happened.
We had fun
in Qiuchi that day.
It's nothing.
Lady Liu.
I like to fool around usually.
I am ignorant and incompetent
but I'm not a fool.
You are also not someone who changes normally.
Something must have happened.
But no matter what,
you should tell me the reason.
Let's speak inside.