Episode 2
Father!
Sister!
Where are you?
Little girl.
Who are you?
I'm Wu Zhen.
What are you doing here?
There was a fire on the street.
It was burning everywhere.
I got lost.
You came here at this time.
This might be our fate.
Who are you?
You're going to die soon.
And I'm the one who's going
to change your destiny.
It's a shame that changing fate
doesn't come free.
There's a price to pay.
What's the price?
The price is…
This young man
is quite considerate.
You're here.
Did I wake you?
No, I happened to be up.
Did you find any clues?
You fought with the female bat
two days ago.
The girl she possessed was sent
to the Bureau of Mystic Investigations.
Upon investigation, the girl is Bi Tao,
a dancer at Xiangsi House.
Xiangsi House?
And the good friend she lives with is
a dancer at Xiangsi House, too.
She's been dancing at Ruyi House lately.
Her name is Zhe Liu.
I knew it.
She's here.
We can't let her get away.
Let's go to Xiangsi House.
Xiangsi House?
Who are you talking to?
You.
Me?
I suddenly recalled
that many Xiangsi House dancers
came last night.
Maybe someone saw something.
I'm free, so I want to go and ask.
If anyone knows where my stuff is,
I won't bother you.
In that case, I'll go to Xiangsi House.
Your Highness is going
to Xiangsi House too?
Why don't you bring more people?
There's no need.
Isn't Young Master Mei going?
Investigating is an official duty.
It's inconvenient for you to come along.
That won't do.
It's a red-light district.
What if you use your authority
for private gain?
After all, you're the man I chose.
I have to keep an eye on you.
Go with Her Highness-- Eh?
Where are you going?
To the carriage.
The carriage?
You call it a carriage?
Wenhua, Mei family servant
It looks like my horse carriage's baby.
Why don't you ride with me?
There's no need.
My carriage is fine.
Slow down, Young Master.
Young Master! No, Fugui!
Fugui!
Fugui.
The carriage is gone.
Lady Wu, what you did was inappropriate.
Longing Pavillion
Zhe Liu, Xiangsi House dancer
Where exactly did you go?
Don't leave me.
No.
Zhe Liu.
Come in.
Why didn't you practice dancing today?
We've been looking for you.
I'm not feeling well.
Today's guests are waiting.
Come with me.
Come and take a look!
Look, isn't that
County Princess's carriage?
As the saying goes,
throw fruit until the carriage is full,
look until Wei Jie is dead.
You're prominent now.
There's no harm in enjoying that.
This carriage is Lady Wu Zhen's.
Who is this young man?
Could he be Lady Wu Zhen's new lover?
New lover?
Let me see what he looks like.
His appearance is really…
Look at his head shape.
He's so handsome!
Not as handsome as you.
Bai Xuanchen…
Free-Spirited Princess
and Handsome Scholar.
Do you like this?
There's also Female General
and Little Guard,
Female Official and Young Master,
Lady Boss and Waiter.
I know. Don't be anxious.
What's the matter?
Nothing.
Sir, are you here for fun?
Longing Pavillion
Lady Wu Zhen.
You haven't been here for a while.
Yes.
This is Mr. Mei
from the Bureau of Mystic Investigations.
He's here today to ask you something.
Young Master.
What a handsome young man.
What do you want to ask?
Yes.
Do you want to ask me or her?
Longing Pavillion
Sleeves Dancing in the Wind
- My lord.
- Wait.
What are you doing?
How dare you!
Get out of the way.
My lord?
Lady Wu.
What are you doing here?
I'm here to…
Pick a fight?
Are you looking for trouble?
I'm telling you, don't come near me.
Let me tell you.
I'm not interested in you at all now.
We don't mind each other's business.
Well… Look.
I have someone new now.
It's too late to regret it.
I might not agree to it.
- Are you all right?
- Wu Zhen, this isn't over!
Shu.
My lord, keep it down.
Don't bring Lady Wu back.
What are you afraid of?
My lord.
Fu Xi.
You came here with Wu Zhen, didn't you?
Why did she kick me and leave?
You--
What's that sound?
You…
So you're here.
Be careful!
It's me. Don't you remember me?
She's really possessed.
This is bad.
This isn't right.
These aren't real bats.
It's demonic magic.
Let's go.
We meet again, Bat Demon.
Don't waste your effort.
Fu Xi
Cat Lord!
She made many mistakes,
but please, at least spare her life.
I won't kill her.
Cat Lord.
What's wrong with her?
After you left,
she probably contracted something unclean
that corrupted her, causing evil thoughts.
That's why she hurt someone.
Someone cast a spell on her.
Demon-Slaying Spell?
Young Master, are you all right?
Are you hurt?
Did someone bully you?
Tell me, I'll avenge you.
I'm fine.
Who is it?
Young Master, don't worry.
I'll just chase her away.
Don't hit her.
Don't worry, I'm also fine now.
So you don't like cats.
Please take her away.
My young master hates cats.
I guess
the cat will be sad.
Sir, you're here too.
I heard a bunch of bats flew here
for no reason.
Is everyone all right?
- Lady Wu…
- Lady Wu was shocked.
She left a long time ago.
It's getting late.
I'll go back and rest then.
Who is he?
Lady Wu's good friend Mr. Shu,
who runs a bookstore in Chang'an.
But Wu Zhen gets shocked too.
Xiaozhen.
Here, have some candy.
Shu.
When will she recover?
You're still so impatient.
I'm not impatient.
He is.
Fu Xi.
Fu Xi, don't be angry.
I didn't really want to abandon you.
We've been together for 100 years.
It's just a bit boring.
I just wanted to go out for a while.
Fu Xi.
It's only been two days since he left,
and you're already upset.
Why are you so impatient?
Earrings come in pairs.
One can't be missing from the pair.
Since we are a pair of earrings,
we should be together all the time.
Being together and inseparable
is touching.
In this world,
not many things are matter-in-fact.
Having souls and developing wisdom
are already very rare.
How can it be meaningless
just because your partner's gone?
Bat Demon.
Our existence in this world
aren't controlled by others or by destiny.
Even if you're just a little earring,
you should have significance.
Being alone in the world
and having company
are beautiful in their own way.
Fu Xi still has
her divine senses.
After she recovers and Demon Underworld
punishes her for hurting others,
you two can stay in Demon Underworld
and live the life you want.
Thank you, Cat Lord.
Wait.
Cat Lord.
I wasn't possessed
just because I lost my partner.
Maybe there's another reason.
- What is it?
- When I first came to Chang'an,
I looked for him in the form of a bat.
Unexpectedly, I returned to my form
one day and fell to the ground.
A Xiangsi House dancer found me.
As I was a bit damaged,
she brought me
to a jewelry workshop in the city.
A jewelry workshop?
Yes.
At the jewelry workshop,
I felt an evil energy.
It made me become unlike myself.
Why would there be
an evil energy in Chang'an?
I remember that evil energy's source was
a stone, a red stone.
A stone?
Could it be the Bone Relic?
Bone Relic?
What's that?
Bone Relic is the remnant
of someone with a grudge.
Wherever it is,
it often causes demonic changes.
No matter whether you're human or demon,
you're easily bewitched by it.
That means
we have to find the Bone Relic.
Mei Residence
Memorial tablet
of Yi Xuanqing and Mei Yuheng
Father.
Mother.
It's been 18 years.
Memorial tablet
of Yi Xuanqing and Mei Yuheng
Why isn't Father back yet?
Your father?
Mother of Mei
Maybe he has other matters to attend to.
I'll only sleep after he reads to me.
Be good and go to sleep now.
You'll see him when you wake up.
Zhuyu.
I've told your father.
He's not allowed
to go anywhere this New Year's Eve.
Both of us
will play with you in the snow
in the mountains.
All right?
All right.
I'll sleep now.
It's been 18 years.
I've now entered the Bureau
of Mystic Investigations' record library.
I wonder if I can find any clues…
to uncover the truth
behind the Heavenly Fire Disaster
back then.
Mother.
Think about it.
If I hadn't gone to Quzhou,
Master wouldn't have taken me
as Changxi Palace's disciple.
I should've stayed away
from worldly affairs.
But before Master died, he said
that your deaths probably
weren't from natural causes,
but caused by demons.
I came back to Chang'an
to find the truth for you.
No matter how hard and dangerous it is…
I'll surely avenge you.
What?
Zhen'er chose someone?
Hey.
This is great news.
It's that easy?
Why do I feel like there's
something fishy about it?
At the birthday banquet two days ago,
Lady Wu chose him in front of everyone.
I heard
she even dragged him in private
and spent a long time with him.
In private?
He's so capable?
What's his background?
He just came to Chang'an.
His name is Mei Zhuyu.
His surname is Mei?
Ah! He's from
the Mei family's side branch.
He should be
Noble Consort Mei's distant cousin.
Zhen'er has been free-spirited
for so long.
How can a young man
who just came to Chang'an manipulate her?
- Well…
- I don't believe it.
What's his strength?
That's right. What's his strength?
His strength? Ah!
Come on.
You have such a handsome man
in your family?
We have such a good-looking man
in our family?
I knew it.
I know my sister quite well.
Why did she focus
on one person so quickly?
She's just
being playful and lecherous.
That's what she would do.
Lady Wu might just be
playing around for a couple of days,
but there's one thing I dare not report.
What is it? Tell me.
He works in the Bureau
of Mystic Investigations.
Bureau of Mystic Investigations?
He's just a mediocre official.
He relies on his looks,
and he's also a freeloader.
Noble Consort Mei.
Discipline your family member.
Boss.
Don't worry, Boss.
Zhe Liu is all right now.
She'll be fine after taking
some calming medicine.
Did the Bureau of Mystic Investigations
suspect anything?
No. They said bats hidden
on Xiangsi House's roof
stole the earrings.
Bureau of Mystic Investigations' Xu Luan
is frightened by the bat rumors.
He said since no one was killed,
he doesn't want to investigate further.
By the way, Boss,
I just got some news.
I'm afraid you won't like it.
- What is it?
- Eunuch Feng left the palace
to head to the Bureau
of Mystic Investigations.
Her Majesty is summoning Young Master Mei.
- What?
- Mm.
Young Master.
Young Master!
The Hu cake shop next door
is popular indeed.
I woke up early to line up
and only got this much.
It's enough.
Young Master.
Since this is
for the Bureau of Mystic Investigations,
that Xu guy
will reimburse it, right?
Don't worry.
That's good.
We're already poor.
I give you two-thirds
of my monthly salary.
How can you say we're poor?
What do you mean, Young Master?
I work so hard every day
without complaints
to serve you well.
Aren't you touched at all?
It's not that.
Then are you going to deduct my salary?
No.
Mr. Mei, bad news!
Hurry, go to the Bureau
of Mystic Investigations!
- What's wrong?
- Something big happened.
The Bureau of Mystic Investigations
is trashed!
Bureau Of Mystic Investigations
Go.
Lady Wu, what are you doing?
Don't you understand, Mr. Mei?
I'm angry.
Why are you angry?
I'm angry at you, of course.
Because of you,
I came to this lousy
Bureau of Mystic Investigations
and almost got hurt by a bat.
But you're ungrateful.
You've ignored my advances.
Forget it
if you don't want to be with me.
I won't force you.
From now on,
I have nothing to do with you.
Don't let me see you again.
That's enough.
Stop looking. Go.
Stop watching. Go home.
It's all your fault!
You're short-sighted!
You're a troublemaker!
You…
My treasures.
Don't force relationship matters.
No wonder they say
County Princess Qinghe
is vain and overbearing.
She caused so much trouble
just to get close to you.
It's fine.
Maybe Lady Wu just likes to tease people.
We'll just stay out of each other's way.
If you ask me,
why rush to put on this show?
Just let the Empress summon him.
I didn't want to get deeply involved
with that mortal anyway.
And my sister is impatient.
If I wait any longer,
I don't know
how much trouble it will cause.
Better to end it as soon as possible.
Young Master Mei might be weak,
but he's so good-looking.
Can you really bear to part with him?
Flowers don't bloom forever.
Just admire and play
with the pretty flowers,
no need to trouble yourself to pick them.
Hmm…
What's going on?
My lady, the road is blocked.
Who dares to block Lady Wu's way?
She's back.
Liu Taizhen, Daughter of Liu Manor,
Demon Underworld Snake Lord
Long time no see, Lady Liu.
It has indeed been a while.
I missed your show.
What should we do then?
I'll perform again for you.
Sure.
Young Master,
Young Master Mei Si is here.
Mei Si? Why are you here?
Everyone in Chang'an
is crazily talking about you.
What are they saying?
They said
it was love at first sight for Wu Zhen
at the birthday banquet.
To get involved with you,
she pretended to report a case
to come to the Bureau of Mystic
Investigations to give herself to you.
But you didn't know how to cherish her.
You'd rather die than submit.
You disregarded County Princess Qinghe
and laid an ambush in Xiangsi House
to investigate the bat disaster.
And Lady Wu's advances never worked,
so she was furious and made trouble
at the Bureau of Mystic Investigations,
saying she wants to cut ties with you.
How can they speak such nonsense
about a woman's chastity?
It doesn't matter. Chastity?
Wu Zhen doesn't care about that.
Yes.
I just heard
that County Princess Qinghe and her rival,
Lady Liu,
got into a fight on the street
over something trivial.
People are gossiping about them.
Lady Liu?
- She's back in Chang'an?
- Yes.
Who is Lady Liu?
The daughter of Minister Liu Gongshen.
My…
fiancée.
Ruyi House
Don't scare me.
I haven't seen you for a few days,
and this is how you welcome me?
What's the matter?
You went to pray with the Liu family,
but were so bored at the temple,
so you've become lively
since you came back?
Is there really nothing going on
between you and Young Master Mei?
What could be going on?
If you really don't like Young Master Mei,
why would you trade
your good reputation for his?
I have a good reputation?
I used him once, after all.
As demons, we should have some conscience.
Besides, I don't care about this.
I heard that yesterday,
someone secretly used a talisman
to disperse the bat colony
and hurt the mother bat.
You heard about it too?
It's such a big deal.
The demon slayers that have been gone
for years are lured out.
It's really interesting.
We need to be careful then.
It's a big world.
It's normal
that there are still cultivators.
As long as
they're not Changxi Palace's scoundrels.
Changxi Palace has been gone
for a century.
You're always thinking about them.
The Changxi weapon
can slay all demons in the world.
This wound
constantly reminds me to be alert.
If they are still around,
the Changxi Palace and Demon Market
will surely have a life-or-death battle.
Who is it?
Stop hiding.
Stop!
Ghosts!
County Princess is so generous.
She only broke a corner of my front hall,
but is repairing the entire
Bureau of Mystic Investigations.
Good job trashing the place.
Do it again next time.
Commander Xu.
If I weren't so lucky,
I would have been killed
by that demon last night.
Commander,
Bureau of Mystic Investigations,
please save me.
What are you talking about?
You're alive and kicking, aren't you?
- I--
- Who wants to harm you?
- I get it now.
- Huh?
You must have heard that
The Bureau of Mystic Investigations
recently solved a bizarre case.
That's why
you came up with this weird rhetoric
to make a big deal out of it
and cause trouble
at the Bureau of Mystic Investigations.
Your goal is to attract customers
for your little workshop. Am I right?
What are you talking about?
- I--
- That's enough.
Ever since I solved the bat case, right?
I've met a lot of strange people
like you every day.
- No.
- How can I not see through
- this minor trick?
- I…
People like you are despicable!
I can't stand it!
- But I--
- But what?
If you don't stop nagging,
I'll arrest you!
I…
Yuzhen Pavilion
Living in the Wild
Little Kitty.
Smell this.
Its incense is made
from a 100-year-old agarwood bone.
It refreshes the mind.
It's also made into a balm.
Apply it on your forehead
to relieve fatigue, very energizing.
Boss.
It is refreshing.
But this smell is too strong.
It is quite hard to sell.
Since it's energizing and refreshing,
say it's a good product for candidates
preparing for the exam.
For candidates preparing for the exam?
Good idea.
Since it's my boss's idea,
shouldn't you give us 20% of Ruyi House?
Dream on.
"Dream on."
Beauty Ling Xiao.
Your Snake Master is so petty.
There's no future with her.
Why don't you work for me?
Cat Lord favors me so much.
I am…
so unmoved.
Because only my lady is in my heart.
Young Master Mei Si has arrived.
If Ruyi House is
for food and fun,
Yuzhen Pavilion is for elegance.
The literati and scholars come here
to enjoy incense and meet friends.
I buy all my incense here.
Young Master Mei Si.
The usual seat.
I'm sorry, Mei Si.
The second floor's
private rooms are full.
Wait, someone even reserved
my private room in advance?
Please wait
at an open table first.
Little Zhuyu.
Wu Zhen.
Lady Liu?
Is that my Lady Liu?
Wu Zhen, I think I just saw Lady Liu.
Lady Liu's not here.
Lady Liu.
I'm hallucinating again.
Stop searching.
Can she hide underground?
Wu Zhen.
By the way, Wu Zhen,
what brings you to Yuzhen Pavilion?
Don't you dislike rouge and powder?
Besides, this is Lady Liu's shop.
You know it's my rival's shop,
yet you keep spending money here.
It seems like Lady Liu
is more important to you than me.
Wu Zhen, I was wrong.
After all, Lady Liu is my…
Wu Zhen, I swear.
I'm completely loyal to you.
All right. Wrap it up for me.
Isn't this the Mei family's young master
from the Bureau of Mystic Investigations?
What's your name?
Mei Zhuyu.
It's hard to remember your name.
If you can't remember it,
it means you're not smart.
Just forget about it.
Young Master Mei,
I heard County Princess Qinghe
used and abandoned you.
How pitiful.
But it makes sense.
She has seen a lot of men.
And you're inexperienced.
How could she not dump you?
What's the matter?
Did you come to Yuzhen Pavilion today
to buy some incense
to win Lady Wu's favor again?
Why don't I give you a tip?
I heard that Yuzhen Pavilion
also has an aphrodisiac incense.
Why don't you buy some?
You…
Living in the Wild
Translated by Coleen Chua