(Moonlit Reunion)
(Episode 29)
You rented the place for a few days' diversion?
Yet you stand here in the dark,
neither eating nor drinking.
Quite a novel way to enjoy yourselves.
If you're finished, may I take my husband home?
Of course.
By the way, I was unaware you were coming.
Had I known,
on this of all days,
I would have invited you to our home.
You are too kind.
It's only proper.
Important guests like yourselves
deserve nothing less than a grand welcome.
Let's go.
When Zhu Yu entered White Night Array,
he claimed he had other thoughts.
It turns out it was all for this woman.
He's blinded by lust.
Who knows.
Why don't you follow them and take a look?
You're saying...
Nothing.
It's just a precaution.
I thought a demon would come to save you,
but it seems the Demon City doesn't care about you at all.
What's the point of suffering here for them?
If you tell me how to get into the Demon City now,
you won't have to suffer anymore.
Otherwise, I can end your life whenever I wish.
I didn't expect you to come.
And I didn't expect to actually find you there.
Knowing you, you wouldn't go to Ruyi Pavilion to catch me in the act,
nor would you believe their words.
Of course you know that.
Because you wouldn't be messing around at Ruyi Pavilion in the first place,
and you wouldn't think you could deceive me.
Wu Zhen, don't help the evil.
Don't move.
Be good.
A so-called 'once-in-a-century genius'
is nothing more than a common man consumed by desire.
I wanted to give you a surprise today.
I never imagined your surprise
would leave me reeling instead.
This is the place.
What you're saying aligns with what we know.
But no matter what we do,
we still can't get in.
The Demon City's entrance lies here.
It's warded by a barrier.
Mortals and unregistered demons cannot pass the barrier.
Wu Zhen, let's talk.
We'll talk later.
Mei Zhu Yu.
When I get back, I'll explain everything.
Lady Hu Zhu.
Please lead the way.
Okay.
(Shadow demon?)
How do you know such an obscure name?
I grew up in the countryside
and am used to tales of spirits and demons.
Besides, Lady Wu comes from a prominent family in Chang'an.
You should know why the Arcane Appraisal Bureau was established.
Everything is recorded, so what's so strange about that?
It seems...
It seems that this is what Arcane Appraisal Bureau has been looking for.
When I was in Quzhou, I heard that to get rid of this miasma,
you need to find the source and clear it out.
You've learned a lot in Quzhou.
But you never said you knew martial arts.
Only because Lady Wu never asked.
So where did you learn martial arts, Young Master?
I learned some basic skills from a senior when I was a child.
He really does wield Celestial Arts.
Boss, if this man has ties to Changxi Palace, we might have a problem.
Where is Mr. Mei?
I haven't seen him since earlier.
I finally found you.
- Brother... - Eleventh Brother.
(Eleventh brother?)
(You have so many siblings.)
Yes. It's very lively in Quzhou.
We're a family of 11 distant cousins.
The first 10 are ranked by age.
Shuang Jiang and I met last.
(I had someone invite you for a drink.)
Didn't you say you were very busy?
I heard my cousin was called here to hunt demons.
I was worried about him, so I came to check on him.
Commissioner Mei, how do you know about this suppression technique?
From the Arcane Appraisal Bureau's Records Vault.
There's a case file from 60 years ago recording such sorcery.
You remember even that?
Remarkable memory.
I grew up in Quzhou and was raised by my master.
Even though he has passed away,
I still want to go back and tell him everything.
You want to go back to Quzhou?
Quzhou is far away. I want to set out today.
So this is the woman you married?
Yes.
You are Princess Qing He?
Zhu Yu, who are these people?
A few old friends from Quzhou.
Wu Zhen?
You once told me that
the seasons change, and flowers bloom in their own time.
Even with spells, one mustn't defy the natural order.
And now, just to get into the Demon City, you're summoning lightning.
You're determined
to enter the Demon City tonight.
Yes.
Have you ever thought about
what happens to us
after tonight?
I didn't mean to hide anything from you.
I'm giving you one last choice.
If you stop here,
there's still a chance for us.
If you insist on entering the Demon City...
If I do enter the Demon City,
what then?
Then this is
the end for us.
Do you choose them?
Or will you choose me?
Kitty.
Cat Lord.
Brother Mei's wife is the Cat Lord?
Your friends are full of secrets.
You have quite a few relatives too.
Brother Mei, are you okay?
Mr. Mei.
Why are you being so aggressive?
What exactly do you want?
What else could we be doing?
Since we practice Celestial Arts,
it is our duty to eliminate demons and evil.
I've seen plenty of Celestial Masters who preach about
righteousness and morality.
They all talk a better game than they play.
I thought Young Master Mei was smart,
but it turns out he's no different from those fools hanging from the ropes.
Who are you calling a fool?
You're like a turtle in a jar.
And you still deny your stupidity.
I didn't know you two were coming.
Had I known, on such a fine day,
I would certainly have invited you both home.
You're too kind.
It's only right.
For distinguished guests like you,
it's my duty to welcome you and make you comfortable.
Sure enough, demons are evil and so treacherous.
You secretly slipped the message through.
Must a demon be wicked by nature?
How can good or evil be judged based on someone's origin,
not their actions?
This shows the character of Sect Leader Chang Ming.
I'm afraid the Changxi Palace under your rule is in disorder.
No wonder it vanished from the world.
The Changxi Palace was driven out by the Demon City back then.
Besides, humans and demons can never be the same.
What about humans?
What about demons?
The demons in the Demon City live and work peacefully,
eating, sleeping, and doing business just like you.
You were born human.
What makes you think you're superior?
The classics say that all demons are evil.
The classics say?
If the classics were always right,
that idiot Shuang Jiang would've been skinned alive by Hu Zhu long ago.
And you idiots shouldn't even still be alive.
That's the Demon City over there.
Open your stupid eyes and see for yourselves
if it's the corrupt and dirty place you imagine it to be.
Eat well, drink well.
Here's your noodles.
Thanks.
Good.
That candy store looks like it has some good stuff.
These little ones
haven't left the Demon City for hundreds of years.
What did they do wrong?
And you,
with your righteous words, are invading this place.
What do you want to do to them?
Demons are demons.
If not eradicated, they will bring disaster.
Mei Zhu Yu.
Even if you've forgotten your duty to the Changxi Palace,
have you forgotten your parents' deaths?
You came to Chang'an to find the Demon City
precisely to avenge them, didn't you?
The Divine Fire rained down 18 years ago,
and countless innocents died because of the Demon City.
Have you forgotten all that?
If you're here about what happened 18 years ago,
I'm afraid you've come to the wrong place.
You claim it had nothing to do with the Demon City,
but words alone prove nothing.
I have proof.
I'll take you there.
What is this place?
Demon Prison.
Just as the mortal world has laws, so too does the Demon City.
The evidence is here?
What kind of evidence?
You probably planned this all along,
luring us here so you could wipe us all out.
Don't be delusional.
I'd be disgusted just letting you into the Demon Prison.
It's here.
This is its cell.
Who?
Sinister Fiend who unleashed the Divine Fire 18 years ago.
You transformed heaven and earth, created the three realms,
and were worshipped by humans.
But now,
it is time for the ruler of this world to change.
Gui Ying, stop.
You want the Demon City to be in balance with the human world?
That's extremely stupid.
Why should these weak and incompetent mortals be allowed to step on demons?
How unjust!
They usually look down on demons, hunt us, kill us,
yet now they can do nothing but beg.
Cat Lord.
This is what Chang'an ought to look like.
We should rule this world.
You are hopeless.
Today, I'll scatter you into ashes.
Do you really think you can kill me?
Back then, Sinister Fiend suddenly appeared in Chang'an
and went on a killing spree.
The Demon City paid a heavy price to get rid of it.
The previous Cat Lord even died because of it.
But you mortals
are always blinded by obsession,
thinking all demons are evil.
You refuse to believe that the Demon City once saved you.
That's just one side of the story from your Demon City.
Who knows what kind of demonic tricks you used
to create a false illusion to deceive the world.
Cat Lord brought back the Mirror of Clarity at the cost of his life.
How can it be fake?
Sect Leader, this mirror is indeed made of a unique jade from Mount Rong.
It can see into one's heart and true nature.
It also has many restrictions on it.
The images in the mirror cannot be tampered with.
It is indeed the Mirror of Clarity.
So, all the images in the mirror are true?
Yes, since the Mirror of Clarity has a record, it cannot be wrong.
Mei Zhu Yu, what do you think?
Are you just going to believe them?
I believe in the Mirror of Clarity.
We went through all this trouble, only to find the culprit is already dead?
No.
Although the Divine Fire Chaos had nothing to do with the Demon City,
the true culprit is still alive.
That's impossible.
The remnant soul of Sinister Fiend.
Since the remnant soul is still here,
it proves that Sinister Fiend's core has not been destroyed yet.
The soul exists because of the core.
The previous Cat Lord must have brought back
this Mirror of Clarity with only fragments of information
to prove to the Demon City that Gui Ying was dead,
when in truth it was only to mislead the world.
Whatever the case, if Sinister Fiend still lingers,
the Demon City will hunt it down to the very end.
If you ask me,
since we've already descended the mountain, why not investigate together?
Sect Leader Chang Ming, what are you doing?
I come to the Demon City to slay demons.
How could this be? What did the Sect Leader do?
The spell he used to trap Lady Hu Zhu also carried the same evil energy.
With so much demonic power for me to use,
how could I just let it go?
This move...
It's him.
Another prey has delivered itself.
The Demonic Spell from Mount Luwei who devoured demonic energy.
Life Transforming Art?
How dare he...
Sect Leader
is practicing evil arts.
Brother Chang Ming, stop now!
Don't make things worse!
Worse?
What have I done wrong?
I'm practicing the Life Transforming Art so I can fight against demons.
So it's with you.
Once I've absorbed Gui Ying's core,
it'll be a service to the world by eliminating a scourge.
- Kitty! - Boss!
Evil shares a common root.
The moment the Life Transforming Art is used,
it will attract the core.
Cat Lord must indeed have hidden Lord Gui Ying all along
to mislead everyone.
Sinister Fiend's core?
No wonder
he gave all of his power as the Cat Lord to Wu Zhen.
How could this be?
Brother Mei.
Watch closely.
Once I devour Gui Ying's core,
it will be vengeance for your parents.
I'm helping you.
I never imagined Lord Gui Ying was sealed within this mongrel.
I wonder if this twist is a good thing or a bad thing?
Is it good or bad?
How can it be inside her body?
That's not going to work.
Changxi Truncheon has long been mine.
Changxi Truncheon, return!
- Zhen! - Boss!
Mei Zhu Yu!
I am the Sect Leader of Changxi Palace.
How dare you use the Changxi Truncheon to kill me!
Brother Chang Ming, you practice evil arts
and are so determined to attack the Demon City.
You're not doing it to eliminate demons and evil,
but to use them for your own gain.
Cultivation is easy for someone with your innate talent.
How could you understand my suffering?
I only chose the path I desired.
What have I done wrong?
How can this be?
Could it be Master?
Chang Ming!
Where did you learn this evil art of Life Transforming Art?
I found it by chance while I was looking through some books.
The rules of Changxi Palace are clear.
Practitioners who practice evil arts are condemned.
You know this.
Master.
It was just a momentary lapse of judgment.
Please forgive me this time.
Master.
I swear,
if I ever practice this evil art again,
my body and soul shall perish, and I shall vanish into thin air.
That's enough.
It's not too late to turn back.
Chang Ming, you have to remember,
the path of cultivation is like climbing a mountain.
There may be shortcuts on the rugged side.
It may seem tempting,
but once you step on it,
you can fall off a cliff at any time and be completely shattered.
Before you came to the Changxi Palace,
I was always the candidate to succeed as Sect Leader.
But since you arrived,
Master had been having second thoughts.
I lost again.
I know your moves, but you don't know mine.
I just got lucky.
You don't have to be humble.
I'm older than you.
I shouldn't have lost.
Master, it's my turn to clean the schoolroom today.
I'll be going now.
Go on.
Don't be disheartened.
Though Zhu Yu is younger than you and joined late,
he is the most talented disciple the Changxi Palace has had in 100 years,
and he has a firm character.
What a pity.
If it weren't for his mortal affairs,
I would have kept him here to be the Sect Leader.
Master.
The position has always been passed down to the eldest disciple.
I know, I was just saying.
Chang Ming, compared to Zhu Yu,
is far less talented.
Talent is something you're born with.
I'm not as good as you.
I have no choice.
He was just one step away.
Lord Gui Ying was about to reappear.
That little mongrel is so lucky.
Zhu Ying is still guarding the barrier entrance.
Ling Xiao, go and help her.
See if it can be repaired.
Yes.
This was our fault.
Even with the Sect Leader's deception,
we believed him so easily because of our past prejudices,
thinking that all demons are evil.
And I am even more at fault.
I was the first to come down the mountain before my senior brothers.
The moment I arrived in Chang'an, I met Lady Hu Zhu and Lady Wu.
They never harmed me and even took care of me often.
But even so, I didn't trust my own eyes and feelings
and still followed the Sect Leader's orders to turn my sword against them.
I'm really sorry.
We only heard stories about the treachery of the Demon City,
but just now we saw food stalls and shops, demons living their daily lives.
If we had not barged in,
they would still be living in peace.
If you all think that Chang Ming's death
is not enough to atone for what the Changxi Palace has done,
I am willing to stay and be at your disposal.
But can the others be allowed to leave first?
Since you've said that, our Demon City isn't unreasonable.
We don't want it to be said that we bully mortals.
You may leave.
But from this day onward,
Changxi Palace must never trouble the Demon City.
Two powers
cannot coexist.
From now on,
Changxi Palace is barred from Chang'an.
Hu Zhu.
See them out.
Gentlemen,
please come with me.
How are you feeling?
You should leave too.
Mei Zhu Yu.
Stay away from Zhen.
You saw with your own eyes that
the murderer who killed your father
lives inside me.
Kitty.
It must be the influence of Life Transforming Art.
Mr. Mei, don't worry. I'll take good care of her.