=Fortune Awaits=
=Episode 1=
On today's business stage,
Kim's Group shows remarkable growth.
Behind this golden, magnificent door,
a storm is quietly gathering.
The rivalry between Kim's Group's two heirs
concerns the fate of the entire group.
Mr. Jin, something happened in Binhai.
Go check it out.
(Demolition Site at Binhai Town)
What are you doing?
(Driver's Home)
Hu! Hu!
Mr. Jin Xiao is here.
(Binhai Town Market)
Young Master Jin Xiao is here.
If you offend him, you're done for.
Retreat!
Mr. Jin,
we didn't send anyone.
Jin Haochen is really in a hurry.
- He Fang.
- Are you okay?
- I'm fine.
Where are you going?
Get out here!
Get out of the car!
Listen to me.
I don't hit women.
I...
- Stop it!
- He Fang!
Let's go.
- He Fang.
Get up quickly.
- Are you okay?
Jin Xiao,
you'll regret this.
(Report on the Binhai Project)
Mr. Jin,
they must be sent by your brother
to stir up trouble in town.
Jin Haochen has disliked me for a while.
Don't worry about it.
But we need
to acquire this land soon.
Understood.
- Go check it out.
- Yes, sir.
Oh my!
What's wrong with you?
You hit my leg!
You can't leave.
Mr. Jin.
You are...?
Let me introduce myself.
I'm He Fang.
You sent people to demolish today, right?
I'm not here for compensation.
I just don't want to move.
But,
you owe me for damages and medical fees
and then apologize in person.
I'm talking to you. Did you hear me?
Jin Xiao.
Who are you?
Why are you touching me?
Taking advantage of me?
You've got some nerve, Jin Xiao.
Shameless!
Where is this place?
Welcome home, Mr. Jin.
Mr. Jin?
Mr. Jin,
you're awake.
Well,
who are you all?
Mr. Jin, what's wrong with you?
The pigs haven't been fed.
I need to hurry back.
Pigs?
Your...
Your brain is hurt?
Why is it you?
Forget it, I won't settle this now.
The pigs are hungry. They're still growing.
Move aside.
Good day, Mr. Jin.
(That Mr. Jin is really cunning.)
(He wants to kidnap me to threaten others.)
Mr. Jin.
I want to see Jin Xiao.
Jin Xiao?
Didn't the doctor say he is alright?
What's going on?
Amnesia?
Car accident?
No, no, no.
We look exactly the same.
Well...
This doesn't make sense.
Did you remember something?
What about after the car accident?
What happened then?
- He Fang!
He Fang!
Wake up, He Fang.
- Sorry, you can't.
- He Fang!
(In surgery)
(Bedside card: Neurosurgery, Jin Xiao)
- He Fang.
- Step aside.
What are you doing here?
I'm Mr. Jin's personal bodyguard.
I'm taking him to another hospital.
Kangxin Hospital will coordinate with you.
This isn't allowed.
You're not equipped to treat Mr. Jin.
Here he is, here he is.
What? Trying to run away?
I'm telling you, it's not that easy.
Your master is fine.
But my friend is unconscious.
Exactly.
Listen to me.
Until we sort this out today,
no one's leaving.
What? You wanna fight?
I'm warning you,
I never hit women.
Don't believe me? Try it.
Ouch, ouch.
How could you hit someone?
- Just wait.
- Don't run!
Don't run away!
That's how it happened.
(So they mistook me for Jin Xiao.)
(We really look exactly the same?)
Mr. Jin, rest assured.
Master Jin will return from abroad
in three months.
You have the top bodyguard,
Miss Zuo, escorting you.
Such incidents won't happen again.
Actually,
I'm not...
Forget it.
I have something to do.
I really need to leave.
Son,
my dear son!
How are you doing?
My poor son.
- Where are you hurt?
- Brother, are you okay?
Let me see.
(Brother?)
(Jin Xiao has an older brother?)
(Then this woman)
(is his mother?)
Madam, Mr. Jin, don't worry.
The doctor has checked.
There's no health issue.
Everyone,
actually, I'm really not...
Since everything's fine,
sign the document.
Everyone's waiting for you.
(Binhai Land Development Project.)
(Then can I...?)
Son, what's wrong?
Mom.
Bro.
I'm glad you're here.
I... I...
My head and stomach hurt.
My arm...
My arm hurts too.
I can't sign this.
Maybe...
Let's put it aside for now.
You...
Young Master Jin Xiao's head was injured.
The doctor said
he needs rest.
That's right.
My brother
is having great luck.
He's pulled through such a big ordeal.
Jin Xiao, get some rest.
I'll visit you another day.
I hope from now on,
you'll always
turn misfortune into good fortune.
Alright.
You all can leave too.
If anything happens,
call me anytime.
It's such a big car accident.
He's completely unharmed.
Unbelievable.
This is indeed strange.
Not sure what tricks he's up to.
Son,
no need to rush.
Since he's not well,
let him rest properly
at home.
Mr. Jin.
Useless fool!
Get out.
Sorry, Mr. Jin.
Do they really think I'm Jin Xiao?
Then maybe I can
abolish the acquisition plan.
Tomorrow will be better.
(Annual gala)
Tonight, we'll camp out.
Don't doubt, don't hesitate.
You are the next lucky one.
Wish you good Luck.
Since I am here,
I should make myself at home.
Will you stay with me in the future?
You serve me.
A bit higher.
Higher, a bit higher.
Use more strength. Are you weak?
You call yourself a bodyguard?
What are you doing?
Sorry, Mr. Jin.
I was too rough.
Mr. Jin.
What are you doing?
- Let me fix your arm.
- Back!
Let me help you.
Mr. Jin.
This is life.
Luck is finally on my side.
(Outpatient)
He Fang.
You're awake.
You...
Who are you?
♪Night falls, the road's short, fate turns♪
♪Who lied to escape judgment?♪
♪How to settle this all?♪
♪Lingering entanglements,
each shining bright♪
♪Some answers remain unspoken♪
♪I was lucky to have a long bond♪
♪To say I like you is too late♪
♪Thinking back to when we first met♪
♪My palms were sweaty♪
♪You deeply attracted me♪
♪Missing ten years for regretful reunion♪
♪I suddenly realized love was deeply buried♪
♪Recalling your laughter and tears♪
♪The closest thought vanished into thin air♪
♪Longing is hard to bear♪
♪You haunt my dreams♪
♪Yet you remain indifferent♪
♪In a flash, I knew love still remains♪
♪Once I pushed away, now regrets undone♪
♪I want to wait until we grow old together♪
♪To fill in the love we've missed♪
♪I long to hold you in my arms again♪
♪I won't let go this time♪