Sorry to bother you.
It's nothing, P'.
How do you know what we have to use for a offering?
Because...
I'm smart.
It's Google, P'.
What is Google?
Google is Google.
But I actually wonder why we need to use Thai desserts?
Don't the Gods get bored of it and want to eat something else? Maybe bingsu or cold crepes?
Bingsu?
Cold crepes?
What are those?
P'Mes, do you really not know?
Well, you you will know them after
you live here for a while.
Oh?
P'Mes.
- P'Mes.
Is something wrong, P'?
Huh?
Is something wrong?
No, I feel a bit weird.
Something like... moving to a new place?
I think so.
Because before this, all I saw was just grave
and a grave and a grave and a grave.
Actually, I also felt the same way the
first time I moved to the dorm.
Well, let's go.
P'Mes.
Can you act like a normal person?
Let's go.
Welcome ~
Oh.
Come in, P'Mes.
How is it? Beautiful?
This is my room.
Did you decorate yourself?
Yes, I did it all.
I love basketball.
Thun!
Uh...P'Mes, this is my bedroom.
But, but, but, but....
Would it better if you sleep out here?
How about over there?
It's totally fine.
I've been sleeping in a grave for so long...
sleeping on a sofa would be much better!
Awesome!
Do you live here alone?
Yes, I live here alone.
I can't live with other, you see?
I always make a mess like this.
If I had a roommate we would have lots of fights.
Some days I also don't take a shower.
Ew... not taking a shower?
But P'Mes hasn't take a shower for longer than me.
There!
Seems like you like teasing people.
Well, it's quite strange.
Like having a ghost as your first roommate?
It is so cool.
Oh~
Why did you come back so fast?
Where are my gifts?
Gifts?
What gifts?
You said you couldn't attend class because
you wanted to go visit your mom.
Then, where are our snacks?
Snacks?
Oh, I forgot.
Why are you guys like this? Can't you
knock on the door before coming in?
I want my key back.
No way.
When you lose your key you will borrow mine.
Isn't that true?
What were you doing?
Masturbating?
What the heck? Masturbating!
Oh ho ~
You have no food at all.
What is your refrigerator for? Huh?
Smile. Smile.
Okay, let's go.
Why are you looking at me?
Go.
Okay, go, go, go, go.
I'm going to basketball practice.
I will be back later tonight.
Who are you talking to?
I'm talking with both of you.
Then let's go.
What? What is it?
But what did you just say?
I'm going to basketball practice.
I will be back later tonight together.
Thun!
Khiem, you're the best.
Okay then...
Thun, it is your turn today to collect the basketballs.
Good luck.
Here.
28. 29.
30. All here.
Plai.
Here is your water.
Are your finished?
I'm hungry.
Sure. I am hungry, too.
Okay.
Ai'Prince, Ai'Khiem!
Let's go!
Okay.
Let's go. I'm hungry!
Want to fight, Prince?
No!
Both of you hurry up!
Oh ho ~
I'm thirsty, too.
Buy it yourself.
Hmmm... you are using two standards here, Plai.
Are you crazy?
Between friend and boyfriend, how could I treat them the same?
Friend and boyfriend?
Fine...
Keep acting like this.
Someday if you two end up falling for each other real...
It would serve you right.
There is no way.
It is better being friends.
Right, girlfriend?
Let's go. I'm hungry.
Let's go.
- I need to finish this first.
- Let's go get changed.
- Where are you taking me?
- To change our clothes.
Oh, right. Let me help.
Come on, let me help you take off your pants.
Stop playing around!
Didn't you say P'Chin invited you to watch a movie?
Why are you eating this much?
Didn't he treat you to a meal?
He did.
But it didn't taste good.
When you eat in front o a guy you have
to look elegant. I can't eat like this.
It is unlike eating with you
guys, it's much more delicious.
But we are all guys, too?
It's not the same.
With a guy like P'Chin...
you have to care about appearance like crazy.
For example, "N'Plai, would you like this?"
Or "N'Plai, P' thinks this one is good."
I can't stand that.
It gives me goosebumps.
Being polite is good.
No! I don't like it.
Was it like...
Sawasdee khrap, N'Plai khrap
Umm... Here it is.
Do you like this khrap?
Yes, this one is good.
Or like this, N'Plai khrap, would you like some steamed egg khrap?
Sure.
Or... N'Plai khrap, would like any of my muscle khrap?
Let me give you some khrap.
N'Plai khrap. Would you like something to drink khrap?
P'Prince will buy it for you khrap.
Why are you guys making fun of him like that?
Hey, where are you going?
To buy some drinks.
I'll go with you.
He must be like...
N'Plai khrap...
Even though I don't have a sports car,
I can make you love me khrap.
Ew ~
N'Plai khrap, can I give a ride home khrap.
Stop teasing here.
Oh, four glasses of green soda, please.
Okay.
Make it three.
Oh?
Plai doesn't drink green soda.
And a glass of red soda, please.
Okay.
You are so meticulous. They were right to pick you
to be the secretary of the Student Council.
I remember this...
because Khiao told me once...
if Plai ever drank green soda...
it means Plai has a crush on him.
Hmmm.
So since first year,
she hasn't drank the green soda anymore.
You remember everything.
Can't believe they both take that seriously?
I know.
Thank you.
Here it is.
Here.
Thank you.
Let's go.
Hey, wait a second.
How much?
40 baht.
Oh. Here.
Thank you so much.
Here's yours.
Here.
Your green soda.
Thank you khrap
And here...
the girlfriend's red soda khrap.
Aw, you are so cute, boyfriend.
You even remember that I don't drink green soda.
Oi~
If you keep playing like this, why don't
you just become a couple for real?
Don't
These are mine.
Why?
You won't share with your friend?
It's mine.
If you want some, go buy it then.
Do you usually eat chocolate?
Last time I brought some from Japan, you didn't eat any.
Well...
I just want to try it.
Just a piece?
Go buy some!
I need to go. See you tomorrow!
See you.
What are you doing?
Do you want to use the computer, P'Mes?
Is that a computer?
Yes.
Wow, so cool!
How is it cool, P'?
It is just an ordinary laptop.
If Thun ever saw a computer from my
time, you would know how cool this is.
If you see my iPad,
P' would think it is from the future.
After 20 years in a grave...
time went on like this, isn't this the future?
20 years? Isn't that like time warping to the future?
Warp?
What is warp?
Warp...
is like time jumping. Time jump to the future.
Do you get it?
Never mind, then.
I know you like it.
So I bought it.
Thank you.
From now on, I will turn on the
electric joss sticks all around the room.
So when I am not here you can use anything in the room.
So you won't get bored, P'.
For real?
Yes.
P'Mes, you know sometimes you act like a kid.
Since...
we are going to live together,
Let's set up some rules.
What are the rules about?
First of all,
wherever P'Mes want to go, whatever P'Mes
want to do, P'Mes need to tell me first.
Are you my guardian or something?
Second...
P'Mes can't use being a ghost to
do anything more than necessary.
Don't play tricks on people.
Don't let them know about you.
If someone finds out, it could turn into a big problem.
Are you threatening me?
Yes, I am.
I am letting you stay here with me...
so that makes me your guardian.
If anything happens to you,
I am responsible for it.
Actually,
I just saying it...
if you're not stubborn, that should me enough.
Okay?
I won't be stubborn.
Who is calling me?
Hello?
Thun, have you arrived at your dorm?
I have. What's up?
How are your grades?
My grades?
Nothing below a B.
Lie...
If you know that, then why do you ask me?
About you going out at night and
drinking. Be sure to not drink too much.
For that I can assure you I only drink a little, for real.
Right...
The other day, I saw that your friends
tagged a photo of you in a bar.
Your face was all red. And you dare
say that you don't drink?
Hey... I am going to have my friends unfriend you.
You are keeping so many secrets.
What time will you come this week?
So I can prepare you some food?
Oh ~
I won't be going this week.
Oh... why?
I have basketball practice this week.
Ah, Okay. Okay.
Talk to you later.
Okay, bye-bye.
What are you looking at?
Well, P', I am going to take a shower now.
- Hey!
What are you doing here, P'?
I was about to ask you to help me...
with that small computer.
But...
I don't think I need it now.
If you don't need it now...
can you get out, P'?
Do you want to have a Facebook account?
Can I?
Of course!
But I have to register for an email for you first.
I'll register for you.
What are you doing?
Do you eat this every morning?
Do you want some, P'?
So...
this is why you are a giant kid.
Let's eat, P'.
Actually, I should let you eat first.
Mes can only eat spirit food, thus Thun doesn't need to prepare another set of food for him.
It wouldn't be expensive.
Sure, we can do that.
Did you sleep well last night?
I did.
My main job is sleeping.
What about you? Sleep well?
Me?
Of course.
Uhh... P'.
I need to go to the university.
What would you like to do today?
What?
You want to use the computer?
P', you already know how to use a computer, right?
Then...
And you know how to type?
I do. It's easy.
This is the internet, P'.
It is used to search for information.
Eh. P'?
What is your full name?
Maybe I could search for you.
I can't remember.
That's alright.
You can just play on the computer when
I am not here so you won't get bored.
Thun, hurry! Are you ready?
Okay.
I'm ready. I am coming.
P'Mes, I am going to class.
See you in the evening.
Due to an act of injustice...
that led to violent riots was...
is subject violations to the law under Article 72, Criminal Code.
Then, that is all for today.
See you next class.
- Thank you.
Hey...
What?
What you did that day led to violent riots!
Hey, you all.
What was the first 15 minutes about?
I couldn't write it down.
Hey,
You can borrow my notes to copy.
I noted all the keywords here.
You can return it to me later.
Let me see it.
Wow! You are good at taking notes.
Can I borrow them, too?
I've changed my mind.
I won't let you borrow it.
What the hell?
"You are good at taking notes."
"You are good at taking notes?"
"I won't let you borrow."
What's the deal? You are so evil.
Don't be an obstacle like that. That is the ninth girl already.
Oh. But look at Thun.
He's been keeping his virginity for this long.
Those who come into his life have to be screened by us.
Really?
Wait! Wait Wait!
Who said that I a virgin?
- Oh!
Oh!
Oh, hey...
~ This isn't like what we talked about together, when you told me you were choosing him and that you'd never... ~
They are singing  by Atom Chanakan, because Plai's "Oh, hey" is part of the lyrics.
- That's enough. That's enough. ~
Come home~
You're crazy!
Who's turn to be the sugar daddy this weekend?
It's yours.
Why do you ask? Are you planning on standing us up?
Me again?
It's yours.
- Me?
- Yes?
Then...
I want to watch a movie.
Huh?
Watch a movie again?
So boring, Ai'Prince.
Then...
What does Plai want to do?
I will let you choose this time.
But if you all want to watch a movie,
I am ok with it.
What movie do you want to watch?
Let's just choose at the theater.
Hey! Wait, wait, wait!
Ai'Thun!
What's wrong?
Did you forget to log out of Facebook?
What is it?
[How to reincarntate]
How to reincarntate...
Shit!
P'Mes?
What do you mean by "How to reincarntate"?
I was playing around on the internet and it asked..
"What's on my mind?"
So you posted a status like,
"How to reincarntate?"
or "How to bring your memories back?" Like that?
I can't do that?
This one is Facebook, P'. It is not Google.
You don't understand?
Let me explain.
This is a website...
is Google.
This is the search bar.
Type in whatever you want to see or want to do to know.
You put it here in this box.
Then the results will show up.
But what you were using was Facebook.
It's like an online house,
like you have an online world.
You can connect with friends through the internet.
It's very convenient and easy.
Hey, let me show you.
This is my Facebook. Do you want to see my photos?
Ai'Prince...
and this is Ai'Khiao.
My close friends that you saw that day.
What about this one?
This is Plai.
Your girlfriend?
Why?
I'm just asking.
Do you want to have a Facebook account?
Can I?
Of course! But I have to register for an email for you first.
I'll register for you.
How about this name?
Mes Mung Ming Who Doesn't Have
A Real Name Like Anyone Else
Do you like it?
I do.
I'm so glad that you like the name.
I will try to like it.
~I keep asking continuously why I love~
~It's like I'm thinking hard that I love you.~
~In my heart~
~An uncertainty~
~It's not like you're someone important~
~It's not like you're someone that I dreamed of in my heart~
~No need to worry~
~What the heart once drawn to keep~
Oh, P'Mes...
I'm leaving now.
~I got eased once I met you~
I will come back soon.
Bye-bye.
~The image of that person is no longer in my heart~
~There is only you~
~You look the best more than anyone else~
~Please be confident~
~Just be yourself~
~In the way that I love is enough~
~No matter what I will love~
~And I love you the most, forever~
How your day, P'.
I'm so bored.
I'm so tired.
~No need to be afraid, no matter what~
I'm going to sleep now. Bye-bye.
~I will love you~
What are you doing, P'?
I'm ready.
Ready for what, P'?
Today is the weekend.
Even though I'm a ghost, I can count the days.
Oh~
I'm in trouble.
Oh, P'...
can we change it to another day?
Why?
I have tutored you you many days.
Didn't you promise me that you
will take me out on your day off?
But today is Ai'Princes day to be the sugar daddy.
I am planning to make him broke.
Then take me with you.
I can't, P'.
If I take you with me, they will figure it for sure.
Like lighting the electric joss stick or talking alone.
It'll be bad,
Let's go another time.
Are you ready, Khun Thun?
I already sent a Line message to Plai...
that you are ready.
Do you know I have emptied my
stomach for 100 years for this.
All just for you, Ai'Prince.
Oho ~
- Are you planning on making the most out of my money?
- Absolutely.
Are you ready? Let's go.
Let's go.
Shall we?
Hey, let's go.
What's wrong?
Stomach ache.
Ignore it. We'll find medicine for you later.
It really hurts.
It hurts a lot.
That much?
Yes.
Do you want to go see a doctor?
That's not necessary.
I'll just stay here and rest.
Are you sure?
I will feel better after I get some rest.
I was planning to eat Korean barbecue
after we watched the movie.
You will miss everything.
Yeah, it is fine. You guys can go.
Are you sure?
Will you be okay?
- Are you sure you will be alright?
Ai'Khiem, hurry! Before he changes his mind!
Oh, so stingy.
You're not worried about your friend?
Forget him. He will be fine.
Let's go.
Get better soon, friend.
Okay, thanks.
You're good at acting.
I'm a future lawyer,
so I need to understand psychology.
Also...
I don't want to break my promise with you.
Thank you.
So where do you want to go?
Hey!?
We are in trouble, P'.
Ai'Prince! Ai'Prince! It's Ai'Thun! Ai'Thun!
Let's go, P'.
Hurry up, let's go.
P'Mes!
That's cool.
Let's go, P'.
259 baht?
I'll order. Pick what you want to eat.
I don't have the heart to order any.
Why?
What kind of shaved ice could be this expensive?
Shaved ice?
This is bingsu, P'.
Oh, yeah, bingsong... bingsu whatever.
That's it. Then...
I'll order for you, ok?
I won't eat it.
Chocolate?
There.
Let me order it for you.
I want to order, please.
OK...
I want the chocolate bingsu.
And watermelon smoothie.
OK.
Do you want to eat this?
Ready?
1... 2... 3...
Dig in!
I thought you said you didn't want to eat?
You look like you really love the dessert here.
Try the watermelon smoothie, P'. It's very good.
You like it, right?
Oh ~
It's 5,500!
This pair of shoes is the same price as a television!
Television?
Do you know the last person who
said that to me was my dad.
Isn't it the same?
It's the same.
Is there something wrong?
Oh, it's nothing.
I'll take this pair, please.
Sure, sir.
Ok, please go the cashier.
You're buying it?
It's 5,500!
You want a pair?
Here are you shoes.
I've paid.
Ok, thank you.
Thank you.
You didn't pay any cash?
I have paid already.
He might be talking on the phone.
People don't use cash anymore nowadays, P'.
What is that?
You're confused?
There are a lot of things for you to learn.
It will be to teach you.
Let's go.
When we let Ai'Prince pick the movie, it
is another cute romantic movie like that.
Oh.
It's my right to choose.
And Plai picked it, too.
It was a majority vote. It was 2 to 1. So we won.
It's your right!
Your right!
You two are always on the same side.
If Thun came with us,
he wouldn't choose that kind of movie.
Oh, it's called democracy. Ever heard of it?
Yeah, ever heard of it?
I forgot to take a social studies class.
What about Ai'Thun?
How is he?
Might have died in the bathroom.
Yeah, or he might...
How about...
I bring you hear again next time, okay?
Do you want to eat anything else?
I am full right now.
Hey?!
We are in trouble, P'.
Ai'Prince! Ai'Prince! It's Ai'Thun! Ai'Thun!
Prince!
What's wrong with you?
Hurry up?
This way, P'Mes!
Ai'Prince!
- Hurry up!
- Calm down.
Hurry up!
In here, P'.
Why do they only love me at times like this!
Hurry up, Ai'Prince! Over here!
Are you sure that it was him?
It must be him.
Why don't you just call him?
Why are we running?!
Right.
Then why did you follow me?
Call him!
Just call him!
Did he pick up?
- I just called.
- Hurry up.
He's not picking up.
It probably wasn't him.
Why would he lie to his friends?
We will see if he lied or not.
Let's check on him at the dorm! Hurry!
- Quickly
- Oh, let it go!
- Hurry!
- Back to the dorm?
- P', hurry. Hurry up,
- What happened?
They are coming! My friends are coming!
What am I going to do? This is not good!
Oh, you guys.
See. I told you it wasn't him.
Ai'Thun, you were here all day?
Of course.
I slept here all day.
I missed the movie, too.
Ai'Khiao says he saw you at the mall.
I told him that it wasn't you,
but he didn't believe me.
Then why did you turn off your phone?
My phone?
Was it turned off?
Oh, yeah.
Here, I turned it on.
You got lucky.
Hey, you guys!
What?
What...?
What about Plaifah?
Right Where is Plaifah?
Hey, she is calling me.
Hello, Plai.
Damn, you made me run like 4 x 100.
I still don't feeling well.
Yes, Ai'Prince and Ai'Khiao are here with me.
He said he saw me at the mall?
That's crazy. Don't believe him.
You guys should go home.
Give me a second.
I want to sleep some more and talk to Plai, too.
Go. go, go.
Was that really not you?
It wasn't me. I was here sick.
But I think...
- Ai'Prince...
- I'm opening the door. Let's go.
See you. I'll go see you when I am better.
Bye.
It's okay now.
Yeah.
They just ran off and totally forgot about me, you know.
And you what?
They asked me as if he was my girlfriend.
If you really had a girlfriend, they would stop.
That's why I don't have a girlfriend.
I really want to know what kind
of girl would be your girlfriend?
I just got home. That's all. Let's end the call.
See you at the university.
Bye.
Ok, bye.
Grandpa, I am home.
I missed you so much.
You are back already.
Didn't you say you will be late?
I missed my grandpa so I came home early.
Sweet talking like this...
what do you want from me?
You do this with your boyfriend.
Your medicine, sir.
Who can I do that with?
I don't have a boyfriend.
Boys nowadays are boring, Grandpa.
Really?
What about Thun?
I heard you call him boyfriend.
Oh...
That is not serious.
We are just joking around with each other.
Actually, being friends is better.
Really?
If we were dating...
and we broke up...
we might not be able to look at each other's face.
I'm going to take a shower now.
I'll come down after to have dinner.
Okay.
Be quick. I'll wait for you.
I'm going to take a shower now.
Hey! It's true.
I didn't know at first...
But do you remember last night
when I kicked your shoes bag?
Does that mean you can touch objects now?
It's not that easy.
But I can do it now.
That's cool.
Hey, P'...
If you can touch me...
you will be no different from an ordinary person.
I think I can only touch objects for now.
But it's alright.
This is good enough.
Now let's see...
I can turn on the television myself.
I can turn on and use the computer by myself.
I can even light the electric joss stick by myself, too.
Or perhaps do the laundry yourself,
mop the floor yourself, or clean the bathroom yourself?
Hey,
are you using me?
It's because you can do it.
By the way, Thun...
Can I ask you something?
Who is your girlfriend?
Why are you asking?
I don't see you taking pictures
with any other girl but Plaifah.
Are you Plaifah's boyfriend?
Why do ask me so much?
Are you my boyfriend?
What does that mean?
You told me once before...
you had a girlfriend,
but I have never seen her.
I used to have one.
But we already broke up.
That day I didn't finish answering your question.
I don't like girls who are bossy.
I don't like girls who get jealous.
It is tiring to keep arguing.
Being single is more comfortable.
Why are you smiling, P'?
I'm heading to class now.
Wait, wait, wait.
Can I go with you to the university today?
No way.
We almost got caught yesterday, P'.
Staying the room by myself is lonely
and I don't have anything to do.
Please, let me go to university with you.
I promise I will do all the housework.
I'll sweep the floors, mop the floors,
wash and dry the clothes,
and even clean the bathroom.
Please.
Please, let me go with you.
You have to stay close to me.
Really?
Thun is the best.
P'Mes.
P'Mes, quickly.
Or else I am going to be late for class.
What's up, you guys?
Hey.
I transferred the dorm rental fees to you.
Add another 500 for your liquor.
I have it noted. Why did you forget that detail?
Fucking stingy.
Ouch! That hurts!
It's all you.
Where's Plaifah?
This morning she said P'Chin will pick her up.
P'Chin?
Chin...
Chin the sugar daddy?
Yes.
Let's wait we should hear him coming soon.
You'll see...
First the sound of someone speeding up.
Followed by the sound of the car exhaust.
See?
Then watch carefully.
His care will stop perfectly right in front of our faculty.
Watch!
And then you will see...
him being a gentleman.
He will open the door for the lady.
See, exactly what I told you would happen.
"Sawasdee Khrap, I'm leaving now khrap."
Walking so beautifully.
Shut up.
You told us you didn't like him,
so why did you let him give you a ride.
Why? Jealous?
My grandfather is in the hospital,
so P'Chin offered me a ride.
What time is it?
Should we head to class?
Let's go.
Shall we? Hurry up.
Hey, Plai, Plai. Plai.
He is really muscular. Are his muscles real?
Stop it!
P'Mes?
Is there something wrong?
It's nothing.
Let's go.
There was a couple riding a motorbike
together and got into an accident.
The woman fell and lost consciousness.
But the man dodn't help her.
Because he thought his girlfriend was already dead.
But then eight days later she died.
In this case, can this man be
found guilty  based on the law?
Professor, khrap?
I think he was found not guilty.
The court said the defendant and it
led to the death of the second victim.
The defendant caused the victim
to fall from the motorbike.
That made her lose consciousness for eight
days without informing anyone.
So the defendant knew the consequences...
that if that victim or the woman didn't die.
He would be found guilty of attempting
to cause the death of another.
Shit! P'Mes!
Go play somewhere else.
Khun Thunyakorn.
Please be quiet.
What's the matter?
I can't keep up with the lesson khrap.
Stay focused, Thunakorn.
If you want to be a lawyer in the future...
how could you show that confused face to the judge?
Khrap.
Ai'Khiem.
Do you think Ai'Thun is being weird today?
Maybe he hasn't recovered from his stomach ache.
That is not relevant.
Can you wait outside the classroom?
If you're here, I can't learn anything.
But you told me to stay close to you.
It is fine to not be this close.
Please go wait outside.
Hey.
If you are not ready to learn,
then you can go outside.
Please excuse me.
Why aren't you going?
He called for you.
He's calling me?
"Ai'Khiem. Ai'Khiem."
I don't think so, bastard.
If you 're in the classroom, I can't learn anything.
Please stay here, P'.
Don't you want me to stay close to you?
P'Mes.
I know. Don't get upset.
Wait for me here in front of the
classroom. I will pick you up later.
That is all for today.
See you next time.
Thank you.
See you.
Plai
Plai, come.
Ai'Prince.
Come here.
What?
Don't you think Ai'Thun seems a little crazy lately?
Maybe he didn't get enough sleep.
That's not the reason.
Ho... He seems like he has been cursed.
Cursed. Don't you know cursed?
Are you sure?
How do you know?
How could I not know?
My neighbor acted like this before.
Don't make me say this...
but it was...
What symptoms, you guys?
Ah... your stomachache symptoms.
- Right
- How are you feeling, friend?
I'm Okay.
Let's go. We have lots of work to do.
Right. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go.
Hurry, what are you waiting for?
What I said is true.
No!
Ai'Prince
What kind of petitions should we be looking for
I can't think of any.
Then...
I will help you find a rare case petition.
Deal! Don't change your mind.
Oi... Let's get something to eat.
I'm hungry and need to eat something. Let's go.
Thun?
Huh?
You guys can go first. I am
going to use the restroom.
What was he looking at?
I told you.
He's being weird.
Do you believe me now that he is cursed?
Yes, I believe you.
Told you so. Let me call my neighbor first.
P'Mes?
P'Mes!
P'Mes.
P'Mes, why are you here?
I told you to wait for me in front of the classroom.
What would I do if you got lost?
How would I find you?
Are you able to go back to the dorm?
P'Mes.
Are you listening to me?
Economic Management, Economic Analysis,
Marketing Management.
I brought them all from the shelves for you.
Thank you.
How many books can we borrow with the library card?
Two books.
But I only have one card.
I have another card with me, P'Mes.
P'Mes.
P'Mes!
Thun.
I think I studied here before.
[Preview]
There is no information in the system.
Is that even possible, P'?
What kind of ghost am I?
No name or age.
If you can't remember your full name,
it will be hard to find out more.
I just want to know what happened to me, that's all.
P'Mes.
Who did he call?
Ai'Prince.
Huh?
Did you check on the security guard?
Yes.
Dude.
Are you sure about this?
I am.
Run!
Who's there?
Ai'Khiem, wait for me.
Hey, stop! Stop there!
Edited Subs and Retimed using ThaiBL, Chingming Subs and GCinee