Add this
Your money here is mine
It's already 500,000 or 600,000
Do you want it
Take it home together
Manage for your parents
Need not
It's better if you help save it
All right
We're this weekend
Planning to go out for an outing and barbecue
Do you want to bring it with you
Little peach came over together
never mind
I've been lately
Don't want to go out
Then you really don't want to move
I'll take the little peach over
Bubble has been making noise recently
Want to play with your sister
Good too
Then I'll bother you and Bingbing
fine
All asleep
Finally got to sleep
Little Taozi was having a crazy time today
My voice was hoarse
How introverted she is
Still a child
Stay at home with your mother for a long time
Don't see outsiders or contact society
This goes on
It's really not good
yes
This weekend
Still reading the report
Bank reserve rate
Already adjusted to the highest point in history
This amount is tight
The review is also more stringent
The workload is full every day
I can only go home after
Let's take a look at these analysis reports
Thank you so much
Come
Then I'll go and rest first
You wait for me
I'll take a break with you
Don't you still have to read the report
Nothing better than you
What's wrong with speaking so numb
On the bank
Is there no news at all
knew
I'll think of another way
Liu Jun
I heard of Taozi
Weekends at your house
It's causing you trouble
The child was taken last Friday
You've just heard it now
Are you
Haven't been home for several days
Don't think about it
I've really been working lately
No time to do anything else
Where are you
Where else can it be
Of course, I'm in the company when I go to work
I'll come to find you
Have something to talk to you
OK, come on
Are you sick
So bad
I'm not sick
Copper futures have fallen too hard recently
Must stay up late to watch the plate
bring it on
Wake up with a cup of coffee
You said you
months ago
Said me speechless
Now I am worried about this
Your financial market
I really don't understand
My dad told me yesterday
The stock index has reached 6,000 points
Your futures
How could it fall so badly
Not just futures
Second-hand housing transactions also fell to the bottom
Nothing at all in the past
The grand occasion of the golden September and silver October
Our company's capital chain
Something went wrong
Do you have six million on hand
The best cash
If not
Please issue a letter of credit for me
Our company's quota
Already reached the top
Can't open it
cash
There is definitely no cash
The heat treatment center is being expanded recently
Money is being used everywhere
Bank monetary tightens
I can only open it for you
Three months letter of credit
Is it OK
That's great
It's only three months
I'm not polite to you
Follow with other companies
The same number of points
Pay your agency fee
Agent fees are not required
You find a time
Send someone here
Financial connection with me
Thank you
Things are resolved
OK
Don't drink coffee
Go home and go to bed quickly
good
Then I'll leave first
Take the clothes
Thanks
What a big deal
Bye-Bye
Eat
Don't eat it anymore
Carrie should be at home
Why doesn't she answer the phone
Such a big brother and sister
What's so strange about going out for a walk
Right
Whoever stipulates that she must stay at home
She has been in a bad mood over the past few months
It's a good thing to be willing to go out
Last week
I went to the villa
You don't know
Her mental state
Isn't this a little bit?
Let's take a look at the direction of the opening in the afternoon
The index is 6,000
Are you not afraid
Don't be afraid
I'll tell you
You'll see the price
Three thousand
Everyone says it's too expensive to afford it
When it was five thousand, someone said
What a bubble to say
What's going to crash
Look at it now
A house worth ten thousand square meters
Crazy robbery
The stock market is the same
You think six thousand is a high position
The next month is 8,000
Not to the top yet
Not the top of the mountain
Just halfway up the mountain
I know better than you if I sell a house
House prices are now available
Signs of decline
Several branches this month
All are zero deals
There is absolutely no situation
You imagined it was so optimistic
I know I know
Observation
I'll observe
Hate
Eat and eat
Eat some more
Have a meal
Jiali
I'm back
A business trip a few days ago
I bought one for you intently
Lucky little hairpin card
Bless you to have a smooth and smooth life
Peaceful and safe
Come on, I'll put it on for you
Is it good looking
nice
Stop her stop her
Hello, please wait a moment
What's wrong
Hello
I am
I know Shen Jiali
What
Comrade police officer
Have you made a mistake
My friend
Her family doesn't lack money at all
How could she do it
What about theft
Not everyone who steals things
It's all because of lack of money
Have you heard of stole
Our colleagues are investigating
See if she has any previous studies
Absolutely no
My friend, she recently
Not very good with her husband
Maybe mentally trance
But it's absolutely impossible to steal something
No quirks
What about this
Not big in itself
Found it in the supermarket
She wears unpaid goods
I just want to see her bag
Have you hidden anything else
But this lady is very uncooperable
The supermarket cannot search for bags
So I had to call the police
That's it
Surveillance videos in the supermarket
Has been sent
Let's finish reading first
Thank you very much
I didn't steal
Liu Jun, I didn't steal
I really didn't steal
It's okay, Jiali
Look at my bag
You see
Nothing to them
Liu Jun didn't have it at all
It's okay
All over
fine
This is the case, no one else blames you
All capital city Hiroaki
Liu Jun
Don't tell others, okay
well
Hiroaki Abura
Don't tell Bingbing either
I won't say it
But Hongming is responsible to you
Hiroaki and others are not good at receiving this
Always talking to sleep at night
Not good-looking
I'm actually very worried about him
You said he was alone
Under such a great pressure
I can't help with anything
yes
I've seen him today, too
But don't worry
He is
Work has been too hard recently
No big problem
You two
All need to be adjusted
For each other and for the child
OK
It's okay, Jiali
fine
Thank you
The market
After a continuous decline of several days
Finally welcoming
A rare rebound
The Shanghai Composite Index closed today
Five thousand four hundred and twelve points
A sharp rise of 4.94%
Trading volume increased compared to yesterday
The stock market has fallen for more than a month
My dad has been buying at the bottom and waiting for the rebound
I don't know if it bounced back
Let him have a meal
Dad, stop watching and have a meal
Still blue chip stocks in the market
But the shortcomings are
This rebound
No significant increase in volume
So how to judge
What is the current market trend
I think
The market rebounded sharply today
It is an oversold nature
These stock analysts
Talk very well every day
In fact, ordinary retail investors
Isn't that just luck?
Put it in your eyes
Clip yourself
Sit there and there
What's the situation very serious
Dad, we have been teaching Xiaopupao
Can't watch TV while eating
You can't be a bad example
Know
I don't believe in those things either
I just watched it casually
Not that I'm talking about you
Your status really needs to be adjusted
My dad said
The easiest thing you are at your age
It's cardiovascular disease
Not only should you pay attention to your diet and rest
And there's not too much pressure
Otherwise, hypertension stroke
This is really not a joke
My in-laws are an expert in this field
I have to listen to him
Yes
Then don't think about having a good meal
OK OK OK
Get me that
Get that for you
Bingbing, I'll tell you
I'm ready for the funds
Buy on dips
After this rebound
I'll clear the stock soon
Don't play anymore
I don't want to make money
Just pay less
How much pressure is there now
Have to leave
I have to make my life
Keep it
Yes or no
Don't eat or sleep
You're not as sensible as Bubble
Yes or no
Let's have a meal
Eat and eat
Don't say it, don't say it
Bubble and eat
Invested in such a big project
Don't tell me
Something went wrong and remembered me
What's the problem
only
It's just that the funds are tight
Mr. Money
Renovate such a building
You have to invest 100 million
More than 100 million
How much does that cost
I'm alone
It must be unbearable
Half of these shares
It's helping several clients to support it
They have special identities
Not convenient for public participation
A regular approach
Just find someone like me
agent
Risk
What about the risks
Futures stocks are falling now
Your own capital chain
All have problems
Now I have to start managing private lending again
This is too risky
Don't worry
Stocks and futures
It won't keep falling
This project
There is no big risk
sister
Completed this project
We both have the rest of our lives
No need to work hard
All can retire early
We used to be a family of four
Living in fifteen square meters
Now we don't have it
Your own villa car
I also have my own store and business
The money you make
Mom and Dad and Me
I didn't even dare to think about it before
Hiroaki
Do you think you're not making enough money
We'll invest in it now
Take this risk
Is it worth it
Because we were too poor before
So I encountered such an opportunity
It should be seized more
I can't let us
Back to the past
Even if there is a slight possibility
None of them can do it
sister
A timid step is hard to move
This is a risk worth taking
You borrow money from private
How much interest can they be given
You guys come and talk about economic trends
As a result, the opening and closing
All real estate markets
Isn't other industries important?
Is people's livelihood not important
Isn't industry important?
I'll say you elites
Can you take some energy out?
Care about other aspects
I won't mention the stocks I bought myself
The strategic investment of the group
There are still a lot of people in your hand
What about the big and small non-bans in a few years?
Are you there
So is mine there
After this ban is lifted
It also limits transactions
Pay me a compensation
That's so uncomfortable
Look at this A-share index
Every drop
That's all real
Cutting the flesh in our hearts
If it were you
You don't have the heart to talk about anything else
I think
It's too exaggerated
Something turbulent in the policy
Finally, it can be pulled up to the stock index
I think compared to China's economy
The size of A-shares is not that big
Big brother
Your tone of speaking
It's a bit too outsider
You're slapping here
Can you do it without studying policies
Anyway, I didn't say it
No more chatting
You come on, I can't beat him
Practiced secretly
Dongdong
You are different from other investors
You're a business
Don't just focus on domestic policies
Lun Copper suddenly fell some time ago
House prices in the United States continue to fall
Plus the hot money pouring into China
Retreat
Your analysis consultant
I didn't study it for you
Global economic trend
this
It's our group
Research report on the international situation
My dad's deputy did it himself
Take it first and see
Any ideas
Let's talk later
drink wine
good
Hiroaki
Good news
My funds have been revitalized
Tell the finances
I'll send someone to find him tomorrow
OK
Remember
Find Liu Jun when you have difficulties
Last month was a trough
Copper futures have turned upward recently
After closing the position
I'm also making a lot of profits
It's been unconfiscated
Although I've solved the problem
But you can't be too careless
Stock index fell from more than 6,000 points
I've never been back
The bubble in the early stage is too great
My capital pool is mainly in the housing market
For me, the stock index fell
Benefit
Good news
Of course
So much money
Withdraw from the stock market
There must be a place to go
Look at what you said
Is it difficult to make money
Either this or that
Out of the stock market
You can only enter your housing market
Then you don't agree
Can you point me the third way
I'll listen carefully
You say it
Where else can I go
I can't say it either
But I just think something is wrong
It shouldn't be so narrow
Macroeconomics
It's complicated
You don't believe in evil
Have to be in this mess
Develop a main line
It's useless to reason
Alright, let's not talk about it
I'm looking at the market
Talk back
Worry
This night
What are you busy with here
What's this dense
Are you modeling
I was complained by two people today
First, Dongdong
Say I act like an outsider
Inappropriate
Then there is Hongming
Say I'm trying to be in a mess
Develop a main line
It's just doing useless work
Their views
I don't agree
But for a moment
I can't think of a reason to refute
So I want to create a correlation diagram
Take major events this year
Policy direction
International changes
Enter all in
Try to deduce it
The next economic trend
And manufacturing
Possibility of impact
Not small ambition
It is also necessary to deduce the economic trend
Are you going to join a think tank
What's your conclusion
The conclusion is that I gave up
Hongming is right
Everything is related to the macro economy
There are infinite variables
Infinite full relationship
Can't deduce it at all
The so-called conclusion
I know now
Why economic field
There are so many liars
Because of this thing
It's impossible to be rigorous
You're pure
Engineering chauvinism
You can't build a model yourself
Just say that economics is not science
Actually, don't care
Where will the economy go in the future
You have to follow the reality in front of you
Manage the factory
Is it going or retreat
There is no advanced choice
Maybe it's because of lack of confidence
Since the expansion of the center
I'm always trembling
Worried
But look at the people around you
Everyone is more confident than me
It seems like I don't care at all
Those risks
I've begun to doubt myself
Can't see anything clearly
There is no way to do it
Confident decision making
You said Tengfei lived to this day
Whether it depends entirely on luck
Has nothing to do with my ability
You are not the only one who feels guilty
After I'm promoted
I often doubt myself
Don't know yourself
Can you be competent for the current position
Otherwise,
Before we go out to work
Let's learn from that pyramid scheme organization
Have you seen it
It's the kind of shouting at each other
Come on, come on, you can
I think this is a good thing
Come
We can't do anything else
The first place in brainwashing each other
Try it, try it
Come
You have to be prepared sincerely
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come
Silently
Hello, are you visiting the house?
Hello, I'm not a house viewer
I'm here to find your boss
Then wait a moment
Sister Wei
Hirohide
How did you come
Sister Wei, it's been a long time no see
yes
Remember you just came to the company
When you go to work
Still a little girl with braids
It's different now
This career has developed
This style has come up.
It's obvious that he's a big business person
When I just worked
I don't know anything
It's not all up to Sister Wei
Teach me step by step
Is there any place to speak conveniently
I'll tell you something
OK, come to my office
here
Hongying
I heard from Old Wu
You're raising funds recently
This year's
There is such a high profit
Almost all old colleagues
All old friends voted
Why don't you call me?
Sister Wei, you misunderstood
First of all
I'm not called fundraising
That is, everyone believes in me
I'm willing to find some benefits for everyone, too
I must have thought of you
But your son this year
Didn't you study in Canada?
That's a big expense
I think you prefer
Keep the money in your hands
This is right
Children studying abroad
The savings in this family
He will use it first
But what about my sister
There is a free money
And the house I live in now
Mortgage out
Can make up a deal, too
This totals about 700,000
You won't think it's too little
How could it be
But Sister Wei
Money is invested in
The principal cannot be moved for at least one year
You're fine
no problem
I heard from Old Wu that he had seen it
In the downtown area of Shanghai
There is such a big building
I trust you
This physical examination result is good
There are a few indicators that are not normal
Much better than last time
My in-laws are right
At our age
Health is the most important
I'll tell you
After the stock market clearance
I slept very, very stable
Not dizzy
I'm not panicked
Everything you eat is delicious
Very good appetite
It's still useful for the in-laws to speak
I advised you at that time.
Say you stop trading stocks
But you don't listen
All in the wind
That's different
In-laws talk
I'm listening with my ears
You speak
I'm using this to listen
Two different paths
Come and eat something quickly
You said this is hot pot
Also changed to Doulao
This one
The price is several times more expensive
You said you are now
Why can you make money so well
Taste is OK
After you clear the stock
That's a lot of cash
You can't keep it on your account
Have you ever thought about it
Other investment channels
My daughter-in-law works in the bank
She knows how to manage money
I was about to ask her
Go back and ask
The bank is dead interest
Where do you put your money
It's definitely not worth it
Tianmao Building in Shanghai
Have you heard of it
Have heard of it
Hongming took it down
A project for renovation
Now in the early stage
You can invest in a stock
Profits after the renovation
It will definitely double
Do you want to think about it?
Hongming is too courageous
He dares to touch commercial real estate
Subprime mortgage crisis in the United States
Not over yet
You haven't invested in the United States
Let’s talk about the current housing market in Shanghai
Very popular
I know this
The project in Shanghai is good
But I'll tell you
The money in the stock market is not all mine
I have to take the principal of the soaring
Return it
The remaining profit
Ajun won't let me move
You may not know
Ajun kept asking me to change a house
He thinks the house I live in now
Too old
There is no place to park the car
Not safe yet
My tires were pricked twice
Even my little granddaughter
I don't want to come to play here
Not familiar
meat
Quick
Quick, quick
What's so anxious
I didn't have time to eat breakfast
Important matters and important matters
Ah Jun
I'll tell you
What about dad's hands
There are five million now
See what can you buy
Can spend this money as soon as possible
Give an idea
I thought it was a big deal
That's it
Is this a trivial matter?
You cleared your stock the day before yesterday
Just one today
The situation of spending all the money
Hold the cash in your hand
Hot
I don't want cash
I just want to spend it
No
Anyway
Five million
right
Spend it out in one breath
Then you can only buy a house
Good to buy a house
I said so yesterday
Then I'm not lying
Who are you lying to
No, no, no, nothing
Where is this property located
You'll really give up
Where is Sanhekou
Opened a new property
A big luxury house in high-end decoration
More than 400 square meters
One set can cost you more than four million
Spend more than 100,000 yuan to buy two parking spaces
Make some furniture and the rest
Choose another good car
Miscellaneous and more than 85 million
Flowers are gone
Mikawaguchi
What is the name of this property
You really bought it
Buy it
No
So many years
You're guarding your old house
Refusing to move
Why did you suddenly change your mind so much
Don't you always advise me
Say I've worked hard all my life
Be happy when you are old
I'll listen to you
Have I said this
Said
Should I enjoy it
How should it be
Have breakfast
Stop eating and looking at the house
Look at the property
My bun
Stop eating, I'll treat you
I just said I would use money to manage my finances
I mention Tianmao
Just change your words
I've decided to buy a house
In fact, it doesn't matter whether you invest or not
The key is
He immediately got ready
That attitude
It's really chilling
Who is Liushitang
Always selfish and suspicious
You think you're helping someone
Find investment channels
But in other people's eyes
You're planning to be a bad person
Want to cheat on him
But it's good
You see his true face sooner
It's better than losing money in the future
he
He's a little selfish
But it's not what you said
sister
You won't be until now
Haven't seen him clearly yet
He is in front of his son
Maintain image
Sorry to find a young girl
But an old aunt of similar age to him
He doesn't like it
Of course I can only hold you and keep it away
As I said, you should break up with him quickly
You'll be entangled with him for a long time
I can't get his sincerity
How about Ah Jun
Open or not
Look at the restaurant
Is this light beautiful or not
The dining table will be here in the future
Baby, let's have a meal here
Look at how it is
This one is nearly six meters tall
Look at my landscape
I'll tell you what's invincible
Come to see if it's good here, baby
There are several rooms upstairs
baby
Go up with grandpa to check out the room
OK
You can watch it casually
good
Let's go up and see if it's OK
It's so beautiful
baby
Is it good to find you a room?
You choose one by yourself
Take a look
You didn't tell me
Your dad is one
The owner of a small street factory
Will you be stingy for life
What's the result now
Four million mansion
I also have a parking space and buy it if I say I can buy it
Repay the full amount
When you buy a larger flat layer
All generous
Then why don't we change with him
You're embarrassed
The windmill is lifted
How about it
I'll tell you about this environment
That's nothing to choose
Look at this green plant
Ajun, look at this
This lawn is so wide
How beautiful this color is
Is this style a bit European
yes
Dad, I'll take her to the front to take a walk
Go and go and play
Let's go
I'll tell you Ah Jun
Run
You and Bingbing are busy with work
This kid in the future
Don't bother your father-in-law and mother-in-law all the time
Send me here
Dad's house let her run away casually
Look how good the environment is
Such a big house
I don't believe you live alone
Dad and Nanny are looking for a hourly worker
Don't live at home
You know I'm not talking about nanny
I know you're not talking about nanny
Dad is about to tell you this
Hongying ignored me for a week
Why
Money is a mess
What kind of building did her brother build?
Renovation project
Honestly this project
Still good
But I'm talking about Qian Hongming
Distrust
I don't want to be financially
What's the ties to him
Renovation project
Hongming didn't tell me
He hasn't told you
I haven't said it's right
You just don't know
Never vote
I'll tell you
Taking advantage of the current situation
Get your entity well
Better than anything
I said
Such an expensive house
It's only been less than three days
Buy it if you say it
Do you want to spend the money
That way no one bothers you
Honestly, this makes sense
Isn't this a cause of trouble?
Hongying is unhappy
She thinks I'm on guard against her
Don't answer the phone
I can't see anyone even if I look for her