[English subtitles are available]
[The Blooms at RUYI Pavilion]
[Episode 31]
[They're all here, just as I thought.]
Your Highness.
Xu Jia, what are you doing here?
Move! Hurry up.
Hurry, come on.
Women from the village
are like that. Dumb.
Stop crying or I'll kill you all.
Please don't. Where's the fun in that?
Let's go.
Your Highness,
where are you going?
I have to save them.
Tell me.
Yesterday, I won quite a lot.
Yes, want to do it again?
Hurry up.
-Don't drink alone.
-Sure.
-Move it all here.
-I'm craving for meat.
This is?
This is Cheji Grass.
I didn't know I could find some here.
When I was treating Guan Ge's chickenpox,
I learned a few things about herbs.
I never thought that it
would come in handy now.
What good can it do for us?
I'll just kill our way out.
Don't.
Among us, you're the
only one who can fight.
We won't be able to run away. Besides,
don't underestimate it.
Wen Xing, leave me now.
Yes.
Nong Nong.
-Stop there.
-Are you new here?
I just joined.
Chief said you've all worked hard.
I'm here to send you guys some liquor.
We've been craving
for it for the whole day.
At last.
Here.
Girl, come join us.
-Sure.
-Cheers. Here.
This must be a good wine.
-Allow me.
-Fill the cup, fill it.
Let's go.
Your Highness, that was really impressive.
-Take them with you.
-Someone is running away!
-Go after them! Go!
-What about you?
I'll distract them,
otherwise, none of us can get away.
You must get them out safely.
This is the material from the palace.
Keep it safe.
It's too dangerous to
leave you here alone.
Go now, quick.
Stop there! Stop running!
Stop running, stop! Grab them!
Hurry, get them! Stop running!
Stop running! Get her!
Quick!
Hurry!
Go after them! Stop running!
Stop there!
Stop!
Fire! Put it out!
Water!
Get some water here!
Put out the fire first.
-Grab her!
-Yes!
[Chief of Qingfeng Hideout]
-Take her away.
-Yes.
Have you seen a girl
with forehead marking,
about this tall?
No.
Excuse me. Have you
seen a girl forehead marking,
who is about this tall?
No, no.
Have you seen a girl
who's about this tall?
-How is it?
-No one saw her, Young Master.
Let's go.
Your Highness,
-bad news.
-What happened?
Her Highness is
trapped in the bandits' hideout.
She gave me this.
She said those materials that
were stolen from the palace
are in the bandits' storehouse.
In order to save those kidnapped women,
she asked me to bring them out first,
while she stayed there.
The stakes are too high.
I had to come back first to report to you
after I freed those women.
Your Highness, I discovered
something else in the hideout.
Weapons from Kushui Village.
Your Highness, there is
something dubious about this hideout.
If you go alone,
you could put yourself in danger.
Let's apply for troop deployment
from the capital.
Once the army arrives,
we'll strike together.
It'll be too late then.
Xu Jia, go and borrow
troops from General Yuan,
the person in charge of this area.
I'll go to Qingfeng Hideout now.
Duke Su,
you don't have the transfer order,
and you want to borrow
troops out of sudden,
he might not agree to it.
But Mr Yuan is my
father's former subordinate.
If I go with Mr Xu,
he'll agree to it.
Thank you, Your Highness.
But
I need you to do two things for me.
Tell me.
First,
I want one personal item of yours.
Second,
I want you to return safe and sound.
Xu Jia,
go with the princess to borrow troops.
-I'll meet you in the bandits' hideout.
-Yes.
Those bandits of Qingfeng Hideout
came every once in a while.
We can't stand it anymore.
Those bandits of Qingfeng Hideout
are really nasty.
What do you think we should do?
[I saw how]
[you were looking at it.]
[So I decided to give it to you.]
Qingfeng Hideout.
-Uncle.
-It's you.
Hurry! Get them!
Brothers, quick!
Hurry up, guys!
Brothers, attack!
Go! Grab your weapons, quick!
Report!
Chief, Deputy Chief,
someone broke into our
place and killed our brothers.
What? Go and check it out!
Go now!
-Let's check it out.
-Go.
-Brother.
Stay here.
If something goes wrong,
do as the man told us to.
Yes.
[Deputy Chief of Qingfeng Hideout]
Take Rong'er with you. I'll meet
you down the mountain at the inn.
Go now!
You've got the nerve to
break into Qingfeng Hideout.
I won't let you leave here alive today.
Little Follower,
you saved me.
Are you all right?
You're injured.
I'm fine.
I'm just glad you're all right.
We need to take care of your wound first.
Come on.
Attack!
We've been fighting all night.
Just him alone.
Attack!
Crash it open.
It's the army. Retreat.
Your Highness!
Your Highness, are you all right?
Are you all right?
Xu Jia,
bring some men with you
to search the storehouse.
Yes.
[The treasures in Qingfeng Hideout]
[carry too many secrets.]
[If anything happens,]
[destroy everything.]
[Do not leave any evidence behind.]
[Remember,]
[destroy everything.]
Shut up.
Answer our questions truthfully,
and we won't hurt you.
Please show me mercy.
Did you kidnap a girl and
bring her here yesterday?
-Where is she?
-Someone else saved her.
Please spare my life.
He's probably telling the truth.
Ms Rong isn't here.
Someone is setting the
valley on fire. Retreat.
The wound is deep,
it goes all the way through
the bone of your right arm.
If you hadn't treated it sooner,
your right hand could've been ruined.
Thank you, doctor.
He needs to get some rest.
Replace the patch every two days.
He can't afford another injury.
I understand. Thank you, doctor.
Come with me to get the prescription.
Yes.
Ms Fu, I'm going
to get the prescription.
I'll leave Young Master to you.
Got it. Don't worry.
All right.
Please.
I'm sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
You were dragged into this because of me.
And you got hurt because of me.
If it wasn't because of me...
Don't say that.
It hurts me
to hear you say that.
Between us,
such formality is not needed.
Nong Nong,
I'm demanding reward
for saving you this time.
Sure.
What reward do you want?
I'm willing to give you everything
I have to pay you back.
No.
I don't need you to give me anything.
I just want you
to take care of me until I recover.
What?
Have you changed your mind?
No, don't worry.
I'll take care of you until you recover.
Good.
Thank goodness.
If Farmer Ju Shui's hand was
hurt and couldn't write anymore,
that would've made me the
most hated sinner in Dayu.
It's fine.
Besides apologising,
I'd like to thank you as well.
Thank you for coming to my rescue.
[Take Rong'er with you.]
All right, rest early.
I'll stay here until you fall asleep.
Your Highness, we're too late.
Those stuff in the storehouse,
we only managed to save these.
Two boxes of them are materials
that were stolen from the palace.
We can finally vindicate Her Highness.
Good job.
This bandits' hideout has always been
the blight on my Weiyang City.
This time,
if Duke Su hadn't
thrown them off guard,
we wouldn't be able to wipe them out.
Of course,
the princess' letter was a great help too.
She's probably waiting for us
at the foot of the mountain now.
Xu Jia,
bring a team with you
to take the chief of
Qingfeng Hideout back to the capital.
Escort the princess
back as well on your way.
Yes.
Rong'er.
Nong Nong.
Your Highness.
Little Follower, you're awake.
Nong Nong,
go back early and have some rest.
No. You need to finish the medicine.
I'll go and decoct your medicine.
Young Master.
What is it?
Ms Gu has sent someone
to bring us a message.
Saying that it's something important.
He's waiting for you in the
tea house across the street.
Let's go.
-But your injury...
-I'll be fine.
-We'll make a quick trip.
-Yes.
Uncle San?
Yes, Young Lady said
Uncle San is an old-timer
of Ruyi Pavilion.
He's venerable, though he
has taken an early retirement.
He had little contact with Ruyi Pavilion.
Xiao Qi and Xiao Ba are
looking for Uncle San now.
Looks like they're going
to ask him to take charge.
Young Master,
I heard that they wanted
to revamp Ruyi Pavilion.
We need to find the token
out as soon as possible.
We've been looking for
the token of Ruyi Pavilion for so long.
Uncle San might have
some information about it.
Both of you,
based on the clues Ms Gu gave you,
hunt them down.
Yes.
What happened to him?
He's limping, look.
-His shirt is covered in blood.
-That's right. Is he hurt?
Sir, how may I help you?
Mr Proprietor,
did a man and a woman come here?
The woman has an ornamental
mark on her forehead.
Sorry, I haven't seen them.
Thank you.
-She's gone?
-There were only a burnt medicine pot
and a fan lying on
the floor of the kitchen.
It's likely that Nong Nong
has been abducted.
-Most likely.
-Wen Xing,
go and deploy all possible resources.
We must find Nong Nong.
Yes.
Mr Proprietor,
did a man and woman come here last night?
Yes, they were here.
Is that man suffering from an injury too?
He is.
I think they went out just now.
I didn't really take much notice.
Mister, Mister.
A man just asked me
to give you this letter.
You have one hour
to get to East Mountain to save her.
May I know where East Mountain is?
Keep going east after
you get out of the city.
Keep walking until you see a hill.
Sir, it's raining soon.
Would you like to buy an umbrella?
It's been a while,
Concubine Rong.
Sir,
-someone was looking for you just now.
-Who was it?
A man who looks high-born,
with a capital accent.
He seemed to suffer from a severe injury.
-It's quite terrifying to look at.
-Xu Jin. Where is he now?
A child gave him a letter just now.
A bracelet came with the letter.
He seemed anxious
after he read the letter.
He asked how he could
get to East Mountain.
And then, he just...
Sir, it's raining soon.
Would you like to buy an umbrella?
It's been so long.
Rong,
do you miss me?
These days,
I've been missing you
and you guys
all the time.
What's wrong?
What are you afraid of?
Don't worry.
I'm not a ghost.
I'm a human.
I'm still alive.
The ones who died
are my parents.
[Father, where are we going?]
[Where are we going?]
[Father, what are you doing?]
[This is a secret passage.]
[You can get out from here.]
[Father,]
[I'm not leaving.]
[Listen to me.]
[Be strong.]
[Go now, Yan'er.]
-[Listen to your father.]
-[Mother.]
[It'll be too late if
you don't leave now.]
[Go, go now!]
[Go.]
[Take care of your mother, Yan'er!]
[Careful, Mother.]
[Mother, why do we have
a secret passage here?]
[Yan'er, there are some
clothes and jewellery here.]
[Take them with you.]
[What are you doing, Mother?]
[Live a good life.]
[Never return to the capital.]
[Yan'er!]
[Yan'er,]
[I've done you wrong.]
[I don't need you to avenge us.]
[I just want you]
[to live a good life.]
For all the suffering that you
have brought upon me,
I'm going to make it a hundred times,
a thousand times worse for you.
Rong.
Rong,
don't be afraid.
You won't be alone.
Beside you,
there are two other graves.
They'll keep you company.
What's the matter?
Are you upset?
These are my father
and my mother's cenotaph.
Years ago,
Father started out here in Weiyang City.
And now,
I've brought them back here.
And you!
Their daughter-in-law.
Fu Rong,
let me tell you,
you and I have been engaged
since childhood.
You still belong to us
even when you're dead.
Take good care of my
parents in the underworld.
Help!
Yan'er has avenged you.
There is one more.
Wait for me.
Rong'er!
Zhang Yan.
Where is Rong'er?
You really are something, Duke Su.
You don't look surprised
when you see me.
Aren't you afraid that the vengeful
spirit will come to claim your life?
Lord Xindu got what he deserved.
Why should I be afraid?
Xu Jin!
Say that again if you dare!
Tell me where Fu Rong is!
Don't worry,
you're going to see her in no time.
Only you're going see her
on the Nether Bridge.
Where is she?
Do it.
If you kill me now,
you'll only see her again
in the netherworld.
Whatever grudges you are holding,
just take it out on me.
Fu Rong has nothing to do with it.
Whether she's involved or not,
that's not up to you to say.
Do it, Xu Jin.
You really love her, don't you?
I would really like to see
how far you are willing to go for her.
Maybe
I could be touched by your love,
and I'll let you see her.
It's known that the sharpness of a blade
can cut through bone and kill instantly.
Don't worry.
This one here
is a blunt dagger.
It's hard to penetrate it into the body,
it's hard to be pulled out.
How about
you stab yourself for a bit?
Stab until I'm satisfied with it.
And I'll tell you where Fu Rong is.
Do it now.
I would really like to see how far
you are willing to go for her.
Where is she?
Do you think you're devoted?
I changed my mind.
Only one of you
can live.
If you're willing to die for Fu Rong now,
I'll let her go.
You're being evasive.
You just don't want to
tell me where Fu Rong is.
Doing this to me
do you still intend to
find out where Fu Rong is?
Tell me!
Tell me where Fu Rong is!
And I'll spare your life!
Since you love her so much,
I'll trade my life
for your pain of not being able
to see her again.
Zhang Yan.
You can't die.
Worth it.
Where is Fu Rong?
Tell me now!
Where on earth is Fu Rong?
Let me tell you,
you're the one
who killed...
Where is Fu Rong?
Tell me!
Fu Rong...
Where is she?
Tell me!
Tell me.
Tell me where Fu Rong is.
Tell me!
Fu Rong!
Wake up!
Rong'er.
Rong'er!
Nong Nong!
Help!
Rong'er!
Judging by his character,
he wouldn't keep Rong'er too far away.
Rong'er must still be in East Mountain.
Why would the rainwater
be intercepted here?
The soil looks like it
has been recently turned.
Could it be...
Rong'er.
Rong'er, Rong'er.