[English subtitles are available]
[The Blooms at RUYI Pavilion]
[Episode 18]
Young Master
The Imperial Guards sent news that
they can't locate him in town
There's no news from the outside
What about that side?
The secret guards
discovered that Duke Cheng's men
were reallocated frequently
Not in the capital,
but in one Hu Village by the countryside
Hu Village?
Have a check on it tonight
Whatever you can find
about Liu Ru Yi's case
If there's anything on Hu,
keep an eye on it
He might be the key to rescue Nong Nong
Yes
This must be the place
I wonder how Mr Ge and Officer Xu are
after separating with us
Xu Jia is there
Don't worry
Logically speaking,
not many will ride horses in such villages
From the hoofprints,
a number of horses came here
All equipped with horseshoes.
They wanted to kill Coroner Hu?
The hoofprints are all dried up
They must've been here for some time
If they've really killed Coroner Hu,
why did they malign you on a jailbreak?
They won't give up so easily
and leave just like that
We shall look for some villagers
and ask for information
I have a way
Don't rub it off
It's important
Your elegance and grandeur
will expose you
Don't be too composed
You two are...
We're siblings who came from Yuzhou
for our relatives
But we came across some bandits
We met them at the Zhe Gu Hill
Why did you go to Zhe Gu Hill?
The bandits on that hill
are really arrogant
We're outsiders
We didn't know about it
My brother was beaten up
in order to protect me
We didn't eat and drink
after escaping from them
Can you keep us in for the night?
This...
We don't have money with us
But this still worth some money
Please keep us in for the night
This hairpin is too precious
Come in for the night
It's fine, you don't have to pay
-Come in
-Yes
It must be tough for you. Hurry in
-Come in
-Thank you
You're such an actor
They believed you
How can I win against you?
So straightforward
If I was really good,
you wouldn't be making fun of me
But to be honest
They wouldn't have believed us
if you hadn't mentioned Zhe Gu Hill
Alright, alright
You've come all the way
You must be starving
-Here, have some porridge
-Thank you
My husband is in the kitchen,
making some dishes for you two
It's good of you to take us in
This is...
It's two bowls of porridge
It's not much
By the way
What is your surname?
How should I address you?
-Xu
-Fu
That's it, you can stop your pretence
I've already known about your identities
You two have eloped, haven't you?
Don't be shy
My family forced me into marriage too
After that I eloped with my husband
and stayed here
Therefore I knew at once
when I saw you two today
That's why I let you in
Ma'am
We're...
Yes
We're husband and wife
It's like this
My mother passed away early
The First Madam always bullies me
My father never cared and
he wants me to marry an old squire
as his eighth wife
I couldn't take it anymore
So I eloped with him
Then,
I came to look for my uncle
He lives in Hu Village
What's his name?
Hu Ming
Hu Ming?
Isn't he the son of Old Lady Wang?
He's a coroner in the capital
He's filial
He always comes home during the festivals
Where does he live?
When you go out from here,
walk along the pebble road
and you'll see a courtyard
That's the place
Then we shall...
It's so late now
The old lady must be asleep
You can go tomorrow morning
But we're sorry that
you have to make do with
our warmer tonight
That's all
Go and have some rest
I'll bring you a blanket
One blanket?
Of course
The weather is not so cold
that you have to use two blankets
I'm just asking
Your...
My husband
What do you think?
I'll follow your cue
Let's rest early then
You're right on, Young Master
There was a coroner surnamed Hu
who went missing recently
It was said he returned home
for recuperation
Perhaps Xu Mao wants him
to have a rest in the nether world
The Imperial Guards pursuing
Duke Su is nearby as well
If the news is accurate,
should we increase manpower?
Send our own secret guards
if he resists, kill him
One more thing
Bring Nong Nong and Hu Ming
back safely to me
As for Xu Jin...
Understood
Nong Nong, you must return safely
I'll sit right here
Go and have some rest
You're tired after a whole day of walking
This is nothing to me
Hurry and rest
These are runnings from a girl's outfit
This was washed a few days ago
Perhaps the servants' clothes
got stuck by accident
You care about it?
I was merely asking
Men are approaching
We can't stay here
Innocents will be harmed
-Let's go
-Wait
Though she didn't want this,
but it's the only one I got
I'll compensate
with something better later
Let's go
Your Highness
More of them are coming
We can't keep running
Split up and search
Your hand
It's fine
Let's look over there
We must leave now
They'll return if we don't
But we can't return to the Hu Village
The most dangerous place is the safest
Not just going back,
we'll go to the Hu Residence
Let's go
Hide
Let's move
Won't they pursue us again?
Those people are ruthless
They're strangers
So they have to avoid the Bureau
and the Imperial Guards
So,
the Hu Residence is even safer
Thank you for letting us in
[Coroner Hu's mother]
You're not leaving my doorstep
If I didn't let you in,
you'd be luring them in
Here
Bandage your wound right away
You'll die if you bleed too much
You're clueless, aren't you?
Move aside
I'll do it
You should leave right away
after you're done
Since you've let us in,
please tell us where Coroner Hu is
We're not trying to harm him
We just want his post-mortem
The thing you said,
what post-mortem?
I don't know what it is
Hu Ming didn't return home at all
I don't know where he is
You're worried that we'll
lure the others here
But even if we're not here today,
you must have been disturbed lately
You let us in because you saw casualties
What a benevolent healer
I believe that Coroner Hu
was influenced greatly
and became such a formidable coroner now
Little girl
It's no use saying nice words
I truly don't know
How can you not know what is a
post-mortem as a healer?
These days,
groups of people came here
and left here repeatedly
It's useless for you to ask me
Those people are trying to be polite
before resorting to force
They might act desperately and harm you
That's right
If Coroner Hu continues to hide,
you may not see each other again soon
To be honest,
I'm the Fourth Prince,
Xu Jin
She is the one being set up
We just want Coroner Hu to testify for us
I'll definitely keep him safe
You're Duke Su
It's here. Search for them
Open up, open up
Open up
Why are you here again?
Make way
-You lot
-Move from here
What are you doing?
I said Hu Ming is not here
I knew you would say that
I'm done with your nonsense
Return to the capital with us
-You can't do this
-Move
-I did nothing wrong
-Be still
-You can't do this
Madam
The Criminal Investigation Bureau
took action
It's dangerous here
I'm fine
I'm worried about Ming'er
Do you know there's a Taoist
abbey under Zhe Gu Hill?
Hu Ming is there
Go to him right now
Walk towards the east once
you leave the village
Hurry and find Ming'er
After I meet my subordinates,
I'll send them here for you
Rong'er
Are you alright?
Let's go
To think we're greeted by this
after a narrow escape
Even if we died here...
I thought you didn't fear death
That's before I knew you
They're coming for us
You're highly skilled
You must hide
This happened because of me
I'll let them take me
They won't take my life recklessly
Take this fan
You can defend yourself
if danger comes
I don't want it
I know you won't run away alone
Just like how I won't abandon you here
But you kept this fan as a
weapon close to you
So I want you to take it
In this lifetime,
we'll never be apart
You're asking a girl's hand in marriage
with just a fan?
I'm keeping it
Don't give anyone else the same thing
This fan
is a one and only
My heart
It's better for me
to be alive than dead
We can spare your life if you're
willing to be captured
Don't worry
-Tie him up
-Yes, sir
Retreat
Commander
Thanks for saving us
We're not here
to rescue you today
-We're under orders
-I know
You're arresting me
We can't disobey His Majesty
Please forgive us
I should be the one to apologise
I feel guilty
towards every one of you
I left the capital
to search for the truth
Did you find any clue?
Wait till I return to Hengjing
I'll give you an answer
This...
From the day the Commander led us,
he never broke his promise
If he said he'll return to
Hengjing tomorrow,
then I'm willing to trust him
-I trust the Commander
I'm willing to trust him too
It's getting late now
Hurry and leave, Commander
Before the gates close tomorrow,
we'll wait for your return
When I return,
I'll bid farewell to all of you properly
Another thing
Send some men
to Hu Village to protect
Coroner Hu's mother
Understood
If you see Mr Ge on the road,
tell him
to meet me at the East Gate
Yes, sir
[I knew it]
[You wouldn't believe me easily]
[The Founders' Hall]
[Master]
Master
Is something the matter?
Do you remember me, Master Hu?
We met at Ru Yi Pavilion before
I don't know what you mean
You're smart, Coroner Hu
But you implicated your mother
She was nearly arrested yesterday
-My mother...
-She told us you're here
Your mother is fine
We're grateful for his help
Is the post-mortem still with you?
If not, they wouldn't be tracking you down
He is...
To be honest,
I'm the...
My surname is Xu
His name is Xu Jin
Your Highness
If you agree to testify,
I'll ensure you and your mother's safety
Things have come to this
The Criminal Investigation Bureau
will never let me off
I trust you guys
I'll return with you
Your Highness
Ms Fu
Are you two alright?
We're fine. I'll enter the city first
You two shall escort Ms Fu
and Coroner Hu
Bring them to a safe place
-I'll follow you
-No way
If you enter now,
the Bureau will catch you right away
We don't know their dirty tricks
You'll suffer from it
-But...
-Wait for me outside
I'll let Royal Father reinstate
a joint hearing
to prove you innocent
Then you must fulfil it
Don't worry
For you,
I'll be fine
Ms Fu
If the Bureau wants to play dirty,
we'll take them on accordingly
Regardless, this is my matter
I can't let you go alone
I must go to the Bureau
Fu Rong
Your Highness
Young Lady Rong
I returned on time
I kept my promise
Rong'er
-Sister
-Rong'er
How did you know we're coming back?
You're here
Rong'er
It's been hard on you
I missed you, Sister
Thank you for all the hard work
in the capital
It's fine, Your Highness
What shall we do next?
I'll go to the palace
Fu Rong will go to the Bureau
That's enough
His Highness said you'll meet again
I believe Fu Rong
will be back home safely soon
I hope so
Anyway
Why did you come today?
You looked angry yesterday
You burned the paper that night
I thought...
[Tomorrow at the East Gate]
[Come if you trust me]
If you want to act,
how can I not cooperate?
It's just that
Guan Ge was injured
I was anxious about it
I burned the paper
for fear of eavesdroppers
How's Guan Ge?
He's fine
How did you know I was acting?
Couldn't I really betray His Highness?
He broke out of jail
He might disappear just like that
I had to look for a new way
I knew it was you
You wouldn't betray His Highness
Then...
I suffered a lot this time
Mostly for your sister
Shouldn't you thank me nicely?
Then...
I'll check Feng Lai Yi's ledgers for you
That's it?
I'm not becoming your accountant
Only if you're overwhelmed with work,
I can help with some
What?
Could it be that
you're not willing to give me the ledgers?
No way
You're not suspicious of me
How can I not trust you?
Get some rest first
You'll be busy afterwards
Nong Nong is back at the Bureau?
Ms Fu returned with Duke Su
The Imperial Guards took him
back to the palace
We wanted to act
But we missed the chance
That useless Xu Jin
How could he let Nong Nong return
to that hellhole?
Useless
You're not playing?
Excuse my prudence, Royal Brother
I'm always losing
in our day-to-day games
This noise today
kept spinning around me
It disturbs my thoughts
If this continues,
I'll still lose the game
You
You're benevolent
We'll stop if you want to
Yes
Stop
Royal Father
Uncle
How do you explain the word Royal Father?
You're my ruler,
as well as my father
You lawlessly broke into jail that night
That's disloyalty
You hid your tracks and did as you please
That's disobedience
In your eyes,
there is no ruler nor father
You told me convincingly that you'll
take over the Imperial Guards
to search for corrupted officials for me
But now?
I'm willing
to bear all responsibilities by myself
I'll never forget
to look for the culprit
But a life is at stake
I can't turn my eyes away
Even now,
you're still thinking of
clearing the name of that female prisoner?
Fu Rong didn't kill anyone
She didn't jailbreak
But she was nearly beheaded in public
I'm not willing to see such
deceits happen upon you,
so I took the risk
This murder
contains plenty of suspicions
I beg you to look into it
[Upright and Honest]
Bring forth the criminal
Who is here on the court?
I'm Fu Rong
Fu Rong
With the presence of all judges today,
you must answer us honestly
If you make a false remark,
it's considered unforgivable
and your family will be implicated
Understood
On the tenth this month,
the owner of Ruyi Pavilion, Liu Ru Yi,
was found dead in her room
When the constables arrived,
you were the one holding the weapon
with hands full of blood by the body
Are you guilty of the crime?
I'm not guilty
Why must I confess?
Sure. Lord Ding
You were the one who caught her
Can you tell us what happened that day?
Yes
Wait
Your Highness
Today,
I'll have a debate with Lord Ding
Your Highness, this might not be suitable
Which one of the law of Dayu states that
she can't have a lawyer?
Today,
I'm Fu Rong's lawyer
-My lordship
-Fine
There's no regulation
to forbid His Highness as Fu Rong's lawyer
Let's not delay
We'll begin immediately
Yes
I'm the prosecutor of the
Investigation Bureau
On the evening of the tenth,
I received a report
about an improper transaction
at Ru Yi Pavilion
Therefore I hurried
and arrived there at a quarter after
I saw Liu Ru Yi on the ground
with a dagger in her chest
Fu Rong was beside her with
hands full of blood
My lord
This is Coroner Jiang
The coroner of the case
Greetings, my lord
I arrived at six in the evening
As it was an emergency,
I roughly examined the body
Then I examined it again carefully
in the Bureau
Liu Ru Yi must've been killed
between quarter to three
to a quarter to four
It matched the time when Fu Rong arrived
The weapon is that same dagger
Fu Rong
What do you have to say about this?
My lord
I did have a quarrel with my
master a few days ago
I wanted to apologise to her
on that fateful day
But I never thought I'd find her dead
when I arrived at Ru Yi Pavilion
Just then, Lord Ding brought his men
Then I was accused as the murderer and
took me into custody
I've seen plenty of murderers like you
I don't expect
that you'll confess to your own crime
Lord Ding
If I was so cruel to kill my master,
would I be so foolish to stay,
awaiting your capture?
We merely arrived on time
and you couldn't escape
From what I know,
Liu Ru Yi has immense strength from
shaping silver all these years
But Fu Rong is weak
If they had fought,
Fu Rong had no chance of winning
Why would she use such a way
to kill her own master?
What if she did it without
Liu Ru Yi knowing?
Lord Ding
That's a wrong speculation
It is written on the scroll
that there were signs of fighting
in Liu Ru Yi's room
The culprit must've fought Liu Ru Yi
and killed her after
These are merely guesses, my lord
Up until now,
she doesn't own any evidence
that clears her from the case
Could Lord Ding and Coroner Jiang's
post-mortem
be problematic?
Your Highness
How can the post-mortem be wrong?
This one
is Coroner Jiang's post-mortem
It is written
that Coroner Jiang arrived at
four quarters to five
But from my investigation,
at a quarter to five,
Lord Ding arrived
with another coroner
But without a reason,
this Coroner Hu
left with his post-mortem
Your Highness
Your words are overbearing now
Coroner Hu had some matters at home,
therefore he left
Your Highness
Is Hu Ming present?
I, Hu Ming, pay respect to my lordships
After I examined the body,
I wrote the post-mortem
After Lord Ding stamped it,
he suddenly told me to stay
away from the case
and asked me to leave
I then returned home
I took the post-mortem
with me while I left
But I was pursued
the moment I arrived home
I've been on the run since
Is that what happened?
Do you know who's after your life?
I don't want to make any conclusion
But please have a look, my lordships
When I arrived,
Liu Ru Yi's eyes and chin
were already stiff
Her fingers as well
Rigor mortis had already set in
She had died around two hours ago
Fu Rong
Where were you two hours before?
I was at home
Any proof?
If you don't trust the people
in the Fu Residence,
you can ask the neighbours
around the residence
With all eyes watching me,
when did I go to the Ru Yi Pavilion?
I believe Lord Ding has found out
I was there before a quarter to five
Lord Ding?
-Yes
-How can Fu Rong murder Liu Ru Yi
when she's ten miles away?
If that's so,
Fu Rong is definitely not the killer
Wise remark, your Lordships
But I want to know
Since Lord Ding read this post-mortem,
why did he make Coroner Hu leave
and insisted that Fu Rong was the killer?
My lord
I didn't read the post-mortem closely
I roughly scanned through it
And Coroner Jiang was here
because I was concerned about
Coroner Hu's experience and
couldn't write a clear post-mortem
I bet you yourself
wouldn't believe those words
I was a fool
I thought that this was a big case
If I can solve it, I'll earn a great merit
So I thought of using my relative
to push away Coroner Hu
As for the post-mortem,
I really didn't read it closely
I never thought that I'd implicate anyone
with my selfishness
I
should die for my mistake
Now that Fu Rong is found innocent,
we shall release her
A declaration will be made
Coroner Hu was terrified by the incident
The Bureau must provide him some comfort
As for Ding Peng,
he's full of selfishness even as
the prosecutor of the Bureau
He almost caused an injustice
He's punished for a year's salary
and 50 canes,
henceforth demoted as a regular constable
Come
Take them away
Respects to Your Majesty
Royal Father
On the murder of Liu Ru Yi,
the Criminal Investigation Bureau and the
Ministry of Justice must not slack
Investigations must be done
until the truth is found
and the culprit caught
Fu Rong
Though you're innocent,
but your behaviour after you were caught
was absolutely ridiculous
Spare the rod, spoil the child
Fu Pin Yan is hereby punished
for three months' salary
And you're punished to copy the
Female Commandment at home
Yes, Your Majesty
I shall obey your orders
Jin'er
Go back with me
Yes