[English subtitles are available]
[The Blooms at RUYI Pavilion]
[Episode 38]
[Shang Yang Gate]
Father.
Second Prince of Xuan Han
has left for Xuan Han today
to prepare for the arrival of
Princess of Xihe.
I have been informed.
I heard
you rejected the daughter
of Minister Li.
I really don't like Young Lady Lee.
Moreover, I don't want to marry
and live with someone I don't love.
Duke An asked to enter.
Allowed.
Announcing Duke An's arrival.
Your Majesty.
Why are you still standing here?
You may leave.
Yes, Father.
Royal Brother.
This is the list of dowry
for the marriage alliance.
Also, as of the status of
Princess Consort of Qingping,
we need to send some dowries too.
They are all written in the list.
Please have a look.
Your Majesty.
May I have a word, Uncle?
Will Princess Consort of Qingping
accompany the marriage to Xuan Han too?
Yes.
Princess of Xihe requested for that.
Royal Brother has approved the request.
May Your Highness win the competition.
Hao'er.
Duke An.
Princess Consort.
Do you know that the Emperor
was mad of Duke Huai today?
Why?
You don't know why?
I have to obey the royal order
to accompany the marriage.
Nobody can help me.
I have a way to let you
stay in the capital.
It's a serious crime to go against
the Emperor's order.
Besides, I don't have a reason the stay.
You're right.
Going against the Emperor's order
is a serious crime.
Do you know that if it wasn't for me,
he would still be kneeling
in front of the palace gate?
He is even willing to forgo
his royal status.
Hao'er does love you deeply.
But you don't even want to try.
Gu Yuan has not been found.
Tomorrow I'll be going with Xu Jia
to Xuan Han along with
the marriage procession.
Mr Ge.
Please continue the investigation
with Lieutenant Guo.
Yes, Your Highness.
Please assist in the matters
at Fu Residence.
Please do not worry, Your Highness.
But
Your Highness will be leaving
for quite some time.
Don't you want to meet Duchess Su
before you leave?
I said
I need more time to consider.
What do you need to consider?
Duke Huai.
Do you really want to go to Xuan Han?
I have no say
in this matter.
No.
If you don't want to go,
I will get you to stay in the Capital.
Your Highness.
You have a great future ahead.
Please don't go against the Emperor
because of me.
Besides, I'm in an awkward position.
Even if I stay here,
nothing good will come out of it.
But the journey to Xuan Han is far
and rough.
Your Highness.
Please don't say anymore.
My life
is like the catkins
flowing with the winds.
I have never had control over it.
Moreover,
we shouldn't have anything to do
with each other.
I'm already content to know
that you care for me.
Your Highness.
Please go back now.
[Be Safe]
Last time when I travelled to the north,
you gave me this lucky charm.
Hence I was able to return safely.
Now you are travelling to the north,
I hope the lucky charm
will bring you back safely too.
Thank you, Your Highness.
[Hao'er does love you deeply.]
[But you don't even want to try.]
Be on high alert.
The wedding procession will arrive soon.
Any mistake
will lead to dire consequences.
Did you hear the General?
Yes, General.
[Hengjing]
Sulphur.
Li Wei.
Get some men to surround this place.
Explosives must have been buried here.
Do not act rashly.
Yes, General.
[Ruyi Pavilion]
This is great.
-This is great.
[Rong'er, as long as you're back safely,]
[three months salary as penalty
is nothing.]
[Even if the penalty is
three years of salary,]
[I'd still be glad to pay.]
[As a parent,]
[I don't expect her husband]
[to support me.]
[I only want her]
[to have a happy and peaceful life.]
Yuan.
Sulphur?
You want to obstruct the marriage alliance
to sabotage the relations between
Dayu and Xuan Han
so that you can please the new king?
Keep dreaming.
General.
Are you alright, General?
Check the suspects.
Make sure the procession is safe.
Yes, General.
Check the suspects immediately.
Yes.
What did you say?
Get up first.
You said Duke An and Zhang Yan
plotted this fire?
Yes.
Zhang Yan was saved by Duke An.
He did not die.
Duke An sent me to tell Duke Su
that you were in trouble at Ruyi Pavilion.
That's why Duke Su went to Ruyi Pavilion.
That night at Ju Shui Pavilion...
You are clever.
You must have figured out.
I was fond of Duke An
and lost all sense of judgement.
I was willing to do everything for him.
I even wanted to steal the token.
But he thinks I was in his way
and wants to kill me.
I went into your room that day
because I was hiding from the guards.
Where is Zhang Yan's body now?
Duke An had arranged
to dispose Zhang Yan's body
before the Bureau arrived.
Not only that.
He arranged some men to disguise
as the Imperial Guards
to kill the people in Ruyi Pavilion.
He wanted to put the blame on Duke Su
and provoke enmity between you
and Duke Su.
Why did he do that?
Maybe it's because
he loves you.
No, wait.
This is ridiculous.
If he really loved me,
why would he lie to me?
He also killed my father.
No.
The fire in Ruyi Pavilion
was not meant to kill Lord Fu.
Zhang Yan made that decision
on his own.
When Duke An sent me to lure Duke Su
to Ruyi Pavilion,
he wanted Duke Su to die.
He hates Duke Su to the bone.
Why did he insist on killing Duke Su?
-I need to talk to him.
-Madam.
You must not go to Duke An.
He is ruthless.
He has gone insane because of you.
Even if you confront him now,
you won't get an answer.
You might get yourself in danger instead.
Duke Su must be on his way
to Xuan Han now.
Please wait for his return
to devise a better plan.
Your Highness.
It is noon time.
Should we depart now?
Take care, Your Highness.
Depart.
[Hengjing]
Your Highness.
What's the matter, madam?
What's the matter?
Did I ever tell you that
my mother was killed in a fire
in Hong Fu Temple.
[My mother was a kind person.]
She was cast aside
just because she has anisocoria.
I was separated from her since young.
I couldn't get to see her
for one last time.
[Uncle San and Xiao Qi, please
investigate Duke An's mother's death.]
Lan Xiang.
Send this letter to Uncle San and Xiao Qi.
Okay.
On your way back,
tell my sister not to worry about me.
Noted.
I need to find His Highness.
Madam.
You can't fight
and the journey is rough.
Let me accompany you.
I could be of help.
Yuan.
How am I able to trust you?
Please trust me one more time, Madam.
I swear
I will never disappoint Ms Liu
and you again.
Thank you, Madam.
[May Duke Huai be safe]
[without injuries]
[and return triumphantly soon.]
Princess.
Stop the cart.
The journey is rough.
Please take care.
Thank you, brother.
I will.
Princess.
I don't want to go to Xuan Han.
We're now only half way there.
The journey is already killing us.
If we continue,
I'm afraid
we won't be able to make it
to our destination.
I want to run away.
But I need your help.
Run away?
Are you out of your mind?
Disobeying the Emperor's order
means death penalty.
We're in the middle of nowhere.
Where can we run to?
I've observed the route just now.
There's a little village
not far ahead.
When we're there,
we can conceal our identity
and live there for a while.
After some time,
we can return to Hengjing.
We can say that
we got separated with the troop.
Nobody would blame us.
This...
Will it work?
This is our only chance.
Once we reach Xuan Han,
we'll never be able to return.
But
if we're gone,
what will happen to Duke Su?
We can't do that.
The Emperor will punish him.
You're the one in deep trouble now.
Why do you care about Duke Su?
He doesn't even want to marry you.
Besides, Duke Su is the royal son.
Even if he made mistakes,
the Emperor will not persecute him.
He'll only receive slight punishment.
It's totally different for us.
If we go to Xuan Han,
we're as good as dead.
Hence we need to run away.
Everything else can be discussed later.
In that case...
What is your plan?
I'm warning you first.
If the plan goes wrong,
you'll be dead.
Stop.
It's getting dark.
We'll camp here for the night.
Assassins!
What is happening outside?
Let me have a look.
Princess.
Assassins are attacking us.
Assassins?
Let's run away now.
This is our chance to run.
Let's go.
You take a rest first.
I'll go there to have a look
and figure out the route.
You be careful.
I can't run anymore.
I'll be back soon.
Stop running.
Madam!
Yuan!
Yuan.
Yuan, you'll be fine.
Madam.
Do not be sad.
I deserve to die.
Yuan.
Actually Ms Liu died because of me.
I even cleared out the secret room,
without a sense of remorse.
And made it look like Ms Liu
had committed suicide.
What?
I didn't mean to kill Ms Liu.
To die today for you,
I don't know if Ms Liu wants to see me
when I go on the other side.
Yuan.
You'll be fine, Yuan.
We'll find you a physician.
Yuan.
Yuan!
Wake up, Yuan.
We'll go see the physician now.
Yuan.
Xu Jia.
Your Highness.
The Princess is missing.
Search the area immediately.
Yes, Your Highness.
Fu Rong.
Let go of me.
I couldn't get Duke Su to love me.
I'm even forced into marriage alliance.
I have no reason to live anymore.
What are you talking about?
Grab on tight.
Fu Rong.
Promise me one thing.
After I die,
please take good care of Duke Su.
You will not die.
You always says you love His Highness.
What would happen to him
if you die?
Besides,
don't you want to know
who wants us dead?
You're right.
I will find out who he is
and punish his entire family.
Yes. Quick, hold on to me.
Quick.
Be careful.
Quickly now.
Why is Gu Yuan here?
Cui Wan.
Princess. Princess.
Duke Su.
-Duke Su
-Your Highness, we are down here.
We are down here.
Duke Su.
Your Highness, we are down here.
We are down here.
Duke Su!
Quick.
-Are you alright?
-Quickly save the princess.
Duke Su.
Pull.
Give me your hand.
♫ Faint shadows and slanted lanterns
illuminate your visage ♫
Duke Su!
♫ When will I comb your hair again? ♫
Fu Rong!
♫ Old dreams come back to haunt us ♫
♫ Love and hate resurface ♫
♫ Waiting for the clouds to clear
and the moon to shine through ♫
♫ I travel across mountains and rivers
just to get a glimpse of you ♫
♫ I'll never forget
the first time we met ♫
♫ Fireflies set the skies ablaze ♫
♫ Inflamming the passion in our hearts ♫
♫ As dream and obsession coalesce ♫
Your Highness.
Wake up, Your Highness.
Wake up!
I saw Gu Yuan's body.
What happened?
Yuan was protecting me all the way
till we found the Princess.
We were ambushed by the men in black.
Princess and I slipped off the cliff
after being attacked by an arrow.
I'm sorry, Your Highness.
Yuan has confessed to me
that the incident at Ruyi Pavilion
was plotted by Duke An and Zhang Yan.
Duke An?
Yuan also told me that
she was the one who caused Master's death.
As for Duke An,
His mother was killed in a fire
in Hong Fu Temple.
You told me before
that you once knocked over a candlestick
in Hong Fu Temple.
I did knock over the candlestick.
But
only some scriptures were burnt.
It didn't cause any death.
Coincidentally,
the day you knocked over the candlestick
was the day his mother died.
Although I was very young at that time,
I still have some vague memories
of that day.
There was no death in that fire.
I had arranged for an investigation
so that I can prove to you
that the people of Ruyi Pavilion
are not criminals.
Rong'er.
I have never ordered the killings
at Ruyi Pavilion.
During the fire at Ruyi Pavilion that day,
Imperial Guards who closed the streets
were fake guards.
It was arranged by Duke An.
Let's not think about this first.
What is important now
is that we find a way out of here.
How can we get out of here?
What if we really can't get out of here?
We'll die here then.
I'm just your concubine.
We're not allowed to be buried together
when we die.
If we really die here,
we'll forever be together.
But that won't do.
There are many pending problems to solve.
I can't leave my mother, sister
and brother.
Let's not die first.
-So should we die or not?
-No, we shouldn't die yet.
♫ I murmur as if I was dreaming ♫
Let's find a way out first.
Let's go.
♫ Before the scene is penned,
we are already parting ♫
♫ Man of my dreams, moon in my lake,
I close my eyes ♫
♫ My remaining desire
slipped through my fingers ♫
♫ The fragrant flower withers away
in the wind ♫
♫ Turning into mud, quelling my
loneliness, warming the winter ♫
♫ The cloud approaches, the rain lingers ♫
♫ Turning sentiments and laughter
into memories ♫
♫ My feelings well up in my eyes ♫
♫ As I think about the long years
till we meet again ♫
♫ Lamenting our separation,
bemoaning our unresolved ending ♫
♫ Why should we acquiesce
if we wish to defy our destiny? ♫
♫ The vicissitudes of life is inexorable ♫
What a sight.
♫ You are willing to wither along
with the pretty flowers ♫
♫ Let the endless cold nights enshroud
our love and hatred ♫
The temperature here is higher.
♫ Let our teary eyes meet as we smile ♫
Hence the flowers
are still blooming.
♫ When it rains again ♫
♫ Bearing our long-cherished wish,
I will walk through life with you ♫
Although it is beautiful here,
but how can we get out?
We've been walking for some time.
I'm tired.
We'll stay here tonight.
We'll start walking again
at dawn tomorrow.
Rong'er.
-If something happens to me
-I don't want to hear this.
-you can find Mr Ge.
-He can make sure you're safe.
-I don't want to hear this.
We've not slept together
as a real married couple.
And you're still young...
What are you doing, Rong'er?
You've now reminded me of it.
It won't be good for you
if people know this.
We can't put this off any further.
What are you doing?
Stop, it tickles.
[Duke An is so cruel.]
-Stop running.
-[He got me into this.]
[And now he wants me dead.]
Stop running.
-Stop!
-Stop running.
Stop running!
Stop running.
Your Highness.
Watch out.
Why are you here?
What about you?
Why are you here alone?
Where is the troop?
I...
I got separated from the troop
and met with two robbers on the way.
I had to keep running.
We shouldn't stay here for too long.
Let's keep moving.
Duke Su.
Fu Rong.
When will you be back?
Princess.
Duke and Duchess Su
are not found yet.
It's all my fault.
They wanted to save me.
What about Yuan?
We have given her a proper burial.
Please do not worry.
I've sent some men to search for
Duke and Duchess Su.
They will be fine.
It's all my fault.
After we find a way out,
you go back to the capital first.
I'll meet you there later.
What will Duke An do to us after this?
There's no news from Ruyi Pavilion yet.
Will we be able to find the truth
about Hong Fu Temple?
If he thinks I did something,
then I'll confront him.
Duke An wanted to kill you when he set
Ruyi Pavilion on fire.
But father was the one who suffered
the consequences.
I don't know how to face him anymore.
How did you get here?
Who are you?
I should be the one asking.
I've been living here.
We fell off the cliff and are looking
for a way out.
Hence we ended up here.
Do you know if there's a way out of here?
Follow me.
Go through the cave and
you'll see the way out.
Thank you.
Can I ask?
Why do you stay here alone?
I have an eye disease.
I prefer to live a quiet life.
This place is hidden,
peaceful and free of disturbance.
So I have continued to live here.
We're really grateful to you today.
Farewell.
Xuan'er.
Why are you here?
Why didn't you inform me first?
General.
You were badly hurt.
Yes. Right.
Xuan'er.
I'm badly hurt.
I'm in pain.
Xuan'er.
-Xuan'er.
-Stop acting.
If you really want to see me,
just tell me honestly.
You don't have to lie.
Xuan'er.
Xuan'er. I didn't do this on purpose.
Don't go, Xuan'er.
General.
You're bleeding again.
Li Wei.
You really have some nerve.
How dare you bring Ms Fu here
without telling me?
Luckily someone told me
you're bringing her here.
If not, I...
General.
You kept calling her name
when you were unconscious.
So I thought you really wanted to see her.
So I...
I do want to see her.
But not at this time.