Hey, Hong Jihyo.
Pull yourself together.
It's white...
White?
White all around me.
Everything.
There aren't any walls.
There's no floor.
But they...
they chose me for a reason.
Who are they?
It's the same...
as Back Yoonsun's interview.
- Jihyo, listen to me.
- Huh?
- What do they want from you?
- Th...
What did they put in your head?
Ah. They're...
They're all speaking to me.
What?
What language are they speaking?
Hey, say that again.
- Jihyo! Hey! Say something!
- Hong Jihyo!
Snap out of it! Hey!
And so it is...
What does all of this even mean?
It means you've made contact with aliens.
When you disappeared back in middle school
at our hideout in the field of reeds.
That's when you met the aliens. Yeah.
What?
Uh...
Um, hey, Bora...
So you knew all of this?
Yeah.
Yeah, I went over to your house
after you left the hospital.
I went there to tell you everything.
Oh...
Hey.
Do you...
do you really not remember anything?
You know, all the things
that you saw, heard.
Really nothing?
I really can't remember.
Only the field of reeds with you.
When we were together.
Field of reeds...
Do you wanna go there?
Huh?
Go there...
If I go in person,
and see it, maybe It will spark my memory?
Let's go.
- Uh...
- Uh, hi, Doc...
Thank you for today.
Sorry, it's late. We'll get going.
- Let's go. Bye, now!
- Hey, hey.
- Thank you!
- Jihyo, hold on! Wait!
Just a minute.
I'll be smoking downstairs, 'kay?
Take a seat.
I'm really sorry,
but seriously, I can't talk for long.
- What was that earlier? Huh?
- Listen, I'll tell you everything later.
Okay? I'm really sorry.
I have to go.
Hey, Jihyo. Hey, Hong Jihyo!
Listen, I really don't have time
for this, okay?
You need the hospital. Seriously.
No, not like this. A real... real hospital.
Where you can get a proper consultation.
No...
I'm sick and tired of hospitals.
I'm leaving.
Hey, Hong Jihyo!
Hey, Jihyo! Hey, Jihyo! Hong Jihyo!
Hey, Jihyo!
Where did you go?
Answer me!
Oh shit. Please just gimme a minute.
Ah...
Was...
was our hideout around here?
Yeah. Yeah, I think so.
So the place I must have
found the camera was...
There?
Shit, was it?
God, is this even the right place?
Oh, Bora, I'm sorry.
What?
For what?
For when I slapped you.
Seriously?
It's fine!
Anyway, we're even now.
I'm sorry, I really hated you then...
I thought that the reason my family
fell apart was all because of you.
I mean, even with
the hallucinations I had...
I thought that...
it was all because of you and your glue.
I also thought it was
because you gave me alcohol.
All this time. That wasn't true.
It wasn't.
What did they say to you back then?
You said the aliens said something to you.
What in the world did they say?
Is there anything else you can think of?
Anything before or after that?
My dad...
- What?
- Actually, my dad told me something.
Yeah, it was after I came back and...
I was in the hospital for a while.
And when I was there,
I remember him saying
that while I was in a daze,
I was rambling gibberish to myself.
Gibberish?
Do you think it's possible that...
that those ramblings might be
connected to...
...what I heard from the aliens?
Bora, let me use your phone.
Uh, hey... Dad, is that you?
Hey, Dad, it's Jihyo. Hmm...
Dad, will you pl... Ju... ju... Calm down.
No, I... Dad, stop.
Listen, I was going to call you, but I...
but I wasn't in a situation where...
Yes, well... Yeah, yeah, I'll go home.
Listen, I'm going home, but right now is...
What?
Say what?
Give me...
- back my... boyfriend!
- Hospitalization?
You...
No, I... I mean, why...
why is she acting like this?
And also, why here?
Well, she's exhibiting all
the signs of schizophrenia.
Hey! Hey!
Paranoia, hallucinations, language
breakdown, et cetera.
- She's a textbook example.
- Hey! Hey!
This is Information we received
from the local police at the time.
- You're welcome to review it.
- So Ms. Hong did this?
I ask you find her as soon as possible
and take protective action.
As you can see, this is
a highly dangerous case of schizophrenia.
Yes, yes, I understand.
Hmm.
There's something fishy.
Things just really aren't matching up.
No. they're matching up too well.
Right.
Okay, let's say Jihyo was crazy
and went on a rampage.
Think about it.
Why would she do that here?
- Why way out here?
- I knew that person earlier.
Who?
The person Ms. Hong was holding onto.
He came with Ms. Hong to the station
because of an assault case.
An assault case?
Wait, Jihyo?
Yeah, he was also from that church.
I think even the police here are fishy.
Yes, Detective Kim here...
Yes. Sure thing.
I'll be right there, yeah.
Don't worry about this too much.
Trust me, we'll take care of it.
Everything's fine.
Please make certain of that.
Hey, Jihyo.
Stop right there.
What?
Don't go in.
Why?
Well, think about it. Isn't this timing...
just way too fucking perfect?
What is?
Why is he coming back right now?
As soon as you escaped from there?
Doesn't this seem
like some sort of trap?
Are you sure it was really your dad?
I'm sure. It was my dad's voice.
What if your dad is being held by them
as well?
Ah, shit, really?
Hey, wait!
Jihyo! Hold on!
Why?
Take this.
FOR OUTSIDE LIVE STREAM
Go on Discord. I'll be listening.
So if something happens, just scream.
Got it?
I'll be back.
Bora. I'm inside.
Dad...
Hello...
I'm home, Dad.
So, where is he?
Come in.
Hello.
Si...
Siguk.
Um...
Uh...
My home...
It's gone.
Yes, thank you so much.
Actually...
DEPARTMENT OF PUBLIC ORDER
I'm calling to see how the kidnapping case
at the New Hope Hospital is going?
Yes.
What? No, that can't be...
No, no, no, no.
Yesterday, the local station came
and searched the entire place.
I was the one who reported it.
No, how...
Yes, well, okay, I understand.
I get it. Okay.
What the...
I'm saying
this isn't a simple intimidation case.
So what does it have
to do with the church?
This... this person
did not need their help.
There were signs
that she was held there illegally.
What are you talking about? Huh?
They've already done an identity
confirmation and everything.
It was all legitimate!
What?
Motherfuckers.
So, about this cult.
I think it's possible they're manipulating
the police from the inside as well.
How did I see that with my own eyes,
and even report it,
only for them to cover it up like this?
They're not covering it up!
- You rookie!
- Shh.
Some crazy patients had an outburst
and you're misinterpreting it!
- That's it!
- Chief, it's not true!
Why did you go to Jeonju
in the first place?
It's like I said, it's a little personal...
- Can't tell you.
- Oh my God, rookie.
Instead of looking into
an old case like that, just...
just focus on our work!
Our work, rookie! Huh?
We're slammed, it's time to crack down!
And anyway, the case you reported
is within Jeonju's jurisdiction.
They'll take care of it there.
Don't think about it.
- This rookie.
- Get back to work, seriously. -
You little...
This member advanced
from a private to a corporal...
MOONHOLE TV FORUM
MOONHOLE... YOUTUBE... UPLOAD
...while waiting for Moonhole's
next video.
No. Mmm. You're overexaggerating.
- Blocked.
- Did she lose subscribers?
I feel like I'm looking
at last year's Bitcoin crash.
What's the point
of editing her videos?
- Move.
- The YouTuber herself went off the grid.
She's probably alive, right?
I think so.
Seeing that she's reading the group chat.
No, not Bora... Petite.
You don't, like, think she's dead, do you?
Gah! Ah, shit!
They're so strong, that bastard, fuck.
Cap, I'll take
an iced caramel macchiato.
Where on Earth have you been?
Ah, my ears! Fuck!
What? I told you I was going out.
You said you were going to buy cigarettes.
Was the convenience store in...
New Zealand?
So what happened? Did you find her?
Find who?
Weren't you going around
looking for Petite by yourself?
You left us behind because you thought
we'd be in danger, you punk. Didn't you?
Why the hell are you crying, you idiot?
I was really worried for her.
- You were worried?
- Gosh.
It's all right, it's all right.
She's back now.
Shhh.
It's okay.
He looks like a criminal,
but he's really sensitive.
An alien implant?
In Troll's head?
Mm-hm.
An alien implant? Oh no.
That has been reported among
people who were kidnapped by aliens.
Mysterious implants kinda like electronic
chips are planted inside their heads.
There are no scars, and no pain.
Can't even see where they did it.
It happened to Back Yoonsun as well.
Wait a minute, the same sort of chip
was implanted in Petite's head too?
- Yeah, she had one.
- Whoa.
- Hmm.
- But the cult took it out.
- Hmm. How'd they take it out?
- Wow.
A drill.
- Reeee! Eeeeh!
- Ah, hell, no.
In my opinion, the important thing is not
how they took it, but why they took it.
I mean, what is it about this chip that
they would name her a Messiah for it?
Well, they said
it's for salvation or whatever.
- Huh?
- Yeah, the cult leader said so.
He said it had something to do
with salvation or whatever.
Anyway, isn't all of this over now?
- You said Troll's boyfriend came back.
- So It's over?
Didn't this start because
she was trying to find that guy?
But if she found him, the cult,
the implant, and all that, it's all over.
Oh!
Going to the store?
Fuck you!
Why'd you turn off your fucking phone?
Wait, are you the owner of this place?
If you're going somewhere,
you should at least tell me.
Is it too much to ask to send a text?
Do you wanna die?
Are there any rooms available?
What? A customer?
This café doesn't have any.
Come on. What, cat got your tongue?
- Don't just stand there, say something!
- Right now, I...
Huh? Yeah, that's him.
It's Direct Kim.
- What?
- It's Direct Kim?
Right now...
Ah, hey! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Daddy's sorry! I'm sorry!
I'm sorry, Younggi. Daddy's sorry.
- Hey, what's going on?
- Please come help me grab her!
- Yeah, yeah.
- What's going on?
- Here! Help me, help me! Come on!
Here, here...
Careful, careful, careful. Younggi! Lift.
- Ah! Ohhh!
- Oh, oh!
- Carefully, carefully!
- Oh my God.
- Aaah!
- The shotgun girl! Shotgun girl!
- It's okay.
- Huh?
- The shotgun girl!
- Oh! Oh!
- Oh, fuck, the shotgun girl!
- Help me!
- What's going on?
- Aah!
- Wow...
- Are you serious?
Wow, wow. Oh!
- Unbelievable...
- Damn it.
Oh... Oh...
Did you get some rest?
Yeah, you should have breakfast,
huh?
McDonald's breakfast!
Yeah, you used to say you wanted
to eat this every day when you were...
Are you happy you made
a fool out of the church?
And tell me, just how long
have you been a rat in our church?
Isn't talking to your dad like that
going a little too far?
What a nice father-daughter
relationship you two have, fuck!
Hey. Are you sure it's her who shot you?
I'm positive.
Defamation of character
and abuse on top of that.
Direct Kim's
daughter's in a cult.
What a funny prank.
Wait.
When were you going to tell us about this?
The whole reason you wanted to get into
the NPC or whatever was because of this?
That was the only option I had...
if I wanted to see her face again.
So you've been lying to us
this whole time, huh?
You said your daughter was kidnapped.
I'm really sorry.
Oh! I don't have time for this! Come on...
Tell me, where is her Holiness?
Her what?
Who? You mean Jihyo?
She's been talking about
"Her Holiness" since earlier.
She really wants to meet Jihyo.
Why?
Bora, come here.
- Why?
- Just a second.
Why?
Listen. Please do me a favor.
Let us stay here for just a little while.
Wait, what?
It's because I don't have anywhere
to take her right now.
The church knows my address.
No! No, no, no, no!
Oh no. No. No way!
Mr. Direct Kim.
What's one reason we should do that?
There isn't one.
There are a lot of people who almost
got killed by those crazy people.
- Exactly.
- You played a part in that.
What?
Well, they ended up like that
because they listened to you.
Bora.
Please help me.
I helped you, right? Huh?
You and Jihyo.
Hey, sir...
See, I'm the owner here.
Not her.
- I'm... I'm just saying.
- How about 150 per night?
Let me check the second floor boiler room.
What? The boiler room!
They need hot water.
No, come on! Send them away!
Hey, give me 10,000 won.
No matter what the situation might be,
food always comes first,
especially for Koreans, hm?
After you're done,
just leave the table out.
Hey, thank you, Dad.
Siguk...
Are you all right? Hey.
What in the world happened to you?
Do you know where Chao Phraya River is?
What?
They said I jumped from there,
from some bridge.
They said you jumped?
Wait, what do you mean?
Well, apparently, I tried killing myself...
What?
I opened my eyes and I was in a hospital.
A Thai hospital.
I listened to what they said...
fell asleep, woke up,
fell asleep, woke up again,
I was at Incheon Airport.
But why Thailand all of a sudden?
I really don't like food with cilantro.
Wait, so you...
Wait, hold on, Siguk.
So then you...
don't remember anything
at all that happened to you?
What's the last thing you remember?
When you asked me to break up with you.
I remember, before going to the bar,
I gave some food to Justin Bieber.
What happened to Justin Bieber?
I nee... need to clean his litter box.
Oh! That guy!
Tell Siguk
he can stay here for a while.
I can sleep in the living room.
Mmm. Thank you.
We should at least do this for him.
What else can we do?
This is one extraordinary...
Because of my kid,
he packed up everything
and tried to kill himself.
...about 60 or 70 years.
The aging process...
- Hey, Dad.
- What?
Do you remember that time...
when I went missing in middle school?
The sturgeon, which takes a long time
to reach its full strength...
You said that I kept saying weird things
at the hospital.
What type of things did I say?
- Why are you suddenly asking me that?
- It's just...
Do you remember anything I said?
No, I don't remember.
Nor do I want to.
Tell me, why are you talking nonsense
all of a sudden? My God.
Please, just let it be.
...of the species to endangered status.
There are people who rescue
the sturgeon from danger
so that it can fully grow,
which takes time.
The migration
for this fascinating creature follows...
He can wear some of Dad's things for now.
Tell him to let us know
if he needs anything.
He's going to have to start from scratch.
All right.
So...
what's going on?
Sorry? What do you mean?
You've been like that
since you were young.
When you have something on your mind,
you avoid eye contact
and sneak around
like you're guilty of something.
- Uh...
- So what is it?
Uh...
It's because of Siguk.
You were like that before he disappeared.
Is it uncomfortable to talk to me?
Is it something
you'd rather solve on your own?
Uh...
Siguk...
See, I really don't think
Siguk tried to kill himself, so...
What do you mean?
It's nothing. Just...
- Thank you.
- What is it?
It's really nothing. I'm sorry.
I'm the one who heard it.
I heard you rambling.
What?
I was the first one to arrive
at the hospital after getting the call.
When I got there, you were asleep
and mumbling something.
Like you were in a trance.
I just thought it was because of the glue.
Do you remember what I said?
Do you remember
exactly what I said that day?
I do...
You just kept saying
the same thing over and over.
Tell me...
Please tell me what was I saying that day.
"Come back."
Wait, what?
"Come back to me."
What are you saying?
You want me to come now?
No, I mean, she said that's what
I kept repeating at the hospital.
"Coming back... back to me."
Coming back? Who is?
What do you mean, who? The aliens!
Why are they coming back?
I don't know for sure, but I think
the thing they implanted in my head...
I think that it must have
something to do with that.
Bora...
Do you think it could be some sort
of device that calls for the UFOs, huh?
A transmitter?
Like a pager.
Ugh, I'm not eating that!
Huh?
What? What was that? What happened?
Just eat it.
- No, nothing.
- I'm not eating that!
Well, so now what?
- What do you wanna do?
- Uh, well...
I guess I'll come over there...
- Yeah, I'll come there first...
- You don't need to because of that.
That's just a theory you have.
Don't you need
to take care of your boyfriend?
Just stay at home for a while.
And don't go anywhere.
No...
- Wait, no, Bo... Just listen...
- You've finally found him.
You need to keep an eye on him
so he doesn't run off somewhere.
No, no, Bora, but this is still...
I'm sorry, but I have something to do.
I gotta go.
Bo... Bo... Bora!
Huh?
Lee Siguk.
Where are you going?
Ah, do you need something?
Can I help you?
I have to go somewhere.
Where?
Um, you should stay home for now.
Wanna go?
Why do you keep asking for "Her Holiness"?
Can she summon a UFO or something?
Tell me... Is that it?
Where on Earth did you get that idea?
The thing that you guys
took out of Jihyo's head,
is that some kind of transmitter?
You summon them, and the aliens come down,
and what happens next?
What is this "Messiah"
supposed to be doing?
I looked over this a bit,
and it's not in here either.
There's only
"Messiah shows up to save mankind."
There's nothing written after that.
So what is it?
What does this "Messiah" do?
Bora, what are you doing?
Hold on. I'm talking to her right now.
What are you going to gain from talking
about this damn cult?
- She's already confused.
- Shut up!
Do you even know anything
about our doctrines?
How dare you talk
to your dad like that!
Tell me, when were you ever a dad to me?
What do you mean, "dad"?
- Agh!
- You punk! What did you just say to me?
- They're getting on better.
- We've nothing to talk about.
Do you know what I've done because of you?
- Well I never asked you to do that!
- Oh, will both of you just shut up?
You.
Listen, If you don't start talking,
you're out of here.
I won't ever let you meet "Her Holiness"
or whatever again. So speak up.
I'll kick you out too!
Okay, I got it.
I'll call Cap now.
No, I... Bora, come on.
Why are you being like that?
- I have to tell her.
- Huh?
I need to tell her Holiness...
that she needs to run away.
What are you talking about?
The Corps is desperately
trying to find her.
And when they do, they'll kill her.
Hello?
All of the believers
think that the Messiah...
Well, they think she's already dead, and...
that she threw away her body,
- that she was martyred.
- Hmm.
This person is the victim.
And we're in a hurry
to find out where this person is.
It's not confirmed
whether he's alive or not.
Tell me, is it true you've
been in touch with Ms. Hong Jihyo?
No... We haven't.
After she left home, she... she hasn't
answered any of our phone calls.
I'm afraid her Holiness's
funeral will be held soon.
Are they really trying to murder her?
They do that, their lie seems true.
The believers,
they're going...
They're going to display her dead body...
DETECTIVE OH YOUNGTAEK
JEONJU JEONWON POLICE STATION
- Contact me on my cell phone.
- Rural police station? You're not local?
This violent incident occurred
in our jurisdiction.
If things get worse,
I'm sure local police will get involved.
And after the funeral ceremony,
Father will take
the Messiah's divine power
and use it in her place.
What? What power?
Ascension.
What?
But you see, the only one
that can give the power of ascension
to the people of the Earth...
Well, it can only be the Messiah herself.
Not Father.
Don't you understand?
Don't you understand? Father Light
will be coming down to Earth very soon.
What the hell were you thinking?
He's coming soon, Sister Seo!
Weren't you embarrassed
acting like that in front of them? Huh?
Still so obsessed?
Obsessed with worldly desire...
- What? What are you gonna do now? Huh?
- Brother Oh, but...
- It's not that...
- You shut your mouth!
We didn't say you could speak!
For someone who is a deaconess,
I don't understand
how you could think so childishly.
Appeasing her like that.
So, what, did you think
you'd get greater salvation?
It's a good thing, huh?
She did it after the surgery. She's lucky.
- It could have caused a bigger problem.
- Oh God...
She should be expelled,
so she won't be saved.
Goodness...
You guys are being too serious
over a deaconess causing a little trouble.
So? Hmm.
So let's wrap all this up.
The Father is making a decision.
Get on your feet.
The sinner must await judgment.
If you die alone now,
you'll be so lonely.
You should really go.
You should leave.
Everything now is...
trivial, anyway.
Hmm?
You know what?
- Father!
- I've been in a great mood these days.
- Everyone looks... so small.
- Father!
Before, I used to hate it,
hate it so much,
the way... they struggled to live.
- Father!
- Nowadays, they look adorable.
Sella.
I was wrong.
- Sella.
- Father!
Father has generously forgiven you.
Thank you, I'm sorry...
The trial is over.
Father, I didn't do it on purpose.
I didn't know this would happen.
- Get up.
- Come on, get up.
- Oh, my...
- Let's go outside, come on.
Oh! I thought I was gonna die!
Father, the memorial invitation
is ready to be sent.
Oh, you're working so hard.
Uh... Okay, good.
And how's the tech team?
Is everything ready?
Sorry, Father.
They say they need a little more time
to get things ready. What should we do?
Hmm.
And make our believers wait even longer?
No.
Tell them to make it on time.
Okay, understood. Light be with you.
Don't worry.
Everything's going to be okay.
Justin!
Justin, I'm here. Where are you, Justin?
Justin, where are you, buddy?
Justin...
Listen, he's not here.
I've already looked for him.
I think someone took him.
Who would take that grubby cat anyway?
Justin. Justin...
He must be hungry.
- Let's go home.
- I don't have a home.
- Don't be like that.
- What about Justin?
I looked for him already.
What were you going to do
when you found him?
Were you gonna take care of him?
Your mom hates animals.
I don't know,
I just tried looking for him.
Did you just try looking for me, too?
If you'd found me, then what?
Didn't we break up anyway?
I'm sorry.
I knew everything.
I knew you felt pressured
when I talked about living together.
I noticed it from the signals
you gave me from the beginning.
I knew it, but I just kept pushing anyway.
If I hadn't brought it up that day, you
might not have broken up with me. Damn it.
Siguk...
But things
didn't go as planned, so I...
I did something as stupid
as trying to kill myself.
How can a person be so idiotic? Oh...
- Why did I even work so hard all my life?
- Come on. It's not your fault!
Hey, Lee Siguk.
Think hard for a second, hm?
Are you really sure you did that? Huh?
I mean, tell me the truth,
did you really try to die?
You cleared everything out of your room
and put it up for rent.
You bought a plane ticket!
Did your really do all that? Huh?
If not me, then who?
I think that it really
doesn't add up at all, huh?
Huh? Do you really
think that's what happened?
I just don't know.
LOVELY AUNT, ARE YOU WATCHING?
DO YOU KNOW WHO THIS IS? LOL
UFO FORUM MODS
Yes, ma'am.
I'm checking her known places now.
Hmm. We should be able to find her today.
Don't worry about it too much.
Don't tell me
not to worry.
We have to find her by the end of the day.
We don't have much time.
Her location just came up.
I'll send it to you right away.
You can take care of the rest.
I'll stand down for now.
Yes, understood.
Ascension...
Hey. Do you think you get a superpower?
The ability to fly would be cool.
Like growing, pfft, wings.
I wanna teleport.
Phswoo!
Trust me, it's not that great.
The ascension they're talking about?
Huh?
You know,
what those cultists call ascension,
it's much different
than what you're thinking.
They just get together and
commit pointless crimes. Okay?
Forget it.
Those cultists are planning
something at Jihyo's funeral...
Jihyo's funeral?
- Oh!
- Hi!
My funeral?
What are you talking about?
Your Holiness.
- Damn it.
- Oh shit!
- Wait! Hey!
- Get off...
What the hell are you guys?
It's you, isn't it? You kidnapped Siguk.
- Calm down!
- Do you even know how broken...
how completely broken Siguk is now?
- Come on let her go!
- You made him into an invalid!
Then you throw him out like trash?
Huh? What is this? Huh?
What did you take out of my head?
- Hey! Calm down!
- Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Just calm down, calm down!
So she's Direct Kim's daughter?
Huh?
So then, he was lying to us
this entire time?
She's... more useful than you might think.
If you ask nicely, she gives out
information. Why are you attacking her?
Bora. Tell me why we don't have
any evidence yet to show.
- What?
- About what we've done.
Aliens... and cult leaders,
and things like that...
It's just... You see, it sounds crazy
to people who hear it, huh?
Even though we've worked
so hard this whole time,
there's no evidence.
Nobody will believe us
if we don't have any proof. Huh?
What's the point if nobody believes us?
Then isn't this whole thing for nothing?
Hey. Do you know what state
Siguk is in right now?
He doesn't even know what happened to him.
You don't know how it feels, do you? Huh?
You don't...
...understand... just how crazy
that makes people.
DIVINE LIGHT CHURCH
BE BORN AGAIN THROUGH THE LIGHT
"Memorial."
FASTING THE DAY
BEFORE THE MEMORIAL SERVICE!
"Ascension is everlasting life
and salvation."
"We must abandon our carbon bodies
in order to receive
our everlasting body of Light."
These people...
think that...
this body is the root of all evil,
so they need to abandon it.
Wait, wait, wait.
Abandoning your carbon body?
So then... doesn't that mean death?
Then why'd
they take the implant?
I'm guessing that alien implants
are some kind of beacon or signal fire.
It must signal the target spot.
Then a fleet of UFOs appear,
and bang! Over!
Everyone dies.
Sounds like destruction, not ascension.
Holy shit, when did the scale of this
suddenly get so massive?
People believe this?
Hey, stop doing that!
Why are you shaking your legs?
I'm not shaking them.
It's mass suicide.
"Ascension" means mass suicide.
It's not the destruction of humanity.
What do you mean?
Well, It's not the first time
that they've done this.
In the past,
they went on about the "ascension,"
and as a group, they all hung themselves.
They convinced people that removing
yourself from your body is ascension.
One of the people who hung
themselves at that time
was her grandmother.
Sadly, she was there to see it.
Anyway...
if these trash people want
to get together and kill themselves.
just let them.
It's not the Messiah's funeral,
it's theirs.
It has to do with all of us.
Jihyo. Whatever's in your memory...
that...
...will bring salvation to us all.
It's there.
What?
The implant is gonna be there.
At my funeral.
With the cult leader.
And?
I've gotta find it.
What?
How?
Wait a second. Don't tell me you seriously
believe in the aliens or whatever.
Yes... I believe it.
I do believe it.
The aliens, or whatever it is.
There was an implant in my head.
And I lost it without any knowledge of it.
And I need that implant.
I'll find it, and get rid of it.
- Stop it. Don't be ridiculous.
- No, Bora, this is...
Oh please, just shut up for a second...
I know, I know, I know.
Bora, you don't get it!
This is happening because of me. Okay?
This all happened
because I lost the implant.
God, I have...
I have to go! No, you don't have to go.
You all don't have to go. Uh, really.
First of all, I... I have to go...
- I've gotta...
- I said knock it off!
Nobody go and do something
that might kill you,
unless you wanna die by my hands.
Wh... where are you going?
Cigarettes.
A memorial service?
- Wait, who died?
- I have no idea.
But as of today, the worship service
and everything was canceled.
How strange, I mean what kind of event
would make them close the church doors?
Do you think it could be
a break or something?
No, no, no, no.
Well, there was nothing in the church.
They got rid of furniture and everything.
I mean, why does everything
they do seem so creepy, you know?
Anything else? That you found?
Hello?
Sehee, I need to help someone
with a civil complaint.
- Okay, I'll call you back.
- Talk to you later.
You were here when Ms. Hong caused
a scene at the church, that right?
You're Ms. Hong's friend.
Open it. Use your computer.
Why is it so quiet here? Huh?
Where did everyone go?
Uh... because Bora's not back yet.
Phillip and Donghyuk already went home.
- And what about the owner?
- The gym.
- At a time like this?
- Mmm.
He's more afraid of muscle loss
than the destruction of mankind.
Hah!
Hey, Jihyo.
Yeah?
What are you doing here?
I'm smoking.
No, that's not what I meant.
You said your boyfriend came back.
He did.
But what are you still doing here?
Wasn't, your goal to find him
in the first place?
Hmm.
Uh, give me a cigarette too, would ya?
Here.
Whew, I don't know how long it's been
since I last smoked.
- See you inside.
- Okay.
Hey,
What?
About my funeral.
When's it happening?
I don't really know.
And what about the location?
Don't you know where it is?
Why are you asking me that?
Tell me. The...
the Messiah is asking you.
Se... seriously?
Why, are you gonna take it back?
Are you?
You're trying to regain
your divine power, right?
That's right.
Okay.
Well, I don't know the location.
But in the security team's group chat,
there should be an announcement.
Tell me, where's your phone at?
Uh...
Uh, well, he took it.
It's in the car.
The keys. Where are the keys?
Where the hell are they?
Where could they be?
Where are they? Huh?
Hold on. Oh!
Oh? I found them!
Huh?
Stay still!
Don't move.
I can't breathe!
Get off of me! Help me!
Help! Help me! Stop!
We've secured the Messiah's body.
We also have secured Sister Abigail. Over.
Uh...
Your Holiness!
Quickly. We have to go.
Younggi!
Huh? Younggi, don't go!
Younggi! Don't. Don't go!
- Mr. Kim!
- Younggi, Younggi...
You can't leave. You can't go.
- You can't go. Please...
- Uh-uh. We have to leave now!
Please, don't, Younggi.
Please don't leave.
Younggi! Don't leave me!
Younggi, don't!
Don't go...
Look out!
Younggi!
What should we do?
Watch out!,
You little shit.
Let's go. Let's go!
Yaaah!
What's going on?
Why is all this happening?
Captain Price.
Get out of here. More people are coming.
Huh?
Younggi...
Mm-hm.
Huh? No, no...
Don't go...
Please, take care of Mr. Kim.
Captain Price.
- I'm really sorry.
- What?
No. No. Wait, wait...
Captain Price.
- Thank you so much, really.
- What?
Please tell everyone else
I said that, too.
Wait...
Hurry up! Let's go!
No. Petite...
Petite...
Hold on, where... where are you going?
Wait, where are you going?