♪ O Light ♪
♪ Please take us ♪
♪ When this world ♪
BLUELIGHT TRAINING CENTER
♪ Turns its back on me ♪
♪ Your worthy Light ♪
♪ Is what surrounds me ♪
♪ The red dusk falls ♪
♪ On the whole world ♪
♪ My soul and body ♪
♪ Are trapped inside the Light ♪
♪ We shall be with the Light ♪
♪ Let us lift up ♪
♪ The cross together ♪
♪ Come to us ♪
♪ The Light of life ♪
♪ Sella ♪
- Hold on.
- Yes?
When are you going to give me the gospel?
Father should be here soon.
Your Holiness!
Your Holiness! Your Holiness!
Your Holiness, your dress is here!
What? What dress?
Well...
Oh, well... we've actually
had this dress ready for years.
But it had no owner until now.
Oh my goodness!
The day has finally come! Oh!
I mean, when you bring the Blessed Light,
you gotta look great!
Like bam! In this dress.
- Some light, please.
- Oh, wait, wait, um...
- I don't think I should wear that.
- What?
Ah, but when you'll be...
well, be in front of all the believers...
- Don't you want to look...
- Forget the dress for now.
I need the chip. Uh... Well, it's just...
The gospel, I mean, I'd like it first.
Now please ask Father
to hurry up, all right?
Yes, of course, your Holiness.
Get out.
Get out, go, get out.
All right, then. Later, then.
Oh!
Your Holiness.
Don't worry.
I promise your secret's safe.
What secret?
Come on, you know what I mean.
Please. The resurrection. I know.
I know...
I know that you never died.
I know!
See, I know that
because I was with you. Hm?
Well, anyway...
Don't worry.
Don't you worry about it, okay?
It'll be... our little secret.
Just between you and me.
Hmm?
Oh, ho-ho! Sella!
Ugh.
You're not going to work
tomorrow?
I'll just tell them
I'm going to a funeral.
What do you feel like eating?
There's coffee and dried fish snacks.
UFO FORUM
Ooh, yeah, I'll have that.
It sounds good. It's so good with coffee.
"Aah".
Mmm! Mmph!
Here.
Thank you.
What? You're on DC Inside?
Oh, this? Jihyo looked that up, I think.
She's on DC Inside, seriously?
I'm pretty sure it's a UFO forum.
A forum?
Yeah, she's been looking up
this kind of stuff a lot lately.
So is this related to what that guy said?
About the lady who can talk to aliens?
- Hey, gimme that.
- I was looking at that...
Oh, Jihyo, Jihyo, Jihyo...
What in the world were you thinking?
Seriously.
- What?
- This is super cute!
Did Jihyo always like this kind of stuff?
The Unicorns?
Where did it go?
God damn it.
Come on.
What are you doing?
What is that?
Hey.
Come here, let's talk for a minute.
Hey!
Hey I'm talking to you.
Hey! Stop for a second.
I said let's talk! Hey!
RESTRICTED ACCESS
DO NOT ENTER
Hey!
Damn it.
Stop. You can't go in there!
Ugh, seriously? Hey!
What are you doing right now?
Where is it?
It's on its way.
It's on its way? Huh?
What's the hold-up then, huh?
Listen to me, Father.
Don't you want to be saved?
Everyone's out there waiting.
Miss Hong Jihyo.
Do you know who...
the scariest person in the world is?
It's someone who believes in you.
Yeah, well, I appreciate these,
uh... words of wisdom,
or whatever you're saying, but listen...
When am I getting my chip back?
I understand that you've had many
things to say since earlier, all right?
However, I'm gonna need it
if I'm going to bring you salvation.
Open it.
Go for it.
It's the reason you're here, isn't it?
You met her Holiness earlier, am I right?
Did she mention anything to you?
What in the world is she thinking?
Was she really resurrected?
She never even died, right?
- Why did she lie to the congregation?
- God, you're annoying, seriously.
Hey!
Listen, I'm-
well, confused about
what I should believe right now.
I mean, um, what's-
Which side is right?
Who am I supposed to trust?
You're close to her Holiness.
Did she tell you anything?
Look, kid. Look.
Whatever you believe
is none of my business.
So you can deal with your identity
crisis by yourself, not through me.
See, I'm busy enough as it is.
Yeesh.
Oh!
UFO...
The Blessed Light.
Where is it?
Where did you hide it?
Ugh, seriously. You think it's a joke?
Where the hell is the chip?
Come on, did you really think...
you were... the Messiah?
What?
Miss Hong.
From the start...
there was nothing in your head.
Absolutely nothing.
Um, uh... um... what?
Ho... hold on.
The chip is bullshit?
Hmm.
But you operated on me.
You even drilled a hole in my head.
That's true. We opened you up.
There was nothing there, though.
This is ridiculous.
What are you even saying right now?
What is that?
Look. Press this here.
- Right, just...
- Taking off.
What could it be?
- Maybe on forward.
- Try it.
We were not able to find any evidence
that you encountered any aliens.
Evidence?
Mean... meaning what?
Now listen, I recalled everything!
Look, I remembered everything
in hypnotherapy. I did.
Back in middle school,
in the field... There, I...
You received hypnotherapy...
after you met me, isn't that right?
Then, you see...
it's highly possible
that you may have made up those memories.
Let's be honest here.
Clearly, I had already planted these ideas
in your head when you went under hypnosis.
All of it, Jihyo, was in your imagination.
Ugh, I fucking knew it.
Hey. Look closely.
That's your god.
"The Light" is here
to bring you salvation.
It can't...
Then...
Then, um... What? Well, then, wait.
What about the hallucinations, then?
And explain how all my electronics
all started malfunctioning, huh?
Miss Hong. Do you hear that?
Do you have any idea...
how many people out there
have said the exact same thing as you?
No, no. I'm not... No.
Those... those things really happened.
Really, they did!
They say that too.
Well, at least...
they firmly believe that it's true.
Miss Hong.
If you really had actually
had some encounter with UFOs...
and were somehow chosen by them,
then you...
You'd be able to call them, right?
Wouldn't you?
So... can you?
Can you call them?
Can you, then?
Can you call those aliens, Hong Jihyo?
I don't know. How would I know that?
You're no Messiah.
I'm disappointed too.
I truly believed. I really believed
that you, you were the Messiah.
No. I... I wanted to believe!
It's been so long.
For so long, I've been
looking for that damn Messiah.
Huh?
Get her!
Oh, shit!
Oh, shit! Shit!
- Damn it!
- Hurry!
We have an intruder. I repeat, intruder.
That means it doesn't exist.
None of it exists.
Like the Messiah, or the aliens...
You're saying it's all nonsense, then?
It can't be nonsense!
If all it amounts to
is just total nonsense...
If, after all of this,
if I say all of it's nonsense,
those people out there,
what happens to their lives?
Do you realize...
how long those people have
been waiting for the Messiah?
So they could achieve
their damned ascension?
So they could receive fucking salvation?
Do you fucking realize how long
they've believed and followed me? Do you?
Do it for me.
Do it.
We need a savior.
Bring salvation to those poor people.
Do it wholly, like the prophecy!
Wh... wh... why should I?
I'm nothing, remember?
Fake it for them.
Act it out. Put on a show!
Even if it's fake.
Do it. So they have a shot at happiness.
So they can die happy, okay?
No.
I won't. No. I won't, I won't, I can't.
I can't lie like that.
- I'm not doing it.
- You already did!
You're even better than I am.
Didn't you kick your friend out?
Wasn't that you, huh?
I didn't. I... I can't.
No, I didn't...
Don't you get it yet? It was you.
You came here on your own, right?
- I...
- So now we're in the same boat.
Look, if we admit that...
that all of this was a big lie,
what do you think they'll do?
Do you really think
that all those believers
will just let you go after this?
Jihyo.
I'm not asking you to kill yourself
like the rest of them. Just...
I just need you to play your part.
Go out there!
Go be their savior.
I won't.
Well, then... survive this.
Survive all of this, and go back.
Back to... your life.
Stay away.
Oh...
An intruder?
Then we'll have to hurry.
The Messiah is ready.
Let's begin.
It's quieter than I expected.
Figured it'd be swingin'.
- If you know what I mean.
- Wow, clean it up. Seriously.
I don't think we'll be able
to get through that, guys.
There any other roads, or...
So, uh, Mr...
Mr. Kim...
Wha...
What the...
Wait, where is he going?
Hey, hey, hey! My car!
Hey, hey! Where's he...
Uh, my car...
Ah, shit. My bag's in there.
Wait...
Wow!
Why is it every time Moonhole goes
to buy smokes, something goes down?
- Uh, uh, Philip, move!
- Aah!
- Damn it...
- Jesus.
What's this?
- Those muscles just for show?
- Gah!
Ah, fuck. It wasn't locked!
Ah...
Oh, cool!
What the... What's that?
Wait a minute.
Isn't that Moonhole?
- Oh!
- Huh?
- Wow, what?
- Damn it!
Get her! Shit!
- Hey, damn it, you little bastards!
- Stop right there! Stop! Hey!
Hey, Cap...
Hey!
Cap, you all right?
Aah!
Cap is Captain Korea.
Um, what?
What the... What just... How are you...
Why are you guys...
For fuck's sake, quit smoking,
would you? Come on.
Hey, our timing was pretty awesome, right?
What the hell? What the hell's going on?
Uh... What's wrong?
- It was all a lie.
- Huh?
Direct Kim was right. It was all a show.
UFOs aren't coming down here.
One thing at a time.
Slow down, okay? Slow down.
Jihyo.
Everyone's gonna die! Hurry!
What's going on?
What is this?
What happened?
No.
Stop.
Don't. Pull yourself together, Hong Jihyo.
REACH ASCENSION AND UNITY!
THE MESSIAH'S MEMORIAL SERVICE
Something's wrong.
This isn't right.
What am I doing here?
What have I been doing until now?
Behold!
Today, we harvest the holy fruits
of our lonely faith!
The time has finally come!
The Blessed Light will
come down to this Earth!
- And those who don't believe...
- What were those people, after all?
They will be greeted by the Light!
And they will be judged!
- I was just being crazy.
- The Blessed Light will be their judge!
The end of our journey was only possible
because of our magnanimous Messiah!
Let us worship her!
Hong Jihyo.
I am... I'm their queen...
I'm the queen of crazy people!
ABANDON YOUR CARBON BODIES
AND REACH ASCENSION AND UNITY!
Shit, man,
we'll get a silver button for this!
Ugh, seriously, no, come on, Jihyo!
Hold on. Is that Miss Troll?
Right?
Behold!
Now the Blessed Light...
Watch, witness as the Messiah brings
down the Infinite Light down to us!
Everyone shall witness the Light,
even those lost,
- those poor souls without faith.
- What's this guy...
Right?
- The Light's will shall be so!
- This guy's fuckin' going for it.
Man, are you laughing right now?
Silver button!
This is weird. What's going on?
Everyone on this Earth
shall receive judgment
by the Light's divine power!
Its will shall be so!
- It shall be so!
- Sella!
Sella!
Oh, the Blessed Light!
- Sella!
Sella!
The light!
- Silver button!
- It's so freaking pretty.
- Oh, they're here! Aliens in Korea!
- They're not real, you idiot!
Hey! Get outta here!
- What?
- Go get the car!
The car?
Uh, Direct Kim...
- He stole it...
- It's Light!
- Brothers and Sisters...
Light!
It is now finally time,
finally the blessed time
to bid farewell
to our useless carbon bodies!
Sella! Sella!
Let us meet in paradise!
Sella!
- Sella!
- What are they doing?
- Are they really trying to die?
Mass suicide?
- Wha...
- Hey. This isn't good.
- Let's get to the car.
- But... but what car?
Wait for me!
Oh, no. Ah. No!
Don't, don't...
I gotta...
Wait. Wait, wait, stop, hold on!
Hold on!
No!
There's no savior!
It was all a lie!
There's no UFO here to save you!
If you take that, you're all going to die!
I can't give you salvation...
I'm... I'm nothing.
I'm so sorry...
I'm sorry.
Bora, I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry...
You have arrived
at your destination.
Route guidance has ended.
BLUELIGHT TRAINING CENTER
I think it's the place. Why
does it look like there's nothing here?
- I'll go.
- Okay.
It's unlocked, see that?
What? Messiah?
Why would you make up
such bizarre things to say?
You did it, your Holiness!
With your divine calling...
...you beckoned, you called,
you brought us the Light!
Come on!
Aaah! What the...
What was that?
Come on, come on, come on, come on!
FROM FLESH TO LIGHT!
THE MESSIAH'S MEMORIAL SERVICE
Blessed be the Light!
Abigail.
You believed in bullshit, see that?
That's salvation.
This is your holy salvation!
This way! Come on!
Honey? Honey!
Father. Father... Help us!
Bo... Bo... Bo... Bo... Bora!
Bora.
- Because of me, you had to...
- Oh, just zip it!
My hands are fucking shaking.
What's going on?
What happened?
Oh, shit. What the...
Bora.
I'm so sorry.
- UFOs... and aliens too...
- They don't exist, right?
I know. It's pretty obvious now.
We can look for them together again.
Isn't that right?
Uh-huh! Uh-huh...
- Oh!
- Damn it.
- Help us!
- I need to be...
We're all going to die!
No, I can't die! I can't die here!
Oh, shit!
You told me lies...
You tricked us. Why?
It's all her fault!
Get her!
- No!
- Grab her!
- Let's get her!
- Get her!
Hurry, Bora! Hurry up.
Grab her now!
Hurry!
It was all a lie...
Bora, go!
Aah! Why isn't this opening?
- Hurry, go now!
- Oh, shut it!
Ah, shit!
Oh! You got it, let's go!
- Filthy liar...
- Get her! Get her!
Why?
This is the police. Now nobody move.
Byungjo?
Police?
It doesn't matter now.
Kill them...
Kill them!
Stay back.
- Stay away!
- Freeze!
Don't move!
Everyone on the ground!
Get away.
Don't move.
- Stay away. Please, please don't!
- Oh, shit!
Hey, here, here!
Get the fuck down!
Get back! No! Don't!
Uh... what's that?
Is... is it a blackout?
Is war breaking out?
No. No. That.
Tayo!
Jihyo.
What... what happened just now?
Captain Price, did you see that?
What I saw...
it left.
You...
You too, right?
Yeah.
Me too.
Honey?
Honey!
Honey.
Honey?
Why did you do it?
Why did you have to go that far?
I really believed it all.
I really believed everything
about this, you know?
All of us did.
Why did you have
to lie to all of us?
Why did you deceive us?
Your only merit
was keeping your mouth shut.
You never questioned me.
Always liked that about you, you know?
If you're going to shoot,
make it quick.
Take this.
It has your mom's number in it.
Call her, okay?
Promise you won't skip meals, all right?
- Oh!
- Oh, oh!
- Petite Auntie!
Oh, oh, oh!
Hang in there a bit longer.
Where... where were you two?
Moonhole, Moonhole, are you okay?
What the... what the hell happened?
Tell you later. Okay?
Jihyo...
Are you all right? What on Earth happened?
Oh, hello.
What the...
Si... Siguk?
Jihyo...
What's with...
Um, what's with your clothes?
Uh...
Then...
I tried to explain what I saw
to everyone else, but...
but of course, no one believed me.
Even though they saw it
with their own eyes.
One person believed me, though...
Siguk...
I told him everything.
From beginning to end.
He sat there and listened,
but when I looked up at his face,
I just knew it.
"Well...
it's all over now."
"Time to head back home."
That was the first time I thought...
that I wanted to go home.
Must've been scary.
How do you seem so fine?
I'm not really fine.
Do I look fine?
Well, uh...
So, then... what happened after that?
How are things with Siguk? Is he
still saying at your place with you?
Siguk went back, to... to his old house.
- But why there of all places?
- Meaning?
Why go back there?
You wanted to get out
of that place, right?
Well, I'm just used to it.
And I'm broke.
Why don't you start fresh
in a whole new place, then?
Just, well...
all that awful stuff happened.
Good things happened there, too.
Right.
Jihyo.
Hm?
Let's break up.
Didn't we...
I mean, didn't I do that already?
Formally speaking, we didn't.
I didn't agree to it then.
I agree now, so let's break up.
What changed your mind, then?
I'm not strong enough...
to live with a crazy girl.
- Jeez.
- Hey, now!
You admitted it, come on.
- Hey!
- Ow!
Jeez! You bastard.
Thank you so much.
For what?
Thanks for not making me do it.
I should've said it myself.
Make sure you take care
of yourself, all right?
But, Dad!
I don't have enough money for the deposit.
I'm broke. How could I live there?
I know, that's why I'm paying for it!
You don't even have a job.
Hey, but if you pay for it,
it'll be your place, not mine.
- Just give in, would you?
- What?
I know you want independence.
See that?
Thank you, Mom.
Don't thank me.
Just help your father become
more independent from you.
if he wants to pay, just go along.
Do you really have to be
so mature about everything?
Wow, this looks nice. Here.
- It's very nice.
- Isn't it?
- But, Mom, that deposit's 20 grand!
- Empty nest syndrome.
That's the world of adults.
Hold on, but, "Mom?"
Is that what you call her these days?
Mmm. Mm-hm.
Well, it's been about 15
years since we became family, so...
Honestly, it became too tricky
to talk to her without calling her that.
So I got used to it.
Anyway, you said everything
was normal again.
Well, it doesn't look
like that is totally true.
Is that so?
Well... if you look at it like that,
I guess so.
This footage was taken
near Gyeonggi Province
where a gathering of the cult known
as the Divine Light Church was held.
MASS SUICIDE ATTEMPT
1,000 PEOPLE
GROUP HALLUCINATIONS
UFO WITNESSED
Strange pipes were spotted.
It seems the inhalation of toxic fumes
that were released caused hallucinations.
Some claimed that they saw an unidentified
flying object floating above the field.
It's believed the hallucinations
were caused by this poison.
JANG
I met Him. I met Him at last.
Who did you meet, though?
The Light. We met the Light.
We finally met the Light.
They all seemed insane,
honestly, you know?
Their eyes were rolled back,
everyone was running around crying.
This incident could have easily
ended as a tragic mass suicide case.
QUICK ARRESTS
CRIMINAL CHARGES ORDERED
But luckily, there were no innocent
victims and everyone was safely rescued.
The police have arrested
the leaders of this movement,
and have begun a thorough investigation
into the power outage that affected...
This was the exact moment, here.
Do you see this?
If it were a normal power outage,
this couldn't have happened.
In other words, the cause
of this blackout can only be seen
as a glitch caused by... alien interference.
As of right now, that's our assumption.
I shot this video.
Do you have any questions?
Yes! Minor Stocks Lover.
Uh... So when...
will you play the UFO video?
All right!
- I don't want to keep having to explain.
- This isn't free. You have to pay.
I mean, just think about it.
You can't take a video
when your phone's malfunctioning.
It was a glitch.
Sure. But you were just telling us
that you saw it.
- Why would we believe you?
- Man, seriously, don't keep bugging me!
Just come on! Do all things in this world
need an explanation?
- Okay, then tell us more...
- Hey, Petite, you're here!
- Hey.
- ...seeing a UFO in person.
But, so, why aren't aliens
trying to suppress humans?
Ah, now,
that's a very interesting question.
- We need daring questions.
- Who are these people?
- Newbies from our forum.
- Conditions of occurrence!
Phillip's gonna choose one of them
to become a mod.
Nice.
Instead, I'll have to explain things
like encounters of the first,
- second, third and fourth kind.
- Bora?
- The next video's ready.
- Upstairs.
- Let's watch the video first.
- Hmm.
- Donghyuk!
- Yeah!
We're still trying to figure
out the extent of the damage.
In related news,
Kim, who was arrested
for murdering Moon Hyungtae,
the leader of Divine Light Church,
responsible for the mass suicide attempt,
has officially been charged
with murder in the first degree.
During the police investigation,
Kim confessed that he harbored
ill feelings toward Moon
due to differences in religious values.
The police currently believe this may be
the motive behind his brutal actions.
Is that the person who met them?
Who met the alien?
STARS AND SPACE
There are many eyewitness
accounts of unidentified creatures.
In this episode, we will investigate one
of these creatures,
who has recently had many sightings,
the mighty Bigfoot.
This furry giant called Bigfoot...
- ...according to the country...
- Oh, hey.
What are you doing?
Researching for my next piece.
What d'you think?
Oh.
- Isn't that the...
- Bigfoot.
The video we are showing you...
I heard that was a fake.
Oh, well, the video's fake, sure.
But Bigfoot's real for sure.
Isn't that thing in the U.S.?
Are you gonna leave, then?
Well, we used to believe
UFOs were only there, too.
I guess that's true.
Now, Bigfoot is a mammalian creature...
Hong Kong, 1945.
A German archaeologist found evidence that
linked the legendary Bigfoot to the lake.
Research has found
even more evidence of their existence.
In view of climate change
and global warming at the lake,
scientists are working against time
to ensure it remains...
At the end...
'76 SEOUL UFO INCIDENT
GRAY REPRODUCTION
Hey. Do you ever watch baseball anymore?
You were such a fan in middle school.
That's what I thought too.
But after the Unicorns disbanded,
I stopped liking it.
I think, honestly...
that I wasn't into baseball, I just...
It's the team I liked, you know?
Mm-hm. Uh-huh.
- I see. Huh.
- What?
Huh?
Uh, it's pretty obvious you got
something to say, so go ahead.
- Um, do you like lofts at all?
- Um, what?
Wanna live together?
Wait, what?
That came outta nowhere.
Wait a minute. I, uh...
I made a list of some places for sale.
Do you wanna read it?
Do you maybe...
wanna read it?
Hey, Moonhole!
What?
Move your scooter
while I'm still being nice about it.
Ugh, seriously.
Stop parking there!
It's for the customers!
All right, all right,
I'm coming, jackass!
Hurry up!
So... any hallucinations these days?
Hallucinations?
The alien with the Unicorns hat.
That's why you came
here in the first place.
That's right.
I remember the Unicorns.
And what about...
anything about when you were hypnotized?
Yeah.
What? What did you see that day?
Was that a hallucination too?
Uh...
I saw some sturgeon.
Saw some sturgeon?
You see, I saw this documentary.
Well, my dad had it on one night.
In the documentary, there were these
scientists studying ecosystems and...
and they were also rescuing sturgeon.
'Cause people just toss nets
back in the ocean...
I mean, the sturgeon,
they get all stuck in those.
And the scientists fish them out and
untangle the sturgeon that get stuck,
- and save them.
- And?
And... before they're released,
the scientists insert this electronic tag
in their back, you see.
Then they're able to track
all of the sturgeon's movements.
Like a transmitter.
Those scientists,
it's almost like they were saying,
"Sure. Go be where you wanna be.
It's fine. Mm-hm."
"Do whatever you want.
Live freely, however you want."
I think they wanted to see and understand
how far these creatures could go...
after gaining their freedom.
So you mean the sturgeon?
I mean the sturgeon.
So, then... how far did that sturgeon go?