"It was 1976,
and 12 lights flashed and moved
extremely slow in the sky of Seoul."
"According to witnesses, it looked like
the lights were headed exactly to Namsan."
BACK YOONSUN'S ACCOUNT OF THE ATTEMPTED
SHOOT DOWN OF A UFO IN SEOUL
"After, many people who claimed to have
experienced mysterious events showed up,
leading to the suspicion
that they were UFO lights."
"One of those people was Ms. Back,
a college student,
who on her way home from her art class
was allegedly kidnapped by aliens."
"After the incident, she claimed
that aliens inserted a chip in her brain
and that she can communicate
with them using the chip on occasion."
And where is she now or what does she do?
"Nobody knows her whereabouts
or whether or not she is still alive."
Come on, Jihyo.
Why are you so obsessed with an event
that happened over 30 years ago?
- What would you do if you found a UFO?
- It's just... so frustrating for me.
Obviously, something's out there,
that's why these stories keep coming out.
I wish... I could witness it
with my very own eyes.
I'm really curious.
Now look! To be a witness.
It's what you want. A UFO formation.
Wow!
It looks exactly the same! It is amazing!
How did you come up with this idea?
- Bora.
- Yeah?
Do you think aliens really came to Korea?
And now breathe.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
All right, next position is Garudasana.
As you breathe in, lift your right leg
and cross it over the left.
Help me!
Oh, my God!
What?
No! No! Call the police now!
- Call them!
- Please come with me.
- Do something, please!
- Ow! Let go!
- Hey...
- Why is he here?
- What is he doing?
- Oh my God. Such a creep.
- What is he doing? He's still in shoes.
- Uh... uh...
- What is going on?
- Shoes!
Oh. Uh...
- What are you doing? Huh?
- You can't come in here.
- Get out! You can't come in here.
- Excuse me. Oh.
Excuse me. Ow!
Please, we have to leave!
You have to come out right now!
- Huh? Call the cops! Call the cops!
- Ju... just a sec. No!
- I swear I'm not a psychopath.
- Hm.
Uh, first of all, I'm sorry, but there's...
I apologize, there's been
a slight misunderstanding.
- I'll solve it soon.
- What is he talking about?
- I promise this won't take much longer.
- You're not fooling anyone!
That bastard right there is a weirdo!
A fanatic! He's a fanatic!
I promise you, I'm not.
- He's a psycho!
- All the psychopaths speak like that!
Hey, ladies! I bet you didn't know.
- On the next floor is a bizarre church!
- I don't believe in that church.
- What are they talking...
- Actually...
- What church?
- The floor upstairs?
- Right above us!
- I'm a Catholic man.
That's bullshit!
How were you baptized?
Thomas...
So, Thomas, why would you go
upstairs to that weirdo's church?
'Cause I'm trying to find my daughter.
And you came here to film me, didn't you?
I saw the title of your broadcast.
The content you create
is about me.
Then make a post.
What?
Open the Direct Kim blog right now
and then post something.
I'll believe you
if you verify your identity.
What? Forgot the password?
Come on, something like that?
BLOG - DIRECT KIM
POSTING
What kind of house is this?
Ugh... there's nothing in this place.
I thought there were gonna be pictures
and maps and things like that
spread out all over the walls.
Like some psycho detective or something.
- Please ask something.
- Huh?
You wanted to meet me, didn't you?
You have things to ask me, so ask now.
Oh. Uh...
Hm... Your...
Your wife and son. Where are they?
In New Zealand.
Oh! They live abroad...
You must be very busy.
You have to send them money
and live a religious life.
How long have you been doing
cosplay with a cultist turn?
Four years.
Have you found something useful
on your daughter's whereabouts?
- I haven't.
- Huh?
I haven't found anything useful.
I don't know where she is
or what happened.
Oh. So then...
what information have you discovered
about the cult in question?
- Did you discover their true identity?
- I don't understand what you mean by that.
They're a cultist church.
You should know that already.
You saw it yourself.
- Why do you ask me?
- You really think I don't know it?
What did you wanna meet me for?
What do you want to know, huh?
I'm not even fully awake,
and you're asking many questions.
So tell me...
How can a human being levitate?
What?
I saw this at the place my boyfriend
last visited before he disappeared.
But I don't think it's possible
for a human being to do that.
Mr. Direct Kim, I need you
to tell me if aliens really exist.
And if they do...
how are they connected to that church?
It's way too early for this.
How can you ask
such a ridiculous question?
SERGEANT KIM BYUNGJO
DEPARTMENT OF PUBLIC ORDER
"Department of Public Order"?
- Ow!
- The door's open.
Who are you?
Good evening, ma'am!
Kim Byungjo. I'm a detective.
Okay.
I'm not...
gonna cooperate.
Huh? Wh... why not?
Hey, ma'am!
Sorry...
Do you remember
Hope and Light Assisted Living?
It's a case that was yours
when you were an officer.
The mass suicide case.
Ugh. Ma'am,
I don't need much of your time.
I just want to ask you
a few simple questions about that case.
Hey!
I don't like talking to the police. Go.
Okay, but...
Where are you going to?
I'll give you a ride.
We can talk on the way, huh?
Wait... Just three minutes! Two minutes!
Just one minute! May I pay for the tax...
What the hell?
- Yes, Kim Byungjo spe...
- Kim Byungjo's phone, right?
- It's me, but who's...
- I was hoping we could meet and talk.
- Is lunchtime good for you?
- Wait.
- Can you tell me who's calling, please?
- You know Jihyo, right? Hong Jihyo.
Huh?
The Newbeginnings Peace Corps?
Yeah, NPC is the abbreviation.
- NPC?
- NPC.
And who are those guys?
A group of young volunteers
from Divine Light Church.
My plan is to join that group.
Why would you wanna do that?
To find my daughter.
But I don't understand
What does finding your daughter have
to do with the NPC thing or whatever?
I'm gonna need much more.
Explain the connection.
I think...
they kidnapped my daughter or something.
Come again?
Kidnapped girl... by the NPC?
Why?
- Is there any evidence of this?
- Of course not.
- Why do you think such thing?
- Because I do.
I believe you have a shitty plan, sir.
Ugh! Upsetting little man!
Shit, man!
You're more frustrating than Jihyo!
I mean...
No, please. You're better at this.
You've gotta be eloquent.
Now just explain this more clearly!
Explain to me exactly,
what did these people do?
Why are these guys your suspects?
- Huh? Did they really kidnap some...
- Honestly, I have no idea either!
That's why I'm stuck like this now!
As for their activities,
even within that church,
they keep it secret.
There's no way to
track out their activities.
The only way is getting accepted
as a member of their group.
And at the moment,
the NPC is suspicious.
And that's all.
Is that really all? Huh?
So, sir... what did you do
during those four years?
Do I really need to remind you that your
daughter's life is probably on the line?
Shouldn't you capture that woman selling
houses and do something terrible to her?
Stop saying things like that.
You just don't know the whole story.
If four years passed, she's already...
She's already what?
You think she's dead?
Now, listen...
She's my daughter
Mark my words, we can't trust that man.
But I can't know for sure
which part of his story's a lie.
Always the ones who look really innocent
are actually insidious on the inside.
Hey.
- Huh?
- Your boyfriend isn't dead.
It was just a minor slip of the tongue.
He's not dead and I know that for sure.
Thank you.
But that's not really
why I'm acting like this.
Then why?
Bora...
I think that now I've lost my mind.
You're starting to freak me out.
What's up?
Yeah, I think that you are crazy!
I know, that's what I'm saying. I don't
know what I was thinking, or why I did it.
Hey!
- Stay right there, damn it!
- Hurry!
- Come!
- Stop!
Quickly!
- Hey!
- Go!
Hey! No!
- Please!
- We'll bring it back!
When this is all over!
I'm really sorry, sir.
Whoo!
Oh my God!
- Hey, bitch! You're seriously crazy!
- Whoo!
Is this Direct Kim's
external hard drive?
I think that he collected...
every photo the cult members posted
on the chats and social media.
- Why?
- Man, I have no fucking idea.
He thought these could be evidence.
No wonder he hasn't found
his daughter, doing stuff like this.
Let's open the next folder...
Sister Hwajung's chat.
Pork belly?
I'm really sorry.
I promise next time I'll be there, hm?
And what are you doing instead
of coming to our sessions?
I'm dealing
with something important, okay?
Yeah, but what are you doing
that's more important than this?
I'll tell you next time we meet.
Hyungwoo, remember...
- You said you could do that thing?
- What?
- Hypnosis therapy.
- Hypnosis?
You said... you went to some seminar
or something when you were in college.
I went to flirt with girls.
Why are you interested in that?
So can it...
bring back my forgotten memories?
And stuff like that. You get the idea.
Jihyo, what are you doing?
Are you still on the phone?
Yeah! It'll be just a sec.
- Hyungwoo...
- It's your turn to do this.
- I'll get back to you later.
- I'm feeling my brain cells die.
Hong Jihyo.
She says whatever and then hangs up.
And so? Found something?
I found that the real estate lady
really enjoys eating.
Cap, I need a refill.
Hey.
I still can't believe any of this.
To think that church guy was
actually Direct Kim all along...
I know...
I think it'd be better if it wasn't.
- Why?
- Ugh.
You said you've been
looking for him for years.
You should be enjoying this.
It's just that I can't believe all I found
was such a frustrating little guy.
- Ugh.
- Whatever.
Oh, fuck, I have a headache.
Damn it.
Huh?
What is it?
What is this?
That's the place.
The place?
Wait. Wait.
Wait a minute.
It's here.
You sure?
Totally.
- It's there.
- Aren't you confused?
I'm not confused!
I'm not confused at all.
I'd never be.
Direct Kim, motherfucker.
I knew there was something fishy
about that real estate lady.
Come on, come on.
The top of my head is so hot.
If you raise me up this high,
I'm too close to these hot lights.
I feel like an ant
under a magnifying glass.
- Gosh!
- Oh... Should I lower you, then?
Lower me down a bit.
Okay.
DOWN
There we go. Yes.
More. More.
Great. More.
Stop!
- What a relief. This is much better.
- I'll lift you to this comfortable height.
And don't relax your back.
All right.
Ooooh, that's good, that's good.
Oh. There you go.
Safe landing.
Great work.
- There. Oh, you did so good.
- Ugh, my back is killing me.
Oh, my back hurts. Oh!
I'm sorry that, uh... I put you through
so much trouble each time.
Hey! No problem.
It's the least I can do, huh?
To receive grace.
COME IN
- Go!
- For real?
Please don't tell me
that you're hesitating now.
And what if we really get caught?
She's at the church service right now.
We need to do it quickly.
What if she forgot something
and comes back?
Oh shit! Are you doing it or not?
We need to know who made that drawing.
Okay, okay, okay.
Please...
UNDER CONSTRUCTION DO NOT ENTER
Oh! God...
Chanwoo, are you busy today?
Not at all.
Well, then, would it be possible
for you to pick up Brother Han? Okay?
Yes, I'll do it. Do you have other plans?
Well, I have something important
that I need to attend to.
- Oh!
- I'll leave it to you, then.
Okay.
Damn it, why isn't this working?
Bora! Do you know how to use it?
- I just saw a tutorial online.
- Don't make me nervous.
You better hurry up, Bora.
Ah, shit! Why doesn't it inflate?
- Please, please.
- Don't rush me.
What?
Damn it.
Ugh! Give it to me. Let me do it!
Damn it!
Oh, oh! Oh-oh!
Oh! Hey, hey! Hey!
It's actually working. Oh!
Yeah! That's it! Just a little more.
Oh, oh, oh!
Hey! Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
Oh, you're doing great! It's working,
it's working, it's working, it's working.
Oh, oh!
Oh! It worked! It worked!
It worked, it worked!
- Oh, God!
- That's it, get in!
Oh!
It worked!
Get in! Get in!
Ah, shit.
Hey.
Why is this so difficult?
- How do I turn it on?
- Huh? What was that?
Try to turn the GPS on.
What are all these switches for?
I don't know how to turn it on.
What? Don't you have a license?
Yeah, but I don't use it.
Oh! God damn it!
HOW TO TURN ON A GPS
This is why we have internet.
Oh shit, this is not happening.
It looks like you have
to start the car to see the GPS.
- But how do I...
- Start the car.
How do I do it?
No...
- Hey, Chanwoo.
- Yeah?
- If you join the NPC, you must do better.
- Hide. Come on. We have to hide, please!
- What...
- I usually don't share all this.
- But you're such a great prospect.
- What do we do now?
- What I have been sharing is a secret...
- The back seat!
Okay.
- Go on. Go to the back. Hide! Hide!
- Of course, I feel honored.
Uh, you're erasing all the stuff
I've shared with you in the chat,
isn't that right?
Ouch!
- From the group chat?
- Oh, yeah.
Of course. Of course,
I'm erasing it all immediately.
That's right.
- With your silence...
- Is the pillar of faith!
Exactly. Good.
Good, very good.
- Ah, shit...
- I'll get going.
Oh, wait! Listen, Sister Seo!
Uh... Mmph...
Uh...
Could you just...
Uh... I mean, you...
You haven't been looking so great lately.
And frankly...
I feel that you're, uh... you've been, uh...
Working in excess.
I am... worried about you.
What can I do?
Chanwoo, you're such a sweet man.
- Oh my!
- Thanks. Thanks.
- You pretend to be so indifferent.
- Uh...
But you're quite considerate. Thank you!
What?
So, what's the word for people like that?
- You remember the slang?
- Uh...
- That word the kids use nowadays, hmm?
- No, uh...
BROTHER HAN
Is that Brother Han?
Uh, answer it, please.
- Go ahead, Brother.
- Oh, yeah.
- You gotta get going.
- Okay.
- See you later. Thank you!
- Yeah.
Hello, Brother Han.
And there's that. Now you get it?
It's just that...
How long has it been
since you started dating?
I'm not dating Ms. Hong.
You say that you're not dating, then...
Are you fucking her?
Sehee, I'm not having sex with her.
There's nothing going on between us yet...
Not yet?
So then you're planning to?
Uh... I'm not planning anything, okay?
Actually, it's just that...
we're keeping contact with each other.
Oh, okay. And what is it
that you guys even talk about?
Listen, hm?
How deeply in love can you possibly be
that your relationship
keeps Jihyo from going home?
Ms. Hong doesn't go home? Are you sure?
Yeah. She doesn't even
come to work often these days.
Her dad was so worried about her
that he even decided to call me.
What?
Well, haven't the two of you
been living together?
Uh...
What?
What is it? Huh?
♪ I want to see the Light's face ♪
♪ I want to praise you forever ♪
♪ We shall leave together ♪
♪ And follow the... ♪
DEACON KIM CHANWOO
Hello?
Yeah, hello, Sister Seo.
This is Kim Chanwoo.
Oh! Chanwoo.
You're supposed to drop off Brother Han.
Yeah. And by the way, Sister,
what are you doing right now?
Uh, I'm driving the car.
Why do you ask?
- Uh, I wanted to ask, Sister Seo...
- Yeah?
Has anything unusual happened?
Like what?
- Why would there be anything unusual?
- What do we do?
- Ah, you're right.
- I'm just driving right now.
What are you talking about?
- No, it's just that...
- What's with you today? Are you okay?
- Right.
- Oh my God. I need to turn left here.
- Chanwoo, right now I'm driving the car.
- Okay.
I'll talk with you back at church.
- All right.
- I'm hanging up.
DAD
- Yes, goodbye.
- I just can't with him.
♪ Mm, mm, Light ♪
♪ Light ♪
♪ I want to see the Light's face ♪
♪ I want to praise you forever... ♪
♪ We shall leave together ♪
♪ And follow ♪
♪ The ♪
♪ Light ♪
Jihyo. Hey, Jihyo.
Hey,
how can you draw stuff like that?
Let me see. Hey! Come here.
Jihyo, where are you?
Come back. Don't leave me.
Let's be friends forever. Hey, Jihyo!
Hey, Jihyo! Quick, get up now.
Hey! You need to wake up now!
Jihyo.
Please wake up now!
Hey, hey, Jihyo.
- Huh?
- Huh? Uh...
I don't understand how you can fall
asleep in this situation.
Please stay awake.
The woman just got out of the car.
Huh? Huh?
ALLOW "MAPS" TO ACCESS YOUR LOCATION?
Oh, damn it.
Where are we?
I can't call a taxi from here.
Let's try going in there.
Have you lost your mind?
The woman said she'd
return to the church later.
Let's wait until then
and break in to investigate.
Why would we go in there?
Huh? It's a house, nothing more.
The house she lives in.
I'm not so sure.
Think about it.
The lady's job is in Seoul,
her church is here,
her license plates are from there.
So why would she...
live so far in this house?
Especially when she's a real estate woman.
Isn't that weird?
THE MARCH OF BLESSING
Sister, it's Chanwoo.
Are you all right?
Jeez!
Whoa, what's that?
Oh. Oh!
Oh, oh, oh!
He's so unbelievable.
- Hey...
- Oh...
Hey... Here.
You. Surveillance.
What?
- What are you doing? Stay here.
- Hey!
- Hey, no!
Damn it!
No, Bora!
Hey, Bora!
Hey!
Hey... Hey!
Mother!
Hey, Ma!
It's time to eat!
I made doenjang jjigae for you!
Mother! Hey, Ma!
Hi, Ma!
I made food.
Do you wanna watch TV?
Yeah? All right.
There you go.
Okay.
Careful, careful, careful.
Okay. There...
- Whoa!
- Nice.
- Wow, Kinder, you're amazing!
- Whoopee!
It's good that we listened to Tayo!
Mom. Say, "ah."
Ugh, isn't it too dangerous?
"Aah..."
It's always you doing it alone.
Mother, I'll peel an apple for you.
So eat that.
I'm going to the church.
I'll see you tomorrow.
You'll be okay at home alone.
I'll be back soon, all right?
Okay.
Careful, careful.
Aaah!
A goddamn cult?
No, are you saying that.. Lee Siguk
is now part of a weird, secret cult?
No!
You can't say anything for sure just yet.
We can't tell Ms. Hong, okay?
She might feel upset, and that's exactly
why I was keeping my mouth shut.
It makes sense, actually...
If it's him who we talk about,
I think it's possible
he got into stuff like that.
So, then... Hmm.
You're investigating this whole situation.
It's not even an investigation.
It's something I looked into
in my spare time, and that's all.
And so? How are you investigating?
I mean, you go out and interview people,
pop some questions?
Sure, for now, I have to get out there,
'cause the computer alone
won't get me anywhere.
All right.
I'll help you.
- With what?
- You said you're doing it alone. right?
And who's gonna help you?
I think two heads are better than one.
Like a dual-core.
No thanks.
Whoopee!
It's good that we listened to Tayo!
Hey, hey, hey.
Pyew, pyew, pyew, pyew, pyew, pyew!
Hah!
This is so fun!
What should we do after the exams?
I'm not sure!
Hey! Don't do that.
Hey!
- Leave her.
- Okay!
Her mind's left the planet.
All right. Let's do this!
- What?
- What do you mean, what?
- Let's start the search.
- Search for what in this house?
I've no idea!
Look for your boyfriend's fingers
or something.
Don't run so fast! It's dangerous!
Oh, no. I'm sorry.
I didn't know.
Thank you, Tayo.
You shouldn't hesitate to give
stern advice, even to your friends.
All right, I'll remember that.
The school classes are over.
What was that sound?
Don't come near me!
- Stop right there!
- No!
You shouldn't hesitate to give
stern advice, even to your friends.
There you go.
Heart doesn't like it!
Be careful.
What did I do wrong?
I can't believe I yelled at a friend.
Tayo.
Huh?
Tayo the Little Bus!
Oh!
Right.
Yes, that's Tayo.
Tayo.
Jihyo, what are you doing?
- Don't waste time on her.
- Tayo.
Come take a look at this.
Tayo.
Tayo... Tayo... Tayo... Tayo...
And now I'm convinced
getting old is terrible.
The aging process is inevitable.
- Yeah...
- Damn.
Why do all of these photos
have the exact same background?
They were taken at the same place.
BAEK-IL NATIONAL WELFARE CENTER
Wait a minute.
This is quite a familiar face.
Hmm?
Oh shit.
So freaky.
Bora, I think I'll...
...search
another part of the house.
Yeah.
Bora! Come here right now!
What the hell does this mean?
- Oh! Hey! Hey! Quickly, hide!
- Shh!
Who's that?
Huh?
- Oh shit...
- Wh...
Return it!
Give it to me!
Gimme a break! The NPC?
That was all nonsense, right?
You just made it all up.
But why would you tell us
such an idiotic lie?
Look! Look! Right away, you got busted!
I did it because I knew you would
go around causing trouble, okay?
Do you know how much
of a pest you are? Huh?
I had, like, a dozen heart attacks
and several strokes today.
Are the drawings locations
where UFOs appeared?
We already came this far, so just tell
us everything you know at the moment.
- What did we see back there?
- Mh-hm. Yeah, we want to know.
- Who drew all those pictures?
- And what is this church really?
And the thing with the aliens?
How are they related?
Uh-huh. Yeah. Did that real estate woman
draw those pictures?
Don't play coy, little man!
We already saw
all the content on this hard drive!
Okay, okay. Just don't yell at me.
Just please be quiet, I'm begging you.
It was the Holy Mother.
Huh?
The Mother. The church's Holy Mother.
You mean like the Virgin Mary?
Okay, and who's that?
What do you mean by that?
You must have seen her inside.
Inside?
Huh?
Did you see her?
The crazy old lady?
But how could that lady be the...
How could she know
that my boyfriend disappeared and...
and paint the exact location, huh?
Huh? Can you please stop
being so mysterious about this?
Just give me a logical answer?
Please?
Are you listening?
Answer me!
Oh, shit. Oh!
Huh?
Now I know where I've seen her before.
What?
You have also seen her before.
Huh?
Back Yoonsun.
What? The Back Yoonsun?
Yeah, the Back Yoonsun
from the UFO Incident.
What's the UFO Incident?
The attempted shoot-down
of the UFO.
In 1978, in the sky of Seoul,
several UFOs appeared in a formation.
Back Yoonsun is the woman who claimed
that she met aliens that day.
Something like that occurred in Korea?
This lady... She claimed at the time that
she could actually contact the aliens.
She said that they planted
some sort of chip inside of her head.
Wow!
Jihyo.
Don't you remember that?
You were totally obsessed
with this in middle school.
And so what happened to this Back woman,
or whatever her name is?
She disappeared after the interview.
A bunch of rumors arose
when that occurred.
Some people said that an institute
kidnapped her to do research in secret.
Yeah, yeah. Come on!
So you're saying that both of you found
Direct Kim and Back Yoonsun, seriously?
The first person to encounter aliens?
But how could she become
the Holy Mother of a cult?
Exactly. Where has she been
all these years, anyway?
I believe she was here.
Look at the date. All of these pictures
were taken after the newspaper interview.
Baek-Il
National Welfare Center.
What kind of place is that?
I have no idea.
It says "National."
it must be a public facility.
BAEK-IL NATIONAL WELFARE CENTER
It's a private psychiatric hospital now.
It's called New Hope.
NEW HOPE PSYCHIATRIC HOSPITAL
HOSPITAL HISTORY
They changed it. It was
Hope and Light Assisted Living Facility.
Where is it?
Uhhh...
Here.
Jeonju. It's only four hours away.
Captain.
Hm?
Take us there.
- Huh?
- You're going now?
- Captain.
No, no, no, I can't, nah. I'll lose muscle
if I don't sleep well. I can't.
- I mean...
- I can give you a meal full of protein.
- Yes!
- Come on, dude!
A nice road trip! I'll go pack.
A nice read trip, you say?
You guys are...
How are you in sync all of a sudden?
Hey, Moonhole.
Why in the world are you doing this,
and why travel there right now?
Would you prefer I went on Christmas?
If you're curious, you... you can go back
to that lady and ask her about all the...
What would I ask an old
lady who's lost her mind?
Then...
perhaps you can ask Direct Kim.
Ugh, forget that man!
I'd rather go ask a sweet potato.
- I... can't stand those places!
- Then don't go, man!
Hey, Jihyo. We're leaving now.
I'm going home. I'll be right back, soon.
See you in an hour.
If you're late, we leave you behind.
- Okay!
God damn it!
None of this is even confirmed.
You don't even know what's there.
- Give me a reason for this!
- Ugh, stop looking for a reason!
Not everything in this giant
world happens for a fucking reason.
MATH 1ST SEMESTER SAMPLE QUESTIONS
HONG JIHYO
THE ATTEMPTED SHOOT DOWN
OF A UFO IN SEOUL
The calm before the storm.
Those laughing at me in the comments
and laughing at me even now,
I never responded to any of them.
But tonight, finally,
I'll be stepping into
the very heart of a mystery.
Are you all the morons?
Or am I the moron here?
Only history will judge that!
Hmm? Hmm?
Are the others... not here yet?
They're never punctual,
you should know that.
- And Captain, where is he?
- He's lifting weights.
At this hour?
He said he wanted to do it now
in case he can't tomorrow.
- 26.27.
- Ah. Bora, here.
Oh.
Oh. Oh!
Whoa!
Hey. Behold.
My work of art.
- Huh?
- Hey.
You are an airhead, you don't remember it.
Oh, amazing!
Even the notes are still here.
Ah, I had no idea highlighters
lasted for this long.
Bora.
I can see aliens.
It started when we were in high school.
I just see them sometimes.
I'm just minding my own business,
and then I see one.
And he's just staring back, I guess.
What are you talking about?
What kind of aliens do you mean?
Mmm...
Well, you know the one we...
the one that we drew together
in middle school?
This here?
Mm-hm.
But it's changed,
'cause I don't see him so often now.
Since when?
I'm not sure.
Since... I became friends with you.
It's incredible.
Why did you always
listen to my bullshit as if it was true?
Was it the reason you left a message
on my blog? That one in particular?
It was that and...
Siguk played a part as well.
But I don't understand
why I'm here,
telling you all about my hallucinations.
I've only ever told my therapist.
The phrase "screen image,"
do you remember that?
Um... If you witness a shocking situation,
something so shocking
that it's completely unbelievable,
the human mind covers up that image
with a different image,
something more... digestible for you.
For example, a drawing like this.
Something so shocking
that it's completely unbelievable.
Like what, exactly?
Well... For example...
an encounter with a real alien.
A real alien?
What if, you know...
I didn't hallucinate?
What if something like
aliens exists in real life, Bora?
What if I'm able to see that?
That makes me a what?
What do you mean? You'd still be an idiot.
120.
121.
122.
Hi, Ma!
Are you already awake?
Gosh!
Did you fall asleep here
watching the television again?
I had already told you
to sleep in your room!
I can't believe you, Mom!
Oh!
Hello, Father.
She's finally shown herself.
She has... revealed...
The Messiah arrived!
She's here at last.
The Messiah!
The Messiah...
She's finally come!