♪The wind stopped
at the familiar face yesterday♪
♪The tenderness you gave♪
♪How to hide it♪
♪The crowd frequently separated us♪
♪Watching the story end♪
♪Then we met again outside the ending♪
♪The end is♪
♪My best expectation♪
=Shameless Lover=
=Episode 18=
How could it not be?
Under the guise of justice,
seizing what one desires.
In my opinion,
your unscrupulous methods
are hardly more noble than ours.
Killing me would be futile.
We have already won.
You will never get the Ice Jade Bowl.
Ice Jade Bowl.
It's finally my turn, isn't it?
This time,
you still want to kill me?
Last time?
Kill you?
You remember?
Yes.
I remember it all.
But I remembered
too late.
This time,
I won't let you succeed.
Hold on,
(Dear.)
(Whether it's my life)
(or my chastity,)
(they're both yours.)
Shen Zhili
is my, Su Chenche's,
only love of life.
If I tell you Su Chenche
is faking amnesia,
would you still send me away?
Why are you still holding me?
I'm not hurt.
Because
I don't want to be apart from you again.
Even until mountains are edgeless
and rivers run dry,
I will not
leave you.
(Master, Senior,)
(I'm sorry.)
(I still couldn't do it.)
(Su Chenche,)
(if there's another chance,)
(I will definitely)
(make your life worse than death.)
(Three months ago.)
Greetings, Lord.
(So, if I die, time resets too.)
Starting from
the first time he killed me,
for some unknown reason
we fell into a cycle of time resets.
Either of us, whoever dies,
will initiate a time reset.
Last time,
I suffered a severe blow to the head.
After the time reset,
I lost my previous memories.
Therefore, he took the initiative.
(Twelfth Night Splendor seeds)
His purpose in approaching you
is to get the three core ingredients
to revive his mother.
Deceived me,
fooled me,
killed me,
and even killed my innocent senior.
If I stood in his way,
he will surely kill me again.
Su Chenche,
this time,
I come with memory.
I won't let you
succeed.
Lord.
I need you to do something.
Yes.
Young master,
are we really going to Huichun Valley?
If this is exposed...
(From the first cycle,)
(she does not remember before death.)
(Then this time,)
(perhaps she also doesn't remember.)
What are you doing?
Young master,
those unharmed and without an invitation
cannot enter Huichun Valley.
I'm helping you.
Let's take a look first.
Yes.
(This is a trap.)
(I didn't see it last time.)
(Why would it be this way this time?)
(Not seeing me.)
(What exactly is she planning?)
(I can only try it out.)
Young master.
Be careful.
Su Chenche,
how does it feel
to be shot through the heart?
Did you feel the pain I felt then?
Young master!
(Half an hour ago)
That trap was deadly.
What on earth does she mean?
Trap?
Young master,
what are you talking about?
And who is she?
I must find out.
Zhili.
You killed my senior,
fooled me,
and kept me from
bringing back my master.
Su Chenche,
even dying ten thousand times
isn't enough for you!
(Half an hour ago)
Qing Xing,
dig a tunnel leading
to the inside of Huichun Valley.
Yes.
Lord,
Twelfth Night Young Master
entered that room.
It's about time.
Go and see how he died.
Yes.
Dear.
(Fortunately, I prepared)
(this sharp dagger)
I finally found you!
Why?
Because you spoke out of line,
recklessly calling me "Dear".
You truly don't remember.
I am Su Chenche.
You are my wife.
Young Master Su,
you might not know
the rules of Huichun Valley.
Without invitation or agreement,
those who broke in
will all die.
So,
you want to do it yourself this time?
I don't know what you are talking about.
But my doing this
is to help you.
(Serious injuries,
paralyzed on one side,)
(that's when I have an opportunity.)
Stabbing twice,
avoiding the vital points.
Do you hate me?
(Su Chenche, how can I not hate you?)
(You claim to control everything.)
(Yet you're unaware I have the memories
from the last cycle.)
(You try to repeat the same old tricks.)
(This time, I will not let you win.)
Young Master Su, you're overthinking it.
We met only for the first time.
Where is the love and hate from?
But if you want to see me,
you must have a fatal wound.
(Now, we can have a proper talk.)
(Crow Silver Needle)
(will surely paralyze half of you.)
(In such case, you'll have to spend
the rest of your life lying here.)
(And I)
(can then obtain
the three core ingredients)
(to revive Master.)
You were badly injured.
How did you...
I've been pondering a question.
Even if you don't remember your death,
don't you even remember
the feelings between us?
Let go of me.
Or I'll make your death suffering.
In your hands,
I've already lost count
of how many times I've died.
I just want to understand one thing.
Why are you acting so out of character?
(After doing so many treacherous deeds,)
(you still have the audacity to ask.)
(It's time to attend to the business.)
(Unable to move.)
(It has come to this.)
It's not good.
Young Master Su committed suicide
by biting his tongue!
This is bad.
(Can't let him off so easily.)
(One day ago.)
(Zhili,)
(this time,)
(don't blame me for using the hard way.)
Answer the question I asked last time,
or we'll repeat the loop forever.
(This time,)
(Senior should show up.)
(I'll take the risk.)
What are you going to do?
You're bullying me!
I am not!
Who's bullying Zhili?
Long time no see.
You've become even more foolish,
to actually be entangled by a patient.
Senior.
Great.
You have returned.
(That time, it must be very painful.)
(It's all my fault.)
Zhili, what is this?
You know that he once died.
That's why you're reacting this way now.
You did that just now because
you knew Hua Jiuye's getting here.
So,
you haven't forgotten.
You are pretending.
Why is this?
Senior, he bullied me.
Even cursed you to die.
He must think we're weak.
You want to die?
Senior!
(Su Chenche,)
(last time, you killed my senior,)
(and this time, you should pay for it.)
Senior, spare his life.
Fortunately, not dead.
(Must resolve this trouble quickly.)
Senior,
I want to borrow your poison.
You, a physician,
want do you want my poison?
He's no ordinary man.
I need a special way
to make him suffer unbearably pain,
the kind that leaves him bedridden.
How so, is he your enemy?
Keep a good watch on Young Master Su.
Yes.
Gnawing at the heart, eroding the bones,
draining the blood,
yet hanging on by a breath.
Zhili,
we haven't seen each other for years.
You've become more and more ruthless.
I like it.
Next,
it's time for our business.
♪If we separate♪
♪Just one step away
from the world of mortals♪
♪Close the mottled door of memory♪
♪Seal up the thoughts♪
♪If you don't ask♪
♪Is there still a good time
in the future♪
♪Every step you take brings more warmth♪
♪Let love take root♪
♪Even if♪
♪Piecing together the broken stars♪
♪Also wish♪
♪Shining for you♪
♪I'm willing to become♪
♪The flowers falling all over the sky♪
♪I will also remember♪
♪Let love freeze at disillusionment♪
♪Even after♪
♪The ruthless fate at the end of time♪
♪Will still be engraved♪
♪You hand in mine♪