♪The wind stopped
at the familiar face yesterday♪
♪The tenderness you gave♪
♪How to hide it♪
♪The crowd frequently separated us♪
♪Watching the story end♪
♪Then we met again outside the ending♪
♪The end is♪
♪My best expectation♪
=Shameless Lover=
=Episode 32=
So I want to become a good healer
to cure patients,
to protect you even more.
But I've only just now realized
that all of this
is fake.
Our past together was not fake.
You can always call me Master.
Master,
I thought
we could go on like this forever,
spend a lifetime in Huichun Valley,
healing the sick, saving lives,
relying on each other.
Wasn't that good enough for us?
Why must you be so obsessed
with Twelfth Night Splendor?
Why be so cruel to me?
Why?
I can't let go of Jiyue.
I can't let go for my entire life.
You have to understand me.
Understand you?
Understand
that you treat me like a pawn?
You've deceived me time and again,
used me,
even harmed the people
most important to me,
turning all my dependence
and trust in you
into a sharp blade,
raising it without hesitation
when you need it,
toward everyone,
and then discard it
without a trace of guilt?
Is that so?
Even if it is, so what?
I raised you up.
Whatever I tell you to do,
you have to do it.
I will not let you have your way.
You really have grown up,
daring to defy me.
Aren't you afraid I'll kill Su Chenche
and let you experience
losing a loved one?
You're so persistent about this,
but don't know that
Twelfth Night Splendor has two seeds.
With this one only,
you can't do anything.
If you really kill Su Chenche,
you'll never be able to bring back
Shen Jiyue.
Zhili?
(Memorial Tablet of Mother Shen Jiyue)
Mother
Shen Jiyue.
Chenche.
Mother?
Never expected my son
to have grown so much.
You're finally here.
Are you here to save me?
You will me, right?
You must save me.
Chenche, please save me.
Chenche!
(Mother,)
(wait for me.)
(Chenche, come here.)
(Come to Mother.)
Su Chenche, don't!
You smelled the Soul-bewitching Incense
and entered into an illusion.
Zhili,
I just saw my mother.
I really saw my mother just now.
Let's go and save her, Zhili.
Even if you don't consider
our relationship as Master and disciple,
for his sake,
you must revive Shen Jiyue.
Right,
Zhili?
Okay.
I promise you.
Su Chenche.
You!
I always
make sure I succeed.
Let's go.
Be careful.
(This cave is like the illusion
just now.)
Mother.
Mother!
Get things done now.
Drive the Gold Osmanthus Toad
out of your body.
What if I tell you
the Twelfth Night Splendor
cannot revive her?
What tricks are you playing now?
Two drops of blood, Twin flowers.
Yin and Yang seeds,
transform into Yin and Yang.
Yin and Yang are ready,
the material transforms.
Thus, life begins.
Yin and Yang move
from beginning to end.
This is a secret phrase
of the Imperial Yuanjiang family.
What does it mean?
The world believes
Twelfth Night Splendor
can bring back the dead,
but in reality,
it merely traps people in a time loop.
It's a curse.
All people are fools.
I only trust myself.
Twelfth Night Splendor can save people.
It does not just save people,
but also enhances my power.
In due time,
I will travel the world with Jiyue,
make her the supreme woman of the world.
The Supreme of the World?
Everything you do
is for your own sake.
I thought all you did
was for nothing more than love,
unexpectedly,
you are so selfish and self-serving.
Killing two birds with one stone,
why not?
I've been planning for over a decade,
raising you as a blood bag,
having you collect core ingredients.
All for today.
Cut the talk, give me
the Gold Osmanthus Toad.
Otherwise,
I will kill him right now.
Why has it come to this?
I have long said
that when I do things,
I tend to make sure.
It's these flowers.
My good disciple,
you are one move short in the game.
But I am very grateful to you.
The Yuanjiang secret phrase
you just mentioned
finally clears up my confusion.
So resurrection and the growth of power
require two seeds.
Yin and Yang constitution.
Yin and Yang seeds.
Interesting.
You should stop being so obstinate.
Twelfth Night Splendor
it's not at all what you think.
♪The gentleness♪
♪As turbulent as the dark night♪
♪Turns into your deep love♪
♪And turns into nothing♪
♪Soft curse♪
♪Around the boundless sky♪
Right.
That's right.
Just like that.
Why has it stopped?
Why did it stop?
The blood has dried.
Then cut it open and
let it continue to flow!
♪Soft curse♪
♪Around the boundless sky♪
Shen Tianxing is meticulous
and highly suspicious.
He will definitely try to separate us.
If so,
let's just play along.
You and Senior go deal with the others.
I'll meet him.
No way.
That's too dangerous.
Have you forgotten
he killed you previously?
Indeed.
If he kills me again,
we'll have to go through
another time reset.
Time can be reset.
Yin and Yang can be interchanged.
There is Yang within Yin,
Yin within Yang.
Does that mean
the beginning is the end,
the end is the beginning?
We now know
you have the supreme Yang blood,
and I have the supreme Yin blood.
Drop the supreme Yang blood
and supreme Yin blood respectively on
the Yang seed and the Yin seed
of Twelfth Night Splendor,
only then was the time reset initiated.
So,
we just need to drip our blood
onto the seeds again
to close the time reset.
No.
We need to swap the two seeds.
Drip the supreme Yang blood
onto the Yin seed,
supreme Yin blood onto the Yang seed.
Thus, we can completely close it.
So this time, we have two objectives.
One, find your mother,
Shen Jiyue's body,
Two, retrieve the Twelfth Night Splendor
and completely break the time loop.
Let's do it together.
♪The end is also the beginning♪
Take the antidote pill.
No.
She is mine.
- Wait.
- No.
You can't take her!
(Master,)
(in this life,)
(we part ways from here.)
Senior,
the flowers in the courtyard
have bloomed.
If you like them, they're yours.
(Jiyue.)
(I'm sorry.)
Young master,
let me help you.
No need.
I have led the troops
to conquer the Cult.
All their members have been dealt with.
All of this has finally ended.
Where is my senior?
He heard that you and my young master
are unharmed,
and was relieved.
He asked me to bring you a letter.
(Zhili,)
(you know I've never liked farewells.)
(The world is small.)
(Perhaps we may meet again soon.)
(Our past filled with entanglements.)
(now we have regained our freedom)
(and have good people by our sides.)
(I hope you an easy)
(and happy life from now on.)
(Hua Jiuye)
(Senior, I'll see you again.)
It seems that he
has gone to enjoy the world
with Ye Qianqian.
That's good.
As long as I know he's still around,
I am at ease.
I will always be by your side.
Forever.
If you stay by my side forever,
what about Twelfth Night?
The Cult is eradicated.
Vengeance is served.
Dawn has broken.
Twelfth Night should be disbanded.
What about you?
Continue being Physician Shen?
Perhaps.
All along,
reviving my master is my faith,
staying in Huichun Valley
is my commitment.
Master is the reason I cannot part
with these.
But it's only now that I've realized
all of this was chosen
by me, Shen Zhili.
What about me?
It was your existence
that made me understand this.
So,
I decided to reward you
by letting you stay by my side forever.
Are you willing?
I couldn't ask for more.
(One month later)
My lord, you're here.
Come on.
Greetings, my lord.
Greetings.
Good.
Study well. The tuition is expensive.
Understood.
Greetings.
Good.
Sit down quickly.
Let me tell you, you must study hard.
Isn't this our new village chief?
- Greetings.
- Good to see you too.
Nowadays,
with so many new roles,
would you mind including Mrs. Su's role?
So many roles,
I'm overwhelmed.
Let's talk about it later.
When exactly is this "later"?
The wedding attire will
be out of fashion soon!
What did you say?
Su Chenche!
What?
Tomorrow is an auspicious time/
What about tomorrow?
Qing Xing, prepare for the wedding!
Yes, sir!
♪Then we met again outside the ending♪
♪Repeat the posture and try to love♪
♪Two hearts approach the shore,
the wind blows, and flowers bloom♪
♪Listen again to fate's arrangement♪
♪We are destined to be involved♪
♪The end is♪
♪My best expectation♪
♪If we separate♪
♪Just one step away
from the world of mortals♪
♪Close the mottled door of memory♪
♪Seal up the thoughts♪
♪If you don't ask♪
♪Is there still a good time
in the future♪
♪Every step you take brings more warmth♪
♪Let love take root♪
♪Even if♪
♪Piecing together the broken stars♪
♪Also wish♪
♪Shining for you♪
♪I'm willing to become♪
♪The flowers falling all over the sky♪
♪I will also remember♪
♪Let love freeze at disillusionment♪
♪Even after♪
♪The ruthless fate at the end of time♪
♪Will still be engraved♪
♪You hand in mine♪