♪The wind stopped
at the familiar face yesterday♪
♪The tenderness you gave♪
♪How to hide it♪
♪The crowd frequently separated us♪
♪Watching the story end♪
♪Then we met again outside the ending♪
♪The end is♪
♪My best expectation♪
=Shameless Lover=
=Episode 21=
Zhili.
Zhili, how are you?
If you must protect her,
then I'll kill both of you.
Zhili, leave here first.
Leave now!
Just die.
Su Chenche, you can't die.
Zhili,
you still care about me.
No.
I just don't want to start over.
Zhili.
Lie down now.
No need.
The arrow must be removed now.
Hang in there.
I can do it myself.
I know you're angry with me.
But don't take it out with your body.
If this wound isn't treated in time,
your life will be in danger.
Wouldn't that be just what you want?
Well.
Don't remember it?
You stole my three core ingredients,
killed my senior,
and even killed me twice.
Are you
going to deny all these?
Zhili,
I didn't...
I didn't steal your core ingredients.
I didn't kill your senior.
And I didn't kill you.
It has started over.
All traces of the past are gone.
You can say anything you want.
But I only believe what I see.
I won't waste words on you.
Just go.
Actually, I...
And,
I must get the Night Shadow Pearl.
If you stand in my way again,
I won't let you off.
This is for healing wounds.
This is for detoxification.
This is for neutralizing.
I have all of these. Take them away.
You'd better keep them,
just in case.
Since you don't trust me,
then I will prove it to you.
Give me three days.
I will let you know the truth.
Okay.
I'm waiting.
I'm here to treat the master's headache.
Divine Physician Shen,
Young Master Su is inside.
You can't enter without summoning.
The flowers in the garden
are in full bloom.
Accompany me to take a look.
(This is how you prove it.)
(Su Chenche, I underestimated you.)
Right, Young Master Su offered
a potent drug for treating headaches.
I'm alright now.
You're no longer needed here.
Yes.
(Sorry, Zhili.)
(I do this only to find the mastermind.)
(Catching him,)
(then you will believe me.)
(No matter what,)
(the three-day promise won't change.)
Thank you
for saving my life last night.
I didn't expect
the young master
saved from drowning last night
to be so handsome.
You were just awesome.
Upon making a move...
Shut up.
Talk too much.
Ji Mingyue said you drowned.
Don't you know how to swim?
You have the nerve to ask?
So you pretended to drown
to enter Mingyue Palace.
You knew the answer.
So you're here specifically for me.
I'm concerned about Su Chenche.
What's going on between you and him?
What has he done to you?
For money or relationship?
For both!
How dare he harm my people?
Message from the main hall.
Ji Mingyue will host a banquet at noon
to celebrate newcomers
in Mingyue Palace.
Young master,
you sacrificed yourself
to get close to Ji Mingyue,
just to force that person to show up.
But now Hua Jiuye has intervened.
If he wins over Ji Mingyue,
our plan
may be disrupted.
It's made according to the dress style
of your father in his youth.
If you wear this,
I'm sure that in Ji Mingyue's eyes,
there's no space for others.
All the young masters in Mingyue Palace
bear some resemblance to Su Shenyan.
If you want to win Ji Mingyue's favor,
you have to be more like him.
For example,
wear this white outfit.
But do not overdo it
like Young Master Xiaoye.
Speaking of resemblance,
wouldn't Su Chenche be more like him?
Don't worry.
Your senior is here.
Even if Su Shenyan were still alive,
Ji Mingyue would only choose me.
(Mingyue Palace)
Young Master Hua arrives.
I knew that in white clothes,
you would look even more handsome.
Thank you, master.
Be seated.
Closer to me.
Since Physician Shen is your junior,
take a seat as well.
Thank you, master.
Why aren't you in white?
My white clothes got stained.
I'll have more white outfits
prepared for you.
Remember.
In the Mingyue Palace,
you can only wear white outfits.
Yes.
Take a seat.
I'm counting on you for this.
Don't worry, I'll take care of it.
Sorry, young master.
Sorry, I didn't mean to.
Now that everyone is here, let's start.
Don't take it to heart.
I just like seeing you in white.
You seem to have lost some weight.
Have more food.
Thank you, master.
(No.)
(We must take the initiative.)
Master,
this tremella soup
is good for beauty and skin care.
Please try this.
Actually, the cook makes this every day.
But no matter how much tremella soup,
I can never be young.
Master, do not be sad.
Just a few rejuvenation pills
can help you regain youth.
Rejuvenation pill?
Does such miraculous pill really exist?
Master, you may not know.
My senior was born
in the royal family of Yuanjiang.
Rejuvenation pills are secret ones
of the royal family.
They do have
miraculous rejuvenation effects.
That's right.
To thank you for saving my life,
I'd like to offer rejuvenation pills,
only for you
to enjoy youth forever.
You are the most considerate.
I am very pleased.
(How about that?)
(This time I will surely defeat you.)
Have some fruit to cool it down.
Master, we've been talking for a while.
You must be thirsty.
Have some fruit to moisten your throat.
Master,
besides taking the pills orally,
you also need to apply herbal medicine.
Except for me,
no one else can do it.
So?
Come and serve in the main hall tonight.
Zhili will come along.
Yes.
Thank you, master.
Master,
here is the herbal remedy
I prepared for you.
Just have a good sleep.
Once you're up,
your skin will become smooth and tender.
Do not open your eyes.
Or fine wrinkles will catch up.
Got it.
Master.
Found it.
(This dragon pattern
is Su Chenche's jade toggle.)
What's wrong?
It was swapped by Su Chenche.
He should have got it.
Keep an eye on the master.
I'll go and settle this.
You finally showed up.
Today is your last day.
Su Chenche, stop.
Senior.
You want to kill him again?
I won't let you do it.
You.
You leave here first.
Zhili,
are you sure he is Hua Jiuye?
Hasn't he done enough disguises?
(There was that peculiar smell.)
(The smell is fading.)
(He)
(isn't...)
Here you are.
Senior.
(This is the real one.)
Senior, just now...
He was ambushed by someone.
Ask him yourself.
Young Master Hua.
Save me.
Save me, Young Master Hua.
(Zhili,)
(are you sure he is Hua Jiuye?)
(Hasn't he done enough disguises?)
Who can it be?
Who is he?
Su Chenche said
that he didn't swap the jade toggle.
He placed his own there.
Although we can't believe
everything he said,
it is possible
that the jade toggle
engraved with the phoenix
is still in Ji Mingyue's hands.
I'm asking you.
What's on your mind?
- What do we do next?
Senior,
I have a plan.
But I need your help.
(I planned to catch him)
(in Mingyue Palace within three days)
(to reveal the truth.)
(But now,)
(I haven't caught him.)
(I've even deepened
Zhili's misunderstanding.)
(How useless I am!)
Twelfth Night Young Master,
why are you so depressed?
Zhili asked you to come and stop me?
She went to Ji Mingyue alone?
Master,
my senior is a bit tired today.
I'll take over for him
for the following job.
I've no idea where Zhili goes,
or what she does.
But today you're going nowhere.
Don't you worry about her safety?
Alright, alright.
How long does the medicine take to work?
Rejuvenation pills are better.
Bring them over.
Rejuvenation pills contain graphene.
It's harmful.
You can have it at most twice a month.
In my Mingyue Palace,
nobody dares to defy me.
Zhili has thorough plans.
She's gonna be fine.
The one with thorough plans
and meticulous thinking.
Quite typical of the current Zhili.
I've known Zhili for over a decade.
You've only known her for a few days.
How dare you call her Zhili?
(It seems that Zhili hasn't told him
about what happened before.)
(This is Hallucination Pill. With fire,
its scent can cause hallucinations.)
♪If we separate♪
♪Just one step away
from the world of mortals♪
♪Close the mottled door of memory♪
♪Seal up the thoughts♪
♪If you don't ask♪
♪Is there still a good time
in the future♪
♪Every step you take brings more warmth♪
♪Let love take root♪
♪Even if♪
♪Piecing together the broken stars♪
♪Also wish♪
♪Shining for you♪
♪I'm willing to become♪
♪The flowers falling all over the sky♪
♪I will also remember♪
♪Let love freeze at disillusionment♪
♪Even after♪
♪The ruthless fate at the end of time♪
♪Will still be engraved♪
♪You hand in mine♪