♪The wind stopped
at the familiar face yesterday♪
♪The tenderness you gave♪
♪How to hide it♪
♪The crowd frequently separated us♪
♪Watching the story end♪
♪Then we met again outside the ending♪
♪The end is♪
♪My best expectation♪
=Shameless Lover=
=Episode 22=
(This is Hallucination Pill. With fire,
its scent can cause hallucinations.)
(Looks like
the Hallucination Pill starts to work.)
You've known some for over a decade,
but it seems you've just met.
You've known some merely days,
but it seems
you've undergone many together.
So you know her well.
Then tell me.
What is she doing now?
It's been on Ji Mingyue's mind
for more than ten years.
Removing it in just one night
is no easy task.
Master,
do you
still remember me?
You.
Aren't you...
Who is it again?
Then, do you remember Su Shenyan?
I do.
He is the one who cares only about me.
Be careful.
Look.
So beautiful.
They're all in full bloom.
Shenyan.
No.
Not possible.
What is this?
I'm so pretty.
And I love him so much.
How could he possibly not like me?
To love someone,
learn to love yourself first.
If you don't even love yourself,
how can you expect others to love you?
I?
I don't love myself?
I am Ji Mingyue.
The entire Mingyue Palace is mine.
Those handsome men in the world.
I can have as many as I want,
in whatever way I like.
How dare you
Judge me here?
Is that real?
But when I look at
this vast Mingyue Palace,
it's not the Peach Garden of love,
but a cage of self-admiration,
where you escape from the reality.
It's the abyss you've created for men.
Cage.
No. Living in such an abyss...
Abyss.
Are you truly happy?
Zhili,
here you are.
Then,
why not let it go?
Let it go.
Just like your pair of thumb rings.
Put them down.
Maybe then you'll find
the one
who truly loves you.
Zhili, look.
So beautiful.
Think about it.
All sweet memories
are merely your fantasy.
The person you love
has never loved you.
All are illusions of your fantasy.
Stop deceiving yourself.
Let it go.
(Both the jade toggles are here.)
(Su Chenche did not swap them.)
I will let go of them all.
Master.
Pass on the Master's decree.
(Mingyue Palace)
Mingyue Palace is disbanded right away.
Let's go.
You are...
Mingyue Palace is disbanded right away.
All the young masters may return home.
The master has moved on
from that person.
Her mental burden is gone.
Mingyue Palace will henceforth
return to normal.
We can go home now.
Let's go.
Then congratulations.
Although it's not easy,
I believe,
having me, the one who is fully
in tune with her, by her side,
nothing is impossible.
Is it you and her fully in tune,
or me and her as soul mates?
It's still too early to tell.
He didn't say much
in the Huichun Valley.
He didn't tell her anything either
in Mingyue Palace.
Obviously, she's not expected
to be too involved,
especially in the upcoming encounter
with people from Yuanjiang.
Send him away.
Yes.
Zhili.
Your senior is no longer here.
I sent him back to Huichun Valley.
♪Seal up the thoughts♪
♪I don't ask if there's still
a good time in the future♪
♪Every step you take brings more warmth♪
♪Let love take root♪
Zhili.
♪Even if I've embraced
the once-extinguished fireflies♪
♪I'll still heat up for you♪
♪I'm willing to become
the flowers falling all over the sky♪
♪I will remember to
let love freeze at disillusionment♪
Zhili,
you still care about me.
From now on,
we're going our separate ways,
and never meet again.
Young Master Su,
let's part ways here.
♪I'd like to save two hearts
from being torn apart♪
♪Break free from the chains
of right and wrong♪
♪Even if lost in this desert like fate♪
♪Still hold on to it♪
♪You hand in mine♪
Only by letting go of
those unworthy of you,
and moving forward,
can you find the one
who truly loves you.
May God bless.
May God bless the master
with happiness.
with good health.
May God bless the master
with great safety.
(My life was saved by the master.)
(My heart is always with her.)
(If there's an afterlife,)
(I wish I could work harder)
(to be with her for more days.)
(Nanluan Town)
(Breeze Inn)
(Su Chenche can't be trusted after all.)
(Now I am fighting alone.)
(So I must get well prepared)
(before the people
from Yuanjiang arrive.)
(Breeze Inn)
Are you come to stay the night?
How much is it to book the entire inn?
May I ask your surname?
Shen.
Lady Shen,
to book our entire inn,
it costs fifty taels of silver.
(Fifty taels? Why so cheap?)
(In this world,)
(no one would do business at a loss.)
May I know the surname of your owner?
Well, this...
I don't like
to take advantage of others.
Here is a hundred taels.
Take it
and clean up the rooms for me.
I have some business
and have to go out first.
Alright, alright.
(Liuyue, owner of Juxian Hall)
Miss, you look new here.
It's your first time to Juxian Hall?
May I ask your surname? How can I help?
I've got experts at all sorts of trades,
be it striking deals or cooking meals,
fighting bandits
or punching bad guys.
Be it for daily care or traveling,
you'll be in good hands.
Great.
I need to hire a few masters.
The very top ones.
Got it.
He is the top assassin
in the assassin's organization.
He is
a renowned Qing Kung master.
He may
look average,
but he is a master of traps.
He is proficient in various languages.
Getting intelligence is a piece of cake.
Various languages?
Then he also speaks Yuanjiang dialect?
Naturally.
His ancestry is from Yuanjiang.
You are rather sharing my mind.
I haven't yet stated my request.
You've already brought the people here.
This is the advantage of Juxian Hall.
The service is always up to standard.
What do you think about them?
If they are not good enough,
I have more choices.
No rush.
I have a few questions to ask.
Is it okay?
You wouldn't think showing up
would be enough
for her to make a decision, right?
Please enlighten us.
She
is clever.
The first question
she wants to ask is...
Whether you know each other.
Whether you work well with each other.
It seems to be about your abilities.
But actually,
she is probing into your backgrounds.
How should we respond then?
Since we're all working in Juxian Hall,
we're somewhat familiar with each other.
We've cooperated a few times.
I think we work well.
If I were to employ you,
you'll serve
one employer or two?
If she asks this question,
it means she's already guessed
that I am your employer.
No need to hide. Just tell the truth.
Two.
(What exactly do you want?)
(Do you think it's touching)
(to do this behind?)
Young master.
If she employs you,
it means there's still hope for me.
Since you are already employed,
it's better
that I just leave you to him.
Boss,
please find someone else for me.
Here's the commission.
The right amount.
Miss, would you like to think about it?
They are all top experts.
They are...
Miss.
Young master, you can't always
hide like this.
Now, no matter what I say,
she does not believe.
Only by unveiling the truth
will she see everything clearly.
(Zhili,)
(you want to draw a line between us.)
(Then I'll help you behind the scene.)
Has Qing Xing returned?
Move.
I'm too tired.
Hey man.
You've taken half a day
for just three miles.
Can you walk more quickly?
My hands are tied up like this.
How can I walk fast?
Why don't you help me untie it?
Untie it?
To let you run away?
This rope of the Mo family
really went through careful efforts.
Afraid that I would run away?
Just save it.
The earlier we arrive,
the earlier we end it.
I'll be fine then.
But don't you
worry about your young master?
Are you sure he's fine on his own?
I've heard
that the head of your young master
is worth a fortune in the Cult.
As you leave now,
if the Cult attacks,
your young master will be in danger.
I...
I'll take a pee.
(During the Mid-Autumn Festival
over the past years,)
(I had tied a knot for my master)
(and senior each.)
Then you will also
tie a knot for me as a gift.
Is it okay?
Aren't gifts
only for birthdays?
Today
is my birthday.
♪Memories are stretching♪
♪Following you♪
♪Love or hurt♪
♪How to resist it♪
♪How to hide it♪
♪The crowd frequently separated us♪
♪Watching the story end♪
♪Then we met again outside the ending♪
Right.
You must aim carefully.
You must hold this steady.
Yes, like this.
Like this?
Right, just hold it steady.
Change another one.
It's not right.
♪My best expectation♪
Congratulations.
Visit the seventh floor
for a custom painting.
- Great!
Awesome!
Bravo!
Right on the point.
Anyone else up for the challenge?
Me.
Young master, please.
♪Two hearts approach the shore,
the wind blows, and flowers bloom♪
♪Listen again to fate's arrangement♪
Sorry, sorry.
♪The end is♪
Great!
♪If we separate♪
♪Just one step away
from the world of mortals♪
♪Close the mottled door of memory♪
♪Seal up the thoughts♪
♪If you don't ask♪
♪Is there still a good time
in the future♪
♪Every step you take brings more warmth♪
♪Let love take root♪
♪Even if♪
♪Piecing together the broken stars♪
♪Also wish♪
♪Shining for you♪
♪I'm willing to become♪
♪The flowers falling all over the sky♪
♪I will also remember♪
♪Let love freeze at disillusionment♪
♪Even after♪
♪The ruthless fate at the end of time♪
♪Will still be engraved♪
♪You hand in mine♪