♪The wind stopped
at the familiar face yesterday♪
♪The tenderness you gave♪
♪How to hide it♪
♪The crowd frequently separated us♪
♪Watching the story end♪
♪Then we met again outside the ending♪
♪The end is♪
♪My best expectation♪
=Shameless Lover=
=Episode 5=
The incense...
It's a muscle relaxant powder
that renders you completely weak.
Fool.
Dear.
What is this?
A life-saving pill.
It can detoxify all poisons.
(You've finally shown yourself.)
(This face...)
This painting...
So the men of the Mingyue Palace
are all selected based on his likeness.
He is indeed extremely similar
to Su Chenche.
No wonder Ji Mingyue
treated him differently.
August lily?
(Why is this underneath the painting?)
There are no signs of rummaging here.
Seems the Night Shadow Pearl isn't here.
I won't be able
to leave this palace soon.
I've taken a fancy to you.
If you behave,
you'll have everything you wish for.
Thank you, Master.
But I already have a wife.
I'm afraid I cannot comply
with your request.
Oh?
What about your companion
in the secret chamber?
You lured me out
so that she could have a chance
to leave safely, right?
But what a pity.
You've underestimated
the Mingyue Palace.
Wait!
Why did you come here?
Put away the sword.
Put it away!
Forgive us, Master.
My brother and I are new
to the Mingyue Palace.
I apologize for trespassing
into your chamber.
Please spare us,
Master.
You trespassed at a curious time.
Could it be that you are here
for the Night Shadow Pearl?
We wouldn't dare.
This is all my fault.
I will do anything to compensate.
But
my brother is innocent.
Please let him go home, Master.
Interesting.
We will go home together.
I can defeat her.
Shut up.
You're not qualified to serve me.
Your brother, however,
can stay and atone for it.
But...
What?
You refuse?
Master, surely you've noticed.
We...
Do you know
the consequences of deceiving me?
Master, please have mercy.
We are...
Take them down.
Yes.
Who do you think you are?
I don't understand why the Master
keeps you alive.
You...
If you touch her,
that will be the end for you.
If you ever do that again,
you won't see make it out alive.
Do you think I would let you
get out of here alive?
Su Chenche.
Dear.
Are you trying to murder
your own husband?
No.
How did you get out?
I borrowed Xiaoye's clothes to get out.
Xiaoye
lent you his clothes?
Without him knowing though.
Strip.
Not bad for
the Twelfth Night Young Master.
Simple and direct.
But this is good.
With these clothes,
it'd be easier to leave.
Leave?
Where to?
Just follow me.
I'll see you off from here.
Go.
Aren't you leaving with me?
I must obtain the Night Shadow Pearl.
Is that more valuable than your life?
It is.
Take care of yourself.
Do you really want me to go?
Okay.
Let me rephrase the question.
Do you want me to stay with you?
This is my own affair.
You don't need to risk your life.
You are my wife.
Fake wife.
(The Mingyue Palace has three halls:
left, center, and right.)
(The Night Shadow Pearl
is not in the main hall)
(or the sleeping chamber
within the main hall.)
(It can't possibly be
in the left or right halls.)
(Then where could it be?)
You were told not to wander around.
The stone forest in the back courtyard
is forbidden to your like.
That is where the Master practices.
A forbidden area.
I apologize, young master.
I won't do it again.
I'm sorry.
Please spare me.
It won't happen again.
♪The gentleness♪
There are more and more August lilies.
♪Turns into your deep love♪
♪And turns into nothing♪
August lilies again.
My master once said
that August lilies grow in stony places.
Perhaps,
there is a secret chamber here.
♪Trampling through love and hate♪
♪Three thousand dusts
drive the turbid waves♪
♪We are trapped at the end of the road♪
♪The battle of dreams♪
Could this be
the entrance to the secret chamber?
♪I fight with myself♪
♪Explore the way back,
the unforgettable love♪
♪Can't get out of the reciprocating♪
♪Who admits defeat♪
♪You are me♪
♪The severe cold and the blazing red♪
♪Even if it melts in the flames♪
Yin and Yang.
The Yang side has a dragon pattern.
The Yin side has a groove.
What is it?
♪It changes endlessly♪
♪The end is also the beginning♪
Where did she go?
Young Master Su.
Are you looking for her?
The more you care about her,
the more I want to torment her.
Your love
will only harm her.
(This jade toggle and the groove
on the secret chamber door)
(are the same.)
What do you want?
What do I want?
I want you
to marry me.
Su Chenche.
Don't be coerced because of me.
Of course I won't.
I'm the one who coerces others.
If you don't let her go,
I'll never be yours.
Don't!
You can't die.
Do you know
the consequences of doing this?
I assume the last thing you want
is my death.
It depends on who is faster.
(Ji Mingyue is by nature stubborn.)
(She's capable of anything when pushed.)
(Now that I'm so close,)
(I must first calm her down.)
Please calm your anger, Master.
You have misunderstood.
He and I
are just patient and physician.
Nothing more.
The reason he did this
is just to get your attention.
There's an old saying that goes
"What you can't have is the best."
He is only
playing hard to get.
Should I put in a few words for you?
Su Chenche.
Can you please stop this farce?
Put the knife down.
The Master is so affectionate to you.
How could you let her down?
Pick an auspicious day
and get married.
You sure know how to read the room.
So, what do you think, Young Master Su?
You...
You really want to see me marry her?
Of course.
Good.
As you wish then.
(Shen Zhili.)
(Don't you have any feelings for me?)
(How could you just gift me)
(to another woman?)
(He must be very mad now.)
(If it were me,)
(I'd probably...)
Ji Mingyue has already
sent out the wedding invitations
to Twelfth Night.
If it weren't for you,
my life
would have been in jeopardy.
Write it down.
What?
A divorce letter.
I can't serve two women
at the same time.
What are you talking about?
That's only an expedient measure.
Don't take it seriously.
Words said cannot be retrieved.
How can I not take it seriously?
I'm going to get married.
I've no time for chats.
Get married?
You belong to me.
Moreover,
if I didn't have a plan,
do you think I'd let you
agree to marry her?
Empty rhetoric.
You have a plan?
Let's hear it then.
I already know where
the Night Shadow Pearl is.
As soon as I get it,
we can leave Mingyue Palace tonight.
So,
letting me marry her
is also part of the plan?
Of course.
I will never abandon you,
no matter when.
Moreover,
without you,
this plan could never be accomplished.
Oh, my dear.
♪If we separate♪
♪Just one step away
from the world of mortals♪
♪Close the mottled door of memory♪
♪Seal up the thoughts♪
♪If you don't ask♪
♪Is there still a good time
in the future♪
♪Every step you take brings more warmth♪
♪Let love take root♪
♪Even if♪
♪Piecing together the broken stars♪
♪Also wish♪
♪Shining for you♪
♪I would like to become♪
♪The flowers falling all over the sky♪
♪I will also remember♪
♪Let love freeze at disillusionment♪
♪Even after♪
♪The ruthless fate at the end of time♪
♪Will still be engraved♪
♪You hand in mine♪