Wow, wow. Whoa.
No, we can't today.
The workshop is canceled. Canceled.
What are you talking about? We're not canceling it.
Look at her face.
Wow, canceling will be worse.
We're about to get fired.
What do we do then?
Send the bus back to the office.
What could we possibly do here?
What are you planning to do Unni?
Okay, everyone. Since it's raining today,
let's all have fun in the office.
Yang Hye Ji | Kim Ho Young]
Move it in here. This way. Move, move, move.
Try hanging it up.
- Like this?
- A little more to the side.
Pull it more.
Yes, pull it.
You're doing great.
This way.
Come on.
Gosh, this is looking great.
Good work, everyone.
Just relax here.
We'll let you know when the game is officially starting.
- Okay!
- Relax, everyone.
Let's go.
Whoever you are, I won't let anyone in so don't waste your energy.
Eun Ho, I heard you're moving out.
Someone wants to see the apartment.
Oh, okay. I'm sorry.
Hurry, hurry.
Peekaboo.
- What's this?
- Okay, get moving.
Peekaboo, Eun Ho.
Kidnapping So Eun Ho. Here we go.
What are you doing?
What are you doing right now?
Honey, relax a bit.
Hey, what are you doing?
What could it be? We're kidnapping you in broad daylight.
Wow. Your tent is close to mine.
Did So Eun Ho not come?
Why are you asking me about him?
I suppose.
It'd be weirder if you knew.
Geez, let go!
Let go.
You know this is a crime, right?
I know. I know.
Okay, we'll officially start the game now.
Gosh, why are you so quiet?
Introduce yourself!
Okay, to introduce myself...
I'm a pillar that's been here for 15 years.
I'm Lee Yeong Ae.
You're so cool!
Okay, the first game is...
called...
Battle Agency.
If there's someone you've always wanted to fight,
you can invite them to the ring and battle with them verbally.
To someone you might want to say, "I'd like to duke it out with this bastard!"
Or if you want to reveal your true feelings to someone
you can use this opportunity to tell them directly.
Okay, the first participant is...
Team Leader Cha Jeong Woo.
Come out! Come out!
- Come out! Come out!
- Come out!
Seongsu Agency's Mr. Perfect. Team Leader Cha Jeong Woo.
Is there an opponent you want to battle with?
So Eun Ho.
Come out.
Daebak. Daebak.
- Come out! Come out!
- Come out!
Come out! Come out! Come out!
Come out! Come out!
Hey, So Eun Ho!
This automatically makes Team Leader Cha Jeong Woo the winner.
A round of applause, please.
Na Eon.
You came, Sunbae?
Shall we talk?
It looks like the work environment has changed a lot.
For both you and the company.
I like it this way.
I've always told you to move on from the incident five years ago and—
How did you do that?
Five years ago.
You took responsibility for everything,
but how were you able to hang on like this?
Because you were taking it so hard.
Sunbae,
because of the people who did that to us,
I've been hanging in there all this time.
But I suddenly had this thought.
The person from five years ago
might be the same one...
who tried to kill me.
Really?
Then who was it?
That's a good concept.
This is so good.
Have some coffee!
Yes.
It's so good.
Okay, okay, everyone.
Yes.
After the tasty dinner,
there will be an event that I have prepared.
It's called Treasure Hunt.
- Treasure Hunt?
- A round of applause.
Everyone, Treasure Hunt has to be played with a designated partner.
Oh, my.
Please reveal the partners!
A round of applause, please.
Oppa, you're my partner.
I hope you have a pleasant time with your partner.
Treasure Hunt starts now!
The prize is very generous.
Very generous.
Hurry up!
Let's go.
Forget it. Treasure Hunt? I'm not a kid.
This is a legitimate date.
Let's go.
I don't expect a lot.
I just wanted to say
I want to keep liking you like I did before.
What?
I just want to like you on my own. I can't even do that?
No, you can't.
Because one's feelings
can grow so immensely that you can't handle them.
So, don't.
How about you and So Eun Ho then?
We can't handle them.
Neither me nor So Eun Ho.
Oh, my God! You scared me! My goodness.
But what are you doing here?
I was looking for the treasure.
Yes, the treasure.
By the way, how could you be like this?
The Treasure Hunt was your idea.
How could you walk away from it like that?
Yes, Yeong Ae Sunbae. Please come to my office for a moment.
Scrap everything but Part 2. "Speak With Your Body."
Let's do the Treasure Hunt instead.
The one where you find prizes and give them away... Treasure Hunt?
I put you in charge because I knew you'd prepare it well.
I'll do my best.
Fighting.
I don't think it's here.
Let's go somewhere else.
- Where is it?
- Where did they hide it?
Gosh, seriously.
Oppa, come over here.
Did you find anything?
Wow.
- What's this?
- What's this? What's this?
I think it's a power outage.
Sunbae.
Sunbae, are you okay?
Hold on a second.
I'll bring someone over.
Don't go.
Don't go, So Eun Ho.
I can manage it myself.
What's wrong with you?
Say, "I'm struggling."
"I'm in pain."
Is it that hard to say?
You're so damn proud.
You just need to say it.
What happened five years ago was an accident.
So, you don't care
whether I leave or not. Is that it?
You'll be in so much pain whenever it gets dark.
Say, "I'm struggling."
"Stay by my side."
Is it really that difficult to say?
I...
need to hear that from you.
So...
So I can come to you.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, So Eun Ho.
Sunbae, do you know...
how I've felt...
all this time?
Hello.
I'm the new intern, So Eun Ho.
No one would know.
I was smiling, but I was going through hell inside.
I joined Kang Na Eon's team.
I'll start dragging her down to the bottom now.
We might not be able to correct what's wrong,
but we don't have to cover things up for them.
When did that happen?
Fortunately, you were a worse villain than I imagined.
And pointing the sword of revenge at you was the right thing to do.
What is it that you want?
You.
I want everything, including your soul.
So I had to be by your side no matter what it took.
And I thought it was an opportunity
when our bodies switched.
An opportunity to defeat Kang Na Eon.
What's going on?
But for some reason,
the more I got to know you, the more different you were than I thought.
I thought maybe you were a better person than I thought.
Go prove yourself.
I kind of like the branding work you did.
I thought maybe you're not as bad as I thought.
Do a presentation with this.
But if you weren't the villain,
who was responsible for all this?
If I didn't visit Segye Group that day,
and if I didn't run into you,
we wouldn't be suffering this much.
We...
wouldn't be hurting this much.
To be honest,
I couldn't forgive myself.
That's why...
That's why I've been hanging in there with all my might.
It's not your fault.
It's all my fault.
So, let's...
stop hurting.
I don't want you to get hurt.
I...
I don't want you to get hurt, either.
♫  It belongs to you and I  ♫
♫  The star we created together  ♫
♫  It will always be there  ♫
♫  Lift up your head when you're tired  ♫
♫  This is love itself  ♫
♫  It's what I've been keeping in my heart for a long time  ♫
♫  You might get lost sometimes  ♫
♫  You might have no one else to blame sometimes  ♫
♫  But try to remember this moment right here  ♫
Eun Ho.
What's this all of a sudden?
I wanted to say goodbye for the last time.
I know you're ready...
to let me go now.
Were you happy preparing revenge for five years?
I want you to free yourself from me
and become happy.
♫  Sometimes the tears build up  ♫
♫  Even if it feels so far away  ♫
♫  When I open my eyes, I see you  ♫
♫  The happy moments that help me forget for a little while  ♫
♫  You will make me happier than anyone, and shine here  ♫
See you later, So Eun Ho.
Are you okay?
Yes.
You look tired.
I'll drive later.
It's fine.
What you told me yesterday...
I'm sure it was difficult for you to say.
I didn't say that to hang onto you.
I just...
said what I felt.
I know.
Therefore... I'm also thinking of doing what I feel like now.
Let me be by your side.
Don't look for the culprit...
who tried to kill you alone either.
Thank you.
To be honest,
I found something.
Sunbae, what's...
all this?
I think this is the original.
They erased their tracks.
The best way they know how.
♫  After the wave of thoughts came to a stop  ♫
♫  The sadness overflows  ♫
♫  I'm holding back, my heart that overflows again with hope  ♫
♫  After hesitating  ♫
♫  I'm hesitating, mmm ~  ♫
♫  The words, just flow out like this  ♫
♫  My days and nights are all about you  ♫
♫  So much so that I forget myself  ♫
♫  So will you stay with me?  ♫