What are you doing?
Are you here because you're suspicious of me too?
Do you know how many times I was questioned by the police in the past month?
I don't trust the police.
It's not my style to trust anyone.
Is this your true self?
How about you? What's your true self?
A stupid but good-natured shoemaker who bet his family's livelihood
on handmade shoes that don't even sell?
- What?
- Or...
a disgusting murderer who killed someone...
because of explosive anger?
Look at this guy.
I tried to tolerate you, but—
Don't get me wrong. I'm here to help you survive.
Geez...
You've got to be kidding.
You think I'd receive help from you people?
Get help if you were victimized
and if you victimized someone, get punished yourself.
Hey.
I wouldn't think it unfair if I had killed Kang Na Eon.
I guess you did want to kill her.
I hope you succeed next time.
Losers.
Is this bad?
Isn't that too much?
- No, it's not.
- Hey, Rex.
Don't put on too much.
My gosh, newbie.
Welcome.
You came.
Newbie?
Jenny's quiz. Should I keep them on or take them off?
Why do I crave beer while eating a diet snack?
I'll just drink it if I crave it.
Gosh, give me one, too.
Let's all drink together since the newbie's here.
It's party time, right?
It's okay. You just need a nap for 30 minutes afterward. Drink it.
I didn't come with any expectations.
But this is still worse than I could have imagined.
Eun Ho!
Welcome to our team!
My gosh, I'm so grateful
that someone so handsome joined our team.
There you go.
Let's take a photo together. One, two, three.
Make my nose pointier, I said.
Just turn me into Pinocchio.
Photoshop my face more.
Is that it?
I'll get you a special desk right here, Oppa.
- Ta-da.
- Come this way.
I know you're really handsome,
but you're still the newbie after all.
That looks like a good spot.
Eun Ho, that's the team leader's desk.
I think...
I deserve to be the team leader... the most here.
I'll work offsite.
What? Already? Aren't we going to have a party?
Look how he's ignoring us.
Team Leader Do wants you in her office.
Team Leader Do?
It's probably regarding the handmade shoe factory.
What factory?
- Let's back up.
- Back up what?
Yeong Ae, create a list of celebrities to model for us and figure out their schedules.
Rex, do sketches for the handmade shoe rebranding.
And Jenny,
Come on.
- Jenny?
- Yes?
Come up with five concepts for social media marketing.
- Me?
- She can't do stuff like that.
My gosh, he's too sexy.
Hey, everyone!
We're having fun tonight!
Enjoy! Enjoy yourselves!
Everyone, Yu Mi's treating you tonight. Drink up!
And our actor. Congratulations on becoming the ambassador.
I put this together for you, but you're acting kind of cold.
Hey. Just worry about me, not him.
And don't let your company call me about modeling for some weird handmade shoes.
Oh, did they? I'm so sorry.
Say no. I'll get you something else instead.
- Really?
- Of course.
- Keep your promise, okay?
- Cheers.
And for our A-list actor—
I'm not sure if you can handle it.
Handle what?
Anything. Everything that Kang Na Eon used to handle.
My gosh.
You were just a dog that Kang Na Eon used to drag around because she exploited your weakness.
Why are you being so loyal?
I even had this thought once.
I wondered if you were the reason Na Eon ended up like that.
Come on, let's face it.
We all know how much she harassed our A-list actor.
Don't you agree?
Come on, she did. Don't you remember?
Stop carelessly pretending... as if you're Kang Na Eon.
You crazy bastard!
- What are you doing? Hey!
- Come on.
- Do Yu Mi!
- Let go! Didn't you just see him?
That's enough!
Let's stop drinking and leave.
Are you refusing to drink because I'm paying for it?
Are you looking down on me right now?
It's because I was going to drive you home.
Let's go.
They called 119 using my phone?
Maybe...
the culprit is somewhere close to me.
Cha Jeong Woo?
It's my fault.
If only I didn't come up with a design like that...
What a foolish bastard.
Team Leader Nam.
Shit. Crazy bastard.
Or... Do Yu Mi?
You must have gotten the call too.
Right? Handmade shoes are no good, right?
It's okay to say no.
Yes, thank you. Okay.
Does he think trying hard will get him anywhere?
Why are you going so far?
It's because I f***ing hate him!
Didn't you see So Eun Ho acting like he's Kang Na Eon or something?
He was nothing but her boyfriend.
He wasn't her boyfriend.
Does that matter to you right now?
Yes, it does.
Forget it.
We're here.
You have time, right?
Come up and have a drink.
- Yu Mi, I...
- What?
Am I not like Kang Na Eon today?
I might as well go see her.
So I could resemble her more.
- The vital signs are good, right?
- Yes.
- Let's go, then.
- Okay.
Here we go.
Hold on for a moment.
Where are you going right now?
Who are you?
I'm Kang Na Eon's guardian.
The director said we can't continue to help her.
The hospital bills haven't been paid.
To the VIP room. Make sure it's the best one.
Okay.
It's maxed out.
Six months installment payment.
It's not going through.
Twelve months, then?
Emergency. Emergency.
Team Leader Do Yu Mi summoned us for a company meeting.
I'll be on vacation.
I think I'm kind of sick.
Losers.
Why do I have to be in this body...
- This is princess-like.
- Don't even think about it.
I want the pink one.
It's nice to get together like this, isn't it?
Yes, Ma'am!
Should the Underdog Team start the presentation?
- Pardon?
- Gosh, what do we do?
What the hell...
What are you doing? Stop shaking.
I'll start the presentation for the strategy to upgrade...
the image of the handmade shoes...
Did you decide on a model?
We need a top celebrity since the theme is "luxury."
Yes. We're making calls while working on the list.
But for some reason...
everyone said no by saying the same thing.
Did someone sabotage us or something?
It's probably because your proposal sucked.
How about the visuals?
Yes... Yes.
I came up with the visuals myself.
This is the first mockup.
It's a luxury rebranding for our top audience.
"Turn the handmade shoes no one wears
into the handmade shoes not just anyone can wear."
Redo it.
Why? Do you not like it?
No. I don't.
What do you think?
Is it because Rex worked on it?
Well, the colors aren't quite...
How strange.
We hired a vendor that Team Leader Do worked with often.
Aren't they pretty good, Art Team Leader?
We do work with them when we need extra hands.
This is how scary framing is.
By the way Mr. So...
you don't think you're Kang Na Eon do you?
Why are we bringing her up right now?
It's because you're acting just like her.
You prepared this by yourself because you couldn't trust your teammates.
You just joined the team.
But you know what?
No one cares, even if you're unconscious for a month or if you start acting like her.
As if everyone wanted you to end up that way.
He'd better stop now.
Gosh, what do we do?
That's enough.
Let's stop now.
My team wants to go enjoy lunch.
Let's stop now. Thank you.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
Let's go.
- Let's get him something tasty.
- Yes.
Tasty food makes you feel better.
You make mistakes when you're new because you're too passionate.
I even yelled at the CEO's office in my first year.
"Let us eat twice at the company cafeteria!"
Sweetie, I don't like how you interrupted me and took over during the meeting,
but since you're handsome,
I'll forgive you if you get me two servings of food.
Did you hear that?
- Something tasty. Something tasty.
- Let's see...
Did you contact Actor Park's management company?
Yes, I'm waiting for them to call back.
- Get an extra large one. Extra large.
- Then we should start with the redesign—
Gosh, you're moving too fast honey.
We can finish by the weekly meeting next week.
They're having a review event.
What would you like, Oppa?
Do you... want to live as losers here forever?
What?
Honey, you're being too harsh.
- How dare you call us losers?
- Don't.
- Let me correct myself.
- Yes, go ahead and do that!
I said "framing" in the conference room earlier.
But you weren't framed.
You guys are actually losers.
You've got to be kidding me.
Excuse me.
You're the one who ignored all the current projects and made us do the rebranding.
You're the outcast and loser on this team, okay?
- Stop it, Rex.
- Geez.
Do you not need to work hard since you have two jobs?
- What do you mean-
- You have a male body,
but the soul of a goddess?
Shit.
Princess!
Oppa, you don't have friends, right?
We'll get going now.
Thank you so much.
Aren't you going home Team Leader?
I need to stop by the hospital.
You can go ahead.
- Let's go.
- Take care.
Why is he going to the hospital?
- He's going to see her.
- Her?
Yes.
Did the actor actually turn us down first?
Yes, got it.
I hope you apologize sincerely for what you said today.
Otherwise, I'm going to take a stand against you.
I wish I could be the one taking a stand.
I mean...
how could we switch back?
No way.
What...
are you doing right now?
♫  Just call me Lady  ♫
♫  Don't call me "Of Yours"  ♫
♫  I just may achieve my dream, get up  ♫
♫  I'm driven by pain, even in the face of challenge and despair  ♫
♫  There is no need to stress  ♫
♫  That's my blue  ♫
♫  Just call me "Lady", don't call me "Of Yours"  ♫
♫  Pointy flat shoes  ♫
♫  Worn-out sneakers  ♫
♫  Whatever it is, I feel like I can touch the sky  ♫