Have us compete in a presentation.
Hey, what are you doing right now?
- Who are you?
- I'm So Eun Ho, the new marketer.
You're new, but you're very ambitious.
Why don't you do the presentation, then?
What should we do with Segye Soju?
Should we fold or not?
Why don't you fold?
What?
Hey.
Hey, what are you... What are you doing...
He came prepared. My gosh.
- That's—
- Gosh, he's sexy.
Last year, each adult consumed 53 bottles of soju.
That's the equivalent of 397 glasses.
Last year, 2.29 billion bottles of soju were sold.
But the total amount of soju consumed was only 20%
of all alcohol consumption.
The market share of Segye Soju, which launched last year,
was merely 4%.
This year's sales are presumed to be negative 120% compared to last year.
At this rate, next year's market share is presumed to...
drop near 2%.
That's why you should fold.
Hey, are you crazy?
You have a point.
But that's your destiny when you jump into the red ocean late.
I jumped in knowing I'd be destroyed by the competitors.
Why? Why? Because I'm sincere about wanting to protect Korea's soju.
I'm against wine and whiskey and stuff like that dominating our market.
Liquor equals soju.
Sincerity. Passion.
Stuff like that can't just become an excuse for losers.
I think our sexy monster is trying to sabotage Team 1.
Yes.
So?
You want me to fold... no matter what?
Fold and... move on to the next game.
Replay?
By doing a premium relaunching,
we'll give Segye Soju a new life and make it a top brand.
That's... a very aggressive suggestion.
Okay, then.
Thanks for sharing, Team 1.
Shall we hear from Team Leader Kang since we're having a competition?
Pardon?
Well, I-I...
No, no. Not Team Leader Kang.
Who's the youngest... in this team?
Hey, hey.
- Pardon?
- It's only fair this way.
I'm not really sure since I don't drink.
Our youngest team member...
How old are you?
- I'm 20 years old.
- I see.
Are you a special high school recruit?
Pardon?
You know...
I am not curious if our special post-high school recruit drinks or not.
Why don't you understand the point of my question?
Is it because you're a high school graduate?
Director, what you said just now is a bit—
Wow, looking closely. There's no way you could compete with Team 1.
Ahjumma.
- Gay.
- My gosh.
And a high school graduate?
You're going too far, Sir.
I'm too understanding, more like.
I'm thinking of giving you a bonus point since you're handicapped.
We don't need bonus points right now—
You old geezer with stinky feet!
Put some socks on!
Gosh, Jenny.
- Jenny!
- My gosh, Jenny!
What?
I thought the MZ generation was strong.
Is this really something to cry over?
What's your opinion as a fellow member of the MZ generation?
I know.
Is this really... something to cry over?
Right?
Prepare presentations on how to make Segye Soju the No. 1 brand in the industry
by Thursday.
The winning team will get the award necklace.
Let's kill it.
Fighting.
My gosh, your makeup is all ruined.
Stop crying, stop.
Jenny, you should be more understanding since you're so nice.
Why should I be understanding?
It's all that bastard's fault.
I'll post on social media that I was bullied at work!
Gosh, don't do that. Please.
That'd only hurt you, okay?
Ahjumma, whose side are you on?
All you do is pretend to care. You damn hag.
- No, no.
- "Ahjumma"?
Didn't you hear what she said?
- Hey, do you think I'm your friend?
- Come on.
I might look young, but I'm at least 20 years older than you, you brat.
Look young, my foot!
You look at least 30 years older.
You're so annoying!
- Gosh...
- Hey, Jenny! Where are you going, Jenny?
Geez, that little brat!
The kids these days...
Seriously!
- Team Leader.
- Yes?
Do you think I look 20, I mean, 30 years older than her?
What's the use of fighting each other?
When our enemy is right there!
Mr. So Eun Ho!
What?
We need to talk for a second.
Why are you suddenly doing this?
I don't know what you're thinking,
but you could've just teamed up with Yu Mi sunbae by yourself.
Why are you dragging us into it too?
What's so bad about giving the Underdog Team a chance to work on a project?
- Sunbae!
- What?
Couldn't you have told me if you had plans like this?
You couldn't even do that between us?
Between us?
What are we?
We are...
We are... We are...
What are we?
Well...
Yes, I'll be there by seven.
See you later, Noona.
"Noona"?
I'll start dating Cha Jeong Woo too then!
Seriously, what's wrong with her?
Okay. Branding 101. Let's start with the marketing research.
One is mean and the other is clueless.
I know, right.
Gosh, seriously. The Girlish Pop-up ended less than a week ago.
Do we have to do this?
I have a show tonight, too.
I agree. I'm against doing overtime.
We're against it!
Okay, okay, okay. We at least need to come together for Jenny,.
Jenny? I don't want to do this even more because of her.
She seriously hurt my feelings.
Come on, don't be like that, Yeong Ae.
Okay, okay. Let's go, let's go! Let's go...
Let's just go home.
I just confirmed this.
Segye Soju is the least popular one.
- I see...
- We'll have another naengmyeon  (cold noodles in broth) .
- Should we clank glasses first, then?
- Geez...
Cheers.
Take your time.
Gosh, it's bitter. Segye Soju is definitely the most bitter.
No way. Princess, you can tell the difference?
My gosh, Unni. Of course. I'm basically a sommelier.
Look at this.
Just Like the Last Time has a bit of sourness to it.
And Salty Dew is a bit sweet toward the end.
But I only drink Seonro is Good Soju these days.
This is the cleanest one.
So, each soju tastes different?
Of course.
You're lying.
Close your eyes. Give me a break...
Unni, have you always been lied to? Come on.
You think I wouldn't know? Shuffle them properly.
Open your eyes.
Let's go.
You little trickster. You can't fool my tongue.
This is Segye Soju.
Daebak.
- Wrong.
- What?
That was Seonro is Good Soju, okay?
What? You're lying.
Seonro Is Good Soju can't be this bad. You're wrong.
Looks like it's difficult for most people to tell them apart by taste.
Why is it not popular, then?
- Please give us a bottle of soju.
- There has to be a reason.
He ordered Segye Soju.
You're right. This is exactly a 4% market share.
Should we ask him why he got Segye Soju?
Shall we?
What?
You scared me. What are you doing?
One, two, three.
- Hello.
We're doing marketing research on the liquor market.
You ordered Segye Soju.
We were wondering why you decided to order it.
Segye Soju?
Geez, what's the deal?
Excuse me. You gave me the leftover one just because I asked for any of them?
I'll get you a Dew instead, then.
Gosh, it's packed.
The inventory is piling up.
We're screwed. Totally screwed.
I'm surprised.
I didn't think you'd ever see me again with your ego.
I'm not the one who wanted to see you.
Is that so?
I don't know who it is, but they're rude.
Did he pick this up from Na Eon?
What's taking so long?
Oh, right...
The one who wanted to see you was Na Eon's boyfriend—
There he comes.
So Eun Ho.
Over here.
You can't come this late after asking me to arrange a meeting.
I guess he's not interested in working with me.
I am... interested.
Okay, this is So Eun Ho.
He's a new hire at Seongsu Agency.
I live with Team Leader Kang Na Eon.
I thought that'd be a more efficient introduction.
What are you suggesting right now?
I'm suggesting you work with me.
We'll relaunch Segye Soju.
As your personal liquor brand, Mr. Nam Yun Hyeok.
Hey, you can't just say that without explaining.
A foreign whiskey brand asked me to be their exclusive model.
Even if you relaunched it,
I won't let you use my face for an unknown geezer soju brand.
Three hundred million won.
If 300 million isn't enough...
- 500 million.
- Are you joking right now?
Looks like you're trying to copy Kang Na Eon.
You can't hire anyone you want just because you'll pay them.
I'm not saying we'd pay you.
I'm telling you to pay us.
- What?
- I know that's still going on.
The thing Na Eon covered up for you earlier this year.
We'll keep that a secret and let you model the relaunch for 500 million.
Hey, you think I'm easy because you're close to Kang Na Eon?
Seriously, what are you two doing?
Hey, So Eun Ho. You went too far, too.
Of course, you're easy.
You get intimidated and act like a dog since you can't handle Kang Na Eon.
- Are you serious, you asshole?
- Aren't we all here for the same reason?
To overthrow Kang Na Eon.
I heard you're Kang Na Eon's boyfriend.
You're taking your lovers' quarrel too far.
Can you really defeat Kang Na Eon?
I'm...
actually...
pretty strong.
I don't play losing games.
I'm not interested in losing, either.
Geez, this asshole...
Geez.
By the way...
you oddly look familiar.
Really?
The way you look at me as if I'm worthless.
It's exactly like Kang Na Eon...
What's that?
Hey.
C-Can we really do this?
Nam Yun Hyeok...
has no way out anyway.
How about you? Are you okay, So Eun Ho?
Hey, So Eun Ho!
Hey!
We're just getting started. Just getting started. Fighting!
Let's get drunk quickly since we're stressed out.
Sounds good. My gosh! You're boosting Segye Soju's sales on your own. Seriously.
- You're unbelievable.
- To be honest, I don't get why people drink.
Wy are you so bad at drinking when you're a working professional, Team Leader?
That's no good!
You're very enthusiastic about this project.
Let's stay enthusiastic. Don't back down.
Don't back down!
Don't back down.
Gosh, what's this?
It's all about not being shy about drinking.
Come here. Here, here. Drink up.
Come on, come on. Drink up.
Gosh, Princess. Princess!
- Drink up. Gosh, good job.
- It's too much for her.
She's drinking just fine.
This is why I drink soju.
- It's tasty.
- Oh? Wait!
I want to go there.
Oh? Isn't that Jenny?
Jenny?
A man? He looks quite a bit older, by the way.
She quit because she was offended. Now she's drinking?
- Geez.
- Really.
Seriously.
I can see why the taxi driver didn't want to come up here.
Gosh, seriously...
Hey, So Eun Ho. That's it, right?
Please say it is!
Gosh, you're so freaking heavy. Seriously!
Okay, okay, okay.
Hey, come on now. When did they take these?
Team Leader Kang is so cute when she's drunk.
I'll post this on social media.
Tell me your ID so I can tag you.
Geez.
Really? You're not answering?
Shit, the battery.
What?
What was that? I'm scared.
Shit. I should go home.
Who's there?
S-Someone was there. What was that?
Shit.
Gosh, who was that?
Who's over there?
I-I saw you j-just now.
Y-You're underestimating me because I'm a woman, right?
I-I'm not just a woman, okay?
T-There's something incredible within me.
Come out! Where are you?
Jeong Woo Sunbae?
"Jeong Woo Sunbae"?
I-I mean, Mr. Cha Jeong Woo?
Mr. Cha?
Hey, hey, your shoes!
The bed...
You're driving me crazy.
Gosh, I'm tired.
Shit.
This doesn't suit him at all.
Gosh, seriously.
What?
I mean, I noticed your hand on mine.
Geez.
Gosh, that reaction makes me feel so sad.
It can't be that bad...
Don't be sad about that. We're men—
What?
I mean, we're bosom buddies.
"B-Bosom buddies"?
Well, best friends. Best friends.
Why do I want to take the subway so badly? I'm off.
Hold on.
I went to the hospital every day.
Before you woke up and afterward.
I was really heartbroken.
That nobody, So Eun Ho, acted like he was your guardian.
Why couldn't I even be your guardian?
Is it him?
The one giving you a hard time?
It's none of your business.
Are you and So Eun Ho serious?
- That's—
- Even though...
I liked you longer than he did?
What?
Don't go.
♫  I'll have no regrets in this moment  ♫
♫  Will you lean in and whisper to me softly please  ♫
♫  The beginning of all of my seasons becomes clearer because of you  ♫
♫  Can you spare me just a glance?  ♫
♫  I'm pouring my heart out  ♫
♫  It's within me now  ♫
♫  The last entry in my diary  ♫
♫  That final period I couldn't write down honestly  ♫
♫  Honestly...  ♫