I think you'd better go.
No, it's okay.
I know you're worried about Team Leader Kang.
Sir, should I take you to the hospital?
No, it's okay.
XU Beauty's new product line that created a buzz with cruelty-free marketing
turned out to be fraudulent. At the headquarters...
The handmade shoe factory.
Did we switch back?
I don't think this is the way.
Follow me...
to the room.
What? Sunbae, w-why the room?
Why am I going to your room?
Strategy meeting.
Or you can live in my body forever if you don't want to.
What?
No! Give me back my handsome face!
You've got to be crazy!
Drive properly, you bastard!
B-Bastard. What's wrong with him? So scary.
Drive faster.
I can't.
This car costs four times my salary. Four times more.
Four times my salary, you mean.
Don't get confused.
You're Kang Na Eon.
Then you're paying for the repair, right?
Talk casually.
- Pardon?
- Don't talk formally to me.
Like friends?
Yeah, like friends.
Listen, buddy. Hey!
I never drive. I'm scared to death right now!
Why don't you drive if you're so good at it?
What am I, your assistant?
You hear me? You bastard.
I'm sorry.
♫  It's over, baby  ♫
What?
Get your act together.
- Rumors said she had a thing with So Eun Ho. I guess it was true.
- What?
They came to work together.
They might wear the same outfit tomorrow.
You guys do it, too.
Carpool.
- Pardon?
Even though you are both married.
No, no. It's not true.
- Daebak.
- It's not true.
- Is it true?
You can't say stuff like that with my face.
Not my style.
Then watch and learn my style.
Okay. You remember what I said last night, right?
I forgot because I was nervous.
- Do you have wrinkles on your brain?
- Come on.
Say only pretty words with a pretty mouth.
Repeat after me.
Take responsibility for everything...
- and do it voluntarily.
I'll join the Underdog Team.
You don't have to start by talking about work.
Are you feeling okay?
Yes.
I-I'm okay.
I'll work hard.
Did she hurt her head when she fell?
I think she's lost it a bit.
Na Eon,
the entire Seongsu Agency will be responsible. It's not just your—
She wants to be responsible on her own. There's no reason to stop her.
She can't be reinstated as the team leader of Team 1 after causing a disturbance.
Don't you agree?
Yes, I agree. I agree.
Not just anyone can take that position.
We have two goals.
Goal 1.
Find the bastard who tried to kill me.
And goal 2 is getting back my position.
Well...
Those aren't our goals. They're both your goals, aren't they?
You used your head for the first time.
If you help me,
I'll put the effort in to switch our bodies back.
That doesn't sound quite right.
Wouldn't you want to get your body back too?
No, I don't.
It might be easier to become an executive in a male body.
All right! Then this is my house! Yes!
Where should we start?
First of all, join the Underdog Team as the team leader.
That way, we can be together for 24/7
and freely look for the culprit.
By the way, if I work 24/7...
do I get paid overtime?
I'll be in charge of the Underdog Team for now and work hard.
Looks like you finally understand the situation now that the video has come out.
But they do say that love for your colleagues is love for your country.
I'll give you a project even though you're on the Underdog Team since we go way back.
I'm different than you.
W-Whoa, thank you.
Sex toy?
Show us what you've got.
Since she caused a disturbance,
- her salary will be reduced for six months and she'll become the team leader for the Underdog Team.
- Gosh!
I quit.
Thank you all for everything up until now.
Thank you and I love you and I'll miss you. I love—
Rex, you're not done paying for the purse.
Please go back to your seat.
Gosh. Damn you, Chanel.
What do we do now, Eun Ho?
You can't act like the team leader when Team Leader Kang comes.
What a pity.
I never pretended to be the team leader.
Gosh, give me a break.
"Do this. Do that."
You were so sexy when you said that.
Let's stop joking around and pay attention.
You know how intense Team Leader Kang can be.
Sunbae! Sunbae!
Sunbae...
What?
Gosh, it hurts.
That son of a bitch.
Wow. They say the job makes the person.
Being a team leader is a nice position.
Gosh, it's so soft.
Hold still, please.
The photo turned out so nicely.
It turned out nicely.
What's with Team Leader Kang?
Why is she so dopey?
And what happened to her awful personality?
That's what I'm saying.
I guess the bitch got a new personality.
Do you prefer the left or the right?
Right.
Definitely the right.
What do you think, Eun Ho honey?
If she suggests a team lunch...
can I run away?
Whoa, why did it come out so nicely?
Check your messenger!
Being a team leader is cool.
Awful personality?
The bitch?
Take a break. Relax...
My gosh! Hey! Why did you invite Team Leader Kang?
Pardon?
You invited me to the team group chat. Thank you!
You're welcome.
Let's have lunch together later.
I'd love that.
Do you want to go to a place I know?
There's a 5,000-won  (~$3.75)  all-you-can-eat Korean place nearby.
They're really amazing.
- I'm definitely coming!
- Sounds good! Sounds good!
- Yay.
- You're the best.
My goodness.
I'm so happy.
You ruined your image.
That's why you shouldn't have said "son of a bitch" using my mouth.
Get to work.
I can't believe this is what you prepared.
Well, which part do you not like?
Everything! All of it!
Start over from the beginning.
- Okay.
Didn't you say you would take care of Kang Na Eon?
Our current prime suspect is...
Do Yu Mi.
What?
Team Leader Do?
Come on, seriously. You're saying she tried to kill someone because she was blinded by jealousy?
Just to get a team leader position?
It's not just a team leader position. It's the most powerful position at Seongsu Agency.
Okay, okay.
There are those type of people...
who would do anything to get what they want.
Wow, were you describing yourself just now?
I'm sorry.
You said you used to be friends.
It's normal for friends to fight while growing up.
I don't have friends.
I can tell.
Gosh, this is no good.
I should become your friend.
Give me your hand.
Here.
Keep it, keep it. Keep it.
I'm sorry, but please don't fall for me.
Hey, hey, hey!
You haven't even eaten today.
Coffee. Alcohol. Coffee. Alcohol.
Are you trying to destroy my body?
I can focus better this way—
Geez. This is no good.
- Let's go.
- Go where?
Let's go. Bring your card with you.
- I don't want to.
- Let's get going.
- Come with me right now.
- Where are we going?
We're just going somewhere.
- It's raining.
- Geez, it's raining.
It's nearby. Let's go.
I'll make you a scallion pancake since it's raining.
- Flour and...
- Pay with this.
So Eun Ho?
Gosh, daebak. What's this?
Is this a Black Card?
I've never seen one in person.
Handle it carefully.
That's not enough. That's not enough.
Wait for me, Sunbae.
Gosh, Sunbae.
Listen to me.
Whether we catch the culprit or our bodies switch back,
we need to eat before all that.
We can just order in.
Do you know how much disposable containers hurt the earth?
Why does my stomach keep hurting?
What's the date today?
Today is the 18th.
That's it.
Come on, it can't be.
It's not true, right? Sunbae, come on.
I'm a man. It can't be, right?
The dressing isn't too bad.
I also made the dressing myself.
Don't be gross and eat someone else's food.
What? Why is that yours?
And it's not like we're strangers.
You're me, and I'm you. You know?
Gosh, my stomach.
How long does this last?
A week at the most.
Just hang in there.
You've been through a lot, Sunbae.
For living like this all this time.
Eun Ho.
What is it?
So, what will you do about the branding?
Gosh, seriously, you're such a workaholic.
You acted all superior, talking about branding and sincerity when we worked on XU.
But you don't seem confident now.
What are you good at, exactly?
I'm really good at naming plants.
- This one is—
- That's completely useless.
We need to do a great job with this one.
If we shake up Do Yu Mi when she doesn't expect it,
she'll crumble easily.
So you're certain Yu Mi Sunbae is the culprit, right?
No, it would've been impossible by herself.
There's definitely someone else.
When Do Yu Mi crumbles,
they'll show themselves.
Shit!
What's wrong with you?
Okay, I'll give it my best.
But I don't know much about that market though.
What kind of marketer only does what they're good at? Huh?
Geez...
Meet with the CEO first.
The brand identity ultimately comes from the creator of the brand.
Where are you going?
What do you care?
The brand identity...
ultimately comes from the creator of the brand.
That's exactly what you said, Da Eun.
For sexy and passionate women,
I take pride in making toys that give them satisfying orgasms.
So, I hope that brand image comes through.
A very racy,
very secretive,
and private...
world of our own.
Yes, racy and secretive.
Gosh, I'm so curious.
Gosh, I hate bright lights.
Is the store currently in the basement?
Women tend to be a bit embarrassed about buying sex toys.
- Don't you agree?
- Pardon? No.
I'm not sure. I don't really use stuff like that.
My husband has a lot of stamina.
I'm the mother of five children.
- I have five boys.
- My gosh!
Unni. TMI. TMI.
- Is it?
- Seriously.
By chance, if it helps to go to the store,
would you like to come with me?
Our hidden,
suppressed,
and secretive desires that we have...
to the uncharted territory.
- Wow.
- Uncharted territory?
Sounds good.
Team Leader?
Let's go to the uncharted territory.
This is even KC-certified.
It's a product that guarantees safety.
Since it's a product that you insert,
it blocks electromagnetic waves,
and it safely takes you...
to paradise!
Amazing.
So I call this one Kkaebi Kkaebi.
As in Dokkaebi  (Goblin) .
- Wow. Kkaebi Kkaebi? Kkaebi Kkaebi.
- Kkaebi Kkaebi.
Kkaebi Kkaebi, I missed you.
Kkaebi Kkaebi, Dokkaebi.
I like the name.
Rex, take notes so we can create visuals later.
- I'm checking them out.
- Look at this.
Yeong Ae, please make a list of product characteristics and prices.
And Jenny...
- Tricky fox and cat.
- My gosh, my gosh.
Me, too.
You should work hard, too.
- Isn't it cool?
- Eun Ho!
Are you still pretending to be the team leader when Team Leader Kang is here?
You're right.
Mr. So. Please be careful.
Aren't you going to answer?
It's because he's immature.
He feels embarrassed and flustered right now. Right...
Okay. I need to go teach him a lesson.
Gosh, go easy. Go easy. Don't be like that.
Oh, my God!
Mr. So.
I did okay, didn't I, Sunbae?
Can't you compliment me?
I even have cramps in your place.
Did you take the medicine?
I took two earlier.
Good job.
In any case,
you created clear roles for the team members.
I thought you didn't care about them at all.
I don't care. I'm just giving them tasks that suit them.
Yes, yes, of course.
What's that now?
Where did he go?
Wow, what's all this?
What?
Gosh, I got spooked.
Gosh, you scared me!
What's going on?
Did you run over because you were worried about me?
Wow! They have stuff like this, too.
How fascinating.
Hey, take it off.
- It's done.
- What are you doing...
Hey, take it off.
Take it off.
I'll take it off if you behave.
- Take it off.
- I don't want to.
- Take it off, I said.
I don't want to. Here, take it.
♫  My mouth was full, baby  ♫
♫  A feeling that lingered for too long  ♫
♫  Intense bitter, yet sweeter  ♫
♫  That's right, in the thrill of the moment  ♫
♫  Everything's changed, I don't know what to do   ♫
♫  I just crinkle my nose, and I feel you for awhile  ♫
♫  If you know you, Bae  ♫
♫  How could I not love you?  ♫
♫  Like in a dream  ♫
♫  I'm afraid to forget everything  ♫
♫  Even if I cover my eyes, even if I try to shake it off  ♫