(Characters, places, organizations, and events in this show are fictional.)
Thank you.
Dr. Prim, when did you first attend an operation?
It was during my first year.
But I didn't get any hands-on.
I spent a while doing other things in there,
like stitches and holding things in place.
When will Professor Archawin let me attend an operation?
It's hard to answer that.
It takes time. He...
If he believes you can do it, you will get in.
Yen, please get the dishes in the back of the kitchen.
- Okay. - Thanks.
Yen!
- Yes, Aoy? - Here.
I brought you some curry. I couldn't sell it out.
Have some.
- Let me pay for it today. - No.
I'm giving some out to everyone.
If you have a family,
I would give you more.
- Don't worry. - Thanks.
Goodbye.
(GMC Medical Center)
Did the patient take NSAIDs, Prim?
Prim?
Did the patient take NSAIDs?
Yes.
Okay.
- Stitch up the wound. - Okay.
Professor, do we need ECMO?
Thank you again.
I will do my best.
Prim?
Boy, take over the stitching.
Okay.
Tired from breathing, throwing up, and unable to eat?
Who taught you to write a case review like this? Are you writing a fiction?
Exhaustion, difficulty breathing, vomiting.
These are the words to use. Fix it.
Yes, Professor.
Hello, Sandee!
Hello, ma'am.
How are you? Does your stomach still hurt?
- It doesn't hurt anymore. - Good girl!
I have some stickers for you today. Do you want some?
- I do. - So...
I'll leave it with Mommy.
- Okay. - This is for her.
- Thank you. - Give it to her after she takes her meds.
Goodbye.
Next case.
Khongkwan, female, age six.
She's getting her fourth session of chemotherapy.
Professor Supansa, from Pediatric Hematology, wants her to be on Port A.
She's staying here for pre-op.
Her parents are at work. They will be here in the evening.
They asked the nurses to keep an eye on her.
Khongkwan, good morning!
Did her parents take her to work?
(Episode 5: Gift)
Play your card. Come on.
If you don't, I will.
Take this!
I have protection against werewolves.
Who dropped this card? Nine, did you?
I don't think it's me, bro.
Not me.
Are you sure?
If you're sure, take me out.
I can choose not to.
Do it!
This guy dropped the card. I saw it.
Then you're mine. I won't hesitate now, bro!
What's that? Doc, why did you peek at me?
And you even told him! See? I lost now.
I really saw it. You snuck that card into the play.
Let me play with you.
We won't!
You're telling everything. That's not fun.
Go play with that one.
She wants to play hide and seek.
Wait a second.
Can I have that back, please?
I don't want to get an injection.
Do you like sea lions?
Oong Oong is a seal.
A seal goes "oong oong!"
That's not a seal.
It doesn't have ears.
That's a sea lion.
It has ear canals
and fins.
Its fins can rotate.
It can walk on land.
And it doesn't go "oong oong."
It goes...
You're so funny, Doctor Sea Lion.
Do you know how they use their fins to walk?
(Dr. Archawin Akephaiboon)
Mr. Arun has been diagnosed with
chronic kidney disease-induced anemia.
Basically, you will have to undergo blood transfusions regularly
because your kidneys produce insufficient hormones.
What should I do next, Doctor?
I recommend a kidney transplant.
If it's successful, you can stop doing dialysis and blood transfusions.
Do you have a child or sibling who can donate?
- He... - I don't.
Doctor.
Put me on the waiting list.
Okay, we will
need you to undergo further checkups.
That information is needed
for the waiting list registration.
Yes, thanks, Doctor.
(Shoan, where are you?)
Do you have my coffee?
- I got it a while ago. - (We're looking for Khongkwan, )
- (a patient from Surgery...) - Come quickly! I'm about to sleep!
Silence, please.
- Why? - (We're looking for Khongkwan Penkrajang, )
(a patient from Surgery, please contact)
(the Information Counter. Thank you.)
(We're looking for Khongkwan Penkrajang, )
(a patient from Surgery, please contact)
(the Information Counter. Thank you.)
(We're looking for Khongkwan...)
Gosh, kids these days.
What's wrong with them?
Your veins are all stiff.
I can't find your veins. Stay still, please.
- I'll do it for you. It won't hurt. - No. I don't want to...
- I don't want to! - Come on.
- It's just a second. - My girl!
Khongkwan.
I don't want to. It hurts.
It's fine.
What's your relationship with the patient?
I'm her dad.
Come on. I'll do it for you. It won't hurt. I promise.
May I do it for you?
Khongkwan.
Let me give you an IV to boost your power.
Before I start, I'd like you to hold my hand.
If you squeeze my hand hard,
you will feel less pain, okay?
Because I'll share your pain.
Squeeze me hard.
Harder.
It's done.
You're right.
Professor, hello.
Thanks so much. I can take this from here.
Hello, Mr. Aof.
Hello.
You look nice today.
When I found out
she was missing from the hospital,
I left the show and rushed to come here.
Khongkwan's dad, you look so gorgeous.
Were you at a cosplay event?
Or are you actually a transgender?
Shoan...
Sorry.
I'll go and round the ward.
How could you say that?
Do not ask anyone that question. It's rude!
I was curious.
It wasn't okay to ask it?
It's quite a sensitive question.
Do you know the phrase LGBTQ+?
Yeah. Mr. Aof is a drag queen. That's...
Sometimes, he dresses the way he does for his shows.
I heard LGBTQ+
can have children.
They just come in many forms.
For example, adopted children,
biological children,
and artificial insemination.
Which one is this case?
Let's just say
these questions
are too sensitive to ask.
Don't ask unless it's your close friend or it's necessary.
Understood.
- Don't ask unless it's a close friend or necessary. - Yeah.
Don't ask unless it's a close friend or necessary.
(Nurse)
Here, Uncle.
I'm sorry. I've been here for a while but haven't come to see you.
You don't have to apologize.
Next time, don't bring a big gift.
How was your project?
Wellness tourism, right? How is it going?
I'm trying to cut a deal with the Middle East.
I also need to raise awareness about this kind of business.
Uncle.
Now that I'm here, can I run something by you?
Of course.
I wonder if you received an offer from A&R Medicine.
I think it feels strange somehow.
How is it strange?
Hi, Copter.
Are you calling me because you miss me
- or do you want your present? - (Dad!)
Uncle Anat is taking me to Phuket for my birthday.
(Please come here soon.)
Phuket?
(I'm on my shift.)
I can't stay out of town overnight.
I want you with us.
I want to go too.
It's just too sudden.
It's too late to trade shifts.
You know what?
When you get back, let's unbox your present together at home.
(Copter.)
(Why would you bother your dad?)
(He's helping me out at work.)
Right.
(Go to your mom.)
So, how did it go with the Director?
I talked to Director Sirin.
She insisted that Professor Prapas has to decide.
If possible, I would like you to come in yourself.
Your words matter more than mine.
(Fine. I'll do that.)
(Let's see how hard it is to negotiate)
(with this Dr. Prapas.)
Right. Please take care of Copter.
(Suchat Jitdee)
(Status: Waiting for Donor)
(Status: Deceased)
Prim.
Is everything okay?
You seem out of it lately.
No. I'm fine.
I'm just tired, I guess.
Professor, wait.
Come on.
Can I not go in?
Don't you know? Ever since your DOT case,
you haven't been able to focus, Prim.
- Get in. - It's not that bad. I'll get better.
Prim.
You're a doctor.
That won't be the last time.
You have to be strong before you can help others.
Just get in there.
Is something the matter? Why do you all look so stressed?
- Good afternoon. - Hi.
It's nothing, May.
Prim is having a little trouble.
Do it.
Let's go.
That's an order.
When did you get here?
A while ago.
Why are you being so harsh with Dr. Prim?
She was so scared that she got pale.
I have to be harsh with her, or she won't do it.
I'm sorry.
What about you?
How did it go with Professor Prapas?
It was good.
We talked briefly, and I asked him about A&R.
A&R?
Yes. He said they were Dr. Phruek's relatives.
- Oh yeah, Win? - Yes?
Next month, my dad is coming back from Australia.
What would you say now?
This time you need to go to dinner with my dad.
You can't say no, okay?
Okay.
Good.
You're the best.
(The doors are closing.)
Mr. Aof, hi.
- Oh, Doctor. - Yeah.
Hi.
Khongkwan's dad, good morning.
Morning.
You look different today. I barely recognized you.
Yes.
We have met twice already. Are we close friends now?
How did you have Khongkwan?
Khongkwan is not my child.
She's my best friend's daughter.
My friend's boyfriend found out she was pregnant,
and he just left her.
My friend and I
had been raising her together since she was born.
Soon after Khongkwan turned two,
her mom was killed in a car accident.
She doesn't have a relative.
That's why I decided to raise her myself.
Khongkwan
is a gift, as her name suggests.
My childhood dream
is to have a child.
That's why I thought
I would do my best to raise her.
Doctor, will my girl be cured?
I've looked at her overall condition.
Khongkwan is
responding to the chemotherapy really well.
She's also getting treatment at a young age.
She will be fine.
Sometimes, I can't help but wonder.
Could it be that because I raised her,
she has such bad luck?
Because I'm not the right gender.
That can't be the truth.
White blood cell cancer
is caused by the over-production of blast cells.
Your gender, no matter what it is,
doesn't affect her good or bad luck.
You're right, Doctor.
But still, people think that
a gay man
can't possibly be a good father.
You're a good person.
You love Khongkwan.
That must mean you're a good father.
They're so cute.
Dad, I need to pee.
You need to pee?
Me too.
Let's go to the bathroom.
(Dinner with Dad. Friday at five at Buraphakin. Don't be late.
Start your day in a bad mood, huh?
What bad mood?
What's wrong?
Did you have a fight?
What fight?
Did you forget? May is my friend.
You're upset you have to see her dad, right?
If you don't want to work for him, just be honest.
Your friend doesn't listen to me.
- Want me to talk to her for you? - Hey! Don't.
The surgeons from Group B this year?
A few of them are interesting.
Especially
- Dr. Shoan. - What?
- Shoan, of all people? - Yeah.
Why? He does a good job. He pays attention. He can talk to kids.
- He's nothing like what you said. - No.
You haven't seen him at his worst.
If he panics inside an OR,
that will be huge.
Someone like Shoan should never have a scalpel in his hands.
- Really? - Yeah.
Interesting.
- Really interesting. - Hey.
- What? - How is he interesting?
You know me. Saying no makes me want to try.
- I have to go. - I'm not saying no.
- Bye. - I'm warning you.
I got work, okay?
- I'm warning you. Listen. - See you.
- Hey! - I'm listening, okay?
When you get inside, check all the equipment.
Yes, Professor.
- Prim. - Yes?
You're assisting Professor Metta, aren't you?
Yes, Professor.
Then go.
For this case,
I'll let Dr. Shoan handle it.
Am I allowed inside, Professor?
Are you a surgeon or not?
I am.
You're a surgeon. You belong in an operating room.
Yay!
Please excuse me.
Shoan, do your best.
Thank you, Professor.
Yay.
This is unorganized.
Hmm.
Blade, please.
Clamp.
Retractor.
Pull it up.
Give me the port.
The port fits in perfectly.
She's stitched up.
Let's test the port.
Yes.
Do you want to try sticking the port?
I do.
Okay. Come on.
Shoan, feel it gently with your hands.
There are three points in a port.
You need to put this needle
in the middle of those three points.
Stick it deep in the base of the port.
Then we'll try sucking out some blood.
If we can suck it out, it's a success.
- Yes. - Hmm.
- I found it. - Hmm.
Okay.
Professor Irin.
We have been informed of an emergency case.
Dr. Shoan is needed for assistance.
Okay. Got it.
You can go and help them. I got this one.
Yes, Professor.
Okay.
Which Professor needs my assistance?
Professor Archawin over there.
You need my help with an emergency case?
I called you here for nothing.
Did you lie to me?
I just don't want you in surgery.
Why?
Because it's too dangerous, Shoan.
Both to yourself and to the patient.
Then when can I perform surgery?
Dr. Prim said if I prove myself to you that I can do it,
you will allow me to perform one.
Shoan.
As long as you have this condition,
you can't perform surgery.
It's too risky.
I was born this way.
There's no cure.
I can't be cured.
I can't be cured of it, Professor.
But I'll prove to you
that I can do everything like the others.
(Buddhist prayers)
I thought you wouldn't come.
I was hesitating, actually.
Professor.
If I had had more time for him that day,
listened to him more,
and not believed in myself too much,
all of this wouldn't have happened.
Win.
Do you still blame yourself?
Think about this. If Wee is looking at you right now,
would he want his brother to have this idea?
That was an accident.
I think Wee would be happy
that his beloved only brother
acknowledged him and believed that he could take care of himself.
How did that turn out?
I don't want that to happen again.
I don't want you to go through what I went through.
Professor.
- Professor. - Give me Mr. Arun's case.
- Good morning. - Good morning, Mr. Arun.
- Morning. - Please sit down.
Please sit down.
It's good you're here. I have good news for you.
Mr. Arun, you have a donor.
- Really? - Yes.
You're really lucky, Mr. Arun. Others usually wait for months.
May I know the name of the donor?
I really want to thank him.
Well, legally speaking,
the donor has the right to reveal
or not to reveal their identity.
- In this case, they... - Doctor.
I heard that organs from someone outside the bloodline
would be rejected by the body
more severely than organs from a relative. Is that true?
In reality, transplanting from someone in the bloodline or not
does not make that much of a difference.
In both cases, we will have to check
the compatibility of both the donor and recipient's blood and organs.
However, the side effect in most cases is
how the patient's body responds to the new organ.
Sometimes, the patient's body doesn't respond
to the newly transplanted organ.
- Well... - Thank you so much, Doctor.
That's enough.
The doctor said it's fine, so it's fine.
Thank you again. Thank you.
- Right. - Congratulations.
Aof.
Aof, is that you, son?
Emergency case!
- Wake up! - Don't tease me with something so real.
How much longer are you sleeping?
Come on!
Dear Miss Prim...
What?
Buy me a coffee, please.
No!
Please, come on.
It's too often.
Can't you order a delivery?
Do that, okay?
Should I go and buy it for you?
No, thanks, Auntie. This guy's lazy.
See? He's growing roots.
Are you a new cleaner?
I haven't seen you before.
I am.
If you need help, you can tell me.
Thank you so much.
You will pay, right? What do you want? I'll order something.
Just a black coffee.
No sugar? Large or small?
Okay. What else?
I can't do anything. I'm too drowsy.
Does Dr. Prapas use this room too?
He doesn't.
Only residents use this room.
My name is Prim. This is Nick.
We also have Dr. Pleum,
Dr. Mummim, and Dr. Shoan. That's all of us.
There's a Dr. Shoan here?
Yes.
See?
I told you. Shoan is an unusual name.
She didn't say it was an unusual name.
- You're a bully. - Just order the coffee.
Aof.
Mom.
Why don't you visit us at all, Aof?
Do you think I can?
Your dad was emotional.
He's been looking for you ever since that day.
Your dad has chronic kidney disease.
He needs a kidney transplant.
The hospital actually said we got a donor.
But I heard that if it's from outside the family, it's
more dangerous to the recipient.
I know I have no right to ask you this.
I'm sorry, son.
Your dad is really suffering.
Can you help him, Aof?
So now I have some value to you, Mom?
If Dad knows it's me,
he probably doesn't want it.
Could you please forgive us and start over?
Your dad and I never stopped loving you.
You love me, Mom?
If you love me, why did you let Dad hit me?
He kicked me out like a dog.
Why did you let him treat me like that?
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
We can just forget all of that.
Let's forget about donating too.
Just come back and be the family we used to be, please.
Please?
Are we really a family, Mom?
Yes?
Khongkwan?
Daddy will be right there.
Wait for me, please.
Daddy?
I have to go, Mom.
Khongkwan, time for your meal.
Don't chew too fast, okay?
Okay. Another one.
Okay.
Hello there.
You're Khongkwan, right?
I am.
You're so cute.
Khongkwan.
This is your grandma.
She's my mommy.
Hello, Grandma.
You're such a good girl.
Here.
I brought you a teddy bear. Is it cute?
- Cute, right? - Thank you, Grandma.
Excuse me.
This is Doctor Sea Lion.
You have a new friend today.
My grandma brought it for me.
May I check on Khongkwan, please?
Yes, Doctor. Please proceed.
She's not your real daughter,
but you're a really good father to her.
She might not be as healthy as other kids,
but I love her so much.
I hope that someday,
she can run around like other kids.
As a parent,
that's all I ask for.
Mom.
Yesterday, you mentioned Dad's kidney.
- I... - Yupha!
What do you think you're doing?
Don't tell me you're still messing with my darn kidney.
- What? - She is, Dad.
Why would you yell at her?
Don't interfere!
I don't want anything from you.
Don't donate anything to me.
I know that well.
You see, Mom?
No matter how much time passed,
he's still embarrassed by a queer son like me.
How could he accept my kidney?
No, my son. Stop.
I'll accept my luck.
Leave us alone.
Go do whatever you want.
Just go!
Go!
Yupha.
Let's go home.
- Wait, honey. - Hey!
Dad!
Mister, is this yours?
Khongkwan, say hello to your grandpa.
Mister... No, Grandpa.
You're my Dad's dad?
Hello.
Honey.
What's wrong, honey?
Please sit down.
Thank you.
It looks like your BP has dropped.
You need to rest for ten minutes.
Are you okay?
Why did you do that?
How could you ask that of him?
I kicked him out of our house!
Why did you kick your own son out?
Because the thing that he is.
I was afraid he'd get bullied.
I was afraid others would be disgusted by what he is.
I wanted him to be a man.
I wanted him to be cured of being gay.
Being gay is not an illness.
It's not something to be cured.
Also,
if you consider good things
that come without you asking for as good luck,
then you're lucky.
Your son is a good person.
He is a great father.
Let's go home.
You're still too weak.
I'm not allowing you to go home.
You need a thorough diagnosis.
Shoan. As long as you
have this condition,
I will never allow a doctor in your condition
to operate on a patient. You can't perform surgery. Do you understand?
I was afraid others would be disgusted by what he is.
I was born this way.
I wanted him to be cured of being gay.
There's no cure.
- I can't be cured. - Oh no! What have you done?
Why are you such a bad boy? I'm working myself to death, don't you know?
I understand that Professor Win is worried Shoan would do something weird.
Shoan probably doesn't feel anything with that, but
there are many better ways to deal with him.
So I...
I came here to talk to you.
If you say Shoan doesn't feel anything,
I would say you're wrong.
He just doesn't know
what he's feeling.
He probably feels it more than we do.
I met him as a boy.
If he feels he loves or likes something,
(he'll develop it as his skill, )
(and incredibly so.)
Oh no! What have you done?
- Why do you keep causing problems? - Ma'am. Calm down.
How can I be calm?
(He is talented.)
(He possesses mental capability beyond ordinary people.)
(What kind of a six-year-old boy)
(would be able to draw those things?)
(But still, )
(what Shoan has, )
(even his own family)
(doesn't understand.)
(As a little kid he was back then, )
how could he have understood?
Is this why you're confident in Shoan?
I wouldn't say I'm confident.
I just believe in him.
All Shoan needs is someone who believes in him
and gives him a chance.
Win is well aware of that,
but he maintains his bias
because of his younger brother's incident.
It's fine.
I'll figure this out.
I appreciate it, Prim,
for telling me.
And thank you for helping Shoan.
Sure.
Dad, I want this hairstyle.
Which one?
Wow! This one, like her?
I'll give you that hair.
I'm sorry.
Wait for a while.
I'll give you that hair.
Wait a second.
I'll put this on you.
This wig
makes you cute in a different way.
Does Grandpa not like you, Dad?
No.
Maybe
I was a naughty boy.
That's why he always raises his voice with me.
Your blood test is okay now. You can go home tomorrow.
Yes, Doctor.
You're not naughty at all.
You're really kind.
You're sweeter than my Oong.
Khongkwan, sweetie.
Khongkwan.
Khongkwan...
I...
I'm really happy
that you keep giving me support.
I love you.
I love you too.
If you love me,
kiss my forehead one time.
Okay!
I'm happy.
You're getting a transplant today. Won't you tell our son?
There's no need.
Don't bother him.
See you on the other side.
Grandma!
Khongkwan.
Good morning, ma'am.
Hi. Morning.
You guys are...
We're Aof's friends.
Yeah? And...
Why are you here?
We're here to support Aof.
Support Aof?
What's wrong with him?
My dad is a superhero.
Actually, Aof told us not to tell you.
He's donating a kidney to his dad.
That's why he asked us to be with Khongkwan when he's in there.
Gosh, kids these days.
Bew.
Dr. Prim said
Mr. Arun Chaichana
will undergo a checkup for a kidney transplant.
These are his kidney results...
Now that we told you,
we should mention that he isn't doing this
because you asked him to.
Can you help him, Aof?
So now I have some value to you, Mom?
If Dad knows it's me,
he probably doesn't want it.
Are you ready to donate?
I'm ready.
What organ would you like to donate?
- I'm donating a kidney. - I don't want anything from you.
Don't donate anything to me.
No matter how much time passed,
he's still embarrassed by a queer son like me.
Please don't cry, Grandma.
(GMC Medical Center - 50th Anniversary)
Khongkwan.
Have you said goodbye to your friends here?
I have.
We looked at her. She's really stable. Also, we got you an appointment.
Come again next month for a follow-up, okay?
- Thank you so much, Doctor. - You're welcome.
Khongkwan, don't hug Daddy too hard. You're hurting him.
- Oh? - Whoa, Nut! It's not that bad.
I made it!
Doctor Sea Lion.
I want to be a fish.
Hey, be quiet. This is a hospital.
It's okay.
Are you feeling fine now?
Yes, Doctor. Thank you so much.
Khongkwan, say goodbye to Dr. Shoan
and Dr. Prim.
Goodbye, Dr. Prim.
Goodbye.
Bye-bye, Doctor Oong!
Oong!
Okay! Let's go home. We need to beat the traffic.
Let's go.
Come on up.
See you next month, Khongkwan.
- Come on, guys. Let's go. - Come with us.
Grandpa, Grandma, good afternoon.
Good afternoon, Khongkwan.
Are you all right, son?
Do you feel any side effects?
No, Mom.
Goodbye, Mom.
Hey.
Bring my granddaughter over for dinner sometimes.
You all can come.
Thank you.
Yes, Dad.
Are you still playing your role?
Don't you have work to do?
Blow it.
Why do I have to blow it?
Today is Nick's birthday, right?
And now, he left to party with his friends.
So, blow it.
Why does it have to be me?
Fine. Don't. I'll blow it myself.
I will.
Are you feeling better?
About what?
Well, forget it.
You got it on your lips.
Excuse me.
It's like I got a new baby brother at almost 30. There's still more.
Hello, Professor.
Oh! I'm on my way.
Okay. I'll be there.
Professor Win needs me. I haven't put this away.
I will do it for you.
Thanks a lot. I'll leave it to you.
I have to go.
Doctor, it's okay.
I'll get it for you.
It's okay. I need to do this myself.
Shoan.
We got a case in the ER.
Doctor, you should go.
I can handle this.
Please go.
Thank you.
Dr. Pleum, wait for me!
Stop causing problems!
I'm working myself to death!
You want me to die soon, don't you?
Why must my son be flawed?
I don't know what's wrong with him!
Happy birthday to Nick!
- Nick is having his party there, right? - Someone got shot!
Professor Prapas, please try these out.
- Thank you so much. - Your hands are shaking.
Close the wound, or we will increase the dose of anesthetic.
No child would remember the mother who left him, right?
I can't stop thinking that Win's cheating on me.
I also know who's in love with Dr. Prim.