♪ Sleep on the Ferris wheel ♪
♪ See the whale on the cloud ♪
♪ Growing old slowly ♪
♪ The pumpkin carriage
travels past the rainbow bridge ♪
♪ The prince gets me to sleep ♪
♪ The flower is gonna eat the castle ♪
♪ Wake up and see the crystal slippers ♪
♪ Covered with butterflies ♪
♪ How can I see you ♪
♪ Oh babe ♪
♪ Close the eyes ♪
♪ Decide in the dream ♪
♪ Sweet dreams ♪
♪ Who is the leading role ♪
♪ Because I love you ♪
♪ Just only for you ♪
♪ My heart is so good ♪
♪ Let’s stay in the dream ♪
♪ Oh ho ♪
♪ You just only for you ♪
♪ Come and hold my hand ♪
♪ Oh ho love ♪
♪ In your heart there’s a monster ♪
♪ And a gentle universe ♪
♪ Let’s go my love ♪
♪ Let’s go ahead together ♪
♪ You just only for you ♪
♪ Oh ho ♪
♪ Let’s go forever ♪
♪ Oh ho love ♪
♪ Because I love you ♪
♪ Just only for you ♪
♪ My heart is so good ♪
♪ I’ll be with you Oh ho ♪
♪ You just only for you ♪
♪ Oh ho ♪
♪ You’re holding my hand ♪
♪ Oh ho love ♪
♪ In your heart there’s a monster ♪
♪ And a gentle universe ♪
♪ Let’s go my love ♪
♪ Let’s go ahead together ♪
♪ You just only for you ♪
♪ Oh ho ♪
♪ Let’s go forever ♪
♪ Love ♪
= Sweet Dreams =
= Episode 10 =
As it goes,
best friends share happiness
and hardship.
I did a rough math,
there are 36 toilets
in this building
and I just finished 6 of them.
Now there are
30 left.
So if we three
can work together,
I’m sure we can finish it up
before dark.
Let’s do it together.
Hello, Miss Zhou?
Urgent meeting?
You won’t start without me?
Your phone is upside down.
Okay, I’ll be right back.
Qi, I just remember that
I need interview
a new employee later.
Oh, my shit memory.
I’ll go get prepared.
Doesn’t anyone of you
still have conscience?
We’re best friends!
Fine.
This is the flow for today’s program.
I have double checked.
No problem.
The host’s question outline
will be sent to us later.
Are you preparing
for tomorrow’s interview, Mr. Bo?
Mr. Wen fought for this opportunity
to get me on TV,
of course I should get well prepared.
You’re welcome.
We’re all for the company’s good.
Well,
I’ll leave you to it.
You go on.
Please.
Mr. Bo,
about the program,
do you need think it over?
I always think Wen Guangqi
has bad intentions.
Isn’t he up to something?
It’s a good chance
for the publicity of our company.
I won’t give it up.
As for Wen Guangqi’s purpose,
we will find out tomorrow.
Let’s go.
Hi.
Chomper,
wait for me and see.
I’ve done a lot homework on
Seven Heroes and Five Gallants.
I don’t believe I can’t defeat you.
♪ Kaifeng got one Justice Bao ♪
♪ He only believes law by law ♪
♪ Brothers come and help him ♪
♪ Wang Chao and Ma Han side by side ♪
♪ Rat Zuantian is light as a swallow ♪
♪ Rat Chedi is a good man ♪
♪ Rat Chuanshan has  strong arms ♪
Who the hell are you?
You finally know to ask who I am
when you wake up.
I am
clever and swift,
strong and skilled,
bold and brave,
just and righteous,
con…
complicated and changeable.
No, that’s not me.
What’s important is,
you and I are
deadly enemies.
I’m that indomitable man.
Bai Yutang is my name!
Shocked by my name?
I’ve defeated you in two rounds.
Tell me, Zhan Zhao,
are you scared of me?
Never heard of you.
Never?
Okay, I’ll show you
what I’m capable of today.
I never expected,
the powerful Zhan Zhao
could have such a wretched day.
A little sacrifice
is nothing to me
to see you’re still
alive and kicking.
Don’t you think you saved my life
so I’ll show mercy on you.
If you haven’t fooled me
again and again,
do I need to set a trap
to get you?
I’ll let you know
you’re messing with the wrong girl.
Are you afraid now?
Thinking of I could be
buried in flames,
yes, I am a little afraid.
Why didn’t you say earlier?
You! You!
Don’t, don’t!
Can you untie me first?
Sorry,
I never thought this coming.
It’s all fake, anyway.
Your eyes close and open again,
it’ll be all gone.
Goodbye.
Hey, untie me!
Bye.
Come back!
Damn rat!
How’s the fire so real?
Is Chomper all right?
It’s a dream, anyway.
Be a hero.
You all right?
Why did you come back?
Maybe I am
out of my mind.
Come on.
How do you feel? Are you injured?
= On Air =
Okay.
Thank you for sharing
the entrepreneurial story with us.
We’ll bring you
more exciting content
after advertisement.
Cut!
This is the last link.
As of now, everything is going well.
Do we think too much?
I don’t know why,
I feel uneasy today.
That’s because you always
worry too much,
like a paranoid.
Hope so.
But as long as Bo Hai’s eyes
are not recovered,
I can’t be relieved.
All staff in place,
we’re ready to start.
Wang, the producer
just asked us
to add an extra link.
Please ask the two florists
compete on floriculture.
Both of them
are masters in the field.
Qi, Qi?
Come and watch this.
Hurry up, it’s on.
What?
Come on.
I heard that these two masters’ floral skills
not only have decorative effect,
but in some extent…
So tiresome.
Now I have to see
him after work too!
Don’t talk. Watch this.
So,
to feast
the audiences’ eyes,
our program team has
specially added
one extra link temporarily.
Next let’s welcome the two florists
to compete on their floral skills,
to bring us excellent floral works
on scene.
Working staff please come to stage.
What are they doing?
No, I need to talk with the director.
It’s live, too late!
He’s over.
Chomper is over.
What’s over?
Say something good, okay?
I believe Bo Hai will definitely win.
Relax.
Honey,
it doesn’t feel right.
The other florist
is finishing,
why Bo Hai’s not yet started?
You don’t understand.
He’s thinking.
Once it’s done in his mind,
then he will start.
Director,
could it become
a broadcast accident?
Do we need to inter-cut an ad?
Wait a minute.
Bo Hai, are you very arrogant?
I’ll get your name mud
in front of everyone.
You’ll never start over.
Look.
Look, what did I say?
I know nothing
about floriculture,
but even I can tell
what Bo Hai made is an artwork.
He’s just making a show.
Make a show?
You make one for me.
Handsome.
Hypocrite.
Successful.
Thanks to substitute.
And super talented.
Cheat.
Cheat the clients,
now the audience.
Not matched.
Ling Guoliang.
What’s wrong with you?
Is Ling Lingqi your biological daughter?
Be confident, okay?
Of course,
now the situation is,
our Qi
doesn’t match Bo Hai,
but it’s hard to say.
Maybe someday,
Bo Hai gets blind.
He starts to like Qi.
What do you say?
Little girl,
be smart, okay?
Don’t always eat, eat and eat.
He’s a good boy,
if you don’t take a move,
he’ll soon be someone else’s prey.
Mom, can you stop
judging people by their looks?
It’s not right.
He has two faces.
He’s not that good
as he looks.
Not good as he looks?
What do you mean?
He had a plastic surgery?
Or his company doesn’t exist?
Or he is a gay?
Don’t leave.
You, you…
Tell us about it.
Okay, be quiet.
Mr. Wen,
Bo Hai’s performance
is really out of our expectation.
But I really heard
Ling Lingqi saying he’s using substitute.
You must hear it wrong.
Or Ling Lingqi
was joking?
Quiet.
Figure it out before you act next time.
Yes, sir.
Bo Hai,
when your eyes
got recovered?
You scared us to death.
This morning.
When you were sick before,
we took you to doctor many times.
You took injections and medicines,
and psychotherapy and so on.
Last time when we were abroad,
we found you an top expert
to treat you.
But this time,
how is it recovered?
Yeah, how?
You recover so fast.
I don’t know.
Anyway,
it’s a good news.
As far as I see,
he must be stimulated
by something else.
I’d like to order a bouquet
for my dad.
Tomorrow is his birthday,
but he’s in sorrow.
Because my mom died of disease
a month ago.
For many times
= Relief Flower Shop =
I saw my dad
crying by himself.
My mom and I had an agreement
that we must give him a bundle of flowers
on his birthday.
But my mom didn’t see
this day coming.
So I’d like to give him the flowers
in the name of my mom.
I want to tell him,
Mom is gone,
but you still have me.
Help me reply to her.
OK.
This bundle of flowers is for your dad.
Please keep it in mind,
the flowers
will blossom again,
and beautiful things
will arrive soon.
You do floral work in the office,
and now in your own home.
Your eyes are just recovered,
do you have to work hard?
The company is growing,
so is its influence.
The brands we’re cooperating with
are reaching a higher standard,
so our work gets more challenging.
But I,
still prefer to read the stories
of common people,
and to use flowers
to deliver their simple feelings,
to relieve them from sorrows.
This bundle of flowers
is the spirit of floral work.
It’s also what inspired me to be a florist.
I got one question
that I wanted to ask you long before.
Why do you hide your name?
You’re like a spy,
running this floral shop
at night
in front of this desk.
Mr. Relief florist.
Sometimes it troubles me a lot
to be famous in this age.
How influential my name is
in domestic floral industry,
you know it.
Narcissist.
It’s a truth.
But in this online shop,
I’m just a common person
who is keen on floriculture.
My friends on line,
no matter who they are,
where they’re from,
whether they’re rich or poor,
they share their stories with me.
So,
compared with
the floral master Bo Hai,
I’d rather to be
the owner of this small flower shop.
But I don’t think
you can focus on your work.
You got 1 million followers,
over half of them are girls.
Check this.
Mr. Relief florist, I love you!
Pick me, love ya~
You’re gross.
That’s what they wrote to you!
= Chairman of the Board Bo Hai =
Awesome.
= Florist Bo Hai
Talking about China Floriculture =
This is Peter Fan,
a home design master.
He’s the founder of the famous
international household brand AiFan.
This is
the big client
= AiFan Household =
we’re on to now.
This old man?
Guess how much you pay
if he designs your home.
1 million?
2 million?
5 million?
Vulgar.
He doesn’t care about money.
He’ll just do it if he likes.
This kind of people is tough.
I also heard that
he’s gonna
visit our company today.
I just saw
those people in Sales Department
gathering around
- an old man.
- Ling Lingqi.
- Could it be him?
- Get the classic schemes you prepared
to the meeting room.
Mr. Bo wants them now.
Okay.
I’ve already got
a rough concept and direction.
Mr. Bo, here are the files.
This is the classic design schemes
of our company in these years.
I believe you’ll get a better understanding
of our company’s design concept
and style after you check on this.
Okay.
I’ll study it
with my people.
I’m glad
to be here today.
Cross-border cooperation is gonna
be the trend in future fashion industry.
Whether two of our companies
cooperate or not in the future,
I hope
we can exchange ideas
anyhow.
It’s an honor
to learn from you.
It’s about dinner time.
If you’re available,
please stay with us for dinner,
and allow me to play the host.
Actually It’s my selfish motive
to discuss more details
on the design scheme with my client.
OK, if you insist.
Make it arranged.
You can get off work
after it’s done.
So I don’t have to
work with you tonight?
Why?
Go.
Mr. Bo,
with all due respect, I’d like to
invite this lady to dinner tonight.
You know
I’m doing home design.
I care very much
about female friends’ feelings.
I’d like to hear her opinion.
She’s new in the company,
and has barely no experience in design.
That’s even better.
I’m sick of
the academic.
I’d like to hear
the voice from a real consumer.
Okay.
Mr. Bo, your place is really good.
This way.
Please, Mr. Bo.
What kind of couple they are?
Such an important client.
Bo Hai just brought Ling Lingqi
alone?
It’s hasty.
This Ling Lingqi can do nothing
but sabotaging.
I gotta tell Bo Hai
to remind him of this.
I often come here for dinner.
It’s quiet and covert,
normal people
won’t find it here.
I’ll lead the way.
Behave yourself,
understand?
I didn’t want to come at all.
Anyway,
just be quiet and sit there.
Less talk more eat.
Beg me.
= Chinese Style Household
Floriculture Design Scheme =
For this Chinese style household
floriculture design scheme,
we’ve found
seven or eight companies,
big or small, for the bidding.
The design schemes of other companies
are quite alike.
They all adopt
various expensive flowers
to foil the household atmosphere.
But your scheme
is different.
You choose
dried peony flower of light color
as the materials.
Can you tell me
for what reasons?
Here’s the thing, Peter.
Peony is a well-deserved national flower,
although she’s dried,
and her grace and pride slacked to some degree,
she’s still holy and pure,
elegant and tasteful.
Looks like
she bloomed again.
This is a flower which cannot be seen
if your mind is not cleansed,
or your heart is not calm.
It delivers
an essence of Chinese culture,–
Zen.
In addition, from practicability,
the target clients
of this series of furniture
are mainly middle-aged people
who have certain
life experience.
In their family,
there must be the elderly and children
who might be allergic
to fresh flower pollen, which might
harm their respiratory system.
Mr. Bo, you’re really a floral master
second to none in China.
I admire your craftsmanship.
Come, Peter.
To our craftsmanship.
Cheers!
I don’t think
I can find a better partner
than you.
Since you’re
interested
in our scheme,
how about
we nail everything down
today during dinner.
Sure.
Miss Ling,
you’re silent.
Why not talk about your opinion?
I think, if we chose
naturally dried flowers,
there is one question
needs to be considered.
Because
the shape and form of dried flowers
are changing over time.
Let’s say, one month after withering,
and one year,
it will look quite different.
Mr. Bo,
how you gonna solve this problem?
Please be relieved,
we have special
drying and
form-fixing technique.
Once our cooperation is finalized,
our Aftersales Department
will maintain and change it periodically.
Then,
I got nothing to worry.
Mr. Bo,
you said Miss Ling
is an amateur.
But the question she posed
is quite professional.
Your company is marvelous.
From president to assistant,
you’re all excellent.
It’s my honor
to work with you.
Actually, Peter,
Mr. Bo is not that excellent as you think,
can you think it over?
Why?
Because
he’s merciless to us.
So we privately
call him
Chomper.
During work hour,
being serious is good.
If you relax, you lose the stateliness.
No.
You don’t understand, Peter.
He’s not just inhuman,
he also has
a big secret.
He…
Are you drunk, Qi?
Don’t drink anymore.
Beg me.
What secret?
I’m curious.
He used to…
Please, please.
Peter,
he’s our president,
but he’s
a wimpy drinker.
He can only drink one glass.
He’d be drunk before drinking the second one.
So he’s drinking water with you.
I don’t know
if you’ve ever seen
a video of a drunk.
That’s him.
It’s hot online.
You people are quite interesting.
That’s why you can be florists.
Your life is full of joy.
Here, Peter, to you!
Okay.
You deserve it.
Have some dishes.
You too.
I always thought
domestic workplace culture
is quite serious,
but here
I spent
a happy hour tonight.
Peter,
my assistant
is a bit drunk tonight,
please forgive her impoliteness.
No, not at all.
Everyone has the right
of speech, that should be
the style of a creative company.
Your assistant is cute.
If she has no boss,
I’d like to be hers.
I’ll never leave my boss.
He’s really nice to me.
He treats me dinner after work.
And he’ll
drive me home later.
Oh yeah?
Mr. Bo is
quite a thoughtful boss.
Thanks. Please.
Do you believe it?
This leading actor,
this overbearing president,
will definitely
fall in love with this leading actress in the end,
this useless girl.
My proposal has already worked.
Say if
Cotillard knows the truth…
How do you know about that?
I watched a lot TV shows.
These are all fixed script.
The actor and actress
looked down upon each other
in the beginning,
so they fought and quarreled.
They’re taking
the quarrelsome lovers routine.
And later
they had crash on each other,
then fell in love
like Romeo and Juliet.
Do you think
it sounds familiar?
Isn’t that Qi and Bo Bai
are in that state now?
Of course.
This little girl.
Show me what you can do.
= Show me what you can do =
She got nothing to compare
with Qi now.
You
watched too much soap opera,
and you’ve lost your mind.
The TV play is made up,
but it originates from reality.
OK, OK, whatever you say.
Should we
care for our real life a bit?
Check the time.
It’s half past nine.
She’s still not home yet.
Isn’t that excessive?
You don’t watch TV plays,
so you don’t understand.
She’s
not working.
In the daytime,
they look troubles for each other,
and they haven’t got even.
Now it’s night,
they will change the place
to fight
and quarrel.
You don’t watch TV,
fuddy-duddy.
You won’t understand.
Full of craps.
You better pray that my money won’t…
Slow down.
Get off if you can’t stand it.
I’m Miss Justice
since I was little.
I can’t help
speaking for him
seeing you cheating
such a kind old man.
But I yielded
to vicious power in the end.
I didn’t tell out
your secret.
I never
owe someone a favor.
Come to work earlier tomorrow.
Get off.
You’re so ungrateful!
And narrow-minded!
My bag!
Chomper, you psychopath.
Look, they fight again.
Look.
OK, stop.
Stop talking about this drama.
You see
what time is it now?
Half past ten.
And she’s still not back.
Something must have happened
in TV series.
Her boss is a decent person,
not Lothario.
A changeful veil
and clean short hair
set off by contrast…
No one is answering.
Presenting an aesthetic sense of asymmetry.
Not answering.
Still not answering.
Leave my show place immediately!
I don’t wanna see you anymore!
Their pace
is too fast for a relationship.
You know her the first day?
She’s a devil!
= Florist Bo Hai =
I…
You think
you would piss me off by doing things like this?
Childish!
Ling Lingqi.
Thanks.
You’re welcome.
Hello, Dad?
You’re the only one I got now.
Chomper,
today I’ll teach you
what’s called “eye for eye”.
Seems there is gonna be a fierce war.
For our friendship,
I bet on Qi.
For capacity,
I go for Chomper.
Dinner is on loser.
Deal.
Chomper.
Now is working time.
Talking about anything
other than work
will get an administrative warning.
Attacking your boss
will be subject to an administrative sanction.
Three times sanctions
will get you fired.
I almost forgot
that you can’t quit.
You can only
stay here.
By the way, tonight,
an important client’s wedding ceremony
requires to use tuberoses
to make a large bead curtain.
This errand is yours.
There are not many tuberoses.
Just tens of thousands.
I have never seen
a bad boss like you.
♪ How long one has to go alone ♪
♪ Before he meets another one ♪
♪ Go and go until the past ♪
♪ Is totally gone ♪
♪ A dream ♪
♪ I’ve gone through darkness and difficulties ♪
♪ Before I see you blooming ♪
♪ Close my eyes and I hear the flower ♪
♪ It says no other option ♪
♪ I must love you just love you ♪
♪ Close my eyes and I hear the flower ♪
♪ It says millions of times ♪
♪ I miss you I miss you ♪
♪ In the day and night ♪
♪ Every flower is searching ♪
♪ The one who hears the flower ♪
♪ Hears himself ♪
♪ In the dream ♪
♪ Every me meets you ♪
♪ I see you shining beautifully ♪
♪ Close my eyes and I hear the flower ♪
♪ It says no other option ♪
♪ I must love you just love you ♪
♪ Close my eyes and I hear the flower ♪
♪ It says millions of times ♪
♪ I miss you I miss you ♪
♪ In the day and night ♪
♪ I miss you ♪