♪ Sleep on the Ferris wheel ♪
♪ See the whale on the cloud ♪
♪ Growing old slowly ♪
♪ The pumpkin carriage
travels past the rainbow bridge ♪
♪ The prince gets me to sleep ♪
♪ The flower is gonna eat the castle ♪
♪ Wake up and see the crystal slippers ♪
♪ Covered with butterflies ♪
♪ How can I see you ♪
♪ Oh babe ♪
♪ Close the eyes ♪
♪ Decide in the dream ♪
♪ Sweet dreams ♪
♪ Who is the leading role ♪
♪ Because I love you ♪
♪ Just only for you ♪
♪ My heart is so good ♪
♪ Let’s stay in the dream ♪
♪ Oh ho ♪
♪ You just only for you ♪
♪ Come and hold my hand ♪
♪ Oh ho love ♪
♪ In your heart there’s a monster ♪
♪ And a gentle universe ♪
♪ Let’s go my love ♪
♪ Let’s go ahead together ♪
♪ You just only for you ♪
♪ Oh ho ♪
♪ Let’s go forever ♪
♪ Oh ho love ♪
♪ Because I love you ♪
♪ Just only for you ♪
♪ My heart is so good ♪
♪ I’ll be with you Oh ho ♪
♪ You just only for you ♪
♪ Oh ho ♪
♪ You’re holding my hand ♪
♪ Oh ho love ♪
♪ In your heart there’s a monster ♪
♪ And a gentle universe ♪
♪ Let’s go my love ♪
♪ Let’s go ahead together ♪
♪ You just only for you ♪
♪ Oh ho ♪
♪ Let’s go forever ♪
♪ Love ♪
= Sweet Dreams =
= Episode 43 =
But I was too young
and I wasn’t careful enough.
Lu Yunqing had something on me.
Mr. Yin!
She met Yin Changhe in the shop
for a secret discussion,
Don’t run!
trying to tell on me.
Mom!
Hai!
- Mom! - Hai!
Help me, Mom! Mom!
Hai!
Mom, help!
- Help me, Mom! - Hai!
Help me, Mom!
Move!
We got people inside! Hurry!
Help them! Hurry!
Mom!
Move!
Mom! Mom!
Mom!
I thought that was it.
Unexpectedly,
Yin Changhe
was burned to death
in the fire.
Lu Yunqing
has also disappeared since then.
This is what they get
for not helping.
Even God helped me!
So,
you made up the story about
Lu Yunqing killing my father,
so that
Bo Hai and I could become enemies
and kill each other.
They killed my son.
Then I
will let their sons
kill each other
and wish they were dead.
So,
I’ve always hated
and trusted the wrong people.
You know too late.
I really want to see
how Yin Changhe and Lu Yunqing
would feel
if they saw this.
William.
You’re insane!
You did
such evil things
for your son!
Are you out of your mind?
Liu Yingjie! Let go of me!
Let go of me!
Liu Yingjie, you bastard!
You want to hit me?
Too bad you can’t.
You’re just like your dad.
A loser.
All these years,
I’ve been fighting
my anger,
my nausea,
treating you like my son,
hoping to see this.
Look at you now,
lying on the ground
like a dog.
How cheap you are!
I haven’t finished my drink.
Here’s to you.
To you and Bo Hai for
helping me
get my revenge.
And to your father,
who deserved to die.
Now that I’ve taken this step,
I don’t care about anything.
Well then,
every day from now on,
we’re enemies.
Whether you can take revenge
depends on
if you can abandon everything for that.
Lu Yunqing
must be responsible
for my father’s death.
But that was a generation ago.
What does this have to do
with you and Bo Hai?
Why would you do something
that hurts everyone, including yourself?
The son shall pay for his mother’s debt.
It feels so good
to see my enemy in trouble.
Will you stop
if I agree to
be with you?
You think you can get
what you want this way?
I already have.
I’m gonna make you pay
for what you did to Qi.
When you beat Bo Hai
and he loses everything,
Ling Lingqi will realize
who is the best man
for her.
I even helped
such a man like you!
I never hated myself
like I do now!
Don’t let me see you again!
I’m sorry, Qi.
I don’t have the courage to see you
or to apologize.
I just know it today
that the belief and ideal
I have been holding
is just
a lie made by Liu Yingjie.
All I did
was digging my own grave.
I’m just a big joke.
Qi.
I don’t expect you to forgive me.
I don’t deserve
your forgiveness.
But I wish
it wasn’t so hard for you.
If possible,
I wish God would
let me bear
all the pain alone.
I’m sorry, Qi.
Take care.
What you think of as desperation
may be full of hope
around its corner.
What is hope?
Hope is flower.
Hope is warmth.
Hope is scattered light
in the darkness of despair.
Hope is being in hell
but having access to heaven.
Even when the world is full of hate,
keep the faith.
Even if the world is full of despair,
keep the dream.
Qi, where are you going?
Going to work.
Work?
Didn’t you quit your job a long time ago?
Didn’t your company...
Work is good.
Young people should be positive
and full of positive energy.
I’ll buy you some breakfast.
No, I’ll eat on the way.
Look at her,
is this a good thing or a bad thing?
Couldn’t tell.
We used to
report problems
like this directly.
Good morning, everyone.
Qi?
What are you doing here?
Working.
I left my resignation letter
with Director Luo.
Get it back for me, would you?
Why are there so few of us?
Where are the others?
Yesterday, when DREAM took over the company,
it put everyone
on hold.
Some colleagues have lost faith in the future
of the company,
so they just stopped coming.
What about Director Zhou and Secretary Chen?
Don’t they care about this?
They
didn’t show up today, either.
I’m going out for a minute.
Cabbage, broccoli,
vermicelli and mutton.
We could have
hot pot tonight.
I’m OK with it.
Do you want clear soup pot
or spicy hot pot?
Spicy.
Okay, I’ll make it for you.
What are you doing here?
I’m here to take the deserters back.
Being Mrs. Mo
has certainly made a difference.
You’ve been so loyal
to DREAM and Mo Nan.
You even start to do
human resources’ job.
Yeah.
I never saw you take the company
so seriously before.
I’m not Mrs. Mo.
From now on,
I have nothing to do with Mo Nan.
I’m here for Bo Hai.
Bo Hai?
He doesn’t even want the company.
What’s the point of
us going to work?
I’m starting to think
everything is meaningless,
except that living in the moment
is meaningful.
Every day, we go shopping, buy food,
make hot pot, and watch TV.
How good life is!
Ling Lingqi.
We’re a little tired.
Let’s go.
Xinyan!
Wait a second.
Well,
whoever the major stockholder is now,
FlowerPlus is still
the fruit of you and Bo Hai.
If the company’s gone,
we can take it back.
But if the company dies,
everything dies.
Besides,
I’m sure
Bo Hai will come back.
Until he gets back,
let’s hold FlowerPlus together,
so that he can see
his career is still here,
his team is still here,
and everything is still here.
The company is run by William now.
We don’t want to
work for him.
That’s why
the company needs you more.
We can’t have DREAM
run around the company,
destroying things.
I’m leaving.
Director Zhou, Secretary Chen,
I’ll see you at work.
Whose side
is Ling Lingqi on?
I’m also confused.
Statistically,
it’s already moved on to the next step.
Lu Baoni,
I was just on my way to see you.
This is a list of DREAM executives assigned
to FlowerPlus.
Patch it through to
human resources.
Okay.
Wait, Secretary Wu.
What’s wrong?
Why isn’t there Mo Nan
on this dispatch list?
Mo Nan?
He’s been fired.
Why?
Do I really have to explain it to you?
A turncoat like him
should have been fired
a long time ago.
Out of sight, out of mind,
or I’ll beat him every time I see him.
= Mo Nan =
A few minutes of your time.
I need to talk to you about something.
Anyone absent from work with no reason today
will be fired.
Go, pack up their stuff
and put it in storage.
Yes.
I want every office desk clear.
Yes!
On what grounds?
These are private property.
You have no right to move them.
Wait a minute.
It’s their personal property.
But the company pays
for the work space.
Do you think the company has the right
to take it back?
You’ve gone too far.
If you can’t take it,
you can quit.
I’ll tell
human resources
to process your resignation first,
and you won’t have to wait in line.
From now on, anyone who
doesn’t show up is considered to be resigning.
And we’re not looking to
fill those vacant positions.
The rest of you
will do all the work.
Of course,
you can resign all together.
The company would never ask you to stay.
When everyone’s gone,
how’s the company gonna run?
Are you deliberately trying
to shut down the company?
The blame for this can only be placed
on Bo Hai’s previous mismanagement,
which resulted in unexcused absences.
If the company were to fail,
it would have nothing to do with us.
Unexcused absences?
We were out of town on business,
according to the company’s plan.
We’re back, aren’t we?
Yeah, it’s on record of the HR Department.
All of these departments
have outgoing applications.
They travel to exhibitions,
visit clients,
or inspect suppliers.
Director Luo.
Why didn’t you say something before?
Why didn’t you ask before?
Besides,
I’ve got a lot of work to do here.
I’m so busy that I can’t even think straight.
Is it my fault?
That’s right.
We’re all in the same company.
We see each other all the time.
There’s still time.
If DREAM’s headquarter finds out
Mr. Liu is firing people at will,
it won’t be good, will it?
What are you talking about?
Boss.
Secretary Wu is just doing his job.
Maybe the way he said it
was a little inappropriate.
A misunderstanding.
Let’s get back to work.
Now that Mr. Liu has spoken,
let’s all work hard
from now on.
There are company rules.
We all have to do
our jobs.
No more tricks from now on.
All right.
Everybody back to work.
Fortunately, you all came back,
or we’d have fallen
for William’s trick.
We didn’t come back
to help you.
We did it to help Bo Hai,
to help the cause we
fought so hard for.
You traitor don’t need to thank us.
Stop it.
It’s all right.
It’s good to have everyone back.
Even though Ling Lingqi
failed Bo Hai before,
I think she did
the right thing today.
So what?
A traitor is a traitor.
At the end of the day,
Ling Lingqi is not
a bad person.
You are simple-minded.
Once a cheater, always a cheater.
After what she’s done
to us and Bo Hai,
can you guarantee
she won’t do the same next time?
She’s probably up to
something again.
Director Zhou.
Secretary Chen.
Actually, you’re wrong about Qi.
Jumble-beads
have an elegant temperament
and fresh smell,
reminiscent of a well-tended
and beautiful summer garden.
Are you looking at me
or the flowers?
I wish your heart be but like mine,
then not in vain for you I pine.
The flowers are in full bloom,
but where are you?
As you can see,
the new theme for this season
is called
“waiting to bloom”.
I used  autumn-color platycodon grandiflorum,
hot tea roses
hydrangeas,
and pointed eucalyptus and sabah leaves
as an embellishment
to create a
demure and mature
yet romantic feeling.
In the past, the theme of the bouquet
was determined by Mr. Bo,
and Design Department was responsible
for the delivery.
Yeah, who are you to decide
next season’s theme on your own?
Yeah.
At least it should be decided
by Deputy Director Wu.
Yeah.
Why did she give the order this time?
She really thinks she’s the landlady?
Quiet, all of you!
Is this still a company?
Or a free market!
Do you have any discipline?
Ling Lingqi is the flower art manager
promoted by Mr. Bo himself.
Her strength
is there for all to see.
Who else is
more qualified to be in charge of
flower art creation than her?
Who else?
Guys,
we’ve all seen what’s going on
in this company.
At times like this,
we must stick together,
instead of fighting among ourselves.
Let’s just keep our heads in the game,
okay?
Go on, Ling Lingqi.
Thank you all for your support.
This season’s new product handbook
is already in the works.
If you have any questions,
just ask.
I’m open to it.
This is my first time
in this position.
All colleagues and predecessors,
I hope you will give me good advice.
Thanks for that.
You’re welcome.
This is the key card to Bo Hai’s house.
You can keep it
until he gets back.
Ling Lingqi.
We know what happened.
We were wrong about you.
I can’t be
the only one apologizing.
Xinyan!
I’ll deal with her at home.
= Mo Nan =
Hello, Mo Nan?
It’s me, Ji Bin.
Ji Bin? How could it be you?
Can you come over and help me
talk to Mr. Mo?
Mo Nan.
Are you here to mock me?
I do look ridiculous.
All I wanted to do was avenging my father,
but only to be used by my enemies
for so many years and
became his revenge tool.
It’s just that you’re too kind.
Because of your kindness,
you were deceived.
Because I’m the stupidest man
in the world.
I’m the one
who ruined Bo Hai and  FlowerPlus.
And I hurt the one
I care about the most.
It’s not your fault.
It’s the people who lied to you.
Mo Nan, why are you
so hard on yourself?
Bo Hai is gone.
Qi…
She hates me.
If my dad were still alive,
he’d be very disappointed in me.
No one will ever forgive me.
And I’m not
gonna forgive myself.
Will you please pull yourself together?
Pull myself together?
Baoni.
People like me don’t have the right
to pull ourselves together.
People like me
should be miserable
and corrupt for the rest of our lives!
That way,
I might feel better.
You might feel better,
but what about the others?
What about Qi and Bo Hai?
Will they feel better
because you’re like this?
Yeah, you’re miserable.
But they’re more miserable than you are!
Mo Nan.
People who do the wrong things
don’t deserve
to be decadent like you do.
What you need to do now
is making amends.
A man must do what he must do.
You made a mistake, you change.
You failed, you start again.
Instead of hiding out here drinking.
What kind of man are you!
If you pull yourself together,
I will do everything I can to help you.
But if you continue giving up like this,
let’s just say I was wrong about you.
Baoni!
♪ It’s good to be alone ♪
♪ Though I smile less ♪
♪ I don’t want to be disturbed ♪
♪ But I still want to be hugged ♪
♪ I don’t accept your kindness ♪
♪ For fear that it will be gone ♪
♪ Or I will never forget it ♪
♪ You smile when you walk to me ♪
Bo Hai.
Wherever you are,
take care of yourself.
I’ll watch FlowerPlus for you
till you get back.
The tulips are about to bloom.
Spring
is about to arrive.
♪ You’re the brightest dream of mine ♪
♪ Lighting up the dark sky ♪
♪ That’s destiny That’s love ♪
♪ That’s the last hug ♪
♪ I say something I don’t mean ♪
The roses are especially in bloom this year.
Rose Eden
has been flowering for three months.
They say
it’s probably to celebrate
my promotion.
Bo Hai.
I’m the director now.
You must be happy for me, too.
♪ Though I smile less ♪
♪ I don’t want to be disturbed ♪
♪ But I still want to be hugged ♪
Our summer theme flowers
sold two hundred thousand bunches,
setting a record
in FlowerPlus’s history.
Chen Mo and Zhou Xinyan
have registered their marriage.
They decided
not to hold the wedding until you get back.
♪ Whispers of love are for ears ♪
♪ But eyes are attracted ♪
♪ I’ve seen so much scenery ♪
Since you left,
the Relief Flower Shop has stopped updating.
People are looking for you on Weibo.
By the way,
you lost tens of thousands of followers.
At the board meeting,
William rejected our proposal again.
This week,
there’s nothing to be happy about,
except that
my mom won the first place
in the community dance competition.
♪ Time only goes by ♪
♪ Caring nothing for our growth ♪
♪ The everlasting love ♪
♪ Turns out to be a misunderstanding ♪
♪ Whispers of love are for ears ♪
♪ But eyes are attracted ♪
♪ I’ve seen so much scenery ♪
♪ But nothing compares with your lies ♪
♪ You’re the brightest dream of mine ♪
♪ Lighting up the dark sky ♪
♪ That’s destiny That’s love ♪
As hard as we’ve all tried,
this year’s numbers
haven’t been great.
But it doesn’t matter.
We’ve been used to
William’s tricks.
We’ll carry on.
♪ We don’t understand love ♪
Bo Hai.
It’s been a year.
Where are you?
How are you?
In the past two months,
sales in North China
have fallen slightly.
We found
there’s a supply chain issue.
But we’ve already asked the Production Department
to raise
the number of suppliers.
It’s not the suppliers.
It’s the cold-chain logistics.
It’s true that the cold stores
are not well-distributed.
Supply costs are too high
in the northern markets
and deliveries are not timely.
Hold a meeting with the Production Department
this afternoon to discuss the problem.
All right, I’ll notice all departments.
Director Ling.
Something wrong with the newly arrived flowers!
These are small and wilted.
There’re even worm-eaten marks.
Our Design Department
ordered Class A flowers,
but these flowers are not even C class!
How did your Production Department do the work?
That’s Mr. Liu’s order.
He said it was to save money.
Okay, that’s enough.
Don’t send
any of these flowers to the shop.
Let’s keep this between us.
I’ll take care of it.
The company opened
more than 20 new shops in a year,
but the cost of the single shop is high
while the efficiency is low.
So, these 20 more shops
have not brought
a rise in market share at all.
In the meantime, we’ve borrowed
a lot of money from the bank,
and this kind of rapid expansion
of the company
will bring huge operational risks.
The expansion strategy
is the board’s decision.
As a marketing director,
you don’t have to worry.
Mr. Liu.
This is the third time this year to lower
the purchase grade of flower materials.
The quality of this batch of flowers
is surprisingly poor.
These flowers
cannot represent our FlowerPlus.
The company is in difficulty now.
The whole point of the downgrade
is to keep costs in check.
If your Design Department thinks of something,
sales can go up the same, right?
No Design Department can
use inferior materials
to trick consumers.
Every downgrade
has a significant impact
on sales.
If we keep doing like this,
FlowerPlus’s brand will be ruined.
Miss Ling,
you got the point.
Why are we in difficulty?
It’s because the cost is too high.
How are we gonna fix it?
Other than downgrading,
there’s only one way to go.
Cut the staff.
Some staff
do the work of four people.
Some staff do nothing
but make trouble.
Cutting staff isn’t about number,
but about cutting the worthless.
I’ll go on business in person.
Find the supplier
with good quality and low price
and try to solve
the problem of purchase cost.
As the saying goes,
a grown girl can’t be kept at home.
Keeping her at home
will grow hatred.
Your daughter
is still single?
You don’t need to worry
about my daughter.
I heard she got a promotion
in the company recently.
Did she get a raise, too?
She got a promotion
but didn’t get a salary raise.
Not at all?
= We don’t go to the hospital… =
To tell you the truth,
your daughter
is really average.
Very average.
But,
my little boy
likes her.
Wait, wait, wait.
Likes who?
As long as Qi
can be obedient and sensible,
and more importantly, be nice to my son,
I’ll settle for
them going out first.
Li Lijun.
You mean
my daughter
is going to date your son,
right?
Yeah.
I ask you,
does she
know about this?
We don’t
need to talk to Qi.
Considering my son
likes your daughter,
she’s already lucky enough.
I’m telling you,
you won’t get a second chance.
Li Lijun.
Let me tell you something.
My daughter is doing just fine.
She doesn’t need a relationship.
No need.
As for
when she’s in a relationship
or with whom, how,
whether or not,
it’s all up to her.
If Qi says
she is never getting married,
as long as she’s happy,
we’re happy, okay?
Here’s to your trip
and success.
We’ll root for you. Cheers!
Thank you.
Guess
what I saw today.
What?
I saw Wu Fan hiding in the warehouse,
secretly trying on
the immortal flower necklace
we made for the client.
He tried on a necklace?
He has such a hobby?
Did you film it?
Group sharing tomorrow morning, 8 a.m. sharp.
From the directors to the cleaners,
I’ll make sure everyone gets a copy.
Good! Good!
Something this exciting
has to be sent to Bo Hai.
What if he sees it
and wants to come back?
We’re all thinking of him.
Is he thinking of us?
A year has passed.
He just disappeared and no messages at all
till today.
We watch the company for him,
and think of him as a friend.
What does he think of us?
No matter how long he’s away from the company,
I’ll always watch it for him.
If he’s away for the rest of his life,
I will watch it for the rest of my life.
I have a business trip tomorrow.
I gotta go.
They’re paying for this, ma’am.
She’s a director now,
how can she still be so stingy?
She’s changed a lot this year.
Yeah.
She used to tell me
everything that was bothering her.
But now,
she doesn’t tell me anything.
She’s holding it in.
I haven’t seen her happy for long.
Don’t you think she is
more and more like Bo Hai?
♪ How long one has to go alone ♪
♪ Before he meets another one ♪
♪ Go and go until the past ♪
♪ Is totally gone ♪
♪ A dream ♪
♪ I’ve gone through darkness and difficulties ♪
♪ Before I see you blooming ♪
♪ Close my eyes and I hear the flower ♪
♪ It says no other option ♪
♪ I must love you just love you ♪
♪ Close my eyes and I hear the flower ♪
♪ It says millions of times ♪
♪ I miss you I miss you ♪
♪ In the day and night ♪
♪ Every flower is searching ♪
♪ The one who hears the flower ♪
♪ Hears himself ♪
♪ In the dream ♪
♪ Every me meets you ♪
♪ I see you shining beautifully ♪
♪ Close my eyes and I hear the flower ♪
♪ It says no other option ♪
♪ I must love you just love you ♪
♪ Close my eyes and I hear the flower ♪
♪ It says millions of times ♪
♪ I miss you I miss you ♪
♪ In the day and night ♪
♪ I miss you ♪