♪ Sleep on the Ferris wheel ♪
♪ See the whale on the cloud ♪
♪ Growing old slowly ♪
♪ The pumpkin carriage
travels past the rainbow bridge ♪
♪ The prince gets me to sleep ♪
♪ The flower is gonna eat the castle ♪
♪ Wake up and see the crystal slippers ♪
♪ Covered with butterflies ♪
♪ How can I see you ♪
♪ Oh babe ♪
♪ Close the eyes ♪
♪ Decide in the dream ♪
♪ Sweet dreams ♪
♪ Who is the leading role ♪
♪ Because I love you ♪
♪ Just only for you ♪
♪ My heart is so good ♪
♪ Let’s stay in the dream ♪
♪ Oh ho ♪
♪ You just only for you ♪
♪ Come and hold my hand ♪
♪ Oh ho love ♪
♪ In your heart there’s a monster ♪
♪ And a gentle universe ♪
♪ Let’s go my love ♪
♪ Let’s go ahead together ♪
♪ You just only for you ♪
♪ Oh ho ♪
♪ Let’s go forever ♪
♪ Oh ho love ♪
♪ Because I love you ♪
♪ Just only for you ♪
♪ My heart is so good ♪
♪ I’ll be with you Oh ho ♪
♪ You just only for you ♪
♪ Oh ho ♪
♪ You’re holding my hand ♪
♪ Oh ho love ♪
♪ In your heart there’s a monster ♪
♪ And a gentle universe ♪
♪ Let’s go my love ♪
♪ Let’s go ahead together ♪
♪ You just only for you ♪
♪ Oh ho ♪
♪ Let’s go forever ♪
♪ Love ♪
= Sweet Dreams =
= Episode 11 =
Chomper.
Now is working time.
Talking about anything
other than work
will get an administrative warning.
Attacking your boss
will be subject to an administrative sanction.
Three times sanctions
will get you fired.
I almost forgot
that you can’t quit.
You can only
stay here.
By the way,
tonight,
an important client’s wedding ceremony
requires to use tuberoses
to make a large bead curtain.
This errand is yours.
There are not many tuberoses.
Just tens of thousands.
I have never seen
a bad boss like you.
Yi, the ceremony tonight
needs a lot of tuberoses,
so get 20 thousand more.
Got it, Mr. Bo.
I’ll order them now.
You…
What?
You want more? Alright.
Give me my bag.
You bag?
Why did you touch my things?
That’s my photo.
It shouldn’t be there.
So, you admit
you are the Chomper.
Did I interrupt something?
Out.
Not you.
You. Out.
This is the contract.
Right, Peter said
the Chinese style product of the
new season will be sent to you later.
Peter specifically stressed that
the new product is still in the secret.
He told us to do a good job
of confidentiality.
Got it.
You may leave.
Qi,
I have a meeting at 4:30 later.
I can help you for
another 25 minutes.
Why do we have
such a weirdo in our world?
I thought of him
as a myth before.
Now when I think about it,
it feels like a joke.
What’s wrong?
Let me see.
Why are you so careless?
Here, let me help you.
Be careful.
I’m done.
How about
you just resign?
Change your job.
No.
I can’t resign now.
If I continue doing this job,
I really will die young.
For me, you’re already there.
Gosh!
I forgot to get that Chomper
an important document.
I need to go.
Mo Nan?
Qi.
This is the new plan of Marketing Department.
Mr. Bo needs to sign this.
Then leave it here.
No.
There are things
I need to discuss with him in person.
I will come back later.
Right, Qi,
Baoni told me about your job.
After I finish my work, I will help you.
That’s my buddy.
Good day.
I’m exhausted.
Isn’t it more appropriate to make
a phone call than just show up?
Congratulations on
Peter’s program.
Chen Mo and I
prepared a bottle of
Chateau Mouton Rothschild of 1982.
I don’t drink.
How about this Minute Maid of 2018?
I can drink that wine for you.
I’m warning you.
Don’t mess up the place.
Here.
Don’t touch this.
You bought durian?
What’s…
What?
Put it in.
Put it in!
What’s…
This thing is forbidden in my place.
What’s wrong with durian?
It’s cute.
- Cheers. - Cheers.
You’re both doing great
in getting Peter’s program.
Boss, this program can bring
a lot of money.
This glass of wine
- is not enough.
- Give us something real.
Fine. Tomorrow morning,
I will notify the Finance Department
to give you the first half year’s…
Hold on.
In your eyes, your partners
who start the business with you
are so vulgar
and value money that much?
Then, you two.
What do you want exactly?
Xinyan, Xinyan…
Xinyan, you are drunk.
I’m not.
Sit up straight.
This is creative.
Bo Hai, how about
I give it a go?
A go for what?
You are making things worse.
You are disgusting.
Xinyan, Xinyan.
Sit properly.
How about another round?
We three are close.
One kiss
is all right.
Don’t let her drink.
Slow down.
Chen Mo,
send her…
Bo Hai,
I need to tell you something.
OK. OK.
For all these years,
I’ve been waiting for you.
You know I like you.
You know it, right?
I’m not drunk.
I’m not.
There’re things I could tell you
only after I drink some wine.
Do you understand?
I didn’t
dare to tell you.
Well, sit up straight. Then talk.
Sit up straight.
Chen Mo.
I think I should leave.
Leaving now?
You bought the wine.
You take care of her.
I’m not leaving.
I’m not done yet.
I mean him.
You sit up straight, Xinyan.
Let go of me. I was talking to him.
How to get her leave like this?
Are you alright?
Want some candy?
I have adored him secretly
since college.
I’ve been there for him
for so many years.
Why did he
still refuse me?
Xinyan, don’t cry.
It’s not only you.
He refuses all women.
Bo Hai is such an idiot
when it comes to love.
Five years.
The company grows from three people
to today’s
group with more than 800 people.
Sometimes,
when I was looking at the mirror,
I felt like
I got more wrinkles here
and another dark spot there.
I asked myself.
I put my youth into this.
Does it worth?
Of course it does.
You know it does.
That’s why you do it.
Yes.
Because I believe
the one who can open Bo Hai’s heart
in the end
will be me.
Alright. Xinyan, don’t cry.
You still have me.
If someday
you become an old woman
covered with wrinkles,
then I could
show some mercy
and accept you.
Back off.
I didn’t order enough.
Braised Spare Ribs in Brown Sauce.
Sweet-and-sour Fish.
But too sour.
When it comes to eat,
Qi becomes selfish.
She invited you to eat downstairs.
You refused
and insisted on eating instant noodles with me.
I saw you
all alone by yourself.
So I condescended to stay with you.
How dare you say that?
To be honest,
your life quality is really bad.
You just eat this
by yourself every day?
Why not change flavors?
I did.
Three days of a week I eat braised beef flavor
and other three days for Lao Tan Pickled Cabbage.
Sunday is Seafood flavor instant noodles.
You’re unbelievable.
You don’t care much
about what you eat.
But you like to play
this childish toy.
This is not a toy.
This is a timer.
It can materialize
abstract time.
Turn the hourglass upside down.
Running out of sand
takes an hour.
Falling from above
takes a moment,
but it changes fast.
Because of work,
I am strict about time.
So I take it with me all the time.
Aren’t you
just doing planning?
Such deep words
coming out of your mouth
is hilarious.
I was too dramatic.
Bad news!
AiFan Household’s new product design
was leaked.
In two minutes,
the news was already
spread by mainstream media.
What about Peter…
= Peter =
What’s going on?
Isn’t this our company’s
new design?
- Yes. – Yes.
How come it was leaked?
No idea.
Who did this?
Look!
AiFan Household’s
new product design was leaked.
That’s our work.
Who did this?
There must be someone
who leaked the news.
Not everyone
has the access to the design.
Leaked? No way!
Isn’t it our company’s
latest design?
What are you looking at?
We…
Excuse me.
I deeply understand
your feelings now.
If this thing
turns out to be our responsibility,
we will do as fast as we can
to give you a satisfactory answer.
Goodbye.
What now?
Find out
how the design gets out.
It’s quite obvious.
There must be
a hidden traitor inside our company.
It’s just awful.
We work so hard
to get clients.
Now it’s in vain.
If I find out who did this,
I will beat
this person up.
Who is it?
The new design
was classified.
Not everyone knows about it.
All files
were in Mr. Bo’s computer.
We need to pin down people who
have access to his computer.
Let’s make a list.
Mr. Bo.
Secretary Chen.
Director Zhou.
And me.
Hello?
Yes.
The Chomper calls me.
I’m coming.
Is it Ling Lingqi?
How is that possible? What are you thinking?
So, you are saying
I am the one who leaked it.
I do want to make a prank on Mr. Bo.
But,
I won’t choose
to fight dirty.
Besides,
this low trick
could be broken in three minutes,
why would I choose this way?
Stop pretending.
This is huge.
If we don’t have evidence,
we wouldn’t suspect you.
The design was transferred
last night.
And this morning,
we have this leaked news.
Besides Mr. Bo,
you were the only one
who have been in this office.
Just because I went into this office
to get files,
you accuse me
of being a hidden traitor?
You are trampling people
to mud and ashes.
Don’t we have surveillance
around the office?
Go check them.
You did this after
you were ready.
That’s why the camera
was damaged.
So, you don’t have evidence.
Then why are you slinging mud at me?
The cleaner is the witness.
She saw you
walking out of this office.
But there was…
Mo Nan?
Qi.
No,
I can’t drag him into this.
There was what?
There was no good
for me in this.
Your real boss is not Mr. Bo,
but Mr. Wen.
It’s not me.
Ling Lingqi,
the way you pretend
is really disgusting.
Believe it or not,
I didn’t do it anyway.
I heard that when people are depressed,
eating sweets makes them feel better.
Mo Nan,
do you believe me?
Ling Lingqi,
even if the world doesn’t believe you,
as long as you say you didn’t do it,
I believe you.
I read you right.
I didn’t tell them about you.
Qi,
why didn’t you
tell them about me?
I don’t know about others,
but I know you.
There is no way you are the hidden traitor.
I am just unlucky.
So, I became their target.
How could I drag
you down to this?
Secretary Chen said
the company is still looking into this.
I hope this could
end soon.
FlowerPlus is
a hot mess now.
I heard that Peter
has already reached out to his lawyer.
All thanks to
our stealth killer.
Go deep inside enemy and win by surprise.
Yes.
The headquarter sent us
a really good specialist.
Two years ago,
he sued
a cosmetics company
for unwarranted patent infringement
in a U.S. local court.
DREAM took advantage of it.
In six months,
the acquisition was completed.
A year ago, he guided public opinion
and made a false news case
bubbling with noise.
The fashion websites involved
were sold to DREAM
at half of the original valuation price.
It only took four months.
I wondering this time,
would our specialist
set a new record again?
The first time William sent you here,
I doubt if he
should appoint
such an important job
to a boy.
I didn’t expect you
to be such a tough character.
I wish our first battle a success
and all success after.
I go inside FlowerPlus
because I want to fulfil
my ambition.
But you,
for a little profit,
you betrayed
your benefactor and boss.
Willingly embrace
the enemy.
I’m not like you.
What do you mean?
I mean
your boss and I
just sit on a boat temporarily
to achieve
a common goal.
After getting off the boat…
If we are not the same,
how come we sit here together?
I’m leaving.
Shi Ji, show Mr. Mo the way out.
No need.
Don’t come close
to me anymore.
Isn’t he just a business spy?
Copy some files.
How hard could that be?
Look how arrogant he is.
He is William’s favorite.
We need to be careful with him.
Be smart.
Yes.
Ji Bin.
Mr. Mo, long time no see.
The project in Nice
was finished.
I specially asked William
to send me here to help, are you happy?
It’s good you are here.
I don’t need to do this all alone
and have no one to talk.
By the way,
I moved to a female colleague’s place.
The balcony.
You need to be careful when you are around.
Don’t be suspicious.
Sure.
There’s another thing
I don’t quite understand.
In Europe, you
were a high-level white collar.
Why did you come back and suffer this?
FlowerPlus is a tough bone to chew.
Otherwise,
William wouldn’t invite me
to handle the business.
Right. According to the company’s practice,
as long as you finish the task,
William should promote you
to President of Asia Pacific.
Think about this.
It’s worth the trouble.
You won the first battle.
Why are you still
unhappy?
I’m just too tired recently.
I always feel like
the one behind this
must be Wen Guangqi.
But this Ling Lingqi,
did Wen Guangqi buy her over?
Did she get something out of this
so she betrayed the company?
But she is
always giggling
and doesn’t care about things.
She doesn’t look like that kind of person.
Don’t you think
the words she said in the office
sound true?
So I think
there may be something else.
Something else or not,
before we have conclusive evidence,
Ling Lingqi is still suspicious.
Bo Hai, you always have grudges
against her.
Are you trying to kick her
when she is down?
Do I look like that kind of person?
You do.
Do me a favor.
The cleaner said
she only saw me walking out
of the office.
Did she already
colluded with Wen Guangqi?
So they want me to be a scapegoat.
Ling Lingqi, you can’t be
so dark because
you are wronged.
You need make things clear
before you make a decision.
Hi, mister.
Did you
see that
cleaning lady?
Ma Guihua?
She went to clean the Glass House.
The Glass House. Thanks.
I heard your cooperation with
AiFan went wrong.
Mr. Wen should know
about that better than anyone else.
Why are you so careless?
Well, you are young.
With your passion,
you manage this big company
all by yourself.
It’s really hard.
You don’t need to work so hard.
Give me a sign,
and DREAM could be
your most solid support.
You are right.
You can’t manage a company
just by being enthusiastic.
At a critical moment,
one needs to be tough.
Doing business is like fighting a battle.
Before the war,
the commander uses the traitor’s blood
to ask for blessing.
Mr. Wen, take care.
The whole company
knows that I testified against you.
Do you have a grudge
and try to revenge?
No, Auntie.
It wasn’t me!
Mr. Bo,
I don’t want to hurt you.
Even if I do,
I wouldn’t choose
that way.
I’m not that kind of person.
Then what kind of person are you?
You just refreshed
my understanding of being despicable.
Don’t you forget that
I still get the goods on you.
You used this
despicable way against me.
Should I do the
same and
destroy you?
Don’t you dare.
I will fight you to the end.
Good.
I’d like to see
what else you can do.
Ling Lingqi, I always thought
you were just a shallow fool.
I didn’t expect you to be so dark
and scheming.
Wen Guangqi could
pay for your conscience.
So could I.
Why didn’t you ask me?
Maybe my price is higher.
Anyway,
I will make you and
Wen Guangqi pay.
Bo Hai, you fool!
Well, this is
quite interesting.
Suddenly, there is a scapegoat
saving us a lot of trouble.
Go make AiFan’s news
more interesting.
This show is getting better and better.
People’s artist!
You almost got me.
Did you see
Wen Guangqi’s face?
He totally believed it.
Next,
we will
do things our way.
That poor Ling Lingqi.
She cried so hard.
Why are you doing business?
You should be
in a TV series.
And you can take me with you.
You play a prince,
and I can be your emperor.
Shut it.
Qi.
Qi, are you alright?
Goodness! What happened to you, Mom?
How do I look?
I went to the mall today.
When passing by the cosmetics counter,
the clerk recommended it.
It is said that this color is good.
I think it’s great, too.
I tired the color for you.
You know?
It’s popular.
A boy-killer’s color.
I want to kill him now.
He misjudged me?
I was wrong about him!
I was blind.
A person with so many problems.
Can everyone
be a president now?
He is a bad person
with abnormal personality.
And his brain
is not working at all.
Anyone could be a president now, right?
I hate
this kind of hypocritical moneybags.
Did he think a person
like him could also
be a domineering president?
Qi, drink some water.
Don’t choke yourself.
“My price is higher.”
Qi,
what’s your plan?
What else can I do?
This is the 21st century now.
They can’t have things their way
and wrong a good person.
The truth will come out.
Mo Nan,
do you have any good idea?
what are you thinking?
She is being treated unjustly.
He is worried
about me.
Right, Mo Nan?
These are all you ordered?
Just three?
= Bo Hai =
Who is this?
Hello, Mr. Bo.
This is Business Daily.
Your company
leaked AiFan Household’s
new design.
I’d like to ask some questions about it.
Hello?
Understand.
Hello? No comment.
Right.
OK, got it.
Fine.
OK.
Please calm down,
I will handle this now.
= AiFan’s New Design Leaked by FlowerPlus? =
OK.
Alright.
Understand.
Hello, FlowerPlus.
Sorry, no comment.
We just
knew about this.
Director Zhou.
Sorry, no comment.
For any
irresponsible words,
we reserve the right
to resort to law.
= Meeting Room MR =
The Sales Department received
many phone calls
from some major clients.
Because of the incident of AiFan Household,
two clients have decided
not to cooperate with us.
The current PR crisis
is escalating.
The Brand Department has
tried every way to refute the rumor.
But the result is not ideal.
Our shops are also under great pressure.
There are several shop managers
now reporting that
reporters went to shops
and made requests for filming and interviews.
Although we rejected them
and forwarded to the Brand Department,
it still
affected the customer’s
consumption experience after all.
Peter
refused to meet with our men.
And also,
he sent two men down
and said awful things.
So,
I think peaceful negotiation
is impossible.
Alright.
After this thing
about AiFan,
our year-end bonuses
are gone.
Seriously?
I’m waiting for that money
to travel.
That’s all on Ling Lingqi.
Shameless!
Keep your voice down.
I don’t understand.
A person like her
should leave the company now.
Who did this?
= FlowerPlus Personnel Regulations =
The copier is out of order.
Take this and write it 20 times.
Isn’t this the company’s personnel regulations?
We got this when we join the company.
Why do I have to copy?
Because recently,
there was a confidential leak.
As a director,
I believe it is necessary
to issue Personnel Regulations again
to rectify the company’s discipline.
What important documents
do you want to copy
so you can leak
company’s secrets again?
A traitor like you
should write the regulations
many times.
So you can remember it.
20 times?
- 20 times! - 20 times!
Right.
Let me tell you.
This time she is done.
I guess after she finished it,
her hand must have been wasted.
What did you say?
Baoni, I…
Who let Qi copy the regulations?
Baoni, most of the time,
when you ask me something,
I tell you the truth.
But, in face of major issues of principle,
I have my rules,
and I can’t tell you.
You two,
go and apologize to Ling Lingqi.
Are you kidding me?
Who is the one should make an apology?
Lu Baoni.
I know you and Ling Lingqi
are BFFs.
But I suggest you not get into this.
Ling Lingqi betrayed us.
To copy the regulations
is just a small punishment.
I say it one more time.
Go and apologize to Ling Lingqi.
Who do you think you are?
How dare you
bossing us around?
Look how angry
she is!
Maybe,
she is an accessory.
What did you say?
Watch your mouth.
You dare to make a move!
I did it, so what?
You are the hidden traitor and you beat people.
Are you really taking the company
as a food market?
Outrageous!
They are fighting!
Let go of me!
Stop! Stop it!
Let go!
Sisi!
Stop!
Crap!
My beautiful face!
- Be gentle! - I’m sorry.
I’ll be more careful.
I’m sorry, Baoni.
It’s my fault.
What does this have to do with you?
It’s not your fault.
They bully you with no reason.
Besides,
you are my sis.
I should take care of you.
If you were a man,
I would marry you.
It’s cruel that you two
are doing this in front of me.
And also,
we are good friends.
We agreed you should’ve called me
before you got into a fight.
That’s not a fight.
Just jostling each other.
Qi,
I can’t take this no more.
They are bullying you like this.
Are you going to take it?
No.
We are going to fight back.
Fight back!
With fist or words?
It doesn’t matter.
There are only three of us.
Can we really beat
tens of them?
Then what shall we do?
♪ How long one has to go alone ♪
♪ Before he meets another one ♪
♪ Go and go until the past ♪
♪ Is totally gone ♪
♪ A dream ♪
♪ I’ve gone through darkness and difficulties ♪
♪ Before I see you blooming ♪
♪ Close my eyes and I hear the flower ♪
♪ It says no other option ♪
♪ I must love you just love you ♪
♪ Close my eyes and I hear the flower ♪
♪ It says millions of times ♪
♪ I miss you I miss you ♪
♪ In the day and night ♪
♪ Every flower is searching ♪
♪ The one who hears the flower ♪
♪ Hears himself ♪
♪ In the dream ♪
♪ Every me meets you ♪
♪ I see you shining beautifully ♪
♪ Close my eyes and I hear the flower ♪
♪ It says no other option ♪
♪ I must love you just love you ♪
♪ Close my eyes and I hear the flower ♪
♪ It says millions of times ♪
♪ I miss you I miss you ♪
♪ In the day and night ♪
♪ I miss you ♪