KILLER
Now, here we are at the Killer Boot Camp.
We even put up a sign behind you.
BOOT CAMP FOR KILLER RECRUITS 2025
How pathetic.
THE LACK OF FUNDS SHOWS
It does look silly.
-Boot Camp for Killer Recruits 2025.
-It's been a while.
Shouldn't we get a code name?
It doesn't have to be fancy.
I'll go with Sniper Cho,
mixing my name with the word sniper.
-That's just an example.
-That sounds great.
I'll go ahead with Young-hee.
That's chilling.
That actually sounds scary.
Make one up for me.
-How does Sook-wreck sound?
-I'll go with that.
-You're okay with it?
-Yeah.
HER CODE NAME FITS HER PERFECTLY
AS IF IT WERE HER GIVEN NAME
NAMING GENIUS
We have to hand it to Sae-ho.
-We'll call him the Fly Killer.
-All right.
I'll go with Fly Killer.
Call me Knife-foot.
Let's add a backstory
where I stab people with my foot.
I like it.
New recruits, do you remember
the third item on your code of conduct?
Code number three. Killers never waver.
-I told you they'd give us water guns.
-You did.
You'll find items
that are familiar to killers.
You'll take turns to become a target.
The designated target
will hold a whistle between their lips
while holding up the water gun
and maintaining composure.
The others have three minutes
to shake the target up
with whatever means necessary.
Should the target fail to stay composed
and end up blowing the whistle,
the others can attack them
with the water guns.
We have prepared a magnificent prize
-for whoever claims first place.
-It's going to be mine.
What is it? Can you not tell us now?
I can share this much.
It signifies our move to Netflix.
-That's amazing.
-Netflix offers top-quality souvenirs.
Let's now decide on the order.
-Kick us off, Fly Killer.
-I'll go first.
-All right, then.
-Go ahead.
FIRST TARGET IS YOUNG-HEE
Is the water cold?
No, it's warm.
So there's warm water inside?
WHERE IS HE GOING?
I'm cooling it down.
It's below zero degrees Celsius outside.
Come on. Why would you do that?
Unbelievable.
I wondered what he was up to.
Me too.
It takes too long
to cool down a full tank.
Let me check how big of a laugh
will get the whistle to go off.
How's this?
Is this unacceptable?
Yes, that counts as it being blown.
Even a tiny scoff is enough
to make it go off, then.
Yes, that's right.
I'll try to hold back from laughing.
WE CAN'T HOLD BACK FROM LAUGHING…
-Is this off-limits?
-Yes.
THE TRAINING TO BECOME
SILENT SNIPERS BEGINS NOW
All right. Ready.
Go.
Do you all remember
the Pyeongchang Olympics?
She thought it was being held
in Pyeongchang-dong.
FLINCH
She said, "I hear my part of town
is hosting the Olympics."
-Surely not.
-I'm not lying.
Seriously, she's not so clueless.
She called me to say, "The Olympics
is being held in my neighborhood."
HER COMPOSURE AND THE MUZZLE ARE SHAKING
-I went, "Excuse me?"
-Come on.
I'm telling the truth.
KILLERS NEVER WAVER
FLARING NOSTRILS
I CAN'T BELIEVE SHE'S KEPT HER COOL
Have you heard
anything new about Jin-kyung?
I heard that she's running
to be the president.
WHAT, ME?
…to be the president.
I heard…
A DARK HORSE IN THE PRESIDENTIAL ELECTION
-…about that too.
-She's holding on.
-The presidential election?
-That was my finishing blow.
I can't believe she held out.
That deserved a laugh, didn't it?
When I volunteered to be her spokesperson,
she went, "What's that about?"
She asked, "What does that mean?"
She didn't know that term.
SHE HASN'T MADE A SOUND, BUT SHE'S LOST IT
Oh, so she didn't know
what a spokesperson did.
Here's the thing, Jin-kyung.
I'll make an offer.
If you blow the whistle loud and clear,
I'll call Woo-seok.
THE BAIT WORKED LIKE A CHARM
Way to go, Woo-jae!
KNOWS HER TOO WELL
-Well done.
-That was funny.
PERSUASION ALWAYS TRUMPS FORCE
If you back out,
I'm calling you a sleazebag.
Aren't we allowed to lie?
Hey!
Of course, we can lie.
-Shame on you, Jin-kyung.
-Can't we lie?
Are they seriously allowed to lie?
That's just wrong.
All right, then.
I'll really make the call
if you blow the whistle again.
WAVERING
-I swear I'll do it.
-Really?
-Blow on it nice and loud.
-Seriously?
WHATEVER, HERE GOES
HE DOES IT AGAIN
I'M WAITING TO HEAR FROM YOU, WOO-SEOK
-I have a friend named Kim Woo-seok.
-Oh, him.
JIN-KYUNG IS DUPED AGAIN
I know who you're talking about.
He's a sweet guy.
-And he always picks up.
-Don't you thoink Jun-ho answer?
-Try Jun-ho.
-Call him.
I think my turn is up.
-What do you mean?
-I've done my due.
Woo-jae is going to call Byeon Woo-seok,
and I got my penalty. Isn't it over?
-Let others take their turn.
-You still have time left.
So you haven't changed.
I'll repeat the rule for you.
I don't appreciate your tone.
-It's a compliment. Always the same.
-Pause the game.
-I hope we're on a timeout.
-Of course.
What time is it?
You want to know the time?
It's 11:01 a.m.
Why did you want to know, anyway?
-We could call Woo-seok now.
-That's right.
You know what, Jin-kyung?
Please edit it
if you think this is inappropriate.
I'm sharing a true story here.
Actually, it happened to me today.
This is me betting everything I've got.
I think I should.
WHAT COULD THIS BE ABOUT?
Tell me the truth.
You saw everything earlier, didn't you?
JIN-KYUNG CAME INTO THE BATHROOM
WHILE HE WAS RELIEVING HIMSELF
She saw everything!
She must have!
THE WITNESS ISN'T DENYING IT
She grinned so brightly, too.
The time is up for Jin-kyung.
That was hilarious.
Let's begin the next round
after we call Woo-seok.
-To Kim Woo-seok, right?
-Yes.
Stop that.
You don't want me to call him? Got it.
Shall we have Fly Killer sit, please?
SECOND TARGET, FLY KILLER
During our break,
I trained myself to always keep my cool.
I did some soul-searching, you see.
-'Kay.
-Let's roll.
Ready, go.
Can you guess what he said
after coming back from the bathroom?
Can you, Jin-kyung?
"My stomach kept hurting so bad,
so I took a dump.
But I forgot to wipe myself after that."
THE WITNESS MADE HIM FORGET ABOUT HYGIENE
I HAVE A FACE TO SAVE AS A K-POP IDOL
He must've been badly shaken.
I'd understand even if he hadn't wiped.
I didn't mean to pry, though.
Why did you open the locked door?
Well, the thing is…
Why did you do it, really?
-Did you know it was occupied?
-I merely thought
the door was stiff
and required force to open.
Did you really see everything?
Let me put it this way.
I know him in and out…
THERE ARE NO SECRETS BETWEEN THEM
After Jin-kyung came back
from the bathroom,
-she told me something.
-What?
"Woo-young is adorable."
HOW ADORABLE
Take it as a compliment.
I'M NOT ADORABLE!!!
I really felt terrible.
When I swung the door open,
I obviously didn't mean to take a peek.
But he saw me too, you see.
He didn't even yell.
He just stayed still, devastated.
HE STILL SEEMS TO BE IN THAT STATE
He just sat there, absolutely stupefied.
THE SADDEST WHISTLING EVER
That's a wrap.
3 MINUTES FELT LIKE 3 HOURS
I saw nothing.
THE NEXT TARGET IS SNIPER CHO
I've matured a lot as a married man.
I can embrace whatever comments
are thrown my way.
HOW PATIENT IS THE NEWLYWED GOING TO BE?
Ready, set, go.
I hear he paid his fiancée a billion.
HIS PATIENCE LASTED ONLY 3 SECONDS
1 BILLION WON PAID UPON MARRIAGE
By the way, how long has he been married?
About a year?
Did he really get married?
I hear his wife demanded
separate bedrooms.
FOR A SHARED BEDROOM,
500 MILLION WON IS REQUIRED
-I thought they were separate houses.
-Just separate rooms.
At least they live together.
Kisses are off-limits.
NO-KISSING ZONE
They haven't had their first kiss yet.
The terms of their marriage contract
outnumber the codes for killers.
Hands down.
-Really?
-There are about 100 of them.
1. 1 BILLION WON PAYMENT
2. SEPARATE ROOMS
3. NO-KISSING ZONE
100. TAXES NOT INCLUDED
Jin-kyung asked me
to hand in her money gift
because she couldn't attend
Sae-ho's wedding in person.
She only wired me about 15,000 won or so
using KakaoPay.
Around then,
Sae-ho called me and said
that I shouldn't have given him so much.
So…
I don't get why he thinks so little of me.
-How much did you give him?
-It was within the ordinary range.
-Just ordinary.
-Tell us the amount.
Why would I put it out in the open?
Tell us. Reveal it.
-Full disclosure.
-Let's do that.
-All right.
-I want full disclosure.
-No secrets.
-Let's be honest.
-What's wrong?
-How much did you give him?
-To be honest, I haven't…
-You haven't given him any?
I haven't had the chance to yet.
Seriously?
Can I call a timeout?
Thanks for sharing.
You're bound to check the guestbook
after the wedding is over.
I found the names
of Sook, Woo-jae, and Jin-kyung
and felt grateful to them.
Woo-young's name wasn't on it.
-Did you just enjoy a free meal?
-I had my reasons.
It's no big deal. Sae-ho left directly
for his honeymoon anyway.
His wife didn't go with him, though.
What exactly can you do as a couple?
WE BEG HIS FAMILY'S UNDERSTANDING
How long does he have to
maintain this facade?
I mean, seriously.
And that's it.
That was hilarious.
If we hadn't brought this up,
you'd have kept going
without giving him anything.
No, I'll talk to him later.
Let me apologize before going in.
I'm going all in. I won't even snort.
Goodness, they're so committed.
RELOADING THE WATER GUNS
Don't we have cold water?
-Why are you using drinking water?
-That's the coldest we've got.
-It was refrigerated.
-She determined to get cold water.
Wait, Jin-kyung.
That cap is for the water bottle.
HEH…
You really are a screwball.
She's freaking hilarious.
How is it possible to be like that?
I'm so jealous.
-You won't blow the whistle, right?
-Of course not.
-Never?
-Sure.
You have no plans to do it, right?
Here goes.
Ready, go.
You're not going to call
Byeon Woo-seok, are you?
If you're not going to anyway,
blow the whistle now.
I'll let you off the hook then.
If you don't, you have to call him.
Yeah, stay still
if you're going to call him.
But if you won't, blow on it.
-Three, two, one!
-The world is watching.
DID YOU THINK THAT'D WORK ON ME?
You're calling him
if you don't blow the whistle.
-You're doing it?
-You'll call him?
-Goodness.
-Really?
Why are you so easily swayed?
You're so weak-willed.
Let's leave him be.
-He said he'd call Woo-seok.
-Okay.
THE FICKLE KILLER
He just said so.
Let's give him a free pass
and get Woo-seok out of the deal.
I mean the actor, Byeon Woo-seok.
DESPERATE
The movie star…
This is a secret between us,
I know congratulations are in order
-for Woo-jae next year.
-Really?
I hear his fiancée is 22 years his senior.
IS HE A COUGAR HUNTER?
The lady was born in 1966.
I hear you're acquainted with her, Sook.
The lady with a sports car.
Isn't her hair cropped short
like an athlete?
I hear he noticed children
being rowdy at a playground,
told them to hush,
and got beaten up by them.
The time is up.
-I didn't find them funny. That's all.
-All right, then.
I'll keep grinding away at it.
I'm opening the bathroom door
on you, Woo-jae.
You're going to scream if you do, man.
Because of the odor?
THE BIOCHEMICAL KILLER
Just get on the phone already.
Wait, let's do that in the next episode.
-In the next episode?
-Yes, please.
-We're keeping it for later?
-Yes.
-Probably in two hours.
-Oh, right.
COMING UP NEXT
A PHONE CALL WITH BYEON WOO-SEOK
I'm pretty much the same as Woo-jae.
PUMPING WATER
Ready, go.
She's now fully 50 years old.
She's in for trouble.
DATE OF BIRTH: JULY 6TH, 1975
JUST A COLD FACT
HALF-CENTENNIAL KILLER
-She's hit that major milestone.
-Sure.
She's no longer an ordinary angler.
She's catching the days with her tools.
SAGE ANGLER SOOK
She's catching time.
You jerks!
Isn't it out of line to bring up my age?
-Sook.
-Did you watch her video?
She showed me a clip of her
catching an olive flounder
and ripping its head off
right on the spot.
With her teeth, right?
COULD BE A REAL STORY…
-Her bare teeth.
-Yeah.
That blew my mind away.
She has such a refined palate, too.
I saw her preparing the bait
to catch more fish
and eating it herself.
FOOD TASTER FOR FISH
Habits get you all the time.
She has that magic touch.
Still, you went too far with the worms.
SPECIAL DELICACY AT FISHERIES
You know how she owns five boats, right?
Oh, that makes sense.
All five captains are her husbands.
UNEXPECTEDLY-SKILLED MAN-EATER
Each boat has a different captain.
-That's it for Sook.
-Okay.
-Look at her.
-You rascals.
She took some hits.
You're all awful.
-You were easy prey.
-That worm bit was good, though.
"You went too far with the worms."
I HAVE SEEN EVERYTHING
HUNK IDOL WHO'S GOTTEN TOO FAMILIAR
I heard that she's running
to be the president.
MEMORY-IMPAIRED PRESIDENTIAL CANDIDATE
I hear his wife demanded
separate bedrooms.
THE NEWLYWED'S SHOCKING SECRETS
They haven't had their first kiss yet.
She's now fully 50 years old.
AND HALF-CENTENNIAL SOOK-WRECK
I'll announce the results
of the composure training.
First, Jin-kyung.
Gosh, you did pretty well.
-Four times.
-Only four times?
You blew the whistle four times.
Sook, eight times.
-That's quite a lot.
-I did laugh many times.
Sae-ho, 23 times.
What, 24 times?
-No, 23 times.
-Right.
Woo-young, 25 times.
Oh, no!
You should've gone into the pool.
You must've gotten hit non-stop.
You must know this already,
but Woo-jae took first place.
-Congrats.
-There's a prize for the winner, right?
-We did prepare one.
-He promised something grand.
We took care to choose a good one.
The training you went through
required you to stay silent.
A noise-canceling gadget?
The task taught you to be secretive.
So, we prepared a fitting item
for your clandestine activities.
What is it?
A set of slippers
to mitigate inter-floor noise.
That's a huge gift.
-I've always longed for them.
-Go get it.
-I'm so jealous!
-Me too.
GREAT FOR STEALTH INVASIONS
PERFECT NOISE-CANCELING
Let them see you.
-His heels are sticking out.
-They don't fit.
HEEL-CANCELING
I'm reminded of the sandals
the Maasai people wear.
As discussed earlier, I'm a generous guy.
You're handing them over again?
PRACTICALLY AN ANGEL
-No, don't.
-You already wore them.
We should bring out our water guns again.
That's a violation of our code
to remain cold-blooded.
KNIFE-FOOT'S GOOD HEART
AT LEAST IT BROUGHT PEACE TO HOMES
COLD SPELL OF WINTER IS NOTHING
COMPARED TO THE ICY HEARTS
OF THESE KILLERS
FROSTY AND LONESOME KILLERS
GATHER FOR A SECRETIVE LUNCH
Look how thick the cut is.
That's one hell of pork shoulder.
Its color is amazing.
-You're here to dine, yes?
-Hello, ma'am.
RESTAURANT OWNER'S TIMELY ARRIVAL
Today's special is grilled pork belly.
FIRST, SHE FIRES UP THE PORTABLE GRILL
Won't we need a camera over here too?
You won't be able to catch us
when you're filming Sook.
I'm worried that all you see
will be the back of our heads.
What was that?
-He said that's just fine.
-Who said so?
KILLER INSTINCT
Our head cameraman.
I'm so disappointed in you.
I thought we had a bond
because we look alike.
THE CAMERA SHAKES
THEY COULD BE SIBLINGS
THE GRILLING FINALLY BEGINS
Can we just eat it?
Yes, please dig in.
-We're getting a peaceful meal?
-What about you?
We're having burgers.
Can I have one, too?
I can't enjoy grilled pork
when you're having some burgers.
But you're going to eat it, aren't you?
That'd make you look weirder.
Can I get some salt with sesame oil?
I don't like my pork belly
with soybean paste sauce.
While we were on hiatus…
Don't be surprised.
-My appetite has increased.
-Really?
-See for yourself.
-Okay.
That's going to be a shocker.
Wait and see.
-This is all cooked, Sae-ho.
-Try it.
-By the way, Sae-ho.
-Goodness.
I took it to be polite…
PORK BELLY TARTARE
Doesn't it look like raw fish?
HOW FRESH
ENOUGH WITH THE PRANKS
LET'S GET DOWN TO BUSINESS
FABULOUSLY SNAPPING HER WRIST
SPRINKLING FRAGRANT HERB-SALT
EFFICIENT HANDIWORK MATCHING HER DARK PAST
SHE DOESN'T STOP
BITE-SIZED MEAT IS LINED UP NEATLY
ONLY MASTERS CAN FLIP THREE PIECES AT ONCE
SHEER PERFECTION PREPARED BY SOOK-WRECK
I think you can start eating, guys.
YUM
Goodness, this is so good.
-It's terrible only we're enjoying this.
-Right.
I hate being a celebrity
at times like this.
We won't fault you
if you didn't eat, then.
GLANCING AROUND
KILLERS NEVER WAVER
-But it's too mouthwatering.
-It's so good.
It tastes even better
because we're together.
A BITE FOR SOOK-WRECK FOR HER TROUBLES
MEANWHILE, WOO-JAE
IS DEVOURING MEAT IN SILENCE
Woo-jae is eating so well.
-Yeah, it must be true then.
-Look at his rice.
He's eating spoonfuls of rice, too.
It's incredible.
WITH DETERMINATION
HE TAKES IN SPOONFUL AFTER SPOONFUL
AS WELL AS THE PORK BELLY
THIS IS CERTAINLY NEW
-You're almost done.
-I have some news to share.
Go ahead.
You know
how I usually pick at my food, right?
But I only did that
-because of the shoot.
-Does it upset your stomach?
It makes me so stressed
that my stomach gets upset.
-I often feel sick.
-I get what you mean.
When I'm on a shoot with close friends,
I feel fine even if I eat while filming.
I used to get headaches at night,
but those are gone, too.
We can tell you're at ease
from the way you eat.
You're the sensitive type, then.
He's hyper-sensitive.
"You're the sensitive type, then"?
You talk like that's news to you
after all these years.
THEY EVEN TOOK PERSONALITY TESTS TOGETHER
-I should tell you…
-We must have a new task.
Wolf it down.
No, don't get anxious.
This is because he's recently joined
Two Days and One Night.
They keep him on his toes.
That's understandable.
We've discussed
your specialties as killers earlier.
-Do you remember?
-Yeah.
We briefly mentioned
being a lady killer or a man-eater.
A FEW HOURS AGO
You're a man-eater in a literal sense.
Can you share your tips on getting someone
interested in you over a meal?
Let's say you're interested in me,
Woo-young.
I'M NOT BUYING THAT SCENARIO
It's just a hypothetical scenario, okay?
-Let's just roll with it, ***hole.
-Go ahead.
-He's interested.
-That's our story.
But I left the table to take a phone call
and haven't made my way back.
Won't that bother you?
If you left the table in haste
for some urgent business…
This is what I'd think.
"Phew."
"At least she can take a hint."
"Thank goodness she isn't obtuse."
There's no talking to you.
SAE-HO DEMONSTRATES HIS SKILLS
THAT CAPTURED HIS BEAUTIFUL WIFE'S HEART
HIS ARM IS TOO SHORT
What are you doing?
Be nonchalant.
SO GENTLE AND CARING
If someone I didn't like did that,
I'd be so ticked off.
HORRIFIED
IF THE TISSUE TRICK ISN'T WORKING…
HOW ABOUT THIS?
How's this?
WORKING UP A TORNADO
TA-DA
Does something like this work for you?
You're begging for attention.
-Look.
-You'd be at it with no one giving a hoot.
Look, Jin-kyung.
HERE'S LOOKING AT YOU
How's my idea?
Rather than using some boring tricks,
I'd make direct eye contact…
STANDING UP WHILE MAINTAINING EYE CONTACT
Here.
Isn't this better?
HUNK OF RAW MEAT
Just give her an entire piece.
It's a token of affection.
THIS IS FROM THAT GENTLEMAN OVER THERE
See? I've gotten her enthralled!
I bet she'll keep thinking about me!
A REAL FRESH CHARM
I spared you one huge chunk of meat.
Isn't that generous?
THAT WORKED SOMEHOW
-That's hilarious.
-Won't this be memorable too?
Shall I cut it?
So, let's talk about our interests.
Have you watched Squid Game on Netflix?
You must've, right, Jin-kyung?
FORCING A CONVERSATION
IN THE SAME WAY HE DOWNS FOOD
DIDN'T EXPECT HIM TO BULLDOZE HIS WAY
Seriously!
SHOOTING DAGGERS AT HIM
THANK GOODNESS YOU'RE MARRIED NOW
-I have another question for you.
-Fire away.
They say all killers
are born from misfortune.
-They have tragic backstories.
-That's true.
So, why don't we battle it out
with tragic events in your lives?
-What does that mean?
-Let's see who had it worst.
SHARE SAD TALES
TO PROVE YOUR WORTH AS A KILLER
Let me start off with a short story.
I once bought a pair of jeans
and had a whole one-third cut off.
I'm not lying.
-But--
-Do you know what saddened me more?
I'll even mention the brand.
I can name it.
I fell in love with jeans from Balmain.
-That's a luxury brand.
-So, I went shopping for them.
Those were actually biker jeans,
-so they had knee pads
-I remember.
-incorporated into the design.
-That's right.
I tried them
and came out of the fitting room.
I then asked the clerk, "How do I look?"
Only to see the knee pads
down on my shins.
What a bummer.
SHIN PADS
No one could beat that tragic tale.
-You poor thing.
-I almost spewed my water out.
I used to bang my head a lot.
CONCERNED
When you're taller than 185 cm,
you can bang your head easily
when you get off the bus.
He's not sharing a sad tale.
He's bragging.
Have I ever told you this story?
My friends and I rented out a cottage
-years ago.
-That sounds lovely.
-Romance is bound to blossom, right?
-Sure.
I had something going with this guy.
And this guy who took interest in me
came to the girls' bedroom to ask me out.
He actually hid in the closet.
When I was about to go into the room
after washing my hair,
these two girls snickered and said,
"Go ahead with your skincare routine."
They then went to the living room.
I didn't get why they were grinning,
but I went into the bedroom.
My stomach had been grumbling
because of the raw fish we had earlier.
I'm getting bad vibes already.
Oh, no. Sook.
-So, I--
-Please stop. You're breaking my heart.
Imagine how I'd feel.
I think that was my last shot at romance.
Anyway, being all alone
made me feel so relaxed.
I must've let out 32 farts or so.
Please add sound effects.
-Like that.
-I was so refreshed.
I didn't feel bloated.
-I hope the floor didn't cave.
-The girls asked,
-I'm losing my mind here.
-"Why are you back so soon?
Where were you?"
And the guy…
Did he pass away?
-He came down the stairs,
-Did he pass out?
trudging down the stairs
looking all sallow.
I had no idea what went on then.
SHRIEKING
My friends filled me in after the trip.
"He wanted to surprise you
and asked us to give you two the room."
But you surprised him.
This story brought back a memory for me.
This happened in America.
I had kimchi stew
at some Korean restaurant.
Naturally, you'd get some food
stuck between your teeth.
I noticed this car parked in the lot.
Its windows were heavily tinted, you see.
So, I used the car's windows as a mirror
and started removing the bits.
-Oh, man.
-How embarrassing.
-Did the driver come outside?
-Who was it?
No, they just drove away.
HILARIOUS
I could console myself with this thought.
"I'm in the US."
"The driver was likely White
or African American."
That's what I clung to.
But I couldn't shake off the fact
that I was near the Korean restaurant.
SQUEEZING HIS EYES SHUT
You were signaling them to go.
URGING THE DRIVER'S INSTINCTS TO LEAVE
It's your turn now.
Misfortunes in my life?
FLY KILLER REVIEWS HIS LIFE
I've always been happy.
CONGRATULATIONS ON YOUR
FIRST TASTE OF MISFORTUNE
IT'S ALREADY TIME FOR DESSERT
If you like your noodles chewy, dig in.
THE DESSERT IS CHEWY INSTANT NOODLES
SLURPING
WOLFING THE NOODLES DOWN
EATING NON-STOP
It's been a while. It tastes so good.
ONE MEMBER GOES ON A RAMPAGE AGAIN
GRABBING A LARGE AMOUNT
AND SLURPING THE NOODLES
A BIG APPETITE AND
A BIG LIST OF MODEL FRIENDS
A FEW HOURS LATER
Hello?
Hey, Woo-seok.
We had something going, remember?
Sorry? Did we perhaps argue?
-No, not "argue."
No, more like a situationship.
You argued with him?
SCREWBALLS OST - REBOOT
Subtitle translation by: Jeongwoo Kim
SCREWBALLS
IN SEARCH OF LOOSE SCREWS