DID SOMEONE PRESS
THE FAST FORWARD BUTTON ON 2025?
HOW ON EARTH DID WE END UP
ON THE LAST PAGE OF THE CALENDAR AGAIN?
LONGING FOR WARMTH
AS THE WEATHER GETS COLD
THAT'S WHY WE CRAVE
STEAMED BUNS, FISH-SHAPED BUNS,
AND FRIENDSHIPS WE ARE THANKFUL FOR
SCREWBALLS END-OF-YEAR SPECIAL
We have successfully finished
the Cho Sae-ho Show,
and now, we will begin the second part
of Sae-ho's Deconstruction Show.
The Cho Sae-ho Show was great.
-You did so well.
-Good job.
-You were awesome.
-It was a one-man show.
It went well because you guys
-were great guests.
-You were the best.
We thought a lot about what kind of show
we should have where Sae-ho's the star
and this is the conclusion
we have reached.
One of the big nicknames that
represent Sae-ho is
-the Serial No-show Guy.
-That's right.
"I don't know them."
His golden age started with,
"I don't know them so how can I go?"
So we planned an event
where Sae-ho's the star,
but true to your nickname,
-it will be an event…
-Like that?
…that you can't help but miss.
You're penetrating Sae-ho's core.
It is called Cho Sae-ho's Funeral.
When I got the nickname
-the Serial No-show Guy…
-You guys are bold.
…a while ago…
It became a meme.
…many people kept asking me to come
and asked me why I didn't come.
Even my parents jokingly said,
"How could you not come
to your own parents' wedding?"
But some of the comments said
-one event that Sae-ho can't attend…
-Somewhere he can't go.
…even though he may want to,
is his own funeral.
I did hear about that.
That's why we came up with this special.
The members can remember
the time they spent with Sae-ho
and offer their respects and prayers
in their own way.
PAYING THEIR RESPECTS TO SAE-HO
WHILE REMEMBERING THEIR TIME TOGETHER
TIME WENT BY AND IT IS NOW THE YEAR 20XX
THERE ARE FUNERAL WREATHS
EXPRESSING CONDOLENCE
AND SAE-HO'S PORTRAIT
LOOKS AS IF HE WERE
STILL ALIVE AND BREATHING
THE FIRST FUNERAL VISITOR
SHOWS UP WEARING BLACK
My goodness.
My goodness. How could this be?
Sae-ho is gone.
Gosh, I am just devastated.
He died laughing at his own joke.
How could that…
-How could he die like that?
-I know.
He was so funny. You made it.
SHADOW AND WOO-JAE COME TO PAY RESPECTS
Gosh, Sook.
Hey. My gosh.
It has been a long time.
-Yes, how have you been?
-Have you been well?
Jin-kyung, did you cry a lot?
Your eyes are red.
-What?
-How is life abroad?
-Life abroad?
-You left Korea 20 years ago now.
After that incident…
We haven't met up since then?
But I met a European guy over there
and we're living happily.
Good.
-But--
-You are very popular.
-So the condolence money…
-Yeah?
I lent the deceased some money
when he was alive.
Can I get it back now?
No, come on.
ME?
Woo-jae.
How could you even say that?
-He's dead.
-Yeah.
But I lent him money.
It was the late Sae-ho's
22nd year anniversary
with his wife this year,
so I prepared 200 won.
Come on, man.
How could you pay only 200 won?
How could you do that?
Isn't his coffin from Gucci though?
-Whatever.-
-It's Chanel.
Is it Chanel?
His shroud is from Chanel.
His shroud is from Chanel?
Unbelievable.
My gosh, Sae-ho.
Gosh, Sae-ho. How could you leave us?
Sae-ho.
-My goodness.
-How could you leave us like this?
I liked you so much.
My goodness. How could this be?
IT'S ALMOST AS IF HE'S ALIVE
My gosh, Sae-ho. How could you die
while laughing at your own joke?
You never know in life.
It was a good death though
because he died while laughing.
Was this the best photo…
Was this the best photo they had of him?
Was it?
What is wrong with this face?
What is this, a mustache?
It was a good death.
Geez, I want to shave that off.
Gosh, Sae-ho. May you rest in peace.
My goodness, Sae-ho.
Gosh, Sae-ho.
We had such happy times together.
Yeah, may you go
where there's Gucci and Chanel.
My gosh.
Sae-ho! See you later!
THE SHADOW IS DEEPLY GRIEVING
Go to the place high up there.
I am bowing to you…
-Why that Shadow…
-…with my whole heart!
HERE'S MY GIANT BOW
-Sae-ho.
-Gosh.
Sae-ho.
Sae-ho, how can I say goodbye to you?
We almost lost another person.
Sae-ho!
Pull it together.
You weren't that close to him.
-Sae-ho!
-Hey.
I don't want to say goodbye to him.
He's acting cute since he's the youngest.
I won't say goodbye to you, Sae-ho.
Bye. See you!
Goodbye, Sae-ho!
He's good.
I'll see you later!
Sae-ho!
Why is he so good at slapstick comedy?
Geez.
Gosh.
BACK TO BEING DEAD
-Gosh.
-How have you been lately, Woo-jae?
Yeah, how has everyone been doing?
Have you been married
six times now, Woo-young?
-What?
-Even though
he got married six times,
he couldn't beat Jin-kyung.
-How many times was it?
-Eight times.
-Jin-kyung is way ahead of him.
-She took
the lead when we were on the show together
-and got to eight.
-Eight times?
You must have no regrets whatsoever.
So where are his kids,
Cho Ola, Cho Kka, and Cho Kka-chi?
I know. I wonder how they're doing.
They aren't here.
-How is Ttess?
-And Cho Kka?
How's Cho Kka?
-There's a Ttess?
-That's the youngest.
-The youngest?
-That's Ttess.
-Cho Ola is the eldest.
-She's the eldest.
She's the eldest.
I think Cho Kka is the second one.
-Kka is the second child.
-Yes, Kka.
Cho Kka-chi is the third child.
-Kka-chi is?
-That's the third.
Kka-chi is the third.
Cho Ttess is the fourth.
-Ttess is the youngest?
-That's the youngest?
-I forgot about Kka-chi.
-They had a great relationship.
You know, Sae-ho used to love meat.
-Why does it taste so good?
-He didn't just love meat.
He loved anything
he could put in his mouth.
I can't just eat this by myself.
I should give him a bite.
Woo-young, hang on.
Geez.
I want to put it in his mouth.
-Don't give it to him.
-Why not?
He's waiting for it.
But Sae-ho…
HMM…
But this is his favorite.
He's waiting for it.
He used to love this though.
Gosh, he can't eat this anymore.
We'll eat it for you.
-These jeons are so good.
-The beef jeon!
-The jeons…
-This is really Sae-ho's favorite.
Do you want some or not?
Sae-ho.
You want some, don't you?
NODDING
You must want this so much.
YES
-Do you want some beef jeon?
-Have some.
Of the two, which one do you want?
The beef jeon.
There. He spoke.
THE DECEASED CANNOT SPEAK
-Have some beef jeon.
-Is Sae-ho still alive?
Gosh, Sae-ho used to really love these.
THE PORTRAIT GETS SOME BEEF JEON TOO
Go on. Eat up.
Jin-kyung, the beef jeon so good.
-Why has the portrait changed?
-It's so good.
He has something in his mouth.
SO FREAKY! THE PORTRAIT CHANGED
Geez. What's up with that?
That's bad luck. Oh, my goodness.
There's something on his mouth.
-My goodness.
-Remove it.
-What's up with this?
-Good job.
Did a ghost do it?
MY BEEF JEON…
What's up with this?
Gosh, the beef jeon is so good.
It's so good.
EVERYBODY BUT THE DECEASED CAN EAT
Next time,
when you all leave me,
I'll order the food from here.
Age doesn't matter when it comes to dying.
-That's true.
-Yeah.
Wait, stop filming.
I told you to stop filming!
-What's going on?
-Stop filming.
A VISITOR BARGES IN
DURING THEIR PEACEFUL MEAL
-Sae-ho.
-Wow.
Sae-ho. Oh, no.
What the heck?
WHO ARE YOU?
Hang on.
Who is that?
Excuse me.
It's me, Sae-ho.
Who are you?
It's Emma whom you admired for so long.
ME?
This is so funny.
I heard you married another woman
right after I dumped you.
SO INTERESTING
She's his ex-girlfriend?
-You cried so much because you missed me.
-Wait, maybe his ex-boyfriend?
His ex-girlfriend.
Pardon me, but how do you know him?
He used to follow me around.
My name is Emma.
Did you lend him money?
-No, you see…
-Yes?
…Sae-ho used to like me a lot.
-When was this?
-Hang on.
-Sae-ho.
-What do we do?
I know
that my cute face
and my traps…
THESE TRAPEZIUS MUSCLES
PFFT
-Look at her.
-…and my muscular thighs.
SCARED
-It isn't easy, is it?
-She got bigger.
I came in first in a bikini contest.
Yes, that's right.
I just got back
from beating Kim Kardashian.
-Beat her in what?
-Beat her to death, maybe.
Sae-ho, do you remember…
what you told me
at the playground in front of my place.
"Emma,
can I kiss you?"
Oh, my.
WHAT HAS THE PAST ME DONE?
-I can finally give you an answer.
-Look.
Yes.
-No way.
You may kiss me.
Portraits don't move.
SOMEONE SAVE THE DECEASED!
-Come on.
It feels like he's alive. Oh, my goodness!
-Come to me, Sae-ho.
-Come on.
PLEASE END THIS SKETCH
-Excuse me.
-This is wrong.
EMERGENCY BELL FOR THE DECEASED
It is rude to do this to the deceased.
Sit down and eat some food.
-Yeah.
-Wait.
I must tell him something.
Okay. Go on.
-But don't touch him.
-Sae-ho.
Oh, boy. Look.
URGENTLY PRESSES
THE DECEASED'S EMERGENCY BELL
Listen, ma'am.
Please don't lay hands on him.
Did Hye-seon's calves
always look like that, Woo-jae?
Wait.
Are the two of you fighting over me?
US? WHY?
I am sick and tired of this.
Fine.
Sae-ho.
SAE-HO'S LADY HAS MADE A FIRM DECISION
May I start a new love?
Blink if it's okay.
OF COURSE
He's blinking many times.
Fine. Congratulations.
From now on,
this is your chance at having Emma.
She's talking about the two of you.
My type is a guy
that is sensitive and feminine.
That's Jang Woo-young.
He's super feminine.
I wonder which guy is
the feminine one?
You tell me, Sae-ho.
All you have to do is blink.
Once means it's Woo-young
and twice means it's Woo-jae.
Which one is it?
-Woo-jae?
-It's Woo-jae.
-He blinked once.
-It was twice.
-Is it Woo-young?
He blinked once more.
-Is it Woo-jae?
-It's Woo-jae.
THE CONNECTION BESTOWED BY THE DECEASED
-It's you, Woo-jae.
-Okay!
-It's Woo-jae.
-I'll give you both a fair chance.
-Isn't this whole thing unfair?
-Yeah.
BUT EMMA INSISTS ON GIVING THEM A CHANCE
All right. Whoever loses
the thigh wrestle with me
gets to have me.
-The person who loses?
-Take Emma!
TIME FOR THE FEMININE MEN
TO SHOW OFF THEIR CHARM
THE THIGH WRESTLE
If your thighs get within
one fist's width of each other,
you lose. Got that?
So if I lose this match,
I get to have Emma?
Don't make me blush!
I think I fractured something.
-Are you okay? You're fine.
-Yes.
-You're fine.
-If I lose, I get to have Emma?
For the first time in my life,
I will stake my life on this match.
Try and have me.
You win if you can
hold out for ten seconds, okay?
-Ready.
-I'll give you 150,000 won, Woo-jae.
Set. Go.
Ten, nine, eight,
six, five,
-four, three…
-Take me!
Stop messing around!
…two, one.
That's it.
Woo-jae, you lose.
SUCH AN OBVIOUS RESULT
Hye-seon wins!
Wait. Woo-young still has to go.
They may both lose.
There's still Woo-young.
Both of them are dying to lose.
But Woo-young has the upper-hand
because she already played a round.
This is your chance too, Woo-young.
You'll never get a chance like this.
The heck?
Sorry. I apologize for the blunder.
Did you do your best?
I put my life on it, Jin-kyung.
You have ten seconds.
Hold out for just ten seconds.
I am determined to get both men.
Here we go.
-Ready.
-Try and beat me. You got this!
Set. Go.
-Ten, nine…
-Wait. Ouch!
Wait. Gosh.
Did he lose on purpose?
-He lost on purpose.
-He did it on purpose.
-Do you want me that badly?
-Wait.
He lost on purpose.
Can you call an ambulance for me?
She split his legs wide open.
-Kim Hye-seon wins!
-Hang on.
You may both have me.
Congratulations!
CONGRATS, EMMA'S MEN
-Then, since you won…
-I was so shocked.
…you may take both of them.
-Yes.
Close the chapter with Sae-ho
-and live happily with those two.
-Woo-jae.
-Sae-ho used to love soju.
-He really did.
-Yeah.
-He loved it so much.
-I poured a cup full of the soju…
-He worked so hard.
…that you loved so much.
-Gosh.
-Our dear Sae-ho.
May you rest in peace.
OUR DEAR SAE-HO, MAY YOU REST IN PEACE
Did she just slap him?
It sounded like a slap.
It turns out that
Woo-young will be
seeing your ex-girlfriend.
Please have a drink.
We should all offer him a drink.
-We should.
-That way…
TAKE A CUP, EX-GIRLFRIEND
Offer him a drink.
Drink it up. Hang on.
I'LL HAVE A GOOD TIME
WITH MY NEW BOYFRIENDS
WAS THAT A BULLET?
Please offer him a drink.
Let's all offer him a drink.
Here, Sae-ho.
Take this.
ACCEPT MY DRINK TOO
GULP
He drank it since he likes soju.
IT'S WATER
The soju you loved so much…
He brought the whole bottle.
Hey. Hang on.
May you…
NOT THAT, PLEASE
DRINK IT YOURSELF
But you used to love this.
I was going to wet your whistle.
No? Okay.
THE PORTRAIT HAS CLEAR PREFERENCES
Do you want some yukgaejang?
Yukgaejang?
Hye-seon, pour some on him.
On my face? No, thank you.
HE MUST BE FULL NOW
Hang on.
You don't put things like this
in a coffin.
Oh, my goodness!
That was close!
-Oh, my goodness.
-That's no good.
-Let me take a look.
-What do we do about this?
-Oh, my.
My goodness.
Let's see.
-Take this. That was close.
-Yeah.
That was awfully close.
-That's it. I can go now.
-Here.
Here it is, Jin-kyung.
These should go…
Yes, for the kids.
-This is mine now.
-Yeah.
Sae-ho, thanks for all your hard work.
-Are you enjoying the food?
-It's so good.
It may be a funeral,
but Sae-ho used to say,
"As long as it's funny, it's okay."
So we thought Sae-ho would like it
if you all played games
and enjoyed your time at his funeral.
While Sae-ho was alive,
there was a program
where he made a name for himself
and created countless legendary moments
and established his very first peak era.
The Tazza.
You'll play the legendary Tazza game.
-Let's give it a try.
-How do you play that game?
While you play this game,
I think it'll feel like
the late Sae-ho will be with us.
-Yeah.
-That's the feeling I have.
-Sae-ho was so good at that game.
Each one of you will dress yourselves up,
sit across each other closely,
and play against the portrait
to beat the Tazza.
Sae-ho's ex-girlfriend Hye-seon
will be the judge.
Emma!
What should I do?
Sae-ho left behind some belongings
that he really cherished
-during his lifetime.
-Gosh.
My gosh.
Goodness. What's in that orange box?
WHAT DID SAE-HO LEAVE BEHIND?
The trophy we gave him on Screwballs.
The God of Talk trophy.
-The God of Talk.
The New Star award he really won
at the SBS Entertainment Awards.
He was so unlucky when it came to awards.
Screwballs' poster.
I don't know why, but there's a collection
of Na Tae-joo's poetry.
His book of poems.
-Sae-ho was a poet.
-Show-off.
Next,
a drawing of Sae-ho
that was personally drawn by his wife.
She drew it so well.
Lastly, you could say that
he shared every moment with this.
His car key.
CAR KEY!
-His car key?
-Can we win this in a game?
The funniest person in the Tazza game
will be gifted Sae-ho's belongings.
-He included his car?
-Awesome.
We thought that Sae-ho would
want his beloved friends
to have these belongings.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I think you would want
the drawing of Sae-ho
and the Screwballs poster the most.
-What?
-What did you say we'd want?
Well, things like car keys
aren't all that important, right?
-No, they don't.
-He's right.
What matters is the car itself.
However, since it's already in there,
you'll get it as a bonus.
Man, I want to win this one.
I'm going to do the best I can.
THE LEGEND OF TAZZA
TRY TO BEAT CHO SAE-HO!
Sae-ho is pretty tough.
It has to be something he doesn't expect.
You look ugly, so it's so funny.
Looks like they're preparing
for the open recruitment for comedians.
Now, let's get started.
THE TAZZA BATTLE BEGINS
WITH SAE-HO IN HEAVEN
SCREWBALLS' MAIN COMEDIAN DUO
SOOK AND SAE-HO!
WHO WILL BE THE ONE TO LAUGH
BETWEEN THE TWO OF THEM?
Ready,
set, go.
MAKING WEIRD NOISES
CALM
I am cool toned.
OH?
Oh, no. My stomach.
My stomach!
COOL-TONED LADY COMPLAINS
ABOUT A STOMACHACHE
My stomach!
Is she giving birth?
Right now?
WHAT IS GOING ON?
Yes, my dear.
Who's this cutie?
SHE HAD A SAFE DELIVERY
Yes, my sweetie.
Yes, my dear.
WAH, I'M A BABY
Sae-ho, you lose.
CHO SAE-HO LOSES
I wasn't expecting that.
That's what she prepared?
I think I'll call this scene,
"Life and Death."
INTERPRETING THIS ARTWORK
LIFE AND DEATH
A baby was born
in front of the funeral portrait.
-Yes, sweetheart.
-There, there.
Yes, my cutie.
That was good.
-Was it good?
-It was very good.
Yes, my dear.
Kim Sook wins.
TAZZA ROUND 1
KIM SOOK WINS!
CHALLENGER JANG WOO-YOUNG
Can I go out?
HELP ME OUT, WOO-JAE
You can't see?
A BLIND HORSE
IS BEING LED BY HIS FRIEND TO COMPETE
You may come out, Sae-ho.
HE COMES OUT CLUMSILY AS WELL
LAUGHING
CURIOUS
THE PRO CHO SAE-HO VERSUS
THE ETERNAL SCREWBALL JANG WOO-YOUNG
WHO WILL WIN THIS MATCH?
We will begin covering
the highlights from sports news.
Ready, set, go.
ATTACKS WITH A HORSE'S NEIGH
He's not there yet. He's not there.
He's not there yet.
Look at Sae-ho.
THE SWIMMING MAN
Sae-ho.
SPLASH SPLASH
STAYING CALM
-You can't see anything, can you?
-No.
-They can't compete then.
-Just keep going.
Keep going.
Sae-ho, look at his now.
GIVE IT A TRY
Go for it, Woo-young.
Do what you prepared.
HMM
But he can't see Sae-ho.
Take it off.
HI
BYE
-He laughed.
-We will begin covering
the highlights from sports news.
SPLASH
WINCE
THE UNMATCHED CLASS OF THE ORIGINAL TAZZA
How is he supposed to beat that?
He is on another level.
Where did he go? I want to see more.
-Sae-ho wins.
-I want to see more.
-Gosh.
-He wants more.
TAZZA ROUND 2
CHO SAE-HO WINS!
You have to beat Sae-ho.
I think this side is ready too.
-This is going to be a close match.
-Yes.
-They are going all out this time.
Sae-ho will attack first.
Ready, set, go!
Look at your opponent.
-A candy.
-Candy!
CANDY!
A STRANGE MAN SUDDENLY APPEARS
THE STRANGE MAN'S CANDY-EATING PERFORMANCE
NOM NOM
LAUGHING
Hey, they aren't laughing at his attack.
-Are they holding it in?
-They are trying.
-They're holding it in.
-No one laughed.
Woo-young's lips are twitching.
-He's slightly smiling.
-They're twitching.
Very good. One,
two, three.
That's it.
It's the rest of the members' turn now.
You may begin your attack.
Ready,
set, go.
GOSH
-It's so nice to go to the sauna.
-Woo-young.
-Woo-young is attacking first.
-He's going first.
I should dry these.
ARMPIT HAIR IN FULL VIEW
Why is it so curly?
He's straightening it.
FLAT IRON ON HIS ARMPIT HAIR
-That's his armpit hair, right?
-Straight hair.
He is doing that to straighten the hair.
It was curly before.
Sae-ho is keeping it together.
-He's slightly smiling.
-Yes, he is.
-That is okay though.
-Yes, it's like level one.
The next one up is Jin-kyung.
She prepared something down there.
JEON SUNGLASSES
What is that on her sunglasses?
Is it beef jeon and meat fritters?
He's in danger of laughing.
She brought another pair of sunglasses.
Boiled pork slice sunglasses?
Boiled pork slice sunglasses.
Sae-ho's laughing.
-Hang on. She has one left.
-There's another one.
Is it pepper jeon sunglasses?
-And perilla leaf jeon!
-Perilla leaf jeon.
AS EXPECTED OF A FOOD COMPANY CEO
-She succeeded.
-Yes.
Have some water.
COUGH
-My goodness.
-I want some water too.
TAKES A HUGE GULP
That's it, Woo-jae.
That's it, Woo-jae!
The all-out attack
-is a success.
-It was a success.
THEY SUCCEEDED IN MAKING SAE-HO LAUGH
-They did so well.
-These ones were good.
They were good. They were clearly funny.
Winners!
TAZZA ROUND 3
JIN-KYUNG, WOO-JAE, WOO-YOUNG WIN!
Listen, we should say
our final goodbyes to Sae-ho
and get going.
-Hello?
-What the heck?
Eun-woo?
Look, didn't I tell you not to call me?
-I have a new boyfriend now.
-Eun-woo?
Don't call me.
Is his last name Cha?
Hey, Cha Eun-woo.
-Cha Eun-woo?
-You deserted?
Hang on.
Wait for me, hot boy!
JUST LIKE THAT, HIS EX-GIRLFRIEND LEAVES
Is she okay?
Take care. Thank you.
THANK YOU FOR APPEARING
ON OUR SHOW AGAIN
Emma left just as coolly as she came.
You just finished
the touching Tazza game with Sae-ho
who is probably
pursuing laughter in heaven too.
We will announce
the final winner at the end.
This is the final segment.
We joked around up until now,
but we will now take a minute
to make a silent tribute to Sae-ho
as we think about
-the time we had together.
-We need that.
At least for this segment,
let's try to be sincere…
PFFT
…as we close our eyes briefly
-and make a silent tribute…
-Okay.
…to Sae-ho.
Everyone,
a moment of silence.
TAKING A MOMENT OF SILENCE
Pick a number from one to four.
-Number three.
-Number three?
Oh, dear. It's a dud.
SAE-HO ALWAYS TRIED TO MAKE US DRAW LOTS
WHEN THERE WEREN'T ANY
We're doing good. Very good.
-We're doing great.
-Good.
SAE-HO AND I ALWAYS HAD
GOOD COMEDIC CHEMISTRY
OUR DEAR SAE-HO WOULD LOSE A GAME
TO GET A LAUGH OUT OF EVERYONE
He did it on purpose!
ALMOST FRIGHTENINGLY, HE SPARED NO EFFORT
FOR THE SAKE OF LAUGHTER
THEY BRIEFLY REMINISCE
THEIR TIME WITH SAE-HO
Please open your eyes now.
-My goodness.
-What the heck?
What the heck?
-It's a real portrait.
-That's too weird.
A PORTRAIT OF A SMILING SAE-HO IS PLACED
WHERE SAE-HO WAS SITTING
Now,
there is a last will
that Sae-ho left behind.
Jin-kyung,
can you read it since Sae-ho
trusted you and relied on you a lot?
Of course.
It's long.
It's Sae-ho's handwriting.
SHE CAREFULLY OPENS SAE-HO'S LAST WILL
"Under the moonlight,
I would like to express the gratitude
that I've kept in my heart
for a very long time."
"To the world
that embraced my quiet self."
"To my family
that introduced me to the world."
"To the friends
who hung out with me in this world
and laughed and cried with me."
"And the people around me who
shared laughter and tears with me."
"I want to sincerely thank you,
and because of you, I was happy."
"And I will always cherish those memories
while I rest in peace."
"Looking back, I regret not saying
thank you when I was grateful,
sorry when I should have apologized,
and saying more often that I love you
when I had the chance."
"Our awesome Screwballs members."
"Sook, Jin-kyung, Woo-jae, and Woo-young."
"I was truly happy to be able
to have such a good time with you."
"Especially Jin-kyung, thank you so much."
"When I was struggling and exhausted
with how pathetic I looked in the mirror,
you made me shine more than anyone."
"Do you remember the text message
you sent me not long after we first met?"
"'Sae-ho, what's up? Let's hang out.'"
"There must have been so many
more awesome people around you,
so why did she ask to hang out with me?"
"With those questions and with gratitude,
I cautiously asked you the day we met,
'Why did you ask to see me, Jin-kyung?'"
"That's when you said,
'You are a celebrity that
I want to see more than anyone.'"
YOU ARE THE CELEBRITY
THAT I WANT TO SEE MORE THAN ANYONE
"As my self-esteem was at rock-bottom,
I came home that day and cried a little."
"There is someone who
actually acknowledges me."
"Though I may not be
the brightest star in the world,
I was a bright star too."
"And so, I vowed to pick myself up
and keep going."
"Everything you said to me until now,
'Sae-ho, I think you're the funniest.'"
"'You're the best. You're awesome.'"
"'You're going to be more successful.'"
"'Anyone who gets to be with you
must be so happy.'"
-"'What's wrong with Woo-jae?'"
-What?
"'I'm so happy that
you're a good friend of mine.'"
Why did he add that?
I know. Why did he include that?
-Why did he do that?
-I didn't say that.
-It has nothing to do with the rest.
-You didn't add that, did you?
"Ever word--"
LAUGHING
It isn't "Ever word." It's "Every word."
"Every word you said
gave me so much strength
and I was so thankful."
"You have such a huge presence
in who I am today."
"And Jin-kyung,
don't try to deal with your struggles
on your own and please let me know."
"When you were having a hard time,
I felt disappointed because
I thought, 'She has such a good friend,
why isn't she sharing the load?'"
"Although I am the one leaving you now…
and if it's okay with you,
please take care of my wife
whom I'm leaving behind."
Gosh.
"Producer In-seok, Eun-young,
and the Screwballs crew."
"Thanks to you, I had a lot of fun."
"Give my spot to Nam Chang-hee."
"Chang-hee has really
hit his stride lately."
"Thank you, thank you,
and thank you so much."
"I am so sad
that this is our last goodbye,
but I'll rest with a bright smile,
so don't worry about me."
"May I rest in peace."
"Very nice to meet you."
"Thank you very much."
My goodness, Jin-kyung.
Why did he write such a sad letter?
On a variety show…
When we asked him to write it,
he seemed to have written it sincerely.
May I ask how you feel
after reading his letter?
We're on a variety show, right?
But that portrait is too…
Seeing him there like that…
It felt like a letter he wrote
before he really left us.
And I also realized this is
how Sae-ho must have felt all along.
I should show more love to him
and treat him better.
I didn't realize how precious it was
to have him by my side,
but I was reminded of how happy I was
to have him by my side.
All right. As Jin-kyung said,
we prepared this segment
into a variety show situation.
Are you okay, Woo-jae?
Why are you laughing?
-Hey.
-Hey!
-Someone died. How can you laugh?
-What's wrong with you?
Oh, come on.
-Is he crying?
-Why is he so heartless?
Hey, what's up with you too, Woo-young?
WHAT'S UP WITH WOO-YOUNG?
-Geez.
-They're such lunatics.
You lunatics.
ARE THEY REALLY SCREWBALLS?
Before Woo-jae and Woo-young
get any sadder…
SOBS
…let us now
-call the star Sae-ho back.
-Yes.
-Sae-ho.
SAE-HO IS RESURRECTED
Sae-ho.
We cried so much.
Why did you write such a sad letter?
At first, they told me
that they might create
a segment like this.
Since this is a variety show,
we talked about making it funny
so we can all have a good laugh.
But someone brought up the idea
of writing a last will,
so I told them that
I'd think about it too.
By taking the time to write this,
I thought I could
look back on the life I led.
From that point,
-the writing came pretty easily.
-I see.
-Really?
-Yeah, as I was writing it,
I realized that I didn't
want to make it sound funny.
I wanted to include my thanks as well.
After Jin-kyung sent me her first message
and when I was on my way to see her,
I wondered why such a huge star
would want to see me?
But she looked at me and said…
Well, Chang-hee was with me too.
She said, "The two of you are
such precious celebrities."
"And you are the celebrities
I want to see. Don't forget that."
When I came home after that,
I was so touched and thankful.
-I'm a bit embarrassed, but I did cry.
-You cried?
What I promised myself at that moment
was to always do
a bit more than
what I can do for Jin-kyung,
so I expressed my thanks to her in that.
When you asked me to
say something nice about Sae-ho,
I jokingly told you that I'd do it later,
but lately, I have been a bit depressed
and have been feeling down.
I was struggling.
Sae-ho saw that
I was feeling a bit depressed
while we were shooting on set,
so he kept on calling me
from that point on.
He called me once the next morning,
twice around lunch time,
and once in the evening.
"What are you doing now, Jin-kyung?"
I felt closer to him than family
because of that.
He has always been
such a thoughtful friend.
THANKFUL FOR THOUGHTFUL SAE-HO
Yeah, the two of you
have such a great friendship.
We did the Cho Sae-ho Show earlier,
but today was truly joyful
because I got to
do something in my own name
that I dreamt about for a long time.
I also thought we could
make people laugh until we die.
The time we will have together from now on
will feel even more precious.
That was what today made me feel.
You are really awesome, Sae-ho.
Sae-ho has more depth to him
than we think.
-No.
-And he's very cool.
When we did the speed quiz
on the Cho Sae-ho Show,
we were worried
it might be too much for him.
So Producer In-seok even asked
if we should stop since we did so many.
Let's just do one round.
We can do more. I'm totally okay with it.
He said in a very low voice.
As long as I can make people happy…
He said, "As long as
I can make people happy, I can never…"
-Good job.
-It was nothing.
I should thank you.
You let me have a great time.
-I don't know if it was funny though.
-It was so funny.
I'm so glad.
I'M SO GLAD
That's when I realized once again
that he is truly admirable.
Sometimes, he isn't as funny,
but I really saw…
-We learned a lot from him.
-…the very professional side of him today.
To be honest, it would not have been
easy to offer his car key as a prize.
-Yeah.
-So…
-He gave his everything.
-We expressed our gratitude,
we expressed how touched we were…
-The car key is the car key.
-Yes.
His belongings including his car key
will be given to Jin-kyung
who gave the biggest laugh to the Tazza.
JIN-KYUNG ACQUIRES HIS BELONGINGS
Let me make this clear.
Only the car key is the gift.
NOT LISTENING
I've never ridden it before.
Me neither.
-I've never driven one.
-I've never had a ride in it.
You know, your wife draws…
-very well.
-She draws so well.
-She drew it?
-I'm so thankful.
She wanted to give me this as a present
for our one year anniversary,
so this is very precious to me.
-Gosh.
-Are you sure I can have it?
-It's a gift.
-Are you taking it?
-I'm going to take it.
-This?
No, you can't. Sell it back to me.
-What about the key?
-What about this?
That should be returned.
-To whom?
-The key?
Me.
-What the heck?
-Look.
I wasn't told that
I had to give them away.
What about these gifts?
That's a book of poems
and the Screwballs' po…
-What?
-Po, what?
The poster for Screwballs.
The poster.
You all did such a wonderful job today.
Thank you.
-Thank you.
-Good job, everyone!
Screwballs is such an awesome team.
On the next episode of Screwballs.
A new sun is rising!
One person isn't well,
but we wish you a happy new year.
You can wash yourselves for the new year.
We're okay, but we don't
want these guys to get the wrong idea.
GET THE WRONG IDEA?
Get your mind out of the gutter.
Us?
-Us?
-I'm still worried.
I'M OKAY WITH IT
We're an asexual variety show.
I've never been to the men's bath.
-Wash up now?
-How much are we washing up?
The Group Deconstruction Show.
You'll go into the bath
and lay bare your true self.
DIG INTO THE SCREWBALLS' TRUE SELVES
It's Netflix,
but can we show our dead skin cells?
I see dead skin cells.
I DIDN'T WANT THEM TO DIG THIS DEEP
I already told you that
-you'd see dead skin cells.
-Lie down.
Come on! Are you crazy?
Oh, no.
This is really a deconstruction show.
Bare yourself
and find your personal color.
It doesn't suit you.
ISN'T THIS PRETTY?
It's the worst.
THE WORST
Shall we try vivid colors?
What the heck?
Can she criticize me like that?
WE THOUGHT
THEY'D GET ALONG IN THE NEW YEAR
No.
THAT'S NOT THE RIGHT COLOR
Let's measure your chest.
Why?
My eyes!
Your chest is size M.
Your stomach is size XL.
My stomach is XL?
LAUGHING OUT LOUD
She's saying my chest is small
and my belly is big.
I quit!
I quit this segment.
CAN THE SCREWBALLS DECONSTRUCTION SHOW
END WELL?
ENJOY THE HIGHLIGHTS AND THE BTS CLIPS
ON STUDIO++'S YOUTUBE CHANNEL
"REBOOT" BY KYOUNGSEO
(SCREWBALLS OST)
SCREWBALLS
Subtitle translation by: Ilyoung Kim