The legendary K-pop idol of 18 years,
2PM's main dancer.
Off the stage, he's a true screwball.
The star of today's
Deconstruction Show is Woo-young.
WOO-YOUNG'S DECONSTRUCTION SHOW
With Woo-young as the leader,
you'll try to be the actual 2PM.
There will be an end-of-month evaluation.
You're insane.
There will be a punishment for the person
who scores the lowest.
They have to go out to the street.
In front of at least five people,
you have to do a solo performance
without any music.
It's "I'll Be Back"!
THEIR DANCE SKILLS CAN'T EVEN BE EVALUATED
SNORT
-And sweep up.
-You got it.
ONE, TWO, ONE, TWO
One, two.
BUT THEY DO THEIR BEST TO LEARN THE DANCE
THE TIME FOR EVALUATION HAS COME
CLEAN TRANSITIONS
PRECISE STEPS
PERFECTLY SYNCHRONIZED TEAMWORK
PERFECTLY REPLICATING 2PM
THE MEMBERS TRULY DID THEIR BEST
WHAT IS THE RESULT?
I think you have gotten even worse
than back then.
LAUGHING OUT LOUD
Jin-kyung's average score is five points.
ALONG WITH CRITICISM
JIN-KYUNG COMES IN LAST
AS LONG AS IT'S NOT US
SHE IS SET TO DANCE ON THE STREET
WITHOUT ANY MUSIC
The menu is awesome today.
It's cold outside, so wear these gloves.
He says the cafeteria food is good.
I'm sick and tired of them.
THE OUTSTANDING DANCERS
MOVE TO THE CAFETERIA
While she goes through
the punishment outside,
you can eat.
-Really? We can eat?
-Can we eat?
-Oh, I see.
-How can we do that?
I'd feel bad.
How could we eat without Jin-kyung?
-Gosh, this is good.
-It's really good.
SOMEONE'S TRAY IS GETTING COLD
-Is it okay?
-It's really good.
-Yeah.
-Gosh.
THIS IS EARTH IN ANOTHER MULTIVERSE
5PM EXISTS IN THIS WORLD INSTEAD OF 2PM
5PM'S UNIQUELY OUTSTANDING DANCER
THE MAIN DANCER TAEK-GYEON
THE ONE THAT MESMERIZED
THE K-POP WORLD WITH HER DANCE
HAS GONE OUT TO THE STREET
TO MEET THE PUBLIC
SHE WENT SHIRTLESS(?)
NOT REALIZING THIS WOULD HAPPEN
Hello.
QUICKLY PASSES BY
LOOKING AROUND
This area is very busy and bright.
It's so bright out here.
JYP IS LOCATED RIGHT IN DOWNTOWN SEOUL
A lot of people are
staring at you over there.
WORD HAS ALREADY GONE OUT
THAT THIS WILL BE FUNNY
The weather is too nice.
I wish it was a bit gloomy.
-It is a really nice day.
-The sun is shining so bright.
The sun is high in the sky.
You get a good day like this
maybe 10 days out of the year.
How can it be so sunny?
That's why you're dressed for the weather.
With your top off.
DRESSED FOR THE WATERBOMB FESTIVAL
You'll play the music, right?
-You dance without music.
-Without music?
Then, do I do this?
We'll prepare chairs for the audience.
That's it.
You remember all of it.
-It's without music.
-Yes, without music.
SHE PRACTICES HARD FOR NOW
LEAVING ALL THE BURNING GAZES BEHIND
SEARCHING FOR AN AUDIENCE
GETTING READY JUST LIKE THAT?
Wait.
-Ask for their consent.
-Okay.
-Would you like to briefly see me dance?
-Yes.
-May I film you?
-There are people inside too.
IT'S LUNCH TIME
SO THERE ARE TONS OF WORKERS FROM NEARBY
AND SO, WITHOUT ANY RHYME OR REASON
SHE PREPARES FOR "I'LL BE BACK"
Unbelievable.
NOW THAT SHE HAS TO DANCE,
SHE IS SO EMBARRASSED
This is mortifying.
Why does it have to be so sunny today?
WHY DOES IT HAVE TO BE SO SUNNY TODAY?
FINALLY, THE MAIN DANCER FOR 5PM
RISES UP FROM HER CROUCHED POSITION!
FLUTTERING
DUM DUDUM
THE AUDIENCE FROM THE VIP SEATS
REACT IN A SUBTLE WAY
PASSING BY QUICKLY
LOOKING AWAY
THE R SEATS DON'T COMPLAIN
BECAUSE IT'S FREE
SPEECHLESS
THERE ARE SO MANY WEIRD PEOPLE OUT THERE
I WAS RAISED PROPERLY
SHOULD I BE WATCHING THIS?
WHAT AN UNPLEASANT SIGHT!
NEGATIVELY KILLING THE PERFORMANCE
THE VIP GUEST IS
SLOWLY GETTING TIRED OF IT
THE PERFORMANCE IS ALMOST OVER
SPINNING
BUT HER ENDING WAS PERFECT
It's over.
GIVE HER A BIG HAND FIRST
THANK YOU FOR WATCHING
How was my dance?
-You dance well.
-Really?
YOU COULD HARDLY WATCH THOUGH
Your children are kind.
They're so kind.
-Here.
-Thank you.
-Thank you for watching.
You weren't shocked, were you?
SHE DOESN'T DENY IT
Okay. Study hard.
Let's go.
SHE STILL NEEDS MORE VIEWERS
Sir, please join them.
I'm going to dance.
-She'll be performing.
-I'm performing.
SHE SUCCESSFULLY RECRUITS
SOMEONE ON THEIR WAY TO A CAFE
I think you have gotten even worse
than back then.
YOU HAVE GOTTEN EVEN WORSE THAN THEN
EVERYBODY SCOFFED
AT THE TRAGIC DANCER TAEK-GYEON
I WILL PROVE MY TALENT HERE TODAY
OH…
SHE DANCES WELL
HER DANCE MOVES BRING PEOPLE TO A HALT
SHE USES THE STAGE TO THE FULLEST
HIS MOUTH DRIES
THE TIME THAT SEEMED LIKE
IT WOULD NEVER END COMES TO PASS
ENDING POSE
THUNDERING APPLAUSE
You dance well.
-Was it okay?
-Yes.
Oh, really?
-You dance so well without music.
-Yes.
You were different
from when you were in Unnies.
Really?
THE EVALUATION HAS BEEN OVERTURNED
-I'll watch the show.
-Thank you for watching me dance.
JIN-KYUNG CLEARED HER MISSION
-Thank you.
-It's so good.
THE MEMBERS ARE BUSY EATING
-Jin-kyung.
-You even locked the door to eat?
-Yes, sorry.
-No.
-Good job, Jin-kyung.
-Thanks.
The food looks great.
-It's so good.
-Is it?
Jin-kyung, I waited for you to eat.
YOU SHOULD AT LEAST FINISH CHEWING
BEFORE YOU LIE
This is the famous
home cooked meal at JYP.
YOU PRACTICALLY INHALED IT
This place is the pride and joy of JYP.
It's their cafeteria
that serves organic meals
-called JYPBOB.
-Yes.
THE FANCY BUFFET LINEUP
Here's all that I ate.
I ate nothing to eat JYPBOB.
I can really eat two bowls of this.
A DELICIOUS AND HEALTHY
HOME-COOKED STYLE MEAL
FOR THE STAFF AND TRAINEES
There isn't even a little bit of MSG.
There's no MSG.
-How can it taste this good without MSG?
-Yeah.
-They want to know if it's free.
-Is it free
to eat at this cafeteria?
-How much is this?
-Basically,
if you apply for it, it's free.
If you apply for it in advance?
-This is?
-If you apply, it's free.
But if you haven't applied for it,
lunch is 8,000 won
and dinner is 6,000 won.
Everyone must apply for it then.
Most people try to.
Even if you were in a rush,
you can eat this meal at lunch
-for 8,000 won, right?
-Yeah.
This place is so nice.
-Isn't it so nice?
-It's so good.
TAKING A HUGE BITE
This is insane.
The stew is so good.
When I ate the stew,
I got a big whiff of
the aroma from the mushrooms.
It was so good.
-It's so good.
-Look.
The suyuk is so good too.
The geotjeori is so good too, Sook.
Let me see.
ENJOYING A PEACEFUL LUNCH
All right.
-Yes?
-Keep eating.
-Just relax and listen.
-I got a bad feeling
so I couldn't eat comfortably.
-I think something's up.
-No, not at all.
Well, since today is
Woo-young's Deconstruction Show,
we want to see
some other sides of Woo-young.
As the youngest, Woo-young has been
doted on so much by the other members,
but at times, he has to endure
the sacrifice and frustration too.
HE HAS TO ENDURE
THE SACRIFICE AND FRUSTRATION TOO
WANTING TO CRY
I endure so much.
Who endures what? Do you mean us?
The youngest endured sacrifice?
I can finally speak up now.
So what if Woo-young was the oldest?
-Flip the Age.
-We'll play Flip the Age starting now.
Hey, can I eat that?
What are you doing? You have yours.
How dare you?
While we're in the cafeteria,
your ages will be in reverse order.
Think of it as your ages being flipped.
Then, Sook is the youngest?
THE 50-YEAR-OLD YOUNGEST MEMBER
-Yes.
-Really?
So Woo-jae is older than me
and this guy is the oldest.
"This guy" is oldest?
THIS GUY?
I mean, Woo-young is the oldest.
And I'm second oldest.
HE SHRINKS BACK WITH ONE LOOK
Yes, Woo-young. Please speak.
Hey, Jin-kyung.
Yeah?
Did she just say "yeah?"
-That's what I say to older friends.
-Really?
Sook, can you get us some water?
SHE HASN'T BEEN ORDERED BY ANYONE
IN A LONG TIME
SCOFFS
-Bring more geotjeori on your way back.
-Yeah.
-I'll be the only one suffering.
-Well, no.
Woo-young, they keep ordering me around.
Guys, come on.
Sook is such a nice girl, you know.
TOUCHED
-Then--
-Why are you still here?
WHY ARE YOU STILL HERE?
You know, Jin-kyung is close to the door.
Why don't you go and get it?
The two of you can go together.
Hey, Jin-kyung.
-I want doenjang soup.
-Me too.
Jin-kyung can get some more doenjang soup.
-Sook, let's go together.
-Yeah?
-Let's go.
-Woo-jae's soup and--
-And my stew.
How long are we doing this?
Ten minutes.
Ten minutes? Okay.
-Guys.
-Ten minutes? What happens after that?
What happens…
Get some Coke Zero from the first floor.
Woo-jae.
-Give me money then.
-Yeah, you have to.
I'll pay you afterwards.
Give me two million won.
Why these brats…
-Girls, get going.
-Doenjang soup and geotjeori?
You're letting dust in.
THEY LEAVE AS IF THEY'RE KICKED OUT
-Geez.
-Unbelievable.
Why are they eating so much? Those jerks.
How could they?
They always order us around
when we are eating.
They're so annoying.
They're so infuriating.
This is bad only for us.
Shouldn't they get their own food?
Why did they tell us to get it?
You'll wolf down some too.
YOU'LL WOLF DOWN SOME TOO
LAUGHING AWKWARDLY
Did you say "wolf down?"
I'm sorry.
How dare you speak to
someone older like that?
You haven't been taught
proper social etiquette.
I'm sorry.
I forgot you're older than me.
WHILE SOOK IS BEING VICIOUSLY SCOLDED
-Hey, Sae-ho.
-Yes.
-Woo-jae.
-Yes, can I help you?
-Yes, Woo-young.
-Look, Sae-ho.
-Yes.
Why are you such a messy eater?
I'm sorry.
-The thing is--
-You messy jerk.
-You're such a messy jerk.
-The thing is…
-Why are you so messy?
-It was so good that I ate in haste.
-Do you have no manners?
-I'm sorry.
-I'm so sorry.
-Hey, Woo-jae.
Sweep your hair to the side.
Let me see your eyes when I speak to you.
THE JERK IS UNAFFECTED
BY THE FLIP THE AGE GAME
Our dear Woo-jae.
Give me a hug. Please.
Just this once. Can I kiss you?
I really like Woo-jae, you know.
-Just hold me.
-Why are you so dirty?
-I used to like Woo-jae so much.
-Hey, Woo-jae.
Woo-jae, we are brothers.
HE'S PISSING ME OFF AGAIN
Why do you hate it so much?
I really like Woo-jae.
-Sae-ho may lack in certain aspects…
-You know,
-…but you should embrace him.
-I really
like both of you.
-Go away.
-Come on.
-Try hugging him. His skin feels weird.
-Hug me.
Let's hug.
I like you both so much.
SOULESS EYES
I really like you.
Did Sae-ho always smell bad like this?
Listen, Woo-young.
You keep saying
that I'm messy and that I smell bad.
I'm married now.
I got married last year.
MEANWHILE, THE YOUNGEST TWO THAT WENT OUT
They love kimchi.
REPLENISH THE FOODS WHILE COMPLAINING
Here they come.
Thanks, Jin-kyung.
THE FOOD DELIVERERS RETURN
BUT SOOK IS MISSING?
Where's Sook?
-Don't sit down.
-Sook is still getting food.
What if she gets lost?
She's only five years old.
WHAT IF SHE GETS LOST?
SHE'S ONLY FIVE YEARS OLD
How can you leave
the five-year-old behind?
THERE ISN'T MUCH TIME LEFT
IN FLIP THE AGE GAME
-Hey, Jin-kyung.
-Yes?
When you grow up…
He makes me nervous.
Any romantic notions about marriage?
ANY ROMANTIC NOTIONS ABOUT MARRIAGE?
-Since we're still young.
-Since we're all young…
I'm going to kill him today.
THEY END THE GAME TO PROTECT THE MEMBERS
So this time, we prepared
a simple game that contains
what Woo-young wanted to tell you.
It's called Hey, You Buster.
-Do you know the game?
-No.
I think I've played it before.
Let me explain.
It goes counterclockwise.
-Okay.
Jin-kyung, you will look at someone,
-point at them, and say, "Hey!"
-Okay.
The person next to Jin-kyung
will say, "You!"
You!
-Then, Sae-ho will say, "Buster!"
-Okay.
The person he pointed at
will start off the "Hey" again.
It starts all over.
Then, whoever you choose
for "Hey" and "You" means nothing.
-Only "Buster" matters.
-Only "Buster."
The point of this game is…
I said that "Hey" and "You"
don't mean anything, right?
-Yeah.
-But if someone is chosen…
MEANINGLESS CHOICES
You're startled.
There's a rhythm to it.
It goes,
"Hey, You Buster. Hey, You Buster."
Let's do a trial run.
-Hey.
-You.
-Buster.
-No.
-I'm the one who should say "Buster."
-Yes.
Jin-kyung showed us
exactly what not to do.
She showed us the bad example.
The only choice that matters is Buster.
Yeah.
DID SHE REALLY UNDERSTAND IT?
-The person who loses has to clean this.
-Yeah.
-Yes. Cleaning it all up.
-Okay.
-Sounds fun.
-Should we start with Jin-kyung?
Two, two, three, four.
Hey, you buster
-Hey.
-You.
Buster!
-Hey. What's up with her?
-What?
-She did this.
-You got it wrong.
SHE PLAYED AT THE LEVEL WE EXPECTED
We're going to eat comfortably today.
After Sook's turn,
it goes back to your turn, Jin-kyung.
Got it? Please?
-Here we go.
-Okay.
-From me?
Ready, go.
Hey, you buster
Hey!
STARTLED
You!
NOW, IT'S MY TURN
-Buster!
-What the heck?
You!
Buster!
LAUGHING
What the heck?
She's so transparent.
My gosh. She is too transparent.
-Wasn't it my turn?
-Yes.
SOOK SHOULD HAVE SAID "BUSTER"
BUT THIS PERSON DECIDED TO BARGE IN
-Start over.
-From whom?
-From you? Ready, go.
-From you.
Hey, you buster
We're starting from you.
What are you--
-Hey!
-You!
Buster!
SOOK'S TURN AS SHE WAS
POINTED OUT AS "BUSTER"
Buster!
AND AT THE SAME TIME
HER PUPILS MOVE RAPIDLY
Hey!
You!
WHAT HAS GOTTEN INTO HER?
Buster!
-Hey!
-You!
Shouldn't I say "You"?
Since I said "Buster",
should I be the one that says "You"?
-What?
-Isn't that right?
-No.
-I said "Buster."
-The one beside you.
-You said, "Hey."
-But I--
"Buster" came to me.
Buster.
Buster!
-Hey!
-You!
Shouldn't I say "You"?
HE SAID "HEY" BUT TRIED TO STEAL "YOU" TOO
Buster.
Hey!
LAUGHING OUT LOUD
BURST OUT LAUGHING
LAUGHING
I'm sorry, but you looked stupid just now.
-It's very confusing.
-It is.
It's very confusing.
-Hey!
-You see--
I said, "Buster"!
But he said, no, I said "Buster."
-Hey! Wait, it is your turn.
-Yeah.
-So what did I say?
-You said all of it.
You did "Hey" and "You."
HE WANTED TO SAY BOTH OF THEM
He tried to attack,
but he fell for it himself.
-It's very confusing.
-Okay. Let's try again.
This isn't easy.
Ready, go.
Hey, you buster
-Hey!
-You!
It's your turn.
-No, it isn't.
-Why not?
This is so frustrating!
-You!
-But…
It starts from here.
RECEIVING MIRROR THERAPY THROUGH SOOK
-Who did you point to?
-It starts from here.
Who did you choose?
-You.
-It doesn't matter.
-Oh, yeah.
EMBARRASSED
That's right.
Did you spike this or something?
HOW COULD THEY BE SO BAD?
-Let's try again.
-Okay.
-Whose turn? Jin-kyung's?
-One, two. One, two, three, four.
Hey, you buster
-Hey.
-You!
Buster!
HE POINTED OUT JIN-KYUNG FOR "BUSTER"!
JIN-KYUNG MUST SAY "HEY" NOW
Hey.
You!
Buster!
Hey!
THE CRISIS RETURNS
You.
-You.
-Buster!
-Hey!
-You!
Buster!
IN THE MEANTIME, SHE FLINCHES
-Buster!
-Hey!
You.
-Buster!
-Your finger.
WE'LL LET IT SLIDE THIS ONE TIME
-Hey!
-You!
-Buster!
Buster!
Hey.
WHAT?
BECAUSE OF SOOK'S "BUSTER"
Hey!
IT STARTS AGAIN FROM JIN-KYUNG
-What's up?
-It's Woo-young.
WOO-YOUNG WHO ZONED OUT LOSES 1 POINT
-We played for a long time.
-Yeah.
You played for a while.
-There were some risky moments.
-I get it now.
I get it now.
From Woo-young.
Hey, you buster
-Hey.
-You.
-Buster.
-Hey.
You.
-Buster.
-Hey.
-You.
-She's wrong.
-What?
-It was my turn.
-That's right.
He said "Buster."
I said, "Hey."
-He said, "Hey."
-He said, "Buster."
Can we check?
-No, it wasn't.
-He definitely said, "Hey."
And it was my turn.
It was my turn to say, "You."
And Jin-kyung said "You" during my turn.
That's why she got it wrong.
You think you're so great?
For your reference,
Woo-jae hasn't gotten it wrong yet.
-Wow.
-Yeah, he's smart.
I'm not smart.
Let's try to do something about that.
Let's do it.
-I don't think he'll fall for it.
-I'm not smart.
No, I won't say anything further.
I'm not smart.
These guys are just too dim.
YOU ALREADY SAID IT ALL
He hasn't gotten it wrong yet.
-Let's attack Woo-jae.
-He's a genius.
-Yeah, attack Woo-jae.
But this game is
the simplest game we've played this year.
-Ready, go.
-This is the hardest one.
-You start.
-Why him?
-You can't get me.
-Start from her.
Ready, go.
Hey, you buster
Hey.
ATTACKS WOO-JAE AS PLANNED
OF COURSE, HE ISN'T FAZED AT ALL
-Hey.
-You!
-Buster!
-Hey.
You.
-Buster.
-You should say it, Jin-kyung.
Why?
Because it's the Buster's turn!
-It's your turn to say "Buster."
-I did it because you didn't.
-You got it wrong too.
-It's because of her.
-Woo-young got it wrong too.
-Geez.
Can the four of them
try doing it without me?
-Can they?
-Shall we?
-I don't think I'll ever get it wrong.
-Go over there.
Can we try an extra round?
But this one doesn't count.
-I really don't think I'll get it wrong.
-Okay.
-All right. Let's do well, guys.
-I'm getting sleepy.
AND SO, A GAME AMONG THEMSELVES BEGINS
-One, two. One, two, three, four.
-Three, four.
Hey, you buster
-Who's going to go first?
-Hey!
You.
Buster.
Hey!
You!
FLINCHING
LAUGHING
-I'm right, aren't I?
-No.
PURE INNOCENCE
Jin-kyung is so funny.
Jin-kyung was…
EMBARRASSED
Do you know what Jin-kyung did
when it was her turn?
She went like this and started choosing.
-She went like this.
-Her face was…
We were going around
and doing Hey, You Buster but she…
AN INTENSE BATTLE OF WITS WITH HERSELF
-Who got it wrong the most?
-This is fun.
This is the current result.
Sook got it wrong four times.
-That's a lot.
-It isn't.
Sae-ho got it wrong three times.
Woo-young got it wrong three times.
Jin-kyung got it wrong 10 times.
-What?
-Gosh, this is…
THE UNMATCHED TALENT!
It's because you couldn't focus, right?
All you have to do is focus.
SO THEY DECIDED TO
TAKE OUT THEIR SECRET WEAPON
TO INCREASE THEIR FOCUS
WITH EVERY DROP OF FOCUS POURED INTO IT
AND WITH 5PM'S PRIDE ON THE LINE
AN ALL-OUT MATCH IS ABOUT TO UNFOLD
One, two, three, four.
Hey, you buster
From you.
-Hey.
-You!
Buster!
-Hey!
-You!
Buster!
Hey!
SOOK ATTACKS SAE-HO THIS TIME
You!
OOPS
Bye, Sae-ho.
-The two of you.
-Why?
Why me?
-He didn't know.
-The two of us
should play a one-on-one 369 game.
-The loser has to clean up.
-Okay.
Shall we just make them
play the Tomato game?
-The Tomato game?
-Let's do the Tomato game.
-What is that?
-To, Ma, To.
We just exchange the syllables like this.
I guarantee that they'll do To, To, Ma.
Ready, go.
-To.
-Ma.
TO MA TO MA?
-To.
-Ma.
To.
-Come on, man.
-Come on.
Let's try again.
I don't want to do it again!
There's no do-over in this.
Come on, man.
-That was a clean loss.
-Come on.
-No do-overs.
-To, Ma, To, Ma was a clean loss.
-He basically ended the scene.
-Come on.
WHAT A CLEAN ENDING
To, Ma, To, Ma, and then, the scene ended.
Let's go down now.
-Clap the slate.
-Do it.
-Okay.
-One, two, three.
-To, To.
-Ma, Ma.
CLEAN ENDING
AFTER THEIR MEAL
THEY GATHER AT THE STUDIO AGAIN
All right.
Let's continue with
Woo-young's Deconstruction Show.
There is a word that has been
representing you lately, Woo-young.
-What he's doing whenever we call him.
-Mixing?
-Mixing.
Can you briefly explain what
this mixing incident is about, Woo-jae?
The mixing incident?
Let me explain the mixing incident.
First of all, whenever we contact him,
he says mysteriously,
"I'm mixing." Like a word that's trending.
We heard it so many times
that the word "mixing" stood out to us.
-Yes.
-That's too funny.
We don't know whether he really was mixing
-or not.
-Who knows?
-No matter how many times…
-Whenever I called him,
-he said he's working on a song.
-Yeah.
That's why we prepared this game.
-You made a game?
-It's a game inspired by your mixing life.
It's called Mixing Baby.
Mixing Baby?
-Oh, mixing baby
-Yes.
-From now--
-I think I know what it'll be about.
We're going to show you photos
of virtual children created by AI.
These children's faces are a mix
of two celebrities' faces.
-I see.
-Oh.
That's why it's called Mixing Baby?
You have to guess
which two people's faces have been mixed.
-Then--
-It's wrong if you only guess one.
You have to guess both.
Then, these are two people
who are of the opposite sex, right?
-Yes, they're all opposite sexes.
-Okay.
This is an individual round.
We'll rank you by the number
of correct answers you get.
From five points to one,
the points will be given
-according to your rank.
-These are hard to guess.
When the game is over,
the first place will
-get an amazing, limited-edition prize.
-Limited?
You may look forward to it.
-Okay.
-Why am I not excited about it at all?
THE LIMITED-EDITION PRIZE
IS REALLY WAITING FOR THEM
There may be someone
who doesn't understand,
so let me give you a practice question.
Show us the baby picture.
Mixing Baby.
How adorable.
-Whose faces have been combined?
-I can totally see the faces.
-Whose faces are in it?
-Isn't it PSY?
I got it. Lee Su-ji.
Lee Su-ji…
LEE SU-JI AND?
-And PSY.
-Okay. Lee Su-ji and PSY.
-That's right.
-Yeah, it's clearly PSY.
-Really?
-That's right. I can tell.
Why was this a practice round?
-Why?
-Gosh.
This is hard.
That's how these questions
will be presented.
You can call out "I got it!"
whenever you are ready to guess.
It's only correct if you guess
-both mom and dad correctly.
-This is hard.
One of the parents
is a Screwballs' member.
-Really? Okay.
-I see.
Shall we begin?
-Yes.
WHO ARE THE MOM AND DAD?
SON, DAUGHTER
Woo-jae?
Who are the mom and dad?
The daughter is so cute.
-I think…
-Who looks like that?
-I think I'm the dad.
-Yes, I see Woo-jae.
It's Woo-jae?
-Woo-young.
-Go ahead.
Woo-jae and Song Eun-i.
Wrong.
-I got it.
-Go ahead, Sook.
Woo-jae and Jung Yi-rang.
-Wrong.
-Is Woo-jae in it?
The left one is so me.
Wait, is it Jin-kyung?
The mom is one of you guys.
-What?
-I see. It's Jin-kyung.
-It's Jin-kyung.
-But those aren't my eyes.
-I got it.
-I got it. Jin-kyung and Cha Eun-woo.
-Wrong.
-I got it.
Jin-kyung and G-Dragon.
-Wrong.
-They're both comedians.
Comedians?
I got it. Nam Chang-hee and Jin-kyung.
-I got it.
-Sorry. I said they're both comedians.
What? Aren't they both comedians?
Isn't Jin-kyung…
WEREN'T YOU A COMEDIAN?
-What?
-Okay. Woo-jae, go ahead.
Sook and Nam Chang-hee.
Wrong.
That's me?
THEY'RE STRUGGLING FROM THE FIRST QUESTION
Sook is correct, right?
-Yes, Sook is correct.
-What?
I got it. Yoon Jung-soo and Sook?
Wrong.
-Gu Bon-seung and Sook.
-Wrong.
-Who is it?
-Gosh, this is so hard.
-Let's reveal the answer now. Show us.
-That's me?
Go back.
ANSWER: KIM YOUNG-CHUL, KIM SOOK
-You can see his sister's face.
-I see it.
-In the right one.
The son's face should have been longer.
She's right.
-The right one is like him.
-Yeah.
-How interesting.
-This is really hard.
-It's fun.
-Next one.
Moving onto the next one.
QUESTION NUMBER 2
I got it.
-Jin-kyung and Park Myung-soo.
-Wrong.
-Is it me?
-No, it's me.
I can see me.
-Woo-young?
-Yeah, it's me.
-Is it Woo-young?
-No.
-I don't think it's Woo-young.
-Is it Sae-ho?
I got it. Jin-kyung…
and Park Myung-soo.
You already said that.
I just said that?
IT HASN'T EVEN BEEN 30 SECONDS
-You said Jin-kyung and Park Myung-soo.
-Yes?
That's wrong.
I THINK WE'RE ALMOST THERE
I got it. Sook and Park Myung-soo.
That's correct.
SON, DAUGHTER
Those are Myung-soo's wrinkles.
POWERFUL FROWN LINES
-But I don't see Sook.
-Where is Sook in those photos?
I used to be pretty like that daughter
when I was young.
What happened to you?
A LOT OF THINGS HAPPENED
Moving on.
THESE CHILDREN LOOK TOUGH
-How cute.
Kids like these are the cutest.
-Look at how cute the daughter is.
-Yeah.
I got it.
Jin-kyung and Kang Ho-dong.
No.
HE LOOKS PRETTY STRONG
-I got it. Jin-kyung and Ma Dong-seok.
-That's correct.
That's correct.
It was Ma Dong-seok.
I can see Dong-seok.
-It wasn't Sae-ho?
-There are some hints.
-Yeah. There is.
-There are hints if you look carefully.
Let's move on to the next one.
-Choo Sung-hoon.
-It's Choo Sung-hoon.
-I got it. Jin-kyung and Choo Sung-hoon.
-Correct.
I'LL DEFINITELY LOSE
TO THE OFFSPRING OF CHOO SUNG-HOON
You're good at this.
Who's this?
Hang on.
THESE CHILDREN LOOK STYLISH
I got it.
Sook and Car, the Garden.
Yeah, kind of.
WELL-KNOWN HAIRY GUY WITH A FULL BEARD
-Wrong.
-I got it. Jin-kyung and Car, the Garden.
-What?
IS IT NOT CAR, THE GARDEN?
I got it. Ko Chang-seok and Sook.
Correct.
SON, DAUGHTER
Yeah, that is Ko Chang-seok. You're right.
You can see it. It gives you hints.
-So funny.
-Here's the next one.
I wish I could get at least one.
THEY LOOK LIKE THEY HAVE A FREE SPIRIT
Is it me?
THE BLEACHED HAIR AND THE BEARD
ARE THE HINTS
-I got it.
-It's Sae-ho.
-Who is it?
-No, it could be Sae-ho.
-Yoo Byung-jae and…
-What?
Jin-kyung.
SON, DAUGHTER
REASONABLE APPROACH!
-Wrong.
-Yoo Byung-jae and Sook.
Correct.
I was going to say Sook.
-You got it from me, right?
-I did.
-Yoo Byung-jae and me?
-I can see it.
You can see it.
Here's the next one.
Who is that?
What the heck? Why is the daughter…
-It's Sae-ho.
-The eyes…
I can see the person's face
from the daughter. Who is it?
WHO IS THAT?
Who is that?
Our producers guessed it immediately
because of the daughter.
The daughter?
The daughter.
SON, DAUGHTER
-Who is it?
-I got it. Sae-ho and Cho Hye-lyun.
That's incorrect.
Woo-young and Cho Hye-lyun.
Wrong.
IS IT NOT HYE-LYUN?
-They guessed it because of the daughter?
-Is it Jin-kyung?
I can see the face from the daughter.
Is it Hye-seon?
-I see Sae-ho too.
-I got it.
Sae-ho and Kim Hye-seon.
Wrong.
Woo-young and Kim Hye-seon.
-Wrong.
-I got it.
Woo-jae and Kim Hye-seon.
That's right.
HE GOT HIS ANSWER STOLEN AGAIN
SHE GOT ALL OF MOM'S MANLY ENERGY
Hey, you can't even
recognize your own daughter?
-I wasn't even close.
-Can't you recognize your own daughter?
Here's the next one.
NEXT QUESTION
Wait. I can see the face.
Oh, is that…
I got it. Sae-ho and Shin Gi-ru.
-Wrong.
-I got it. Woo-young and Shin Gi-ru.
That's correct.
SHE STOLE ANOTHER ONE
You can totally see Gi-ru's face, right?
LOOK CAREFULLY
THERE ARE TONS OF HINTS
NEXT QUESTION
WHO IS THAT?
-I've seen those lips before.
-Yeah, you're right.
I'VE SEEN THOSE LIPS BEFORE
-I've seen those lips before.
-Whose lips are those?
-They look very familiar, right?
-Yes.
Whose lips are those?
I got it. Jin-kyung and P.O?
-I can see P.O.
-Right? Can you see him too?
Wrong.
It's a model and comedian couple.
It must be Jin-kyung.
LET ME SEE
-Chang-hee and Jin-kyung.
-Me and Yang Se-chan.
-Who did you say, Jin-kyung?
-Yang Se-chan.
-And?
-Hong Jin-kyung.
-That's correct.
-That's Se-chan's lips.
-It's Se-chan's mouth.
-I see.
-I thought those lips looked familiar.
-I knew I've seen those lips.
As a way of taking a break,
shall we try to guess our members--
-Among ourselves?
-Okay.
-I didn't guess any.
-Here it is.
SON, DAUGHTER
-I got it.
-Woo-jae.
-Sae-ho and Sook.
-No.
-Wrong.
-I got it.
Woo-jae and Jin-kyung.
-Wrong.
-I got it.
-Sae-ho and Jin-kyung.
-Correct.
CORRECT
-You see, that's your hat.
-You're right.
It's the one from your profile photo.
JIN-KYUNG IS WEARING SAE-HO'S HAT
-So that's how you guess them.
-You're right.
Your son and daughter are cute.
Interesting.
Let's make it a little more difficult.
-You guys aren't in these at all.
-Okay.
-This may be a bit hard.
-This requires skill.
-It'll be fun from now.
-Yeah.
NEXT QUESTION
THEY LOOK VERY MISCHIEVOUS
I got it.
Kang Jae-jun and Lee Eun-hyung.
Wrong.
I see Eun-hyung though.
Whose eyes are those?
Is the right one Nucksal?
-Was one of them correct?
-Looks like Nucksal.
Didn't I guess one of them right?
-No comment.
-No.
I got it. Nucksal and Lee Eun-hyung.
-Correct.
-Okay.
You could clearly see Nucksal.
-And the eyes were Eun-hyung's.
-Yeah.
Gosh, I don't think I can guess these.
Here's the last one.
-Okay.
THEY LOOK LIKE THEY'RE CLOSE TO SOOK
Well, I think I know one of them.
-Song Eun-i.
-Yeah, it's Song Eun-i.
It's definitely Eun-i,
but who's the pretty one?
I got it. Song Eun-i and Kim Je-dong.
-Wrong.
-I got it.
Jung Hae-in and Song Eun-i.
-Wrong.
-I got it. Song Eun-i and Yu Jae-seok.
Song Eun-i and Kim Young-chul.
You're almost there.
I got it. Song Eun-i and Ji Sang-ryeol.
SON, DAUGHTER
-Correct.
-Wow!
Wow. I see it though.
I see Sang-ryeol's face.
-Yeah.
-How did you guess that?
Can't you see it?
Sook is doing an excellent job.
-I know.
-It's so hard.
-I have an eye for this.
-Yes, you do.
These are the results.
-Sook.
-Yes?
You guessed five correctly.
-Yes!
-You guessed a lot.
Woo-jae guessed three correctly.
Sae-ho guessed three correctly.
Hey, you tied.
Jin-kyung guessed one correctly.
-Woo-young didn't guess any correctly.
-You didn't get any?
But you like mixing so much.
I won't ever do mixing again.
-Don't lie to us.
-You've been mixing for seven years.
My goodness.
WORK HARDER ON MIXING
This will be the last game for
Woo-young's Deconstruction Show.
You're an 18-year veteran K-pop idol,
Woo-young.
-You worked longer than Woo-jae.
-I'm the youngest here.
-Based on the year you debuted.
-Yes.
Our star Woo-young
was sensational around the world.
Do you have a secret
to your long-running success?
Well…
Can you please speak faster?
-Write it down for us later.
-Okay.
-Get it in text form.
-That would be better.
-Yes.
-I'd feel more at ease with that.
-Yeah.
The thing is that
many stars end up in trouble
-when their private lives…
-They were exposed.
-…are photographed.
-Yes, that's right.
How have you never been caught
for the past 18 years as a celebrity?
I blocked them well.
I BLOCKED THEM WELL
-Sometimes they don't get blocked so well.
-That is true.
Well, this is a very personal story,
but I spent all the money I saved on that.
To block all of that.
-Is that why?
-Yes.
A star like Woo-young,
who is loved by the public,
can be cast aside in an instant
-if they're caught up in some controversy.
-Yes.
The reason why Woo-young was
able to be a long-running idol is
-because he did "this" well.
-This?
-What is it?
-This game is…
-The title seems very grandiose.
-What are you trying to connect it to?
This game is called Avoid the Paparazzi.
That's what you ended up with?
You will each take turns
-being a paparazzi.
-Okay.
The person who becomes the paparazzi
will wear a blindfold
and rely on their five senses
to take photos of the other members.
When the game starts,
you may move around freely within the box.
Then, the paparazzi will say, "Stop!"
At that moment, the others have to stop
and look towards the paparazzi.
The paparazzi will move three steps.
After moving three steps,
they will take the paparazzi cut.
TAKING THE PAPARAZZI CUT
EACH PAPARAZZI GETS 3 SHOTS!
If we can recognize the face
of the person that is in the picture,
that person will get one point
-deducted.
-I see. Okay.
PAPARAZZI ORDER
1 JIN-KYUNG 2 SAE-HO
3 WOO-JAE 4 SOOK 5 WOO-YOUNG
HONGPARAZZI IS STARTING OFF
MOVING SILENTLY
GETTING READY TO
TOY WITH HER FROM UNDER HER NOSE
Jin-kyung, you may call out
"Start" and "Stop" three times each.
GIGGLE
Ready, go.
HONGPARAZZI STARTS TAKING PHOTOS
WHAT'S ON HER CELL PHONE'S SCREEN
Excuse me, but can you
do the "Start" first?
HE ALMOST HAD TO RETIRE
You can't say "Stop"
-when you haven't started.
-Yeah, start first.
She has to say "Start" first but…
STARTING FOR REAL
UH OH!
SHE SAID STOP AS SOON AS
HE TAPPED HER FROM BEHIND
SHE CAN MOVE 3 STEPS NOW
NERVOUS, NERVOUS
You can take three steps.
APPROACHING THE VETERAN IDOL
HE'S A TOP STAR AFTER ALL
BUT SHE CAN'T GET THE DIRECTION RIGHT
WAS SHE ABLE TO CAPTURE HIS PRIVATE LIFE?
THE STARS ENJOY THEIR PRIVATE LIVES AGAIN
HE EXPOSES HIS LOCATION
WHILE TRYING TO MOCK HER
WHY DID YOU COME THIS WAY?
SHE MOVES TOWARDS SAE-HO!
TAKING A SUPER CLOSEUP SHOT
SHE WALKS STRAIGHT TOWARDS THE SOUND
SHE'LL RUN INTO THEM AT THIS RATE!
WILL WOO-JAE'S PRIVATE LIFE
GET EXPOSED TOO?
It's over.
-Why did you hide behind me?
-No, I didn't.
-All right.
-Please!
-The first one.
-Not my face.
It was Woo-young.
She got it exactly.
BEAST-LIKE IDOL WANDERS ABOUT
WITHOUT BEING ABLE TO SEE
Do you know what's scary, Jin-kyung?
-She turned around all of a sudden.
-She lifted it.
She lifted it like this all of a sudden.
It was so freaky.
She was pointing at his butt first.
PROUD TO GET A SCOOP
SHE WAS RIGHT UNDER THEIR NOSE
IN THE SECOND ONE
WAS SHE ABLE TO TAKE A DECENT PHOTO?
Next.
LAUGHING OUT LOUD
-I got him right in the face.
-Shouldn't we protect him?
REVEALING EVEN HIS PORES
-This is too funny.
-So funny.
CHO SAE-HO LOSES 1 POINT
-Next.
Woo-jae.
WHILE HE WAS TOYING WITH HER,
WOO-JAE RAN INTO HONGPARAZZI
-Next.
Woo-jae.
-Come on.
-No.
-What's this?
-She must have gotten you
instead of Woo-jae earlier.
-I think this is my hair.
-Your hair.
You're right.
You see, Sae-ho tried to
hide behind him, so I scolded him.
He got caught.
Geez.
-Serves you right.
-Okay.
HE TRIED TO HIDE BEHIND WOO-JAE
WHOM SHE RAN INTO
CAUGHT WHILE TRYING TO BE SNEAKY
-Serves you right.
-Sae-ho got caught twice.
-Congrats.
-Sae-ho's turn.
-You did a great job.
-Sae-ho.
What a shame.
IT'S CHOPARAZZI'S TIME TO COLLECT PHOTOS
HIS FIVE SENSES OPERATE ON FULL CAPACITY
WHERE SHOULD I GO
HE TAKES A STEP TOWARDS SOOK
HELP
LOOKING AROUND
LAUGHING
CHOPARAZZI'S CLOSEUP SHOT
Did I get someone?
THE STARS ENJOY THEIR PRIVATE LIVES AGAIN
SHE LOWERS HERSELF TO HIDE THIS TIME
I HEARD FOOTSTEPS BEHIND ME
IS IT ME AGAIN?
CHOPARAZZI GETS CLOSER AND CLOSER
SHE FALLS BACKWARDS
WITHOUT BEING ABLE TO SCREAM
I THOUGHT I HEARD SOMETHING FROM HERE
TRYING NOT TO LAUGH
SHE ENDS UP BURSTING OUT LAUGHING
What? Is it Sook?
SHE TAKES IT OUT ON INNOCENT WOO-YOUNG
THEY TRY TO HIDE BEHIND EACH OTHER
MEANWHILE, THE TWO MODELS
FOLLOW CHOPARAZZI CLOSELY
YOU NEVER KNOW
WHAT'S RIGHT UNDER YOUR NOSE
ARE THE TWO MODELS HIS TARGET THIS TIME?
AGAIN?
DID HE PUT A GPS ON HER?
What the heck? Is it you again? What?
-What the heck is going on?
-Hang on.
What's up with him?
-What's going on?
-What's happening?
-He is so annoying.
-Gosh.
-Let's check the photos.
-This makes no sense.
Here's the first photo.
It's Sook.
UP CLOSE AND PERSONAL,
LOOKING INTO KIM SOOK'S LIFE
Why did he take that photo from so close?
He must have lost his mind.
-Why did you only take photos of me?
-I know.
The picture is gradually coming together.
I got three points deducted all at once.
KIM SOOK ALONE GOT 3 POINTS DEDUCTED
IT'S JOOPARAZZI'S TURN TO TAKE PHOTOS
STAR SOOK DEVELOPED SOCIAL ANXIETY NOW
I heard something here and here.
AT RISK!
NOT EVEN ALLOWING HIMSELF TO BREATH
You can't use your hands.
-Okay.
-No using hands.
But it's okay if you bump into them.
LETTING IT SLIDE JUST ONCE
HIS INVESTIGATION STARTS UP AGAIN
THEY EXPOSE THEIR LOCATION WHILE TUSSLING
HE ATTEMPTS TO TAKE PHOTOS
WHERE SAE-HO AND JIN-KYUNG ARE
SWINGING HIS HEAD AROUND
ACTING LIKE HE'S BUMPING INTO THEM
THE MASTER OF USING TRICKS
I heard something.
TRYING TO PHOTOGRAPH SAE-HO TWICE IN A ROW
JOOPARAZZI LOOKS VERY RELAXED
GO AWAY
YOU HAVE TO FACE THE PAPARAZZI
GOING TO PHOTOGRAPH YOU 3 TIMES IN A ROW
USES THE ACCIDENTAL BUMP TACTIC
I bumped into him by accident.
It's an accident.
He's shameless.
Is it Jin-kyung?
WHY DO YOU KEEP COMING AFTER ME?
That's it. I got three.
That's it.
-Isn't it so annoying, Sae-ho?
-Hey.
You kept following me.
-You were like that too.
-Really?
-You kept following Sae-ho.
He may not have gotten any photos.
He was too close.
He may not have taken any.
-Sae-ho was--
-Here's the first one.
LAUGHING OUT LOUD
CHO SAE-HO'S BEST ANGLE HOWEVER…
I really did a great job with that.
It looks like he took that photo for you.
The second one.
Post this on your Insta.
SADLY, HE DIDN'T GET HIS FACE
SO IT DOESN'T COUNT
This is clearly Sae-ho.
You can see half of his body.
-The third one.
-So close.
I was able to avoid it.
You kept trying to attack me.
That was so close.
Ready.
4TH ROUND SOOKPARAZZI
Set.
TIME FOR REVENGE, SAE-HO
Go.
MAKING A WRONG GUESS
USING DISRUPTING TACTIC
WOO-JAE WHO IS RIGHT BEHIND HER
AND SAE-HO WHO IS RIGHT IN FRONT OF HER
SOOK'S CELL PHONE SCREEN
SHE CAN MOVE 3 STEPS NOW
SLIDING
MOVING TO THE WRONG PLACE
PHEW WE'RE SAFE
Can I take the photo now?
You may take the photo.
I took it.
DID SHE GET THE K-POP STAR?
THE STARS MOVE AROUND AGAIN
THE THREE SUPERSTARS ARE STANDING
RIGHT IN FRONT OF SOOKPARAZZI
THE K-POP STAR IS AT RISK
OF BEING CAUGHT AGAIN!
FORTUNATELY, SHE DIDN'T NOTICE HIM
IS SHE CAPTURING
JIN-KYUNG'S PRIVATE LIFE NOW?
I took it.
RUN
THE TWO STARS ARE CAUGHT ON HER SCREEN
I think someone's here.
IS IT FINALLY TIME FOR REVENGE?
THE K-POP STAR FACES
AN UNUSUALLY HIGH NUMBER OF CRISES
HE GOT NERVOUS AS WELL
I took it.
I got three photos.
-Let's take a look at the photos.
-Did I get any?
-Hey.
-Who's that?
-Woo-young.
-Who?
-It's Woo-young.
-Woo-young.
Anyone can tell that it's Woo-young.
I got you, Woo-young.
Deduct a point from Camera Director too.
We're in it together.
Yeah, Woo-young.
-Where did I take it from?
-Next.
THE SECOND EXCLUSIVE
-Jin-kyung.
-That is such a clear shot of her.
It really is a clear shot.
Next.
-Wow!
-What a relief!
-This one.
-I got them.
Yeah, this one.
Who's that up there?
Hey, that's my arm.
But his face isn't showing.
-Yeah, I knew someone was in front of me.
-You can't see his face.
SHE WAS SO CLOSE BUT DIDN'T GET HIS FACE
I think someone's here.
PHEW
I got everybody.
We all got a point deducted.
YOUNGPARAZZI IS READY
I can't use my hands, right?
USING TRICKS
Go forward.
-Can I start?
-Go forward?
IF I GET YOU, YOU'RE RUINED
TRIES TO GET SAE-HO
FLINCHING
ENCOUNTERS YOUNGPARAZZI UP CLOSE
HE GETS CLOSER WITH EACH STEP
Did Sae-ho always smell bad like this?
I SMELL SOMETHING BAD HERE
UNPLEASANT SMELL, UNPLEASANT SIGHT
DISGUSTING
HERE YOU ARE
HE'S USING TRICKS IN A NEW WAY
STAR CHO SUCCEEDS IN ESCAPING
HIS TARGET IS STAR JOO THIS TIME
You can't use your hands.
HE'S USING HIS NOSE INSTEAD OF HIS HANDS
NERVOUS
WEIGHING HIS OPTIONS
BETWEEN THE TWO MODELS
AVOIDING HIM
LIKE A BEAST,
HIS FIVE SENSES ARE WELL-DEVELOPED
QUICKLY ESCAPING
ARE THEY BEHIND ME?
THE TWO MODELS ARE CAUGHT ON HIS RADAR
DETECTS THEM WITH ANIMAL-LIKE SENSES
TURNS ON HIS OLFACTORY SENSOR
ATTEMPTING TO TAKE A SUPER CLOSE SHOT
YOUNGPARAZZI ENDS HIS INVESTIGATION
Man, you really used your senses.
You knew it was me, didn't you?
Let's see the first photo.
REVEALING YOUNGPARAZZI'S EXCLUSIVE
He's in many photos.
Sorry, Sae-ho.
-I'm sorry, Sae-ho.
-You got me.
You went to the dermatologist today.
The second photo.
THE SECOND EXCLUSIVE
-It's Woo-jae.
This one doesn't count.
-It's clearly Woo-jae.
-If only I turned my body…
Yeah, you should have turned your body.
Third photo.
LAST EXCLUSIVE
-Hey! It's Jin-kyung and Sook!
-Hey!
Two birds, one stone.
WHY AM I THERE?
-Jin-kyung, Sook, and Sae-ho.
-Hey.
-How did you take that?
-How did you do that?
-How did you get me?
-Awesome.
That's awesome.
Here are the scores.
-Sook.
-Yes.
-I was in a lot of photos.
-Yeah.
-Four times.
-Four shots.
-You were in four shots.
-That's a lot.
-You took three shots of me, Sae-ho.
-If I only turned…
SORRY
And Jin-kyung,
you had two photos taken of you.
-Not bad.
-You had two photos taken.
-You avoided it well.
-Sae-ho, there are five shots of you.
-Congratulations.
-Gosh.
-Congrats. You're the best shot of today.
-I'm in a lot.
WELL, AIN'T HE A SUPERSTAR
Woo-young was in two shots.
-You avoided it well.
-Yeah.
-Woo-jae, you were in one shot.
-Yes!
Wow. What the heck?
Let me announce the final ranking.
As I said before,
there is a limited-edition prize at stake.
I think I'm in last place.
-You're tied for last place.
-Jin-kyung and me?
It's Sae-ho and Woo-young.
SAE-HO AND WOO-YOUNG ARE BOTH LAST PLACE
It's because I had many shots taken.
TIED FOR LAST PLACE TOGETHER
That's an honor too.
Third place.
-Jin-kyung.
-Okay.
I'm satisfied with it.
Now, it's between Sook and Woo-jae.
I hope the person next to me
is in first place.
I hope I can be in first place.
Sook got a lot right earlier.
-Congratulations. Today's winner is…
-But I was in many shots.
-…Woo-jae.
-I wonder.
1ST PLACE JOO WOO-JAE.
What's the limited-edition prize?
What is it?
-Gosh, Woo-jae.
-I'm curious.
He always comes in first.
I'm curious what the prize is.
And so, Woo-jae showed off his talent
as an idol and came in first.
Today's prize is
from the eternal idol of Screwballs.
-Woo-young?
-Woo-young's soul itself.
The masterpiece that was born
after endless mixing.
IT CAN'T BE
-Limited edition.
-An autographed CD.
You get Woo-young's solo album.
Do I get an autograph?
You get one right now.
-I have this at home.
-This is a really limited one.
-I have one at home too.
Is it "Simple Dance"?
This is a new one called "Think Too Much."
His name is Woo-jae.
Spelled like the Korean word for annoying.
He's annoying?
-No, just Woo-jae.
-Okay. Woo-jae.
WOO-JAE, LOVE YOU
WHAT ARE YOU DOING? WOO-YOUNG
"Woo-jae, love you. What are you doing?"
CAN'T GIVE UP ON TRYING TO BE FUNNY
Thank you for letting me
give this to Woo-jae.
-Congrats.
-I should be giving this to everyone here.
-But it's a limited edition.
-Yes.
REFUSES WITH KIND WORDS
There are a lot of photos in this.
How do you feel?
-How do I feel?
-You must be so happy.
-Of course. It's a limited edition.
-So happy.
Aren't you so happy?
HE CAN'T EXPRESS HOW HAPPY HE IS
Try to look happy, man.
-Smile.
-Yeah, smile.
I've been dancing and playing games
for about five hours,
but I got such a nice gift.
Try to look up and smile, Woo-jae.
I really like the song "Think Too Much."
-I'll listen to it even more.
-Congrats.
-We are happy that you are
happy about it as we expected.
Congratulations.
CONGRATS
Woo-young, can you tell us
how you felt about this episode?
When I became the star,
I felt like
I became someone really amazing.
-You don't know what to do with yourself.
-That's right.
I would like to be able to
show my gratitude
when the time is right
and my circumstances allow--
How about our team dinner?
-To thank you all--
-Treat us to dinner.
Let me check my time again
-with my manager--
-You have to check again?
-I'm sick and tired of this.
-Also…
-Do you have a 2PM group chat?
-Yeah.
-To message each other?
-Why don't you send our short-form video…
-Okay.
-…and type three words.
-What?
Bring it on.
BRING IT ON
Yeah, send "Bring it on."
Nice!
-I'll work harder. I'll be back.
-Woo-young.
I'll be back!
On the next episode of Screwballs.
Very nice to meet you.
Thank you very much.
We will now begin the Cho Sae-ho Show.
LAUNCHING THE CHO SAE-HO SHOW
THE CHARACTERISTICS OF THE CHO SAE-HO SHOW
SAE-HO OVEREXERTS HIMSELF
The Cho Sae-ho Show is very charming.
That's all for the Cho Sae-ho Show.
See you again. Goodbye!
-But the Cho Sae-ho show is fun.
-Don't go!
My throat hurts so much.
HE POURED OUT EVERYTHING HE GOT
IN HIS FINAL MOMENTS
Gosh, Sook. I brought 200 won.
Sae-ho, why did you leave us?
Gosh, Sae-ho.
PLEASE ACCEPT MY BOW, SAE-HO
Who would bow like that?
SAE-HO'S TIME OF ORDEAL
Let's all give him a glass.
Geez. You don't put
things like these in a coffin.
STEALING HIS BELONGINGS
THE ENDLESS ATTEMPTS AT GOING TOO FAR
You haven't forgotten me?
Yes, you may kiss me.
Why are you laughing?
Hey, he died.
-How could you laugh?
-What's wrong with you?
SAE-HO'S FUNERAL
WHERE SAE-HO WASN'T PRESENT IS COMING SOON
ENJOY THE HIGHLIGHTS AND THE BTS CLIPS
ON STUDIO++'S YOUTUBE CHANNEL
"REBOOT" BY KYOUNGSEO
(SCREWBALLS OST)
SCREWBALLS
Subtitle translation by: Ilyoung Kim