A SECRET GEM SITTING SNUG
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE FOREST
LUSH GREEN LANDSCAPE
AND ANIMALS WELCOME YOU
Hello.
PERHAPS THIS PLACE IS GODS' SANCTUARY
ON THIS VERY DAY…
A PARTY OF THE GODS IS BEING HELD HERE
WHICH GOD WILL JOIN THE PARTY FIRST?
ALONG WITH THE GODS
I'm the Hungry God.
Can I have a bite to eat?
I'm starving.
TODAY'S DRESS CODE: GODS
WE DIDN'T SEE THIS TWIST COMING…
I'm so hungry.
Oh no. My stomach grumbles.
FULLY IN CHARACTER
Try tiptoeing.
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
Is he joining us or not?
WHAT ON EARTH IS THIS?
Here. I'll give you a hand.
-Is there something here?
-Hold my shoulder.
-Is she supposed to be a ghost?
-Hold my shoulder. Go on.
I'm so hungry.
This guy barely has enough meat on him.
HE'S PUT IN MORE EFFORT THIS TIME TOO
Jeez. What's he doing now?
What are you supposed to be?
Master of Ice!
I'm the Ice God.
Well, you do look like an idiot.
Like I said, I'm the Ice God.
He kind of looks the part, doesn't he?
I like your concept.
HE DOES LOOK THE PART
GET A GRIP
Jeez.
Oh no. What's this now?
A RED SPECK OF CHILLI POWDER RUSHES IN
What's this now?
-What on earth?
-All souls of this earth
shall know the sting of the spice!
I'm here to give you that burning taste.
I am the Capsaicin God!
-I'm Capsaicin
-Hey!
I'm Capsaicin
I'm here to make your tongue burn
You'll feel the might of spice.
WE DON'T WANT TO SEE HIM
EVEN IN OUR NIGHTMARES
I'm the Capsaicin God!
-It suddenly feels like a children's show.
-I'm Capsaicin
IN THE MIDDLE
OF THE RED CHILLI POWDER'S BIT…
FULLY IMMERSED
He's that guy from the Slave Hunters.
Capsaicin!
POSE
HA-HA
We've got a bum there.
"Isn't it just grand?"
Is he the guy from the Slave Hunters?
But that character wasn't a god.
No human is free from committing sins.
Freeze!
SHE GETS IT NOW
-Along with the Gods.
-I see.
-Is he that god from Along with the Gods?
-The hairy one.
You have committed many sins.
HE'S THE KING OF THE UNDERWORLD,
OR SO HE SAYS
NOM
I'm the Hungry God.
ALL THEY CARE ABOUT
IS THEIR OWN CHARACTERS
-Hello, everyone.
-Sinners.
What a fine day for TV entertainment.
I'm your host,
the Grasshopper Yu Jae-seok,
God of TV Shows.
We have a stellar set of guests today.
Welcome, everyone!
AT ANY RATE, ALL FIVE GODS ARE HERE
Please get rid of this pest for us.
-As the God of TV Shows, I thought…
-Will you be our host for the day?
-What a nice idea.
-You even sound different.
Over the last few weeks,
I've monitored our show's performance.
When the show first launched…
ACK
THE HOST IS HAVING EXCESS PHLEGM
You have sinned a lot.
-When our show first launched,
-She's a shady one.
Netflix hadn't released
When Life Gives You Tangerines yet.
Are you wearing a wig?
-Well, yes.
-Oh, so that's a wig.
It was before the launch
of When Live Gives You Tangerines--
Give it a rest
and let me do my part, okay?
Jae-seok would've pulled through
no matter what his castmates did.
Jae-seok can keep it going no matter what.
You should try that too.
When the show first launched,
-it performed--
-Look at that camera.
-Hello.
-Don't forget to show your teeth.
Hi, when our show first launched,
-it performed very well--
-Look right in here.
-Let me share my Screwballs analysis!
-Oh, you're looking good.
DOESN'T CARE THAT SHE'S MAD
FLAP, FLAP
Let's try the intro one last time.
Kick us off with a greeting. Standby, cue!
Hello--
ACK
FLAP, FLAP
Spit it out or something.
-I didn't realize Jae-seok was so amazing.
-That was hilarious.
I'm seeing you in a new light.
You're admirable.
-I love you, Jae-seok.
-You nailed it.
What were you trying to say, Jin-kyung?
Here goes.
We had a great buzz
when Screwballs first launched.
We held first place
in the Top Ten Shows in Korea for days.
It seemed like we were on the rise.
-Then came When Life Gives You Tangerines.
-She has a point.
After that, our show has almost
disappeared from the charts.
But here's the thing.
Are you trying to throw shade
at the When Life Gives You Tangerine team?
No, of course not.
You want to blame them for our downfall?
I watch that show.
-It's my favorite.
-I never said that.
I cried buckets watching it.
-"The throne was ours."
-Wait.
-Stop it!
-"We want to put our roots down
right there on the throne."
"But with When Life Gives You Tangerines…"
Please add a subtitle saying
that this is Jin-kyung's personal opinion.
-It doesn't reflect our team's opinion.
-That's not what I intended.
I absolutely adore the show.
It's my all-time favorite.
Yeah, that's true.
But the show ended, you see.
This is the perfect opportunity
for us to go full steam ahead.
That's what I thought.
SLIDING DOWN
DARN IT
You sure are the God of TV Shows.
The heavens are helping.
-What with the phlegm and the headband…
-When Life Gives You Comedic Moments.
EXHAUSTED
-Sorry, Jae-seok.
-Tell us.
What is it that you want?
-What do you want us to do?
-Reclaim first place?
I mulled over this issue last night
and realized that there was a reason
why the first episode did so well.
AND WHAT IS THIS REASON
THAT EXPLAINS THE FIRST EPISODE'S SUCCESS?
Let me spell it out for you.
It's Byeon Woo-seok.
When Life Gives You Tangerine
has been updated in full,
-so we could--
-So this was your angle?
-We have hard-working crew--
-Have you ever thought long and hard
-for the show?
-I talk to Director Park on the phone…
-Let's hear your pitch.
-My pitch?
What can we do to reclaim the top spot?
Let's hear your take. Mine is Woo-seok.
We just have to do our best!
-Let's give it our all!
-Hey.
CRACKING UP
GOOD LUCK, GUYS!
You'll be attending an exclusive event
open to only the top elite
of the celestial world.
You've been invited to the party
of the gods named "Along with the Gods."
IN TRUTH, THEY'RE RATHER DIM
TO BE CALLED "TOP ELITES"
While the five of you were having fun,
-one more god has arrived.
-Really?
-Are we having a guest?
-Is that it?
Could it be him?
-Don't tell me…
-Guys!
Is the God of Drama Series here?
Can he really be here?
-Is this for real?
-Oh, my.
Hey, Jin-kyung. The crew rented
this whole place for today's shoot.
-What?
-What on earth?
SERIOUSLY, WHO IS THE GUEST?
Can't you give us a hint?
Is this person a global star?
Our guest is a god.
A god? Really?
What if…
What if it's Lee Su-ji, the God of Acting?
I love you, mister.
-Su-ju? I love her.
-That sounds likely.
It may be Hye-seon
dressed as the God of Mothers.
IT'S NOT NAM CHANG-HEE, IS IT?
THEY LOST INTEREST IN THE GUEST IN A FLASH
-We've kept our guest waiting for long.
-Oh, dear. Really?
-Let's invite them here.
-It's our first guest on Screwballs.
I'll now give you
a brief introduction about our guest.
He is the God of Beauty,
voted the most handsome man in the world.
"The God of Beauty"?
Voted as the man
with the best sculpted face in the world.
Gosh, really?
Scientific analyses
crowned him as the Asian man
with the most perfect face.
He was also handpicked by current idols
as the most handsome one of them all.
After his group's debut in 2013,
they were hailed as the best newcomer
in and out of the country.
-In 2013? That's BTS.
-It has to be them.
They were the first group to reach No. 1
on Billboard Hot 100 and Billboard 200.
-Oh my.
-It must be BTS.
It's Jin.
They were the first Koreans to perform
at the Grammys or give a speech at the UN.
-Goodness.
-It's Jin, all right!
Good looks, physique, talent, charms,
-tact, and sense of humor.
-Hey, Jin!
This God of K-Pop has indeed everything.
GOD OF K-POP
Here's our first-ever guest on the show.
-Seriously?
-Please come in!
-For real?
-It's not a joke?
Don't pull our legs, okay?
-Is this real?
-Can it be him?
FIRST GUEST ON SCREWBALLS
JIN FROM BTS
-Oh, man!
-Goodness!
ON THE VERGE OF TEARS
THIS IS JAW-DROPPING
BEDAZZLED BY THE WORLD-CLASS STAR'S VISIT
-Jin is here!
-Hey, I mean…
I watched the BTS… just yesterday…
I swear I watched clips
of their live performance.
UNABLE TO HOLD BACK
-Can this be real?
-I can't believe it!
-Goodness, welcome.
-It's incredible.
-Hey. It's been so long.
-It really has been so long.
It's so nice to meet you.
AN IMPROMPTU MEET-AND-GREET EVENT
-I can't believe Jin is really here.
-Goodness, what's going on?
-What are you playing at?
-Coming through.
You useless boots!
Jin was giving me a handshake.
-Hey, it's been a while.
-It's so nice to see you again.
-What are you doing over there?
-Gosh, you're so handsome.
And she's right.
HE FEELS AWKWARD STANDING BETWEEN
THE GRASSHOPPER AND THE HUNGRY GOD
THE NATION'S TREASURE, BTS
THE GROUP'S ELDEST MEMBER AND ITS PILLAR
HIS AURA AND GOOD LOOKS ARE UNMATCHED
"NEURAL NETWORK ALGORITHM FOUND
THAT JIN'S FACIAL FEATURES
OVERLAP WITH THE FEATURES
OF THE BUST OF ZEUS, THE GREEK GOD"
THE ARTIST WITH ENTICING SILVER VOICE
THE FRIENDLY AND CHEERFUL MEMBER
WHO ALMOST SEEMS LIKE THE GROUP'S YOUNGEST
HE NEVER SHIES AWAY FROM DOING SLAPSTICK
NO ONE IS MORE DEDICATED
AT MAKING THE FANS SMILE AND LAUGH
GOD OF K-POP, JIN OF BTS
Hi, I'm Jin from BTS.
WELCOME
-This is insane.
-You can say that again.
I was told
that today's dress code was gods.
Goodness. His costume has wings
just like Sae-ho's.
-I'm not sure what…
-See? Sae-ho's has them too.
MOM, I'M SO ASHAMED RIGHT NOW
-Go stand next to him.
-I heard that the theme was gods,
but you're all dressed as ghosts.
You can step away now.
-Seriously, guys.
-What are you dressed up as?
I'm the Capsaicin God.
I'm Capsaicin
Did you have to invite him here
when we're in silly costumes?
Yeah, give us a heads-up.
This is embarrassing.
Let us look presentable, okay?
Look at the state of her.
We have a special guest, and she's a mess.
Come on, I'm the God of TV Shows.
I was taken aback when I saw the wings.
But when I actually saw you guys,
I realized how neat my costume was.
Who's your inspiration today?
Eros, the Greek god of love.
-Oh, right.
-Eros, huh?
-He's also known as Cupid.
-That's right.
-If he truly existed, he'd look like you.
-Agreed.
WE AGREE TOO
-Surely not.
-I meant it.
-I have a question for you, Jin.
-Ask away.
-How come you're here on our show?
-I'm curious too.
Because Screwballs…
-Can I be perfectly honest?
-Sure.
Your show's the hottest.
GOSH, HOW CONSIDERATE!
Let me hear you scream!
Lift up your arms! We're doing the wave!
-Let me hear you scream!
-Come on, the wave!
DNA
What's going on over there?
-We never had that move in our choreo.
-Oh, my bad.
I got so worked up.
DNA
Are there really no moves like this one?
I'm sure you're aware, but we customize
our show to any superstar guests.
Really?
We're like tailors.
If there's anything
you want to add or take away,
-we'll oblige.
-Really?
That sounds like a show
worth visiting again.
-While you were watching our show,
-He's so witty.
did any of us perhaps spark your interest?
Is there anyone you'd like to know better?
-I've worked with Jin-kyung before.
-I see.
ME?
Even then, I was puzzled
because I couldn't understand her.
In a good way.
-Look at her.
-It's a compliment.
-Jin-kyung.
-Let him finish.
-I meant that in a compliment.
-Think positive.
Watching episodes of Screwballs
made me think
that she was wilder
than I originally thought her to be.
-But in a nice way, right?
-Sure.
Show us your beaming face
just when Jin first joined us.
It was a compliment.
-He says it's a compliment.
-But back then, Jimin…
I meant Jin…
But back then, Jimin…
JIMIN?
-I can't believe you got us mixed up.
-No!
WHAT JUST HAPPENED?
-I can't believe you got us mixed up.
-No! Please, it wasn't like that.
-Just a second.
-Take her away.
-I didn't mean…
-This way, please.
-I meant that Jin--
-Over there.
-Take some time for self-reflection.
-When Life Gives You Lemons.
-Have you lost it?
-She's too far gone to make lemonades.
-She's rather forgetful.
-That can happen.
Hear me out. Jin visited my place,
and I was a nervous wreck.
I didn't know what to do
-or what to say.
-He visited your place?
Honestly, I was a bundle of nerves.
That's understandable.
Now that we've become friends,
could we exchange numbers?
-Of course.
-Really?
He can choose not to answer your call.
Exchanging numbers is nothing.
-Save her number under "Don't Answer."
-You look so scary up close.
We did say we should meet up for soju,
but I forgot to ask for your number
by mistake.
"By mistake"? Are you sure?
-Was it really just an error?
-Of course.
But I do tend to make mistakes a lot.
-Will you be making a few more today?
-I'll have to consider that.
I've heard enough stories about you
being a natural on variety shows,
but you really have no trouble
coming up with counters.
He's so sharp-witted.
-He never falters.
-He's got certain charm of his own.
I saw your pictures from the Gucci show.
YOU LOOKED AMAZING
-I looked breathtaking there, didn't I?
-You were so…
Bragging, much?
The photos blew my mind away.
-I went, "Who's that good-looking guy?"
-Hold up.
Are we sure this is the real Jin?
THE REAL JIN
-Are we sure?
-Of course.
-He's not an imposter.
-Really?
After your discharge from the army,
we've seen you everywhere including
streaming platforms, TV, and YouTube.
-You've been very active lately.
-That's true.
-What are your plans for the future?
-What on earth?
THAT CAME OUT OF NOWHERE
-You wrote it up for us to read.
-I'd appreciate a smoother segue.
-A smoother segue?
-That was off.
Are you that eager to wrap things up?
-No one's ever said that on our show.
-Seriously.
-I got so startled.
-What on earth, dude?
I saw the cue card there.
You shouldn't just read it
like a textbook.
-I thought you were saying goodbye.
-You're a veteran.
Seriously, you're an experienced MC.
You took 30 minutes to film your intro.
I spent half an hour over there.
-Let's keep it natural, please.
-You know the drill.
Let's return to our original topic.
Right, Kian's Bizarre B&amp;B
is being released today.
-That's right.
-The day of this shoot, that is.
I'm releasing an album
as a solo artist, too.
HIS SOLO ALBUM IS IN THE WORKS
The main track's title is
"Don't Say You Love Me."
-"Don't Say You Love Me"?
-That's right.
Sorry, but "Don't Say What"?
I know my pronunciation isn't the best,
but that was in English.
Are you warning the other person
not to tell you they love you?
The song is about lovers
on the verge of breakup going,
"I'd die without you."
Oh, so thematically,
it's similar to Chonam Zone's songs.
-Dang it.
-What on earth?
Knock it off, okay?
-Hey, Sae-ho.
-Seriously, keep it down.
Maybe there are some similarities.
MAYBE YOU HAVEN'T LISTENED TO THEM YET
Tell you what,
if our shoot is to your liking…
What I'm leading into is this.
We've had an idea floating among us
about adding one more cast member.
But as Sae-ho's replacement, right?
Oh, as your replacement?
-Woo-young is right.
-For real? You'd be my replacement, then.
-The promise--
-Would I be paid the same amount?
I don't think you'd agree
to the level of my salary.
Naturally, you'd need to negotiate terms.
-Sure, I'll have to do that well.
-How much do you charge per episode?
Jin-kyung has some funds,
so we can lean on her for some dough.
You have a grand place.
-She sure does.
-If you sold it,
I'd join you as a regular.
Let's do that, Jin-kyung.
-Hey, Jin-kyung.
-Jin-kyung.
-Just put it up for sale.
-We could have Jin as our colleague.
I'll sign up right away.
I can cancel a few engagements.
-It's not too much for you, is it?
-Stand strong, Jin-kyung.
You can't back down just yet.
I'll list it up for now.
Yes, do that. We're all set.
Jin can join us
the moment the sale is finalized.
WE LOOK FORWARD TO HEARING GOOD NEWS
There's a café on the grounds here.
-They have excellent coffee.
-The 9 Block Cafe.
-The crew are very grateful to Jin--
-No, he can't have!
He paid for 70 coffees in advance for us.
That's incredible.
We should be treating him instead.
Gosh, you didn't have to.
The credit goes to my agency.
-I had no knowledge of this.
-My goodness.
So modest, so cool.
He's feigning ignorance here.
Sure, I'm footing the bill.
I might have made a small contribution
by suggesting it,
but I couldn't have arranged it
without the help of my agency.
-Are all members of BTS like this?
-They're on another level.
ANOTHER LEVEL INDEED
Does that mean
that we can enjoy Jin's treat?
All the cast and crew?
It's really nothing.
I do this quite often.
Still, kudos.
That may be the case,
but it's the first for us.
If you'd like,
I could do a repeat for your next shoot.
Are you serious?
Gosh, you're so incredible.
We appreciate the kind gesture,
but if you're not joining on the shoot…
-Let us enjoy free drinks.
-Really?
-I'm taking back the offer, then.
-Just take the free drink.
-You and your nit-picking.
-Ride along and leave the set.
-Who are you to stop Jin anyway?
-I only meant we'd love to see him again.
-What is your problem?
-Hang on. When's our lunch break?
Shut it. Who cares about lunch breaks?
What is the matter with you?
Just a moment, everyone.
We have a world-class star guest today,
so we need a few shots
of his grand entrance.
-You want some insert shots? Go ahead.
-Exactly, we'll be doing just that.
If you have a moment, Jin,
could you do the slate?
-So we can use it for a transition point?
-Yeah.
Come on, though.
"If you have a moment," really?
Just a second, Director Park.
You're the authority figure here.
Try not to grovel, okay?
-You're going too far.
-I'm no different from you.
-I have a ton of time.
-He might be busy.
Three, two, one.
Gosh, he looks picture-perfect.
Standby. Cue!
IT'S LIKE A MASTERPIECE
Jin is coming our way.
-Here he comes.
-You can tell it's him from his lips.
If gods were ever born in human form,
I'm sure one would look like him.
-I'm no model.
-How handsome.
-You're not one either.
-My goodness.
His features are beautiful.
The light looks lovely on him too.
-Good job.
-Thank you.
-I appreciated your responses.
-Did you like them?
-He knows he's hot.
-One more? Okay.
-Do we get to shoot the inserts too?
-What?
-I know how tired you must be.
-So it's for our sakes?
But I'm not tired at all.
How would he know if we're tired or not?
I'm wide awake.
I'm doing great, in fact.
-"I know how tired you must be"?
-Excuse me.
Do you usually shoot people so up close?
What's going on here?
-He always rushes us.
-What on earth are you doing?
What's going on here? Seriously.
Jin, do you mind walking
at 60% of your pace earlier?
-Got it.
-Take it a bit more slowly.
This looks like a shot
from a drama series.
-Is this the camera you use for us?
-That's how it looks.
-Have you always used this camera?
-That looks unfamiliar.
-Is it a bigger battery?
-Why does the picture look different?
Standby. Cue!
-Just standing there…
-It's like a shot from a drama series.
-Why do we never get a shot like this?
-He has great proportions.
-You can say that again.
-He looks amazing.
-Director Park always asks us to run.
-Why is life so unfair?
How is his face so small?
-We're always told to run to save time.
-Life is unfair, truly.
HELLO, HANDSOME
-Nice.
-Thanks.
-Great job.
-You're on another level.
-Who's next?
-No, that's it.
It was awkward to do that
before professional models.
Turns out I never was one.
-What on earth?
-The slate, please.
Three, two, one.
-Dear God.
-While they're both Asians…
YOU CAN GUESS THE REST, RIGHT?
To celebrate Jin joining us
as a special guest,
we brought what precious souvenirs
we had at our office.
Is that right?
-Thank you.
-We brought all we could.
Wait, what is that?
Isn't that Netflix merchandise?
-We made special preparations.
-What are those?
-Really?
-I'd love to have the towel set.
Those are the gifts for today.
As you can see, the towels are color-coded
for each day of the week.
-How cool is that?
-I dig it.
The towel set is so cute.
What's the best item on your list?
We have an Apple Watch.
WE DIDN'T HOLD BACK TODAY
Really?
Hold on. Is it really a smartwatch?
Of course.
We wouldn't have crafted a watch
with an apple, would we?
Wait, here's what I think.
Seeing how they piled them together,
they're going to remove an item
one by one.
Oh, no. We would never play tricks
when we have Jin joining us.
This is such a lovely show.
I'll tell my guys to make an appearance
after their discharge.
Applause, everyone!
YOUR COMMENT JUST NOW…
WE'RE SAVING THIS CLIP AS PROOF
Applause, everyone!
NEXT TO FINISH THEIR MILITARY DUTY
ARE RM, JIMIN, AND V…
Let's save that clip
and use it in all our previews.
-I can't exactly force them.
-Of course not.
-It's for them to decide.
-But I can make recommendations.
I'll tell them that there's
this amazing show called Screwballs
where the crew offers
very expensive gifts.
We're excellent hosts, if nothing else.
Let's get the party of the gods in
full swing. This is Along with the Gods.
Now, Jin-kyung.
Jin told us the title of his main track--
Just a second.
PADDING OVER
-Don't, okay?
-Don't do what?
-Just don't do it.
-I don't get it.
Can she say that to our showrunner,
"Do you have a death wish?"
JUST A FRIENDLY CONVO
I think she said,
"Are you such a daredevil?"
-That's what I heard too.
-I never said such a thing.
-When Life Gives You Threats.
-We were only fooling around.
She sure can swear like a sailor.
I noticed that
when we shot Run Jin together.
WHAT, ME?
Hey, Jin!
I PROMISE TO DO BETTER
That was a joke.
Jin shared the title of the main track
on his upcoming solo album earlier.
It's "Don't Say You Love Me."
That gave us the inspiration
for the first game of the day.
It's called Don't Say.
-"Don't Say"?
-We're not to talk, then.
The name speaks for itself.
-Certain keywords will be off-limits.
-Okay.
-You'll each be given a headband.
-It won't be easy.
The signboard on it will show
one restricted phrase
and one restricted action.
Actions too?
The person who made the least violations
-will be the winner.
-Do they get the prize?
-The winner can take one from the pile.
-So they can only choose one?
Are there any penalties
for whoever places last?
There is indeed a penalty.
It's something of a variety show staple.
-The loser gets a finger flick.
-A finger flick?
-But if Jin places last…
-I don't want to hurt him.
Oh, no. It's all right.
Jonathan once gave me a headlock,
making my tongue stick out.
-Really?
-You bet.
That must be why he's rarely on TV lately.
SO THAT'S WHAT HAPPENED
-I haven't seen him around lately.
-That explains his recent absence.
-I finally get it.
-That's what must've happened.
But these days,
the fans don't get so upset
even if I get pushed around a bit
on variety shows.
-Really? Then can we sort of relax…
-Could we push you around?
Sure, feel free to do that.
Hey, guys. Let's make a promise
not to tiptoe around Jin.
-All right.
-We're in agreement, right?
You won't mind us getting in your hair
as we get to know each other better?
-No, and you don't have to brush my pants.
-Oh, it's nothing.
-I noticed some dirt.
-Thanks.
I'd do it for Woo-young too.
-Don't touch me.
-What's your problem?
WE LOOK FORWARD TO THE DAY
THAT WE ALL BECOME GOOD FRIENDS WITH BTS
Please remove the covers
on my count of three.
Here goes. Three, two, one.
Nice and slow.
KEYWORD: JIN-KYUNG
ACTION: COVERING HIS MOUTH
KEYWORD: ANY REJECTIONS
ACTION: SHAKING HER HEAD
KEYWORD: THE CURSE "IC"
ACTION: POINTING A FINGER
KEYWORD: BRO / BROTHER
ACTION: SPREADING OUT BOTH ARMS
-Nice and slow.
-Okay.
KEYWORD: BUNGEE (JUMP)
ACTION: HOLDING UP BOTH ARMS
KEYWORD: YES
ACTION: NODDING HIS HEAD
This won't be easy.
Give me those covers.
I'll take care of them. Go on.
-It looks so simple.
-Let me take them.
-You're such a gentleman, bro.
-It was nothing.
Gosh, it finally dawned on me.
Jin is wearing wings today.
His and mine give off
completely different vibes, right?
-Doesn't he wear it better?
-They are of different sizes.
-He has long arms and a fine proportion.
-Go on.
-Compare your reach.
-I bet his is much longer.
COMPARE OUR REACH, ALL OUT OF THE BLUE?
-Compare your reach.
-I bet his is much longer.
-Let's see.
-Raise your arms like this.
-He has such long arms.
-Can you stand up for a second?
-Then…
-His arms are as long as Woo-jae's.
Why don't you hold up your arms too?
Let's see how far they go.
HOLD UP OUT ARMS?
+1 VIOLATION
Wait, that's not right.
We should hold them like this
to prepare their length.
-My arms aren't on the short side.
-I wanted to compare your heights too.
I wanted to compare your heights too.
+1 VIOLATION
-You'd tower over any of us.
-See? Notice the difference?
HE TENDS TO DO AS HE IS TOLD
Why don't you try it, Sook?
-Try what?
-Go ahead.
I'm just…
-Why don't you try it, Jin-kyung?
-Go on.
What about you?
THE WHOLE GROUP JOINS IN
TO KEEP SAE-HO IN THE DARK
Woo-jae sure has the longest reach.
But you're so tall, bro.
How tall are you exactly, bro?
You want to know my height?
I'm 188 cm tall.
You're 188 cm tall? My goodness.
BARELY HOLDS IT IN
AS JIN MAKES 2 VIOLATIONS
Okay. Hey, Jin-kyung.
Why don't you play
a one-on-one game with Jin?
I'd love to see you two play a game.
-How about Look This Way?
-Look This Way?
Okay.
Here's a suggestion.
Let's not do this motion as we play it.
-How else do we play it?
-Look this way.
SPREAD OUT YOUR ARMS
Look this way.
SNORTS OUT A LAUGH
I'll take the first turn, Jin-kyung.
Look this way.
COME ON
I'M SPREADING OUT MY ARMS!
Come on, focus on our game!
SHE MAY AS WELL TELL HIM
HIS FORBIDDEN ACTION
After the day's shoot ends,
-we're bound to have the losing player.
-And?
Let's pick a penalty for that person.
-But Director Park laid out one.
-No, forget about that.
We need something proper.
Like what?
You know, the thing Jin-kyung did.
THE THING THAT JIN-KYUNG WOULD OBJECT TO
-All right.
-Me?
It's bungee jumping.
-All right. It's bungee jumping.
-Me?
-That's it. How about it?
-Bungee jumping.
-There's a platform nearby.
-You want us to bungee?
-Yeah, bungee.
There's a bungee jumping site close by.
-That came out of nowhere.
-How's bungee jumping?
Let's bungee.
YOU HATE THE IDEA, RIGHT?
Bungee?
All right. Let's go!
YOU'RE GOING ALONG WITH THIS?
+1 VIOLATION
-All right. Let's go!
-We're doing what now?
Guys, just a second.
-You're bungeeing if you place last, Jin.
-How does that sound?
I just can't do that.
Can you do it, bro? Have you tried it?
Well, the bungee jumping…
Let me give you a simulation.
You hold up your arms like this
and jump from the platform.
THE RED IMP TRIES TO SET UP JIN,
NOT REALIZING HE IS BEING PUNKED
HE'S ONE DEVIOUS HYENA
Let's do a quick role-play.
-Play the part of the instructor.
-Okay.
Give me the countdown.
All right. Three, two, one. Bungee!
ALL IT TOOK WAS A SMALL BAIT
TO GET HIM TO SAY HIS KEYWORD NON-STOP
-One more time.
-Three, two, one. Bungee!
-I missed the beat. One more time.
-Hey, focus.
Three, two, one. Bungee!
Do I jump like this?
One more time.
-Why are we even discussing this?
-Come on.
Let's do it. Three, two, one. Bungee!
-Have you tried bungeeing?
-Yes, I love it, actually.
How many times have you bungeed?
More than 10,000 times, I think.
I meant it.
Whenever I got bored, I'd go try it.
LOOKS LIKE YOU'LL BE BUNGEEING TODAY TOO
You must really enjoy bungeeing.
Sure, I'm a huge fan. Have you tried it?
I did try it once,
but I teared up on my way down.
-Really?
-Sure.
So are we all set
on having the losing person jump?
-Shall we, then?
-But it's so terrifying.
In that case, let's have a casual game.
-A casual one?
-That's right.
We'll take turns to ask questions.
The person asked
must answer either yes or no.
For instance, "Do you know BTS?"
How's this instead of speaking out loud?
Let's do something else
to make the game a silent one.
THE ICE GOD IS TRYING TO TRICK
TWO FELLOW GODS WITH ONE GAME
IN THAT CASE…
Okay, then we'll cover our mouths
since we're not to speak out loud.
Cover them up.
-Shall we start the game like this?
-Yes, cover it up.
Hold your hand like this.
+1 VIOLATION
-Don't show it.
-Okay.
-But we're allowed to ask a question?
-Speak only then. Stay silent otherwise.
Nod if you agree
and shake your head if not.
Yes, that's it.
HEH-HEH
+1 VIOLATION
Here goes.
COVER UP YOUR MOUTH TO GET READY
+1 VIOLATION
-Who asks the question?
-Who goes first?
OH, SNAP
Who's going to ask
if we all have to cover our mouths?
At least one of us should not cover it up.
And who's it to be?
Why don't you kick us off?
Does he have to cover his mouth
as he asks?
-Why don't we all move in that direction?
-Okay, that's a good call.
It seems Jin is the only one
with a clear head.
Why don't you come to the center?
Can I do that? Thank you.
Ready, go.
+1 VIOLATION
This is a multi-player game, okay?
-Goodness!
-Gosh, the wind.
I didn't take a peep.
-I doubt it.
-I swear I didn't.
I have a question for Woo-young.
-Don't speak out loud.
-Did you tell the truth about not looking?
If you didn't see it, do this.
If you did see it, do this.
LET ME THINK
Yes.
+2 VIOLATIONS
You're not supposed to speak.
You either nod or shake your head.
Did you look at it or not? Go on.
Did you see your signboard?
No.
-Nod or shake your head.
-Why aren't you getting this?
-Jin-kyung.
-Let's continue, nice and neat.
You adore me, don't you?
KEYWORD: ANY REJECTIONS
Woo-young.
Yes?
-Woo-young.
-Can't you tell me you adore me?
Woo-young.
-Woo-young.
-Can't you tell me you adore me?
GO ON, REJECT IT
Woo-young.
ANSWER MY QUESTION
Yeah?
-Woo-young.
-Just tell me you like me.
You're not listening to each other at all.
Tell me you like me.
-Woo-young.
-At least admit you liked me.
-Please tell me you like me.
-Woo-young.
Just kiss already.
So you know our history?
-We're a married pair on the show.
-Really?
-We didn't get a divorce yet.
-Please tell me you cherish me.
I'll do that if you answer.
WHAT ARE YOU, A KID?
DO BETTER, WE HAVE A WORLD-CLASS GUEST
Let's play a game!
-Have you heard about the new 369 Game?
-How does it go?
You're supposed to say numbers out loud
and clap on multiples of three, right?
But in the updated version, you cover
your mouth for non-multiples of three.
LOOK CLOSELY, WOO-JAE
That counts as two.
The next person says, "Three!"
And we go back to mouth-covering.
For five…
DO THIS AS MANY TIMES AS THE NUMBER
EXCEPT FOR MULTIPLES OF 3
Let's say we reach 30.
Do we have to do that 30 times?
Here's an idea for multiples of five.
-Okay.
-We'll do this.
-For multiples of six…
-I have a suggestion.
-Okay.
-No, take a look at mine.
We'll do this for multiples of five
-and this for multiples of six.
-Just a minute.
You made it too complicated
with so many rules.
Let's do this for multiples of seven.
This is what we'll do.
Let's do this for multiples of eight.
THE INTENTS ARE MORE THAN BLATANT
Let's try the game
without additional rules.
My nephew taught me this.
They play this at school.
For three, say the number out loud.
For four, do this.
-I got it.
-Really? Let's try it, then.
-Do we scream for all other numbers?
-Yes.
Let's roll.
Three.
Dang, I lost.
TOO BAD
What the… Get on playing.
That wasn't funny.
-But I already lost.
-Go on so Jin-kyung can play.
Come on, don't hang my nephew out to dry.
THAT WOULD BE VERY ILL-MANNERED OF US
Jin-kyung, do you like me?
Woo-young.
Others would play mind games,
but you guys do whatever
that comes to mind.
Wait, is Sae-ho older than you?
Of course, Jin-kyung.
He can't be younger than Jin, can he?
Jin was born on December 4th, 1994.
Gosh, you got it wrong.
Really? But I can't be wrong.
I mean, I was born in 1992.
Oh, in 1992.
Are all other members of BTS
younger than you, Jin?
Yes, I'm the eldest brother, so to speak.
Do they always call you "bro"?
Well, I guess they do call me "bro."
You can use the same title to her.
Oh, really?
-Me too.
-Call me "bro."
-You want me to call you "bro"?
-Yes.
You can add my name if you'd like.
Can you call me "bro" too?
Bro.
He's so polite.
Gosh, I love it.
Can you call me "bro" too?
DOUBTFUL
-Go on. Try it.
-What's wrong?
You go ahead and say it to me first.
Jin-kyung, bro.
That's no biggie. Go ahead and do it.
If you won't do anything,
why bother with the games?
-He's right!
-It's just that
I'd love to get that Apple Watch.
-Let's play the Times Table Game.
-Okay.
Here's another neat game
my nephew taught me.
-Nephew again?
-I'm not making it up.
Just how old is he?
He's ten ears old.
I mean, he's ten years old.
-Ten what?
-He's ten years old.
Ten-year-olds don't play the 369 Game.
I hear kids these days
use English for their games.
It's called, "Don't You Say Korean."
-You can't speak Korean. Just English.
-Okay, got it.
Let's start with you. Point a finger
at the person you want to go next.
If your question is, "Seven times three,"
they should go, "I see. Twenty-one."
SOOK'S KEYWORD "IC"
IS DISGUISED AS "I SEE"
Seven times seven.
I see. Forty-nine.
There we go.
One, two, three, four.
Sook, three times four.
I see. Twelve.
HEH-HEH
Good job. Go on.
+1 VIOLATION
Jin-kyung, nine times seven.
I see. Sixty-three.
You're so smart, Jin-kyung.
-Call me "bro."
-Right, my bad.
Try it again.
I'm sorry. I apologize.
Let's resume the game.
One, two, three, four. Go on!
-Sook.
-Again?
Four times five.
I see. Twenty.
Man, you're good at this.
-One, two, three, four.
-Hurry it up.
Jin, seven times seven.
I see. Forty-nine.
One, two, three four.
Don't act all cutesy.
You're getting on my nerves.
Hurry it up, okay?
You're supposed to dance, actually.
We should all be dancing.
-One, two, three--
-Sae-ho.
-Yeah?
-Nine times seven.
I see. Sixty-three.
One, two, three four. Sook, two times two.
I see.
LOL
Woo-jae, eight times eight.
One, two, three, four.
YOUNGSTERS ARE DELIGHTED BY THE JACKPOT
-Sook.
-Come on, not again.
Let me think. Nine times nine.
THE KIND-HEARTED ELDEST MEMBER
DOES HER BEST
I see.
-Jin.
-Yeah?
MULTIPLE VIOLATIONS
-Seven times…
-Seven?
two.
-Let's do jumping jacks while we're at it.
-You, Seok-jin.
Let's add jumping jacks to the game.
Let's go. Come on.
LET'S DO THIS
I'M GOING TO POINT AT YOU
I'M GOING TO MOVE MY ARMS
I'LL DO MY BEST TO KEEP UP
THERE'S NO WAY I'M FALLING FOR THAT
Someone's not getting on with the program.
I'M GOING TO BE SO OBVIOUS
I'm afraid the jumping jacks
might make my headband slip.
Why don't we hold on to the headband
and dance like this?
-I see, you see
SHE ENDS UP SABOTAGING HERSELF
-Like this?
I see, you see
-What's gotten into you?
VIOLATIONS KEEP PILING ON
EVEN WITHOUT THE CREW'S DIRECTION
WE'LL SIT BACK AND ENJOY THE SHOW
Wait, let's try this.
-I see, you see
-Just a second.
-Let's do this instead.
We'll each make a signature move.
Let's take turns to introduce it.
What's your move, Jin-kyung?
-Me? I guess…
-One, two, three, four.
I see, you see
-That's me.
-Here's mine.
WHO'D FALL FOR YOUR TRICKS NOW?
I see, you see
DEAR ARMY ACROSS THE GLOBE,
WE REALIZE OUR CAST MAY SEEM DIM
You could sprain your neck that way.
That's why I suggest this instead.
PLEASE BE PATIENT AND UNDERSTANDING
I see… Darn it.
Here's my signature move.
THE ULTIMATE VERSION
-I like the idea.
-I see, you see
-What's going on?
-What?
You added so many moves.
IS THIS A BTS DANCE?
It's too complicated.
I've never seen anything like it.
Here's what I'd like.
I see, you see
You need to point at the next person.
That's not for me, personally.
-Why?
-The moves are too feminine.
BELATED FOREBODING WASHES OVER SOOK
-It was too much.
-How's this?
I see, you see
-I dig the move.
-I'll take a pass.
IS THIS NOT TO YOUR LIKING?
IF THAT'S THE CASE,
HOW DO YOU FEEL ABOUT THIS?
You could point your fingers
as you play along. It's neat.
No, it doesn't seem that way to me.
I suddenly don't like playing at all.
How's this?
WHAT DO YOU THINK ABOUT THIS ONE?
For goodness' sake.
You might as well just spell it out.
LOL
Just read them out loud.
There's no way we'd do as you asked.
Don't be absurd.
All together!
-One, two, three, four.
-One, two, three, four!
EVERYONE IS TRYING OUT
OTHER PERSON'S FORBIDDEN ACTION
We could try another game.
It's a fun game.
Let's give it a go, one last time.
It's called the Swimming Game.
My nephew introduced it to me.
Swimming Game
If someone says "freestyle," we do this.
If the command is breaststroke,
we have to do this.
If you don't, you're out.
-Okay, I like it.
-For butterfly stroke, do this.
I dig it, actually.
-Ready, go.
-Go.
Swimming Game
-Swimming Game
-Your nephew plays weird games.
Freestyle!
-Do we have to do this as a group?
-Yeah.
It's your turn.
Make it fun while you're at it.
-Your style, bro!
-You'll then all imitate what I do.
THEY'RE OBVIOUSLY TARGETING ME
-Jin can go next. Ready, go.
-Which style do you want?
Swimming Game
WHAT STYLE SHOULD I GO FOR?
I'm not familiar with swimming styles.
Freestyle, brotterfly…
"Brotterfly"?
YOU WENT TOO FAR WITH THAT ONE
-Brockstroke. What else is there?
-"Brotterfly."
-Broggy paddle.
-Hold up.
Those were mispronunciations,
nothing more.
Still, good work, Jin-kyung.
I appreciated it.
Let's move on.
Please check your cards
on the count of three.
Three, two, one.
CHECKING THE KEYWORDS AND ACTIONS
Oh dear. Goodness!
Goodness!
Never did I imagine
having "bungee" on my card.
Three, two, one. Bungee!
Woo-jae, Woo-young, and I
are probably neck-and-neck at the top.
-I'll announce fourth place first.
-Let's hear it.
-It's Jin-kyung.
-Oh, my.
-Jin-kyung placed fourth?
-She's in fourth place?
-She must've shaken her head a lot.
-I didn't, though.
-But you did while dancing.
-She sure did.
Oh, you're right!
-I made quite a number of violations.
-Did I make many too?
I'd say it's down to "IC" or "bungee."
Really? Did I say "bungee" that often?
I'll announce third place.
It's Jin.
-I placed third.
-Jin?
-He didn't spread his arms.
-Did he only do that once?
He did so way more than that.
No, I didn't. I did this instead.
We'll review the video.
I think that's in order.
An ARMY member tallied it up,
so the result may be compromised.
Who is it?
WE KEPT IT FAIR
-Let's see. He has such long arms.
-Raise your arms like this.
-We have a tie in first place.
-A tie in first place?
They made nine mistakes each.
-We have a tie?
-Congrats, Woo-jae and Woo-young.
-How cool. I wish I did better.
-Brothers for life.
One of you said
the forbidden keyword 15 times
and did the forbidden action 14 times,
making 29 violations in total.
The other person said
the forbidden keyword 15 times
and did the forbidden action 53 times,
making 68 violations in total.
Did I make so many, though?
You placed last, Sook. Congratulations.
-Congrats!
-I pointed at someone 58 times?
-Me?
-Back when we were playing the game…
We danced, remember?
We don't have much time,
so let's hurry things up.
-We have to give her the finger flick?
-If that's the case,
-let's slap her wrist instead.
-Whatever.
-I'll let Jin take the honors.
-But why?
-We can do it too.
-Don't bother.
I don't want to, though.
Please hear me out.
My finger flick won't be fun at all
because it's neither strong nor weak.
But she can pull off a double roll.
-Really?
-She has it in her repertoire.
Understood.
When he taps your forehead, take a roll.
Choose your gift first.
-How are you settling it?
-Rock-Paper-Scissors?
I'll let Woo-jae take the prize.
How come?
Do Rock-Paper-Scissors
and yield after you've won.
That'll be much better.
I make my own decisions.
-Come on, follow my advice.
-Just this once.
What are you, a crayon?
Sure, I'm the color red. Go on now.
You'd look much cooler when you yield
after winning Rock-Paper-Scissors.
I'm taking back my initial offer.
Rock, paper, scissors!
I'll take the winner's prize.
JEEZ…
Wow, that was so smart.
WHICH ONE WILL HE CHOOSE?
Leave a good one for me, Woo-young.
-So?
-Pick this one.
-I want this one.
-Okay.
It must've been placed
in the center for a reason.
-I bet it's a tumbler!
-Unwrap it.
-You can do it sitting down.
-Hooray!
Is it a pair of shoes?
-What are those?
-A hat and a pair of socks.
-Are these official Netflix merchandise?
-Of course.
-How cute!
-I'm so jealous!
They only give you these
when you participate in their show.
Gosh, how stylish.
An idol can always pull off a look.
WOBBLY
I'm so jealous.
You're a lucky guy, Woo-young.
-Okay, let's move on to the finger flick.
-Please do.
It's been 20 years since I've tried.
Step forward when you do it.
-What? That's not necessary.
-Step up to her when you flick.
It's not easy to land a precise hit.
My flick doesn't pack a punch.
DON'T WORRY, I'VE GOT YOU
A LIGHT TAP
THE HALF-CENTENNIAL'S
PASSIONATE PERFORMANCE FOR JIN
I'm just not used to hitting people.
See how devoted she is?
-I never got the hang of the trick.
-I feel bad, though.
Look, blood is coming out of her mouth.
I can't believe you, Jin.
Gosh, he gave me
the gentlest finger flick.
He barely placed his finger there.
CONTRARY TO HIS WORDS, HE ONLY MADE A TAP
He's such a gentle soul.
-Okay.
-Let's move on.
I wanted to land a strong hit.
My flick doesn't pack a punch.
YOUR BEAUTY ALONE
IS ENOUGH TO MAKE US SMILE
YOU'RE ALREADY AN AMAZING COMEDIAN
A FEW HOURS LATER
Here we are at the party of the gods.
While this is an exclusive event
open only to the gods,
-we have…
-What is it?
We have received intel
that one human snuck in.
I see.
How amusing.
We have such an impudent mortal among us?
That's what the intel says.
THAT MORTAL, COULD IT BE JIN?
Man, it's so upsetting.
-I'm so ticked off.
-What's wrong?
ENJOY THE HIGHLIGHTS AND THE BTS CLIPS
ON STUDIO++'S YOUTUBE CHANNEL
"REBOOT" BY KYOUNGSEO (SCREWBALLS OST)
Subtitle translation by: Jeongwoo Kim
SCREWBALLS
IN SEARCH OF LOOSE SCREWS