♪The tempestuous northern wind,
the tempestuous martial arts world♪
♪Blades and bows drawn♪
♪What is youth without bravado?♪
♪With a wave of my hands, the world
flows through my fingertips♪
♪Traveling the world with a damsel♪
♪The wind blows,
the moon's reflection on the water♪
♪The night has been cut short♪
♪Who there is hiding in the shadow?♪
♪Oh, the long journey.
Fate wills if we live or die♪
♪But let's give our shot at this world♪
♪Fight together as two♪
♪Right or wrong, I'll brave the storm,
watching as things rise and fall♪
♪Black and White, as the drum sounds,
it's for passion and justice♪
♪The fury, the wavering blades♪
♪I catch a glimpse of the divine beauty♪
♪How can we determine
if the soul is flawless?♪
♪Let's see who can rule the world♪
=Who Rules The World=
=Episode 2=
I'll drink it on my own.
No need to be sanctimonious.
Not many get to be fed medicine by me.
Does
the renowned Bai Fengxi
dislike bitter medicine?
(In Memory of Yan Yingzhou)
I'll definitely keep
the promise that I made to you.
So rest assured.
(In Memory of Yan Yingzhou)
Don't tell me
you're going to build a hut
and guard the tomb here.
Anything I want to do
doesn't concern you.
Stop pretending to be nice.
Did you think
no one knew what you did in Mount Xuan?
Hawks drove the foes away.
Black Foxy was indeed behind this.
Indeed,
I can hide anything
from the world.
Yet, I couldn't hide anything from you.
You may be a known hero.
But I know you'll never do anything
that does you no good.
You're realistic and selfish.
I just didn't expect it.
You had the chance
to save Yan Yingzhou.
Yet, you watched
him fight hard to his death.
I have my reasons for my actions.
The poison in your body
has been suppressed for now.
If you want to remove it completely,
you need to head to the Han's Residence
for Buddha Pill.
Thank you for reminding me.
We shall part here.
(You'll understand)
(that it was Lord of Jizhou's greed)
(that sent General Liefeng
to his death.)
Bai Fengxi,
how dare you show yourself here.
We're going to avenge
the Han family today.
The Han family?
What happened to the Han family?
You killed everyone
in the Han's Residence
and burned down their home.
Yet, you're feigning ignorance.
The Han family has been massacred?
You wanted to snatch medicines
during Mr. Han's birthday feast.
He refused to give you any.
So you resented him.
Bai Fengxi, what else can you say?
All of you sure are good at talking.
You could just
say a few things
and pin this crime on me.
Who else would do it if not you?
Mr. Han is an amiable man.
You were the only one
who had a beef with him,
and the rest were all his friends.
That's right.
I take responsibility for my actions.
But I'm not involved in this matter.
Do you think you're innocent
because you say so?
Bai Fengxi,
do you really think nothing
of Beizhou's martial artists?
Today, we'll avenge the Han family!
She has been
with me these few days.
-Who are you?
-Who's there?
Mr. Fengxi?
What is he doing here?
I know you won't believe me.
But give me a few days.
I'll get to the bottom of this
to prove my innocence.
All right.
For Mr. Fengxi,
we'll spare you this time.
Bai Fengxi,
I hope you'll keep your word.
Leave.
Why did you follow me?
There is something strange
about the massacre of the Han family.
I just want to figure it out.
(How could this happen
to the Han family?)
(I must check it out.)
Sir,
the fire in the backyard
has been put out.
I want to know why this happened too.
Zhong Li. Chuanyu.
-Yes, sir.
-Stay here.
Yes, sir.
There's not one survivor.
Judging from the condition
of the bodies,
the attackers' motive is clear.
They wanted to annihilate
the Han family.
They were attacked with curved blades.
Soultaker Sect is behind this.
Soultaker Sect?
The reason Soultaker Sect wants
to annihilate the Han family
must be the medicines.
They were killed
because they have something valuable.
It is really the most outrageous thing
in the world.
It's not just for the medicines.
There are the Han family's
medicinal prescriptions too.
Anyone who possesses
the Han family's prescriptions
and refines them into pills
will be a great help
to war or the martial arts world.
There are 55 people
in the Han family, as far as I know.
But we were missing one person.
By the way,
did you see a child's body?
The Young Master of Han family, Han Pu?
No.
Han Xuanling must have hidden him away.
Let's search for him.
Don't come any closer!
Don't worry. We won't hurt you.
Go away!
These are the prescriptions
they were looking for.
As expected from Black Foxy.
Did you come
for these prescriptions that day too?
There is one option
if you want to find clues
about the Soultaker Sect.
If you spread out the news
that you've found
Han Pu and the prescriptions,
they'd come looking for you
instead of you looking for them.
I know.
But if you do this,
you'll put yourself in danger.
You can stay out of this.
Why is he still not awake?
You're up?
You must be starving.
I made plain congee for you.
Plain congee is the best
for someone who's starving.
Wait for me.
Black Foxy has sent people
to bury your family
at the Han's ancestral grave.
You can rest assured.
I won't hurt you.
I'll take care of you and protect you.
Don't worry about what happened
to the Han family.
I'll get to the bottom of it.
Take it as repayment
for giving me medicines the other day.
(If you spread out the news)
(that you've found)
(Han Pu and the prescriptions,)
(they'd come looking for you)
(instead of you looking for them.)
(Black Foxy's plan is not bad.)
(But this child is still shocked
by what happened.)
(If I do it,)
(he'll suffer.)
(But I can make some changes
to the plan.)
(Black Foxy is good at trapping people.)
(It's nothing if I trap him once.)
(It's decided, then.)
Do you want another bowl?
Stop the carriage.
Come out now.
You've followed for four li already.
This is the best place
for you to make your move.
Hei Fengxi, hand over
the Han family's prescriptions.
She used my plan against me.
Interesting.
What if I refuse?
That's not for you to decide.
(Shang)
It looks like we won't
be going back for now.
Chuanyu, head out first
and see how things are back home.
Zhong Li, come with me.
-Sir.
-Yes, sir.
We've wasted a lot of time
during this trip.
If anyone finds out you were not
at the residence,
I'm afraid there would be a danger.
Don't worry. It won't take too long.
We might reap great benefits this time.
Keep me informed
of the situation at home.
Yes, sir.
How is he?
He suffered a shock.
He must have been sleeping
and waking with a start these days.
I've calmed his nerves with acupuncture.
He can have a good night's rest now.
Thank you.
I said that for him.
I guess
it's time for us to settle some scores.
What scores?
You did come up with the plan.
If you want to get even,
you should get even with yourself.
If I'm alone,
I won't even set you up.
I just don't want the child
to see such a sight.
Your qi flow is still irregular.
Since you have the Han's prescriptions,
why didn't you refine the Buddha Pill
to remove the poison from your body?
It belongs to the Han family.
Even if I need it,
I should ask Han Pu's permission.
He's still in shock
and has never spoken since.
You didn't think that way
when you tried to rob them
of the medicines back then.
I did that to save people's life.
Since Soultaker Sect has found you,
did you find anything?
If you want the clue,
you should pay the price.
Black Foxy,
I'm afraid I have to count
the money you sold me for.
Stop wasting time and tell me.
I found this
on one of the bodies.
A silver leaf?
(Shang)
What does "Shang" mean on this silver?
To prevent the silver leaves
from being lost,
some rich people will make
some marks on the silver leaves.
This silver leaf is pointing to a clan.
The Shang family of Yucheng.
It's one of the two major clans
in Yucheng.
The family is rich and powerful.
So they were the ones
who colluded with Soultaker Sect
to snatch
the Han family's prescriptions.
But why?
We'll know after we ask them.
(Shang)
Pour the tea.
You want me to pour you tea?
That's originally Zhong Li's seat.
Naturally, Zhong Li would brew
the tea too.
Now that you've occupied his seat,
it's only natural
that you take over his duty.
But
you can choose
to switch places with him.
You can drive the carriage.
All right,
I'll pour you this tea.
Your skills in the art of tea are
better than Zhong Li's.
How about considering being
my maidservant?
So I can drink nice tea every day.
I don't have nice tea,
but I do have two fists.
I'd like to experience
your skill
Phoenix of the Highest Heaven.
Then I wonder
if your Darkness under the Heaven
can take it.
I've never met anyone
who's not willing to suffer any losses.
There are many people in this world.
How could you've met them all?
You've never met someone like me
because you've known too few people.
That's all.
I don't like
everyone.
They all say Prince Huang Chao is proud.
It seems that you're prouder than him.
Is there no one
who can grab your attention?
Not really.
There's one.
Tell me.
Tell me
which unlucky lady is that.
Xiyun of Qingzhou.
You may be skilled.
But you're still lacking more
to Xiyun in other aspects.
I'm sure you've never met her.
(Eight Pagoda, Dadong)
(Young Fengxi)
(Young Feng Xiyun)
When Xiyun was ten years old,
she wrote
the "Ten Strategies of Jingtai"
and gained fame worldwide.
After that, she left many poems.
She was an incomparable talent
since ancient times.
"Dejected and frustrated over wine.
Expressing bitterness in sorrow.
We don't know the fate
of someone on a shallow shore.
It's easy to feel heartbroken
when in a foreign land."
What's wrong?
My father taught me this poem before.
Just cry.
You'll feel better after you cry.
I'm hungry.
Zhong Li, stop the carriage.
Bring me my food container.
Sir,
we already ran out of food.
Didn't I tell you to prepare some food?
Miss Feng finished them all.
You didn't prepare that many anyway.
It's your fault
that the food is delicious.
One of the comments made
by Fountain Abode on you is
your love to eat.
I think that's wrong.
You were even greedy for food.
Where can we find food
in the wild?
I knew you were spoiled.
You would die from cold and starvation
if you became homeless.
Wait here.
I'll find something to eat.
Since you've started speaking,
I need your help on one thing.
Angelica root, lily magnolia, lychnis,
jilong wood, heavenly snow lotus seed,
and wanlihong.
These are the ingredients used
to refine Buddha Pill.
How did you know about these?
I read this prescription
on the day of your father's
birthday banquet.
I promise you
that I won't do evil
with your family's prescription.
Since you already know the prescription,
why do you still need my help?
I've tried several times
and failed to refine it into pills.
You've tried several times?
Jilong wood, heavenly snow lotus seed,
and wanlihong
are hard to buy.
You actually tried several times.
This is my last batch
of medicinal ingredients.
I can't fail.
Why do you need to refine the pill
when you're not poisoned?
I see.
You were doing this
for Bai Fengxi, right?
From her complexion,
there's some poison left in her body.
Bai Fengxi saved your life.
Saving her is
not only to help me.
You failed to refine the pills
probably because the method
of extracting medicine was wrong.
You must leave.
Yingzhou,
we're here to bring you home.
Order them to exhume the body
(In Memory of Yan Yingzhou)
and bring Yingzhou's body back to Jizhou
for a national burial.
Yes, Your Highness.
Your Highness,
I've sent the men to search Mount Xuan.
We didn't find Bai Fengxi's body.
I think Hei Fengxi has taken her away.
Then the Empyrean Token
must be in Hei Fengxi's hand.
We must not let the thing
Yingzhou defended with his life fall
into the hand of others.
(In Memory of Yan Yingzhou)
I won't allow it
even if it's Hei Fengxi.
Order the men
to find Hei-Bai Fengxi's whereabouts.
I want to meet
these two masters myself.
Yes, Your Highness.
(Tianshuang Sect)
Hand over Bai Fengxi
and the Empyrean Token!
I've told you
(Tianshuang Sect's Disciple, Xiu Jiurong)
that Bai Fengxi has yet returned.
We don't believe you!
Let us search Tianshuang Sect!
(Tianshuang Sect)
Are you trying to break into our sect?
Why don't you look at yourselves
(Sect Leader's Daughter, Bai Langhua)
in the mirror?
If you want to enter,
you'll have to defeat us first.
(Tianshuang Sect's Leader, Bai Jiande)
Stop it!
(Tianshuang Sect)
Greetings, Master.
Are you trying
to make Tianshuang Sect your enemy?
Master Bai,
we naturally don't wish
to make you our enemy.
The Empyrean Token concerns the world.
We only want to obtain
the Empyrean Token
and escort it back to the Imperial City
to end all conflicts.
Could it be
that Tianshuang Sect is coveting
(Tianshuang Sect's Disciple, Gu Yu)
the Empyrean Token?
We have no intention to do so.
If you speak nonsense again
and slander Tianshuang Sect,
I won't be polite.
We naturally believe
in Master Bai and Tianshuang Sect.
But Bai Fengxi...
She's our sect's disciple.
She naturally won't covet
the Empyrean Token.
But if you still want
to make a scene here
and disturb our cultivation,
I won't let you off the hook easily.
Master Bai, we'll take our leave.
We'll take our leave!
Bai Fengxi sure is a troublemaker.
It was only a couple of days ago
when you pestered the storyteller
to tell the battle
at Mount Xuan three times.
You also kept saying
that Bai Fengxi is your Martial Sister.
I was happy on Tianshuang Sect's behalf.
Gu Yu, take them inside.
Yes, Master.
Han Pu is already asleep.
Thank you.
Who are you thanking me for this time?
I'm thanking you on my behalf.
Pu gave me a Buddha Pill.
I know you must be the one
who provided the medicinal ingredients.
I just don't want you to delay me
when we reach Yucheng.
I should say the same thing to you.
I'm hungry.
We just had dinner four hours ago.
They say a generous person has
a big stomach,
while my stomach is as vast as an ocean.
Come on. Let's eat something.
I'm not hungry.
Yes, you are.
You don't have any money.
It's not that.
It's too heavy for me
to carry money around.
Come on, don't waste time.
Let's go and have something to eat.
Otherwise, I'm going
to eat around for free
in your name.
Ladies and gentlemen,
there are many experts
in the martial arts world.
-But among these experts...
-Excuse me.
A plate of beef, a roasted goose,
and a stray of steamed buns.
Please wait for a moment.
Sir, please have a seat.
They're Immortal Tianji
and Immortal Taiyin.
Those two immortals have long lived
a secluded life
from the martial arts world.
Why didn't you pick a room?
No one knows their whereabouts.
You're indeed a picky person.
Isn't it great to be in a lively crowd?
The soldiers pressed the border.
It was bleak,
and the smell of blood filled the air.
These two showed their skills
during the battle.
They were the famous Hei-Bai Fengxi
from the martial arts world.
The battle was in full swing.
The corpses
were lying all over the ground.
Only a few remnants
were still struggling to fight.
-Then, the earth fell apart.
-Please enjoy.
In that instant,
people wet their pants in terror.
Do you have a small change?
I don't bring small change.
I only have silver leaves.
It turned out to be Bai Fengxi.
When Bai Fengxi flared up,
a man in black stood at the other end.
This person was...
Thank you.
Hei Fengxi, who is on a par with her.
Both of them...
Miss, what's the meaning of this?
It's to reward you.
Thank you, Miss.
But you need to do me a favor.
It has always been Bai-Hei Fengxi
in the martial arts world.
There was never a saying
of Hei-Bai Fengxi.
Please don't make this mistake
in the future.
Yes, of course.
So please repeat it.
They were the famous Bai-Hei Fengxi
from the martial arts world.
-Then Bai Fengxi and Hei Fengxi
-Thank you.
fought together.
This battle put everything upside down.
Heaven and earth changed color.
When Hei Fengxi roared,
the dragon emerged from the clouds.
That's the reason you ask
for money from me?
I don't like being inferior to others.
Bai-Hei Fengxi sounds nice.
As it reached the clouds,
it saw Queen Mother had
a peach banquet in a flash!
(It's about time the matter is solved.)
Feng!
It looks like they've made their move.
Sir.
So you already knew.
Did you think I really wanted
to eat with you?
From the clean plates,
I guess so.
I didn't want to waste food.
If we hadn't left,
they wouldn't have come.
I'm sure you know where they went.
Since when did you find out?
From
the moment you chose the inn.
Fountain Abode is set up
all over the country.
You'd set up everything
before you set out anywhere.
And this time
you chose an inn.
Sure enough, you know me best.
Of course.
Zhong Li, lead the way.
Yes, sir.
No need. Just give us the address.
Bring Han Pu back.
No, I want to come with you.
No...
Let's go together, then.
Follow me.
(Wang's Tofu Store)
Sir, this is the place.
It's you!
I'm going to kill all of you!
It was them! They did it!
They killed my family!
I'm going to kill them!
Han Pu.
Tell us.
Where are the rest
of the Soultaker Sect's members hiding?
They...
Are they...
They've taken their own lives.
Han Pu,
those from Soultaker Sect are dead.
You can say you've avenged
your family's death.
But you must remember
you must never kill anyone.
Killing people won't make anyone happy.
Even if it's for revenge.
Paying blood with blood
will never end.
It's going to be endless.
I'll get rid of the rest
of the Soultaker Sect.
But you must not stain your hands
with blood.
Understand?
Let's go.
Master,
the people we sent were found out.
(Soultaker Sect's Leader)
They were all killed
by Bai Fengxi and Hei Fengxi.
As expected of Hei-Bai Fengxi.
I suppose they've found some clues.
That's why they're coming to Yucheng.
Since that's the case,
I'll be waiting for them here.
(Hot Spring Palace, Yongzhou)
(Hot Spring Palace)
Chuanyun.
(Hei Fengxi's Guard, Ren Chuanyun)
Why did you come back by yourself?
Where's Young Master?
He still has unfinished business.
He's heading to Yucheng with Zhong Li.
Yucheng?
It's less than half a month
before the autumn hunting.
If he failed to return in time,
what should we do then?
Why is Young Master going to Yucheng?
Is it for the Empyrean Token?
He said
he'll obtain a great harvest in Yucheng.
I understand.
(Hot spring Palace)
I hope he can make it back in time.
Third Prince has been keeping
an eye on us.
I'm afraid there might be trouble.
While you were away,
Third Prince had come
to probe around several times.
Young Master has already figured it out.
This letter is from Young Master.
(Chuanyun, I'll leave
all the affairs at home to you.)
(Spread words that
I have relapsed from my old injury...)
I guess this is all we can do now.
Let's meet with Miss Huan
to follow Young Master's order.
(Hot spring Palace)
Are you trying
to use these to compensate
for yesterday's food?
Don't underestimate these raspberries.
They're sweet and sour,
and they complement the tea.
It's tasty.
Are you sure you don't want to try it?
I...
Tasty, right?
I knew you'd like it.
Master,
we've destroyed Fountain Abode's
hideout in Yucheng.
There are no survivors left.
All right.
I just don't understand one thing.
You've set up traps
to wait for Hei-Bai Fengxi to come.
Won't destroying the hideout alert them?
Once they know
we've destroyed the hideout
of Fountain Abode in Yucheng,
they might not come to Yucheng anymore.
You underestimate these two too much.
These two won't be scared
by this incident.
Do you know
what Hei Fengxi's biggest strength is?
It's said he has a move called
"Darkness under the Heaven".
Hei Fengxi's strength doesn't lie
in martial arts.
But the intelligence network
of Fountain Abode around the country.
These hideouts are his eyes.
They observe the country
and collect intelligence for him.
Losing Fountain Abode would mean
losing half of his strength.
I understand now.
Are you all right?
You've been sitting there all day.
Did anything happen?
Just worry about yourself
and don't disturb me from thinking.
Tell me.
Tell me about it.
Fountain Abode may provide intelligence
to the world.
But its hideouts are hidden.
I've recruited
many skilled people for every branch.
But Soultaker Sect actually destroyed
my hideout in Yucheng in one night.
It looks like I underestimated them.
We must not take
the person behind this lightly.
So you're scared now.
I'm not scared.
I just don't know how
to find the Shang family
and find out the truth without the help
from Fountain Abode.
Black Foxy,
you're usually smart.
Why are you a fool now?
I'm not a fool.
Yes,
you're not a fool.
You were too dependent on external help.
You built up
Fountain Abode step by step.
What about before that?
Have you forgotten that you used
to be in the martial arts world?
Thank you for reminding me of that.
Since Soultaker Sect knew
we're heading to Yucheng,
I'm sure they've set up
many traps for us.
Do you still want to go?
Of course. Why shouldn't I?
I'm brave, so I'm not scared.
It looks like you already have a plan.
Yucheng is an important city
of Shangzhou.
It's the richest place.
The Shang family is one
of the two local tyrants in Yucheng.
We may not be
their match if we join hands.
The only way to handle
a local tyrant is
to find another local tyrant's help.
Since you already have a plan,
I'll take some rest then.
Indeed,
you may be a particular person.
But your carriage's couch is
really comfortable.
Wake me when we reach Yucheng.
Gadgets and trinkets for sale!
(Denglin Restaurant)
Come again.
Thank you, Feng.
Eat more.
The food in Denglin Restaurant is
delicious.
I feel sorry for the food
from the way you gobbled them up.
You don't know anything.
They are happy to be eaten by me
because they're converted
into my strength.
Yes.
You're right about that.
This one is delicious.
Han Pu, eat some.
Thank you, Feng.
When are we going
to the Qi's Residence?
We'll wait for them to come to us.
This horse...
What are you doing?
This horse is excellent.
I want it.
-Make an offer!
-Feng,
this meat is very salty.
Is it?
You might not know who I am.
(Young Master of the Qi Family, Qi Yun)
I'm Qi Yun of the Qi family
in Yucheng.
Tell your master
that I want this horse.
I've told you
that this horse isn't for sale.
It's not up to you to say that!
You look like a sticky bean cake!
What did you say?
Mung bean cake.
You...
Time to go.
It's time for you to make an appearance.
Me?
There's no free lunch in this world.
Now?
I knew he was up to no good.
Wait here.
You must be his master.
I want this horse.
Make an offer.
My servant has told you
that this horse is not for sale.
You might not know who I am.
I'm...
You were so loud just now.
Do you think my Young Master is deaf?
Fine.
Since you know
I'm the Young Master of the Qi family,
how dare you treat me so arrogantly?
You're going to regret this.
You're going to sell me this horse
whether you like it or not!
Master Zhao!
I wanted
to let you make the offer.
But now...
See?
Only two silver leaves left.
This is the price of your ignorance.
I'm afraid
you were the ignorant one.
Xi, it's your turn.
(Xi?)
Zhao Qinghou,
you're the leader of Qiujiang Alliance
who has become the manservant
for a household, aren't you?
Since you know who I am,
don't seek trouble.
You speak without thinking.
Since I know who you are,
that means I'm not scared of you.
You'd better leave now.
I shall see what skills you can show me.
Mr. Qi, anything else?
Just wait here.
Carry that useless thing!
Carry him!
You called "Xi" very smoothly.
Black Foxy,
what exactly are you up to?
I thought we were going
to work with the Qi family.
Now, you taught Mr. Qi a lesson.
What exactly are you thinking?
The more powerful
you are in cooperation,
the more benefit you'll get.
♪Like the dissipating fog,
you become clearer♪
♪Like the hawk that soars freely,
you reject the shackles♪
♪Your white silk is as light
as a feather and yet it moves my heart♪
♪Ripples come at me
but I don't want to dodge♪
♪Wind is just the outline of the cloud♪
♪Black is the lock of the White♪
♪Night is when the Day sleeps♪
♪You are a part of me♪
♪Right or wrong,
don't worry about the why♪
♪Pain or joy,
they are from our obsession♪
♪If some things cannot be taken apart♪
♪Then let's face
the uncertainty together♪
♪Let tears run dry♪
♪Let's stop in another place♪
♪Let love sever
all happiness and sadness♪
♪And pierce through
the vicissitude of life♪
♪With a merry start, don't worry
about a sorrowful end♪
♪A full moon will be more intertwined♪
♪If some things cannot be taken apart♪
♪Then let's face
the uncertainty together♪