♪The tempestuous northern wind,
the tempestuous martial arts world♪
♪Blades and bows drawn♪
♪What is youth without bravado?♪
♪With a wave of my hands, the world
flows through my fingertips♪
♪Traveling the world with a damsel♪
♪The wind blows,
the moon's reflection on the water♪
♪The night has been cut short♪
♪Who there is hiding in the shadow?♪
♪Oh, the long journey.
Fate wills if we live or die♪
♪But let's give our shot at this world♪
♪Fight together as two♪
♪Right or wrong, I'll brave the storm,
watching as things rise and fall♪
♪Black and White, as the drum sounds,
it's for passion and justice♪
♪The fury, the wavering blades♪
♪I catch a glimpse of the divine beauty♪
♪How can we determine
if the soul is flawless?♪
♪Let's see who can rule the world♪
=Who Rules The World=
=Episode 1=
(In a world divided
into seven factions,)
(the Imperial Family)
(rules the Six States
with the Empyrean Token.)
(Within the martial world)
(lies the two strongest individuals,)
(the Head of Fountain Abode,)
(Hei Fengxi,)
(and a heroine from Tianshuang Sect,)
(Bai Fengxi,)
(both of whom are stuck
in a perpetual fight for superiority.)
(Interestingly,)
(as indifferent to others
as Hei Fengxi is,)
(he will always attend)
(every challenge Bai Fengxi issues.)
(Thus, many jest)
(that wherever Bai Fengxi is,)
(Hei Fengxi will surely be there too.)
(Now, their story begins
in the Dadong Empire.)
(Dadong)
(Crown Prince of Dadong, Jing Yan)
Your Majesty, the Crown Prince
requests an audience with you.
Bring him in.
(Dadong)
The Crown Prince, Jing Yan,
will now meet with His Majesty!
(Emperor Chunxi of Dadong)
Greetings, Father.
I wish you a life
of longevity and prosperity.
I was told
that the Empyrean Token went missing.
Are you panicking?
I...
Remember.
You are my son,
the future Emperor of Dadong.
Nothing in this world can faze you.
So
what should we do next, sir?
The loss of the Empyrean Token
will provoke different reactions
from the Six States.
Your Majesty,
let's sit tight and assess.
Just proceed with the plan.
(Dadong)
Emperor Chunxi of Dadong
has issued a decree
to the lords of all Six States.
Find the Empyrean Token.
(Fountain Abode)
It's okay, Cangyi.
Take your time.
(Hei Fengxi's Servant, Zhong Li)
Sir.
Heavy rainfall this year
has inevitably affected
the taste of the fountain water.
Sir, Cangyi came back with a message
that the Imperial Family lost
the Empyrean Token.
Emperor Chunxi has issued a imperial decree
and tasked every State
with its retrieval.
The Imperial Family's power
is on the decline.
The Six States are coveting the throne.
And now, the Empyrean Token
went missing.
There must be some machinations.
Zhong Li.
Ask everyone here
to collect more info
about the Imperial Family
and get to the bottom of this.
Yes, sir.
(Head of Fountain Abode, Hei Fengxi)
(Six States shall retrieve Empyrean Token)
(and return it to the Imperial Family.)
After the establishment
of Dadong Empire,
(Lord of Qingzhou)
to keep the power in check,
(Lord of Beizhou)
the founding father, Emperor Weilie,
forged the Empyrean Token.
(Lord of Shangzhou)
It is the symbol of sovereignty.
(Lord of Jizhou)
Whoever possesses it
(Lord of Youzhou)
will be the rightful ruler of the world.
Empyrean Token carries the world.
Get the Token
and the world will be yours.
Make an announcement.
(Lord of Yongzhou)
Let everyone
in Yongzhou search for this token.
(One Month Later)
(Mount Xuan)
(General Liefeng of Jizhou,
Yan Yingzhou)
(Dadong Empire Map)
Your Highness,
(Jizhou's General, Xiao Xuekong)
Yan Yingzhou has found the Empyrean Token.
(The Heir of Lord of Jizhou, Huang Chao)
Good.
Where is he now?
He's currently in Beizhou.
The other States
have sent their respective envoys.
Dispatch our people
to get Yingzhou to safety.
Yes, Your Highness.
If the Empyrean Token
belongs to Jizhou,
it'll be a matter of time
before the entire world follows suit.
I haven't seen
these many dimwits in a while.
How fun.
(Disciple of Tianshuang Sect, Bai Fengxi)
Lin Yin'an of Youzhou,
why are you intervening now?
Were you trembling in your boots
when you saw Yan Yingzhou's long blade?
You're asking for my blade.
Come down now!
I dislike your manner of speech.
You're the Heroine Fengxi?
Do you know me?
Bai Fengxi, as beautiful
as she is lethal. Everyone knows that.
Are you interested
in the Empyrean Token too, Miss Feng?
I couldn't care less about the token.
However, I quite like
this Yan Yingzhou.
You are strong, Miss,
but you are outnumbered.
Why should you meddle in this business?
If you can compensate for my loss,
I'll leave right away.
Name your price.
I was having a nap
and you interrupted my sweet dream.
Do you know who I dreamt of?
Queen Mother of the West. She invited me
to the Divine Mountain, Kunlun
to wine and to admire fairy dances
with her.
Oh, the bliss!
She even gave me a Divine Peach.
Just when I was about to take it
from her hands,
all of you barged in.
If you can
give me this Divine Peach,
I'll leave right away.
I don't want Yan Yingzhou
or the Empyrean Token.
He, this woman is just taking us
for fools.
Chase her!
Catch me if you can.
(Pure and Elegant)
Sir, I just received news
that General Liefeng of Jizhou,
Yan Yingzhou,
got the Empyrean Token.
All other States
are hunting him right now.
Jizhou
sure is doing everything
to get the token.
Sir, now is good timing.
Are we not going in to interfere?
You see the full picture
but you fail to understand humans.
Humans?
All Six States have their own agenda.
Whoever gets the Empyrean Token first
will get a head start
but they will have to face
the siege from the rest.
It's unfortunate for General Liefeng
that he has to deal with it now.
Sir,
another update.
Bai Fengxi of Tianshuang Sect
rescued Yan Yingzhou.
Is your rival, Miss Feng,
after the token as well?
Let Cangyi follow them closely.
Noted.
(Is she here too?)
(It must be just an act of heroism.)
(Well, she has always been like that.)
Thank you for your intervention,
Heroine Feng.
May I know why you saved me?
Three years ago.
In Changfeng City.
In Changfeng City?
That day,
Jizhou and Shangzhou waged a war.
To protect the commoners,
you and your army
held the Shangzhou army
in the Liefeng Pass,
north of Changfeng City.
You won the war
but you also disrupted
the military pacing
and were duly punished
by the Lord of Jizhou.
War is among soldiers.
The commoners are innocent.
And that
is why I saved you.
You care about the people
and your nation.
You shouldn't die to thugs.
What I did today
was just fulfilling
all commoners' wishes.
You have a sense of justice,
Heroine Feng.
Heroine Feng,
I have another favor to ask.
To deliver the Empyrean Token to Jizhou?
Sorry, I can't help it.
I'm used to lounging around.
Do it yourself.
I might not survive for long.
You met me.
You still stand a chance to live.
Do you know the Han family?
Do you want to get some medicines
from them?
You catch up quickly.
I am a close friend
of their family's head.
I will get Zifu Powder and Buddha Pill
from him.
You'll be fine.
Take this first.
You will live for another day.
I will bring
medicines to you within a day.
(Pure and Elegant)
Sir, Cangyi fetched another message.
Miss Feng is now heading
to the Han's Residence.
No trace of Yan Yingzhou.
She is trying to get some medicines
for him.
Find her and we'll find Yan Yingzhou,
and the token too, of course.
Many are
looking for her now.
Didn't Han Xuanling
send us an invitation?
Yes.
Good.
Let's pay him a visit.
(The Hans)
(Han's Residence)
(Birthday)
(Han's Young Master, Han Pu,
Han's Family Head, Han Xuanling)
Mr. Han!
May you live long and prosper!
Thank you.
My beloved guests.
Today is my birthday.
I thank you all for coming
to share this joy with me.
A toast to everyone!
How festive.
You again?
Better late than never.
I too would like to wish you, Mr. Han,
a long and prosperous life.
Bai Fengxi.
If you stopped dropping by here,
I definitely would live longer.
You have snatched medicines from me
many times.
Today is my day
and I will let you slide just this once.
Please leave at once.
Otherwise, pardon my aggression.
You set the rule
that whoever wants medicines from you
needs to pay a thousand pieces of gold.
You practically forced me to steal.
But don't you worry.
All your medicines did not go to waste.
They saved countless lives.
You should thank me, you know.
Enough of your twists and turns.
Never have I seen anyone
as shameless as you.
This is a warning.
Leave now
and never come back again!
I have an emergency too
so I won't stay
for your birthday dinner.
One pack of Zifu Powder
and one Buddha Pill.
I'll leave once I get them.
Someone!
Get her out of my sight!
What a fine brew!
You did not skimp for your
60th birthday.
You...
Enjoy the feast while you can, everyone.
Mr. Han
is celebrating his 60th birthday today.
God knows if there will be his 61st.
Why do you wish ill-luck upon my father?
Young child,
knowing how stingy your father is,
we truly don't know if he will spend
as much for his next birthday.
Han Pu.
Back off.
Housekeeper, take him away!
Hurry up.
Bai Fengxi.
In terms of martial arts,
I am far inferior to you.
That's why you snatched many medicines
from me.
But
if you want
to attempt the same thing today,
I will not surrender easily.
Mr. Han,
today is your birthday.
Just stay aside
and let me teach her a lesson
on your behalf.
I will need
any help I can get.
You stole my pig trotter!
Too slow.
Try harder.
(Han's Residence)
Sir, there's a brawl inside.
As usual.
Choking?
Does it hurt?
Let me help you.
Zhong Li, announce our presence.
Noted.
Can we talk now?
Wait.
(Birthday)
Mr. Han.
My Young Master came bearing
good wishes.
Who is your Young Master?
Hei Fengxi of Fountain Abode.
(Hei Fengxi?)
(Why is he here?)
Oh, Mr. Fengxi.
Show him in.
Did you invite Hei Fengxi?
Do you truly think you're the strongest
in the world now?
Don't you know
some guests are best uninvited?
I just know
an uninvited guest like you
is a pain in the neck.
You can't distinguish friends from foes.
How did you survive thus far?
Black Foxy!
Come out now!
Or else, I'll skin you!
You have never changed a bit.
As uncouth as ever.
Sir.
The time it takes
for you to settle in comfortably
is enough for me
to take a nap already.
You have not improved at all.
I ought to, truth be told.
I hate to be in the same league as you.
It's the greatest misfortune ever.
May I remind you
that you should mind your posture now?
Otherwise,
"as beautiful as she is lethal"
will sound like a joke.
Greetings, Mr. Fengxi.
Pardon
this sorry state of affairs.
Greetings, Mr. Han.
You traveled far to my abode,
Mr. Fengxi.
I owe you a proper welcome
but
unfortunately,
I'm in a pickle at the moment.
May I ask for your assistance?
You want me to teach Bai Fengxi
a lesson?
And
please make her
pay me back the medicines
she stole from me.
Mr. Han.
I have used all your medicines
and I have no money with me.
What to do then,
Mr. Han?
It's simple.
Apologize to me in person
and leave her thieving hands here.
I'll forgo our past grievances.
Take them away then.
This accursed life!
Why do I have to know
a troublemaker like you?
Mr. Han,
how about I apologize to you
on her behalf?
I can't possibly accept it.
She stole your medicines
to help others.
It's not for personal gain.
Consider her gesture as accumulating
good merits for your family.
Please muster your generosity
and forgive her youthful misbehavior.
As for the stolen medicines...
Give me a price, Mr. Han.
I'll settle the payment.
I...
While her boisterous act might have
offended many heroes here,
it is but her playful nature.
Do take it as a harmless joke
and I pray
that you will be generous enough
to not hold her accountable.
Again, I apologize to all of you
on her behalf.
(He is known to be cunning.)
(What is he plotting today?)
You're too courteous, Mr. Fengxi.
We will not hold any grudge
against Heroine Feng, of course.
Now that the dust has settled,
to celebrate
Mr. Han's birthday,
I have brought 100 pots of fine wine.
Would all of you love to have a sip?
Thank you, Mr. Fengxi.
Please wait in the adjacent yard.
(Whatever. I'll get the medicine first.)
Thank you.
Mr. Han.
The thing inside
is worth 100,000 pieces of gold.
It's more than enough to pay
for the medicines I stole.
Can you give me
one more pack of Zifu Powder
and Buddha Pill?
This is the payment
for the medicines she stole.
Please accept it, Mr. Han.
Can you give her what she asked for?
Sure.
Of course.
I shall retrieve the medicines now.
All right.
Oh, lord.
Bai Fengxi, stand right there!
Stay there!
My medicines will be all gone now.
Stay right there, Bai Fengxi!
Bai Fengxi.
Give me the Empyrean Token.
I don't have it.
Leave now.
Don't make me angry.
Nonsense.
You rescued Yan Yingzhou.
If you don't have it,
then tell me where he is now.
Don't force our hands.
I, Bai Fengxi,
is not averse to blood.
Yan Yingzhou!
Idiot!
Come.
Zhong Li.
Why did our Young Master
treat these people to wine?
It's because
he doesn't want them to go to Mount Xuan
(Hei Fengxi's Servant, Ren Chuanyu)
to cause more trouble for Miss Feng.
So what is the relationship
between them?
You are always with him.
Tell me.
I saw Miss Feng several times
when I was with our Young Master.
But every time they saw each other,
they fought.
Why?
To see who's the best.
To find out whether Hei Fengxi
or Bai Fengxi will rule
the martial world.
I truly have not met
a woman like Miss Feng before.
She refuses to conform.
Don't you think so?
I do. Yes, she is being uncivilized.
But somehow, I feel
that she's meant to behave that way.
I even envy her a bit.
Maybe
Young Master is into Miss Feng.
Right?
I think so too.
Yes.
You see, Young Master is...
Sir.
Who do I like?
Everyone inside is drunk.
We should leave now.
Any update on Mount Xuan?
After Miss Feng returned,
Yan Yingzhou is nowhere to be found.
Everyone
is looking for him in Mount Xuan now.
(I think he just doesn't want
to burden Bai Fengxi.)
(Given her nature,)
(that will just make her more committed
to this affair.)
(It seems like)
(a tough battle awaits tonight.)
Yan Yingzhou.
Heroine Feng.
These are the Buddha Pills.
This is Zifu Powder,
for external wounds.
Please take it.
Thank you, Heroine Feng.
Why did you leave on your own?
I rescued you.
You are not a burden to me.
Come. This way.
Let's go.
Yan Yingzhou.
Hand over the Empyrean Token
and you will be spared.
Bai Fengxi,
do you think both of you
can flee this mountain?
Do you want to fight together
and clear a path for us?
I'm glad you asked.
With a chance to fight together
with Heroine Feng,
I have no regret in my life.
Go!
Empyrean Token!
The token is poisonous.
They escaped again.
At this point, you should leave first.
Eat these.
You...
Two Buddha Pills
will be enough to counter the toxin
in my system.
I saved them just in case.
These four Buddha Pills
are not the antidotes to the poison,
but they can prolong your life
for the moment.
Given what you're capable of,
you just need to go to the Hans
and ask for more Buddha Pills
to save yourself.
They are here.
I will lure them away.
Just find an opening to sneak out.
I know I shouldn't burden you
with any more tasks
but please deliver this blade
to Prince Huang Chao.
I will repay your kindness
in my next life.
I, Yan Yingzhou, am here.
Who's here for a duel?
Sir.
Miss Feng is safe
but Yan Yingzhou lost his life.
Who would know that Yan Yingzhou
would meet his end
in Mount Xuan?
(They couldn't find the Empyrean Token)
(so they would go after her now.)
Deliver this message.
Let Sun Si arrange accordingly.
Noted, sir.
Yan Yingzhou is dead
but the Empyrean Token is still missing.
Bai Fengxi has it then.
Who are you?
(Servant of Fountain Abode, Sun Si)
Sun Si of Fountain Abode.
Why are you in our way?
My Young Master said
that Mount Xuan is a dangerous place.
Why don't all of you turn around
and have a moment's rest
by the foot of the mountain?
Why should we do that?
My Young Master is not trying
to coerce everyone into leaving.
Do note that
my Young Master set up
many traps in this mountain.
Hike the mountain
at your own discretion.
I heard in the Han's Residence,
Hei Fengxi helped Bai Fengxi.
I'm sure
both of them are working together.
Those are my Young Master's words.
Whether you choose
to believe them or not, it's up to you.
I'm just the messenger
to deliver a warning.
Fountain Abode has intervened.
I don't know what its Head is plotting.
It's dark and the path
is littered with traps.
I quit.
Let's go.
All right.
I don't believe that Hei Fengxi at all.
Let's go.
Yan Yingzhou.
Where are you?
You're late.
He's already dead.
Dead?
Who are you?
You don't need to know.
Hand over the Empyrean Token
and it will be a quick death.
No way.
Sir.
The Soultaker Sect arrived at Mount Xuan.
They surrounded Miss Feng.
Those vermin
came as well.
Should we...
♪Like the dissipating fog,
you become clearer♪
♪Like the hawk that soars freely,
you reject the shackles♪
♪Your white silk is as light
as a feather and yet it moves my heart♪
♪Ripples come at me♪
♪But I don't want to dodge♪
♪Wind is just the outline of the cloud♪
You're safe now.
♪Black is the lock of the White♪
♪Night is when the Day sleeps♪
♪You are a part of me♪
♪With a merry start, don't worry
about a sorrowful end♪
Is this the Empyrean Token?
This token
is a counterfeit.
Northsea Iron shines blue under light.
This token does not carry
such characteristic.
So Yan Yingzhou is just a decoy?
Huang Chao already has the token?
Yan Yingzhou
is the leader
of the Four Jizhou Generals.
The Heir of the Lord of Jizhou, Huang Chao,
appreciates good talents.
He won't sacrifice Yan Yingzhou
like this.
So this token is a fake one
from the get-go?
Everyone fought after
a fake Empyrean Token?
Circulate this fake Empyrean Token
and make all heroes lose their lives for it.
The mastermind will reap the benefit.
What a huge web he cast.
Now that we know the token
is a counterfeit,
should we head back, sir?
Wait.
Check if she is okay
before we return.
Zhong Li.
Build two huts
next to the cavern.
Noted.
Greetings, Your Highness.
Status report?
General Yan lost his life in Mount Xuan.
Has Yingzhou died?
Yes.
A bloody battle broke out in Mount Xuan.
We were too late.
General Yan was outnumbered
and lost his life.
Rumor has it that Bai Fengxi
has the Empyrean Token now.
Bai Fengxi with the plain white attire.
She has the Empyrean Token.
Any news about her?
Nothing so far.
Your Highness, I will send someone
to look for her now.
Since
Yingzhou is dead,
let's return...
We have to head to Mount Xuan.
Let's bring Yingzhou
home.
Noted.
You're awake.
I didn't know
you would get poisoned as well.
The token is poisonous.
If you had notified me,
I could have saved Yan Yingzhou.
If I had notified you earlier,
you would have arrived earlier
and had the token.
Sorry
to have left you out
of this excellent opportunity.
Our misunderstanding runs deep.
You couldn't find Yan Yingzhou
in Mount Xuan
so you thought I had the token.
That's why you visited
the Han's Residence, didn't you?
You got me out of the pickle,
supposedly,
but you didn't expect
that I didn't have the token with me.
Therefore, you followed me
and waited for its reappearance.
But I didn't take the token, did I?
No, you didn't.
You know the token
is hidden within the blade.
Why didn't you take it and leave?
Per the rules of Fountain Abode,
one thousand golden leaves
for an answer.
I think you're too poor for that.
You ignored the Empyrean Token.
Either something's wrong with you
or something's wrong with the token.
It's a fake token then?
What a vicious scheme.
I already found Yan Yingzhou's body
and buried him in Mount Xuan.
He was stabbed 32 times.
I admire his fearlessness.
However,
he could use some help
with his martial arts.
Black Foxy.
His fearlessness made you feel
all ashamed, didn't it?
Everyone knows the bravery
of General Liefeng.
Unlike a certain foxy person.
All his reputation is but a scam.
You need to rest for several days.
Don't overexert yourself.
Sir, the medicinal broth is ready.
I was thinking,
if you came in contact with the
poison from decaying vines
and you couldn't make it,
then
this world
would only have one Fengxi left.
Why did you save me then?
I won't be grateful for you, you know.
I won't blame you
if you leave me to my own devices.
But you, Black Foxy,
are always plotting for something.
I saved you for the Empyrean Token.
Unfortunately, the token is fake.
If you die as well,
my investment will be in vain.
It's as if
I have been outwitted by the mastermind.
I hate being outwitted.
Therefore, you can't die.
Wait,
you forgot something.
If I die,
no one will know your true face.
Life will be boring.
Come.
I expended a great deal of effort
to concoct this broth
to save you.
You concocted it?
It must be more poisonous
than decaying vines.
Miss Feng.
To save you,
Young Master even used his
much-cherished
millennium-old snow lotus.
When you were unconscious, you puked
every time we fed you medicine.
-Zhong Li.
-Young Master had to feed you himself.
When did you become this talkative?
Your tongue can use some snipping.
I will take my leave now.
I'll drink it on my own.
No need to be sanctimonious.
Not many get to be fed medicine by me.
Does
the renowned Bai Fengxi
dislike bitter medicine?
♪Like the dissipating fog,
you become clearer♪
♪Like the hawk that soars freely,
you reject the shackles♪
♪Your white silk is as light as feather
and yet it moves my heart♪
♪Ripples come at me
but I don't want to dodge♪
♪Wind is just the outline of the cloud♪
♪Black is the lock of the White♪
♪Night is when the Day sleeps♪
♪You are a part of me♪
♪Right or wrong,
don't worry about the why♪
♪Pain or joy,
they are from our obsession♪
♪If some things cannot be taken apart♪
♪Then let's face
the uncertainty together♪
♪Let tears run dry♪
♪Let's stop in another place♪
♪Let love sever
all happiness and sadness♪
♪And pierce through
the vicissitude of life♪
♪With a merry start, don't worry
about a sorrowful end♪
♪A full moon will be more intertwined♪
♪If some things cannot be taken apart♪
♪Then let's face
the uncertainty together♪