The next show here is suitable
for audiences aged 13 and above.
May contain images, sounds or content...
that needs to carefully evaluated when viewing.
Audiences under the age of 13
should receive advice when watching.
Can we just be friends like before?
Friends my ass, Ai'Chin!
Do you mean friends
who hug each other...
kissing each other.
Play guitar and sing love song together.
Help me finish the food that I don't eat.
If you mean that kind of friends...
I don't want anymore!
Yu...
You and I...
can no longer go
back to the way it was.
Ai'Yu!
What's wrong with you?!
Where are you going?
Can you not go?
Let me go, Ai'Chin.
Am I doing the right thing?
Or, actually...
I have no no
right to be angry at him?
It hurts my head!
I packed all my things like this..
where am I going to stay?
I'm gonna call Ai'Zeemai
Hello?
What's up, Yu?
Hello, Zeemai. Are you at home?
I am.
Can I go see you?
I'm having some trouble.
Of course.
OK, see you at your house?
OK, see you.
Is it too little?
I'll add more.
Yu...
What kind of makeup is that?
Speak for yourself.
Why is your face like that?
I'll tell you later.
Let's get inside first.
What makeup is that?
Your makeup look like a singer.
- Is it that bad?
- Yes.
Tell me.
Don't just sit there.
I like Ai'Chin.
And I...
OK. I know everything now.
No need to continue.
You do?
I can tell for some time now.
Yes, that's what it is.
What should I do now?
Seriously, you shouldn't
run away like this.
Talk to him clearly.
Think about it.
If you're angry at each other but
see each other at school everyday...
won't that makes you feel awkward?
Yeah, you're right.
I'll clear things up with him later.
Right now, I need to rest.
Last night, I didn't sleep.
OK.
Go rest,
I'm gonna go wash my face.
E'B, what's wrong?
You've been
upset for many days now.
I miss that guy.
He never think about calling me?
Go to him,
forcefully and not holding back.
Do you think it's a good idea?
Absolutely. Trust me, you can do it.
Fight to get him.
Get a grip!
I will regain my pureness back.
Here you go.
Enjoy your meal.
What will you have?
Move away.
Move, I'm in a hurry. Move!
So, what are you
gonna do about that night?
Let's clear things up.
Don't you feel guilty whatsoever?
Again?!
OK.
I don't know.
Just a moment.
P'Tin.
I miss you.
Let's date.
Alright, wait here for a sec.
He'll be mine for sure.
He's be mine.
I've been lonely for so long.
Eat this and go home.
Again?!
Fine!
You wanna play it that way?
You'll see.
Miss customer.
P'Tin, are you really
not gonna date me?
Why is this again?
Your order is here.
P'Tin...
I miss you.
Let's date.
Wait just a sec.
Again?
Excuse me.
P'Tin, how are you gonna
be responsible for this baby?
Again?!
I can't take this anymore!
Tired from school today?
A little, you?
Not at all.
I'm tired about something else.
What is it?
Tired of missing you.
How sweet.
Are you this sweet to everyone?
No.
Just with you.
I believe you.
So...
are you going anywhere tomorrow?
I'm free tomorrow.
Why?
Let's go for a date?
OK.
Yes!
Then stop being cute.
Go to bed.
OK, see you tomorrow.
Good night.
Zeemai.
I've made up my mind.
I think I'm gonna go back.
You miss Chin?
No.
I just remember
that I paid for the rent.
It would be a
waste if I don't live there.
I'm leaving.
See you at school tomorrow, Yu.
You forgive me?
Yes. Forget about it.
Just let it pass.
As for...
about me liking you...
don't think about it too much.
I've made up my mind.
I won't have any
feeling for you anymore.
We'll be friends again.
Alright.
That's good.
You can date Tisa as normal.
I'm gonna take a shower, it's sticky.
P'Jed.
Did you wait long?
No.
What should we
have for lunch today?
Up to you.
Why so easy on me?
If you think so, then invite me
for dinner some other times.
But...
I eat a lot, can you handle that?
Absolutely.
So, shall we go lunch?
Yes.
That restaurant?
Sure.
That one?
Did you have fun today?
I had so much today.
Thank you so much.
So...
what day will be our next date?
Next date...
What day do you mean?
The day we'll be boyfriends.
You're such sweet talker, P'Jed.
[ In Thai, smooth tongue is said as "bpahk
wahn" which translated as "sweet mouth" ]
It really is sweet.
I'm leaving.
Let me know when you're home.
Are you asleep?
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
Really?
Yes.
Then, give me your hand.
I want to give you something.
It's my turn to clean the table today.
But I'm tired.
Please do it for me?
That cute expression again.
Do you think I'm gonna fall for that?
Sure thing, Zo. I'll do it for you.
Then, I'm counting on you.
He doesn't love me and
on top of that, he tricked me.
Such a terrible guy.
But I'll do it for you.
L.
I have something to give you today.
Really? What is it?
Close your eyes.
You can open them now.
Where is it?
It's this handsome
face that I want you to see.
Is this it?
Handsome but weird.
I already know you're handsome.
Thank you, God.
For giving me this handsome face.
Do you like this then?
I knew you have
something for me for sure.
This. Do you like it?
If you like it, you can photo of it.
Is this it?
OK, I'll take a photo of it.
Again?
- Let's go, Zo.
- Where?
- Just go.
- Have you taken the photo?
Let's just go from here.
- You can keep the photo.
- Let's just go, Zo.
Yu.
How are you?
I'm OK, I'm good.
So, why are you walking alone?
It's Ai'Jed's turn
to clean the classroom.
And Ai'Zeemai clean the
classroom in Ai'Zo's place.
So, have you eaten?
No yet, I'm about to.
Me too.
You don't have anything to do?
No, I'm free.
Then let's go eat together.
Eat together?
Well...
Aside from rice and alcohol...
what else do you want to eat?
You're making
that shocked face again.
Your shocked face is kinda funny.
Let's just go.
Shall we sit here?
It's good.
What?
It's just the chicken.
It's true.
What class you'll
have in the afternoon?
English class.
The teacher is very good,
I like him very much.
Chin, why did you took my veggies?
I eat them.
Sorry.
I want that.
Give it back, I want it.
OK, alright.
Pat.
I'll feed you.
You're not eating?
Yes.
Tisa.
You're still hungry yet?
I'll feed you.
What mood are you in now?
It's good.
Another bite.
How's it?
Chin, do it properly.
It's full in your mouth.
Pat, I'm sorry.
Are you alright?
Tisa, I'm sorry.
Do I look that hungry?
It's alright.
I'm OK.
Sorry.
Seeing you're feeding me that much...
you don't have much left for you.
Take mine.
I want this.
Can I?
Of course.
I'll give them all to you.
Tisa, where are you going?
I'm not telling.
Wait for me.
More?
No more, it's enough.
Zeemai.
Why are you doing this in Ai'Zo's place.
I don't see any problem with it.
Zo has an errand to do.
Don't you think
about liking someone else?
How can we change our heart
to love someone else that easy?
But I think you need to
start changing yourself first.
I don't think Ai'Zo will take
any interest with you looking like this.
Why?
What's wrong with my looks?
It's old-fashion, dull and plain.
Like a plain soup.
Ohm
Sawasdee krub, today we'll...
we're shooting the series...
I mean take a photo for posters.
Yes, yes
Let's go again.
Sawasdee krub, we're going to
take photos for the series posters.
Acting like everything never happened
Right now, they're...
This is Mr. Pairat, the photographer.
Sawasdee krub.
Oat
How's today?
I'm very nervous.
It's my first job that I have taken.
It's Oat's first filming series
I'll do my best.
Dong
Sawasdee krub,
I'm here to support N'Ohm.
How are you feeling?
Well, kinda scared.
Because it will be our turn next.
N'Ohm, all the best.
Good.
Look at each others' eyes.
Smile and make it like...
You look down to him.
Smile. 1, 2...
Move closer to him.
Sawasdee krub.
How's today.
What will you do today?
We'll be taking photos.
Today, we're changing the
environment to the studio.
What is your name?
I'm Tee.
Tee, Sawasdee krub.
What will be shooting?
Is it your first time?
Yes, first time with Cloth Lab.
1, 2, 3. Look here.
1, 2... Smile.
OK, 1, 2, 3.
Do it like... yes.
Pie
Thank you.
Tensed?
Come take a photo unexpectedly!
Yes.
The camera is here.
Pray for blessing before performing !
I'm so nervous.
Shy?
Very shy.
First time?
It's not like shooting photo that day.
So I'm bit scared.
Start.
1, 2, start.
Be natural and touch his nose.
1, 2...
Cloth Lab Entertainment proudly present...
the behind the scenes of poster
photo and new photoshoots...
for the stars of Restart(ed)
or Can I Love Again.
What's the atmosphere like?
If you're ready, let's take a look.
Sawasdee krub,
welcome to the filming site.
Today, we're going to take a
collection of photos of Restart(ed) actors.
Or "Can I Love Again".
There are clothes that
we designed ourselves.
It's to be used in the
series and for the actors.
Please stay tune.
These outfits are so
cute and suitable for the kids.
Please submit your work
Sawasdee krub.
How's the concept today?
Today's good
because it's a new concept.
It's like a real simulation scene, it's great.
Please stay tune if you want to
know how the photo session is.
How are you preparing for today?
I watched a lot of cartoons.
I'm very well prepared.
See you later.
Sawasdee krub.
How's today? What are you
doing with these 3 different styles?
We're doing photo modeling.
Photo modeling.
That's it?
Photo modeling
and photos for posters.
That's right.
Please watch our work,
we guarantee you'll be happy with it.
Thank you so much, bye.
How did it feel to shoot
a poster for the first time?
Yes, it's very nervous the first time.
Look forward to what role
I'll be playing. You have to wait.
What do you think
with the actors' poster shooting.
Watch more, follow channel Cloth Lab
Entertainment and see you next week.