The next show here is suitable
for audiences aged 13 and above.
May contain images, sounds or content...
that needs to carefully evaluated when viewing.
Audiences under the age of 13
should receive advice when watching.
Zeemai.
[Previous Episode]
If it's not me...
don't go out for dinner with anyone, OK?
I should be the one thanking you...
for watching movie with me tonight.
I'm going up to my dorm now.
See you at school tomorrow.
Get home safely.
You two are close.
It's not weird for me
to be close with anyone.
Why are you come back so late?
We were watching movie.
You can watch it here.
- It's not the same.
- It's same.
- It's not.
- It is.
I'm not arguing anymore.
Have you eaten?
Yes.
I had dinner with...
Tisa.
Are you going somewhere this Saturday?
This Saturday...
No.
Are you asking to go somewhere?
Wanna sleep in my place?
What's that, P'Jed?
Sleep at your place?
That's alright, forget it. I was kidding.
No.
I can go.
But you have to ask
permission from my mom first.
Do I have to ask her?
Because you want a
"daughter" to sleep at your place...
so you have ask her mom.
If you can get her permission...
I'll hug you all night.
Really?
Later...
I'll cook fried chicken with
basil that you like. Do you want it?
OK.
You're home early.
I finished my assignment early and had
nothing else to do, so I came home early.
I bought some drinks, want some?
Thanks. Just put them there,
I'll drink later.
So...
did you went out with Tisa today?
No, she...
was mad at me for some reason.
What about you and Pat?
The usual.
Do you like him?
Why do you ask?
I'm your friend.
Can't I ask?
Friends doesn't need to know
everything about each other, right?
I want to know.
You can't even tell me that, I guess.
There nothing between us,
why would you want to know?
You know in your heart...
what you're feeling, right?
I don't have any feelings for you.
Go and shower already.
I leave them here.
Do you have to take this many?
E'Jeng.
Finished?
My shoulder is about to break.
Hurry up.
E'Wa.
You're not done yet?
It's too high, I'm trying here.
Steady, dude.
Come, let me help.
You're moving again.
Got it.
All these?
Thanks, dude. I've waited for
you for so long. Where were you?
Sorry, I just came
back from the restroom.
I bought some sticker
from my neighborhood.
Can I paste them on you?
Go ahead.
Do you like it?
Are you two acting in
a lakorn for me to watch?
Dude, hurry up.
I'm hungry.
I'm done.
Do you want to go
to the topokki restaurant?
No.
I don't want to see P'Tin.
You're bickering with him again?
No.
Which restaurant you want to go then?
The Cafe.
The one that says "Hungry" in front.
Are you going to peek
at the handsome guy again?
After some guys again.
You're not?
E'B, stand still.
If I text him first, I lose.
It'll ruin my reputation.
It was just a one night stand.
Why am I thinking about it?
I didn't feel like this before.
Handsome,
can you take a photo of me?
1, 2...
One more.
Did you get it?
What are you doing, wild kid?
What's it to you?
How can you talk
to your husband that way?
What husband? You're delusional.
Hey, be nice.
I went out of my way
to chat with you here.
But I don't want to chat with you.
Come and see me
at 7 AM on Saturday.
Why do I have to go?
Just do what I said.
Ano.
What?
When I'm here alone with you...
I just realized that the first time
I met you, you had a silly face.
But I'm handsome now.
Who says that?
Many people.
By the way, Ano.
I have something to tell  you.
What is it?
I've decided...
to be serious with that guy.
The other day,
when I went on date with him...
I've agreed to be his boyfriend.
I just want you to
be the first to know.
Good.
No!
Where are you going?
What's the matter with him?
Zeemai.
What's wrong with your ear?
It's nothing.
For real.
Is it hurt?
A little.
Hey, Pat.
What's up?
Have a sit.
Shall we start the discussion?
Yeah, good idea.
Are you sure?
With an outsider with us?
Pat is with me.
Why can't he join?
I'm just asking.
Let's start the discussion.
Ai'U.
Those two are going to fight now.
Will I have to get involved?
U...
they're not gonna
beat up each other, right?
Come now, guys.
Do your assignment.
Pat, help me and check this out.
Do you think this looks good?
Do your think it's all correct?
Let me have a look.
They're all good.
You're good.
You're very good indeed.
Dude.
Do I have anything else to do?
I don't think so.
Do you have an errand to do?
I'm going to have lunch with Pat.
I haven't eaten yet.
Go ahead.
Then, shall we end it here today?
We'll continue next time.
Yeah, good idea.
Sure thing.
Chin, let's go.
Pat, let's go eat.
See you.
I'm leaving now, see you.
I'm going.
Don't follow me.
Chin.
Chin!
What should we eat today?
Well, anything.
Up to you.
What were you thinking about earlier?
It's about the assignment.
It's nothing.
Assignment?
Chin.
Do you still wants to date me?
What's wrong?
Do you realized that you've been
taking less and less interest about me?
I think it's the still as usual.
As usual?
You're interested
about U as usual.
Not about me.
Can you stop
mentioning about U?
Why? I want to say it.
U, U, U, U!
I said stop!
Excuse me.
Go eat by yourself.
U.
I'm not making
you uncomfortable, right?
No.
Why do you think that?
Well...
It's about Chin.
You don't have to think too much.
I don't have any
feelings for Chin anymore.
You know, right?
About how I feel for you.
I do.
You're not being with me...
to forget about Chin, right?
No.
I'm easy to forget things.
Do I even have a chance?
If you want me to answer it now...
I probably can't.
Let's take it slowly.
Sure.
I can wait.
We'll slowly get to know each other.
I'm Jed.
Jed Nipattamthai
I'm here to ask your permission...
to take your
"daughter" out for the night.
How many days?
Well...
For a start, it'll be for a day.
In the future, it might be more.
What is your relationship with Wa?
I'm...
I'm his boyfriend for a week now.
What day will he go?
This Saturday.
Anwa.
I send you to school to learn.
But you bring home a husband?
And have a family.
Of course.
I'm counting on
you to take care of him.
I'll entrust him to you for a day.
Thank you!
Mom, thank you.
Thank you, Mom.
Ja.
Get home safely, P'Jed.
Of course.
See you this Saturday, little one.
I'll pack my things tonight, OK?
Absolutely.
I'll let you know when I'm home.
OK.
Bye.
U.
What is it?
Can I ask for something of you?
I'm tired.
Can I hug you?
I don't think that's a good idea.
Why?
It's just a hug.
No reason.
But I think it's better not, trust me.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
Did you had a fight with Tisa?
Yeah.
It's gonna be alright,
don't be stressed.
Things will get better.
Yeah, I'm not stress about it.
But...
you're really not gonna let me hug you?
No!
Are you free today?
Yeah, why?
I want to ask you to a dinner.
Wanna go?
You're gonna have dinner with Tisa...
that you ask me instead?
Well...
I want to eat with you.
Can't I?
You come to have dinner with me
only when you got in a fight with her?
Come now.
You're free, right?
OK, see you in the evening.
It's already 7 AM.
Why isn't he's here yet?
Cruel P'Tin
If I said to him to stop this,
will he still pestering me?
Why isn't he pick up?
OK, I'm here.
You're late.
I just got back from handing in
my assignment to the professor.
You're late, so it's your treat.
Alright, sure Mom.
Alright, Dad.
What are you smiling? Let's go.
Where are you taking me?
Come now, just follow me.
I'm hungry again, P'Jed.
Then, I'll go get
some strawberries for you.
You can watch the TV while waiting.
OK.
Wa.
Take it.
Thank you.
What are you watching?
A lakorn.
It's all the same thing.
Look, I've changed into
so many channels already.
They're all like, an auntie
came to the house or an office.
The cleaners are there
sweeping and mopping the floor.
Then suddenly something
very dramatic happened.
Then she tells everybody,
"I'm the president of the company".
It's been 3 dramas and they're all like this.
Do you have any other
drama recommendations?
We can guess the plot off all of them.
It should be changed like...
something more chaotic and twisting.
It'd be more interesting.
You think so too, right?
Hello?
Hello, Jed.
Are you with Chin?
I don't know where he is.
I haven't seen him since the noon.
OK, thank you.
Zeemai, are you with Chin?
No.
I haven't seen him since noon.
OK, thank you.
Can you wait for me?
I'll be back ASAP.
Sure thing.
I'll wait here.
Why do you call me?
Where were you?
I was having dinner with U.
Dinner with U?
Then why didn't you pick up your phone?
I didn't hear my phone rings.
You didn't hear...
or pretend not to hear it, I wonder?
So...
why do you call me here?
If I'm not in a fight with my dad,
you wouldn't come, right?
Chin.
Don't leave me.
Don't leave me like this again.
I promise...
that I won't be demanding again.
U.. what are you doing?
Pat
U
Pat...
Pat
U... what are you doing?
Can you wait for me?
I'll be back ASAP.
U?
Let's go home.
Why did you went there?
I went for dinner.
Alone?
With a friend.
A friend who often
makes me wait.
A friend who
always left me alone.
A friend who always makes me sad.
Forget it.
Give me that. I'll dry your hair.
U?
Are you alright?
You're burning up.
Chin.
Thank you for
dropping me off.
Get home safely.
Hello, U. Are you still there?
U is in my room.
Who are you?
Let me speak to U.
I'm Pat.
U is sick.
Let him wait there.
I'll come and pick him up.
I don't think so.
When he wakes up...
I'll send him home myself.
Also...
don't do that to U again.
If you do...
I won't let it slide.
A guy like you?
What can you do to me?
You'll see.
I...
will take U from you.
You coward.
Damn it!