I'll send the foreign guns
to Fort Udon Kampanat
to defend against those Srichai bandits.
I'm assigning you
to lead the transport of them.
Khun Pra Saming,
his sword was covered with poison.
They're behind that symbol.
I'm going to blow up everything in here,
including your life,
and mine.
Hey!
Khun Aek!
Kamduang.
Light it, Dear.
Don't worry about me.
I was so focused
on having you protect Khun Aek,
that I forgot you could be in danger too.
Your life matters more.
Let's split up and search for them.
I'll fight by your side to the very end.
Khun Aek!
Kamduang!
Come out!
No matter what,
you can't escape from me.
Your sword
can't harm my invincibility spell.
Lucky me, I found a good charm.
It must be from a local woman.
Today is your unlucky day,
Srichai.
You're using that filthy thing on me?
It fits
a savage bandit like you perfectly.
Wrong move.
I've already found a way
to protect against that trick, idiot.
What are you trying to do?
I know you've got invincibility.
And I know your weakness
lies in your nine orifices.
You!
Kamduang, now!
Kamduang!
Dear!
Dear.
Freeze!
If there is a next life,
I pray we are truly husband and wife,
with no deceit or trickery.
Yes.
If there is a next life,
may we stay side by side forever.
Are you done with your sweet nothings?
Don't even dream of reincarnation,
because your souls
will belong to me as eternal slaves!
Ohm… Release.
Dear, Dad's here to save us.
What the hell is that?
Shaman Dum,
what is it?
The Chakra of Divine Flame.
The most fearsome sacred weapon.
Can you fight it?
Impossible.
I've never seen anything like this.
I think we should run.
Let's go.
Thank you, Dad.
If you hadn't come, we'd both be dead.
Same here.
Uncle Yod, you saved me again.
Luckily, I ran into
Khun Pra Saming and Ping,
so I made it in time.
What kind of sword is this?
It's the Seven-Metal Sacred Sword.
It's deadly.
It's the only thing that can fight
the Chakra of Divine Flame.
Look,
it even chipped the chakra.
Chakra of Divine Flame…
I've never heard of it before.
It's one of the rarest sacred items.
Once every thousand years,
it emerges from the volcanic core.
When cooled, it becomes the hardest
and sharpest element.
I've never seen you use it, Dad.
The Chakra of Divine Flame
is only used in real emergencies.
It's powerful, hard to control,
a sacred weapon worthy of a kingdom.
Anyone who owns one keeps it secret.
It's too dangerous.
Even without saying, I can guess.
Using the chakra
must take immense power.
It nearly drained me completely.
I'm too old now.
It may be time to pass it on…
maybe to Kamduang
or you, Khun Aek.
If you'll excuse me,
I must return to Thung Yai City
to report to Khun Pra Saming.
Dad, let's escort my dear,
I mean,
Khun Aek.
I'm afraid Bandit Srichai
might come back to ambush him.
- Yod!
- Teacher!
Are you alright?
You've used too much power.
Let's rest at Khun Aek's house first.
That'd be good.
Would you mind
if I stay at your place?
I'd be honored.
Teacher,
have a sip of water.
It'll help you regain strength.
Slowly, Teacher.
Let's go.
Are you alright, Dad?
Yes.
Are you okay?
Dad.
This is strange.
Why did he suddenly fall ill?
Was it because of using
the Chakra of Divine Flame, Uncle Yoy?
That's just how illness is.
It can strike anytime.
Yip. Yip.
Yes, sir?
Go prepare a room for Uncle Yod.
Yes, sir.
Teacher,
you must be exhausted.
Please have a sip of water.
I'm going to see Khun Pra Saming
at the City Hall.
You stay here and look after your father.
But you must be tired too, Dear.
Why not rest a bit before you go?
Just hearing you call me "dear"
makes me feel fully recharged.
Kamduang.
You shameless woman!
Yeesoon.
Please go, Dear.
I'll handle things here.
Khun Aek, I'm not talking to her.
I want you to tell her clearly
that you love me
and tell her to leave.
I can't do that, because--
Please go, Dear.
Khun Pra Saming must be waiting.
Don't worry.
I'll speak with her nicely.
Khun Aek.
What are you doing? Let go!
I said I'd talk nicely.
But honestly,
I really want to punch you in the face.
Go ahead and try.
I'll have the patrols put you in jail.
You lied to me.
You said you slept with him.
So what?
It's none of your business.
I loved him first.
You came later and stole him from me.
How could I ever be nice with you?
Another lie.
What lie?
That I stole him from you.
The truth is…
he never cared about you at all.
Kamduang!
Go on, try me.
But I'll tell you now.
I hate liars the most.
If you slap me,
I'll beat your face until
it's ruined for the rest of your life.
Kamduang!
Here's what we'll do.
Wait until Khun Aek returns.
Let's ask him directly.
If he says he loves you
and I stole him, I'll leave on my own.
But if he says he doesn't care for you,
you leave. Deal?
No!
No matter what he says,
I will be his only wife.
Sir, Khun Aek requests an audience.
Let him in.
Yes, Sir.
This way, Sir.
What is this?
What's going on here?
Please don't resist, Sir.
You've got some nerve coming back here.
Do you take me for a fool?
What have I done wrong, Sir?
You gave the foreign guns
to Bandit Srichai.
You are a traitor.
You didn't expect
we'd unmask you so quickly, did you?
What are you talking about?
I don't understand.
Where are the guns?
I came to report
that they were stolen
by Bandit Srichai.
How could they steal them
when the time and route were classified?
I don't know.
But they used dark magic.
Do you have a witness?
Only I survived.
Enough lies, Khun Aek!
You shameless liar!
I'm telling the truth.
You insolent traitor!
I'll show you what the real truth is.
Bring him in.
This morning, someone
tried to steal the foreign bullets.
I caught him.
S
He's one of Srichai's men.
How did you know where the bullets were?
Khun Aek told me.
When?
Yesterday.
He delivered the guns as agreed.
Bandit Srichai wanted more bullets,
so Khun Aek told us where they were
stored. I went to take them.
You dare lie?
Ask him yourself
if it's true.
Take this scum to jail.
Khun Pra Saming, he framed me.
So much for your cleverness.
Now that you got caught,
is that the best excuse you've got?
I'm not lying.
That's not the truth.
Take Khun Aek to prison.
Khun Pra Saming, I'm telling the truth.
Someone's framing me!
Please listen to me! Khun Pra Saming!
Yeesoon.
Did you hear?
What's happened, Mother?
Khun Aek has been arrested for treason.
He's been taken to prison.
Prison?
What? Khun Aek is a traitor?
Khun Aek is now a disgrace.
Being near him will only bring trouble.
So what?
You want me to end
the relationship with him again?
I don't know what to tell you.
You must think clearly,
what's worth it and what's not.
He's a traitor.
He doesn't just lose title and land.
His house,
fields, wealth, everything will be seized.
Then…
he will have nothing left?
That's not all.
If Khun Pra Saming is enraged,
he may order execution
for seven generations.
And what I fear most is…
that we'll be implicated too.
Has that traitor still not woken up?
Not yet, Sir.
Awake now,
Khun Aek Itthirit?
I trusted you.
Sergeant Boonchai, wait outside.
I'll interrogate Khun Aek myself.
Yes, Sir.
If you're going to execute me, so be it.
But please,
spare my father.
This one's going to be a bit tough.
Actually,
this case is full of suspicious details.
Does that mean…?
Yes.
Didn't I tell you before
that I trust you?
Yes, Sir.
But I had to say this
in case you got upset
that I punished you.
So all this has been an act?
Exactly.
The bait is set.
We're just waiting
for the true culprit to bite.
We just don't know when.
Then we must set a trap, lure them in,
and catch them when they slip up.
You can't go in.
I said, you can't go in!
Move aside, Sergeant,
or don't say I didn't warn you.
It's Kamduang.
This is getting messy. I'll handle it.
What's the meaning of this?
You can't go in!
Let go! If Kamduang can go in,
why can't I? Move aside!
Hey!
This is a government office!
This isn't a place
where just anyone can barge in.
Kamduang came in first, she speaks first.
Let me speak first.
I came to make it clear
there is nothing
between Khun Aek Itthirit and me.
People keep misunderstanding us,
so I had to come clarify myself.
Let me emphasize again.
There's no relationship
between Khun Aek and me.
We're merely acquaintances.
But this morning,
you brought me breakfast.
You must be mistaken.
There's nothing between us.
And what about you, Kamduang?
What do you have to say?
I have nothing to say.
I came to confront you, Khun Pra Saming.
Right now, I'm the acting governor.
If you insult me, you'll be punished.
I'll gladly take the punishment.
Khun Aek has worked
tirelessly for Thung Yai City
and lived up to his noble position.
He's loyal, dedicated,
risking life for this land.
And you, as his superior,
instead of honoring him, you disgrace him.
You are an unfit governor.
Kamduang, that's enough.
No, I won't stop.
Nothing can stop me now.
If you have any conscience left,
release him now.
I can't just release him.
He's accused of treason.
If you don't release him,
then die!
- Stop.
- Stop, Kamduang.
I said stop.
Hand over the knife.
Hand it over.
Sergeant.
You're reckless, Kamduang.
Even if you're his wife,
you didn't need to go that far.
You're mistaken.
Mistaken how?
I'm not doing this as his wife.
I do it as the one who stands beside him.
I've seen that
he always think about this city.
I've seen his struggles with my own eyes.
He's a loyal servant to this land.
I vouch for him with my life.
If you won't let him go,
then take my head along with his.
Kamduang,
go home. Please, listen to me.
Dear,
I made a vow.
If you die, I'll die with you.
Interrogating traitors
is brutal.
Are you sure
you want to go down with him?
Yes.
Because the truth is the truth.
He is a good man.
But you are the unworthy governor.
Watch your mouth.
Insulting the governor
is punishable by death.
You only became governor
because of your father.
Left on your own,
you couldn't even herd buffalo.
Say one more word--
You bone-headed, shoe-faced, mangy mutt,
rotten elephant, worthless trash,
flea-ridden gutter rat!
Kamduang!
You insolent wench!
I've got nothing to do with this.
I'm leaving now!
Sir!
Kamduang!
Take these two and behead them!
Yes, Sir.
Yod. Yod.
Why are your nails purple?
Looks like you've been poisoned.
What poison?
Don't just say things, Uncle Yoy.
Yod.
Thank you very much.
My informant says
Khun Pra Saming
has ordered the execution
of Khun Aek and Kamduang.
Is that true?
Why so sudden?
Khun Pra Saming
and Khun Aek are close friends.
I can't believe
he'd issue that order so easily.
That Kamduang woman stormed the city hall,
shouted obscenities,
and even drop-kicked Khun Pra Saming.
So,
if that's not a death sentence,
I don't know what is.
Too bad
I didn't get to see
Khun Aek die with my own eyes.
Either way, he's dead.
You've won.
Finally, the day has come.
In that case, let's not wait any longer.
Let's just get the money and run.
They've made a move?
Yes, Sir.
The father and son
dug up what they had hidden,
packed their things,
and are preparing to leave town.
Thank you, Ping.
I'm just doing my duty, Sir.
Where are you going, Khun Pra Mek,
Khun Men?
None of your business.
Who says it's not?
My business is stopping you.
What do you mean?
You two are under arrest.
And what exactly
are we being arrested for?
Come with me. You'll find out soon enough.
My son and I were just visiting relatives.
I hope you have a good reason
for doing this.
Even if it's by city order.
Don't worry.
I wouldn't arrest you on a whim.
Say what you confessed.
Khun Men hired me to spy.
If there was any movement of foreign guns,
I was to report it immediately.
Where are the guns being taken to?
To Fort Udon Kampanat, Sir.
Thank you.
Say what you confessed.
Khun Men and Bandit Srichai
sent me into the city
to stage a fake robbery
and pin it on Khun Aek.
Weren't you afraid of dying?
Khun Men promised I'd only be jailed.
Once Bandit Srichai seized the city,
I'd be released
and paid 20 taels.
What a disgusting lie.
I'm a noble of Thung Yai City.
Why would I conspire with bandits
to betray my own city?
Maybe for this.
S
This belonged to Praya Jade,
our former governor
killed by Bandit Srichai
over ten years ago.
How did it end up with you?
I didn't know.
Someone sold it to me.
I never checked where it came from.
S
And these gold bars?
They bear the city seal.
These can't be legally traded.
What's your excuse?
Khun Men Maenmueang.
Pra Mek Sawan Phansaeng.
Are you both still denying it?
The evidence is clear.
Fine. Yes.
I conspired with Bandit Srichai.
At least I got the satisfaction
of seeing you
kill your beloved friend Khun Aek.
Without Khun Aek,
you would never beat Bandit Srichai.
Satisfaction?
Why do you hate Khun Aek so much?
I just hate his face.
You're alive?
I don't know why you hate me.
But if you hate me,
attack me.
Why destroy the whole city?
Khun Aek.
You all set me up!
Damn you!
Good deeds bring good.
Evil deeds bring ruin.
Blame yourself, Khun Men.
Khun Men!
I apologize
for my temper, my rudeness,
and for insulting you so badly.
Don't worry.
I forgive you.
Besides, your drop-kick
actually fit my plan perfectly.
I have work to do.
Make yourselves at home.
- Yes, Sir.
At first, I thought you'd be mad
I pretended to be punished.
Of course I was!
And you let me act like a lunatic
without a word.
I'm sorry, Kamduang.
It's okay.
Once I knew you were safe,
I was just happy.
I'm lucky to have you as my wife.
I believe now
that fate exists.
There you go again, Khun Aek Itthirit.
The husband and wife thing
was just an excuse
so you could finish your gun mission.
What's fate got to do with it?
What if we became
husband and wife for real?
What did
you just say?
When we return home,
I plan to ask Uncle Yod for your hand.
Kamduang!
What happened to me?
You fainted.
I remember now.
I had a strange dream…
that you were going to propose to me.
It wasn't a dream.
It's true.
I want you to be my wife.
It's a dream. It's just a dream.
Ah.
It can't be real.
This isn't real.
It is.
It is real.
How can it be,
when I've never once heard
the word "love" from you?
Because before,
I didn't know my own heart.
But now I know
that you're the only one in it.
Kamduang,
I…
Khun Aek, sir!
Come in.
Sir, Madam.
What is it, Yip?
It's Sir Yod…
Yod!
- Dad!
- Vet Yoy.
- What's happened?
- What's wrong with him?
His heart stopped beating.
Dad!
But then it started beating again,
very faintly.
Why is he like this?
I don't know.
He showed no signs beforehand.
I'll go fetch the royal physician.
This is a strange case.
I've never seen anything like it.
Could it be something other than illness?
What do you mean?
I'll go summon the monk.
This isn't a case
of possession.
But I can't say what disease it is either.
What should we do now, Dear?
Stay calm.
As long as Uncle Yod still breathes,
we don't give up.
There must be a way.
There are skilled healers
like Nun Nok from Wat Tai Koh,
or Master Saeng, the miracle doctor.
As for black magic,
it's possible that Yod
was affected by a wandering spirit
and struck by dark magic.
You'll need to consult someone
knowledgeable in that field.
Yes, venerable.
I shall take my leave.
I'll see you out.
Dad…
please don't leave me.
Don't worry.
I'll send people to find the best experts.
I believe someone will be able to help.
Thank you so much, Dear.
Keep your spirits up.
Don't give in.
Kamduang,
how is Uncle Yod doing?
Dad is gone…
I'm so sorry.
Don't worry.
I loved
and respected Uncle Yod
like my own father.
I'll take care of everything
for him the best I can.
But you must stay strong,
so he can leave without worry.
Uncle Yod,
I pray that…
Uncle Yod is still breathing,
but just barely.
You're right.
He's still breathing, Uncle Yoy.
I swear, this morning,
he had no breath at all.
It happened last night too.
Yes.
He stopped breathing,
then slowly started again.
What exactly is happening to him?
Could it be the poison
of the Sleeping Bug?
Sleeping Bug poison?
Kham…
Where's Kham?
That's right.
I haven't seen Kham at all.
Yes,
he disappeared yesterday.
Kham!
Sleeping Bug poison
comes from a mysterious hill tribe.
Almost no one knows it.
It's tasteless, colorless, odorless.
It causes the victim
to linger between life and death,
sometimes breathing, sometimes not.
After two or three days,
they die for real.
Why do you suspect Kham?
Kham's mother was from that tribe.
He's the only one
who knows about that poison.
But why would Kham poison my father?
He had a reason.
What reason?
What did my father do
to deserve that kind of hate?
It's because of me?
Chakra of Divine Flame…
I've never heard of it before.
It's one of the rarest sacred items.
I'm too old now.
It may be time to pass it on…
maybe to Kamduang
or you, Khun Aek.
That's what Yod said.
And that's why Kham bears such hatred.
Where are you going?
To find Kham.
He's the only one who knows
about the Sleeping Bug poison.
He likely didn't make it out before
the city gates closed yesterday evening.
He's probably still here.
- Open the city gate.
- Yes, sir.
Stop!
Close the gate.
I'm here to arrest a criminal.
Is this an order from you or the governor?
My order.
Only the governor can give that command.
You can't. It's against the rules.
Do as I say.
If anything happens,
I'll take full responsibility.
But, Sir, the punishment
is to be flogged 100 times.
I accept that.
But I cannot let the criminal escape.
Close the gate.
Damn it!
You bastard, Khun Aek.
Yeesoon!
I just heard news about Aek from
the market and rushed here to tell you.
Is it about Khun Aek being executed?
That's not the truth.
Then what is the truth?
All those claims about him
committing treason
was a ploy to lure out the real criminal.
Now he's receiving honor
and might even be promoted to Praya.
So I made the wrong decision again?
I'm so sorry.
It's because of me
that you ended up like this.
Because of what happened
between me and Kamduang,
Kham was angry at you.
Without me,
this wouldn't have happened.
I will find Kham
and bring him back to lift the poison.
I hope you forgive him.
And after that,
I'll ask you,
Kham,
and Kamduang
to return to the way you lived
before you knew me.
I'll make that happen
before it's too late.
Kham!
Hey! Stop!
That's the signal. They've found Kham.
I'm going after him.
Yes, sir.
Uncle Yoy,
where is he going in such a rush?
To find Kham.
What?
Why didn't he tell me?
Or…
Or what?
Or is he going to kill Kham?
Why would you think that?
He looked stressed.
I think he's stressed
because he blames himself
for what happened to your father.
What do you mean?
I overheard him talking to Yod.
He feels guilty
and thinks it's his fault
your father is gravely ill.
Kham's hiding in the temple.
I've assigned men to keep watch.
I didn't want to alarm the public.
Good.
I'll go find him myself.
If anyone sees him, do not harm him.
Understood?
Yes, Sir.
Wait, Dear.
Kamduang?
I know what you're trying to do.
You want my father and Kham to reconcile,
so Dad will give me to Kham.
Right?
Yes.
What do you take me for?
Something to be given away so easily?
I don't intend to force you.
If you don't want to go, I won't make you.
You blame yourself
for Dad's poisoning.
Yes, it's my fault.
You're underestimating my father's heart.
He loved and respected you genuinely.
That's why he gave you the sacred item,
to protect righteous men like you.
It's not your fault.
Kham is jealous
because of his own greed.
Why must you blame yourself?
You always stand for justice for others.
You should give yourself
that same justice too.
I'll capture Kham alive
and make him reveal the antidote.
And if he refuses to talk,
what will you do?
Then I'll have to be firm.
And what if he agrees,
but only if I become his wife?
Would you be willing?
If not?
Then I'll still be firm.
What if he forces you to choose
between the antidote and me?
What will you choose?
I won't choose.
I'll take both.
I don't really know Kham.
Do you think he'd truly change
and give us the antidote?
Right now,
I don't think I know him anymore.
Kamduang!
Kham!
Khun Aek.
You forced me to do this.
You stole that from Dad?
Yes.
Why is it with him?
Hey!
Give back the Chakra of Divine Flame.
Keep dreaming, Ping.
What's going on?
Something terrible
has happened at the city office.
That Bandit Srichai
shot a letter tied
to an arrow into the city.
That scoundrel!
We won't let him dictate terms.
Everyone agrees. We'll fight him.
I'll fight alongside you
to protect this land.
You must stay alive
and die after me and Khun Aek.
Spread out.
Open the city gates and burn it all down.
Yes!
Subtitle translation by: Panuwat Baikeawon