Besides Qianyuan Pill,
what else did she take?
One Kunling Pill,
one Hongma Pill, and two Wuling Pills,
one Xuanyuan Pill,
and one Tianqiong Pill.
Go inform Master.
Yes.
Miss.
You're awake.
Master.
Where is this?
Chongyang Temple on Mount Zhongnan.
Don't move.
You're poisoned.
You need proper rest.
In just one day,
you took
our 10-year refined pills.
Your body can't withstand it.
I'll help you neutralize these pills
and expel them.
Two more days of treatment,
and you'll recover.
Do you also want the evil sutra?
That's not an evil sutra.
The Nine Yin True Sutra
was created by Huang Chang,
a martial arts master.
I've heard it contains
not just techniques
but deep analyses
of the essence of martial arts.
It helps
ordinary martial artists improve
and helps gifted ones
progress leaps and bounds.
All your struggles
for it.
Is it really worth it?
Jialan.
You don't understand
what the Nine Yin True Sutra
means to us.
What does it mean?
It means supremacy,
unrivaled power,
untold wealth,
unshakable authority,
the power
transcending laws and morals,
and unrestrained dominance.
Taoists say
small temptations mislead,
while great ones corrupt.
Petty gains make people
abandon principles.
The Sutra is the biggest temptation
destroying humanity itself.
Jialan.
I won't force you
to tell me the location.
After the duel on Mount Hua,
whoever becomes champion,
I urge you to reveal
how to find the Sutra.
Only then
can you escape
this bloodshed.
Thank you, Master.
I understand.
(The Legend of Heroes)
=Duel on Mount Hua=
(Adapted from Jin Yong's novel,
The Legend of the Condor Heroes)
=The Five=
=Episode 5=
Jialan doesn't want
to see you.
But she hopes
you will
win the duel.
How is she?
She's recovering well.
Why?
What's your question?
For vengeance.
For 300
dead souls on Mount Baituo.
For dead innocents
in Shiyang Fort.
Satisfied?
In three days,
what will you do?
Defeat all challengers.
Claim ultimate victory.
No one
can confidently say something
like that.
Are you that certain?
For Feng Heng,
I must win.
True.
If we join forces,
we'll win for sure.
Why should I work with you?
I know you hate me for setting snakes.
But you said,
you need one chapter.
If Wang Chongyang,
Hong Qi,
or Emperor Duan gets the Sutra,
do you think any of them will
give you one chapter?
I will.
Now, all I have is my life.
Either I'll become the winner
or die on Mount Hua.
See you then.
I'll try to win
at any cost.
Yaoshi.
Will you
abandon our friendship?
Let go.
Take care.
Sect leader.
The coffin is loaded.
I'm leaving.
Don't delay.
You pacify
Elder Wu's family.
Give him a grand funeral.
Go now.
Yes.
Sect Leader.
Yesterday,
I made a mistake,
trusting a sorcerer
and misleading others.
Please
punish me.
Rise.
If you think so,
I'll be upset.
Do you think
I can't even
hear the truth,
and I hold grudges against you?
Elder Xu.
Tell our men
that I'll get the Nine Yin True Sutra
for our sect.
Yes.
Take care.
The duel will come in two days.
Should we join it?
I think I'll pass.
Gauge your ability realistically.
Can you defeat those
from Chongyang Temple?
Huang Yaoshi,
Master Wang,
Leader Hong,
and Emperor Duan,
we can't beat any of them.
But Ouyang Feng,
a guy from the Western Regions,
isn't particularly formidable.
I heard from a guy
in Chongyang Temple
that Ouyang Feng killed
one of Ming Cult's Guardians.
Impossible!
His martial arts can't be weak.
Your Majesty.
What's wrong?
I'm thinking about Qi.
What about him?
Well,
when we first met in the martial world,
we hit it off.
I never expected
that he'd become like this.
I think
I should persuade him.
I don't know much about his past.
Right now,
I don't think
he will listen to you.
If the Nine Yin True Sutra
falls
into the hands of Qi,
disaster will follow.
Given his current arrogance,
he'll become the world's target.
Many people will attack him.
He will be in grave danger.
Moreover,
given his current achievements,
he's already this domineering.
If he truly
masters the Nine Yin True Sutra,
I fear
he will cause greater calamities.
Stop worrying about him.
Anyway,
how confident are you
in the upcoming duel on Mount Hua
to claim victory?
Others' capabilities
remain unknown to me,
but regarding Hong Qi,
I hold no absolute certainty
of defeating him.
Previously,
at Junshan,
we once fought.
I lost to him.
All these years,
my skills have improved.
I'm sure
he has also improved.
Moreover,
his 18 Dragon-Subduing Palms
have grown better,
shocking the martial world.
Don't be pessimistic
before the duel.
Be confident.
If you secure the Sutra
at the duel on Mount Hua,
fulfilling your ambition,
could you truly
abdicate the throne
and wander the martial world?
The throne
has never
been what I want.
Good.
I will
roam the martial world with you.
And we are
a gallant couple.
Emperor Duan. It's cold.
I brought you another quilt.
Leave it there.
Good night.
Senior.
Do you think our Master
looked for the Sutra
across the martial world these months
only
to safeguard it
for the martial world?
Anyway, obtain it first.
Then,
our Master decides
whether
to study it
or not.
Outrageous!
Who gave you the guts
to slander our Master?
- Please
- punish me.
Leave!
- Yes.
Master.
Forgive them.
They...
Regarding the Nine Yin True Sutra,
every word and deed
becomes suspect to others.
Even blood kin
and disciples face suspicion,
so I cannot blame strangers
for questioning me.
Master.
We just moved in.
It's quite humble.
Well...
It's alright.
I don't mind.
Master,
how does the Ming Cult
have unique martial arts?
The 18 Dragon-Subduing Palms
are remarkable.
It's a secret technique.
How could he replicate it
with precision?
So indistinguishable.
Legends tell of a master from Tubo
from years past
who knew a unique skill,
the Xiaowuxiang Technique.
Its practitioner can
mimic any martial technique,
replicating its form perfectly.
The strong masters
may even defeat opponents
with mimic moves.
I see.
It is
such a marvelous technique.
But that person always
acted weird.
No one knows
what's behind him.
Master, good night.
I'm leaving.
(Those who know me know my sorrows.)
(Those who don't wonder what I seek.)
(When I failed to defeat the Jin,)
(I hid in an ancient tomb for years.)
(Zhaoying,)
(you persuaded me every day)
(to leave the tomb.)
(You accompanied me through dark days.)
(I owe you.)
(So far,)
(you've been gone for years.)
(I'm just a mortal.)
(I'll die eventually.)
(I feel I won't last long,)
(and I'll see you again.)
(Yet we haven't expelled the Jin,)
(and the Sutra has stirred things up)
(in the martial world.)
(It's full of conflicts.)
(The Jin will exploit our weakness.)
(Should the Sutra)
(fall into vicious hands,)
(disaster would come.)
(Men face undeserved praise)
(and unwarranted blame.)
(How can I force the masses)
(to comprehend me?)
(I'll stake my reputation)
(to preserve the martial world's peace.)
(Guard it as long as I can.)
(Though nobody understands me,)
(I'll act with a clear conscience.)
Emperor Duan,
your guest has arrived.
Just tea.
I knew you'd seek me.
Speak your mind.
Qi,
we're alone now.
State your purpose.
Why must you
have the Nine Yin True Sutra?
I don't crave the Sutra,
yet I must get it.
Why?
Xing,
you were born a prince.
Whether you like it or not,
you must become emperor.
That's your fate, right?
That's it.
I was a slave.
The lowly folks like me
hate predetermined fates.
The Nine Yin True Sutra belongs to none.
Why should Wang Chongyang
keep it?
Because of his martial arts
or reputation?
Neither in truth.
It's because of his status.
I lead
all beggars.
This time,
I'll champion their rights.
I seek not the Sutra.
I fight
for the nobodies' dignity.
When Emperor Qin toured Kuaiji
and Zhejiang,
Xiang Yu and his uncle
witnessed imperial grandeur.
He vowed aloud,
"I can replace him!"
Qi,
if even Xiang Yu thought so,
shouldn't we aspire more?
I don't get it.
I mean,
Xiang Yu
saw only
imperial extravagance,
never considering
the people's suffering
from such excesses.
He didn't mean
to save the masses.
He craved status
and prestige.
People
praise Xiang Yu as heroic,
but Qi,
when people face empty fame and glory,
it's easy to lose their way.
Even Xiang Yu couldn't
meet your standards,
then naturally,
I can't either.
Sure.
We all crave empty fame.
We're all lost.
But as an emperor,
why do you
want the Sutra?
Qi.
Do you
remember our agreement?
What agreement?
We once vowed
to defeat the old martial artists
and shake the martial world.
Now,
as the leader
of the world's largest sect,
you act like a local tyrant,
relying on your massive following
to endlessly...
Ridiculous!
The size of the Beggar Sect
isn't my doing.
It's done
by emperors like you.
If you rule well,
and people have food,
who will join me as beggars?
The one expanding my sect
is not me,
but you.
Are you a good emperor?
You're soft-hearted,
thinking Confucian governance
will work.
But you're easily manipulated.
An emperor like you
makes people suffer.
I believe
I'm doing better
than you.
Yes.
I admit
I'm not a good emperor.
That's why
I've been thinking
about the meaning
of the Nine Yin True Sutra.
How can it benefit the people?
If I can
obtain the Nine Yin True Sutra,
I'll strengthen Dali's army,
protecting my people
from war's devastation.
Conflicts would end,
and tragedies cease.
Qi.
If you
understand my purpose,
will you withdraw?
Well said!
Had I not known you so long,
I'd buy it.
I know you
pretty well.
You've obsessed over martial arts,
neglecting governance.
Now, you're clever,
using the people as an excuse.
Listen,
I've promised my men
to get the Nine Yin True Sutra.
I must bring it back
to honor my word.
You expect me
to retreat on your say-so?
How would I face my men?
Leader Hong.
Let's duel on Mount Hua.
Good.
(Since the Nine Yin True Sutra appeared)
(in the martial world,)
(it has brought endless bloodshed.)
(Today,)
(we gathered here.)
(There are five directions,
namely, east, west, south,)
(north, and center.)
(Five victors will)
(ascend Mount Hua's summit)
(for the final duel.)
(The ultimate victor,)
(the greatest martial artist,)
(shall have the Nine Yin True Sutra.)
(With his unmatched skills,)
(none)
(could seize the Sutra from him.)
(This is a duel)
(on Mount Hua.)
(All participants)
(exercise restraint.)
(Never take lives)
(unless absolutely necessary.)
(There are four lines
to find the Sutra.)
(Through perilous cliffs you must trek,)
(beyond Lord Lao's
plowed ravine's neck.)
(Where pines conceal the sacred ground,)
(in hidden grotto the sutra's found.)
Master.
(Jin of Xiliang)
(Nine Yin True Sutra)
This small book
has plunged the martial world
into chaos.
Jialan.
Before we determine the winner,
you must keep this book.
My sect will protect you.
Where's your staff?
I came
not as the leader of the Beggar Sect.
Your skills have improved, Emperor Duan.
Thanks.
Xing.
Given our past friendship,
I've shown restraint.
Leave now,
and you may leave unscathed.
I'm carrying hope
of the living
and aspiration of the dead.
I cannot retreat.
Then you must defeat me.
I've lost.
But it's exhilarating.
I'm convinced.
You said you served the people.
I believe you.
Qi.
I'm a beggar,
yet I don't beg.
You're a mighty ruler,
yet yesterday,
you talked to me
like a beggar.
Have you considered?
Even if I withdraw,
would Wang Chongyang retreat?
Would Mr. Huang withdraw?
If you fight for Dali,
then act like a ruler!
Obtain the Nine Yin True Sutra
with your own hands.
Yes.
Thank you for your advice, Leader Hong.
Don't use these empty words
to flatter me.
I can see through you,
yet I'm confused about myself.
Yes.
You claim
to get the Sutra
for your sect.
I have questions.
Do your men
follow you
for the Nine Yin True Sutra?
Do they covet supremacy?
Or do they just
need a good sect leader?
You have a long way to go.
Take care.
Qi.
When we first met,
we hit it off straight away.
You astonished me at first sight.
Unexpectedly, one word
made you wait three days.
How exhilarating!
I remember it was a rainy day.
If only those days
could've lasted longer.
Enough.
If...
Cut it out!
We can't
go back in time.
If we join forces,
victory would be assured.
(Qingsong Pavilion)
But I don't trust you.
Let us each
face our own desperation
within our separate abysses.
Yaoshi.
You don't know
how terrifying a man becomes
when he's lost everything.
Yaoshi.
I used Knockout Powder on you.
You'll sleep for at least two days.
Have a good rest.
Stop struggling.
You've lost.
Yaoshi.
Return to Taohua Island.
I'm weakening.
Go home.
♪Alone in this mundane world,
embracing night's sway♪
♪Wandering horizon's edge,
boundless without trace♪
♪A roving hero,
where's the true rare breed♪
♪Yet drawing from heaven
and earth's deep core♪
♪Slicing through disputes,
erasing ties of hate♪
♪Amid rising storm winds,
countless thoughts fade away♪
♪Momentary fame, endless wandering days♪
♪In this martial world,
a poetic page turns♪
♪How could this world have♪
♪Unrivaled skills that transcend time♪
♪Yet mortals strive
for glory and debate♪
♪On mountain peaks, time gallops past♪
♪Victory and loss stem from our core♪
♪Who'll recall my blade's dance of yore♪
♪All covet endlessly♪
♪A lifetime's pursuit of greatness rare♪
♪Through countless battles,
none will retreat♪
♪Forged by daylight, tempered at night♪
♪Enduring time's relentless flight♪
♪Even supreme techniques become♪
♪A flash in the pan♪
♪How could this world have♪
♪Unrivaled skills that transcend time♪
♪Yet mortals strive
for glory and debate♪
♪On mountain peaks, time gallops past♪
♪Victory and loss stem from our core♪
♪Who'll recall my blade's dance of yore♪
♪All covet endlessly♪
♪A lifetime's pursuit of greatness rare♪
♪Through countless battles,
none will retreat♪
♪Forged by daylight, tempered at night♪
♪Enduring time's relentless flight♪
♪Even supreme techniques become♪
♪A flash in the pan♪