♪Our tangled destiny
has trapped my heart in this life♪
♪Will I see you again in the next life♪
♪Keep a piece of peach blossom
to remember the past and say goodbye♪
♪But I still miss you
with tears in my eyes♪
♪Dig a hole, plant a tree, but the leaves
and flowers remind me of our past♪
♪Sow the seeds of love,
but they bloom on the wrong path♪
♪Move on, let go,
forget everything about you♪
♪Flowers fall on the road
where I fell in love with you♪
Remember,
no living things
can leave or enter the capital
before midnight.
Aye.
(Cut off the Crown Prince's
communication with the city.)
Close the gate!
(Block him out of the city.)
(So, you leave the city alone)
(to distract me)
(and assassinate the prince.)
(How can I watch you die?)
=Stolen Love=
=Episode 34=
My Lady, all 300 archers are ready.
With your order,
we'll kill that vile prince
with a thousand arrows.
Crown Prince is a suspicious
and cunning man.
You must be very cautious.
Without the tiger tally,
you mustn't take action.
Prince Su selected all of us,
and we've fought the enemy
with General Xiao.
My Lady, don't worry.
Thanks.
(The Cibei Temple)
Next.
Move.
Wait.
What are you doing?
My Lord, this...
The ceremony
cannot be delayed.
If we miss the timing,
will you be responsible?
Move.
(Xiao Chuyi, I knew you'd come.)
(I'll fulfill your wish.)
(In Memory of
the Warriors Died in Luoxia Ridge)
Witness by heaven,
blessed by god,
Tianyu's soldiers
shall return to the homeland
and be remembered.
Today,
I, the Crown Prince,
came here to pay homage to
all the soldiers.
Xiao Chu...
Scream.
Scream so that they can hear you.
Are you crazy?
Can't you see the situation clearly?
What situation?
Isn't it the situation where your master
the Crown Prince
pretends to mourn my dead brothers?
Or the situation
where the murderer
can insult
the victims as he wants?
Or should I put it as
a situation
where a traitor to the nation
wants to keep his position
by sacrificing my brothers' blood?
Chuyi,
please stop.
I have something more important to do.
What's so important?
Are you...?
You...
Chuyi!
Pray for the protection of the spirits
and the prosperity of the nation.
Protect the Crown Prince!
How dare you assassinate me?
Do you know...?
Don't move!
General Xiao,
assassinating the Crown Prince
is a capital crime.
(In Memory of
the Warriors Died in Luoxia Ridge)
You didn't even kneel
to their souls.
Do you have a heart?
Kneel!
Brothers.
(In Memory of
the Warriors Died in Luoxia Ridge)
Look who's here.
The Crown Prince
is here to kowtow and apologize!
Kowtow!
I was confused
and made a mistake.
- General, mercy.
- Did I tell you to stop?
Kneel!
(Chuyi, you can't die.)
If you kill him,
I'll die in front of you!
Yun,
I know you want to save me.
If one of us has to die,
it has to be me.
Watch out!
Yun!
Yunxi!
Do you think I'm an idiot?
Tear Xiao Chuyi into pieces!
Aye!
Arrows!
Run!
Lu Yunxi, you really want to kill me.
General, we're here.
Who sent you?
We swore to fight and die with you.
Take her away.
Leave me here.
Take the prince and leave.
I have a plan.
How can I leave you?
Let's enter the temple.
Let's go.
Xu Da.
Guard the surrounding areas.
Find a place to lock and
keep an eye on him.
Amitabha.
Abbot, sorry for this.
General, no apologies.
If I can survive,
I'll definitely repay you.
Abbot, please prepare
a guest room for us.
This way.
The Crown Prince
was kidnapped by criminals.
Now I'm your leader.
Everyone, find a way to break in
and rescue His Highness.
If we break in, will they hurt...?
- Break in!
- Aye!
(The city is shut down.)
(I'll be the one)
(who writes the story.)
(I hope you'll all die here,)
(as long as Yunxi is safe.)
Only I can unlock this.
If you use force,
the liquid inside
will melt the pills.
Xiao Chuyi,
why don't you kill me
and get the cure?
Xiao Chuyi,
do you dare?
If you kill me,
everyone here and their family
will be eliminated,
including Lu Yunxi.
Let's wait and see.
When we go back,
I'll tell my father.
Go to hell!
That vicious woman!
I'll torture her to death!
How dare you do this to me?
Xiao Chuyi!
General,
they're trying to break in.
We can only guard it for one day.
Any mint leaf?
Find a way
to contact the soldiers Yun arranged.
Tomorrow morning,
we'll break out together.
Yun.
Don't move.
It's okay.
(It's the Hell Poison from Wujiang.)
(The shadow guard of the Crown Prince
is from Wujiang.)
You...
If we don't eliminate it,
it'll invade your organs via your blood,
and you'll die in extreme pain.
Hang in there.
But...
♪Took vows as the wind passed by♪
♪Seems to have forgotten
the passing of time♪
♪Linger on the past, wish♪
If you can't bear the pain,
just bite me.
I can handle it.
Then let's make a deal.
Every time you scream,
I'll take off a piece of your clothes.
How can you tease me
at this point?
You know me.
I keep every promise I made.
♪But I still miss you
with tears in my eyes♪
♪Dig a hole, plant a tree, but the leaves
and flowers remind me of our past♪
♪Sow the seeds of love,
but they bloom on the wrong path♪
♪Move on, let go,
forget everything about you♪
♪Flowers fall on the road
where I fell in love with you♪
My Lord,
we've taken down the ambush
Lady Lu arranged.
Great.
What about the Cibei Temple?
We've been trying
but haven't made any progress.
Keep trying.
Leave them no time to rest.
Aye!
General.
The poison had infected your lungs,
and you absorbed
Lady Lu's poisonous blood.
Doctor Wu's medicine
doesn't work anymore.
What about the ambush?
They were intercepted by Zhou Yanyu.
Xu Da.
Tomorrow morning,
I'll break out with the Crown Prince
and kill him in public.
Protect Yun.
Ask her to surrender to Zhou Yanyu.
I'll take the blame
for killing the prince.
Yun will protect all of you.
General, no!
We can't watch you die!
I already died once.
If it wasn't for my love for her,
I wouldn't have survived.
Besides, I don't have much time left.
As a soldier,
I'd rather die with glory.
I can not only cure Che
but also avenge the brothers
died in Luoxia Ridge.
Any mint leaf?
General! General!
♪My cries♪
♪And sighs♪
♪Are buried in the snow♪
♪Horses run♪
♪Into my dreams♪
♪And I see you again♪
♪You left♪
♪Broke my heart♪
♪Wish you could hold me in your arms♪
♪Even your name♪
♪Is a forbidden word♪
♪I've traveled a thousand miles♪
♪Only to keep the moon in sight♪
♪For it once shone upon your face♪
♪When you looked at me in the eye♪
♪I've said goodbye a thousand times♪
♪Only to call your name again♪
♪For it's the only thing♪
♪I'll never forget♪
♪I've traveled a thousand miles♪
♪Only to keep the moon in sight♪
♪For it once shone upon your face♪
♪When you looked at me in the eye♪
♪I've said goodbye a thousand times♪
♪Only to call your name again♪
♪For it's the only thing♪
♪I'll never forget♪
♪Till the day that I die♪