♪Our tangled destiny
has trapped my heart in this life♪
♪Will I see you again in the next life♪
♪Keep a piece of peach blossom
to remember the past and say goodbye♪
♪But I still miss you
with tears in my eyes♪
♪Dig a hole, plant a tree, but the leaves
and flowers remind me of our past♪
♪Sow the seeds of love,
but they bloom on the wrong path♪
♪Move on, let go,
forget everything about you♪
♪Flowers fall on the road
where I fell in love with you♪
=Stolen Love=
=Episode 42=
(Dad,)
(Mom,)
(I'm not a good son.)
(I'll reunite with you...)
Chuyi!
It's over, Yun.
Yes.
It's over.
Let's see a doctor.
Let's pick Che up.
Che is just up ahead.
We're almost there.
Yun...
I...
I think...
I can't keep my promise.
Chuyi.
It's okay.
Hang in there.
We're almost there.
Chuyi!
We only need the cure.
I'll look for it.
Let's look for it.
You'll get better.
You won't die.
Yun...
It's snowing...
Yes.
Chuyi.
Chuyi,
we'll be reunited very soon.
Let's get out of here.
Let's go to a peaceful place
where no one knows us.
Chuyi,
I want to eat rick cakes.
Let's go home, okay?
Chuyi...
You'll be alright!
♪Will I see you again in the next life♪
♪Keep a piece of peach blossom
to remember the past and say goodbye♪
♪But I still miss you
with tears in my eyes♪
♪Dig a hole, plant a tree♪
Yun...
Whatever you want...
Whatever I want...
♪Flowers fall on the road
where I fell in love with you♪
♪Pray to god, look back♪
Chuyi...
Chuyi!
♪Hear the rain, watch the Milky Way,
but how can I forget about you♪
Chuyi!
Speaking of General Xiao,
his wife Lu Yunxi
finally reunited with him
after seven years.
How could she
watch him die of poison?
So, she took General Xiao
to look for the cure.
The childhood sweethearts
have shared
the same promises and dreams.
The groom fought in the frontier,
and the lady remarried her enemy
with regrets.
The general eliminated the enemy,
and the lady could only
blame god.
Nonsense!
Arrogant Quack, how dare you?
Old man,
how dare you talk nonsense
and distort the facts?
Why don't you tell
the audience your story
and let them be the judges?
When I was traveling around,
I saw a couple by the river.
The general didn't die,
and the lady had no regrets.
They have a son and a daughter,
but they're living a secluded
but carefree life.
Che, be careful.
Mom.
Slow down.
Since Wujiang surrendered to us,
my brother has visited
many doctors in Wujiang.
I'm afraid there's
no cure for you.
- But...
- But what?
You've tried all the herbs in the world
and found they can only
relieve the pain,
and my death is just
a matter of time, right?
I'll keep looking for the cure.
No need, Liuyun.
This is amazing,
isn't it?
Be careful, Che!
Mom.
You're standing so far.
Perhaps because of that,
the rest days of my life
are so precious.
Dad!
Come and play with us!
Come here!
(Happy Film Finishing Day)
(The End)
♪My cries♪
♪And sighs♪
♪Are buried in the snow♪
♪Horses run♪
♪Into my dreams♪
♪And I see you again♪
♪You left♪
♪Broke my heart♪
♪Wish you could hold me in your arms♪
♪Even your name♪
♪Is a forbidden word♪
♪I've traveled a thousand miles♪
♪Only to keep the moon in sight♪
♪For it once shone upon your face♪
♪When you looked at me in the eye♪
♪I've said goodbye a thousand times♪
♪Only to call your name again♪
♪For it's the only thing♪
♪I'll never forget♪
♪I've traveled a thousand miles♪
♪Only to keep the moon in sight♪
♪For it once shone upon your face♪
♪When you looked at me in the eye♪
♪I've said goodbye a thousand times♪
♪Only to call your name again♪
♪For it's the only thing♪
♪I'll never forget♪
♪Till the day that I die♪