♪Our tangled destiny
has trapped my heart in this life♪
♪Will I see you again in the next life♪
♪Keep a piece of peach blossom
to remember the past and say goodbye♪
♪But I still miss you
with tears in my eyes♪
♪Dig a hole, plant a tree, but the leaves
and flowers remind me of our past♪
♪Sow the seeds of love,
but they bloom on the wrong path♪
♪Move on, let go,
forget everything about you♪
♪Flowers fall on the road
where I fell in love with you♪
=Stolen Love=
=Episode 23=
Yunxi...
I'm Yun.
Yun.
But you've never allowed me
to call you Yun.
I can only call you Yunxi.
Yanyu.
But I like hearing you call me Yun.
Yun!
Do you know how much I wish
I could call you Yun like he does?
You're my Yun.
Lord Zhou was drugged...
Don't worry.
I won't tell anyone.
It's you.
Where are you going?
Don't let me catch you.
Who catches whom?
Want me to catch you?
Whatever.
Then catch me.
Don't run!
Slow down.
General, you mentioned
the Cibei Temple yesterday.
I believe you know
I went to Luoxia Ridge seven years ago.
I didn't mean to hide it from you.
I don't need to hide it.
When I heard about your death,
I was devastated.
However, my deepest fear
was my future.
Will I be alone
for the rest of my life?
Then how do you explain
why you brought the letters back?
Just a small favor.
I don't believe it.
I'm an orphan who was thrown into
the Orphan Cave by my parents.
I was born a heartless girl.
You saved me
and asked your mother to adopt me.
I had to act good
because I was afraid you'd dislike me.
If nothing happens,
I'll behave myself.
However, if anything happens,
I'll only protect
myself.
Don't demean yourself.
You're not like that.
I know you're not a heartless person.
General.
The kind version of me
is what I want you to see.
Since you came back,
you've mentioned the crimes
the Zhous committed many times,
but I've never asked.
Don't you want to know why?
Lu Yunxi...
You knew it all along
that it was that vicious old woman
who destroyed my family.
The old general
was a brave warrior
who'd never surrender.
Why would he kill himself
for fear of punishment?
Yun.
Tell me.
Do you have a reason for doing this?
You've always wanted
to get revenge, right?
Tell me.
Revenge?
I serve Lady Zhou every day.
If I wanted to get revenge,
I would've poisoned
or assassinated her
a long time ago.
Why would I wait until now?
Xiao Chuyi!
I just want to live.
I want to live
a peaceful and wealthy life.
You want to live
a peaceful
and wealthy life.
Okay, no problem.
I'll get revenge myself.
It has nothing to do with you.
I just want you to know
no matter what you do,
I'll protect you and Che.
Mom!
Young Lord Che, slow down.
Thanks, General.
(Chuyi.)
(We had such a peaceful night together.)
(It's worth it.)
(From now on,)
(I'll risk my life to get revenge.)
(If you knew this,)
(you'd definitely stop me.)
(I have no choice.)
My Lady, why are you here?
Where's Lady Zhou?
The lady in charge asked you over.
Who else
could it be?
My Lady, you're too impatient.
Lady Zhou is very healthy.
If Lady Zhou and His Majesty find out,
they'll punish you
for your disobedience.
Let's go. Stop wasting time.
On the 20th day of the last month
of the 20th Yong'an year.
Lord Zhou, do you remember that day?
Why did you go to the water dungeon?
Did Lord Jiang's wife catch a cold
on the Dragon Boat Festival
of the 25th Yong'an year?
What medicine did you give her?
How did you know?
Lu Yunxi, who are you?
My Lords, don't be nervous.
If I'm a simple and silly girl,
will you trust me
to be a good lady in charge
of the family?
Indeed, Lady Zhou is old.
She shouldn't be bothered
by family issues.
Lady Lu, we're at your service.
Thank you,
My Lords.
Goodbye, My Lady.
If she decides to expose it,
what should we do?
If she wants to replace Lady Zhou now,
she'll have to threaten more people.
She knows the secrets.
Many people will try to kill her.
We have to be careful of Xiao Chuyi.
Xiao Chuyi wants to protect her,
so what?
There are many
more powerful and vicious people.
If they take action,
Xiao Chuyi and Lady Lu will be doomed.
Lady Lu, is it too hasty
to take action now?
We can't wait.
It'll only get more dangerous.
I have to become the lady in charge
before the ancestral worship ceremony
on the Mid-Autumn Festival.
Cuixi, go back and wait for my message.
(Zhou's Mansion)
My Lady, I'll keep
that in mind.
When they reselect the lady in charge,
I'll do whatever I can to help you.
Please don't forget us when you succeed.
Thanks, My Lord.
When I assist Yanyu
in managing the family,
I won't forget what you've done for us.
Goodbye.
My Lord, I've arranged
everything as you told me.
This carriage will never reach
the capital.
Send a message to our soldiers
and the bandits around.
When they see the carriage,
they shall kill her
without mercy.
Aye.
Chuyi!
Yun.
Don't be afraid.
You'll be alright.
Yun, Yun.
Hold onto me.
♪My cries♪
♪And sighs♪
♪Are buried in the snow♪
♪Horses run♪
♪Into my dreams♪
♪And I see you again♪
♪You left♪
♪Broke my heart♪
♪Wish you could hold me in your arms♪
♪Even your name♪
♪Is a forbidden word♪
♪I've traveled a thousand miles♪
♪Only to keep the moon in sight♪
♪For it once shone upon your face♪
♪When you looked at me in the eye♪
♪I've said goodbye a thousand times♪
♪Only to call your name again♪
♪For it's the only thing♪
♪I'll never forget♪
♪I've traveled a thousand miles♪
♪Only to keep the moon in sight♪
♪For it once shone upon your face♪
♪When you looked at me in the eye♪
♪I've said goodbye a thousand times♪
♪Only to call your name again♪
♪For it's the only thing♪
♪I'll never forget♪
♪Till the day that I die♪