Mr. Zhen wants the secret account book of the orphanage.
Yes.
The boss doesn't want
to alarm Gao Yao first.
But only you two
know where the account book is.
I'm just the nominal CFO.
All the accounts
are managed by Dean Gao.
I know
the boss won't blame you.
Okay.
I'll cooperate with Mr. Zhen.
If it weren't for my sister's illness,
I wouldn't have stayed here this long.
The copy of the account book
is as planned.
Now you must, as quickly as possible,
collaborate with Zhen Shida to launder money
as Yang Gaoming.
Does he trust you now?
With Gao Yao as a stepping stone,
he has now lowered his guard against me.
In his eyes now,
Yang Gaoming
is just a greedy bastard.
Besides,
how could he give me 500,000 yuan for nothing?
He will come to me again.
I just don't know
how to deal with
the J behind him.
We'll see.
I'll go out.
Hao Qing,
are you okay?
Come on.
Listen to me.
Inhale.
Exhale.
Hao Feng.
Hao Feng, look at me.
Listen to me.
Inhale.
Exhale.
Breathe out.
Breathe in.
Are you feeling better?
Respiratory alkalosis.
It happens when you're under a lot of stress.
How do you know how to do this emergency treatment?
I don't know.
I just feel like
I've done this before.
Aren't you going out?
Call me if you need anything.
It's done.
The nanochip
implanted in the neck
can monitor memory fluctuations in real time,
even
restore them.
Calm down.
Slow down your breathing.
What do you want?
My phone.
Look at this.
Power adjustment
can stimulate memory recovery,
but if you turn it to the maximum,
the chip overload
will burn all nerve nodes instantly,
and the person will die of a sudden death.
The decline of human memory
has always been a difficult problem to solve.
But if there is a decisive breakthrough,
it will definitely help a lot of people.
I don't understand all this,
but no matter how ambitious you are,
you should cherish your body first.
Do you understand?
Unfortunately, it's a double-edged sword.
It can save lives,
but it can also kill.
You passed.
This is your new mission.
Mr. Hao Feng,
I'm your new personal butler,
Jia Yu.
I remember everything.