What's going on?
Where's my diamond?
I'm asking you where my diamond is!
Mr. Zhen,
didn't you take
the Heart of Black Diamond?
So it was a distraction.
I don't know anything.
I didn't see anything.
The Heart of Black Diamond
is missing.
How are you going to balance the books?
Heart of Black Diamond
must have been stolen by Hao Feng's brother.
Hao Feng's brother?
No way, Boss Zhen.
Isn't he dead?
We saw it with our own eyes.
Did you forget?
The organization has investigated.
He's not Hao Feng's brother.
He is Hao Feng.
Impossible.
Hao Feng is dead.
Hao Feng has been dead for a long time.
I saw it with my own eyes.
His ashes were scattered in the river.
You're so sure.
Then recall what you did
about that thing
a year ago.
I did as the organization asked.
I...
I did it perfectly.
I didn't expect you to be so heavy.
Hao Feng.
Relax.
Hurry up.
Right.
Remember my face.
Perfect.
His head is pierced.
He's dead as a doornail.
300 million.
You took
300 million crowdfunding funds all by yourself.
Hao Feng took the blame for you.
Boss Zhen.
what a good deal.
The organization promised me
that I could keep this money.
But...
But I can give it back.
I can give it to you.
Please let me go.
Okay?
You have no money now.
How can you...
You know so many secrets of the organization.
Do you think you can live anymore?
Ex...
Exper...
I'll give you all the data
from the lab.
Besides that,
I really don't know anything else.
You...
Didn't you die?
Jia Yu,
kill him.
You two...
So you two are together.
Mr. Zhen.
No.
With our relationship,
calling you Mr. Zhen is too formal.
Right?
Brother Era.
You're really not Hao Feng's brother?
That's right.
I am Hao Feng.
Impossible.
I killed you back then.
I killed you with my own hands.
The one who died at your hands
was my brother Hao Qing.
Now that you finally admit your crimes,
my brother's spirit in heaven
can finally rest in peace.
Your amazing performance just now
is being broadcast live
on all the LED screens in Sunset Glow City.
What do you mean?
By the way,
And this black diamond heart,
on behalf of the victims of the fund blow-up,
thank you.
After I died back then,
an old colleague who trusted me
stepped forward to claim Hao Feng's ashes.
Since then,
I became his younger brother, Hao Qing.
Back then, the Memory Tree project blew up.
J needed someone to take the blame.
He informed me
to give Zhen Shida an order,
to kill you with his own hands.
He killed you.
I don't know when it was.
So that night,
I wanted to warn you.
But I didn't expect
that it was that night.
It's all over.
Actually, at that time,
I didn't fully trust you.
After the incident,
I thought you betrayed me.
So I did something to you.
A year ago,
in the hospital,
I implanted a chip in you.
The memory observation chip
you developed.
But I will help you take it out.
You could have killed me with it at any time,
but you didn't.
So it doesn't matter anymore.
I've said
I've given my life to you.
Jia Yu,
I hope from now on,
you can live your life to the fullest.
How come it's you?