Godfather
They're here.
President Zhao
Welcome, welcome!
Please, have a seat.
President Li
I've heard so much about you.
It's an honor to meet.
Not at all.
President Zhao
Your visit to Rain City
is truly my honor.
As for me,
I am absolutely sincere
about sitting down with you
and having a real conversation.
About the Zuma Land distribution rights.
However,
the price you offered before
is a bit off from market trends.
Is that so?
President Li thinks my price
is off the market trend.
Then let me ask you,
what do you consider a trend?
Selling discs?
No, that's not it.
What I mean is,
look,
developing the game and its extras,
plus future promotion,
all cost a significant amount.
You know China is huge,
and the market is risky.
If no one is interested,
then I, Li Changtian,
would end up with nothing.
My father told me,
in business,
there are gains and losses.
If someone tells you
there's no risk
and you can make money,
and wants you to invest,
he's lying to you.
President Li
You just said
China is huge.
That's right.
Your father was absolutely right.
So that means
we still have things to discuss.
We do.
But
it has to be on my terms.
President Zhao
How about this?
Since you're rarely in China,
why not stay here
and enjoy a few more days?
Give me some time
to think it over.
Then President Li can start thinking now.
Thank you for the hospitality.
Wait,
the food isn't all here yet.
I'm on a diet.
Uncle
President Zhao
If you can't decide,
I might just
look for another game company's product.
Business is about mutual agreement.
If that's the case,
we'll work together if fate allows.
Godfather
Her attitude suddenly got tough.
Did someone
offer a higher price than us?
Things have changed a bit.
Someone is competing with us
for Zuma Land's rights.
Who is it?
It's someone who used to
sell cartridges for us in Raonan District.
He was supposed to go to Korea
to sell a half-finished game.
But he took a liking to Zuma Land
and wants to bring it back to sell.
Isn't he just a dog I raised?
Now he dares to compete with me.
Does he really think
Li Changtian is soft?
Godfather
So what do we do next?
A bratty girl,
a lowlife street vendor,
the two of them dare to team up
and show off to me.
Looks like they have a death wish.
The one at the door earlier
was her trusted aide, right?
Yes.
He's Chinese.
His name is Jiang Long.
Find a time
and set up a meeting with him.
This time, you guys—
Was it thrilling or not?
I'm really jealous of you.
I wish I could've gone too.
It was as exciting as it gets.
It was as intense as possible.
Come on.
I made this for you myself.
First,
to celebrate your triumphant return.
Second,
to celebrate our 996 Internet Café
finally settling the lawsuit.
That's a must.
Now we can achieve greatness again.
Cheers!
Come on, cheers!
Come on.
Cheers!
I also want to thank everyone
for helping me with all your effort.
If it weren't for Old Pan's game,
we wouldn't have earned this money.
Without this income, we'd have no cash.
Without this money,
we couldn't have fixed the 996 issue.
So, Old Pan,
here's to you.
Hey, hey—
You two haven't met for just half a month,
Is it necessary to act so dramatic?
Let's sit down
and drink together.
To Old Pan!
I have an announcement for everyone.
Our 996 Internet Café—
I've had workers renovate it.
Except we don't have much money for new computers.
But I promise, inside,
it's exactly like before the incident.
No problem.
This trip to Korea was fruitful.
I tried out a game there.
Let me tell you—
After we both played it,
I truly think
if we get the rights to this game,
Which game?
Zuma Land.
If we can get
the rights to Zuma Land,
everyone here
can make a fortune.
Is this Land expensive or not?
Three hundred thousand.
US dollars.
Our café just had trouble.
That's way too expensive.
No way, no way.
That's impossible.
It's way too expensive.
If others dare to ask this much,
it means their product is the real deal.
Tell me how this game works.
Let me see if I can make it.
So, it's an online game.
We used to play mostly offline games.
It has classes, like mage—
warrior—
and you fight monsters, level up.
Of course, you can also PvP.
Right?
Zhou Mingrui, I admit—
this game you mentioned
does sound pretty awesome to me.
But the problem is—
Even if it has Shuke Beta,
even if it has Black Cat Captain,
it's still not worth that much.
Yeah, it sounds interesting.
But we really can't afford it.
It's not about affording it.
I'm saying we can find a way.
To win, we need the right info.
We have to get the first slice.
If we grab it before others,
we're the winners.
This game is just too expensive.
It's expensive now.
Listen to me.
What are you doing?
Stop arguing.
How about we drink?
I have something important to say.
Three hundred thousand dollars.
If you can't raise it in seven days,
the chance goes to someone else.
Zhou Mingrui.
Can you change your impulsive ways?
Where do we get three hundred thousand?
He's always been like this.
Come on, come on, let's drink!
Sister Feng,
your cooking skills are impressive.
I noticed
this seafood is delicious.
Mr. Jiang is here.
Nice to meet you.
Please, have a seat.
No need to be so formal, Mr. Li.
Sit, sit, sit.
Pour the wine.
Mr. Jiang,
this wine today—
I specially brought it from your hometown,
Shanxi,
flown in by air.
Try it.
Here, a toast to you.
Come on.
A toast to you.
How's the wine?
Authentic.
You didn't invite me just for a drink, did you, Mr. Li?
Just making friends with you.
Mr. Jiang,
how do you like today's dishes?
Do you like them?
They're good.
Feels like there's a dish missing.
Why not serve it already?