This series is based on a fictionalized story inspired by the story of BTS's album,
The Most Beautiful Moment in Life,
and is not related to BTS members and their families.   Child actors and animals were filmed
in safe conditions under the supervision of their guardians.
The teacher?
But why should I
keep it secret from Cein?
Oh?
This is Cein's house key
Where did you get it?
Ma'am?
What about her?
Why is she in danger?
No way she didn't...
Again?
But how do you know...
what hasn't happened yet?
911, what's your emergency?
Sir
Please help me
I think...
my brother's dead
He's bleeding in the head
Please come quickly
Jeha was bleeding in the head...
I understand it's hard
to recall what happened
But thanks to
your swift call
he's less hurt
He was so shocked that
it's been days, but he's still like this
Mingook
Wipe your tears
and tell them what happened
Ok
On that day...
I was on my way
to an internet cafe with my friends
If you continue to hate me,
I'll just go and die there. Just as your mom did
What's all this?
I...
saw Jeha going into that house
I thought he might be in danger...
so I followed him
Annoyed, aren't you?
- But inside
- Wanna hit me?
Go ahead
- Cein Min...
- Hit me!
- Hey
- Cein was...
beating Jeha up
He said he was going to kill him
I tried my best
to stop him
But he...
hit my brother
with a brick...
Let's leave here
Stop and let's leave
Please?
- I was so scared
- Sir
Please help me
Witness statement of stating that he was scared
because Cein beat up Jeha
This is what
Mingook has testified
Is there anything different
from what you know?
A few days ago...
some people
saw you fighting with Jeha...
after you found out that
he had been tracking you
Is that why you struck Jeha?
Cein
According to Mingook...
you sent a text to Jeha
that you'd kill him
The whole situation's against you...
by a large degree
Mr. Min
If Cein continues refusing to talk...
you are aware that
this case will be reported
based on Mingook's statement...
right?
Cein Min
Is it true...
or not?
Come on, say something
They were always together...
almost everyday
Did he...
really say he did it?
I don't get it
How can he...
Why? Why aren't you eating up?
What are you worried about?
You know Cein
Our elderly might look cold on the outside
but he couldn't have done it
Especially not to
Jeha
We just need to
stand our ground and wait
The truth will come out...
and everything will be back to normal
I bet
What do you mean by...
"back to normal?"
Here
Here, where we're at right now
Here, where all my bros are at
I thought you were the smart one...
but I guess not
We?
My bro?
Jooan, have you seen Haru today?
Is he also doing the interview?
Hey, Jooan
What
What?
Are you still pissed off at Haru?
Don't be so petty
You know he's sick. Don't do that to him
I didn't do anything to him!
Hey, Jooan
- What's going on?
- Seriously!
Leave me alone!
It's not real!
Hey, where did you go?
None of it is real!
Your friend
doesn't exist
It's not real, you idiot
No, he was right here until just now
Look around
You're alone
You were alone from the start
Your friend doesn't exist
you lunatic!
Jooan, you also met him
before
This is the one
This is the friend you were talking
You were talking to your
own reflection in the glass!
How...
How did it become this bad?
How did you end up like this?
You should've told us!
Haru
Are you sick again?
- Where have you been?
- Huh?
I was always here
Oh, you mean Jooan?
He's an interesting guy
Sometimes, he can be stupid
and very silly
What the
I thought you weren't here
I'm always here
Jooan seemed to be
avoiding you today
It must've been upsetting
Of course, I'm here to console you
Thanks
But the thing about Jooan...
I didn't mention it to you
because you might feel disappointed
How did you find out?
I know everything about you
How?
Because I'm you
Mom
Yes
You sent my phone for repair?
Yes, I think you dropped
and broke it that day
Then can I borrow yours?
I want to call Cein
Call who?
Are you out of your mind?
You're here in this state
because of him
I'm fine, really
The doctor said
I'm recovering more quickly
than expected because I'm young
Why do you omit the part where he said
they'll run more tests
and you must get some rest?
You will stay in bed and be discharged
without causing any trouble, ok?
I studied really hard this time
for the midterm exam
Dad will be pleased if my grades go up
So Mom
I'll go and take the exam...
I already discussed it with your school
They'll send one of the teachers
and let you take the exam here
They don't have to do that
I know...
you're trying to go
to the school to see Cein
He's suspended...
so he won't be in school anyway
What?
They suspended him?
I'm here
Yes
Did the interview go well?
You must be tired
Did your father go to work straight away?
Yes
He wants to know...
how Jeha's doing...
in the hospital
I'll give him a call
I'll go home...
to do some housework, and come back
Stay with your brother, ok?
Do you hear me?
Mingook
- Yes
- Can I talk to you for a minute?
While I'm at home...
can I ask you to watch over Jeha...
make sure he doesn't get out
and meet anyone?
Never let him use a phone, ok?
I won't be long
Have some sleep
With things going on...
it must be hard to focus on your studies
Besides, you're close with both of them
It must be awkward to take sides
As the attack was more violent
than I thought...
the School Violence Deliberation Committee
will be held the day after tomorrow
I believe it won't last long...
since Cein Min
admitted to everything
Did Cein really do it?
Cein admitted to everything
the victim's brother has testified
If it weren't true...
there would've been another narrative
School transfer...
or expulsion will be
the most likely outcome
What do you think?
Pardon?
- About what...
- Oh, I just...
wanted to know your opinion
It is true that
lately, Cein has been
acting dangerously
Transfer...
school?
I'll look up schools near company housing
Despite how much you wanted...
I shouldn't have let you stay
You punk
How dare you ignore my message?
I've been easy on you lately, haven't I?
Come on
Hey, what's going on?
I also know
what happened between Cein and Jeha
I don't feel good about it, too...
but we talked about this. There's
- nothing we can do...
- Shit
Shut up if you don't know anything
What did you just say?
Sh... Shit?
You made a big mistake, Jooan Kim
Apologize this instant
Don't make me get mad at you
I told you to leave me alone
Hey, I'm warning you
In count of three
you'll find yourself in big trouble
One, two!
Two and a half
Two and three-quarter
Hosu
Haru...
What about Haru?
Schizophrenia
- Excuse me, sir
- Oh?
Yes, Hosu
Is there something you want to say?
Yes
It's not about me
It's about my friend
I'm worried about him
What is it?
My friend's a little ill
He takes his own reflection on the mirror
as his friend
At first, I thought...
he really made a new friend
I mean...
I wished he did
After Haru transferred to a new school
and made new friends
his condition improved
So I thought...
my son...
could get better, too...
like...
other kids
It's been difficult
not only on him
but on you as well
I fully understand
But
it is true that his symptoms
have worsened
If possible
I'd like you to hospitalize him right away
It's the middle of the semester
And he told me
after the glass was broken
he no longer sees the imaginary friend
It could be that
the imaginary friend disappeared
temporarily due to a mental shock
But
if we don't treat
the fundamental trauma
he isn't remembering
it will appear in a different form
Sir
Could you meet up with my friend?
No
We'll hospitalize him during the vacation
If the rumor spreads again...
it won't be good for Haru
Of course. I'd be glad to
They might redevelop the area...
Didn't you say they won't?
I mean...
they just might
I want us to have a plan
just in case
I asked around
If we get the deposit
there's a place we can go
It's a bit small
There's no...
deposit
Why isn't there...
a deposit?
I'm asking you
Did you use it?
Did you use the deposit in advance?
What did you use it for?
I paid your father's hospital bill...
Dohyeon's...
settlement fee...
living expenses...
- here and there...
- Here and there?
I gave you the money
I gave you the rent
and the living expenses every month
Even for the hospital bills
and Dohyeon's settlement...
I worked to make up for it
There are a lot more that
I didn't tell you
If I told you
it's obvious how you'd have reacted
Mom
Don't you understand...
what that deposit meant for us?
After Father ended up like that
his company ditched that money
as a compensation
You know well how
we spent that money on this house...
instead for his surgery
If only we paid for his surgery
he would've been able
to get up on his legs
I know
You think...
I used it because I wanted to?
I used it because we didn't have any money
Why don't we have any money?
I gave you the money!
How could you use the deposit?
You should've asked me
for more money instead
Dogeon!
I know what you think
But I didn't
use that money for myself!
So we don't have anything left?
This trashy furniture is
all we have left?
Mom
Let's just...
go to our aunt and...
We're not going to your aunt
They don't help us one bit
but they go around
showing off every country
they've been to
What do you want to do then?
When they come to destroy this house,
shall we all die under the rubble
in our sleep?
The student you're tutoring
You said he's rich
Can't you ask
his parents to pay you
in advance?
Everything will be paid with
your wage anyway
So it's me again
- Huh?
- It's me
Isn't it?
It all boils down to me
Of course
Mom
Don't you ever...
feel sorry for me?
Don't you feel bad for me?
Everyone else feels sorry for me...
but why is my hard work
taken for granted by my own family?
- Who would...
- Why do I have to live like this?
If we live in destitute to save money...
even discharging Dad from the hospital,
will it be ok later on?
You really believe so?
Is there ever an end to it?
Mom
Yes?
Are you feeling uncomfortable?
Want to go to the restroom?
Mom
Can I talk to Cein
over the phone just once? Please?
Just once
I said you can't
I'm sure he was surprised, too
He's not as tough as he looks
Mom
You can't see him anyway
Why?
Why can't I see him?
He will either be asked to...
transfer school...
or be expelled during the Deliberation
Your dad strongly protested that
he can't let you go to the same school
with someone like him
Mom
It's not Cein...
who called me out...
to that place
- Mingook...
- I know
Mom
You knew?
But why...
Jeha
We need Mingook more than him
These days, Mingook can't even
meet your eyes
He used to be so anxious
to get at us
But from now on...
he can't get at you
And...
whatever the reason...
it's Cein who struck you
My son
You're all I've got
You said you'd protect me
This is our house...
and our family...
ok?
Dogeon
I didn't know you were up there
- You weren't answering your phone
- Jooan
For today...
just leave me alone
What? I can't hear you
I said, "Leave"
Please
Come on
If I go back home
my dad won't let me out
because he's scared to be alone
He's getting worse
Even just now, I told him I'm going out
and he threw a frame at me
So what?
What do you want me to do?
Huh?
What's going on?
Did something happen to you?
What's wrong?
Stop asking me
I also don't know
what I should do!
I'm sorry
So please, just leave
What happened?
Darn it
Dohyeon got into trouble again, didn't he?
Tell me, Dogeon
There's a lot going on even without him
What if I told you?
Can you fix it for me?
- Come on, Dogeon
- The only thing you can do
is talking about yourself
Whenever there's trouble
you feel better after pouring it
out on me, right?
After you're gone
I feel crushed
even under a thin blanket
Who should I
confide in?
Why isn't there anyone by my side?
Why should I live like this?
I just want to evaporate
into thin air
Dogeon
Do you know what I hate
the most about myself?
I get used to things, whatever that is
I give up and don't even fight on
No...
I don't even want to fight
I see you pouring out your anger
and I get vicarious pleasure
After that, I grill you
not to do that...
and even rationalize myself
that I'm right
That's who I am
I'm a despicable coward
So what am I to console others?
How could I understand other people?
Shoot
I didn't know
you were having such a hard time
You should've told me a long time ago
Thanks...
for hearing me out...
all this time...
and I'm sorry
Haru, Haru Park
It's him again
He's not real. He doesn't exist
Haru Park
Good morning, Oneday
Yeah, Hosu
Did you have breakfast?
- No
- Really?
You look more handsome today
Oh, right. Haru
There's someone I want to introduce
To introduce to me?
Who is it?
You have to meet him
I took out my savings for you here
Our Oneday
If you keep drinking
the milk I give you...
you'll grow up to three meters
Were you...
upset with me?
Well
I was a little busy lately
The care period is ending soon...
but to get into a support facility...
I must have a job or a certificate
I can bear it if I get hungry
or if I don't have enough clothes...
but to imagine
having no roof over my head...
even a super ultra positive guy like me...
got impatient
So...
even when I knew
how much you liked me
I couldn't look out for you
I admit it
So...
you got upset and
got yourself a new friend?
New friend?
It's ok. Jooan never
wanted to tell me...
but I begged him for days
That's how I found out
Anything about you...
I want to be the first to know
If that friend
were a source of strength to you...
I don't think it's something bad
Everyone
needs
a listening ear
I'll be that person from now on
So you can...
tell him to go
I...
I also want to do that
I guess he still
has something to tell you
Do you still see him?
I said leave! It's not you!
I don't need you!
Haru
Haru Park
Look at me
Look only at me
You see me, right?
Right?
Are you real?
What?
I hope you are real...
out of all people
Yes
I'm real
I won't leave you even if you asked me to
I won't disappear
No...
I can't disappear
The person you mentioned...
Is he real, too?
Are you real?
I hope you are real...
out of all people
It's no use!
Mr. Min
You should've educated your son first
before bringing these petty gifts
Yes
Due to my shortcoming
I couldn't keep my son at bay
As you wished...
we'll move to a different area...
and transfer school
Never again...
we'll be in the vicinity
of your sons
So please don't let it
escalate to a criminal case
I beg you
Hyunjoong Kim
Put away your book
You know what happens if
you're caught cheating, right?
I heard it's the start of
your midterm exam
Yes
Can I look forward to your grades again?
Sir, I believe you're aware
but the Deliberation Committee's today
I already have a lot on my plate
but was forced into being
the committee chairman
I heard it roughly that
he hit the boy's head with a stone
That will be a straight out expulsion
The house that caught fire
I heard he's the son
His mom died during that incident, right?
Yes, well
there was a rumor that
he killed his mother
Even for the beach incident...
whenever something comes up
he gets
the most suspicion
I don't know
how he held out without moving
Why is he still staying here
after all that fuss?
Well, I'm not sure
Sir, I thought
it over
Instead of expelling him
how about transferring him
to another school?
From others' perspectives...
you are showing consideration
to both the perpetrator and the victim
and it'd look more positive
What do you think, Hwan? Your friend...
You also know him
Well
I guess both options
wouldn't be so positive for you
Did everyone get it?
Survey on School Violence
This survey will be anonymous
so please provide your honest opinions
- Ok
What is the appropriate measure
for the recent school violence?
Well, there are the detention...
expulsion...
and school transfer options
There are several measures we can take
But...
wouldn't it be awkward
to run into Cein
in the neighborhood?
Not just for Mingook or Jeha...
but for you, too
Ah, of course
You two are friends for now
so Cein...
won't go around
talking about your grades
But you never know
what will happen to your friendship
Consider your father's case
He was so close with his friends
People fall apart...
not after a fight...
but when they're sorry to one another
The feeling of hatred
is a knife pointed
towards the other person...
but the feeling of remorse
is a knife pointed towards myself
But still...
Instead of expulsion, school transfer...
will force him to move
to another neighborhood
Wouldn't that be more reassuring?
Language and Media Midterm Answer Sheet
I guess that could be better
Sorry?
It'd be better for Cein to transfer...
school
What is the appropriate measure
for the recent school violence?
4 School transfer / 5 Expulsion
The test?
Of course, I did well
Mrs. Kim, I can't make it today
I promised to go
somewhere with Haru today
so I'll be late
By the way, where are you going?
Redevelopment opposition rally?
They aren't going to redevelop
Why would there be a rally?
Oh, hold on. I'll call you back
Hosu
Oh, Haru. You're here
I'm sorry
There's something
I must find out
Could you wait for me a little bit?
You know what, you can go
to the academy first
Let's go together. I'll wait
Will it take long?
I don't think it'll take long
Wait
He's going to start his class soon
Don't worry. He's a good person
I told him a lot about you
so it won't be awkward
to meet him alone
I promise
You don't trust me?
You'll come soon, right?
I'll be there as soon as it's over
I'll text you
the location now
You can go there yourself, right?
Yeah, I can...
but come quickly
Ok, go first
Hello
Did Legislator Changjun Kim...
He just went in
What do you believe in?
You don't believe in superstition,
and you don't have a dream
You really don't have any?
Everyone talked about
their dreams except you
I don't
Those things are unnecessary
I thought it over
after listening to you guys
And now...
I know what I want to become
No need to hear it out.
I know it'll be bad
It's not bad
You'll be surprised once you hear it
Your older brother
My older brother?
What do you mean?
You wanna be my older brother?
Yeah
If I'm ever reborn...
I want to be your older brother
Ah
After you're reborn
you wanna get at me
rightfully as the brother?
No
I love that I have you...
but you don't have
anyone to look after you
So when I'm reborn...
I want to be
the brother figure for you
So whenever you're going through something
I'll help you out
What do you think?
Guess how many times
I mentioned "brother" just now?
Haru...
Oh, it's raining
Sir, thank you for your hard work
Excuse me, sir
Hello
I don't know whether you remember
but I'm Hwan's friend, Hosu Jeong
May I know what will happen to Cein...
You will find out
- in a few days...
- It's alright
He waited because he was worried
We made our decision after thoroughly
looking into
the perpetrator's situation...
so don't worry too much
You'll find out the disposition...
through the school announcement
And there's one more...
I mean...
Actually
I live in the orphanage in District 2
There are a lot of kids like me
If that area gets redeveloped
those kids need to
be split up
So...
I know you've said you won't
redevelop during the election...
but the mood isn't so optimistic
I'm old enough to leave the orphanage
so it's not a problem for me...
but for younger kids...
I am already working on
the Children Leaving Act for
juveniles over the age of 19
and shelter-related laws
So please wait it out
I'm really grateful for that...
but Songjoo...
won't be redeveloped, will it?
Sir!
Cut it out
I knew we'll meet again
First grade class seven,
Cheongyun Elementary School
Haru Park
Run
Grass Flower Arboretum
Haru
Are you ok?
Let's run away again
You can't win this, and you know it
We can hide better this time
A place where
you'll never meet that monster
There will be such a place somewhere
No...
there isn't...
unless I die
Isn't surviving...
exhausting?
You also said it's hard
You want to rest, too
No
I want to live
People might think it'd be better
to die than to live like this
But no, I want to live so badly
Even if it pains every day, I want to live
So...
you die
I will live
I'll kill that monster...
and I'll live