Student Gu!
Marry me!
Student Gu! Student Gu!
Student Gu, don't run away!
Student Gu!
Student Gu, listen!
You've already been surrounded by my love.
You can't get away!
- The student who's holding the flowers!
- Here you go.
The student with his hood on!
The student without his hood off!
Student Gu!
Student Gu! Student Gu!
Don't run, Student Gu!
Come on, stop him!
Flowers! Flowers!
Clumsy.
- Go for it!
- Student Gu!
Student Gu!
[Destined to Meet You]
Student Gu! Student Gu! Wait for me!
Don't walk so fast!
Student Gu!
Student Gu! Student Gu!
What are you trying to do?
Proposing to you.
Miss Jin, cut it out.
Hurry and leave, I'm begging you.
Student Gu, I haven't finished.
Student Gu! Ring! Ring!
What are you doing dressing like this?
Look how old you are. You're not from our uni.
That's rude.
What are you doing here?
I'm here to for Student Gu over there. To propose.
Propose?
Understood.
There's an unknown outsider over here at Area C who says she's here to propose.
Unknown identity?
Bring her to the security office now.
Let's go to the security office. Come on.
Once I finish my proposal, I'll go to you.
If I wait for you to finish it, I won't have a job anymore. Let's go!
My flowers! Don't pull me!
- Sir! Sir!
- What are you doing?
- What?
- Sir, sir!
I'm sorry. We're rehearsing for a play.
She's the external help that I invited.
Play?
- Live-action play.
- Live-action play?
Sir, we are indeed rehearsing for a play.
"The President and Her Little Husband."
I'll take her away now.
Sorry.
My flowers!
- Wish you pass every exam!
- Thank you.
You'll find a boyfriend if you don't have one.
- Wish you pass every exam.
- Thank you.
Thank you for joining today.
Wish you pass every exam.
Stop!
- Stop there!
- Let me through!
Wish you pass every exam! Wish you pass every exam!
Stop right there! Don't run!
Student Gu.
Slow down, Student Gu.
Slow down! My... My leg hurts.
Miss Jin, I made it very clear to you. I have no reason to marry you.
If this is to complete the plans for your family, stop here.
I can't help you.
If you think those three reasons are not convincing enough, we can think of something else.
Unreasonable.
I'll help you over there to rest.
I can't walk anymore. It really hurts.
All right, give me your foot.
The floor is too cold.
What do you want, then?
Please.
Your heart's beating very fast.
It's not.
Really.
Thump, thump.
My heart isn't there.
Rest here first and ask Qiu Bi to pick you up.
I still have classes to attend, so I'll go now.
Stop doing things to hurt yourself.
Wait.
Other than those three reasons, I have another reason why I have to marry you.
I need to get married now,
and I hope that person is you.
Tell me honestly.
Why does that person have to be me?
If I tell you that I fell for you at first sight at the bar,
would you believe me?
No one believes in love at first sight now.
If I were Student Gu, I wouldn't either.
All right, don't wander off and wait for me here.
I'll go get the car.
We'll go home.
Qiu Bi...
♫ I fell in love with your name and your gentle eyes ♫
Why did you come back?
♫ But I can only wait for a sunny day ♫
♫ You took away my weakness and complicated feelings ♫
♫ And I couldn't stop my heart from fluttering ♫
These shoes will be more comfortable.
Only my mother helped me change my shoes when I was a child.
♫ You willfully gave up everything significant ♫
Miss Jin,
I'll marry you.
What did you say?
♫ You ran away after only writing half a story
or you worried too much ♫
Let's get married.
♫ I want to love you, hug you, I can't help it ♫
♫ Please don't rain ♫
If I tell you that I fell for you at first sight at the bar,
would you believe me?
♫ Still no reply to the message, and I can't miss anything ♫
♫ If this isn't love ♫
♫ Why are there traces of it pacing up and down in my heart ♫
♫ The cruelty with a little pain is piling up in the corner ♫
These flowers are mine.
Can you give them back to me?
♫ I fell in love with your name and your gentle eyes ♫
♫ But I can only wait for a sunny day ♫
♫ You took away my weakness and complicated feelings ♫
♫ And my heart couldn't help fluttering ♫
♫ But time changed the whole century ♫
Where is she?
♫ You willfully gave up everything significant ♫
♫ You ran away after only writing half a story
or you worried too much ♫
[Don't leave, there's an Easter egg!]
♫ I want to see you, hold you, love you ♫
Mister!
Mister! Did you find these flowers over there?
These flowers are mine.
Can you return them to me?
No. I found these.
That's all I have!
Hey...
Sorry! My future wife gave these to me!
Oh, my daughter and son-in-law.
How sweet.
Welcome!
You...
Why did you move my things to your place?
Because you are going to stay here.
I will be staying at your place?
Have a look at your future home!
I've told Old Jin,who is my dad,
that we had been in love with each other and living together.
I just didn't know you were the third son of the Gu family.
Since you and I are destined, we'll proceed with our marriage.
I...
Although I've agreed with our marriage,
I... still need some time.
What are you waiting for? Let's get it done as soon as possible.
I will ask Qiu Bi to cancel my meeting tomorrow and we'll register for our marriage.
Tomorrow?
Tomorrow...
I don't think I can make it.
Tomorrow is not the right time.
Don't worry.
I've checked. Tomorrow is an auspicious day.
A good day to get married.
That's not what I meant.
Is it because you have not graduated?
If I am not wrong, a student can get married even if they haven't graduated yet.
Stop worrying.
I...
I am not old enough to get married.
Before you become an adult...
I mean... You shall stay in this room before you are old enough to get married.
Don't you dare to step into my room!
Actually, I'll be old enough in a week.
That's not the problem now, Gu!
I've been an adult for almost ten years.
But I have been keeping myself busy for a kid like you,
who isn't even old enough to get married. I...
I am only five years younger than you.
That is not the problem.
Five years ago, I had already graduated and secured a job.
But you were not even an adult.
You hadn't even completed your college entrance exam.
No way! This is too scary.
Unbelievable!
Miss Jin!
I am not a minor.
Rongrong's husband-to-be is still a student?
Not only that.
He's an undergraduate who hasn't even graduated from the university.
I think... there must be more to it.
Don't be suspicious.
Considering her personality, this must be a lie she told to deal with Mr. Jin.
Jin Rongrong's getting married... Could it be an arranged marriage?
This concerns your status in the Jin family.
Wu Youyong, you stole my idea and made me take the blame for you.
Don't let me see you again!
Liang Jingjing, you...
I am sorry! I am sorry!
Stop there!
- Who is she?
- I'm doomed!
An intern of our company.
Liang Jingjing! Why are you here?
I am talking to you!
Mr. Jin and Mr. Wu, you got the wrong person.
You...
When did she come in?
Since when did she eavesdrop on our conversation?
Shall we make her...?
Did we say anything just now?
I... I think we said... What did we say?
Qiu Bi, you should know what to say when Old Jin asks you. Right?
I know. I shall never let Mr. Jin know that Student Gu has not turned 22 years old
and that he is ineligible to get married.
I shall tell Mr. Jin that you
and him are quite intimate
and are spending a good time together. Right?
That's right!
Don't move!
She...
What did she want you to tell me?
Ms. Jin is worried that you might send her for another blind date,
so she asked me to let you know
that she and Student Gu are spending a good time together.
As a boy, you should protect yourself when you stay at someone else's place.
Ms. Jin's first love doesn't seem to be normal.
It's more like one-sided love.
Let go!
One-sided love? I don't think so.
Let me show you this.
Mr. Jin, did you capture this?
How is it? They look sweet together. Right?
Yes!
Sweet?
I have liked Gu since he was young.
In the past, I always felt awkward.
After all, Rongrong is five years older than him.
But look at them now.
They look good together.
Mr. Jin,
If I tell you a secret about Ms. Jin and Student Gu,
will you give me a pay rise?
20%.
Ms. Jin and Student Gu met each other before the blind date.
They went home and...
Qiu Bi, do you want more year-end bonuses?
[Primary school, pre-school]
7 plus... 6 years of compulsory education,
[University, high school, middle school]
3 years of high school and middle school, and 4 years of university.
[23 years old]
He should be old enough to get married. Right?
Is he lying to me because he regrets it now?
He's even a straight-A student.
He's handsome and his handwriting is pretty good, too.
Just this?
Pitiful boy. I shall send you some money.
You have received 100,000 yuan.
Did he hide it under his pillow?
Gu Congbei.
Is it under the blanket?
It is not under the blanket.
Pocket...
Where is his pocket?
"As a boy, you should protect yourself when you stay at someone else's place."
Don't worry. I didn't lie to you.
I will turn 22 in seven days.
[Gu Congbei]
[Birthday: November 11th, 1999]
What about this?
Let's register for our marriage seven days later, on your birthday.
You can spare the betrothal presents. I don't need the money.
But let me know if you need my dowry.
I don't need them either.
Please don't do sneak attacks in the middle of the night again, Miss Jin.
[You have a new message]
[Refund received]
You brat!
♫ You said that you like rainbows ♫
♫ The sunlight and rain are just like our wonderful love ♫
♫ You like your every single second with me ♫
♫ Afraid that I won't hug you anymore ♫
♫ But you never know ♫
A reminder! Five days to go.
Don't you run away!
Got it.
Good night!
♫ How wonderful the smile from your lip corners is ♫
♫ I don't need to think because my heart is racing ♫
♫ The love between us is obvious to everyone ♫
♫ The exclusive love that you gave me ♫
♫ You are cute like a kitten ♫
♫ Making me agree with you unconditionally ♫
♫ The pink tune between us keeps track of our noisy nights ♫
Ms. Jin, could you sign this?
I am getting married at 10:00 a.m. the day after tomorrow.
Make sure my schedule is free.
[Mr. Jin, the latest good news!]
[Ms. Jin is marrying Student Gu in two days.]
[Okay. That's great! Keep me updated with the good news.]
That's all for this meeting.
♫ Afraid that I won't hug you anymore ♫
Bei,
I'm not working today. Let's have dinner together!
Sorry. I've got something to do. Let's take a rain check.
♫ How wonderful the smile from your lip corners is ♫
♫ I don't need to think because my heart is racing ♫
♫ The love between us is obvious to everyone ♫
♫ The exclusive love that you gave me ♫
♫ You are cute like a kitten ♫
♫ Making me agree with you unconditionally ♫
♫ The pink tune between us keeps track of our noisy nights ♫
♫ And the trace of our love ♫
♫ Everything is just right ♫
Wait a minute.
Done.
Let's do this!
Hurry up!
I am sorry. You can't do this for your marriage certificate photo.
Let's do this then!
♫ The exclusive love that you gave me ♫
I am sorry. You can't do this either.
♫ Making me agree with you unconditionally ♫
♫ The pink tune between us keeps track of our noisy nights ♫
♫ And the trace of our love ♫
♫ Everything is just right ♫
Okay! This is good!
Closer.
Qiu Bi.
Seriously?
Give me 40 minutes.
I am only out for half an hour. Why can't you solve it yourselves?
Wait for me!
I am sorry. I need to go back to the office for an urgent matter.
- Shall I send you to the university first?
- It's fine. Go ahead.
Are you sure?
I'm not a primary school student.
All right. University student, I'm leaving.
- Do you think... it is better to keep our marriage a secret at this stage?
- Miss Jin.
After all, you are still a student.
Up to you.
Okay, I shall return to my office then.
Submit your proposal to me by next week, then.
- Let's call it a day.
- Okay.
How's your marriage?
Student Gu is so calm and quiet. I got the right guy.
Great choice!
Oh, right! Mr. Jin is waiting for you in your office.
He wants to talk to you about the development plan.
Just keep him waiting. I need to buy something first.
What are you buying? Trust it with me.
- Why do you have to do it personally?
- I need to choose it personally.
I got it!
This is strange.
Why doesn't she have a fridge in her house?
Let's have dinner together at home after I get off work.
Okay! I'll wait for you.
Mr. Jin, you have waited for me for a day?
Rongrong,
I heard that you sprained your ankle.
I brought you some ointments so that you can keep them in your office.
You heard about it?
I sprained my ankle a week ago. You even know that?
Right...
Before your mother married into the Jin family,
she would always visit us even when Old Jin only had a slight cough.
Rongrong, I don't mean anything else.
I have something to add regarding the New City Area Development Plan.
Mr. Jin,
we don't need to discuss business outside of working hours. Right?
I just want to do my best in this matter with you.
I know Old Jin's plan very well.
He's just trying to give me some pressure.
I understand.
Considering how stingy I am,
I'm not willing to share my family's money with my ex-classmate. That's sure.
Qiu Bi, let's have a meeting five minutes from now.
I just want to do my best in this plan with you.
I've always been professional at work.
Since Old Jin has given you this opportunity, let's see who has the last laugh.
I am still working. Let's talk later.
When will you...?
Are you awake?
You're back.
I'm sorry. Something came up at the last minute.
Were you waiting for me?
No.
I was doing my homework.
Did you cook all these?
I don't even have a kitchen at home, but you managed to cook all these.
Heat them up if you are hungry.
I'm going back to my room.
Wait a minute.
I have something to show you.
Come on.
I am used to living alone.
I don't know what to prepare if two people are to live together,
so let's first change our toothbrushes, cups, and toothpaste into matching pairs.
I spent a long time choosing them.
Also...
I bought matching towels too.
This color is for me.
The blue one is for you.
If you like this color, you can take it too.
Did you...
- choose all of them personally?
- Yes.
Of course, I have to choose our things personally.
Do you like them?
There are more.
You bought me this mug last time.
I bought you another one, too.
They are a pair.
Today is an important day.
I want to do one more thing.
Come here.
Sit here.
Wait for me.
Today is not only the day of us getting married.
It is also your birthday.
I hope that you can stay happy every day after getting married.
♪ Happy birthday to you! Happy birthday to you ♪
♪ Happy birthday to... ♪
♪ Happy birthday to... ♪ Hurry up! Make a wish!
Make a wish! Hurry up!
Hurry up! Your wish won't come true after 12:00 a.m.
Hurry up! Make a wish!
Hurry up! What are you waiting for?
Why are you not making a wish?
Hurry up! Make a wish! Hurry up...
♫ Please don't rain ♫
♫ I can't make it to the shelter ♫
♫ Curling up on the sofa, staring at the phone ♫
♫ Still no reply to the message, and I can't miss anything ♫
♫ If this isn't love ♫
♫ Why are there traces of it pacing up and down in my heart ♫
♫ The cruelty with a little pain is piling up in the corner ♫
[Don't leave, there's an Easter egg!]
Let me see what nickname you saved for me.
[Miss Jin]
Miss Jin?
How formal it is.
[Edit nickname and tags]
[Stay tuned for the next episode]
[My boss]
[It's said that everyone will only fall in love once.]
[Every romance after that is simply us seeking his or her shadow.]
♫ But time changed the whole century ♫
♫ You willfully gave up everything significant ♫
♫ You ran away after only writing half a story
or you worried too much ♫
♫ I want to see you, hold you, love you ♫
♫ I want to love you, hug you, I can't help it ♫
♫ Please don't rain ♫
♫ I can't make it to the shelter ♫
♫ Curling up on the sofa, staring at the phone ♫
♫ Still no reply to the message, and I can't miss anything ♫
♫ If this isn't love ♫
♫ Why are there traces of it pacing up and down in my heart ♫
♫ The cruelty with a little pain is piling up in the corner ♫