[Episode 4]
I told you to look into Liang Jingjing,
but why did you sneak photos at Rongrong's office?
Liang Jingjing can participate in the New City Area Development Plan,
so she must have some connections.
Her real information is definitely inside Ms. Jin's office.
And?
Liang Jingjing's information in Ms. Jin's office is the same as that in HR.
So, she isn't a spy.
Spy?
Rongrong placed a spy in her own company's project, instead of other companies?
Are you stupid?
[JC. Group]
That makes sense.
Think about your explanation.
Follow me to apologize to Rongrong later.
Yes.
Xichen,
when I was hiding in the wardrobe,
I saw that Gu guy secretly using Ms. Jin's computer.
Speak.
What shady things were you up to that you had to hide in the wardrobe?
I was dragged in by them.
And then, someone let out a very smelly fart,
and then you came.
No, why did you look at me when you talked about fart?
Wu Youyong was the one who farted. Can I let out a fart that smelly?
It's you!
Is this what matters?
Go out first.
You, come back!
I... I just came in to take some photos.
Then I entered the wardrobe and saw Wu Youyong!
He was also taking photos. And he farted...
- Speak. What did Old Jin ask you to do?
- Old Jin...
- How did you know Mr. Jin asked me to come?
- Of course!
Is he your father or mine?
Mr. Jin asked me to take some photos of... you and Gu's... daily office romance.
Give me the camera.
- I really didn't capture anything much...
- Now!
Give it to me!
Rongrong.
Enough for you.
Rongrong, I want to talk to you about something.
Mr. Jin, you entered my office without knocking.
You must be in a rush.
How can I help?
Wu Youyong saw that Gu fellow using your computer in your office.
Every time he appears, the timing is so coincidental.
Aren't you the least bit suspicious?
Firstly, he isn't "that Gu fellow."
He's my husband.
Is there a problem with my husband using my computer in my office?
Next, why did you, Mr. Jin,ask Wu Youyong to secretly come to my office?
This is a misunderstanding.
I wasn't trying to pick on him.
Ever since you accepted me as a member of the Jin family,
we are siblings.
- Can we work together for once?
- Jin Xichen.
Let me make it clear to you again.
JC Group is my company.
I accepted you as a member of the Jin family because I'm grateful that you saved me.
Other than maintaining a superficial relationship with you, I will not work with you.
Even if you do not believe me,
for the interest of the company,
you should check the security footage.
[Destined to Meet You]
[New City Area Development Project]
[Construction Project Tender]
[Tender]
[520,424,011 yuan]
Impressive.
You got Jin Rongrong's base bid price so easily.
Good for you.
Make sure you keep your promise.
Return my mother's building to me.
If not, there's nothing I won't resort to.
How can you speak to your elder brother like that?
That building is useless to us.
But I overestimated Jin Rongrong.
Independent woman?
She's just a brainless, rich beauty who is greedy for handsome men.
She got cheated by a gigolo like you.
Watch your mouth.
Don't! I was kidding, kidding!
That brat...
Wait till I get my hands on the land, I'll let you suffer!
This little brat is pretty strong.
[Security Footage 02-31-23]
[Trash]
[Are you sure you want to permanently delete this file?] [Yes]
You haven't eaten?
Didn't I ask you to come back earlier?
Why did you just come home?
I...
Something urgent cropped up at the university.
I went back for a while.
Next time, get Qiu Bi to fetch you.
Let's eat.
It's okay, I've eaten. You should dig in.
Wait.
What happened to your face?
Earlier, I...
I accidentally bumped into something.
- I'll get going.
- Wait.
Come with me.
[First aid kit]
I said I'm fine.
Don't move.
Do you know why I haven't had a good relationship with Old Jin since I was a child?
He wants to care about me, understand me,
but he never says that out loud.
He always does things behind my back.
Like today, he got Qiu Bi to secretly enter my office.
If I didn't know Qiu Bi any better, I would think he was a spy.
Bei,
why did you go to my office today?
I told you that I just went to meet you.
I need to take this call.
Okay, I got it.
Qiu Bi called to say that Old Jin fell and broke his leg.
Is it serious?
He needs surgery. I'll be at the hospital the whole day tomorrow.
Bei, for tomorrow's bidding for the New City Area Development Plan,
I authorize you to go on my behalf.
Can you do it?
Thank you.
I'm going to the hospital.
♫ Meteors want to tell you how deeply they're in love ♫
♫ Trying to draw the biggest arc in the night sky ♫
♫ My wandering mind is occupied by you ♫
♫ I can no longer reach your world ♫
♫ I remember you turning around and saying thank you ♫
Please.
Do not waste the chance I'm giving you.
♫ Your tears were rolling down your cheek ♫
♫ I'm used to looking at your photos ♫
♫ Surviving tough times after falling in love with you ♫
♫ Refusing anyone who reached out to help ♫
♫ Waiting for the peaceful decomposition of time ♫
♫ I'm at the tipping point of depression ♫
♫ Having memories take up my personal time ♫
♫ Casting my mind back to the past, again and again ♫
What's the result?
The two brothers of the Gu family won the bid.
♫ I remember you turning around and saying thank you ♫
What about him?
He gave up on the bid on your behalf.
♫ Your tears were rolling down your cheek ♫
[Stay tuned for the next episode]
♫ Surviving tough times after falling in love with you ♫
Rongrong, why did you let Gu Congbei bid for the company?
He gave up the bid.
Who's going to bear the consequences?
There are no consequences for anyone to bear.
Jin Rongrong, you're letting your emotions get the best of you!
Jin Xichen, you're too arrogant.
Since the day I've known you, you've always overestimated your capabilities.
You kept trying to get me on board with the New City Area Development Plan.
Now you know the reason I rejected you.
This land has a risk of sinking.
Old Jin had given us many clues throughout the project,
including how this land has been pumping underground water in excess.
But you were too eager to prove yourself and ignored all the warning signs.
To put it simply, this land may look lucrative on the surface, but in fact,
whoever wins the bid will end up with nothing but a mess.
Now you understand.
Giving up the bid was the best choice.
You're looking for me?
I heard it'll rain tonight.
I have a car even if it rains.
And I have an umbrella in the car.
Even if there isn't, Qiu Bi will deliver one to me.
Gu Congbei, if you're still trying to hide the truth from me,
please refrain from appearing before me for the time being.
♫ But I can only wait for a sunny day ♫
♫ You took away my weakness and complicated feelings ♫
♫ And I couldn't stop my heart from fluttering ♫
Ms. Jin, why are you still here?
Something urgent cropped up. I need to handle this first.
♫ You willfully gave up everything significant ♫
♫ You ran away after only writing half a story
or you worried too much ♫
Bei is still waiting for you.
♫ I want to see you, hold you ♫
♫ I want to love you, hug you, I can't help it ♫
Let him wait.
♫ I can't make it to the shelter ♫
Excuse me.
The rain is so heavy!
Let's go.
Come.
♫ If this isn't love ♫
♫ Why are there traces of it pacing up and down in my heart ♫
♫ The cruelty with a little pain is piling up in the corner ♫
♫ Please don't rain ♫
♫ I can't make it to the shelter ♫
♫ Curling up on the sofa, staring at the phone ♫
♫ Still no reply to the message, and I can't miss anything ♫
♫ If this isn't love ♫
♫ Why are there traces of it pacing up and down in my heart ♫
♫ The cruelty with a little pain is piling up in the corner ♫
Miss Jin.
It's barely raining now.
No need for an umbrella.
It's still drizzling.
Let's go home first.
Wait.
Hear me out before you decide whether to let me go home with you.
Here, have some water.
Jingjing, do you mind getting her a warm one?
You've made a good observation of me.
You must have done your homework trying to get close to me.
This is one of your habits I discovered after we got married.
I know you're sensitive to low temperatures, hence we don't have a fridge at home.
The air-conditioner needs to be maintained at 26°C.
All your drinks must not contain ice.
What would happen if I didn't quit and just handed the documents over?
So you expected it all along. I was worried that...
That I'd be deceived by you?
Or were you worried that I wouldn't notice what was wrong with this plan?
I...
Ms. Jin, Bei has his reasons.
Explain!
Jingjing, you're still young and gullible.
Be it a man or a boy, all of them share the same problem.
They will never be able to treat you with honesty.
Before the entire thing is set in stone, I wasn't sure if you'd believe me.
However, only by making the two brothers of the Gu family completely believe the reason I got close to you,
would they bid with everything they have.
Now, they're debt-ridden.
After some time, when the land begins to give them troubles,
they will come to me and sell their shares.
Then, I can recover all of my mother's assets.
I'll be able to protect my mother's lifetime of hard work.
I'm sorry for not telling you about this sooner.
Tell me the truth, then.
Since when did you plan to get close to me?
From the day I showed up at the Gu family's place?
Or that chance meeting outside the pub in the alley?
I've been trying to approach you since you appeared in the pub.
Gu Congbei, you sure planned for everything.
Do you believe in love at first sight?
- Even without this, I will also...
- What "love at first sight"?
Do I look like a 17-year-old to you?
Why would I believe something as ridiculous as "love at first sight"?
Ridiculous?
When you asked for us to get married, you said you fell for me at first sight!
Don't tell me...
you simply made that up to dupe me into marrying you?
What do you mean by "duping you"?
I proposed to you fair and square!
You said yes yourself!
Since we're on the topic, didn't you lie to me as well?
The reason why I hid a part of the truth
is that I believed this entire thing would not compromise your interests in any way!
Jingjing, come here.
Look at him and remember what an arrogant man looks like.
Also, if in the future, a man tells you anything about "love at first sight,"
you must never believe him.
Yes.
In the future, if any woman tells me about "love at first sight," I'll never fall for that again!
You're married to me!
Who else do you wish to hear "love at first sight" from?!
Wait a minute!
Shouldn't you guys be untangling the misunderstanding over the development plan?
What's that got to do with "love at first sight"?
Is that important?
- It is!
Ms. Jin.
Ms. Jin, calm down! Ms. Jin.
Ms. Jin, calm...
What's wrong with you?
If I were Ms. Jin, I'd be fuming mad too!
I didn't want to pick up a fight.
She's doing this for you.
To lure those two dummies from the Gu family into the trap, she pushed the plan forward on purpose.
Be more mindful!
[Divorce Agreement]
Miss Jin, I will not sign the divorce agreement.
I didn't get married to divorce!
Not for divorce, but for the assets.
- What kind of melodrama is this?
- Open up, Miss Jin.
We need to talk this over. I admit this entire thing...
Miss Jin! Miss Jin!
Am I your roommate? Don't I have a name?
I called you Miss Jin because you're the one who kept calling me Gu.
- As a form of respect, I could only call you "Miss Jin."
- Respect?
If you truly respect me, why would you stay the night at my place on the first day we met?
I stayed the night because you complained it was cold.
You were crying and making a fuss.
In that situation, how could I leave you alone?
Did you forget how I took care of you all night?
Something like that happened?
What about before?
Why did you follow me home?
You were just horny!
I'm horny?
I'm horny?! Did you forget what you did to me?
What did I do?
This!
Then...
♫ The setting sun dashed past the sky without a sound ♫
♫ Like how I chased after you over endless miles ♫
I see it now, Gu Congbei.
You were the one who swapped my Long Island iced tea for alcohol.
- Swapped for alcohol?
- I was surprised!
I ordered tea. Why did it become alcohol?
I can't believe you'd stoop so low to use me!
While I certainly did try to get close to you,
Long Island iced tea isn't tea but a cocktail.
I don't believe you.
Take a look yourself, here.
So?
So it's not tea but a cocktail!
So you're pissing me off over a glass of Long Island iced tea?
I...
Long Island iced tea really is tea and not a cocktail!
Is that important?
[It doesn't matter whether Long Island iced tea is a cocktail or not.]
Long Island iced tea is really a cocktail?
How did I not know about that?
So embarrassing.
Why is it so cold?
I'm sorry, I was...
Tonight, I'm sleeping in your room.
Why did you suddenly lay down in my room?
If I sleep in your room, you can just go sleep in mine.
I won't.
Are you trying to prank me?
Hurry and go back to your own room.
Or else, I'll...
♫ The neon lights flash while the wind blows ♫
♫ We meet at the bar down the street ♫
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have argued with you
about whether Long Island iced tea is actually tea.
♫ Fate has no loopholes ♫
You and I...
♫ It can't control you or me ♫
Why are you in my room?
This is my room.
I'm not cold anymore.
The bed is warm, too. You go sleep in my room.
My AC is broken.
- Jin Rongrong, are you crazy?
- Just pretend I am.
Get out.
Set the AC to 26 degrees.
So my purpose is to warm the bed?
You used to eat ice cream?
You were much cuter before.
[My boss]
I'm not switching rooms with you again.
Gu Congbei, come over here. I feel terrible.
I'm coming right now.
How is it? Did you fix it?
The program's not working, it's probably broken.
What should we do?
Can someone come to fix it today?
- We'll find someone tomorrow.
- No.
This house is too cold.
If it's too cold, add another duvet.
I'm going to freeze to death.
I'll go to a hotel instead.
- The hotel is warmer.
- Miss Jin.
Miss Jin, what's wrong?
- Are you all right?
- Why is it suddenly broken?
It was fine this morning.
What's happened?
Miss Jin.
Miss Jin, look at me.
Take a deep breath. Deep breath.
Try it.
Deep breath.
- I can't.
- How are you feeling?
I'm still so cold.
Miss Jin.
I'm so cold. So cold.
Someone broke it on purpose.
♫ Quick, listen to the voice in your heart ♫
♫ It seems to be quite piercing ♫
♫ Becoming more steadfast, wishing to hug you tight ♫
♫ This time, I'll observe you carefully ♫
♫ You're the one who came into my life ♫
♫ And told me happiness can be easily reached ♫
♫ You are irreplaceable in my dreams ♫
♫ Meeting you again until the dream ends ♫
♫ Waiting for the next shooting star ♫
♫ To realize the promise we made ♫
♫ We'll never be apart again ♫
♫ Forget about keeping a safe distance ♫
♫ Your embrace gives me all the courage I need ♫
♫ Waiting for the next shooting star ♫
♫ Watch time flow through your eyes ♫
♫ Go on a journey with me ♫
♫ Not thinking of the deep philosophy ♫
♫ Only the both of us existing in this moment ♫
Dig in.
Thank you for last night.
I'm very sensitive to temperature.
- But about the...
- Rongrong.
What did you call me?
Rongrong.
Why didn't you call me Miss Jin?
You don't like it when I call you Miss Jin.
So starting today, I'll call you Rongrong.
Is that okay?
That works. It's just a name.
Marrying you wasn't originally part of my plan.
I did take advantage of you.
I'm sorry.
But from the moment I agreed to marry you,
I treated this seriously.
Also, I said to you in the beginning
that once I get married, I won't get divorced.
Rongrong, I want to live happily with you...
for the rest of my life.
I...
I'll think about it.
You need to think about it?
Rongrong, stop thinking about it.
Rongrong.
If you don't believe me, we can do it your way.
We can sign a contract.
Rongrong.
If one's not enough,
we can sign two!
Rongrong!
Rongrong.
I said I would think about it.
♫ You said that you like rainbows ♫
Wait!
♫ You like your every single second with me ♫
♫ Afraid that I won't hug you anymore ♫
He wants to kiss me goodbye?
♫ That I want to be by your side forever ♫
♫ How wonderful the smile from your lip corners is ♫
♫ I don't need to think because my heart is racing ♫
♫ The love between us is obvious to everyone ♫
♫ The exclusive love that you gave me ♫
See you tonight.
♫ Making me agree with you unconditionally ♫
♫ The pink tune between us keeps track of our noisy nights ♫
Hello, Mr. Qiu.
I am Gu Congbei.
Sir.
[Gu Congbei's actions]
I promise this info is true.
Gu Congbei plotted all this to get closer to Rongrong.
Xichen, if you put your attention on your projects,
I trust that you will have found the problem with that land long ago.
Sir.
Bei did approach Rongrong with ulterior motives.
But he's never done anything to hurt the Jin family.
You know they are still young.
A few words and pictures don't mean anything.
Since they are already married, let them solve their problems on their own.
You are their senior, so you should be more forgiving toward Bei.
No matter how much I care about the company,
at the end of the day, I'm still seen as an outsider.
Ms. Liang, you're here.
Didn't I say to not call me Ms. Liang?
Mr. Jin?
Mr. Jin, why did you drink so much?
Every time I see you,
I get very unlucky.
Then I'll disappear.
Mr. Jin?
Ms. Liang, are you leaving?
I told you not to call me Ms. Liang!
You mean Rongrong was locked up in a reefer truck five years ago?
One that transported ice cream, actually.
That's why she's so sensitive to the temperature.
Did someone plan the incident?
Ms. Jin doesn't like talking about this.
Student Gu, you need to first promise me that you won't tell her I told you this.
Ms. Jin said that it was a pure accident.
She was trying to save a cat so she went into the reefer truck and unexpectedly got locked in.
The truck's freezing system was suddenly turned on.
If Mr. Jin didn't find her in time, the result might have been horrible.
Ms. Jin doesn't want to remember this incident, so she just let it pass.
[Stay tuned for the next episode]
[It's said that everyone will only fall in love once.]
[Every romance after that is simply us seeking his or her shadow.]
♫ The setting sun dashed past the sky without a sound ♫
♫ Like how I chased after you over endless miles ♫
♫ Could it be the secret of the galaxy ♫
♫ Leaving no trace even as they chase after the starry sky ♫
♫ Imagining the distance between us,
I can't stop thinking about you ♫
♫ Like there is now something more between us ♫
♫ I'll take you to the Milky Way,
becoming smitten by your gentle look ♫
♫ A journey to the stars, no matter how far ♫
♫ The clouds stole a sip of the wine I hid on the rooftop ♫
♫ Led away by the night wind while slightly tipsy ♫
♫ Accidentally bumping into your chest ♫
♫ Quietly hiding behind the stars ♫