(tarot cards)
(This program is sponsored by the Broadcasting and Communications Development Fund of the Ministry of Science, Technology, Information and Communications Technology)
(This drama is purely fictitious. The characters, place names, group events, medical terms, etc. have nothing to do with the facts. It is hereby stated that the child actors were filmed in a safe environment)
Mom I'm scared
Mom, I'm scared. Open the door quickly, Mom.
Emily's mother is busy
Open the door quickly and go back to sleep
I told you I'm busy
Why is your child so sensitive?
What's up
Strange noises can always be heard in the room
I already told you it was the water heater. How many times do you have to tell me?
No, it's completely different from that voice.
Let her go back quickly, won't you?
What did you say? Be careful not to be overheard by the children.
I told you it was the hot water heater. Go back and go to bed.
I'm scared
Go back to bed quickly. Mom is busy.
What's this
Eun San, is this your thing?
not mine
Go back to your room quickly, really
(tarot cards)
(Mom in the rental area)
Yingzhi’s mother is here. Isn’t she here yet?
I asked her to park the car
There's an asbestos smell in the underground parking lot recently
But doesn’t her daughter think it’s a bit immature?
I heard that Youngji occasionally said strange things to Eunsan
They are playing together there
Be careful if she hears you
She is also lucky
We never interact with residents in rental housing estates
That's right
Why do high-end communities have to interact with rental housing estates?
We study hard
Not to hang out with poor people
Don't say that they are still children.
What's wrong
what happened emily
Hello Zheng Enshan
are you kidding me
I saw you when you came out
Damn why is the room so messy?
Why did I take out all my cosmetics?
("Spider and the Candy Shop")
hateful
This dust is really annoying
Zheng Eunshan, I have seen you
Come out quickly, really
Yingzhi, what are you doing?
sorry
Hello Zheng Enshan
what the hell are you doing
Mom was scared, right?
You are so abominable
Hey mom, I'm going out to meet my friends.
Do you know how to restore the room before coming back?
don't want
Why
tidy up
knew
Can I take off my makeup now?
What do you say?
You put this in my mother's room, right?
I didn't put it there
who would it be if it wasn't you
Don't you often do strange things?
Bring it to me to see
I know this thing
Isn't it just an ordinary card?
This naked woman is a god
Behind is the Big Dipper
The water is flowing
From this water will be born human beings and create the world
so what
That is to say, your mother is praised as a god
Isn't it because your mother is supporting you?
Where is your husband?
Business trip
Oh my God, how could this happen after only a short time?
Yingzhi mother
I've kept you waiting for a long time, haven't I?
If not, I just came here
Thanks for your hard work
Oh, there's no need to do this.
What happened in Eun-san's room just now?
Nothing
They are playing with cosmetics
Turning into a ghost scared me a lot
Could it be that Yingzhi took advantage of your cosmetics without permission?
Such expensive cosmetics
I can't stand it
My Yingzhi is a bit special
If you use it too much, I'll buy one for you.
what is this
Do I want you to pay for the cosmetics?
yes
That's it
Yinghao's mother is
This is 500,000 won, but it looks like street food.
What do you think of the fabric?
Just wear it for a season and throw it away.
Buy it first
So be it
Good style
Mother Yingzhi, why don’t you buy some? The price is okay too
Um
Every time like this she would pretend to be on the phone
Shopping is really not an easy activity
Thanks
Yingzhi’s mother, this is not an expensive thing.
Last time I noticed the collar of your shirt was loose and dirty.
Let me wear this for you
No
This is not expensive
for you
Thanks
Do you prefer zombie makeup or vampire makeup?
What's the difference
Don’t you even know this?
Really stupid
Do you prefer faceless male makeup or clown makeup?
Don't like either of them
All right
Then put on zombie makeup
Because of you, I also became a zombie
what did I do
Didn't you see this?
How can you blame me?
Shut up
I was just trying to help you...
I told you to shut up
You go home
My mother said she would wait here for her return
So what does it have to do with me?
Go away, go away
let me help you
Get away
Hello, are you okay?
The size should be OK
certainly
very beautiful
hope you like it
like
I'll get it, okay
So annoying
I will accept it in the end
But you have to pretend to save face
Why did you give her clothes?
Of course I owed it to her as a favor.
Otherwise, why would you give it to her?
Or if it weren't for her daughter
Something big happened to Eun San at that time
How can there be stray dogs in such a high-end community?
You only paid attention to her because of the sentiment at the time.
But this relationship should be broken off, right?
Why to break
The problem is that she doesn't know what's going on
I thought she would leave voluntarily if we gave her a wink.
did not expect…
Because I want to get along well with Eun San
Only if you can keep this relationship in the future will you delay leaving.
This is obvious
Very clever
that is
brazen
I know
Why
It's so noisy
not me
It rang from your place
Damn it's so annoying
Curious?
Yesterday you went to the bathroom
I saw it when I was alone
What did you see again?
Things always fall off there
Drop something
A woman fell three times on her head from there.
Bang bang bang
Didn't you see any traces there?
You are so annoying
Scared?
What are you afraid of?
I'm not afraid
By the way, Yingzhi’s mother
There will be a gathering for mothers in our community this Saturday
You go too
Mom in the community?
Yes
It’s a gathering of mothers of Eun-san’s classmates
You can go too, okay?
Wisdom
Yingzhi, don’t you say hello?
yes
goodbye
Ah, see you next time
Thanks
be careful on the road
good
Wisdom
Do you and Eun San not get along well?
I've been trying my best to endure it.
Mom, I'm sorry
Emily where are you
I'm in the living room
Why don't you call me without looking for me?
Hey, how can you find a house this big?
Not a big deal
Didn't you and Yingzhi have any unpleasant incident today?
she is very annoyed
She is the only one living in the rental housing complex
I heard everything you said
Eun San
I said you can't be picky when it comes to eating.
Eat junk food occasionally to improve your immunity
I don’t want it if you don’t want it
Why is this kid so rude?
hateful
Eunsan Eunsan
You slept too long too
Yingzhi is here, get up quickly
You two have fun
So annoying
What's wrong
Hey, what did you mean yesterday?
What to say about a woman falling off
Want to know? You can see it too
What's the meaning
Then let me show you
Is there a washbasin?
Also need mirrors and matches
I don't know. It should be in the kitchen.
Go get it
If you take Yingzhi’s mother with you,
You won't be disliked by them, right?
Blame us for lowering their level
Will not
The community residents regard us as angels
After all, no one cares about the residents of the rental community.
Anyway, you know what the plan is for today?
Eun San’s mother, you can’t pretend to be nice again.
When did I have you again?
If it happens again I will ignore you
What's wrong
It's nothing, maybe it's just dazzling
boring
Is the water surface moving?
Of course if you put a match just now it will move.
are you a fool
Then I'm going to start
Close your eyes and never look in the mirror
good
Bloody Mary Bloody Mary Bloody Mary…
The woman just came to the mirror
If you have anything to ask, just ask.
Who are you
I'm the one who's always lived here
She said she knows you very well
Why fall from above?
because she made a mistake
Said he made a big mistake in this house
So what can we do to drive her away?
have no idea
She said it depends on your performance
Didn't I tell you not to look in the mirror?
You're bored and don't want to play anymore
Are you really not playing anymore?
But maybe we can drive her away
Forget it, I won’t play with you anymore
Late and late
Who is this…
She is Yingzhi’s mother
Say hello to Yingzhi’s mother.
Hello everyone
Our children are all classmates
We all live in the same neighborhood and this is the first time we have met.
Does Yingzhi’s mother also live in Building 3?
I live in building 10
I see. It turns out you live in the building at the back.
No wonder
So what?
We are all parents in the same class
yes
That's right
That's right, that's right
right
That's right
They're all in the same class
Anyway, today is a regular gathering day
Let’s discuss the matter of children attending classes in groups during the holidays
Isn’t that pretty good too?
So we will charge by group every month...
some dues
Yes, let’s collect the membership fee first.
Two million won per person, right?
Yingzhi’s mother doesn’t need to pay
Anyway…
Yingzhi’s mother didn’t accept it
Teacher’s courses…Consulting services
Course consulting services refer to…
I mean, have you ever had any consultation?
You and the class teacher
You never called me alone
Then you must not have heard about Yingzhi either, right?
Is it about Yingzhi?
You also know that her grades have dropped significantly, right?
To be honest, her English ability is not up to standard.
Well, just treat it as if it had just been transferred here not long ago.
I heard that when the children are together
He often does strange things
What strange behavior did she do?
For example, stealing something
She said her hands and feet were unclean
Originally, she gave people a rather gloomy impression.
At least she can still play with Eun San
I heard that the children often isolate her
There's nothing wrong with Yingzhi
She never said anything to me
no problem
I didn’t say anything. How can I talk to my mother?
Yes, it must be difficult to speak
That's right. It must be difficult to speak.
I...go to the bathroom first
good
Don't know how to observe words and emotions at all
What should I do?
What's up
Is there a restroom here?
If you are not a resident of Buildings 1 to 5
(Non-smoking apartment)
You can't go in or out of this place
Can I use the bathroom temporarily?
You can use the restroom in the mall over there.
It's too far over there
Yingzhi mother
You don't have a keycard here?
I am a resident
OK, please come in.
Hello
There are a lot of people today.
Looks like we have to wait a while
Are you OK
Damn it, no, I said no
my doll
Why is it missing? I'm so annoyed.
Hello
Didn't you say you wanted that before?
right
What does it mean
It's impossible to disappear suddenly
Anyway, I didn’t take it
I haven't asked you yet. How can you answer first?
Ah, it seems you are feeling guilty, right?
I told you I didn't take it
Just look for it again
I don't like you from the beginning
Your family is still so poor
Only your house is a rented house
What does it matter?
From the moment I played with you
I heard a strange sound in the room
The doll was also stolen by you
I said it wasn't me
Yeah
That's what your mother took away
Your mother is also a beggar like you
Isn't it? Yingzhi
Don't talk about my mother
What can you do
Hello
hateful
Mother
Come on, help me pull her away from Emily
Let it go, let it go, what do you want to do?
She stole my doll
I told you it's not me
So you beggar
Hello
Hey, damn, loosen up!
Emily let's go
You're here, come in
correct
Let’s go to Eun-san’s room and have a chat.
Put on slippers
Yingzhi mother
can you tell me the truth
Have you seen that doll?
That was Eun San's favorite but it's missing
But Eun San said
She saw with her own eyes that Yingzhi took it away
Isn't that quite big?
Yingzhi didn’t get it back
I haven't seen such a doll at home
No
Think about it carefully
I think
It’s normal for children to have some conflicts among themselves
but
The mothers also said that Yingzhi’s hands and feet were unclean
Why do you even say that?
Yingzhi is not who you say he is
What
Could it be Eun San...
Are you lying?
After me…
Let’s ask Yingji later
Wait a moment
Stop for me, mother Yingzhi
I'm a little panicked
You come and go together because of us
I thought we were all the same friends
but not like this
Eun San's mother
Other mothers have said this
Why hang out with people in the tenement area?
without prejudice we
I just accepted you, don’t you know?
I wanted to always be on your side
do you know
All right
People should flock together
If you don't want to, then forget it.
You actually feel uncomfortable being with us, right?
No, it’s not what you said, Eun San’s mother
I turned around and looked for it
If not I would buy you a new one
Yingzhi mother
Do you know how much that is worth?
Can I still ask you to compensate me for one?
Let’s talk about Yingzhi’s mother
when you eat with us
Every time I say I'm full, I still look at other people's faces.
What's wrong
are you crying
it's so funny
Really
Not like a joke
The plan worked, right?
What's this
why is it here
Hey, is this what you hid?
No, I hid it
Show that to your mother quickly
After seeing it, you can drive away the ghosts
Are you lying again?
What is the relationship between ghosts and dolls?
Now my mother is being scolded for this.
So that's it
But what to do
This has nothing to do with me
Or should I destroy that doll now?
Or throw it out the window
It's like it never existed from the beginning
for you
ruin it with this
What are you talking about?
put the knife down
If you don't destroy it now
Maybe that ghost will follow you for the rest of your life.
Then I don't want to
This is your choice
Oh, Eun San’s mother was so terrible just now
That's right
Have we gone too far?
We need to treat Eunsan’s mother well
But this is also the sincerity of Eun San’s mother
On the contrary, it's quite good
Did you just see Yingzhi’s mother crying?
Oh, now that it’s reached this point, it’s time to admit it, right?
Yingzhi’s mother is also quite pitiful, right?
But how old is she?
How many candles should we put in?
Just insert one
Ignition is very troublesome
Really? Well
It should be fine if you insert it in the middle, okay?
It would be great if you can persist to this extent.
At least give it a blessing
Yingzhi mother
Happy birthday to you. Happy birthday to you…
Here comes the surprise
what happened
Isn't she here?
Are you out?
Oh my god
Come and help
Use force
pull up
What should I do
what to do
How to do how to do
sorry
I wanted to perform well
(No entry or exit cordon under investigation)
uncle
Is that true? What?
Several mothers who died after falling from the building here
Was it done by people from the rental area?
that
It's all rumors
They are not residents who live here at all.
Who is that person?
How did she get to know these mothers?
I don’t know. Since then
No one said they had seen her, right?
Okay, then I'll go first
Goodbye
They are the bad people
I will definitely find you a good friend this time
Um
I will listen to you carefully
You can't be too picky about people
Eat some junk food occasionally
Um
It's now
do not come
go away
Go away
let me help you
(Safety Rules for Children's Amusement Parks)
You stand behind me and don't come over.
go away
let me help you
do not come
Go away and don't come here
help me
(Children in rental communities are prohibited from entering and exiting the children's amusement park. Safety rules. Please take care of the amusement facilities. Please abide by the usage hours (9:00~18:00))
do not come
(The card of Hope and Longing reversed indicates disappointment and disillusionment)