[English subtitles are available]
[Beauty of Resilience]
[Episode 23]
Chen Yan!
Here.
Have some water.
Wangyue,
it's been many days.
Don't go there anymore.
Even if he turns into a corpse,
I have to dig him out.
But the generals and the soldiers...
I've told them to withdraw.
Then I'll do it myself.
Wangyue,
just take it as Chen Yan
was killed
at the battlefield.
Impossible.
He's not dead.
He must be waiting for me.
He's waiting for me now.
Wangyue,
wake up.
Chen Yan is dead.
He will never come back.
Wangyue.
You're awake.
Get up and eat something.
Sister.
Have some food.
We're worried about you.
Mu Nan.
Is he really
not coming back?
Wangyue.
♫The two ends that can't be cut off♫
♫The tears wet the opposite bank♫
♫How can I bear the separation if it's you who'll be with me♫
Chen Yan!
♫The loneliness that can't be cut off♫
♫Only our love is unchanging♫
♫The two ends that can't be cut off♫
♫I can't see through the dark night♫
You're back.
♫When the green mountains turn white-headed♫
♫Can we keep each other company♫
Is it really you?
♫I'm afraid you don't have enough clothes♫
Yes, it's me.
♫The night is so cold that it's hard to keep warm♫
You're not dead.
♫The two ends that can't be cut off♫
♫I can't see through the dark night♫
♫When the green mountains turn white-headed♫
♫Can we keep each other company♫
[Wei]
♫I'm afraid you don't have enough clothes♫
♫The night is so cold that it's hard to keep warm♫
Chen Yan! Chen Yan!
You brat.
♫I'm afraid you don't have enough clothes♫
I knew you were alive.
You really came back alive.
♫The night is so cold that it's hard to keep warm♫
Let me have a look at you.
How could I die?
You're so tough.
Chen Yan.
What happened?
Marshal,
I sank into quicksand that night.
But I didn't expect that
there was a secret tunnel down below.
That's why
I was able to survive.
Oh, really?
Yes.
It seems to be a secret tunnel dug by people in the past.
One tunnel leads to Gu City.
And the other
leads to the depths of the desert.
Let me ask you.
What's going on
between you and Wangyue?
Marshal,
we...
How dare you say "we?"
It's a mere waste that I've thought highly of you.
How dare you
covet the apple of my eye?
Father.
It has nothing to do with Chen Yan.
Shut up!
Marshal,
Wangyue and I love each other.
Please give us your blessing.
You're a nobody.
A toad wishes to eat swan meat.
Do you want to die?
If I have to give up my life
to be together with her,
I will die without regret.
Fine.
Now that you're not afraid of death,
today,
I'll grant your wish.
Father.
If you want to kill him, you have to kill me first.
Marshal,
I've died for Wangyue once.
I don't mind
dying again.
Attaboy!
That's what a man should say.
You
deserve my daughter.
Get up.
Silly boy.
Don't you want to?
Hurry and thank Father.
Thank you, Fath…
Marshal.
Pass my order.
Three days later,
we're holding a wedding for Princess Wangyue
and Chen Yan.
♫The warm breeze blows the flowers down, and who is as pretty as a picture♫
Great!
I'm getting married.
♫I wanted to say something but stopped because I can't tell my miss in three lives♫
♫I only hope I won't wake from this good dream and spend my life with you♫
♫But all the memories emerged and made us both upset♫
♫Between Heaven and Earth, I'm so in love that I struggle alone♫
Pass my order.
Three days later,
we're holding a wedding for Princess Wangyue
and Chen Yan.
♫My heart misses the glimmer and cannot let it go♫
♫I'd rather fall in love even if I know it's my fatal lot and I don't even have tears anymore♫
♫It's hard to choose and I have no one to express my love to♫
♫I won't leave my love and let's wait until spring comes♫
♫In this life, let's be happily together♫
Mu Nan.
Sister.
What are you doing?
Stuff for the wedding.
Didn't Marshal say
we're going to buy the stuff
from the best shops
tomorrow?
I just want to make it myself.
But I really
can't figure it out.
Why don't you take a look?
Let me see.
It doesn't hurt. I'm fine.
It doesn't hurt?
I know you too well.
You can't bear any pain.
You practiced martial arts when you were little.
Every time you bumped against something,
you just cried out loud.
Your crying was earthshaking.
There was one time when you cried,
the whole mansion was alarmed.
They thought there was a fire somewhere.
But I didn't expect
a man who was afraid of pain when he was little
can fight the battles so bravely
when he grows up.
It's my fault.
I still treat you like a child.
You've grown up
and you're a general now.
Don't worry.
I won't tell anyone about
your embarrassing things.
I won't let you get embarrassed.
Sister,
do you really like Chen Yan?
Does Chen Yan
like you as much as
you like
him?
Of course.
He's even willing to die for me.
I think
something
is missing on this.
Is it better like this?
Let me have a look.
Not bad.
It's getting late.
I'll take care of the rest.
Go back and rest.
I’m off then.
Okay.
Pheasant Skewers.
Crunchy Eggplant with Purple Perilla.
Slimy Secretion of A Hundred Worms.
Yum, yum.
It took the bait.
I thought it was some kind of wild animal.
Are you a soldier?
A general?
You can't speak?
I'm leaving then.
No, no, no.
So you can speak.
M-Miss.
It's dark and windy here.
I don't know who
set this trap here.
Leave now.
It's dangerous.
Young man,
It's dark and windy.
If I leave,
you will be suspended in this tree
until you die.
It's not bad
to be suspended in a tree.
Are you sure?
There's a forest here.
Over there,
there is a thousand-year-old pine.
The feng shui is great.
And in front of you…
One, two, three, four, five.
The fifth tree.
It's a 10,000-year-old tree.
There's a dragon vein underneath.
Why don't you
reconsider it?
Forget it.
I don't want to go anywhere.
I'll just die here.
Maybe this is just my fate.
Give me a break.
If you want to die, why did you use that knife
to cut the rope?
Just live well.
Miss.
Where are you?
Stop looking.
Go home.
See you.
A few days ago,
why did you avoid me?
I didn't.
The Wei Army has been investigating closely recently.
Really?
Yes.
You did a good job
about Wangyue.
You know it all?
God bless our Jinghe.
The day you and Wangyue get married
will be the perfect time
for our surprise attack.
At the time,
you and I
can work together from inside and outside.
We will catch the leader
and get rid of Sima Jin.
What's wrong?
Wei and Jinghe
are sworn enemies.
But the princess
love me wholeheartedly.
I really can't bear
to lie to her like this.
Don't tell me
you're having some feelings for her
which you shouldn't have.
Wangyue and I
truly love each other.
Complete your mission well.
I'll pretend I've not heard
those lunatic ravings you said.
Yin,
I can't be
a heartless person.
Can you break your word and forget your benefactor then?
Don't forget who saved you
and gave you dignity.
Now,
you want to betray me
because of a woman.
You're too foolish.
I understand.
Then think about it.
I gave you your life.
Don't let me down.
This mission is very important.
Must Wei and Jinghe
fight until both sides are ruined?
If you waver
because you hanker
after a woman,
not only will you ruin
the great opportunity to build a career,
but you will also
let all our efforts go to waste.
I can't do it now.
Yan.
When you succeed and return to Jinghe,
there'll be plenty of noble ladies for you to choose from.
But in my heart…
in my heart,
there is only Wangyue.
Between the woman and your  spiritual debt,
you can only choose one.
I…
Why is it so lively here?
This is the market of Gu City.
Haven't you been here before?
You're busy with military affairs.
You don't have time to shop.
We need to buy some clothes and jewelry for the wedding.
I'll take you
to go shopping.
Let's go.
What do you need, young lady?
I'm just looking around.
This one.
I'll take it.
Five cents.
OK.
I'm just looking around.
♫It's the fog under your eyes♫
Why did you buy it?
I just want to
buy it for you.
♫That makes it rain at the Mount Ba♫
That's the exact amount here.
Okay, thank you.
♫Who will I sigh for in this life♫
Come on.
I'll take you somewhere.
♫I will remember the past when we part♫
♫I've buried my heart in autumn♫
These are the prayer notes of the people.
♫It's your frown♫
They believe
when the wind blows through them,
♫That brings the sorrowful clouds♫
their wishes can be taken
to heaven,
♫Who will I meet in this life♫
and the gods will grant their wishes.
Let's write one too.
♫Sadness or joy are predestined♫
Okay.
Come here.
♫Love and hatred made me suffer a lot♫
♫What's the date of the Palace in the sky♫
Thank you.
♫I'm only waiting for you♫
You're welcome.
Hang it here.
♫To appear in my dreams♫
♫The courtyard is lush with sycamores♫
Shouldn't it be "Forget the mortal affairs
[Forget the mortal affairs and live this life with "Wangyue"]
♫It only hopes that one day♫
and live this life aloof from the world?"
Why did you change
♫There'll still be a phoenix to roost♫
the famous line of the poem?
But I think
the words "with Wangyue" is
much better than
"Aloof from the world."
♫I'm still looking for you until the sun stains the clouds♫
♫Like a duckweed waiting to be married♫
♫I'm still looking for you♫
♫The Destiny whispers to me that it is hard to find the Netherworld♫
If possible,
I wish I could forget everything
♫My love for you will never change♫
and spend the rest of my life with you.
Greetings, Princess.
It's such an honor
to have you here.
Scarves and chains upstairs
and jewelry downstairs.
You can choose whatever you want.
How about this one?
It's not bad.
Boss,
pack this up.
This one. Okay.
OK.
[Jin's]
I heard that he's a spy from Jinghe.
The Jinghe dogs deserve to die.
When will he be beheaded?
I must observe the execution that day.
Kill him! Kill you!
Spy!
It's him.
Kill him! Kill him!
Jinghe Dog, drop dead!
You deserve to die!
Kill him, Jinghe dog, spy!
I want to kill the spy!
Kill him!
What are you thinking?
Nothing.
Many Jinghe scouts have been caught recently.
But we got nothing from interrogating them.
I wonder
if we'll get any information useful this time.
Let's go.
What are you doing here?
I'm getting you out of here.
If you dare to come in,
I'll bite my tongue and kill myself.
Yin!
I'm a Jinghe scout,
while you belong to the Gu City Army,
and you're the son-in-law of the marshal.
I can't watch you
die without doing anything.
If my death
can make you come to your senses,
then my death won't be in vain.
Go back to where you belong
and complete your mission.
Let go of your love.
This is my last wish.
[Wei]
Chen Yan.
What are you doing here?
You haven't asked me
about your marriage with my sister.
Do I need your permission?
You want to fight?
Alright.
No more fighting.
No.
Not enough!
Come again.
Again what?
I can't fight anymore.
I admit that
your martial arts are better than mine.
But if one day
you betray my sister,
I won't let you go.
Who dares to say
he never lets others down?
I don't care if you let others down,
but you can't
let my sister down.
You don't understand
about us.
Why not?
You're good at martial arts.
If one day
I'm gone,
I'll rest assured
to leave Wangyue to you.
What do you mean?
Nothing.
We are all soldiers.
Who knows what will happen tomorrow?
Don't worry.
From now on,
as long as I am here,
I won't let anything happen
to Wangyue and you.
A meteor?
I heard that
if you wish upon a shooting star,
your wish will come true.
When did God ever
grant a wish?
You're right.
It's just some rumor.
[Wei]
[Behead]
The execution is today.
Let's use the enemy's blood
to console our heroes in heaven
and to pray for victory in the coming battle.
Pray for victory.
[Order]
Decapitation!
[Behead]
You deserve it! Let's go.
Okay.
Here you are.
Eat.
I heard there is a place
where you can eat buns and porridge every day.
On the 1st and 15th days of every month,
there's even meat.
Do you want to go there?
Come on. Hurry up.
Can you do it?
A bit to the left.
Okay.
Should it be higher?
Is this okay?
Yes.
[Happiness]
Get busy, guys.
I've finished cutting this.
Let's have a wedding party tonight.
Okay.
Let's get drunk.
I'm coming.
You four
do a good job.
Our Outpost Battalion
is sort of Chen Yan's family.
I didn't expect Captain Chen
to get himself married into the marshal's family so soon.
Watch your mouth.
Chen Yan married the princess
with dignity.
Their baby will have the name
of Chen.
Yes.
In that case,
his child
will call us uncles.
Yes.
That's right.
We'll have a nephew.
Right?
Nieces and nephews.
♫It's the fog under your eyes♫
♫That makes it rain at the Mount Ba♫
♫Who will I sigh for in this life♫
What a perfect match!
Marshal, you're so lucky.
♫I will remember the past when we part♫
It seems that after the war,
you'll have a grandson.
♫I've buried my heart in autumn♫
♫It's your frown♫
♫That brings the sorrowful clouds♫
Because we're in the army,
everything is done plainly.
♫Who will I meet in this life♫
You two deserve a better ceremony.
When we return to the capital in triumph,
♫Sadness or joy are predestined♫
I'll make it up to you.
I feel more than lucky
♫Love and hatred made me suffer a lot♫
to be able to marry Wangyue.
♫What's the date of the Palace in the sky♫
Father Marshal,
please accept
♫I'm only waiting for you♫
my kowtow.
♫To appear in my dreams♫
♫The courtyard is lush with sycamores♫
♫It only hopes that one day♫
Good.
♫There'll still be a phoenix to roost♫
Okay, get up.
Come on.
♫I'm still looking for you until the falling flowers return with spring♫
I wish you
be happy forever.
♫I'll love you till my life ends♫
♫I'm still looking for you until the sound of hooves fades with the strings♫
♫I hate that there's no time to meet♫
♫I'm still looking for you until the sun stains the clouds♫
♫Like a duckweed waiting to be married♫
♫I'm still looking for you♫
The ceremony is completed.
♫The Destiny whispers to me that it is hard to find the Netherworld♫
Bravo.
Bravo!
Bravo! Bravo!
♫No matter how thick the fog is and how hard it is to find the Netherworld♫
♫My love for you will never change♫
[Wei]
Chen Yan is really lucky.
Here.
I didn't expect him to marry the princess for real.
If it weren't for us,
he wouldn't get married so easily.
Yes.
That's right.
In my opinion,
he got married
thanks to us.
Am I right?
That's right.
Of course. Drink.
You're right.
Marshal! Marshal!
Don’t stand on ceremony on this wedding day.
Come, have a seat.
This is the wedding banquet.
Here.
Let’s have a drink together.
To the Marshal.
Come on.
Well,
After winning the battle
and return to the capital,
do you
have any plans?
My parents have arranged a marriage for me.
After the war,
I'm going back to get married.
Good.
What a loser.
It's not easy for you
to guard the border.
When we go back,
I'll go drink your wedding wine.
Great! Great!
Marshal,
let me toast you.
OK. Come on.
Let's all have a toast to you.
Cheers.
Cheers!
Come on. Cheers.
Fill it up.
Okay.
Come on.
[Happiness]
♫The sunset is just right♫
♫It's like a dream♫
[Happiness]
♫If you take the beauty♫
♫In your eyes♫
♫Don't make the love too strong♫
♫How much it entangles♫
♫The thoughts♫
♫The hourglass along your fingers♫
♫Where do we go from here?♫
Wangyue,
marrying me,
♫Spread out your palm♫
do you regret it?
♫If all your obsessions are empty♫
If I betray you,
♫Remembering the past♫
what would you do?
♫All that you've given me♫
You won't.
If you betray me,
♫A little more touching♫
I'll kill you
♫A little less frightened♫
and die with you.
♫How many times I've been in love♫
I have no regrets
if I can die in your hands.
♫The more fate plays tricks on me♫
♫The more I sing the praises of love's nirvana♫
♫A wisp of dust and sorrow♫
♫Blow away like the wind♫
♫Who plays on his heart in tears?♫
♫I can't help but reach out♫
♫To the thoughts♫
♫Don't ask, don't tell♫
♫Just hold each other♫
♫Fold a feather of tenderness♫
♫And it's immortal♫
♫Believe in love and loneliness♫
♫Learn to be foolish and brave♫
♫It's hard to turn back♫
♫You don't have to understand if you don't want to hear♫
♫Even if it's a dream♫