[English subtitles are available]
[Watch on kisskh.co]
[Beauty of Resilience]
[Episode 1]
[Watch on kisskh.co]
At the beginning of the whole world,
Immortal Realm, Human Realm and Demon Realm were formed.
Outside the three realms,
only the phoenix
was a divine beast born with heaven and earth,
and it continued to awaken from nirvana.
Now the phoenix has long disappeared.
Time came to the triennial activity
of measuring the immortal bones in Human Realm's Dayu Kingdom.
An eccentric vision suddenly appeared in front of the Immortal-Revealing Mirror.
Since then,
a new chapter of entanglement between the three realms has opened.
[Capital of Dayu in Human Realm]
[The Minister's Mansion]
[Wei Zhi, handmaid of the Minister's Mansion]
Time to work.
My name is Wei Zhi.
I'm a handmaid of the Minister of Rites' Mansion
in Dayu.
Everyone in the mansion calls me a jinx.
Because anything unlucky
would fall on me.
What were you doing?
[Thinking About What You Hear]
Did you do it on purpose?
Were you trying to kill me?
What a jinx!
Hurry up.
But
the measurement of the immortal bones is about to begin.
After that,
and after entering the Egret Academy,
I can let my mother and brother
live a good life.
I don't have to
be a handmaid anymore.
Lady Lingyue.
[Wei Lingyue, Third Daughter of the Minister's Mansion]
Which hairpin are you wearing today?
You don't need to bother.
I've already put it on.
Is that all?
Isn't it too plain?
You're going to take the immortal bones measurement.
This is the most important thing
in the life of our people in Dayu.
You said I was going to
take the immortal bones measurement.
Then how I look wouldn't matter.
It's almost time.
I'll go check on Jingyue.
[Wei Jingyue, Fourth Daughter of the Minister's Mansion]
Lady Jingyue, Lady Lingyue is here.
Sister.
You came at the right time.
Why haven't you
changed your clothes?
Help me have a look.
Which one should I wear?
Come on.
Look.
Is it too tacky?
Not this one. Take it away.
Is this blue one
too bright?
Every piece looks good to me.
Sister.
Why are you dressed
as usual?
Why not?
Today is the triennial
big day.
All the people in the country
who have reached the age of 16
have to go to the Immortal-Revealing Mirror to measure immortal bones
and complete the coming-of-age ceremony.
By then,
the nobles and high-born ladies
will gather together.
So what?
Sister.
Based on our
background, appearance and character,
I'm sure we have immortal fate.
Maybe we'll
be selected by Egret Academy.
How many eyes
will be looking at us then?
Shouldn't you be well groomed?
Egret Academy
selects the best talents
for Dayu.
The selected ones
are all talented.
They have heavy immortal bones and determined immortal fate.
Only a few students can be produced every three years.
It's not that easy to enter.
If we two can't enter,
who else can?
Especially you.
There is no better person than you.
You can just
say that at home.
Be careful with your words and actions when you are outside.
As the Minister of Rites,
and the supervisor of the coming-to-age ceremony.
If people think
he abuses his power,
it will ruin his reputation.
That'll be terrible.
I know, Sister.
You're talking
more and more like Father.
Help me decide
which one I should choose.
Nanny.
Are we setting off?
Set off? Where are we going?
To measure immortal bones at the coming-of-age ceremony.
You even want to measure your immortal bones?
Don't bother.
Your mother is here.
She wants to take you back.
Let's go.
Hurry!
Father.
The new tea is here.
What is this?
Is it for people to drink?
[Minister Wei of Dayu]
How many people
have no food to eat?
It's good to have tea.
Yes.
Is everything ready?
Father,
everything is ready.
We can go now.
You two
are going to measure the immortal bones today.
You must
be careful with your words and actions.
I understand, Father.
San'er,
take care of Si'er.
Don't make her
a joke for being unstable.
Yes, Father.
Father.
By the way,
Is there anyone else in our mansion
who has turned 16 and is going to the coming-of-age ceremony?
Master,
there's a also handmaid
named Wei Zhi to go.
Her?
Father.
Wei Zhi originally
worked in my room.
But she always caused trouble,
so I sent her out
to do some rough work.
She acts weird.
She's definitely a jinx.
All right.
She's just a handmaid.
Watch out for her outside.
Don't be rude
and embarrass our family.
Yes.
Mother.
Thank you, Nanny.
I'll take her away then.
Just go.
I changed your birthday
to Xinyou Year.
[Gu, Wei Zhi's mother]
Remember.
Don't spill the beans later.
Why?
I've arranged a marriage for you.
The Chun family at Crossbridge.
It's a rich family.
The bridegroom's just in poor health.
He has a slight limp.
Mother, I'm not getting married.
Today is the coming-of-age ceremony.
I‘m going to measure my immotal bones.
With your fate,
if I don't change it,
even a cripple wouldn't want you.
Why are you measuring the immortal bones?
I want to enter the Egret Academy.
If I enter there,
I can change
our family's situation.
Our situation
was caused by you.
Stop dreaming.
Go back with me.
I'm different from others.
Once I enter the academy,
I can make changes.
I've accepted the betrothal gifts
to pay for your brother's schooling.
If you have a conscience,
don't talk about nonsense.
Lady Jingyue just asked me to do something.
I'll go tell her.
The nanny will arrange it.
You don't have to go.
What are you doing?
Lady Lingyue.
Please save me.
Why are you yelling?
Are you crazy?
Tell me, how can I save you?
My mother has arranged a marriage for me.
But the bridegroom is a cripple.
I don't want to get married.
Lady Lingyue, please save me.
Marriage is
a matter of parental choice.
How do we have the right to interfere?
Shameless.
Are you her mother?
Yes.
You're getting more and more impolite.
How can you bring people into the mansion at will?
Take her away.
Hurry!
Lady Lingyue.
Lady Lingyue, help me.
Today,
are you going to the coming-of-age ceremony?
People of our status
don't have to go.
I'm talking to her.
Where is your turn to interfere?
Lady Lingyue.
I'm 16 today.
I was going to measure the immortal bones.
That's it.
The coming-of-age ceremony is set by our law.
It's mandatory for all youths
over the age of 16.
What?
Are you going to the government office?
I dare not.
Wei Zhi.
You were sold to our mansion.
Three months before the end of the five-year contract.
Then you still belong to our Wei Mansion.
It's not up to anyone else to decide.
Today,
you follow Lady Jingyue.
Let's go to the Immortal-Appealing Mirror
to measure the immortal bones.
Thank you, Lady Lingyue.
Hurry up.
Sister.
Why did you
help that jinx?
After all,
she belongs to our mansion.
If word gets out,
people would think the Minister's Mansion
bullies a servant.
For nothing else,
we have to think about
the reputation of our father.
It was actually because you were soft-hearted.
[Yan Yue, son of the late Heavenly Empress Xi Cai]
Please give me some food.
Go away.
What a lack of vision.
Don't know what day it is today?
Go away!
Hurry up.
Don't miss the coming-of-age ceremony of the ladies.
Hurry.
Hurry!
Get up.
Go buy some food.
Thank you. Miss.
Wei Zhi.
She can see me?
[yu]
[Ming Lang, Young Lord of Gucheng at the border]
Look.
This is the third son of the Ming family.
He is really handsome
and talented.
That's right.
I’m Ming Lang.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Liu Chang.
[Liu Chang, son of Mighty General]
We meet today because of fate.
We might be classmates in the future.
That's right.
[Bao Liang from Baosheng Private Bank]
Mr. Ming.
[Xiao Jin, son of Deputy Minister of Personnel]
Mr. Xiao.
Mr. Liu.
Mr. Chen.
I'm Bao Liang.
Nice to meet you.
How do you know us?
My family owns the largest money shop,
Baosheng Private Bank.
Business
is all about connections.
If I am fortunate enough
to be your classmate in the future,
please bear with me.
You sound confident.
It seems that
the rumor that the supervisor of the immortal bones measurement
accepts bribes
is not an empty rumor.
The son of the Deputy Minister of Personnel
is quite straightforward.
In the future,
if the Imperial Advisor
needs my help,
you will let me know.
I will do anything.
Look.
This is the carriage of Minister Wei's familly.
This time,
the two daugthers of the minister
are also here for the coming-of-age ceremony.
The more outstanding is the third daughter
whose looks and character
both rank the first
in the capital.
Really?
Look how beautiful she is.
She's gifted and smart.
In my opinion,
we don't even need to measure the immortal bones.
The children of families with high positions and lots of money
would have immortal bones that naturally weigh
a few more taels of than others'.
Don't talk nonsense.
Aren't you afraid of being beheaded?
That's right.
The two daughters of Minister Wei's
are really beautiful.
They deserve their reputation.
Brother Ming Lang.
The Imperial Advisor has arrived!
[Imperial Advisor of Dayu]
The auspicious time has come.
In the 12th year of Yongding of Dayu,
the coming-of-age ceremony starts now.
18 people are divided into a group.
Please come to the Immortal-Revealing Mirror to measure the root bone
and determine the fate of immortality.
Next group.
[Qing Huan, Chief of Imperial Guards of Heavenly Realm]
[Holy Temple in Demon Realm]
Hua Rong shines again.
Phoenix reappears in the world.
[Supreme Lord of Demon Realm]
Phoenix.
Yan Yue.
What's going on?
Father,
there is an unusual sign
appeared in the Immortal-Revealing Mirror in the Human Realm.
The Immortal-Revealing Mirror?
[Heavenly Emperor, King of Heaven Realm]
[Heavenly Empress, Wife of Heavenly Emperor]
The Immortal-Revealing Mirror shows divine signs.
The phoenix...
The phoenix has descended.
The phoenix has appeared?
Since ancient times,
Phoenix has been an auspicious sign.
Its arrival this time
is a blessing for Your Majesty.
[Emperor of Dayu]
Dayu
will be in great luck
and create a prosperous world.
Well said.
Your Majesty,
the most important thing now
is to find the true phoenix
so that we won't let Heaven down.
What do you think, Imperial Advisor?
When the unusual sign appeared,
18 youngsters were
in front of the Immortal-Revealing Mirror,
attending the coming-of-age ceremony.
But there's only one true phoenix.
Unfortunately,
the Immortal-Revealing Mirror is broken.
In my opinion,
we should recruit these 18 youngsters
to Egret Academy
and ask a master
to guide them,
so that we can find the true phoenix.
Good.
Then, I'll leave this matter
to you, Imperial Advisor.
Yes, Your Majesty.
[Heaven Realm]
Yan Yue,
the Immortal-Revealing Mirror showed an unusual sign.
It meant the phoenix reappeared in Human Realm.
What do you think?
When the unusual sign appeared,
18 mortals
were measuring immortal bones in front of the Immortal-Revealing Mirror.
The true phnoenix must be one of them.
By testing
their blood with Immortal Techniques
can we find the true phoenix.
This phoenix
is still in puberty.
Its bloodline is deeply hidden.
However,
after three bloodline stimulations,
its power will dominate three realms.
If the phoenix's power
is controlled by Demon Realm,
wouldn't it bring a catastrophe?
Not only Demon Realm,
any other place will
covet the power of the phoenix.
Therefore,
we Immortal Realm must strike first.
Yan Yue.
Yes, Father.
I order you to go to Human Realm
to find the true phoenix as soon as possible
and lead it to good.
Make it under the control of Immortal Realm.
Yes, Father.
Qing Huan will help you.
Yes.
Yan Yue.
Slow down.
I haven’t finished.
Are you not satisfied with
Heavenly Emperor's arrangement?
You don't want to work with me, do you?
No.
Why?
You are too nagging.
The selection of phoenix in Human Realm
is no small matter.
It's said that when the whole world started...
The History of Three Realms.
Even if you knew
what happened to the phoenix,
what about Egret Academy?
You don't know, do you?
300 years ago,
Egret Academy was founded in Dayu.
Generations of mortals
practised and cultivated there.
But in recent years,
Egret Academy
recruit only nobal descendants
and teach some shallow skills
of Qimen Dunjia.
Besides,
Dayu has recruited these 18 youngsters
to
Egret Academy.
You're going to Human Realm
to become a teacher.
Yan Yue.
Yan Luo and I are here to see you off.
I heard you prating
from afar.
You are the leader
of the Imperial Guards of Immortal Realm.
What're you talking like an old maid?
My cousin Yan Yue
was so annoyed by you.
Don't go.
I haven't scolded you yet.
What would you scold me?
-Stop!
-When are you leaving?
Right now.
[Yan Luo, Rain God, Son of Heavenly Empress]
Not bad for you.
You are the best model in Immortal Realm.
It is our duty
to share the worries of the Heavenly Emperor.
This is your duty as the Red Sun God,
not mine.
Yan Luo.
It's time for you
to go back to work in the Heavenly Court.
Stop wandering around.
Mother.
Why are you back?
I was selected.
I can go to study
at Egret Academy.
We're going to make it.
Egret Academy?
Don't go.
Why?
You should tell me.
Who are we?
What kind of place is Egret Academy?
You want to get Wei Ye and me killed,
right?
But
I just want you
to live a good life.
Shut up.
I'll tell you one thing.
You're not allowed to go to Egret Academy.
I want to go.
I don't want to be a servant forever.
You don't want to be a servant.
You want to be a devil?
Instead of letting you kill us,
let me kill you now.
Mother!
Don't hit Sister!
Why did you stop me?
If it weren't for her,
how could you lose your father and grandfather
without being born?
How could we
live such a miserable life?
I only know
[Wei Ye, Wei Zhi's Brother]
Sister is good to me.
Burn her to death!
[Ten years ago, Gucheng]
I just want to save my daughter.
I have no intention of rebellion.
Arrest him!
Grandpa!
Sister, does it hurt?
Don't blame Mother.
She was just too tired.
Sister, have some.
Osmanthus cakes.
Keep it for yourself.
This is the best dissert
in the world.
I saved it for you.
It's rare for Mother to buy it.
You must be ignorant.
The best dissert
in the world
is Gucheng Rice Cake.
Gucheng again?
Where is Gucheng?
Why didn't you buy some
and let me have a taste?
Sister.
Are you really going to
Egret Academy?
Of course.
This is my admission document.
So, are you not going to
come back to see me often?
After you finish reciting the Complete Collection of Yu Poetry,
I should be back.
By then, no one dare
bully us.
And then,
I can be a physician
or draw talismans for others
and make a lot of money.
When we have money,
we can go to Gucheng
to have Rice Cake.
Mother.
Forgive me for leaving without saying goodbye.
Don't worry about
me being bullied at the academy.
As a maid for so long,
I've already mastered all my skills.
You don't need to worry about my true identity
as Feng Zhi being exposed
and causing trouble.
I will devote myself to cultivation
and be careful.
[Egret Academy]
Get lost.
You're so annoying.
Sister.
No one other than students of the Academy
is allowed to enter.
She's our nanny.
You're students as soon as you enter the Academy.
[Gatekeeper Taoist of Egret Academy]
You have to do everything yourselves.
She will leave
once she sends our luggage in.
Each person can only
bring one lugguge with you.
As for the rest of your luggage,
don't take them with you.
What?
Well, I...
We understand.
[Egret Academy]
Sister.
Wait for me.
Catch it.
Let's go.
[Egret Academy]
When did you catch up?
There are only three women's dorm.
One of them is small and leaking.
And...
I'll take it.
That's what you should do.
[Xinju Hall]
[Jingxiu, Dean of Egret Academy]
I'm Jingxiu, Dean of
Egret Academy,
Welcome
to Egret Academy to learn the way and cultivate.
An immortal
is a man on the mountain,
who stays away from the mundane world
and hides in forests.
From today onwards,
I hope all of you
can clear your mind
and cultivate myself.
When the ten virtues come true,
you will ascend to immortality.
All of you are destined to be immortals.
The Academy appoints a Penglai Immortal Envoy
to teach you.
It's him.
This master looks young.
Is he qualified to teach us?
How can a female student
still have the mood to cultivate?
Master, I'm sorry. Master.
A cultivator
shouldn't be frivolous.
Everyone,
Rule number one
of Egret Academy,
respect your master.
Yes.
Egret Academy
is not as independent
as Penglai Heavenly Island.
I wonder if you are used to living here.
A cultivator
should be at ease with the situation.
I heard
you and the Imperial Advisor are old acquaintances.
[Penglai Heavenly Island]
[Penglai Immortal Envoy]
He's out.
Heavenly Envoy, our country has admired you for a long time.
We used to write to each other.
I wish I could see you in person.
I'm lucky
to pick you up.
I didn't expect you
are so young.
You can't judge one's cultivation
by appearance.
You're right.
Heavenly Envoy.
Do you know why our Academy
was named Egret Academy?
Please tell me.
The egret is delicate but tough.
It soars in the sky,
proud and independent.
Dean.
Are you worried that
I will be affected by the Imperial Advisor
and be unfair in the selection
of the phoenix?
The true phoenix is destined for heaven.
No one
can change.
In that case,
I worried too much.
Gather at once.
Oh no.
I'm late.
Master.
Let's go.
We're late. Hurry up.
Hurry up.
I'm late.
Here.
Stand still.
Get out of the way!
The first step to practice the Way
is to strengthen your body.
The first step to cultivate immortality
is to organize your grooming.
You're in a bad mood and don't look good.
Everyone will be punished.
Once you entered the Academy,
there will not be
young masters and ladies.
You only have
one identity,
which is a student.
As a student of the Academy,
you must obey the academy rules strictly.
Everyone
must be familiar with
and strictly abide by the rules.
Those who violate
will be severely punished.
Rule number two
of Egret Academy,
self-discipline.
After one joss stick,
the magic will automatically be lifted.
I'm paralyzed. I can't take it anymore.
Well, are we here to cultivate
or to experience hell?
Exactly.
Yes, we're here to cultivate.
Sister,
I've never been so tired in my life.
Alright.
I can't stand up.
Master is here.
Master.
You're going to study by yourself today.
Study the rules of Egret Academy.
Recite it tomorrow.
Yes, Master.
What?
We have to serve that master
like a servant?
No, we're here to cultivate,
not to be slaves.
We have to take turns
to clean the class.
And the school.
You may not know
we have
an expert in chores.
Be it washing, cooking,
carrying water, cutting wood,
sweeping the floor, or cleaning the toilet.
There's nothing she can't do.
Stop it.
Come back.
This is
the maid that our Wei Mansion
bought for
five taels of silver.
What was her name again?
She didn't seem to have a name.
Since she's in our family,
her surname would be Wei.
She was
like a rotten branch.
So,
we called her Wei Zhi (branch).
What if she's a phoenix?
Then wouldn't I have offended her?
Lord Phoenix.
Could you please
help me clean the classroom?
Could you? I’m asking you.
Lady Wei Jingyue.
Master just said
we are equal at the Academy.
There's no distinction between noble and lowly.
Master also said
Rule number two of the academy
is self-discipline.
Wei Zhi.
Your mother sold you to our family.
We spend money and you spend effort.
It's reasonable.
Look at the last page
of the academy rules.
It is strictly forbidden
to talk about matters related to the phoenix.
The violators will be expelled and discharged immediately.
[Demon Realm]
From now on,
you are my eyes.
This tree has no demon aura.
This is a great idea.
No one can break
my secret technique.
I thought Egret Academy
was so powerful and sacred.
In the end, there are so many evil spirits.
Isn't this Wei Zhi?
You're the only one
to serve others.
This is too much for you.
I feel sorry for you.
Show some respect.
You're so pretty.
Would you like to be my father's concubine?
It's hot.
You can't even joke.
Master.
Your clothes are clean.
I set a barrier.
How did she get in?
Wait.
How did you get in?
I knocked.
I'm asking you
how you got in?
I walked in.
What's your name?
Wei Zhi.
Raise your head.
Master.
What's wrong?
Are you okay?