=No Pain No Gain=
(Adapted from the Qidian novel)
("Losing Money to Be a Tycoon"
by Qingshan Quzui)
=Episode 20=
(This story is purely fictional)
This video was obviously
made by someone
Zhou Muyan hired to smear us.
I'm going to Fingle right now
to beat him up.
Scoundrel!
Don't.
For crying out loud!
I swear I'll mess Zhou Muyan up.
Alright, calm down.
I must punch him now.
(Looks like)
(this "Da" company isn't that serious
about making games.)
(There's barely any visible marketing.)
(Who knows where the money went?)
Don't act impulsively.
You can't hit people.
If you do, we're in the wrong.
Yes.
Get a lawyer.
Sue him.
Lin Wan, don't worry.
The internet remembers.
I'll repost Zhou Muyan
yelling at employees
at Sky Fire another 200 times.
Yes.
Let's see if everyone knows
what kind of person he is.
You led us to plan
the Divine Mountains and Seas.
How do you want to fight back?
We'll all follow you.
Follow.
Yes, we'll do what you want.
Thank you.
As long as you're here,
I won't be affected.
Don't worry.
I'll have the legal
issue a clarification now.
We can't let him slander us again.
The key issue now
is how we save
the Divine Mountains and Seas.
If this keeps up,
it'll really go down.
We need to think about
how to turn this around.
Easy.
He slandered us,
so we just slandered him back.
Isn't it just spending money? Spend it.
Don't be impulsive.
How dare someone like him
brag about his game?
He'll crash sooner or later.
This time,
it's really brains vs brawn.
Zhou Muyan
has already
written our script for us.
Here. I'll stop writing
Northern Continent for now.
I'll craft a story for him.
- That works.
- Yes.
I'll post that video of his.
Follow
his persona and arrange it.
Heaven closes one door,
but opens another window.
Zhou Muyan showed up again.
You must seize this new chance.
The Divine Mountains and Seas
is already online.
You've done right by them.
Stop dwelling on it.
You owe no one.
Wait.
That expression looks off.
You aren't thinking of joining them
to go after Zhou Muyan, are you?
You're really something.
We're done.
He's softening again.
Get ready to drive forever.
Wake up.
If the Divine Mountains and Seas wins,
we'll have no way
to get Sima's bonus.
- There's no way.
- No way.
In this world,
we can have one less
so-called good game.
But I
won't let people
who truly gave their all
be let down.
Here.
Comrades.
No matter what,
we must spend on promotion.
We absolutely can't lose to Zhou Muyan.
I agree.
Yes.
100% agree.
Lin Wan, what do you think?
The company has already invested a lot
in developing
the Divine Mountains and Seas.
Let's see what Mr. Pei says.
Lin Wan, look at everyone's enthusiasm.
Sure. OK.
No problem.
Mr. Pei
will definitely agree.
Amazing, Mr. Pei.
Mr. Pei.
Amazing.
Mr. Pei is the best!
Mr. Pei
will definitely agree.
Awesome.
He'll agree for sure.
Absolutely no problem.
That Zhou Muyan went too far.
He's a real jerk.
Yeah.
You know what just happened?
Totally at ease.
You have no idea.
Yeah.
This time, you...
Leave it to me.
You're not her match.
Xin, this time, no matter what...
Move aside.
The budget is approved.
Don't lose to someone like Zhou Muyan.
For the Divine Mountains and Seas,
the budget
has no limit.
No limit.
Wait and see.
I'll go
and make 800 marketing plans.
We must win this promotional campaign.
Sibo won't let you down!
Awesome!
Let's go!
- Alright.
- Let's go. Come on.
(Losses: The Divine Mountains and Seas,
Zhongdian Web Fiction,)
(Feihuang Pictures,
Dreams Fulfilled Immediately)
(Profits: Sloth Gym, Phone Booth,
Returning to Shore, Four Wall Apartments)
(Tengda Total Assets)
Mr. Pei, I'm sorry.
Sibo let you down.
We planned so many strategies
and reached out to all kinds of creators
and video bloggers,
but they all said their schedule
is full for the year.
They can't take new jobs.
Zhou Muyan
really went all out.
Attacking Tengda is now the trend.
Anyone speaking for us gets attacked.
Smaller accounts
that didn't receive the job
dare not speak either.
They can only observe.
This time,
they're really trying to kill us.
It's fine.
This isn't your fault.
We'll think of a solution together.
Since online marketing won't work,
we'll go offline.
Promote in our own stores.
Break through their blockade.
Alright, Mr. Pei.
We'll keep pushing.
But there's good news, Mr. Pei.
I brought back an old friend.
Who is it?
♪Dangers and control♪
♪I'm confident and I know that♪
♪Sometimes I intimidate♪
You think the Divine Mountains and Seas
is a bad game, right?
What's bad about it?
Come on, let's debate.
I want to see...
(A true masterpiece)
(Is it truly not fun, or were you)
(The Divine Mountains and Seas 2.0)
(led by these marketing accounts?)
Come on.
(The Divine Mountains and Seas
Offline Dungeon Tournament)
(Huge prizes await.)
(Tournament)
Everyone.
The Divine Mountains and Seas
offline dungeon competition, co-hosted
by M&Y Internet Cafe
and The Divine Mountains and Seas,
is about to begin.
The prizes are generous.
We hope everyone
will actively participate.
(Co-Branded Set of)
(the Divine Mountains and Seas)
Download and register
the Divine Mountains and Seas now.
This 888 co-branded set
will be free for you.
Reach above level 10,
and you can also enjoy
a 50% discount here.
Reach above level 20,
and you can get
our annual Gold VIP membership card.
That sounds interesting.
How to download this game?
(The Divine Mountains and Seas)
Please scan the code.
Scan this one?
Okay, thanks.
♪Underneath my red eyes♪
(The Divine Mountains and Seas.
Explore the unknown. Fearless heroes.)
Welcome.
Scan the code to download and register
the Divine Mountains and Seas.
After successful registration,
you can get five free chances
to use the phone booth.
Please take a look.
Here.
Take a look.
Scan this code.
Come take a look. What is this?
(Zhongdian Web Fiction.
The Divine Mountains and Seas Fan Fiction Contest)
Zhongdian Web Fiction hosts
The Divine Mountains and Seas
Fan Fiction Contest.
The winner
will receive generous rewards.
- Good.
(Four Wall Apartments)
Register and download Tengda Games'
Divine Mountains and Seas.
Register and download
the Divine Mountains and Seas.
Follow The Divine Mountains and Seas.
Register and download Tengda Games'
Divine Mountains and Seas.
Is it fun?
Download it, please.
It's fun.
Register and download Tengda Games'
Divine Mountains and Seas.
I saw online
that it has all bad reviews.
Trust us.
Give this game a chance.
Play for two hours,
and you'll get one month free
at Four Wall Apartments.
♪Blow up♪
(The Divine Mountains and Seas
officially launches.)
(Support #TheDivineMountainsandSeas#.)
(Ruan Guangjian: We must
support #TheDivine MountainsandSeas#.)
- Can the script still be amended?
Yes.
- It can be reposted on Weibo.
- - It can be reposted on Weibo.
(Lu Zhiyao: #TheDivineMountainsandSeas#
I wish my fans get tons of equipment.)
(Shi Huo: #TheDivineMountainsandSeas#
This game is great, just like me.)
Kind words build good bonds.
Harsh words hurt hearts.
(I knew Mr. Qiao
took ads with principles.)
(Please.)
(I hope everyone stays rational.)
(Give this game a chance.)
(Trust me.)
(This game will definitely
bring everyone a huge surprise.)
(Is Tengda being smeared?)
(Thanks!)
I'll kneel to you.
After you go back,
help us promote
the Divine Mountains and Seas.
Okay?
- Okay.
Thank you all.
Welcome.
Isn't this that...
Yes.
The one who throws money around?
It's him.
Seems like him.
Support the Divine Mountains and Seas.
Welcome.
- Hello. Welcome.
♪Baby, I'm a monster♪
Welcome.
Please come in.
♪Blow up♪
♪Baby, I'm a monster♪
♪Rock the way♪
(Support #TheDivineMountainsandSeas#)
(Game Download Rankings)
(Infinite Imagination,
The Divine Mountains and Seas)
(Powerful Launch,
Pre-Registration Welcomed)
(Crafted By Skilled Masters
to Build A Beautiful World)
(The Divine Mountains and Seas.
Explore the Unknown.)
Sorry.
(The Divine Mountains and Seas.
Explore the Unknown. Fearless Heroes.)
Everyone.
Keep eating
and don't stop looking.
Here, look this way.
The Divine Mountains and Seas.
Tengda's newest game.
It's super fun.
Well... There's a QR code.
Everyone can scan it to register.
Anyone who registers by scanning
gets free dishes.
Okay?
Scan it.
Scan here.
Mr. Li Jr.,
why are you doing this yourself?
Quick, I'll do it.
Look, how many times have I told you?
You need to spread them out.
Why put them all together?
Is this resource integration?
Right?
Your info needs to be direct.
You just need to...
Here.
Move aside.
Mr. Li Jr.,
it's Mr. Li calling.
Tell him I'm busy.
I'll call back later.
Mr. Li.
Mr. Li Jr. is...
Yes.
Mr. Li Jr.,
Mr. Li sounds angry.
This one.
Dad.
This time, Tengda is up against
Fingle under the Dayake Group.
Why can Fingle secure so many
overseas game licenses?
It's because it's backed by Dayake.
You know
the interests involved.
You openly supporting Tengda like this
will cause unimaginable trouble
for Fuhui.
No, Dad, I really...
I barely recognize you now.
You never cared about this before.
Yes, Fuhui has grown strong lately,
but what about you?
You care
more and more about connections
and appearances.
Do these things
matter more than your son?
Times have changed.
Fuhui today
has countless eyes watching it.
Shi.
You're not a child anymore.
It's not the time to care about loyalty.
Sacrificing the small to save the big
is something you don't need me to teach.
Got it, Dad.
Fingle is wealthy and powerful.
Once the game launched,
it crushed Tengda.
Isn't it because Tengda is new
and took some of your market?
But, Dad,
I think what we should consider now
isn't how to monopolize.
What we should think about
is how to make it bigger.
Isn't that right?
If an industry
has only one player,
that industry
is truly finished.
(Game Category Rankings)
They used Tengda's businesses
to promote
the Divine Mountains and Seas.
Download stats and online popularity
are rebounding.
We need to think of another way.
I can't lose this time.
This is our last chance.
I didn't expect Tengda
to be this resilient.
I thought
we'd beat them
with no chance to recover.
Looks like...
We'll have to go all out.
(Stay true to our mission,
succeed for the greater good.)
(Through a video leaked from Tengda,)
(we can see)
(Tengda's English name is Tengda,)
(but it's written as Tenda on the wall.)
(One G is missing.)
(They can't even spell)
(their own name correctly.)
(You can see that it's full of bugs.)
(And Tengda's abbreviation is TD.)
[*"TD" can stand for "unsubscribe" in Chinese. ]
(It obviously means unsubscribe.)
How childish.
There's something even more childish.
Look.
(Expert Who Can't Soar)
The new set by Infinite Imagination
is called Expert Who Can't Soar.
This is too much.
Let's make one, too.
Make
a dull, lifeless rock.
They attack Tengda,
and you scold their leader.
Wouldn't that make it easier
for them to find faults?
Then what should we do?
It seems
Fingle hasn't done anything wrong.
They made a game for the first time
and were led astray by Zhou Muyan.
Didn't Mr. Pei say
those attacking us
are just minor nuisances?
Just ignore them.
Wait.
Now
it's no longer minor.
Look.
I searched
the Divine Mountains and Seas online.
All results are Infinite Imagination.
What does this mean?
Did they block our keywords?
They actually did.
Anything
about the Divine Mountains and Seas
shows Infinite Imagination.
This tactic is too shady.
Check Net blocked us.
Check Net
dominates all search engines.
If everyone searches
the Divine Mountains and Seas,
it automatically redirects
to Infinite Imagination's results.
That'll cause us big trouble.
Zhou Muyan clearly did this.
Our data just started to rise,
and he played dirty tricks again.
Though not clever,
it's effective.
They probably aren't just messing
with the search engines.
I'll check elsewhere.
We're likely
blocked on other websites too.
Everyone.
Something happened again.
(Conference Room)
Now it's not just Check Net.
Almost on all social platforms
and short video platforms,
our traffic can't rise.
I asked Mr. Qiao.
He said this is called
traffic limiting,
keyword blocking, or something.
Our keywords have been blocked.
Mainly, we haven't had
any binding cooperation
with other platforms.
We're indeed passive now.
Once everyone searches
the Divine Mountains and Seas,
it automatically links
to Infinite Imagination.
Why does Zhou Muyan
have so many despicable tricks?
How much did he pay these companies?
We pay double, triple,
and make them block them online!
If we do this,
how are we different from him?
It's different.
Mr. Pei, the Divine Mountains and Seas
is the fruit of our labor.
We must win this time.
Sibo.
Look at you.
Working 9-to-6 every day,
your eye bags are huge.
Is it different from overtime
at the old company?
Everyday, Infinite Imagination
updates, gives benefits,
and updates for big gift packs.
My upgrade resource pack
must keep up,
or users won't stay.
Lv.
How long has it been
since you left on time?
Aren't you supposed to be a slasher?
No time for that now.
Zhou Muyan is full of dirty tricks.
And you.
I don't even want to say it.
You lose your temper thrice a day now.
What? Ate gunpowder?
I'm not losing my temper, Mr. Pei.
Look online.
It's full of bad reviews.
Look.
(Does Tengda think they're all that)
(because some of their games succeed?)
(They think their products
are guaranteed hits?)
(When it comes to big games, we can see)
(the real production level
of some companies.)
(I suggest playing Infinite Imagination.)
Mr. Pei.
I understand your point.
Of course, we can't
be like Zhou Muyan and his kind.
But if we don't act, what about
the Divine Mountains and Seas?
Do we just watch them
suppress us?
Yeah.
Look.
I know.
Everyone gave their all
to the Divine Mountains and Seas.
It's indeed a good game.
Everyone has high expectations for it.
So, getting this feedback after launch,
everyone is angry.
Me too.
But are these comments
only from
Zhou Muyan's slander?
Mr. Pei,
if you put it that way,
you reminded me.
When I was at Sky Fire,
I already felt it.
Think about it.
Tengda,
a new company,
made four games that all succeeded.
Competitors are watching.
The Divine Mountains and Seas
is our first
large-scale multiplayer online game.
Many veteran game companies
already disliked us.
So they waited for Zhou Muyan
to spread rumors,
and everyone piled on.
Lin Wan.
Do you remember I asked you
why you like making games?
Reality is sometimes too heavy.
We want a safe harbor
and a utopia.
Yes.
Life
can suffocate people.
You can't escape it,
but we can nap
and dream.
You have ideals
and emotions.
I believe you can do it.
Because games
can let many people
momentarily forget the harsh reality.
Now,
can it still make you forget
reality's troubles?
A creation
is actually the creators'
true emotional vessel
and reflection.
But look.
Everyone is full of worries every day,
trapped in marketing wars.
Can we
still create happiness for players?
We now
betray our original intention
and drift farther away.
If games
want to attract players,
they can only rely on heartfelt content
and new gameplay.
We should
calm down and think about
what we can do
for the Divine Mountains and Seas.
Is it just about defeating
a mere Zhou Muyan?
Zhou Muyan's nothing.
Trash.
He's an industry parasite.
People like Zhou Muyan
will never disappear.
If we want a real rival,
there's only one.
It's ourselves.
I saw a comment saying
there are too many newbie tasks.
They're right.
I recently thought about it carefully.
We set up
many gameplay features and characters,
pushing them all to players at once.
This makes newbie tasks
tedious and long.
I take responsibility for this.
When I played earlier,
I felt the time in the newbie village
was too long.
I couldn't enter the main map.
Bao, you should have mentioned it
during the test play.
I thought it was a minor issue.
Because once you get to the main map,
it's really fun.
You enlightened me.
I think it's similar
to writing a script.
If the story background is too complex,
the audience abandons it.
Right?
- Yes.
Exactly.
Then I'll optimize the program.
I'll put those gift packs and XP
into the tasks.
Will this improve the player experience?
Definitely.
Another optimization method
is to let players
interact with the real world
in the Divine Mountains and Seas.
For example,
when players reach a restaurant
in the Divine Mountains and Seas map,
they can actually order takeout
and have it delivered to them
in real life.
Good idea.
This really breaks
the dimensional barrier.
This can work, right?
No problem.
Huang.
Can we have players
read Zhongdian Web Fiction novels
in-game?
That should be fine.
Don't we
have a wishing pool area?
Can players
directly message Mr. Ma's
Dreams Fulfilled Immediately account?
- Yes.
- Yes!
Adding real-world interaction
like this makes it even more fun.
Of course.
I also have an idea.
When I play the game,
there's a character
with a really long face
and very small eyes.
I think it doesn't look good.
Let's ask our art team
to fix it up first.
Can we...
Lin Wan, let me tell you.
Well... No.
Can we...
This way...
This...
Wait...
Isn't being ugly a problem?
Being ugly.
Shouldn't we reflect on that too?
(Stay true to our mission,
succeed for the greater good.)
Ms. Lin Wan.
Thank you for your hard work.
- Ms. Lin Wan.
Ms. Lin Wan.
Thank you for your hard work. Yada.
Comrades.
Infinite Imagination
is still increasing player benefits.
Listen up.
Hello, players.
To thank you for loving and supporting
Infinite Imagination,
starting today,
anyone who registers
Infinite Imagination
will receive
discounts on downloads
for other games published by Fingle.
(Infinite Imagination)
Log in and play over two hours
for seven consecutive days,
and you can download other Fingle games
for free.
Fingle really went all out.
They spend money to promote
other games they represent,
bleeding funds
to support Infinite Imagination.
Don't worry about them.
Just focus on our own work.
Remember what Mr. Pei said?
- Surpass yourself.
Back to work.
Wei.
Have the newbie missions been optimized?
We simplified them.
They're no longer cumbersome.
Yeah.
The game's trial experience
is much better now.
Lv, Yada.
Is it okay on your end?
Mr. Pei really reminded me.
I was only writing code,
completely ignoring player feedback.
We need to communicate more with PMs.
Don't worry.
I've put all the rewards and gift packs
into the missions.
Fully coordinating with Lv.
The update will go live soon.
Mr. Pei is right.
A game attracts players with gameplay.
We should let players
focus on enjoying the game.
Everything goes back to the game itself.
I've modified it.
(Are people still playing
the Divine Mountains and Seas?)
(Seems like they quietly updated it.)
(How smooth. Tengda actually listened.)
(All the parts
we complained about are fixed.)
(I ordered takeout in
the Divine Mountains and Seas.)
(Half an hour later,
it actually arrived.)
(Tengda. Amazing.)
(Tengda, what god-tier move is this?)
(You can read web novels in-game?)
(Zhongdian Web Fiction's novels
are a bit abstracted,)
(but the process of collecting
fragments is interesting.)
(The real-world collab in
the Divine Mountains and Seas)
(is incredible.)
ID.
Can't Compare to Boran.
The Divine Mountains and Seas, Zone 49,
Revelers' Zone. Takeout has arrived.
Whose is it?
Mine.
Coming.
(The Divine Mountains and Seas)
It's out.
The fragment dropped.
(The CEO Has an Exclusive Crush on You)
You got a fragment to read
the extra chapter
of Chit & Chat's novel.
I've always wanted
to read this extra chapter.
But in The Divine Mountains and Seas,
fragments drop randomly.
Each player gets different texts.
Which dungeon
did you get this fragment from?
(The Divine Mountains and Seas
launched a wishing mode,)
(collaborating
with Dreams Fulfilled Immediately.)
(Attention.
Dreams Fulfilled Immediately)
(no longer receive private messages.)
(Use the wishing pool
in the Divine Mountains and Seas.)
(I tested it, and it works.)
(The Divine Mountains and Seas)
Travelers
of the Divine Mountains and Seas.
Don't worry.
So far,
we've received
tens of thousands of wishes
from travelers.
(Please give us a little more time.)
(We'll help everyone...)
(We'll help... We...)
(We'll help everyone
fulfill their wishes one by one.)
(Stay tuned)
(to the Divine Mountains and Seas.)
(Scan the QR code to download.)
Ms. Tang.
This player wants a free meal
from the private kitchen. Approve?
No problem, approved.
Ms. Tang.
This player wants to join Tengda.
How should we reply?
Thank them for their interest.
And tell them to follow
the recruitment info online.
Oh, right.
Give them
a few more sets of game equipment.
Got it.
Ms. Tang.
This player wants Lu Zhiyao's autograph.
Mr. Lu, I'm here to visit.
I need your help with something.
Mr. Lu.
Well...
Could you provide
some autographed photos
for the Divine Mountains and Seas
players?
Originally,
I added a few lines to your character.
But after thinking it through, it's
better to add them to Shi Huo instead.
You add a few lines of dialogue,
and I'll sign a few autographs.
(Tang_Student)
(I really got Lu Zhiyao's autograph!)
(- I want one too.
- Me too!)
Is that how you film vertical videos?
You just rotate the monitor vertically.
Where's everyone?
Mr. Shi.
No, what's the rush in calling me over?
I can't amend the script.
Why should Lu Zhiyao's autograph
be used as a gift?
It's Mr. Lu.
He offered it voluntarily.
I'm not voluntary?
I'll also provide some.
Enough.
I believe many friends
already received...
(autographs from Shi Huo and Lu Zhiyao.)
This collab in
the Divine Mountains and Seas
breaks the barrier between
reality and the game world.
(Do you still have extra autographs?)
(Completely)
(Can Mr. Qiao draw me too?)
(connecting them.)
(Truly an industry miracle.)
Okay, no problem.
Mr. Zhou.
Continue optimizing.
What's up?
Tengda released a new update,
fixing several
previously criticized points
and also implemented
an internal collab between the game
and Tengda's ecosystem
to attract players.
Looks like
it's working.
Then find a way to suppress it.
But the budget...
Eric
might not give us
that much support.
After all,
Fingle
isn't ours either.
Just ignore it.
Keep going.
As for Eric,
I'll convince him.
Come in.
Yada.
Want something to eat?
I'll order some takeout.
Later.
Wait until I finish this.
After the update releases,
new players will start coming in.
We have to optimize the program quickly
to ensure smooth gameplay.
Speed it up.
Okay.
I missed mealtime again.
I'm so hungry
that I'm getting hypoglycemic.
I'm so hungry.
Everyone.
You'll only
have energy to work after you eat.
Snacks alone won't do.
You need quality protein.
Here it comes.
Here.
Put them here.
Everyone.
From today on,
your meals
will be provided
by the private kitchen.
Don't just stay there.
Come over and eat.
Come.
Hurry up, come on.
It's fine, come on.
Everything's delicious.
How is it?
Come on.
There's more.
There's some here too.
Eat that one. That steak is good.
Everyone.
I have more good news to announce.
Mr. Ma, Director Zhuang, and Sibo
have contacted a popular anime IP.
The rights holder tried out
the Divine Mountains and Seas
and thought it was excellent,
so they've decided
to collaborate with us.
- Great!
Thank you all.
Our shoot
won't start anytime soon.
Director Zhuang and I
don't have much to do,
so we came to help out.
Thanks, Huang.
Well,
the game
is connected to film and TV,
so I was thinking
maybe I could help expand it
from a story perspective.
Not now.
Eat first.
Yes.
We'll expand later.
Eat first.
Eat up.
Sibo. You've done a great job
with this game.
The rights
to the Divine Mountains and Seas
are with you, right?
We have to do film and TV.
I'll go talk to Mr. Pei.
Stop right there.
Stop it.
This isn't open yet.
Everyone.
Good news.
Check Net,
several social media platforms
and short-video platforms
that blocked us
are all sorted out now.
We hadn't officially partnered before,
so we used this opportunity
to sign
new strategic cooperation agreements.
Now you can find
information
about the Divine Mountains and Seas
on all platforms.
Come.
Lin Wan, eat first.
Come eat.
You worked hard.
Everything's good.
Steak.
There's more. Looks delicious.
This steak is good.
This is perfect for ladies.
Hardly any oil at all.
This one's good.
That one's fine too.
Eat more.
Eat up.
(Infinite Imagination was fun at first,)
(but later it's just bad.)
(The gameplay's repetitive,)
(with severe homogenization.)
(Infinite imagination my foot.)
(You can tell
they didn't put in effort.)
(Who knows where the money went?)
(They should've paid me.
I'd do a better job than them.)
(In the end, it's about the game itself.)
(When competing in games,
quality is above all.)
(There was a time)
(you couldn't find the Divine Mountains
and Seas on Check Net.)
(It was definitely Fingle's doing.)
(It's finally fixed now.)
(Tengda wouldn't
pull such dirty tricks.)
(I officially announce)
(unconditional support for Tengda.)
(I support
the Divine Mountains and Seas.)
(The Divine Mountains
and Seas Fights Back.)
(This game is amazing!)
(I can't stop playing!)
(Profits: The Divine Mountains and Seas,
Private Kitchen, Sloth Gym)
(Returning to Shore, Four Wall Apartments,
Zhongdian Web Fiction)
(Losses: Feihuang Pictures,
Dreams Fulfilled Immediately)
(Tengda Total Assets)
What are you all doing?
You can't even figure this out?
(General Manager's Office)
Useless!
Eric.
As long as you increase my budget
a little more,
I can definitely beat
the Divine Mountains and Seas.
I will beat them.
Eric. Give me one more chance.
Mr. Zhou.
I will definitely win.
I'm not here to discuss that.
This is no longer about
whether to increase the budget.
After verification by all departments,
during promotion, Infinite Imagination
incited abuse,
stirred conflict,
and fabricated false information.
These malicious actions
have crossed the bottom line
of game marketing practices.
Relevant authorities require our
cooperation with the investigation.
They don't know anything.
This is just normal marketing.
Just tactics.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
Don't worry, I will...
I... I'll explain everything clearly.
I'm afraid it's already too late.
This incident
has caused serious damage
to Fingle, to me,
and to my father.
You've been in this industry
a long time.
I hope
you can see the bigger picture.
I understand.
Eric.
I... I'll explain everything clearly.
This was all my personal behavior.
It has nothing to do with the company.
Mr. Zhou.
Xuming.
I've dragged you down.
Mr. Zhou, don't say that.
All these years,
you've always taken good care of me.
Work hard.
There will be other chances.
As for me,
there's probably
no chance left in this industry.
Xuming.
You've followed me for years.
At this point,
tell me the truth.
Where exactly am I worse than Pei Qian?
Why would you think that, Mr. Zhou?
You're outstanding.
How is he even comparable to you?
But ever since Pei Qian appeared,
my life
has felt like hitting a wall.
You've seen it all.
I've always worked diligently,
never daring to slack off.
I always met
every request from my superiors.
Do you think those projects
were ones I wanted to do?
Every project the group assigned me
was a tough nut to crack.
But no matter how hard they were,
didn't Sky Fire
always complete them
seriously and thoroughly?
We also became
the most efficient studio
in the industry.
But now,
I don't even know how I lost.
Mr. Zhou.
Pei Qian knows nothing.
He's just lucky.
A fluke.
Pure dumb luck.
Xuming.
I'll trouble you
to send me one last time.
Okay.
Where to?
(Shenhua International)
Qian.
Dreams Fulfilled Immediately.
Well...
Where is he?
What's wrong?
I must have been mistaken.
I thought...
It's nothing.
I must get revenge today,
I'm telling you.
Hello, everyone.
Welcome to
What Happens in the Gaming Industry?
Recently, Fingle has been suspected of
malicious commercial competition,
drawing widespread attention.
The relevant authorities will launch
a rectification campaign,
focusing on self-media accounts
chasing traffic without limits,
spreading false information,
inciting hostility and abuse,
and other online misconduct.
Relevant regulations will
be issued to strictly punish
seriously problematic
and non-compliant platforms,
actively maintaining a clean,
harmonious online environment.
♪The rain has stopped,
and the sky finally clears♪
♪Yet water still drips from the eaves♪
♪The sun rises,
and dark clouds all disperse♪
♪But why won't my heart dry out?♪
♪Evening glow
washes over unspoken monologues♪
♪Old photos
dusted with a layer of white♪
♪The future we promised♪
♪Was never unwrapped after all♪
♪This wind blows and blows♪
♪Blows but cannot dispel
the haze in my heart♪
♪Longing is rain-soaked kindling♪
♪Like patches of damp moss♪
♪It won't ignite a shred of warmth♪
♪Time spins and spins♪
♪Yet cannot turn back that warmth♪
♪Memories are patches of light
not yet dimmed♪
♪Right and wrong
drift into the evening breeze♪
♪I want to ask, but all questions are♪
♪Blown away by this wind♪
♪Blows but cannot dispel
the haze in my heart♪
♪Longing is rain-soaked kindling♪
♪Like wet moss, clump after clump♪
♪It won't ignite a shred of warmth♪
♪This heavy rain falls, falls, falls♪
♪But it won't wash away
the lingering regret♪
♪We were predestined scenes in a script♪
♪Pushed aside,
with no room to advance or retreat♪
♪Sinking
into the boundless sea of people♪
♪No longer connected♪