=No Pain No Gain=
(Adapted from the Qidian novel)
("Losing Money to Be a Tycoon"
by Qingshan Quzui)
=Episode 12=
(This story is purely fictional.)
Welcome to
the Returning to Shore Cup
Poetry Contest.
(Returning to Shore Cup)
Currently, our record holder is
Qian Liang,
Mr. Qian!
- Qian!
- Press forward without hesitation!
Up next, let's welcome
today's challenger,
Mrs. Wang Mingxia!
Let the contest
begin!
Mr. Qian, recite a poem.
He Zhizhang, Tang Dynasty.
Ode to the Willow.
Like emerald jade,
the willow stands so tall,
ten thousand
green silk ribbons gently fall.
Who cut these slender leaves
so fine and neat?
The spring breeze in February
is like a pair of scissors.
- Excellent!
Mr. Qian, there's no need to worry.
Returning to Shore has
a dialect recognition function.
Mrs. Wang,
it's your turn now.
Du Fu, Tang Dynasty.
On Hearing That the Imperial Army
Has Recovered Henan and Hebei.
It's said that suddenly
Jibei is recaptured.
At first, I hear it,
tears soak all my clothes.
I turn to see my wife and children.
Where has sorrow gone?
I loosely roll my books and poems,
joy near madness grows.
In daylight, singing loud,
I must drink deep.
With youth as company,
how gladly I go home.
- Excellent!
Liu Changqing, Tang Dynasty.
Seeing Off the Monk Lingche.
In dusky green,
the Bamboo Grove Temple stands.
Faint, distant bells
resound at evening's end.
Wang Wei, Tang Dynasty.
Birdsong Valley.
In quiet ease, osmanthus blossoms fall;
Night deepens,
spring hills lie empty, still.
Wang Bo, Tang Dynasty.
In the Mountains.
The long river grieves,
its course seemingly stalled.
From ten thousand miles away,
my heart yearns for home.
Wang Changling, Tang Dynasty.
(Poetry Contest)
Seeing Off Guo, the Clerk.
The Huai River
glimmers green beside the gate.
Reined-in horses linger,
bound by the host's heart.
Lu You, Song Dynasty.
The Long Ballad.
The nation's wrongs unavenged,
heroes grow old.
At night, the treasured sword
in its case still rings.
When shall we triumph,
feast the valiant host;
As midnight snow
weighs down Feihu City's walls?
(Victory)
- Excellent!
Excellent!
Mr. Qian, that's alright.
You've already done great.
We still have plenty
of prizes waiting for you.
(Sloth Gym)
This is a lifetime membership card
for Tengda's Sloth Gym.
This is great!
Come, Mr. Qian.
Let's take a group photo
as a keepsake.
(Returning to Shore Cup,
Jinchuan City's First Poetry Contest)
Recently,
the Returning to Shore Cup,
Jinchuan City's First Poetry Contest,
has been held in full swing
at multiple parks and communities
across the city.
(It is reported)
(that this surge in
poetry-reciting enthusiasm)
(is linked to a game titled)
(Jinchuan City's First Poetry Contest)
(Returning to Shore.)
(The game gained rapid popularity)
(and sparked widespread social attention)
(due to its unique design)
(that cleverly integrates elements
of classical poetry into gameplay.)
(The game "Returning to Shore"
is a platform where gaming meets)
(traditional culture to spark new ideas.)
Not all video games are bad for us.
There can also be games
that combine education
with entertainment
and help people improve.
Tengda
has always held such a belief.
We devote ourselves to developing
more positive
and meaningful games for players.
(For Returning to Shore,)
(not only did we develop)
(the Poetry Contest Mini Program)
(and hold the Top Ranking Contest,)
(but we also held many offline events)
(in the city.)
(Our goal is to enable
groups beyond players to join in)
(and foster a nationwide passion)
(for classical poetry culture.)
What do you guys think?
Bao, you looked pretty photogenic.
Really?
You looked much more energetic on TV.
But it feels awkward
when I see myself on TV.
Ms. Lin Wan, people
have been contacting me non-stop.
They're requesting authorization
for a poetry event.
Me too.
Numerous university clubs,
community groups,
and even senior universities
have approached us.
Many people had
signed up for the event online.
It's way more than I had imagined.
We need to test the mini program
as soon as possible.
Alright.
Let's do it, then.
Time to work.
Returning to Shore Program Team!
Come to the meeting room!
I'm sorry, Mr. Pei.
The hype of Returning to Shore
is primarily focused on
schools, communities,
and the elderly.
Judging by the current trend,
we can only break even at most
by the end of the month.
It's way less than Divine General Pact
and Deserted Island Sharpshooter.
It's our fault.
Did you say
that Returning to Shore
will break even this month?
Barely.
This is primarily due to your strategy.
My strategy?
What strategy?
Did you forget?
When I asked you about
the game's promotion,
you told me to increase
the publicity cost
and spend as much money as I should.
So, that's why you held
a lucky draw in Jinchuan, huh?
Lv,
I'm sure you've devoted
a lot of effort into
this project as well.
So, did you just come to
and get off work on time
just to set up
a good image in front of me?
No. Mr. Pei, that's not it.
This project...
He didn't work overtime at all.
He was just fast and efficient
in writing code.
Yeah.
Mr. Pei, after that, I realized
that you were different
from other business owners.
That's why I wanted to try my best.
But don't worry.
Although I don't work overtime,
I promise to finish my tasks on time.
It's because this job
is a piece of cake for me.
Mr. Pei, before this, you said
that Returning to Shore must strive to
reach the standard of a top-tier game
and that the investment in art resources
must be maximized.
Since you were so supportive,
Ruan Guangjian and his department
actually gave this project their all.
The original artwork
is absolutely stunning.
Mr. Pei, Ruan Guangjian is here.
Mr. Pei,
I have to apologize to you.
I admit I did a half-hearted job
on Divine General Pact's artwork.
Sorry about that.
It was because
I thought you were
a terrible...
No, I mean,
an ordinary business owner.
That's why I gave you that.
I didn't expect you
to let me pass on the first draft.
And, you even paid me a lot for it.
My partners and I thought
that we'd let you down.
Therefore, this time,
I'll surely do my best.
Back when Guangjian was at rock bottom,
fresh out of school,
he was tormented by his client
until he questioned his existence.
But after meeting you,
he thought that producing
excellent work was worth it.
The ink-wash style Lin Wan had chosen
fits perfectly with poetry.
Thus, I was hugely inspired.
Mr. Ruan, it's all thanks
to your excellent work.
It has gone viral in the original art,
cosplay and the ancient
art style communities.
It has become widely popular.
Ruan
Guang
Jian!
Where are your glasses?
Thanks to you,
I made quite a fortune.
After we met
at the phone booth that day,
I had LASIK surgery the other day.
Now that his vision is normal,
he draws much faster.
But the problem is,
ours is a soul-like.
It's a difficult game.
And, it has a theme related to poetry.
The sarcasm is off the charts.
Who actually plays a game like this?
Mr. Pei, you're right.
This time, besides conventional gamers,
we also received many organic fans.
Returning to Shore
has sparked a nationwide craze
for learning classical poetry.
Even public opinion has turned positive.
Why didn't you guys
tell me about it earlier?
We thought you knew
that our back-end data was skyrocketing.
Look at how happy Mr. Pei is.
Mr. Pei is so happy.
(Multi-Front Loss Strategy:
Staff Management, DreamForge Capital)
(Games, Zhongdian Web Fiction
and Privite Restaurant)
(When you see a beautiful view,)
(all you can say is
"Stunning" and "Legendary", right?)
(Or you'll say that it's gorgeous.)
(But besides that, we can also say,)
(Beauty beyond naming unfolds;
Pure radiance fills the river city.)
(The river winds
beyond the world's expanse,)
(Mountains hover,
half-seen in misty trance.)
(Lately, the Chinese-style game,
Returning to Shore,)
(integrated classical
poetry into gaming,)
(sparking a renaissance
in traditional Chinese culture.)
(It has let more people realize)
(that beyond internet slang,)
(we possess such magnificent poetry)
(and a truly magnificent language,)
(letting us rediscover Chinese romance.)
I won't be reimbursed for this.
Mr. Pei,
are you having a good time here alone?
Did I look like
I was having a good time?
Weren't you having a good time
when you did this?
You can think
whatever you like.
Lin Wan,
it's like this.
Your parents and I
have the same thought.
We hope that you can return
to Shenhua International.
Stop getting involved with
Returning to Shore. It has no future.
But why?
Did my parents approach you?
Mr. Pei, don't worry.
I won't cause any trouble for you.
I know. As an employer, you're worried
that an employee like me
cannot endure hardships.
But that's not who I am.
I've finally achieved some results
with Returning to Shore.
I plan to make an English version
and sell it internationally.
No!
You mustn't.
Just look at you.
You're already very capable.
Stop putting in that much effort.
You have to give your future self
some space to grow, right?
You're exaggerating it.
No, I'm not!
Lin Wan,
I'm begging you here.
Please go home.
Don't stay here anymore.
Mr. Pei, you're right.
I do need to go home
in a few more days.
I'll head back and ask my parents
if they have any good suggestions
for the game.
No!
Right now!
Go home right now!
I'll book the ticket for you!
Wait, Mr. Pei.
My parents are in Jinchuan.
They came here to visit me
as they knew I was busy lately.
Mr. Pei,
where will we celebrate
our success this time?
(Profits: M&Y Internet Cafe,
Private Kitchen,)
(Sloth Gym, Phone Booth,
Returning to Shore)
(Loss: Zhongdian Web Fiction)
(Tengda Total Asset)
(Ms. Mei)
(Mr. Pei,)
(please pay)
(the management fee for this year.)
(There's a discount if you pay it early.)
I'm on the brink of bankruptcy.
Reincarnated As
A Poor Man Again?
That hits too close to my heart.
It's so relatable.
Why isn't anyone reading this?
(Zhongdian Web Fiction, Confirm Payment)
Forget it.
I still have to pay off my loan.
I don't have the money for this.
(Liang Qingfan (Designer))
(Ma Yang)
Hello, Ma Yang.
Qian, what's going on?
You didn't even reply to my texts.
All of our projects were huge successes.
Let's celebrate our success.
I've already booked a restaurant.
Your favorite restaurant...
I'm not going!
(Troubles)
Have some lobsters. This sauce.
By the way, Mr. Pei,
Jinchuan TV Station said
that they wanted to make an
exclusive film for Returning to Shore.
When are you free?
I'll arrange an appointment for you
and their person-in-charge.
We can talk about it later.
Mr. Pei,
our website has already
gained a foothold.
I was wondering if we could develop
some subscription-based projects.
We can't just keep publishing novels
without making a profit.
What do you think?
We've already made a lot of money
with DreamForge Capital.
The new proposal that I wrote
and Zhang Wang's new project...
Why did Ms. Xin not approve them?
You have no idea.
My proposal was flawless.
It was so perfect
that it almost made me shed tears.
If you keep this up,
there's no way I can surpass Li Shi.
Why are you asking me?
How should I know?
Go and ask Ms. Xin yourself.
Help me persuade her.
She never listens to me.
She just rolls her eyes
whenever she sees me.
If you keep this up,
we'll have nowhere to spend
the 20 million yuan we received.
Keeping it...
How much did we receive?
20 million yuan.
Why didn't you transfer
the money to my bank account, then?
Didn't Ms. Xin tell you?
A business owner liked
the business model of Sloth Gym.
He signed a 20-million-yuan contract
with us right away.
What's wrong with Mr. Pei?
He's happy. Just look at him.
He's trying to pretend
that he's not happy again.
You see?
Mr. Pei is so happy.
Since everyone is here,
let's take a group photo
and commemorate this happy moment.
Sure.
- Alright. Hurry.
- Okay.
Hello. Miss,
can you help us take a photo?
Come. All of you, sit here.
Here, help us take a group photo.
Alright.
Okay.
Ladies and gentlemen,
take a group photo.
Okay.
Have a sweet life!
20 million yuan!
(Away with all the troubles,
have a sweet life)
What?
Li Shi invested 20 million yuan
in Sloth Gym?
Deity above,
please accept my offerings.
From now on,
you'll enjoy the main course
while I'll enjoy the soup.
Let's make it a win-win situation.
It's decided then.
Mr. Li Jr.,
this is my first time seeing you
so generous
with giving Yakult away.
What do you know?
In the business world,
a generous heart
will earn you the world.
Prepare a car for me.
Okay.
(Mingyun Villa)
All your dishes have arrived.
Please enjoy.
Isn't this the fish I just caught?
It's super fresh.
Alright, thank you so much.
Go and take a bath.
Okay.
Mr. Li Jr.,
I appreciate your kind intention,
but can you please not
treat me to a meal next time?
Just wire the money to my account, okay?
Mr. Pei,
you still like to crack jokes,
don't you?
When I invited you
to Ming House for a meal,
you rejected me every time.
Now, I've come all the way
to your private kitchen
and caught a fish here.
I'm sure you'll enjoy
the meal now, right?
I'm not joking.
I was dealt
a serious blow in life recently.
I'm at my lowest point in life.
I won't be able to last for long.
To be honest,
I can barely pay my mortgage now.
The meal you're having today
is costing me a few months'
worth of expenses.
Mr. Pei, I didn't expect you
to be this straightforward.
It seems you do take me
as a real friend.
Mr. Pei,
when it comes to business,
having a tight cash flow
is actually quite common.
I do find myself in
that situation sometimes as well.
Don't worry about it.
Perfect timing.
I think the 20 million yuan
I invested in Sloth Gym
should have arrived
in your bank account.
I hope it can help you
resolve your crisis.
Wait. Were you the one who invested
20 million in us?
I told you already.
I'm trying to make it
a win-win situation here.
And, in addition
to these twenty million,
all future profits from my gym
will also be shared with you.
Mr. Pei, calm down for now.
Actually,
I came here today
because...
Mainly, I wanted you
to reveal the next step
of our investment plan.
What should we do next?
What other trashy investment projects
does Jinchuan have?
The kind of project
that, at first glance,
could save my life,
and simultaneously
wipe out your entire 20 million.
You don't understand at all.
Those projects
are too common.
They're not enough.
I need that kind of godsend project,
the kind nobody else wants to touch.
The bigger the project, the better.
The more investment, the better!
I think I understand something.
You see,
Mr. Pei,
you don't have
sufficient funds right now.
That's right.
Even so, you don't want
a stable project that can
make us a stable profit.
You think it's pointless.
Now, you want
to make a huge comeback, right?
Fine.
I'll share all of my investment secrets
with you today.
Okay.
Buy on dips, not rallies.
Seek losses, not gains.
Mr. Li Jr.,
do you know if there
are any projects in Jinchuan
that are at the bottom
of Jinchuan's investment chain?
I've just thought of one.
Mr. Pei,
why are you drawn to this project?
This place is pretty nice.
This is the only building
within a ten-mile radius.
It's not obstructed by anything.
The developer positions this project
as an urban landmark
that has integrated diverse functions,
including high-end apartments,
quality residences,
and trendy commercial districts.
They also intend
to develop a gigantic city park.
It's right downstairs.
A park?
Where is it?
It's right under our feet.
At least a corner of it.
This is something else.
This...
It's quite rough around the edges, huh?
According to the materials,
traffic here is convenient.
There's only a dirt road.
With elevated highways
extending in all directions.
They're not connected to anywhere.
With outstanding infrastructure.
It's empty and desolate.
And, in the future, it'll...
Mr. Pei, I can't make myself read it.
Why don't you read it...
I'm buying it.
I'm buying
the entire building.
Mr. Pei.
You are
truly extraordinary.
So, Pei...
No, I mean,
Mr. Pei.
I thought you called me here
to discuss Mingri Apartments.
Why did you get yourself
another apartment?
Mingri Apartments belonged to me.
The one Tengda had bought
belonged to my family.
How could I renovate my own place
without renovating
my family's place first?
Mr. Pei,
your dedication to your career
is truly admirable.
No wonder you're the boss.
I thought you were just a deadbeat.
No.
I mean,
since you're entrusting such
a huge project to us,
I definitely won't let you down.
This is our design proposal for
the interior style of
Tengda's apartments.
Let me show you.
This is the creamy Instagram-style look.
This is the minimalist look.
And, there's one look
that suits you perfectly.
It's the Splendor of Success look.
Of course.
We also offer a new
Chinese-style light classical look.
They're too traditional.
If so, please tell me your request.
Mr. Liang,
is it possible
to equip Tengda's apartments
with more amenities
than any other apartments on the market?
We will provide users
with 100-inch 4K TVs,
a complete professional audio system,
a screen with a projector,
a variety of viewing options,
even gaming consoles,
an automatic clothes dryer
that can gather dust automatically,
a cleaning robot,
smart locks,
and a leather sofa
with a fully-functional massage system.
And smart home appliances as well.
Regarding the AI human
body sensing system
you mentioned last time,
we'll install that too.
Mr. Pei,
if you include all of that,
the cost will be quite substantial.
For the sake of the users' experience,
the cost shouldn't matter.
Mr. Liang,
just go ahead and shop with confidence.
We won't aim for the best,
but we'll aim for the most expensive!
Alright.
And, don't worry.
With our company as a guarantor,
your wages won't be defaulted.
Alright.
Mr. Pei,
if so, does that mean
we need to step up
our hard furnishing game too?
If both hard furnishings
and interior decor are top-notch,
the apartments will sell like hotcakes.
You see,
I know the interior decor
is already extravagant.
But when it comes
to the hard furnishings,
we should go for a huge contrast.
The bigger the contrast is, the better.
I've decided.
We won't put any wallpaper,
any flooring,
or paint the unit.
Walls and floors are pure concrete.
It's all about that raw
and unpolished look.
We'll show them
the scene of ruins and rubble,
with a refreshing change of pace.
Mr. Pei,
wouldn't this style of interior design
be too avant-garde?
I'm worried
that many clients won't be
able to accept it.
How could that be the case?
You see, I...
I mean, a friend of mine
actually moved straight
into an unfurnished house.
And, he's still living there.
That's what Tengda does.
We only attract people
with the same frequency.
We never force relationships.
And, Mr. Liang, remember this.
The users are strictly prohibited
from doing their own renovations.
We must retain
the authenticity of the apartments.
Okay.
Understood.
Mr. Pei,
but in the future,
how are we supposed
to introduce this unit to our clients?
I mean, the huge contrasting style
that you're going for.
This apartment
is drafty on all sides
and bare.
We'll call it
the Four Wall Apartments.
(Shenhua International)
Mr. Liang,
I'll be depending on you in the future.
Mr. Pei!
No worry. Just spend the money quickly
and without any hesitation.
Tengda will back you up.
Don't save any money for us.
- Alright, Mr. Pei.
- Okay?
Okay, Mr. Pei.
Mr. Pei,
I finally caught you.
Are you free now?
Mr. Pei, now that Returning to Shore
is officially on track,
I've made another
preliminary game design proposal
for an MMORPG.
It's called
The Divine Mountains and Seas.
Please review it.
(Preliminary Game Design Proposal)
No rush.
You've worked overtime
every day on Returning to Shore.
It's already been tough on you.
Other employers
might only care about your results,
but I only care about
how much sleep you've gotten.
When you're free,
you should head to Sloth Gym more often
and rest there.
I saw online
that many people with insomnia
have been cured.
Mr. Pei, it's fine.
I'm not suffering from insomnia.
I'm not tired either.
I just wanted to show you my proposal.
I see great potential in this game.
I can feel your enthusiasm.
However, since its founding,
Tengda has released four games.
And, each of them is very popular.
It's perplexing indeed.
I often wondered
if we truly had the capability
to create such hit games
and whether or not
we deserve all of this.
Mr. Pei,
every time Sky Fire releases a game,
they think they're amazing.
But you? You reflect upon
your past actions.
You're already better
than 99% of our peers.
But the development of Tengda Game
has stalled.
I think our priority is to...
I think our priority is to
think.
We need to figure out
the kind of games that
current users like to play.
We need to figure out how to create
a groundbreaking
and innovative game.
Mr. Pei,
could it be that you're not interested
in developing new games at all?
How could that be?
Don't worry.
I'll surely review your proposal.
You must remember this too.
Think more,
feel more,
and produce less.
Mr. Pei!
That's my laptop!
Could it be
that my idea was too immature?
Was it why Mr. Pei
was uninterested in it?
I don't think that's possible.
I've reviewed your proposal
thoroughly.
As the chief playtester of Tengda Game,
I can tell you this
with the gaming instinct
I was born with.
If we make The Divine Mountains and Seas
according to your proposal,
it'll definitely be a hit.
I feel the same.
I want to play the game
just from reading your proposal alone.
Do you guys truly think so?
But Mr. Pei told me to reflect upon it
and be more innovative.
That's because
he didn't read your proposal.
How else can your proposal
be more innovative?
What's there to reflect upon?
He'll know that this game
is the kind
that he wants to develop after reading
your proposal.
Thanks, Bao, Lv.
I almost lost all confidence just now.
But after hearing that from you two,
I feel pretty touched.
Why don't we work on it together?
With Bao's meticulousness
and Lv's technical support,
we'll definitely hit the mark.
It'll definitely shut Mr. Pei up.
Sure.
But, wait, I'm not working overtime.
Mr. Pei caught me
when I worked overtime last time.
If he catches me again,
I'll be in huge trouble.
I have to be useless
so that people won't be able to use me.
I know that.
I won't tell you to work overtime.
I just want to know if you...
No.
Bao,
without the support of
a world-class
and god-tier
back-end developer like Lv,
we should be mentally prepared.
It'll take us at least
60 years to complete the game.
Yeah.
You see,
without the help of a prodigy like Lv,
there's no way
The Divine Mountains and Seas
can be as perfect as we imagined.
Yeah.
What a shame.
Wait.
I'm quite interested
in The Divine Mountains and Seas.
I can help you guys
when I slack off during work hours.
You're welcome.
Cheers.
Four Wall Apartments is my last bet.
I absolutely cannot let
the previous tragedy of
back-to-back betrayals happen again.
All those betrayers
could always find my weaknesses
and target them.
No.
I have to form a department
and keep them in check.
Pei...
Mr. Pei,
what's going on here?
You actually recognized me?
Put this on and turn around.
Turn around.
This concerns Tengda's
confidential information.
Do not show it to anyone.
Tang,
it must've been tough on you
after joining DreamForge Capital.
I observed you in secret.
I found out
that although you don't like to speak,
and have a low sense of presence,
you're very trustworthy.
After giving it much consideration,
I've decided to entrust you
with an important mission.
Are you
ready?
The instructions
are in here.
(Four Wall Apartments)
Mr. Pei, please come in.
The Four Wall Apartments
has reached the handover standards.
The wall and flooring
are all concrete.
The furniture and appliances
are top-of-the-line.
It's also equipped with
whole-home smart control.
The users will definitely experience
a stark contrast.
Mr. Pei,
the whole-home smart control
can be accessed with AI voice control.
As per your design,
we've set up commands
for users to change the scene at will.
You may give it a try.
Golden splendor!
Mr. Pei,
you wanted this, right?
Correct!
Mr. Liang,
your design
matches my requirement perfectly.
Good job.
Cui,
I'll leave the rest to you.
Mr. Pei,
thank you for your trust.
Thanks to you,
I've been promoted to the regional GM.
It feels so surreal.
What about this?
I'll double-check it with you.
I want to confirm
if you have any requests
concerning the sales
and rental of these units.
For example, the price and so on.
The Four Wall Apartments
is only meant for rent, not for sale.
Only meant for rent?
Only meant for rent, not for sale?
That's right.
To ensure the users' needs are met,
no subletting or short-term rentals
are allowed here.
We'll provide users
with 24-hour housekeeping
and butler services.
Look at all these appliances.
There will be frequent updates
to their software.
We'll update them on a regular basis.
They're available for lease
starting at ten years,
with payment required, in full upfront.
In full upfront?
If so,
Mr. Pei,
don't you think
the price is too high?
You see,
for example,
if you wish to take
the high-end approach,
Jinchuan has plenty of wealthy people.
They have plenty of other choices.
The thing is,
you're not allowing the clients
to do their own renovations.
They have no reason
to choose this unit.
Mr. Liang,
tell Cui
about the concept of our apartment.
With affinity,
even walls cannot keep us apart.
Without it, even face-to-face, we pass.
That's right.
Therefore, our apartments
must strictly adhere
to environmental standards.
You see, renovation was just finished
not long ago.
It must have high levels
of formaldehyde.
Therefore, we should
leave it for the time being
and let it air.
Mr. Pei,
we didn't do any renovations at all.
The furniture we used was all
made from eco-friendly materials.
We've been airing them for some time.
As per your request,
we hired professional help to
remove the formaldehyde smell.
Three times!
It's way lower than normal standards.
No need to air them any longer.
Even so, that won't do.
We should follow maternal
and infant safety standards.
For the sake of our children,
we have to let it air!
(Shenhua International)
(Tenda Directive No. 1 (Top Secret)
Management Trainee Program)
(Tang,)
(as a management trainee,)
(you must do your internship)
(in all departments,)
(fully engage in
the work of every department)
(and every individual,
and play your part to the fullest.)
(As for the specific details,)
(you may follow my instructions.)
Mr. Pei told you to join
the Gaming Division?
That's right.
Mr. Pei said
my main mission
is to do my internship
in all departments of Tengda.
Do you guys need any help?
Tang,
you're not in the same field as me.
You don't know how to code either.
I don't need your help.
Lv,
I have to criticize you for that.
Tang is a management trainee.
She's here to learn.
You know?
You should be nicer to her.
Tang, it's fine that you don't know
how to code.
You know how to play games, right?
Come and test
the games with us for now,
okay?
Sure. Thanks, Bao.
It's like this.
The system requirements
for a playtester are quite demanding.
This is the new
top-of-the-line PC I purchased.
You should try it.
Okay.
The Gaming Division is truly different.
Even the keyboard
and screen can be folded, huh?
Who said it could be folded?
Bao,
why don't we do some playtesting?
Son,
I think I should pick you up.
This...
Why don't we try another move?
Try to stretch your waist slowly,
especially you guys
who always sit too much.
I can't
move my waist.
Mr. Ma.
I can see
that your eyes are wet.
Your lips are dry too.
Is that so?
I think that's a sign
of kidney damage.
What?
Kidney damage?
But it's fine.
Experts said
that it would gradually recover
as long as you drink water
every half an hour.
I'll remind you.
Mr. Ma, it's time.
Time to drink.
That's about it.
Mr. Ma,
stop playing.
time to drink.
I'll drink it myself.
Huang,
do you need any help
with Zhongdian Web Fiction?
The works published by these authors
aren't very popular.
They feel dejected.
Help me encourage them
and cheer them up. Thanks.
Encourage them, huh?
Are you working? How's it going?
I've been joining Zhongdian Web Fiction
for quite some time,
but my posts barely get any views,
usually just single digits.
I feel like giving up.
Just give up, then.
You've been writing for some time,
and they barely get any views.
And, you're upset about it too.
Say, could it be that this job
isn't meant for you?
But I write for a living.
What else can I do?
You could start doing self-media.
Since you like to write stuff,
you can write scripts,
or even make vlogs.
I think that'll prove to be
a better prospect for you.
If you get famous,
you'll have your own IP.
Vlog?
Mr. Pei,
should I continue with
the management trainee program?
I've been following your instructions,
but I feel like
something's off about everyone.
They're all trying to avoid me.
What should I do?
Tang,
it's been tough on you.
You may cease
your operation for now.
And, tell everyone
that the Four Wall Apartments
is ready for occupancy.
Alright, Mr. Pei.
Management trainee...
I wonder which genius came up with that.
Now, I can prevent any backstabbing,
and I'll be compensated, too.
I have a 100-inch TV now.
I also own a house with
two rooms and one living room.
The Four Wall Apartments
have lost so much money.
I suppose the renovation
of Mingri Apartments
is just around the corner.
(Tengda Family,
congratulations on moving in)
(Partner with Tengda, Share the Journey)
(The house is rented,
but your life isn't.)
(Four Wall Apartments Grand Opening)
♪Come on, baby. Get ready♪
(Tengda Games)
♪Don't panic♪
♪Come on, baby. Get ready♪
Mr. Ma, am I dreaming?
Mr. Pei actually arranged
accommodations for us as well?
(Four Wall Apartments Welcome You)
(Grand Opening)
(Welcome Home)
Where else can we find a boss like him?
Time to drink!
Mr. Ma, tell me.
Nobody is touching my PC again.
Just forget about your PC.
Look at the new apartment
Mr. Pei has prepared for us.
♪Just follow your feelings♪
♪Up, and down♪
Mr. Pei is so nice to us.
He even arranged accommodations for us.
What a great boss.
- Welcome home!
Mr. Pei is too nice to us.
(Easter Eggs at the end.
Don't miss out.)
(Using Classical Poetry to Decode Internet Memes)
When we want to praise
something or someone,
we say 666 or "That's amazing".
But we can also say...
I speak of the noble man,
gentle and warm, like polished jade.
Ah, the worthy gentleman:
cut and shaped, filed and refined.
Not for fame or profit
does he tread the road of honor;
his talent alone lifts him
to the celebratory heavens.
If we feel happy,
besides saying "I'm hyped"
or "This is unreal",
we can also say...
When the great roc
rides the rising wind one day,
it soars straight up,
ninety thousand miles away.
With unbridled joy
and soaring thoughts we fly,
longing to ascend the blue heavens,
gaze at the bright moon high.
I see the green hills rich
with grace and charm,
surely the hills, seeing me,
feel the same in turn.
Head thrown back,
I laugh aloud and stride out the door,
How could people like us
be mere weeds of the moor?
If we feel sad,
besides saying "emo"
and "in my feels",
we can also say...
Delicate dice bear
red-bean marks within,
such lovesickness,
carved to the bone, do you know it?
All worldly affairs
are but a vast dream,
how many autumn chills
does a lifetime endure?
By daylight, sing aloud
and drink without restraint,
with youth as our companion,
how gladly we journey home.
This feeling may one day
become a memory to recall,
yet even then, it was already
steeped in confusion and regret.
When we see beautiful views,
besides saying "Unreal"
or "GOAT",
or "This is stunning",
we can also say...
Beauty beyond naming spreads,
pure radiance fills the river city.
Ten thousand acres of waves shimmer,
breaking the moonlight,
a whole day of breeze and dew
carries the fragrance of lotus.
The river flows
beyond heaven and earth,
mountains appear
and vanish in mist and void.
My heart is as clear as flowing water,
my body as light
as drifting white clouds.