[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[GIRL SINGING]
The flying birds
are dear to God
It doesn't fade
The flying birds
Are dear to God
It doesn't fade
So don't be sad
Stay positive!
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[WINGS FLAPPING,
BIRDS SQUAWKING]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[WAVES SPLASHING]
[FISHERMAN 1]
Hurry up, everyone!
The storm is coming!
Come on!
[FISHERMAN 2] Hey, move it!
Hey, missy!
What are you doing there?
The storm is coming!
Go home!
[MAN] Grace!
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Ow--[MUFFLED SCREAM]
[THUNDER ROARS]
[WATER SPLASHES]
Did you hear that?
Hear what?
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
Missy?
Missy!
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[SARAH] Grace!
Excuse me.
Grace?
Oh!
Sir! Do you remember me?
I'm Sarah. Do you have any
information about my daughter?
Why did they let
the kid wander off?
There's a thunderstorm
and the waves are strong.
[BYSTANDER 1] I heard
it's not an accident.
The kid might've
jumped into the sea.
[BYSTANDER 2] Seriously?
You think a kid would do that?
It's definitely
not an accident.
Who knows, it could
have been premeditated.
- That's right.
- Someone pushed her.
[BYSTANDERS MURMURING]
That must be her stuff.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[BYSTANDERS MURMURING]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[APPLAUSE]
Yes. Don't worry.
I will not miss my flight.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[APPLAUSE]
[HOST] Thank you, Section Narra.
I'll have everything ready
by then.
The grant is very
important to me.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Yes, I will.
Yes.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
Hey, why aren't you
in your costume?
Uh... I forgot.
Oh, did you also forget
to take a shower?
- You stink.
- Yeah.
- You smell bad.
- Your clothes are dirty.
And you have lice too.
- Get out of here!
- Leave!
- I didn't do anything wrong!
- Stay away from us!
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[CLAMORING]
[GRACE] I didn't do
anything wrong!
Just stay there!
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Kids, get ready.
You're up next.
Hang on. Where's Grace?
We haven't seen her, ma'am.
She hasn't shown up.
[APPLAUSE]
That's your cue.
Do your best, okay? Go.
So, you're really leaving?
Teacher Patty,
Happy Teacher's Day!
Thank you.
I'll be leaving for Hong Kong
next month.
Are you sure about that?
Thank you, dear.
You really want to study
migratory birds?
Won't that be boring?
Thank you, dear.
Thank you, thank you.
I've always wanted
to study ornithology.
I just didn't have the money.
That's why I worked hard
on that proposal.
I'm glad it was approved.
Hey, Anna.
You also worked hard
to get a teaching license.
Are you saying the year
you spent here was for nothing?
I only became a teacher
to fund my studies.
I never planned on
doing it long-term.
Thank you.
That's a shame.
You're such a great teacher.
The kids listen to you.
They listen because
they're scared of you.
[GIGGLES]
But seriously, Anna,
the kids need us here.
Have you talked to the principal
about this?
You know you're his favorite.
I'll talk to him soon.
But he can't change my mind.
[PATTY] Thank you.
Thank you so much.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[STUDENT] Why did you force
me to give that?
- It's okay, dear.
- I didn't want to do that.
Let us give a round
of applause
for Section Acacia!
[CHEERING, APPLAUSE]
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
Oh no! They're not in sync!
Classmates, follow me!
[TEACHER] Grace,
what are you doing?!
[APPLAUSE]
[GROANS] Grace! You don't
even have a costume!
[UPBEAT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[TEACHER GROANING]
[TEACHER GROANING] Aah!
My water just broke!
Ugh!
Aah!
[PEOPLE CLAMORING]
[TEACHER CONTINUES GROANING]
[MAN] Call for help!
[CLAMORING CONTINUES]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[STUDENTS SHOUTING,
LAUGHING EXCITEDLY]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS]
Mm. What are the five senses?
Hearing, smelling,
tasting, um...
Common sense?
[STUDENTS LAUGHING]
Shh!
I just taught you that
yesterday.
I want to go home.
"ACCEPTANCE LETTER"
"Booking Details
Booking Date: April 19, 2025
Passenger Details
Anna Grace Sarmiento"
[PHONE RINGING]
Hello?
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
That was fast. I guess
you only answer my calls.
Auntie has something
important to tell you.
Charlie! Charlie, wait--
Hello?
Anna!
Mama.
Why aren't you
answering my calls?
Did you receive
your sister's invitation?
She sent it to your
email last week.
Yes, I got it.
So, when are you coming home?
I'm sorry, Ma.
I won't be able
to come home yet.
Huh?
Why?
I still have school.
You have school?
Are you taking up
your PhD?
No, I mean at an
elementary school.
I work there.
What happened?
I thought you work
as a research assistant
at a university?
It's a long story, Ma.
Can I tell you next time?
[SIGHS]
Anna, this is
a special occasion.
We must be complete.
You haven't been home
in ages.
You need to be at
your sister's wedding.
Oh-- Oh, Princess, talk
to your sister.
If she doesn't want to come,
don't force her.
We'll be fine without her.
Oh my goodness.
Anna...
Please, for my sake.
Come home.
We also have
to file the inn's income tax.
I need you here.
What happened to the
accountant I hired?
I fired them.
I don't like their attitude.
And besides,
you always did our
income tax returns before.
Don't pass it on to others.
You know I only trust you.
Alright.
I'll do it myself.
But, Ma, about the wedding...
Alright.
Think about it.
Next week, Charlie and Princess
will be there.
Princess will have
her dress fitting.
Pick them up
at the airport.
Spend some time with them.
It might change your mind.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
You two...
You didn't help me
convince Anna to come home.
Why are you forcing
her to come to my wedding?
Princess,
I'm doing this for you.
I don't want Wilson's parents
to think negatively of us.
They might think
our family is complicated.
How exactly are
we complicated?
We're doing perfectly fine
without Anna here.
Hey, Princess,
don't be like that.
Anna is still your sister.
Doesn't seem like it.
She hasn't been
home in what?
Eight years?
Erin barely remembers
her anymore.
Right, Erin?
You know, if I were Anna,
I wouldn't want
to go home either
because of that
attitude of yours.
Charlie, Princess,
don't fight at the dinner table.
There's nothing wrong
with my attitude.
You are the problem.
You guys are too nice.
You still treat her
like family.
You keep reaching out
even though
she clearly abandoned us.
She doesn't care
about us anymore.
How can you say that?
She's the one solving
our problems about the inn.
She fixes everything
even though she's far away.
Because Mama tells her to.
Other people can help us, Ma.
We don't need her here anymore.
It would still be better
if we were all here.
How will that happen, Ma?
Dad is gone.
- [ERIN] Princess.
- We'll never be complete again.
- Enough.
- Why?!
I'm telling the truth!
[CHARLIE] Geez,
here we go again!
[HELENA] Enough!
Stop arguing.
Why, Ma?
You know that I'm
telling the truth.
After Papa died--
I said enough!
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GLOOMY MUSIC PLAYING]
[WATER SWOOSHING]
[WATER SPLASHES]
[GLOOMY MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GASPS]
[BREATH QUIVERING]
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Hey, can you...
tone it down with
Princess? She's pregnant.
I don't know what's up
with Princess, Auntie.
We get along,
but it irks me when
she badmouths Anna.
Can you blame her?
It's because of Anna.
Anna just up and left...
without saying anything,
didn't tell us where
she was going,
and it took ages for her
to show any sign of life.
Look, even now,
she hasn't come back.
I don't get Anna either.
I've asked her so
many times to tell me...
why she left, but she won't say.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
But sometimes, I
understand Princess.
She was so young back then.
She feels like she lost so much.
It's a shame she
didn't take after you.
[SOFT MUIC CONTINUES]
Me? Why me?
Your strength.
When Uncle passed,
you held it together.
I remember when
he was still alive,
he treated you like a queen.
He didn't let you work
because he knew you
came from a wealthy family.
But when he was gone,
you managed everything.
You took on all
the responsibilities
without blaming anyone.
I had to. I had to
do it for all of you.
What would've happened
if I had given up?
That's why, Auntie...
That's why Anna saw that
too, didn't she? She helped you.
She was the one who thought of
turning your house into an inn.
If Princess only knew
that Anna made sure she
could finish her studies.
It wasn't just Anna.
We all worked hard and
sacrificed to make this grow.
Especially you.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GLASSES CLINK]
Alright, finished or not,
pass your papers to the front.
Ms. Sarmiento.
- Sir.
- Can I talk to you?
I'll really go to the
principal's office.
I have something
important to report to you.
If it's about your leaving,
Teacher Patty already
told me your plan.
But before you go,
can I ask a favor?
While Teacher Thelma
is on maternity leave,
can you take over her class?
I need you to keep an
eye on Grace Banaag.
She's a bit of a problem.
She's stubborn, always fighting,
and when she does show
up, she's either late or asleep.
I'm counting on you to help her.
[OVERLAPPING CHATTER]
Because of you, Teacher
Thelma gave birth early.
Didn't I tell you not
to join the dance?
- Yeah!
Your performance was all
over the place, out of sync.
I had to step in and help.
Even so, you didn't
have a costume.
- You shouldn't have joined.
- Exactly.
You shouldn't have joined.
You didn't even have a costume.
I said I had a costume!
Really? Then bring it tomorrow
- Yeah, bring it tomorrow.
- Sure, bring it.
You don't have
one. You're lying.
Your mom didn't
buy you one, did she?
- Liar!
That's not true!
My mom bought me one,
at the mall. It was expensive!
Really, Grace? You don't
even have soap at home.
You're always dirty and smelly.
Yeah.
Maybe Grace isn't
loved by her mom.
She doesn't take care of her.
- Her mom doesn't love her!
That's not true!
My mom loves me!
She takes care of me!
Then why doesn't anyone
pick you up after school?
You were probably just
picked up from carabao poop!
[LAUGHING]
- Poop!
Where are you going?
- Her mom doesn't love her!
- Stop it!
- [THUDS]
- Thank you!
Thank you!
- Oh my--
What's going on here?
Ma'am,
Grace was fighting with us.
- Yes, ma'am, Grace started it!
- Yes, ma'am, it was Grace!
Grace Banaag?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
My name is Ms. Anna Sarmiento.
I'm the substitute teacher
for Ma'am Thelma Reyes.
Now, I would like to
speak with your parents.
- Yes, ma'am.
But, Teacher...
What?
Can you not talk to them?
I'll just apologize.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
You know,
you shouldn't apologize
just to get out of trouble.
Do it because you
did something wrong.
I still want to speak
with your parents.
Understood?
- Yes, ma'am.
Okay, moving forward,
I want you to group
yourselves into five.
Discuss what you've
learned in the chapter.
Then, you will present it to me.
Understood?
- Yes, ma'am.
Do it then.
Can I join your group?
No, we might get lice
if we let you join our group.
Can I join your group?
There are five
of us already.
Scion.
We don't like you.
Go away.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[KNOCKING]
Good morning, Grace.
Is my class boring?
[KIDS LAUGHING]
No, ma'am.
Shh!
Why aren't you joining
the group work?
Can I just do it
by myself?
You think you can
do it alone?
Of course.
Get a piece of paper.
Write down everything
you need to do.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Can I just memorize it?
Alright.
If you don't want to participate
in today's activity,
you'll get a zero.
[MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING]
[MELLOW MUSIC CONTINUES]
Pipo!
Pipo?
[CHICKEN CUCKOOS]
Eat it, Pipo.
[MELLOW MUSIC CONTINUES]
Let's eat, Pa.
Grace, where's my coffee?
[SARAH YAWNS]
My goodness!
Didn't I tell you not to bring
your chicken inside the house?
[CHICKEN CUCKOOS]
Pipo is nice, Ma.
If you hadn't won
that chicken at the fair,
I wouldn't have let you
bring it home.
What time is it?
Didn't I tell you
to wake me up at five?
I'm going to be late for work.
It's not five yet, Ma.
Pipo hasn't crowed yet.
Damn it, Grace!
You still can't read time?
What are you even
learning at school then?
- I've learned some things, Ma.
- What?
I danced really well
on Teachers' Day, you know.
They loved my performance!
Teachers' Day?
Is that what you needed
a dress for?
It's okay, Ma.
It's already done.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
But I was still the best
among them.
I take after you.
Shh!
Don't say that.
Don't be like me.
We shouldn't be the same.
Do you understand?
[UTENSILS CLINK, CUP THUDS]
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Ma...
What is it?
I don't have any money.
No. My teacher just wants
to talk to you.
No way. What did you
do again this time?
Just make something up.
I don't want to.
[CHITO EXHALES DEEPLY]
[SARAH] Oh.
Chito!
Where have you been?
Hey, why are you coming
home just now?
- I went to find money.
- Huh?
Here.
For the household expenses.
Let me see.
Aww. You're the best, love.
Wow, four thousand.
Grace, serve your uncle food
so he can eat.
[CHITO] You're serving me
just rice and soy sauce?
Nothing else?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
That's all we have.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Is that so?
You should've told me
so we could've bought food.
Don't worry. Hold on.
Go buy some food
at the eatery, okay?
Just buy one order
of adobo, okay?
[GLASS SHATTERS]
Oh!
Son of a--
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Hey.
What's with that glare?
- She's not--
- Be quiet!
You think you're
so tough now, huh?!
Why are you glaring at me?
Do you want me
tp pluck your eyes out?!
[SARAH] Chito. [GASPS]
[THUD]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SARAH] Grace! Grace!
- [CHITO] You brat!
- Chito!
What?!
Discipline your daughter!
Look how rude she is!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
A home full of violence.
Grace, what the hell?!
Why is still there no food?!
I'm starving here.
Go prepare something.
You almost started a fire.
What happened?!
A love that is
not reciprocated.
I love you, Mama.
You love me too, right?
A sense of compassion
she will find in others.
You should take a shower
every day
so you'll avoid
getting sick.
Grace, tell us.
How did you get that bruise?
Saving Grace: The Untold Story.