Hey, Taek. Hey, Taek.
Good timing.
Your maid
She pushed me and threatened me.
Just out of jealousy?
Am I Sung-hwa's fiancee?
Did you push her?
Yes.
Apologize to her. Okay.
I'm sorry.
How is it?
Can you get up?
No.
Hold me.
Oh, right.
That plate is specially made.
It's not expensive.
RMB 100,000, please. RMB 100,000, please.
Uncle Chang will ask you for compensation.
What?
100,000 won.
Taek.
How could you do this to me?
Come here.
What are you doing, Young Master?
A slap and a date?
I can't take it.
I'll do it myself.
Why should I believe that?
a person who can't even take care of himself
can take care of me.
The police will be here soon.
You have to cooperate with the interrogation.
Have you figured out what to do?
At this point,
do you still think
I killed Sheng Xi?
You know very well.
What's wrong? Are you scared? Are you scared?
Are you scared?
What's there to be afraid of?
I didn't do anything wrong.
Miss Qiao,
We have a few questions for you.
Please answer honestly.
Okay.
I heard you're the closest person to Sung-hwa.
Is there anything unusual about him?
Yes.
Young Master Sung-hwa always has
a serious disdain.
It's just that he's good at hiding things.
No one noticed.
On the day of the accident,
you didn't push him to the back garden
to the back garden as usual.
You asked for leave.
Sung-hwa went to the backyard alone.
Then something happened, right?
Yes.
The police found out that
the wheelchair brake failed.
You're the only one
is you.
You're the one who committed the crime.
Yes.
I touch wheelchair every day.
But I just did a routine check on the wheelchair.
instead of tampering with it.
I also checked that day.
No problem.
Ms Qiao.
Please tell us the truth.
What should I say?
First,
I'm not at the crime scene.
Second,
I didn't touch a wheelchair that day.
If you want to suspect me,
Show me your evidence.
We have no choice but to get on the lie detector.
Did you tamper with Young Master Sung-hwa's wheelchair?
No.
You want to kill Young Master Sung-hwa?
I didn't.
Who ordered you to do this?
No one.
I'm not under anyone's orders.
You just mentioned the sadness of Sheng Xi.
Are you implying that
he has a tendency to commit suicide?
I'm not sure.
I don't know how Young Master died,
but I will find out the truth.
Young Master Sheng.
We've done as you said.
But I'm curious.
why you made us pretend to be the police
to act like police?
For an answer.
But I think
the final result
I'm sure he'll be able to rest in peace.
Yes.
I lied.
I didn't go to the church that day.
I made up my mind
to confront Sheng Huaijing.
But I didn't expect something happened to you.
Sheng Huaijing.
I will record the evidence that you forced me to kill Sung-kyung.
For my mother and Sung-hwa.
this time,
I won't let you control me anymore.
Any news from Qiao Wan?
No.
You threatened her
to tamper with the wheelchair.
But I don’t think she’ll do it.
She already wanted to disobey you.
I don't think Qiao Wan can trust you anymore.
Of course I won't put all my stakes
on a piece.
Hello, Uncle Chang.
What is it?
Something happened to Sung-hwa.
What?
After the accident,
I had to play along
to deceive Sheng Huaijing.
I killed you.
while stabilizing him
and investigate your real cause of death.
Congratulations.
You're cleared of suspicion.
When necessary,
the car must be changed for Wang.
Qiao Wan.
It's time for you to fight for me.
Doctor.
How is my mother?
Miss Qiao.
Your mother often fainted.
But we can't find out the reason.
I personally think
it's related to the side effects of antipsychotic drugs.
You can't take
these pills.
I'll prescribe medicine for her later.
Okay, thank you.
It's okay.
Your mother's illness
to all hospitals.
I'm the only one who can save him.
How are you going to thank me?
As long as you can cure her,
I won't owe you anything.
That's good.
He's awake.
Mom.
Who are you?
I don't know you.
I'm not your mother.
Don't be afraid.
My baby is here.
Go to sleep, baby.
There will be a big wolf outside.
Keep all secrets in mind
I'll take you to your dream.
Grey Wolf!
Don't take my baby away.
No.
It's okay.
Qiao Wan.
Old Madam has agreed to let you stay.
Uncle Chang.
Should I say thank you?
The police proved you
to clear your name.
This is a good thing.
From now on, serve him as much as you can.
What about Young Master Sung-hwa?
Who will prove his innocence?
If he died for no reason,
will he be able to rest in peace?
I've been with Young Master Sheng Xi for so long.
He had a hard life.
It's a relief for him
to leave like this.
The dead can't come back to life.
We have to look forward.
You all want to forget him.
But I won't.
I will find out the truth
and avenge him.
Young Master.
Qiao Wan is very determined.
It seems that we must find out the truth.
Fine.
Let her investigate.
The show is about to start.
But she's still Sheng Huaijing's woman.
Aren't you afraid she'll tell her?
You should tell her.
Then Sung Huaijing will show his fox tail.
But this woman
is a liar.
She's very cunning.
What does she want?
I'm worried that
it's too dangerous to fake death to be reborn.
We must be careful every step we take.
Young Master.
Qiao Wan asked me to take a day off to church tomorrow.
I'm ready.
Don't worry.
We'll wait for tomorrow.
Did she notice anything unusual?
No.
She would never have thought
your leg has recovered.
We can take this opportunity
to start our first plan.
Even if they suspect us,
it's too late.
In the future,
in this world.
Only with secrets.
with secrets.
Sung-hwan.
I’m leaving.
Don't be sad.
There are too many regrets in this life that can't be realized one by one.
You have to pull yourself together.
Live on for me.
and lead Sheng-hyuk to the right path.
We'll be brothers in our next life.
Let me protect you from the wind and rain.
I will fulfill my father's last wish.
and my brother's wish.
Next,
will be a tough battle.
Uncle Chang.
Young Master.
Master Sheng saved me
to save me, an orphan.
Without him, there's no me.
My loyalty to the Sheng family...
to you.
my loyalty to you.