Why bother?
I don't even need to team up with Shengze.
You're already completely defeated.
What cards do you have left to fight us?
I suggest you turn yourself in.
Who says I don't have any cards left?
Aren't you one of them?
Give it back to me.
A tracker.
Shengze is that worried about you.
Wanwan.
Shengze.
Let her go.
It's simple.
If you die, she lives.
Even if I die, you won't escape.
You were the real culprit behind that accident.
Sheng Huaijing.
So what if I was?
What's so urgent that we need to talk now?
I still need to take Shengze to school.
Why did you destroy that formula?
I've already told you about this.
The production and market approval -
I can handle it all.
You just focus on the research.
I've told you many times.
That medicine works quickly,
but it's highly toxic.
It absolutely cannot go to market.
If this medicine goes to market,
then Shengyi will become the top pharmaceutical company in Nicaragua.
You know how difficult things are for Shengyi now.
Our company -
the livelihood of hundreds of employees
is in your hands.
What are you still hesitating about?
Even if my family's company goes bankrupt,
I won't do something that harms society.
I know you've just joined the company
and are eager to prove yourself.
But you must remember
that no matter what you do,
you should always
do the right thing and follow the right path.
Cut the crap.
You must give me the prescription today.
You want the prescription?
Over my dead body.
Don't push me.
Let go!
Will you give it or not?
Call the police quickly.
Call an ambulance.
Ma'am.
Is this your daughter?
You.
What are you trying to do?
The dash cam is already broken.
As long as you don't tell anyone,
and I don't tell anyone, no one will know I was here.
Otherwise,
I can't guarantee what might happen to your daughter.
You're a smart person.
You understand what I mean, right?
I understand.
Call the police after I leave.
Don't try anything clever.
I'll have someone watching you.
Kid.
Sir.
Hang in there a little longer.
The ambulance will be here soon.
Sir.
It's
too late.
Take this.
You killed
my father.
You drove Qiao Wan's mother insane.
Today,
I'll make you pay for it.
It's not enough. Still not enough.
That car accident should have taken you away instead.
It's all because of you.
I have nothing left now.
You must die in front of me today.
Let's start with the legs.
Watching you become crippled again
will be so much fun.
Shengze, don't!
Okay.
Shengze, stop!
Please don't!
Shengze!
The arm.
Sheng Huaijing, put down your weapon
and surrender immediately.
I'll say it again.
Put down your weapon.
Don't struggle in vain.
What's not meant to be yours
you can't have it no matter how hard you try.
Shengze, are you okay?
Wanwan.
Do you know
how terrified I was of losing you just now?
I know.
Let's never be apart again,
okay?
No.
I'm afraid I can't stay with you anymore.
I need to go to the hospital now.
Shengze just fell asleep.
No need.
I won't go in to see Xiaoze.
It'll only make me angrier.
I told him to take care of himself.
But he keeps
getting hurt for you.
If you ever dare to let him down,
just remember
all these injuries he suffered for you.
Don't you agree, Mrs. Wang?
Yes, madam.
But Qiao Wan is also very stubborn.
Once she commits to someone, she won't change her mind.
Anyway, let's head back now.
Why are you in such a hurry to leave?
I have a flight tonight.
What made you decide to join Doctors Without Borders?
Thinking about it now,
my life before
seems like I was always living for someone else.
After everything I've been through lately,
I suddenly realized something.
Life isn't just about romance.
There are many other important things.
It's time I lived for myself.
Feng Jing, thank you.
You're really brave.
Have a safe journey.
You too.
Shengze, I'll give...
Shengze.
Hello.
Have you seen where the patient from Room 205 went?
Oh, you're Mr. Sheng, right?
I just saw him going
toward the back by himself.
Thank you.
Shengze.
Your leg...
My leg is disabled again.
Perhaps this is what fate intended.
You won't be in a wheelchair forever.
You'll definitely get better again.
I promise you.
You promise me?
Yes.
If I can stand again,
you'll marry me right away.
Miss Qiao, let's go.
We're going to get our marriage license.
Shengze, you're such a scoundrel.
That's enough, Wanwan.
You promised me yourself.
You can be angry all you want,
but we can't delay getting our marriage license.