Sir, your flowers.
Chief An.
Thank you for taking time
to attend our young master's memorial service.
Please accept our condolences.
This way, please.
I apologize, everyone.
I'm late.
Nephew.
I am late.
I couldn't see you one last time.
It's truly heartbreaking.
Mother.
Please control your grief.
You must take care of yourself.
Don't pretend to care like a cat crying over a dead mouse.
As long as I'm still breathing,
I will never hand over
the company to an illegitimate son.
I respectfully call you Mother,
so why must you be so hostile toward me?
Although I'm only 9 years older than Sheng An,
I am indeed the old man's biological son.
You wouldn't want
Shengye to eventually fall into the hands of outsiders, would you?
Miss Qiao.
You tampered with the wheelchair.
You have an alibi.
The day of the incident,
I took time off to go to church.
Your undercover mission is over.
I'll find time to help you leave.
Save my mother first.
You're trembling.
Mr. Sheng, please don't change the subject.
Put this on.
I'll save your mother.
Young master.
You must be my uncle.
Nice to meet you.
I've heard so much about you.
You're alive.
Uncle, you're joking.
I'm Sheng An's brother, Sheng Ze.
You're the one the Sheng family left on East Island to die.
Sheng Ze.
When I first became conscious,
Sheng An came to see me.
He often mentioned a name.
Called Qiao Wan.
He said
the owner of this name was important to him.
My brother's body is barely cold,
and you couldn't wait
to hook up with my uncle.
I'm just kidding.
Why does he look exactly
like Young Master Sheng An?
What's going on?
Have we seen a ghost?
Brother came too late.
Leave everything else to me.
Rest in peace.
I am Sheng An's brother,
Sheng Ze.
I've been recovering on East Island
and never appeared in public.
When I heard about his death,
I came as quickly as I could.
Sorry for startling everyone.
My apologies.
Sheng Ze, that living corpse.
After lying in bed for so many years,
he suddenly recovered.
What medical miracle is this?
Or is our Sheng family fortune
attracting all kinds of flies?
Is our Sheng family so easily fooled?
How dare I try to fool the Sheng family?
But Uncle,
your nephew has returned.
Why aren't you happy?
Whether you're an impostor or not,
we'll know once we open the coffin.
Master
please don't.
Get out of my way.
No.
You're nothing but a servant.
And you dare interfere in my affairs?
Even if I am just a servant,
I am the young master's servant,
and I won't allow anyone to disrespect him.
Please show some respect
and let the young master rest in peace.
What if I don't?
Stop it, you ungrateful son!
I can prove
that he is indeed my grandson.
He's Sheng An's identical twin brother, Sheng Ze.
I'm not trying to gain sympathy.
If I can prove my identity...
Then is this
enough?
My father
before his death
left a secret will.
If I could recover,
then I would
inherit Shengye.
Grandmother, I've been unfilial.
I've returned too late.
It's good to have you back.
You've been through so much these years.
Our Shengye company finally has a successor.
I said get out.
You're Qiao Wan, right?
You're fired immediately.
You're hurt.
I'm the 17th one, right?
What?
The 17th servant you've fired.
You can't even keep track anymore, can you?
Young master, I actually envy you.
You can find your life's purpose in painting.
So don't put too much pressure on yourself.
Just feel it with your heart.
You think you know me well?
Don't be so presumptuous.
You can think I'm being presumptuous.
I just know that health is your greatest asset.
You need to eat properly.
What's this?
It's nut powder I ground myself.
Nuts are good for the brain.
They might even help you find inspiration.
I don't eat things of unknown origin.
What if you're trying to poison me?
Your hand is injured.
Let me feed you.
Sheng An, I only found out later.
Our meeting was just
a carefully planned setup.