Young Master Sheng'an.
Open your eyes and look carefully.
Who am I really?
Young Master Shengze.
Please show some respect.
So you finally recognize who I am.
My brother was just buried.
And you couldn't wait
to climb into my bed.
I didn't.
I just woke up here.
I don't know anything.
Last night,
I think I saw Sheng'an.
He was running away
when he was attacked.
That's what happened.
Tell me more.
This Sheng'an you saw,
was he alive or a ghost?
Stop pretending to have a headache.
I'm not pretending.
I'm telling the truth.
Whether you believe me or not,
I will find out the truth about what happened last night.
Right now,
you're the prime suspect in Sheng'an's incident.
Be careful.
Don't implicate yourself in your investigation.
Is what she said true?
Yes, madam.
Qiao Wan goes to church to pray every month.
This time was no different.
She also asked for my permission as usual.
I heard that
you're the only one who takes Sheng An to the garden for walks.
How is it that as soon as you're gone,
something happens to him?
Mrs. Wang.
Kneel down.
You all
need evidence even if you suspect me.
If you dare to take the law into your own hands,
I'll fight to my last breath
to ruin the Sheng family's reputation.
Still so defiant when death is near.
Hold her down.
Second Master.
I thought you invited me for a meal.
So early in the morning,
all this fighting isn't appropriate.
Uncle,
you don't seem like someone who meddles in others' affairs.
For the sake of my nephew who died tragically,
how can I not get involved?
Huaijing,
you're actually protecting this harbinger of misfortune.
Mother.
It's not that I'm protecting her.
It's just that right now there's no evidence,
and forcing a confession
wouldn't look good if word got out.
How about this?
I'll take her back with me.
She'll stay at my place.
She wouldn't dare to escape anyway.
Let's go.
Nobody's going anywhere.
She's a suspect.
And she's also my maid.
I need to keep an eye on her at all times.
To prevent her from conspiring with villains to harm my family again.
Since when did she become your maid?
Grandma.
No.
She has already harmed Sheng An.
If she dares to make any rash moves,
I'll be the first to turn her in to the police.
Oh well, never mind.
Ever since you came back,
I've been determined to make it up to you.
Once Sheng Ze joins the board,
you'll need to support him well.
Don't worry,
I'll definitely support him properly.
Uncle,
please look after me in the future.
Last night,
Someone was drinking here.
Morning.
By the way, Feng Qing.
Did you hear
any strange sounds last night?
What did you hear?
A woman's scream.
It was pretty creepy.
Do you think it could be haunted?
Hello.
This is Dongdao Sanatorium.
Is this Mr. Sheng Ze's residence?
Yes. What can I do for you?
Mr. Sheng Ze
left something in the drawer of his hospital room.
What is it?
It seems to be an envelope.
Please leave it where it is.
I'll send someone to pick it up.
Get the car ready.
We're going to Dongdao Sanatorium.
Yes, sir.
They've already heard.
What do we do now?
Whatever it is,
we need to get it
before he does.
You did this, didn't you?
What is this?
I don't know.
Stop pretending.
I saw you meeting with my uncle at the funeral.
The word 'spy' is written all over your face.
At the funeral, Mr. Sheng and I were just having a normal conversation.
Young master, you need solid evidence for everything you do.
Is that so?
Then come with me to Dongdao Sanatorium.
Prove your innocence yourself.
Young master.
Wait.
That nurse is calling you.
Uncle.
Are you looking for this?
Then tell me.
What's inside?
What's in the envelope
is obviously a letter.
All these years while I was bedridden,
whenever I was conscious, I studied medical formulas.
I dare not forget my father's instructions,
nor dare I forget
the original purpose of our company.
And you?
What have you done?
I think lying in bed has damaged your brain, hasn't it?
I'm a businessman,
not a philanthropist.
With your father's theories,
the company would have gone bankrupt long ago.
Fortunately, he died early.
Shengye's success today -
you should really thank me for that.
Mr. Sheng.
Shengze must have come prepared.
We can't be sure if that letter is genuine or fake.
He's eager to prove his identity to convince me,
so let's play along with him.
I should have dealt with that half-dead Shengze
from the beginning.
I was careless.
Put it down.
How dare you!
Touching my things.
What secret is hidden in this letter
that makes you point a gun at me?
Or perhaps
you don't know either.
You really think I won't kill you?
Young master, I was wrong.
I shouldn't have looked at your things.
But
I just helped you deceive Mr. Sheng.
Doesn't that
prove my loyalty?
You'd better think carefully
about how to get back.
What does he mean?
We're done for.
1 hour and 27 minutes.
Not bad. Faster than I expected.
Thank you for the compliment, young master.
Young master.
Any other surprises?
Just tell me everything.
No rush.
Let me think about it slowly.
Shengze.
Who are you really?
Why did you happen to appear
right after young master Sheng'an's death?
What secrets are you hiding?
I will definitely find out.