Anan.
What should we do,
Anan?
Anan.
Over here.
My mom is being really tough this time.
She even locked the door.
You guys have to get me out of here.
The window is locked too.
Why is it so serious this time?
Where are you going?
I...
Playing the guitar again?
I'm just going out for a bit.
The kid wants to go out for a while.
Just let him go.
Don't think I don't know what you're doing.
You're itching for a beating, aren't you?
Give me the guitar.
Hand over the guitar.
I've had enough!
What have you had enough of?
Anan, you promised me yourself
that you wouldn't do music anymore.
Have you ever asked me what I want to do?
I've loved music since I was little.
Do you understand that?
I don't even play in front of you anymore.
What exactly do you want from me?
You said you'd manage the homestay properly,
but you're back to this nonsense again.
Now you're even lying to me.
Playing guitar and forming a band,
how is that nonsense?
What has music ever done to you?
What on earth do you want me to do?
Bring me the lock.
No way.
We can't just wait around.
I'm going to steal Anan out.
Stop right there.
Do you think the fire isn't big enough?
You want to add fuel to the flames, don't you?
So what should we do?
The competition is in three days.
Brother Liuma isn't going on stage.
Just the two of us?
I'll figure something out.
1987.
Come on.
Taste my cooking.
Thank you, Uncle.
I have to say, that brat Anan really is something.
He never brings you guys home for dinner.
All day long, he just knows how to run around outside.
I quit.
Uncle.
Anan really loves music.
Besides,
making music isn't a dead end.
This competition won't take long.
Could you please
give him another chance
and let him try again?
I'll be honest with you.
There's a reason
why I don't let Anan study music.
Alright, that's it for today.
Okay, Bro.
After a few more gigs,
we'll get a better sound system.
We have to, Bro.
You got it, Bro.
Let's go.
I'm off.
Your aunt
took Anan
back to Lincang.
Then she met me.
She didn't want Anan
to be like his biological father.
In our family,
nothing is bigger than heaven and earth,
except for his mom.
This time,
his mom is really angry.
I understand, Uncle.
Mom.
Mom, I really love music.
Mom, let me go to the competition.
Mom, please let me out.
Anan.
You...
Hurry up.
Why are you here?
Come here.
It's inside out. Can't you be reliable?
Hurry.
Faster.
Why are you here too?
Cut the crap.
Let's go.
Why is the paint on my wall peeling?
You have to compensate me for it.
Damn. They're really having an affair.
Slow down.
I...
You taught them to do this, didn't you?
Honey.
I wouldn't dare.
Don't play dumb with me.
You're right, Honey.
I'll go get those little brats,
bring them back,
and teach them a lesson. God.
That's enough.
Who cares if they live or die?
Hurry up and open the door.
We have a business to run. We need to make money.
Yes.
You can't even feed yourself,
yet you still play music every day.
Wait a minute.
That was so intense.
I feel like my heart
is going to jump out of my chest.
Save that for later.
Bro,
why do you have the keys?
I just ran out like this.
How am I supposed to go home?
But
I know all about Anan's hard work
in music
over these years.
Thank you, Uncle.
Uncle,
what about Auntie?
Don't worry.
Your auntie's bark is worse than her bite.
You need the right method to coax her.
I'm an expert at that.
Come on. Eat up.
Stop fooling around. Hurry inside.
We're going to win.
We'll be the champions.
Right.
Let's practice.
Now,
just sing.
Mangshi,
Radio Calisthenics Band,
Wildfire Club,
Urticaria Band,
The Tenant's Dog,
Lost Bicycle.