DJ, drop that bass!
I'm going to tell him how I really feel.
Claiming the truth!
Who left this open?
Emergency!
Emergency! It's Max!
Shit, what the hell was that?
Was that a dream?
See you at the party.
There.
A little bit to the left.
Where?
- It's a little curved.
- Where?
Right there.
There.
Here?
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Scratch it more.
Finally.
Did we...
Hey!
No!
No way! No!
Fuck, no!
I'm not G for G! I'm straight!
Did I say you were?
Shit. Fucking wasted.
But thanks. You let me sleep over.
You're such a gentleman.
Get out, bitch!
And for the record,
I was just drunk last night.
So don't act so familiar.
And nobody will hear about this!
Guess I'll cherish it in my memory.
Get out!
So annoying!
My head hurts.
Me too.
What a night.
You had fun?
Ugh, my head is splitting.
But wait… last night, did we
rip each other in half, too?
Is this a hangover...
Morning.
Or did my buddy down there
get blasted too?
- What happened to you?
- Eat up.
Shit, I forgot to text my mom!
Don't worry. I already told your parents
you spent the night here.
And I already sent them
your drunken photos.
- I saw that.
- Right?
My head hurts.
That means you should hydrate.
Actually, you, too.
You look thirsty from
all that fun last night.
Sucked dry, were you?
Miss Bubble Tea.
With popping boba!
Popping all over the place.
I had a delicious time.
Good for you.
Wait, 'good for you'?
A little bird told me that sex with the ex
happened last night.
That's what I thought.
Or at least I wish I was sure.
Shit, imagine that? Karla and I
have been holding it in for so long…
Then last night,
she finally agreed we do it...
And?
I can't remember anything.
What?!
Yeah!
Well, I know that I kissed her.
Then she climbed on top of me.
Okay…
Then I don't know
what happened next.
Huh?
Ugh! I can't remember my one great sex!
You know what, just eat.
You might remember after.
Eat up.
Yeah. Let's eat.
Hotdog?
Eat? Hang on, did I get to eat last night,
or did she do all the eating?
I hate this!
Love, sorry for all this.
You don't need to be here.
Come on.
Don't make me feel bad.
Careful.
Is that why you didn't call me?
We already did everything.
Why act all shy now?
Well, not all.
Don't worry about it.
I want to do this.
Why?
It's such a hassle for you.
Don't be dramatic.
I'm your girlfriend.
Shouldn't we have
each other's backs?
Besides, I want to
meet your parents, too.
You don't talk about them much.
No, sorry... But they're not coming.
Why? Out of town again?
It's just a thing.
Our family, showing weakness.
Besides, I don't want
to bother them with this.
They're too busy.
Busy?
Love, this is a big deal.
You got hospitalized.
It's okay. I'm used to it.
In fact, people know me here.
Because every time I'm sick,
I stay here.
At least I have people here
looking after me.
Aww.
Don't worry, I'll take care of you.
I promise.
Okay?
- Hey.
- How's it going?
- I'm good.
How did it go last night?
Were you around
when the ambulance pulled up?
You were at the party?
Why didn't I see you?
I didn't see you either.
I can't remember anything.
Pretty wild last night.
I can't remember anything either.
But Karla and I talked, and then...
Sorry. I forgot
I have to go to Mads.
Can we just talk later?
All right.
I sure missed a lot
of things last night. Even Issa!
Hey.
Not that kind of 'miss'.
Gibo, pull yourself together!
Maybe you didn't get enough sleep?
It's not that.
No extreme diet
you're trying out?
No.
Rub this on your temples
and take whiffs of it, too.
Drink plenty of water.
You're probably just dehydrated.
Do you often feel faint?
It's been more frequent lately.
But I have anemia and PCOS,
so that could be related.
I'm taking my medicine, though.
Ah, okay.
Better to consult with a doctor.
You probably just need
to adjust your treatment.
- Okay, nurse.
- Okay.
Students,
it has come to our attention
that there was a party last night.
Not only that, there was one student
casualty in that unsanctioned event.
Let me just remind everyone
that though this is not illegal,
we do not encourage such get-togethers
especially without adult supervision.
You're in senior high now.
Think carefully about your actions
because they will affect your future.
Always exercise discretion and control!
Karla.
Karla!
Stop it!
What's this? Huh?
What the fuck is this?
Can't you scratch your own itch?
That's nothing!
Nothing?
Are you trying to insult me?
You think I can't drop you
whenever I want?
Don't think you can use this against me.
I'm gonna end this on my fucking terms
because I am the man here!
I call the shots, not you!
Why? Why is it always you?
Because you're a fucking kid!
Is that all I am to you?
Because you're acting like a child.
I thought I was just there
to give you directions.
To help you. I thought
you could be what I need.
No, please. Lem!
I'm sorry. Please.
I really need you right now.
Sorry?
I don't need this right now.
Okay, guys.
We're at the final leg
of the drafting season.
All right, listen.
We have a good problem.
You guys really put on a show.
But not everyone makes the team.
Okay?
Only one reserve player.
The rest will be trainees.
But here's the thing.
Only the official members of the team will
be eligible for the athletic scholarship.
So get your prayers in
and may the best players win.
So, guys, do your drills!
Let's go!
Hi, love.
Hello.
I brought bread, fruits,
and instant noodles for you.
If you're feeling hungry
at night, just grab some.
Aww, thank you.
You're welcome.
This is good for three days but if
you get extended, I'll stock up more.
Ugh, three days. Hassle.
I'll miss a lot in school.
Even in the org.
Nevermind that. Leave it to me.
I'll cover for you.
Okay?
The notes and readings, sure.
But what about the party?
I won't make it in time for the
campaign period for student council.
Imagine all those volunteer work
and those educational sessions.
It's all for nothing.
And my dad is expecting me
to get a position.
Can you have a proxy?
You mean 'sub'?
Ah, yes. That's what I meant.
I'll be the first runner-up
while the grand champion is recuperating.
When you're all better,
I'll pass you the crown.
Just like that.
I'm not sure.
No worries.
I'll think of something.
Let me handle it for you.
Just focus on getting better,
and I'll focus on doing
better in the party. Deal?
While that's broken,
I'll content myself with this.
Oh no, love.
Okay, guys.
Today we will be announcing the official
members of the Harmon High Basketball Team.
Here we go. In no particular order.
Let's go.
Hidalgo.
Boom.
Asistio.
Thanks, coach.
Okay. Bautista.
Chua.
Lustre.
Let's go!
Mariano.
Tolentino!
Ordonez.
Yes
Perez.
De Guzman.
Sy!
Yes, coach!
Nolasco, Jr.
And our sole reserve is…
That's you for sure.
Gomez.
The rest of you, trainees.
Dude, that’s okay.
Sorry, man.
There must be another way.
You'll figure it out, man.
Okay. So now, we will be announcing
your next practice schedule.
For now, okay, guys, party. Party up.
See if you can talk to coach.
For sure, man.
Find a way, okay?
You'll get in, for sure.
Just talk to coach.
Go on!
Coach, can I ask for Gomez's standing?
I was thinking maybe
you could pick me as reserve instead.
I'm fine to take that spot.
Well, you're not lazy.
I really need that scholarship, too.
We'll see what we can do.
See me at the office.
Really, sir?
Thank you!
Karla, Karla. Wait.
Sorry to ask you this.
I hope...
I mean...
No offense...
Did something happen
between us last night?
Jog my memory!
Or we can just do it again.
I'm game!
Gibo!
Yes.
Really?
As in… sex?
Sex, all the way, homerun,
exchanging body fluids level?
Shit! I wasn't wearing anything last night.
I meant protection.
I had nothing on, right?
Raw? Raw meat!
We really stayed on the grind!
Shit, shit, shit!
Sorry, my bad.
It's not that I have regrets
or anything, but…
I simply meant whatever happens,
I'll take responsibility.
Face up, stand up,
kneel, anything!
Gibo, you're overreacting.
No, I just wanted to reassure you.
Karla, I just want you to know
that I'm here whenever you need me.
Okay.
Karla.
Does this mean…
We're back together?
That we'll do it again? Come on!
Or did it mean nothing?
Like it's just a casual thing to you?
Sorry but I'm really confused.
I don't know either.
Maybe.
It's a maybe.
A maybe? Even though
we almost made a baby?
We need to start the campaign now.
Wait a second. Where the hell is Max?
Present, sir.
I'll present on his behalf.
You know, proxy.
We're still at the filing stage,
he's still a running candidate
and already there's a substitution?
If he's going to play it like that,
let's just drop him!
Heck no!
Luke. Look here.
Swear on the bones of the cow
my daddy butchered,
I'll fight to the death for this party.
If you're going to drop Maximus,
I won't stop you.
But let me run in his place.
That way I'll fight his fight
under my name.
I have something
our opponent doesn't have.
The softness, the strength, the charms…
and most importantly, the heart.
My victory is your victory.
Mark my words.
So give me a chance to take charge.
Bet on me, Mavic Lagdameo!
And I, thank you!
Oh, hey. I made you smile.
Don't deny it.
All right, let's give it a shot.
But I'm telling you now,
it won't be easy.
I'll grind you down for preps.
Grind me, you say?
Bring it on!
Try me.
Ugh. Fuck.
Hey! Be careful.
You might fall.
Wes.
What are you doing here?
Did you think Mavic
would just leave you without anybody?
She asked me to look
after you, of course.
Here.
Don't you have class?
Technically, I don’t.
I have something with the choir
but what I did was this.
So I told them I'll go to
the hospital for a checkup
and who knew I'd find you here, too?
What are the odds of that?
So just relax. I'm here now.
Come, let's sit you up.
There we go.
Sorry, but when was the last time
you took a shower?
Hey, Issa! Did you wait long?
Ah, yeah. I'm almost done, though.
I'll go ahead.
Ah, wait. Give me five minutes.
I have news for you.
I already know.
I read your status.
That was fast.
Well, for the record, that's it for now.
Karla and I are still complicated.
Nothing's for sure.
But you must be sure enough of something
to change your status.
Well, anyway, congrats.
I'm so happy for you guys.
I guess that's that. Thanks for the effort,
but now that you're sort of back together,
I'll have to avoid any more complications.
So can you please stop
with the flowers and letters?
What flowers and letters?
The ones you left on the bike?
Huh?
Ah, nothing, nothing.
Forget I said all that.
Forget I said anything.
Except for the congratulations.
I hope you're happy, Gibo.
- What are you...
- I'll go ahead.
Issa, why did you assume?
Hey.
Flowers? Letters?
Is she dropping hints?
Is she telling me
she wants to receive them?
Just tell me straight up. Jeez.
Okay, again.
Whenever you're delivering your speech,
look at the audience,
don't forget to breathe in, and…
Don't forget to pose!
Pause.
You'll stop
when you do a pose, too.
Same-same.
Here.
This is our sample ballot.
On election day, the Chronicle
will be alert for beats for sure.
So show up early and
get your photo taken.
That way, you'll be the first one
to show up on people's media feed.
Alright, let's try.
Let's practice.
And then?
You ready?
Okay, do it.
Project.
Smile for the press.
Go on.
Shoot the ballot.
Oh my gosh! I'm sorry.
We're good for today.
Yeah.
I think we have a winner.
I mean…
We'll win this for sure.
I meant I will win. Sorry.
All right.
Shit, shit, shit, fuck.
Steady. I don't bite.
Well, sometimes I do.
Sorry.
- There's nobody...
- Family?
I get it.
Mavic already told me.
And you don't have
to feel sorry for yourself.
Not like you're destitute.
I've never engaged in self-pity.
Luh, luh, luh, said the turkey.
Your mouth says something
but everything else says
something differently.
What everything else?
Your eyes, your eyebrow…
And your voice thins out
whenever you get defensive.
I think you were hurt
really badly, Maximus.
So you cover up your feelings
even before you can feel them.
And whoever hurt you,
I hope they lose their sense of taste.
You don't have to worry.
I won't hurt you, okay?
You don't have to be defensive.
Wow.
I didn't even say much.
How did you get all that
from there's nobody?
I don't know. Intuition,
divine intervention, whatever.
All I know is, we click.
Got something in your ear. Hang on.
Sorry!
- That's okay.
- Sorry.
If not him, then who?
Ah, boss, boss.
Let me get that for you.
I might get in trouble, sir.
No, it's okay.
We can handle it. Thank you.
Okay, thank you.
Thank you, sir.
- If you could just bring that out. Thanks.
- Thank you, sir.
You're doing too much.
I owe you big time. Promise.
It's nothing.
Don't worry about it.
Why did you jolt up
like that anyway?
You seemed electrified
when I touched your ear.
I don't know. Sorry.
Sorry about the mess.
That's alright.
It was just shampoo, jeez.
You're probably the most uptight,
scared little boy I ever met.
It's true!
It's like, all your emotions are inwards.
Like you're holding back.
Try to chill.
Let it out.
How do I do that?
How indeed?
Let's try something.
Go along with me.
I think you know this song.
You can do it!
♪  Look into my eyes ♪
♪ Forget everything else ♪
♪ In your life ♪
♪ Forget about the world ♪
♪ Listen to my voice ♪
♪ Serenading your heart ♪
- Sing with me! Come on!
- I don't...
I'm not a good singer.
Just sing it! Come on! Sit up!
Come on! Come on!
Come on. Wait.
Here we go!
Relax! Oops, careful.
- There we go.
- Okay.
♪ Let's make the most of this moment ♪
♪ Or it might pass us by ♪
♪ Stay with me ♪
♪ Let's paint the night ♪
See, you have a good voice.
What are you acting all shy for?
One more time. Let's try again.
One, two, three, go!
♪ Look into my eyes ♪
♪ Forget everything else ♪
♪ In your life ♪
♪ Forget about the world ♪
♪ Listen to my voice ♪
♪ Serenading your heart ♪
♪ Let's make the most of this moment ♪
♪ Because it might not come again ♪
♪ Stay with me
and let's paint the night ♪
God.
We're taking it slow?
Okay, let our lips touch
before our bodies.
Okay, ma'am, our lesson
for today is Biology!
Feel all this blood pumping,
I'm ready for it!
Do you like that?
Of course!
Hell yeah, doggie!
Somebody hold me back,
I wouldn't be able to hold it in!
Huh?
I don't know!
What's with the switch? I'm getting
confused! But strangely turned on!
- But it feels good! What's going on?
- Maybe you want me?
I like you, Gibo!
I like you, too!
I like that!
Keep going!
What a mess!
No, you're a mess!
Give it to me, Gibo!
Are you close, Gibo?
I'm gonna explode!
Shit!
Issa?
That was a wild review.
What a long test.
What's with you?
You were in a wild mood, too.
You caught me there.
I guess I'm reviewing
this intensely because…
I want to ace the main exam.
Gibo, I think I want to try
to understand my husband more.
Actually, me too.
I think we're good.
Is it because of your ex?
You know what,
I know what this is.
This will be over soon.
But I didn't expect that
I will actually miss you.
Yeah, I actually miss you already.
We're still gonna see
each other in class, won't we?
Of course!
You're not yet done
with your extra hours.
Oh, right.
This time, I'll make you
do real work.
Wow…
I want to say thank you.
Not just for the sex,
but for trusting me.
After that breakup with Karla,
I kept thinking what was missing,
what was wrong,
if there's something about me
that made her second guess.
Man!
So I'm grateful. Really.
I found a confidant, a friend in you.
You also helped me
gain back my self-confidence.
Wait, is this everything we've reviewed?
Sounds like it's effective.
Well, now we have
to face our own test.
But you have a good heart.
I know you'll do well.
I am telling you, Felize.
You "do" well.
Oh! Wait, I almost forgot...
I have something to show you.
Check your phone.
Here, I'm sending it to you.
There you are.
That's the clean edit.
Send it to your husband.
This is for my eyes only!
But why? You have nothing to lose.
Yeah, I do. You.
And how you make
me laugh so hard.
That's okay. I kept a copy, of couse.
So I can review you.
So, you like it?
It's something, huh? I told you.
- That was fun.
- Yeah.
Sing it to win it!
You just gained a new song
in your karaoke arsenal!
Well, not really.
I don't sing karaoke.
At all?
- No… - You've never done
karaoke in this country?
May God have mercy on your soul.
So, what? What? Keep grinning.
You're turning up your charm,
are you, sad boy?
Hey, I'm not a sad boy.
Well, that is up for debate.
But you know what, in all honesty,
you're good. I think you're okay.
And you're cuter when you're carefree.
In fairness, you're not so bad yourself.
Not so bad? Wasn't I great before?
Not so bad? A little bad?
What's that?
Like fat? From eating
all that extra rice?
What are you talking about?
No, not bad. I mean not bad.
- Feeling better?
- Yeah.
Shit, shit! Come on!
Answer your phone!
Sorry, sir. I didn't know
you were here.
Issa. Sorry you had to hear that.
My girlfriend's ignoring my calls.
Ah, sorry. Too much information.
That's okay, sir.
Like you said, more information...
To counter misinformation.
I see you're doing good sa Chronicles.
That sigh was a notch too deep.
Did you do something
for her to ignore you?
I think it's about what I didn't do.
I get it.
Or she finally came to her senses.
So, Issa, don't go out there
breaking hearts, okay?
I can take it from here.
Go on, you may go.
Issa's still here? Should I wait
for her? What, like a boyfriend?
Yes!
Fuck.
Looking for me?
Issa?
Issa.
Hunter.
You need to report Coach right now.
No.
I need the scholarship.
So, what?
You're just gonna let him
get away with this?
You've been on the team for so long!
You might even see each other in college.
You're just gonna suck it up?
For the scholarship?
I'm embarrassed, okay?
I'm ashamed to go this low!
And because I'm such
an idiot... Fuck!
I'm pissed off.
But what can I do?
I'm so stupid!
Hunter, it's not your fault.
None of it is your fault, okay?
Sorry about earlier, alright?
I lost my cool.
Everything got confusing.
Can we clear things up first?
What happened last night? Huh?
I've been trying to call you several times.
You weren't answering.
And you usually don't do that, right?
You usually answer my calls.
I just treated you the same way
you treated me
when you were at that party.
So now we're even.
So we're just gonna keep
getting back at each other?
You'll list all my sins
and use them against me?
If I'm getting back with somebody,
it won't be you.
And who would that be?
Your ex?
Huh?
Did you finally kiss?
Did you finally have sex?
Did you also moan like with me?
Get this through your head.
You're mine.
Someone might see.
I don't care. Got it?
You're mine.
How do you know
which person is being true to you?
Is it the person
who's seen you stark naked?
The person who fully embraces you
with all your baggage,
and your anger?
What are we doing here, Issa?
You'll see.
Here. You can let go
of all your anger here, okay?
Just scream it all out.
Nobody will pay you no mind.
If someone comes out, I'll take care of it.
So just let it all out, okay?
You sure?
I'm sure. Watch me go.
Go!
Louder!
More!
Is it the person who goes along
with your crazy ideas?
The person who makes room for your joys…
Or the person who waits patiently
until you can take the
first step hand-in-hand,
and rise together towards success?
She sure is taking her time.
I'm starving.
Maybe she's just
leading me on as usual.
Karla. Where the heck are you?
I think she just ghosted me again.
I swear, Karla. You sure are consistent.
You keep leaving me hanging.
Who are you going to choose?
The person who's always by your side?
Or the person who only shows up
when they need something?
The truth is, I don't need
titles, or power.
Because I'm empowered all on my own!
But I want to serve you.
I want to put a smile on your face.
All my actions will have you in mind.
So please give me a chance
to champion your causes.
Harmon High,
this is Maria Victoria Lagdameo,
your champion!
And I, thank you!
Tell me what you think
of my speech, love, okay?
Love, the campaign's settled.
I'll tell you about it later.
I filed for candidacy.
But this is for you, love.
Have you eaten?
Love? Hey?
Alright, go to sleep.
Max…
It's you.
Harmon High, I want to serve you.
This is not something
you'll get through on your own.
I won't be on my own.
You'll be here, right?
Who are you dating?
Is it that slut, Issa?
Do you prefer her over me?
Yes, fine!
I think you should
break it off with Gibo.
Why?
Are you jealous?
Are you really just messing with me?
You want to ruin my life?
Answer me!
Where would I hide?
Wes!
Help! Emergency!
Ah... Let's break up.