=Legacy of the Storm=
=Episode 6=
(Zhang Residence's Sorrow, Murder Case)
It was a paper figure!
It was actually a paper figure.
Yuan.
Have you had too much to drink?
I just had a few drinks.
I'm telling you.
Have you ever seen a paper figure
that can walk and talk?
Our residence must be haunted.
Zhang Yuan.
We're having a banquet.
Why are you talking nonsense?
Oh.
Father.
It's not nonsense.
I was thinking
of asking some experts to take a look.
Isn't it a coincidence
that Mr. Sun is here?
My dear.
What's the matter?
Are you feeling uncomfortable again?
No.
I had too much fun drinking with you today.
Oh.
How about I accompany you
back to your room to rest?
You can go to Quan Palace for treatment
another day.
Thank you for your hospitality today.
Now I have had three rounds of drinks.
I had a great time.
Alright, please bear with me.
It's late.
Stay in my residence first.
(Zhang Residence)
No one believes me.
When you see it yourself one day,
you will know, and you will regret it.
That sorcerer
said I'm very lucky tonight.
I'm going to defeat everyone.
Defeat everyone.
Here.
Watch your step.
What's this?
My master
likes to listen to Second Madam
play music to help him sleep.
Sir, please look.
Here.
Your rooms are here.
Please.
Pick one.
Ah.
You've had your meal
and taken your money.
When do you plan
to leave General's Residence?
Gao.
Why the straight face?
Are you full of anger?
You'll have too much pent-up fury.
It's bad for your health.
Hmm?
Do the people from your hometown
talk so close to each other?
Yeah.
Stop trying to get close to me.
Stay away from me.
Oh.
I was safekeeping it for you earlier.
I now return it intact to you.
Do you think
I'm as greedy for money as you?
- You can keep it.
- Hey.
Gao.
We're partners.
Two plus one makes five.
I'm not your partner.
You and I are definitely
the most invincible team in the world.
With my wisdom and your sword...
Ouch!
Don't move.
Isn't it just a stupid sword?
Do you have to be so heavy-handed?
I'll leave General's Residence tomorrow.
We'll never see each other again.
Hey, Gao.
Well...
Reconsider being partners with me.
Get lost.
Step out of the clouds.
Unreachable heights.
Look up at the bright moon.
Still in the dark clouds.
This is a very ominous sign.
(Zhang Residence)
No one believes me.
When you see it yourself one day,
you will know, and you will regret it.
God.
What have I done wrong?
(Zhang Yuan's mysterious death)
(made Gao Lingfeng realize)
(the seemingly peaceful
Yanyun City and General's Residence)
(must be hiding a turbulent conspiracy.)
(All this is closely related
to the fight over divine artifacts.)
(If he wants to find out his identity,)
(he must get to the bottom of it.)
(To Be Continued)
=Episode 7=
(Orthodox Style, Solving A Case)