(Park Hae Jin as Yeol Chan)
(Kim Eung Soo as Man Sic)
(Han Ji Eun as Tae Lee)
(Park Ki Woong as Yeol Chan,
Park Ah In as Jung Eun)
(Kkondae Intern)
300 dollars.
All I got was 300 dollars.
My monthly salary
I couldn't tell anyone about.
On top of that, he said he'll pay me
when he gets the investment.
"Good for you."
"Other people
pay to learn these things,"
"but you get paid to learn to work."
What a load of nonsense.
I couldn't...
I just couldn't take it anymore.
What?
"Is your brain filled with
udon instead of brains?"
That doesn't count
as office harassment?
No. "Udon" isn't exactly
an abusive word.
I mean, we can't say
only abusive words are...
wrong to say to others.
He said a lot of bad things to me.
You haven't signed
an employment contract.
By any chance,
do you have anything...
that can prove
the hours you worked...
like a work log or a list of times
that you clocked in and out?
I don't have anything like that.
Then by any chance,
could I use my diary as proof?
Hey, where is she?
Where's this idiot?
How can you eat anything right now?
All you ever do is waste food.
It has only been a couple of months.
Why did you quit already?
It's not like I wanted to quit.
I can't believe your attitude.
What will become of you
with this kind of attitude?
Do you think
I make money for doing nothing?
I put up with hearing things
I don't want to hear...
and my boss who nags at me
all the time to make a living.
What are you packing?
Stop nagging her while she eats.
You're too soft-hearted with her.
That's why she still can't
earn her keep at this age.
That's why she's
still acting like a dimwit.
- Put this away.
- Goodness.
My goodness. What's with you?
Don't you dare dream of taking
a speck of dust from my house.
I won't.
I won't take anything!
Get out right now.
Get out of my house.
I'm leaving!
I'll leave, okay?
I told you to stop already!
- Tae Lee. Tae Lee?
- I'm leaving!
I can't believe
I had a kid like her.
You. Did you think
you'd survive in this industry...
after doing this to me?
(Interviewer)
It's her, right?
The girl who sued Mr. Jang.
It's her.
(Prej FNC 2019 Internship Recruit)
He threatened me saying
I'll never survive in that industry,
and I couldn't survive.
- A food company?
- Yes.
Wait, you studied fashion.
But you suddenly want to
get a job at a food company?
I love eating.
Hey, loads of people desperately
want to work there, but they can't.
I'll give it a try.
Excuse me, hello.
This is my first day here,
- and my name is Lee Tae Lee.
- One second.
All right.
Thank you. Thank you.
Lee Tae Lee.
Tae Lee, Tae Lee, Lee Tae Lee.
It's a new start. Let's go.
I decided to begin my life
in a different industry.
Hello, I'm Lee Tae Lee.
You're right. My name sounds
like "Italy", Lee Tae Lee.
Hello!
I'm the senior intern
who'll begin as of today,
Lee Man Sic.
"The senior intern"?
What are you doing here?
Wait, a senior intern?
I thought you were
recruited as a director.
Did you lie to Mom?
What happened to you?
Your mom didn't say
you began an internship.
I didn't want her to
get hopeful again.
I was going to tell her
if I get a permanent job here.
Listen up.
If your mom ever asks,
I came here as a director.
Do you understand?
- How long will you hide this?
- That's none of your business!
What about the people at work?
I don't think anyone knows.
We don't have to tell them.
Nothing good will happen.
So what? You want to pretend
like we're strangers?
We may be a family on paper,
but we're as good as strangers.
What's the problem?
Nothing. I never said
there was a problem.
You better step up your game.
Don't get in my way
of getting a permanent job.
That... That little brat.
How should I address you?
How should we address you?
Intern Lee? Sir?
Mr. Lee Man Sic.
That's his name.
How else should we call him?
You're right.
It's his name, all right.
But why do I feel so uncomfortable?
Goodness. I'll only feel
uncomfortable if you think that way.
Please treat me the same way
you'd treat them.
This is my motto.
"Be an adult, not a kkondae."
You're not old-fashioned at all.
(A rise in one-person households)
All right. Whatever.
What am I trying to learn?
My subordinates will do this
once I become the vice president.
Focus, focus!
You should rest now.
I'll write about rockfish ramyeon.
Okay?
You're so smart
and have good character.
So why haven't you found a job yet?
Goodness.
You must've gone through so much.
Ga Yeol Chan!
Goodness.
Hey, why are you imitating me?
I'm your daughter, Man Sic, babe.
Man Sic.
What brings you here?
Hey, Mom!
Why are you here?
Is this where you've been
working as an intern?
In the same department
with your dad? Both as interns?
Mom?
Dad?
Open this.
I was going to tell you.
I was going to tell you the truth
once I got in.
That's why I...
What do you take me for?
A fool? An idiot?
How could you deceive me
like this? How?
I...
That's not it.
Everything's fine.
Come on, honey.
Why didn't you tell me sooner?
I didn't want this
to become a disadvantage for me...
upon getting hired.
That wouldn't have happened.
It was a blind recruitment,
and you guys are merely interns.
It's kind of weird
for a father and his daughter...
to work at the same place
as interns.
Then were you going
to deceive me forever?
Isn't that the purpose
of blind recruitments?
You could've really twisted
the family tree.
What family tree?
What if we ended up dating?
Then he could've become
my father-in-law.
What nonsense is this?
What kind of ridiculous comment
was that?
- Father, that's not...
- "Father"?
- Mr. Lee...
- You little scumbag.
- How dare you lust after her?
- Dad!
You're dead meat today.
Dad!
- Don't do this!
- Sir!
I thought dating in the workplace
was forbidden?
Dad, stop it!
- Didn't you say that?
- That's not it!
That's not it! Nothing happened!
Go ahead, tell him.
- Nothing happened.
- That's right.
Look at you two.
It's obvious
that something happened.
- What did you say?
- Stop.
You said it was forbidden.
- That's enough!
- How dare you?
- It's nothing.
- You punk.
- Hold on.
I already feel bad for smooching
and then rejecting him.
"Smooching"?
- You little scumbag.
- No!
How dare you smooch her?
How could I have told you?
How dare you?
Don't hurt him. He's innocent.
Hit me instead.
Hit me.
I thought it was all over.
So why are you defending him?
Wait.
I don't know.
Why am I doing this?
So Mr. Ga confessed to her
but got rejected?
I think that's about right.
I thought he abhorred
dating in the workplace?
I know, right?
Stop it!
Goodness.
How could he be...
Hold on. In hindsight,
they do look strangely similar.
Gosh, thank goodness
we didn't go out.
Does it hurt a lot?
I'm sorry you got beaten up
because of me.
That's fine.
But thanks to you,
my reputation has been tainted.
And I don't think
it'll be recovered anytime soon.
Let's be frank. You're the one
who made the mistake...
of mentioning him
as a father-in-law.
Is that why you told him
about our smooching?
Are you proud that you smooched
and then rejected me?
Why don't you
just tell the world about it?
What?
What did he say?
Darn it.
Move aside.
Will this also affect Ms. Lee
regarding her evaluation?
You said dating in the workplace...
could affect our evaluations
in giving us permanent jobs.
There's nothing going on between us.
If she rejected you,
doesn't that mean
you still have feelings for her?
That's not true. It's not.
And about what I said last time,
I was meaning to apologize sooner.
But you guys didn't pick up.
Are you sure it's not because
you got caught?
No. I said, no.
I wanted to apologize to you...
regarding dating
and your evaluations.
It had nothing to do with her.
I wanted to apologize sooner.
I'm sorry. I crossed the line.
That's okay, sir.
How could I have told you?
How dare you?
Don't hurt him. He's innocent.
Hit me instead.
Hit me.
I thought it was all over.
So why are you defending him?
Wait.
I don't know.
Why am I doing this?
If she rejected you,
doesn't that mean
you still have feelings for her?
That's not true. It's not.
Do I like that guy?
No.
I must've been crazy back then.
What's there to like about him?
Snap out of it.
You don't have time for this.
Wake up, Tae Lee.
Who is that? Who is it?
Who is it?
What?
Dad.
Why are you here at this hour?
Look at that.
No wonder you're a professional.
There's no doubt that
you were the former ace of Ongol.
Have you called your mom yet?
She's ignoring me as well.
Should we add some rice?
Sure.
How's my house?
I like it.
- It's nice, right?
- Is that a toilet?
This rhino is my pet.
This lunchbox looks delicious.
Let me try it.
Don't you know who I am?
Of course, it's going to be tasty.
Isn't it tastier
than your mom's food?
Yes, it's good.
Dad.
No.
You didn't even hear me out.
He and I have a long story.
What are you talking about?
I wasn't talking about him.
Dad.
My goodness, Mr. Ga. Did you
buy all of the drinks yourself?
- Okay. Let me.
- Yes.
All right. Let's see.
Which one of these drinks
is the most expensive?
- My gosh.
- Thank you for the drink.
- Thank you.
What's inside this drink?
It's sweet and salty. It's so good.
Goodness, this definitely got
my blood sugar going.
We had a distasteful
incident yesterday.
I ask that you stop talking...
about my scandal with an employee
whose surname starts with L.
Seriously?
It's only a scandal.
Let's not get the wrong idea.
We all should chant it.
- It's only a scandal.
- Let's not get the wrong idea.
- It's... Yes?
- Mr. Oh.
How's the 55th anniversary project
for Joon Ramyeon coming along?
It's going well.
Unlike someone,
I don't have time to date.
So I've been working diligently.
Come on, Mr. Oh.
By the way, your evaluation is
around the corner.
Are you guys preparing
for it, interns?
- What?
- Yes.
Did you get a partner
for your presentation?
- Not yet.
I heard they'll get extra points
for pairing up with senior interns.
Other senior interns are
in high demand.
Gosh!
I heard from other senior interns
that everyone is...
wanting to pair up with them.
Hello, I'm Intern Hong.
Hello, I'm Intern Lee Su Jeong.
I hope we can work well together.
- Enjoy it.
- Enjoy the food.
Okay. Why are they giving me food?
My gosh, look at all this food.
That small dog's poop is
as big as a person's.
My gosh, how do you put up
with such a hard job like this?
I heard the CEO is a complete jerk.
Hey.
- What's this?
- What?
Why is my name last?
Whether it's our age
or the order of the Korean letters,
my name should be placed
before yours.
Hey. Listen.
You didn't even help that much.
And you want your name
to come first?
Of course.
That's why we call you kkondae.
Hey, switch our names.
But why is no one
reaching out to me?
My goodness. What will happen
if I don't get a partner?
What do you say?
You know the presentation
assignment with a partner?
I heard it's a deathmatch
where only one person passes.
Right. If we pair up,
will you let me win, Dad?
Your mother wants a divorce.
So what?
You want to beat your daughter
at this presentation?
Do you think you can beat me?
Gosh.
This is why no one wants
to pair up with you.
What? Managing director?
Sir, I don't want
that kind of position.
And I'm not qualified...
Once I'm gone,
someone else will take
over the company.
Do you think my son, Joon Su,
can protect the company?
But still.
I can't take that position.
I'm not telling you
that you must take the position.
Then?
I'm trying to...
feel someone out.
Do you want me to be your bait?
Here.
Sir, you recommended Mr. Ga...
as the junior managing director.
What?
Mr. Park was let go because of
the sexual harassment scandal.
So there's an opening.
So I recommended him. So what?
Is that the highest position
you'll give him?
- Or...
- Or what?
are you thinking about making him
the managing director too?
My gosh.
Well, that's not my concern.
I'm sure the committee
will do their due diligence...
to check if he's qualified.
Darn it. You scared me for a while.
The committee and qualifications
are mere formalities.
In the end, they'll vote if they
want to appoint me again.
What's up with this vibe?
Dad! Are you seriously thinking
about backing him up?
And you'll just toss your son aside?
Gosh, I'm not backing him up
or anything.
If you want to get appointed again,
you should do your best to survive.
No way!
Right. I happen to be
the chairperson of the committee...
to check qualifications
of the candidates.
Is that so?
Well, then I know
it will be in good hands.
What?
I can't hold it in. Mr. Ga.
Are you getting promoted
to the junior managing director?
Well,
nothing has been decided yet.
I see.
Mr. Oh. Come here, Mr. Oh.
- What?
- That's not the position.
- Then which position is it?
- It's the managing director.
There's a rumor going viral online
and on tabloids...
that Mr. Ga might be
the next managing director.
Managing director?
Let me call you Managing Director Ga
very carefully.
My gosh.
I remember the first time
we met, Mr. Ga.
You said you wanted to work hard
together to the end.
- My gosh, I thought...
- I have big news!
I heard this from my friend in HR.
There's only one permanent position
available for our team.
What? So 1 of the 3 interns
will get the permanent position?
Didn't you see that coming though?
No, not just that.
Including Ms. Tak.
Only one of the interns or Ms. Tak
will get the permanent position.
What? What is this about?
These two just started dating.
And they are a father
and a daughter.
Are they supposed
to fight for the position now?
Goodness.
Mr. Ga.
(Marketing and Sales Department)
It's me.
What is this about?
I have a question for you.
Is it true that our team only has...
one opening
for the permanent position?
Oh, that? Yes, that's true.
How can that be?
You can't let contract workers
and interns compete with each other.
Ms. Tak should get
a fair evaluation.
You know,
the truth is that Ms. Koo
was very firm about this.
Why would she have influence
over the job openings for my team?
Hello, sir.
She's at a seminar right now.
(Senior Managing Director's Office)
The person you have reached
is unavailable.
You'll be directed
to the voicemail box.
My gosh.
Seeing how he's
so desperate to help,
there really must be something
going on with these losers.
You're still here.
Yes.
I needed to do something.
Well,
did you get a partner?
What? No. Not yet.
Goodness.
The evaluation is around the corner.
What have you been doing?
How can you still not have one?
Hey,
do you want to pair up with me?
Do I seem...
that easy to you?
Gosh.
I didn't say that.
It's just that
I'm out of a partner too.
If you choose me, you'll stand out.
Isn't that why?
Well, it doesn't matter
whom I pair up with.
I always shine.
What do you want me to do?
You've been working.
- What?
- For decades,
you've had everything to yourself.
And you're still trying
to take our spots.
Isn't that too much?
(Spicy Chicken Ramyeon,
Spicy Webfoot Octopus Ramyeon)
Therefore, I believe the age of...
super-cheap ramyeon
that sticks to the basics will come.
Our team of young men, Park and Soo,
propose "Youth Ramyeon",
the most cost-effective ramyeon
that costs only 39 cents.
That's the end of our presentation.
Thank you.
(Internship Evaluation:
Final Interview)
- All right. Park Chul Min.
- Yes, sir.
- And Joo Yoon Soo.
Who came up with
this super-cheap ramyeon?
We came up with it together.
We said we would say that.
Is there a problem?
No, sir.
- So? You made this together?
- Yes.
I'm sure one of you
brought it up first.
It happened almost at the same time.
It was uncanny.
Show them a smile.
We can talk later.
(Pulruri Food:
Internship Acceptance)
(Number 6083496, Park Chul Min)
Where are you?
What's with this company?
- What do you mean?
- If we have to compete,
senior interns should
compete with other senior interns.
How can you put us up
against young people?
Why? Did someone tell you off?
No one does that.
It feels like I'm taking away...
young people's jobs to survive.
If you don't feel confident, say so.
Stop making excuses.
But you should at least
go the full distance.
Then give up your spot
for young people or whatever.
Hello.
- Do you have a partner?
- No, it's okay.
- I'm Lee Man Sic.
- It's all right.
- Hello.
- Could you...
- We already have one.
Let me show you...
- It's all right.
- I'm sorry.
Darn it.
Why don't they realize
how talented I am?
Oh, I'm Lee Man Sic. Hello.
Do you have a partner?
Well, yes, kind of.
What about you?
Me too.
Gosh, this isn't easy.
Mr. Eom, don't go the wrong way
and make this work.
- Ms. Ok.
- Hey.
- What brings you here?
- Goodness.
We need to set up a time.
- Gosh.
- What time should we do it?
Well, either two or three o'clock.
Then let's do it at 4:00pm,
and eat dinner together.
We can do it!
No, I'm thankful.
You're the best.
No, I'm grateful that
you're willing to do this with me.
- Dad.
- Stop that.
Gosh.
You still haven't found
a partner for the presentation?
No.
Why?
That's why you need to stop saying
things like, "Back in my days".
You should humble yourself
when you approach younger people.
And hear out their ideas...
instead of asserting only yours.
Who would do this with me
if my daughter won't?
You can't do this with me.
One of the partners will
end up getting dropped.
There's only room for
one more person in our department.
We should've teamed up...
and made sure one person wins.
I'm so sorry.
It's okay. I have loads of people
who want to do it with me.
Take good care of Man Sic.
Thank you for understanding. Bye.
Fine, okay. Let's do it together.
Will you really be my partner?
Okay. Let's do this.
If we do an awesome job,
I'm sure they'll take both of us.
Let's do this thing
called coexisting.
- Man Sic.
- Tae Lee.
Okay, let's do this.
The person you have reached
is unavailable.
You'll be directed
to the voicemail box.
Please leave your message...
- Yes?
- I'm all finished.
Okay.
(Ga Yeol Chan)
Yes, Mr. Ga. What is it?
You're here.
Take a seat.
Why are you getting involved
with our team's recruitment?
You need to see this first.
("Joonsu Food's Controversy
of Recruitment Corruption")
What is this?
It hasn't been released yet.
Didn't you think they were weird?
Your interns.
Do you think it was a coincidence...
that your team ended up with interns
who are below the standard?
Say hello to them.
For the next six months, they'll be
a part of Marketing and Sales,
Ms. Lee Tae Lee and Joo Yoon Soo.
Why did the ones I gave
the worst scores make the cut?
Mr. Namgoong Joon Su was
behind all this.
He gave you
the worst interns on purpose...
to get you in trouble.
Is that why you said...
our team can only recruit one person
including the contract worker?
To be precise,
we will only evaluate
that contract worker for this job.
What about the others?
- What will happen to them?
- It all depends...
on what you do.
What do you mean?
If you step down as a junior
managing director candidate,
I'll stop this article
from getting published.
Are you trying to make a deal
with those interns?
What did they ever do?
Ms. Koo, have you
always been like this?
What is this...
This article will be published
tomorrow morning.
Once this gets out,
what do you think
will happen to them?
Of course,
the Audit Team will be involved.
Depending on the gravity
of the situation,
- this could become a criminal case.
- But...
But it's not their fault.
Lower your voice, will you?
Don't get emotional.
They were never going to make it
into our company anyway.
They only inconvenienced the others.
If you care about them that much,
you should think of ways
to keep them from getting hurt.
Don't make this worse, okay?
Let's be discreet about this
and make them leave.
Let's just sugarcoat it
and make it look like...
they didn't pass the evaluation.
Gosh, you've become quite bold.
Since you've been nominated
as the junior managing director,
you've become brazen enough
to call me over like this.
Are you crazy?
What have you done to them?
Do you even know how valuable
getting a job is...
to them?
No.
Come on.
What should I do?
Aren't you getting hungry?
Should I make some ramyeon?
I'd love that.
Okay.
(Increase in Household Purchases...)
(Current Condition and Prospect
of ASEAN E-Commerce Markets)
(Singapore)
You're amazing.
When did you prepare all this?
(Malaysia)
(Indonesia)
Only one of the interns
including Ms. Tak...
will get the permanent position.
Since your interns weren't aware
of this corruption,
they won't face any charges.
Since they didn't solicit anyone
in order to get in,
they don't have to leave
the company either.
There are many cases
where the employees involved...
in the corruption were punished.
However, there were rarely any cases
when the hired employees...
were punished.
Ironically, many of them continued
to work at their companies.
Nevertheless, they'll need
to be interrogated, right?
Yes. Once the investigation begins,
they will know eventually
that they were the subjects...
of this corruption.
- Yes?
- Please revise them.
- Okay.
- The White Chicken Ramyeon order?
You can just email it to me.
Yes, it's mansigi at...
Oh, you already know it. Yes.
(Final Assignments
for 2020 Joonsu Food Interns)
(1st: Group project,
ways for Joonsu Food to improve)
(Choose the topic of your choice
and do a presentation.)
(2nd: Individual project)
(Complete
the on-the-spot sales mission.)
Excuse me.
Like we thought,
we can pick our topics.
But what is this "sales mission"?
They'll give you an item
and tell you to sell it.
They'll observe
how quick-witted you are.
This mission
was really difficult for me.
I think Mr. Lee would be good at it.
You know it. I'm the best
when it comes to selling.
Goodness.
You're still here?
Yes.
If you want to sell an item,
make them feel like they need it.
They may not need it at the moment,
but make them feel like they do.
That's the basics of sales.
Why are you telling me this?
Because everyone can see...
how desperate you are.
You should watch it.
Seeming too desperate
won't look good to your superiors.
I know it's easier said than done.
I'm sorry about last time.
I've been very sensitive lately.
(Current Condition and Prospect
of ASEAN E-Commerce Markets)
(Singapore)
What are you doing?
This is nice.
The weather is lovely.
Dubu looks really calm. Hey, Dubu.
That's strange.
He's not welcoming of strangers.
- Him?
- Yes.
No way.
- It's the truth.
- He's so gentle.
Not at all.
Dubu, stop faking it.
You're so fake.
Even if...
only one of us gets in,
will we still be able
to continue this relationship?
Should we...
end it here?
If...
I get disqualified,
I'm afraid that I'll blame it
on our relationship.
I might...
look back...
and despise what we had.
Thanks...
for saying it first.
Why are you so cheerful?
Here.
What is this?
(Good Luck)
These are good luck taffies.
I didn't know
you were this considerate.
Thank you.
By the way,
is it really that big of a deal?
I mean...
Everyone's jumping
through all sorts of hoops...
to land a permanent position.
There are so many companies
out there, you know?
There you go again.
You're making me lose my appetite.
Hey. What if...
Hypothetically speaking,
how would you feel
if you either got the job...
or didn't get the job
not based on...
your qualifications...
but based on external factors?
Darn it.
I should kill everyone involved.
I can't let them be.
Wait, it doesn't mean...
you won't get the job.
Will you feel the same way
if you get the job?
In the end, someone else will be
robbed of their chance at the job.
Besides,
that's totally patronizing me.
Okay. Just eat it.
I'll eat this taffy
and get the job...
fair and square.
Here I come.
Did you decide?
I'll withdraw from the junior
managing director position.
Please bury it.
Tomorrow is D-day.
Yes.
Good job.
- Let me pour you one.
- Okay.
My gosh, Man Sic.
You managed to work...
for a younger boss...
with your pride and temper.
My goodness.
I know things didn't work out
with Mr. Namgoong.
But you know,
I'm always rooting for you.
You know that, right?
Are you already drunk?
Why are you being so nice to me?
That's not like you.
You punk.
You punk. Bottoms up.
Hey, slow down.
Gosh, you can drink.
Hey.
- You punk.
- If you didn't betray the CEO,
we would have been heading
to a better place together.
You darn traitor.
Hey.
If I'm a traitor,
does that make you a sidekick?
- What?
- You could have chosen anyone.
But you're acting
like that lame jerk's sidekick.
You've been buttering him up
all this time.
I shouldn't even keep you
as a friend.
Hey, it's because
I have to keep my head above water.
You punk.
- Sure. I want my head underwater.
- Underwater, my foot.
- You pay for this.
- Man Sic.
Anyway, good luck tomorrow! Okay?
I don't need luck.
Fostering e-commerce markets
in the ASEAN countries.
Developing e-commerce
in Vietnam is the masterplan.
Three years ago,
Indonesia road mapped e-commerce.
Gosh, you've gotten so much better.
Well done.
But since you're doing
a presentation,
why don't you do hand gestures
to look cool?
And have this intense gaze.
- Shall we try again?
- I plan to establish...
the infrastructure of e-commerce
and payment systems.
Let me tell you about the smartphone
markets in the ASEAN countries.
The average Internet penetration
rate in ASEAN countries...
is 53 percent.
And 89 percent of the users
have smartphones.
And it's expected that 56 percent
of the smartphone owners...
will be involved
in an online transaction.
The governments
of ASEAN countries...
I just gave it a try.
Not only is newtro
a fashion philosophy...
Newtro...
Dad, why did you ask me to present?
Mom said you were really good
at giving presentations.
They always signed the contracts
when you did the presentations.
I'll do a great job
for the both of us...
and get you a job there.
Okay? Don't you know who I am?
I'm Lee Man Sic's daughter. Right?
Their per capita income will double
when it hits 2036.
(Final Interview for Interns)
Are you guys nervous?
- No.
You are smarter
and have more potentials...
than these kkondaes here.
Don't let us intimidate you.
You have been working
at the company for six months.
Show us
what you have learned so far.
- Yes, ma'am.
Good luck.
There are 1st and 2nd rounds.
But today, we'll proceed with
the individual assignment first.
And you'll deliver
your presentations later.
(Sell a cell phone to a man
in his 60s.)
Me? That's too bad.
I just bought
a new cell phone last month.
This isn't the cell phone
I want to sell to you.
I want to sell you my phone.
You want me to buy your phone?
Why would I do that?
Can he do that?
It said, "sell a cell phone".
It didn't specify I had to
sell a particular cell phone.
That wasn't in the rules.
- He's right.
- He has a point.
It's a bit embarrassing
to tell you this myself.
I had worked at a ramyeon company
for over 30 years.
This phone comes
with all the contacts of buyers...
I met while working
at the company for 30 years.
You'll recognize their names
when you hear them right away.
They are big names in Korea.
I bet you wanted to get
their contacts, but you couldn't.
But I have contacts of people
who work in logistics abroad.
(Interviewer)
And don't forget the owners
of small import companies.
I believed in them when
they started off as street vendors.
I believed in their potentials.
Mr. Kozosky, the supervisor
of BC Mart from Russia.
Mr. Cholongkutok,
an import buyer from Mongolia.
Mr. Baduduk Grumi from Nepal.
Mr. Adelaman from the Arab Emirates.
Mr. Eungekong
of Kong Mart from Vietnam.
Mr. Andes Mendoza from Brazil.
Mr. Panchobia Baldes from Mexico.
That's pretty useful.
China?
Mr. Binghao. "Thank you, Man Sic".
Is that the guy who signed
the contract with Binghao?
Yes, that's right.
Everyone, the moment
you buy this phone,
it will be the same as having
thousands of troops and horses.
You will be buying my experience...
of 30 years and my identity
with this cell phone.
I'll buy it. 200 dollars.
I'll buy it. 300 dollars.
300 dollars. Any other takers?
I'll buy it for 3,000 dollars.
- Sold!
- My gosh.
- No!
- He said he'd sell it to me.
That's it.
Well,
the forecast said it'd rain today.
I'm not buying.
If you want to sell an item,
make them feel like they need it.
They may not need it at the moment,
but make them feel like they do.
That's the basics of sales.
Wait.
What?
- What is he doing?
- What is that?
- What are you doing?
- What is this?
- My gosh, what is that?
- What are you doing?
Why did you bring that?
- What will you do with it?
- What?
What are you up to?
I'm sorry.
I'm not doing this
because I want to.
Are you really going
to splash water on her?
I'm sorry.
Come here.
You lunatic!
Hey! You!
Stop!
(Sell rice to a man in his 30s.)
- What is it?
- What did she pick?
What is that?
That's rice. Rice.
No, I don't want it.
Could you come out for a second
and give me a hand?
Okay, let's do this.
You've covered your eyes
and played tag before, haven't you?
Try to tease me
without letting me catch you.
That hurts! That hurts.
What will you do?
I'll buy it. I'll buy the rice.
That hurts! I'll buy it, okay?
Okay, I attached
my performance record.
(2020 Evaluation:
Tak Jung Eun, Marketing and Sales)
(Your mail
has been sent successfully.)
I wonder if my dear Yoon Soo,
Yoon Soo, Joo Yoon Soo is all right.
I hope he doesn't get too nervous
and get dropped...
after preparing so much for this.
No, I'm saying my life will be
much easier if he makes it.
They probably began
their team presentation by now.
First off,
we analyzed our consumers...
and made a graph
with their opinions on health.
People's confidence regarding
their health drops with age,
but their interest in a healthy life
continually increases.
If you end up getting me dropped,
I don't think it'll feel unfair.
Women were...
- You can do it, Yoon Soo.
- especially interested...
in weight loss products.
People are more interested in
staying healthy as they age.
(Strategy Proposal to Enter
the Online Market in ASEAN)
You can do it!
Gosh, I'm so nervous.
All right!
Let's see it.
(Strategy Proposal to Enter
the Online Market in ASEAN)
Team Joo Yoon Soo and Eom Han Gil...
prepared a strategy proposal...
to enter the online market
in the ASEAN region.
Will the senior intern
do the presentation?
Yes, Mr. Joo prepared everything,
so I just hopped onto his project.
I'll make sure I do my best
to cause no damage to Mr. Joo.
NTY Foods is...
a company that distributes and sells
products such as...
the famous Francegles potato chips,
Toktok Cola, Horgendaz Ice Cream...
all over Thailand through
online and offline markets.
They've been showing
continuous growth in Thailand,
so we kept a close eye on them.
Recently, it seemed like they were
hoping to expand their business.
I've never heard of this company.
Their size and growth
both look very stable.
(Final Interview for Interns)
An intern found this company?
No, sir. I didn't do this.
It's all thanks to Mr. Joo Yoon Soo.
Come here.
What do you mean,
you contacted them yourself?
Yes, sir. I tried contacting them
through their email address.
They showed interest, especially
for our Spicy Chicken Ramyeon,
so I sent them one of our catalogs.
When did that happen?
Yes, sir. I sent it two days ago.
They contacted us back
right before the interview,
so I transferred
the email to Mr. Ga.
Yes, I just scheduled a meeting.
Give him a hand.
We have to drop a guy like him?
Team Lee Man Sic and Lee Tae Lee...
want to propose
a way to improve our products...
through renewing our package...
and implementing newtro marketing.
Not only has newtro
captured fashion and culture,
but it has become a mega-trend...
even in the food
and distribution industry.
"New", means fresh,
and "retro", means
an old-fashioned style.
These two conflicting values
came together...
to create unique stories
that touch people's hearts,
leading people to spend their money
on emotional values.
You all know Chamjincheoreom soju
became a huge hit...
after they returned with
their old toad packaging, right?
Also, this is a water bottle
that was literally in...
every single household
in the 80s and 90s.
It's this juice bottle
from the Starmont company.
After its launch in 1963,
Joon Ramyeon became
a big trend in the 80s and 90s.
There are stories of...
our grandfathers, grandmothers,
mothers, and fathers in the ramyeon.
There's the story of a mother...
who couldn't waste the package
and packed seasoned seaweed...
for her children's lunch box.
There's the story of a father who
threw in thin noodles in ramyeon...
because ramyeon was
still too valuable back then.
We can use these stories...
- Don't try too hard.
- to make a retro edition...
- Why are they trying so hard?
- and launch it for a limited time.
(Interviewer)
Great job. Good job!
Great job!
Who's that?
I'm Lieutenant Lee Geun Seok
of Intellectual Crime Team...
- of the Seoul Metropolitan Police.
- So?
Mr. Lee Man Sic, Ms. Lee Tae Lee,
and Mr. Joo Yoon Soo.
I have questions to ask you
regarding recruitment corruption.
I need to ask you to come with me.
Recruitment corruption?
What?
(Kkondae Intern)
Are you allowed to do this
if you're rich and powerful?
Do you think we're a joke?
You need to be wise.
Depending on what you say,
either Ga Yeol Chan
or you will get fired.
Does Mr. Ga know...
that you're
President Namgoong's spy?
I'm not a spy!
You seem to love our company.
Yeol Chan...
You have to leave as soon as
you're done with the noodles.
May I stay here for a while?
What?
(Kkondae Intern)