Was...
Go Cheong-myeong
there to meet her?
Chan-sung, come here!
This came for you.
HOTEL DEL LUNA
It's from Man-wol.
-It's from Jang Man-wol?
-Yes.
THANK YOU
"Thank you"?
Don't run away.
Even if I go berserk, do crazy things,
and vanish one day,
please stay by my side.
I won't let you vanish.
Trust me.
She fired a competent guy like you,
but she eventually
ended up reinstating you.
I guess she wants to be nice to you now.
My sincerity touched her heart.
My god, what's this?
Is this a tiger print suit?
Make sure you get a good price for this.
Then as a reward,
I'll get you a tiger print suit like this.
God, she's unbelievable.
This is a luxury brand. It's really sexy.
You should try it on. It'll look funny.
No, forget it.
Who wears tiger print suits?
But if you don't wear it,
Man-wol will feel upset.
It looks really expensive.
And it'll upset me as well.
I want to see how it looks on you.
I didn't give her the money I got
from selling the painting.
Where did she get the money to buy this?
She wouldn't go to a luxury brand store
just to get a suit for me.
Hey, this is actually really nice.
Veronica's coming to Korea next week.
How about I buy the same suit?
It might make me look
really wild and different.
No, don't do that.
You don't want to shock her.
You know nothing
about being in a relationship.
It's necessary to surprise
your partner once in a while.
Whatever.
Man-wol said she was going
to a department store the other day.
I guess that's when she got this.
You met Jang Man-wol?
Yes, a few days ago.
She asked me to help her sell something
she inherited from her grandfather.
What? "Something she inherited
from her grandfather"?
They're a couple of pure Arabian horses
on a farm in Qatar.
I heard even the royal family
wants to have those horses.
Do you think you can help me sell them?
Sanchez, are you close to Mansour
by any chance?
Mansour?
No, I'm not.
But purebred horses are very rare.
So someone in my equestrian club
will want to buy them.
That's great news.
If you help me sell those horses
at a high price,
I'll get you a white suit
just like this one.
But why are you asking me for help
instead of Chan-sung?
I can't trust him.
Why not?
He just got reinstated,
so he's really busy.
Please help me with this, Sanchez.
If you ever happen to come
to my hotel in the future,
I promise that I'll treat you well.
Oh, really?
Of course.
My gosh.
The chairman...
I sold the horses for your sake.
By the way,
those horses are really expensive.
She got those horses in return
for letting him make the dream call.
I should never be off my guard.
I should always make sure
to tighten the reins.
Mr. Koo. All the guests are
requesting the special service.
They heard of this
because of Chairman Wang,
so many of them wish to make
a dream call to the living people.
This is a service
that Ms. Jang has only offered in secret
to guests who pay special fees.
What should we do?
We should be fair
in providing our service.
I'll handle this.
Okay.
Hey.
What? Why didn't you put it on?
I was looking forward to seeing you
dressed in tiger print.
This is my workplace.
If the owner says it's fine,
then it's fine.
See? I even bought this
to wear when you come dressed
like a tiger.
That's a horse print. A zebra.
What do you think? Pretty, isn't it?
It gets on my nerves.
You don't like it?
You're so picky.
Fine, if you don't like
tiger prints or zebra prints,
then let's go. I'll get you
something that's your cup of tea.
We have no time to do that.
We have a lot of special requests
from our guests.
You need to take care of them.
A dream call is only offered to those
who pay a special price.
You already got paid.
The horses. You took the horses.
Darn you, Sanchez.
I won't meddle with that money,
but you have to help the other guests.
REQUEST FOR SPECIAL SERVICE
Chan-sung, do you think
the dead will only say nice things
when they appear in a dream?
"I died because of you.
You have to die with me."
What if they resent and curse the living?
Resentment and cursing.
That's why I look into each and every one
of their cases
and take a special price
only when the circumstances look right.
It's not just about money!
You're right.
I had the wrong idea about you.
It wasn't because of money.
You were concerned.
Yes. It's all for my guests' sake.
I only do it for those
who can pull this off.
What do you take me for?
In that case,
I will make some rules
to single out those who can do this.
Seriously!
I'm the one who took the horses.
Why is he acting like that?
I'll tell you the secret
to our naengmyeon stock.
It's because you were
the most diligent one among my staff.
Listen up.
Naengmyeon?
I love naengmyeon too.
The secret is...
My gosh.
Is that you?
Thank you so much for everything.
Your band's music gave me
much comfort to my last breath.
-"Your band"?
-He must be in a band.
I knew your music and dance
would end up touching
the heart of the world.
That's not for someone she actually knew.
Look, it says...
I WISH TO TELL SOMEONE I LOVE...
I love you!
I'll love you forever!
Having fun?
Stay on top of everything, will you?
Yes.
He's leaving today,
and he wishes to talk to his wife
before he leaves.
Am I allowed to make only one call?
Yes, just one call.
In that case, I wish to call someone else.
I got into a car accident with my son.
I wish to talk to the man
who hit us with the truck.
You cannot make a call
to blame or curse someone.
Please leave.
It's not that I wish
to blame or curse him.
I wish to apologize to him.
I'm glad you were just put on probation.
Glad? Two people were
hit by my truck and died.
LETTER OF RESIGNATION
I can't do this job anymore.
If you quit this job,
how will you make a living?
You are the people I killed...
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I can't be forgiven for what I have done.
We're sorry.
It's our fault for suddenly jumping
in front of your truck.
It was a mistake.
We had bad luck,
but we gave you too much pain.
I'm sorry.
I hope
your life doesn't get ruined
because of us.
I'm sorry.
And thank you.
I feel much better now.
Son, shall we go?
Thank you.
Should we call it a day?
We only have a few guests left.
Let's finish up today.
Tell them to come in.
The flowers are in full bloom.
Let's not be too worried.
The flowers have finally bloomed.
They might stay pretty like this
for a long time.
Mago is trying to take Ms. Jang.
Flowers bloom only to fall.
We have to go before Ms. Jang does,
so let's prepare ourselves for that day.
Gosh, I'm so tired.
Do you know how tiring it is
to let ghosts talk to the living?
But thanks to you, many people will smile
when they wake up from their dreams today.
You've done well,
so I'll make you smile too.
What?
How?
Are you going to put on
the tiger print suit?
I knew it. You sent that to me
to make me look ridiculous.
Hey, if I put in that much money
to have a good laugh,
it means I tried very hard.
I tried very hard to make you laugh too.
I made a reservation
at the rice cake soup place
where you failed to eat
and came back angry many times.
Let's go.
What?
They don't take reservations. It takes
at least two hours to get a table.
I used my connection from Harvard.
Can you major in rice cake soup
at Harvard?
The son of that restaurant is an alumnus.
I reserved the entire place
at the closing time.
Let us hurry.
Hey, wait.
You should change into an outfit
that fits the soup.
This isn't an ordinary rice cake soup.
It's made with bead-shaped cakes.
I'll wear something special.
Look here.
I'm okay.
Sanchez is only three years older than me.
If I eat three bowls
of rice cake soup today,
can I talk casually to you
like Sanchez does?
What?
Sanchez calls you by your first name.
You want to be on a first name basis
with me?
Okay, just eat 1,300 bowls
of rice cake soup.
Even Kim Jun-hyun can't eat that much.
Don't underestimate Kim Jun-hyun.
Okay, then.
One rice cake will be worth one year.
No, one rice cake for one hundred years.
You fraud from Harvard!
You think you could age that easily?
After I eat 13 rice cakes,
I'll start calling you Man-wol.
Do as you please.
When a human ages 1,300 years, he dies.
Challenge. I'll take 200 years first.
It tastes better
because it's worth 200 years.
Being on a roll, I add 300 years more.
They look so pretty now.
Why must they fall?
It's sad.
Now I have 300 years left.
Are you nervous?
Then, I just have to eat 500 years more.
Are you stupid?
I will eat faster.
No, I will eat faster.
I now have 100 years left.
Add 200 years for me.
I was famous for eating fast at Harvard.
I'm already 3,500 years old.
-Adding 600 years.
-I'm 3,600 years old now.
You can't beat me. Just acknowledge it.
I'll also eat those earrings after this.
Nonsense.
I've found the motive for the murders.
It's this website called Helllo.
Helllo? Is it some social club?
It's "Hell" and "lo," meaning "to Hell."
The name is a play on words.
Helllo. What is the website for?
It's an old community
with more than 100 thousand members.
At first, they just shared
their problems on it.
But it's gradually become a real hell.
Now, they post curses and slanders
about other people.
It's like an emotional trash can.
-So?
-The suspect posted
several slanders about his wife.
He wrote comments on slanders
about six others who were killed.
The slanders about the victims
had a high number of views and comments.
Now you're looking
at the post and comments
criticizing one of the victims.
KILL, KILL!
If one uploads a slandering post
about people he hates,
the others curse them together.
That's what they do on the website.
What about the suspect?
Did he carry out the curse?
He thinks he's some kind of demon?
Except for Lee Do-yeon,
the wife of the suspect,
the victims were killed by someone
who they had never met.
They didn't even know why.
So this man is not the killer, right?
I told you. I was right.
The owner of that car is the killer.
There was a ghost in that car too.
You saw it.
But you can't call the police
without any evidence.
There's the composite sketch.
That thing you always see
in criminal investigation dramas.
Let's do that.
I'm good at drawing.
You'll get into trouble
if Ms. Jang finds out about this.
Tell me everything you remember about him.
Tell me anything.
81GI 0963
I didn't meet the Koo Chan-sung guy.
I moved the stuff with a high school girl.
I really had a hard time
because my car broke down.
Do you know the girl's name
or her phone number?
I don't know her phone number.
She contacted us through the SNS account.
Do you really work
at an entertainment agency?
Are you a casting director?
I guess.
She is quite attractive,
so I wanted to meet her.
She can't be in show business.
She's really weird.
What's weird about her?
She's soft in the head.
No, she's not crazy. She sees ghosts.
That's right.
Ghosts?
Yes, she sees ghosts.
Everyone in our schools knows.
You shouldn't make up rumors
about your friend like that.
I'm telling the truth.
She talks to herself.
She follows someone when there is nobody.
She follows ghosts?
That's interesting.
Mr. Kim, I looked at the new menu.
You changed the name of
our signature cocktail, Tears,
to Tear Wine.
Ms. Jang said it was too pretentious.
Why? It was a good name.
Tears and cheers.
It has a nice ring to it.
A Harvard graduate like you
thinks it's not bad, right?
Ms. Jang's picking on me for no reason.
It's the signature cocktail of our bar,
so I think you should work on it
a bit more.
Something like Angel's Tears
or Devil's Tears.
You think so? Angel and Devil?
I will make a note and give it to you.
Harvard knows how to teach
their students properly.
What are the guests doing
in the middle of the day?
They are those who were killed
and buried secretly.
I heard we had those guests.
I heard the killer was caught.
That's what I heard too.
But Ms. Fourth Choice keeps saying
something is not right.
I don't think the man
the police caught is the culprit.
There was a ghost in this car too.
The owner of this car is suspicious.
81GI 0963
Yu-na, you're still too young.
You shouldn't get involved
in a violent crime like this.
I agree. You should concentrate on school.
Then, let me finish the sketch
I've been drawing.
I'll show it to you when I finish it.
I'll look into it if there's any problem.
So you have to tell me.
Okay.
REQUEST FOR SPECIAL SERVICE
They are the additional service requests
we have received today.
Oh, dear.
It's such a bother.
You probably saw the flowers.
Why aren't you saying anything?
Have you all decided to get on the bus
to the afterlife?
We are preparing ourselves for the worst.
And I...
will leave after I see
that family completely destroyed.
You told me your daughter had to die
for the family to carry on
their family line.
No matter how impatient you feel,
you must not do what you did 42 years ago.
If you become an evil ghost and vanish,
your 200 years
of hard work at this hotel
will go down the drain.
My grudge is so deep
that I don't care about those years.
There will be a lunar eclipse soon.
Yes.
I hear the moon will be covered
for quite a while this time.
I'll prepare for it.
Sir.
Do you need anything?
I'm thirsty.
I'll bring something to drink
to your room.
This way.
A long lunar eclipse...
Mr. Koo Chan-sung,
we need you to come with us.
We brought him.
Come closer.
Who are you, and why did you look for me?
Do you recognize me?
Of course.
I even saw you on today's morning paper.
I've been admiring you.
But why did you call for me?
I hear you're working at a hotel
that's registered
at the Jung-gu District Office.
Yes, that's right.
Will you take me to that hotel?
I'd like to meet with the owner.
Do you know...
my boss?
Hotel del Luna's Ms. Jang Man-wol.
I used to be
a manager who served Ms. Jang
at the hotel.
Didn't you get off work early today?
I brought a pleasant guest.
Ji Hyeon-jung,
do you still skip work
and leave the front desk unattended?
Ms. Hwang!
Goodness.
What brings you here?
You're not dead, are you?
You still can't tell the difference?
I'm alive.
You scared me.
By the way,
should I call you President Hwang now?
I'm only a candidate for now.
Mr. Kim. Ms. Choe.
Ms. Hwang is here.
My goodness. You two are still here.
Ms. Hwang.
It's been a long time.
It's been a while.
Has it been over 30 years
since we last met?
You've gotten old.
You still make
such straightforward comments.
Do you have a lot of guests
at the hotel right now?
I can't see anyone else
other than the hotel's employees now.
There are a few.
There's Ms. Jang.
Your hotel has become so big.
It's all thanks to you, Mun-suk.
Thanks to the money you made back then,
we were able to move to Myeong-dong
and got big.
It seems you've become a big shot too.
I saw you a lot on the phone.
I hear you'll become a president
of somewhere big soon.
I'm just a candidate for now.
I'm thankful you let me free.
Do you think I let you go
because I wanted to?
Mago thought someone talented like you
shouldn't be tied up to a place like this.
She gave you the medicine behind my back,
and you couldn't see ghosts anymore.
So I had no choice but to let you go.
I wish you had stayed
for a few more years back then
and made more money for me.
I'd have quite a lot of land
in Gangnam right now.
Thanks to the experience here,
the way I see the world
and the things I value
have changed greatly.
Sure. It seems like
you are doing a lot of good work.
Why are you here anyway?
I have a favor to ask of you.
A favor?
Of course.
I know there's nothing
you would miss here.
You must be here
because you want something.
Oh, right.
I brought a present
that might suit you well.
Gosh.
You shouldn't have brought such a thing.
Oh, my god.
Okay. What's the favor you want?
It's something trivial,
but very important.
We're getting
another big lunar eclipse after 39 years.
This country was seeing
an economic revival at that time.
And thanks to Mun-suk's appearance,
Ms. Jang was able to turn the poor
business into a successful one,
laying the groundwork for the wealth
and luxury she's enjoying now.
She worked here
for about seven to eight years.
I never imagined such a person
would've worked here as a manager.
Because Ms. Jang doesn't leave
any traces of the human managers
who used to work here.
However,
I wonder why she came here when she has
such a big event happening soon.
We're going to take human guests?
Is that possible?
Yes, because a lunar eclipse is coming.
Are things different with a lunar eclipse?
When the moon's covered during an eclipse,
the Guest House of the Moon's presence
is exposed.
That's why we get quite a few human guests
during eclipses.
Even humans are able to see our ghost
guests when they come into our hotel.
So, do we accept human guests
on the day of the lunar eclipse?
The front desk turns them away, of course.
But...
Did that happen in 1981?
When Mun-suk was here
during a lunar eclipse,
some newlyweds stayed at our hotel.
I'm sorry, I didn't realize
it's past the curfew.
-I'm sorry.
-Is it this way?
Yes. That way.
HOTEL DEL LUNA
I think this is a hotel.
The lunar eclipse better end soon.
-Excuse me.
-Do you have a room?
Newlyweds?
They came to Seoul for their honeymoon,
and now it's past curfew.
If we turn them away now,
they'll have to spend
their first night at the police station.
I feel bad for them.
Let them in, then.
This is your room.
Please go in.
-Thank you.
Thank you so much.
The couple spent
their first night at our hotel.
At that night, a human baby was conceived
for the first time
at this ghost hotel.
And that baby grew up to be
Korea's most talented soccer player.
Really?
He got conceived here?
Yes, apparently. I was shocked too
when I heard about it earlier.
Anyway, he's going to become
Mun-suk's son-in-law.
-Really?
-She went to meet her future in-laws
and met the newlywed couple.
They were all so surprised.
What an interesting coincidence.
But then again,
this place is full of unimaginable things.
I guess it's natural that the baby
turned out to be someone special.
She wants us to let her daughter
and future son-in-law
stay here for one night so they can
also experience the same thing.
Then, are we going to let them stay
in the room that the King stayed in?
No, they're humans.
They should stay in Room 404.
Room 404?
But no one can check out of that room.
The only way you can check out
of our hotel is head for the afterlife.
Then how are they supposed to check out
of Room 404?
Are you worried about them?
Then why don't you go in there
and check for yourself?
On the night of this year's lunar eclipse,
we'll be welcoming human guests.
They're newlyweds.
It'll be their honeymoon.
They made an official reservation
this time,
so get ready to treat them well.
-Yes, ma'am.
We need to get food and decorations
that are fit for humans.
I'm excited to hear
that we'll be getting human guests.
But where's our manager?
He went inside Room 404.
Then I guess he won't be
returning tonight.
Whatever the case, I'm really excited.
Veronica.
Are you in Wai Tan in Shanghai?
Yes, I was in a meeting,
but I came out to eat lunch now.
-Sanchez, I'm so upset at you.
-Why? Why are you upset?
I miss you so much.
You really make it hard
for me to focus on work.
I'm going to scold you.
Veronica, I can't wait to meet you
so you can scold me.
Veronica.
I found a way to get scolded by you
forever. You can look forward to it.
Gosh, what are you
going to surprise me with this time?
I can't tell you. You can come here
and check for yourself.
Chan-sung's here.
Say hello.
Hey, Chan-sung.
Hi, Veronica.
Veronica, I'll call you later.
I love you. Goodbye, my love.
Bye.
-Is Veronica coming to Korea?
-Yes.
She's in Shanghai right now.
She's going to come in two days.
So I've been thinking...
I'm planning to do
something really important.
And I'm thinking about doing it
at your hotel.
My hotel?
Veronica's been to all kinds
of hotels all over the world.
When I told her that you work
at a really special hotel,
she wanted to take a look.
I'm also quite curious.
No, you can't do it at my hotel.
Chan-sung, you're not exactly working
at a decent hotel, are you?
-What?
-You had to invite someone
to our house to sell a painting.
And Man-wol even asked me
to sell her horses.
Are you guys struggling financially?
Yes, it's pretty bad.
My goodness.
Chan-sung, let me know
if you're having a hard time.
You can't just endure everything
with love.
Okay?
Okay.
Fine, let's break up.
My gosh.
Mi-ra's fighting all the time.
She and the cop must've been enemies
in their past lives.
They fight all the time.
But she always goes out to meet him.
What? You're not the only one who's busy.
I'm busy too.
You talk like your job is
to save the world.
You think you're a superhero or something?
What?
They were enemies in their past lives.
Sanchez, let's all eat together
when Veronica comes to Korea.
-She's coming in two days, right?
-Yes.
-That's the day of the lunar eclipse.
-Yes, I know.
I was planning on watching
the lunar eclipse at the rooftop bar
in your hotel that you bragged about.
Maybe next time.
I'm sorry.
They could get startled
if they run into other hotel guests.
So we should empty the adjacent rooms.
We already informed the guests
on the fourth floor.
We're moving them to other rooms.
You really are well prepared.
The dinner menu is great.
What kind of drink are you going to...
Are you going to serve them these drinks?
I took your advice
and created my own signature menu.
They're the Angel and Devil.
It's incredible.
But I'm not sure if humans will like them.
Could you try them?
Sure.
Put half of them on the dinner table
and the other half in their room.
Yes, sir.
It's a bee.
I guess the bee came along
since these are real flowers.
I guess we don't have
any bees or butterflies here
since the flowers here are not real.
By any chance,
are there also bug ghosts
that look like fireflies?
I've never heard of anything
called a bug ghost.
Oh, I see.
Then what was that?
Should I put this bouquet in their room?
Yes, sure.
That one looks more romantic.
Wait.
I'd like to put one in my office.
Please follow me.
God... I'm so tired.
You got a lot of special requests
again today, didn't you?
You're all so excited
about those human guests.
I'm the only one
who's taking care of our actual guests.
My gosh, the day feels so long.
My goodness, I'm so tired.
Then here's something to wake you up.
This is a real flower, so it smells nice.
We have tons of flowers in our garden.
None of them are real.
No, wait. Your flowers are real.
That tree of yours is
filled with beautiful flowers.
What's with you?
Are you showing off?
I'm entitled to show off.
The flowers bloomed
the moment I hugged you.
If I knew this was going to happen,
I should've hugged you
instead of buying you champagne.
What are you doing?
I never asked you to hug me.
Are you crazy?
I was asking for the phone.
Okay, here. I'll let you hug me.
Forget it.
You arrogant, greedy fraud from Harvard--
You look so pretty.
I put the additional special requests
on your desk.
You should get back to work
after you get some rest.
Darn it.
I won't let you vanish.
Trust me.
It's real.
You,
I'm going easy on you
because you have a soft heart.
The lunar eclipse has begun.
There will be special guests
coming tonight.
Please do your best
to get ready for the guests.
Everyone seems quite excited.
As the moon gets covered,
they can feel the hotel's presence
is shown to the world.
And human guests are coming as well.
That makes them
feel like they're alive again.
Welcome.
You made a reservation, right?
How long has it been
since you passed away--
I mean, how long has it been
since you got married?
Right, you got married today!
Congratulations.
Please follow me this way.
We'll take your luggage to your room.
You can enjoy your meals first.
These cocktails, Tears, are
our hotel's signature cocktails.
This beautiful one is called
the Angel's Tears.
And this one is called the Devil's Tears.
Why are you so happy?
I hated looking at the full moon.
But look, it's all gone now.
It feels so good watching that.
This is my favorite moment ever.
The whole moon is covered now.
The moon will be different
when it comes out again.
Perhaps it'll know how to be kind
and cut down on spending.
After our human guests
check out of the hotel,
would you like to go out
and see the new, kind moon?
You evil moon.
Do you want to die, Chan-sung?
I'll take that as a yes.
This is why I love my name.
I love how it means "yes."
It's like everyone agrees with me.
It's perfect.
Zero looks like a circle.
And "Koo" means a circle.
Koo Chan-sung.
Sure, Mr. Zeroth Choice,
your name is Mr. Okay Koo now.
What do you mean?
My English name is Andrew.
Chan-sung isn't just okay,
it means "agreement."
Agree, Andrew, whatever.
You're just Okay Koo to me.
Okay?
Okay Koo,
the lunar eclipse is finally complete.
You're right.
This sign means it's yours, right?
Yes.
I wonder if he was waiting for her.
Ms. Jang.
Our guests would like
to go into their room now.
Okay, the lunar eclipse is complete.
It's perfect. Take them to Room 404.
Yes.
Once you go inside,
please don't come out of the room
until you check out.
I already heard about this room
from my parents.
Have a good night then.
A world-famous soccer player
was conceived here.
Who do you think will be next?
You've been a kid for 70 years,
so you wouldn't know this.
But things like this
don't happen just overnight.
I know that it doesn't happen
just overnight.
Why are you laughing?
I know it all.
Really?
Don't just assume
that I don't know things.
We're talking about lives here.
It's not a conversation
a Grim Ripper could jump into.
I hope
that a great scholar will be conceived
this time.
I hope the child will receive
a Nobel Prize.
I hope that triplets will be conceived
so that they'd win three Nobel Prizes.
All the guests and employees at the hotel
are rooting for Room 404 right now.
Veronica hasn't arrived yet?
I waited for her,
thinking that her flight was delayed,
but the flight was never delayed.
She's not even picking up her phone.
Chan-sung,
do you think Veronica knew
I was going to propose
and is avoiding me
because she's feeling pressured?
Veronica loves you more than you love her.
No, I love her so much more.
Veronica has never broken
any promises with me.
I just got a text.
It must be from Veronica.
I'll call you later.
Sanchez.
Sanchez!
An accident? What happened?
Veronica got hurt.
I think she got into a car accident
in Shanghai.
I have to go now.
How badly is she hurt?
I have to go and see.
-I'm sure she'll be fine.
-Yes.
Hey, I have to stay there
until she gets better.
Okay.
Where's my car key?
I have to go.
Even if you go there,
you won't be able to see her.
Hey, don't say that.
You won't be able to see her.
It's too late.
What's with you?
It's not too late!
If I go now, I can see her.
Sanchez.
I'll let you see her.
What?
If you come to my hotel now,
you can meet her.
Hey. What the hell are you talking about?
Do you trust me? We don't have much time.
You won't be able to see her
if you're late.
Mr. Koo.
There is a lady guest
who'll come in right after us.
We'll be waiting for her
at the Sky Lounge.
Please bring her over
after the beauty service.
Sure.
Let go of me.
What are we going to do here?
You'll see once you go out there.
I'll tell you after you see this.
Hey, how are you working here?
This is a very special hotel.
It's a hotel for the dead.
What?
I have no time to explain.
You can see the dead
until the eclipse is over.
So,
you'll have only a little time
to say goodbye to Veronica.
What?
Stop joking around.
How could she come here?
Because she's dead.
She is here.
Sanchez, Veronica is dead.
I'm sorry...
I surprised you like this.
Don't cry too much...
for me.
I lived
a happy life thanks to you.
My awfully handsome love.
Goodbye.
Mr. Koo's friend
had to say goodbye to his love.
Such a sudden death leaves
those left behind
with great sorrow.
I only see the dead these days,
so it's been a while
since I saw the sorrow
of the living.
Yes, come in.
Did you have a great night?
Yes. We won't be able to forget
the time we spent
in this hotel.
Thank you. Take care then.
It's exactly like what my parents told me.
It's a hotel you can never find again.
When we have a baby later,
let's find the hotel and have the baby
go on their honeymoon there like we did.
I'd like that.
Veronica's funeral will be held in Italy.
Sanchez will stay there for a while.
I feel so sorry for Sanchez.
He couldn't even see
his girlfriend's last moments.
He didn't get to say goodbye.
He saw her. He got to say goodbye too.
He learned that death isn't the end,
so I'm sure Sanchez will be able
to get through it.
So he got to say goodbye.
But how did he see her?
Didn't she die in Shanghai?
Gosh, this coffee smells so good.
You should have another.
I'm sorry.
She's really tailing me.
Why would such a cute student follow me?
I better ask her.
I heard they really enjoyed their stay.
Thank you.
If you end up quitting your job
at Hotel del Luna, come look for me.
Ms. Jang told me
that you're quite competent
and recommended you to me.
I don't think I'll be quitting.
According to Ms. Jang,
you're going to quit soon.
There's a guest
Chan-sung will have to send off himself.
Once he sends off that guest,
he'll probably leave this place.
Did she say that?
Did they come up with a new rule
for the hotel manager?
Who is the last guest
you'll be sending off?
It's someone...
I like a lot.
It'll be difficult for you.
I think so.
It's too hard for me to console myself...
by saying I know it's coming.
What were you doing? Were you sleeping?
I'm awake.
I'm looking at the moon.
The moon?
How can you see the moon during the day?
I don't know.
It must be pretty hard
to miss something you can't see.
Where are you?
I'm on my way home.
Wait at home. I'll come to see you.
What is it, Yu-na?
81GI 0963
I've found that car.
Where are you right now? Where?
Don't move. Stay right there.
Why did she follow me all the way here?
Yu-na!
The man in the sketch
and the owner of that car look alike.
Could he be the culprit?
What's the matter?
He looks a lot like...
someone I know.
I'll look into it now. You should go home.
Okay.
I told him to wait,
but he's making me wait.
Anyone here?
Is anybody here?
The dreaded Mago has come
instead of the one I've been waiting for.
Why?
I'm the deity you've been waiting for
the most.
Am I wrong?
You didn't care about reincarnation,
healing, and connections.
You only wished to see me and vanish.
So? Are you here to do that for me?
I've heard the flowers have bloomed.
You finally have
something to lose too.
Do you think
I'm afraid to see the flowers fall?
What about the one
that helped you bloom the flowers?
What if you lose him?
Long time no see, Chan-sung.
Man-wol, you conceited and foolish thing.
Did you say you weren't afraid
to see the flowers fall?
No.
Your flowers will begin to fall
when you become afraid.
So the price Chan-sung needs to pay
in return
won't be fair nor reasonable.
You can stroke my hair in your room
to help me fall asleep.
What's with you? You're too naughty.
You were really scared.
I don't want you to pay the price,
so I'll do everything I can
to clean up after you.
Don't be afraid when you leave me behind.
This is how I, just a weak human,
love you with all my heart.
Subtitle translation by Wayne Ryu