One, two, three!
Yeah, why, is there something?
Seriously?
Did she die?
Holy smokes!
Breaking News: Actress Cheon Song Yi
falls during filming, her life in danger
Has he gone crazy?
He has gone crazy.
Breaking News: Actress Cheon Song Yi
falls during filming, critical condition.
What's the matter? By now...
Shouldn't you be meeting with a prosecutor about now?
If you're complying with our agreement?
What do you think I will do to you?
I am going to kill you.
Me? You will?
You dare?
That's right.
I will kill you. Now.
Just as you did to Cheon Song Yi,
I will kill you with the same method.
Die!
My Love From the Star
Episode 14
A week before the incident
I am sorry. Are you alright?
Yes, I am fine.
Thank you.
Perhaps, can't you erase memories?
Excuse me? Erase what memories?
If you watch movies,
there was something like that, why...
When aliens press something like a button,
people's memories all
get erased, something like that.
Can't you do something like that?
That's a movie, isn't it?
You have the ability to stop time and you have psychokinesis...
For someone who can do most anything,
why can't you do that?
-You really don't have that ability?
-No I don't.
True, now, you don't know when the powers
you do have might disappear either.
When they work, they work, and when they don't, they don't.
Now, well, it's just the luck of the draw,
even your supernatural powers.
Since it's unnerving, what do we do?
I'm wondering if the only thing I can do
is to disappear well.
Because there is nothing I can do here anymore.
Do the things that I am able to do (for her).
What is that you can do (for her) now?
By chance,
you are not thinking of that, are you?
That, you can't do.
If you use your abilities to kill someone, then...
Was that it?
It was something like that?
There was something like that?
I think I need to meet Do Min Joon.
I have considered the offer you made.
You said you would take the blame
for everything and disappear for me.
I figured I'd have nothing to lose.
Honestly, I've been gradually becoming annoyed with this as well.
If you'll just keep your promise,
I don't have any reason to go further than this.
I'm someone who has many things to lose.
If
you break the promise...
I know that you are a special person.
You've shown me many times, haven't you?
I've even tried to get rid of you somehow.
But I also know well that that won't happen.
If I bother you pointlessly,
I know full well that it will cause me unnecessary hardship,
so why would I? I am not that foolish.
If you break your promise
I will get rid of you myself.
That I'm someone who can do that,
as you said, you should know well
since I showed it to you many times.
Yes, I know it well.
You know, about what Hui Kyeong mentioned before...
You know about Jae Kyeong 's wife...
Have you, by any chance, heard anything about her?
How would I know?
It's because there's something that she told me
before their divorce that still bothers me.
She told me
that Jae Kyeong is scary.
She asked me to save her.
You give them an inch and they take a mile.
I took in a girl who was basically an orphan,
and made her my daughter-in-law.
But she shook off all that was offered and ran away.
And now what?!
How dare she say he scares her!
But don't you feel that way as well?
Even though he's someone that I gave birth to,
I find Jae Kyeong  a little difficult.
There's not a single fault in him.
But somehow, unlike with Hui Kyeong,
I get very cautious around him.
That's why, he's my successor.
That rascal was born with the inclination to be a top honcho.
He's different from Hui Kyeong.
What happened to him when he was young
still bothers me, and--
Why are you bringing up such an ancient story?
Didn't I tell you never to mention it?
- I'm home.
- Ah, you're here.
Yes.
- Please rest.
- Alright.
I was thinking about visiting oldest brother's grave
next weekend, would you have time to accompany me?
Yes, let's go together next weekend.
3 days prior to the incident.
Haneul Mental Hospital
Are there any patients with the name of Yang Min Joo?
There's no one like that here.
How many patients are there in this hospital?
What?
Why do you want to know that?
It's just that this seems like a pretty big hospital.
Despite that, you can say immediately after hearing the name, that there isn't such a person here without looking it up.
You must be very smart.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Anyway, there's no one like that here,
so please go back.
Oh, I see.
Okay.
2 days before the incident.
You heard the news, right?  That our Se Mi
and Song Yi will be working on the same movie.
Ah yes, Mother. I heard our Se Mi here
strongly recommended Song Yi...
Yeah, she's like that.
She's so kind that it's killing me, CEO.
Even after being treated like that by Song Yi,
I don't understand how she can be like this.
No. Song Yi, in the past, had also persistently
insisted  that she acted with Se Mi.
When the director said that it won't work out,
she said that if Se Mi didn't do it, then she wouldn't either!
She always made such a huge fuss about it
that it annoyed the hell out of-
It's all in the past.
As it were, pay close attention to it, please, President.
Of course.
I'm taking care of her a lot even now.
Also, please send more of Se Mi's staff to the scene.
So that everyone can tell she's the main character.
And so that there would be a huge difference
between her and Cheon Song Yi.
Mom.
And, I'll say this as the topic came up.
What?
"The 2nd Cheon Song Yi" or something,
don't let there be news like that anymore.
Uttering "insurgence of supporting actor" or whatnot.
Mom, stop it.
He probably understands already.
We have good news.
The billboard ad
that our Se Mi has been longing to do,
we've got it!
Really?
When I checked with his company, the summer vacation
Managing Director Lee Jae Kyeong took
was from July 24th to July 27th.
The cell phone base station used at that time was
confirmed as the one in Cheong Pyeong.
However,
on Han Yoo Ra's side,
from July 24th
to the 27th.
Also Cheong Pyeong!
They found out about the vacation home in Cheong Pyeong.
I think you must take precautions.
One day before the incident.
- We can look around, right?
- Yes.
This is the private villa of Lee Jae Kyeong.
He rarely comes here.
Well... He spent his vacation here last summer.
If you go down 2 kilometers from here,
his family villa, owned by the Chairman, is there.
He spent his summer vacation over there.
Then who usually comes here?
Either foreign buyers the Managing Director invites or
his personal guests have stayed at this place.
Did Actress Han Yoo Ra ever come here before?
Yes. She came last summer.
I heard that because she was the department store's model
that the Director let her use it.
She came with some man.
Is this him?
Yes. It is.
Your memory is really great.
You can remember someone you
saw last year so quickly.
I think I must have contracted some kind of disease from you.
What?
Everything fits so perfectly, but
why is it so weird?
Why does it seem like Do Min Joon isn't the one?
Actually, Do Min Joon is going to come tomorrow.
Where? Why?
He says he will... turn himself in.
I see...
What?
Really...
He's a  really  strange person.
When the time never ended for me
no matter how much time passed by,
I never once thought of that time
to be precious.
However,
now, if I could gain even a single day to be with her,
I don't believe I'd care even if I lost everything I have.
But...
Even if I throw away everything I have,
I now know the fact
that I cannot gain that.
What gives?
Could there be nights when so many stars
can appear in the Seoul sky?
Do Min Joon...
Did you really come from one of the stars
from up there?
Why didn't you just say you don't like me and be done with it?
Why did you say things like how you
came from the stars and such, that
I would  be forced to think about you
every time I look at the night sky?
And I
know this, too.
When you start to love someone,
you also start to have fears.
Because I might not be able to protect someone I need to protect,
I'm afraid right now.
The day of the incident.
Yes, hello?
This is the movie 'Witness' team.
Ah, yes. I'm almost ready. I was about to leave.
The director wants you to come without any make-up.
You know, it's an action scene. . .
Of course I won't. Do you think I would?
I won't.
Hey. Why are you looking like that?
You said you were going to put make-up on yourself.
It won't do. Let's stop by a (beauty) shop.
It's fine. I'm going to be jumping down
and running in the mud anyway.
What good is putting make-up on? Just go.
What about the car?
I can drive.
It won't look good, though.
I mean, what's up with Manager Do?
Oh, Manager Do. I'm glad to see you.
- You don't work for Song Yi anymore-
-- He doesn't.
He doesn't?
Can I take the elevator first?
I think it will be uncomfortable for both of us
to take the same elevator.
Hey, why are you like that? Did you two fight?
Should I talk to him later?
This won't do. I'll call him and set it straight.
Mom. . .
What?
If you bother him,
I will just go live with him.
What?
I like him a lot.
So I confessed to him, but was rejected.
Are you crazy?
When there's Hui Kyeong. . .
I know.
It is hard for me to take care of my feelings, so. . .
Hey.
Are you crying?
You are, because of a man, crying?
Yeah.
I'm crying.
Because of a man, I'm crying pathetically.
So, don't bother him.
Just now, I wanted to cling onto him,
but barely held it in.
You are crazy.
Yeah.
I'm crazy.
Prosecution Service
Are you crazy?
Why? Why do you think like that?
Otherwise,
I have to kill Lee Jae Kyeong.
Whether I kill him or stop him,
it's one or the other.
If I don't, Cheon Song Yi could die.
Cheon Song Yi told the detective
about the relationship between
Lee Jae Kyeong and Han Yoo Ra.
There's no time.
Prosecution Service
Then, promise me just one thing.
You won't ever do it.
Because of an inhuman bastard like him. . .
I can't let it happen.
Promise me.
At least promise me!
I told you to ignore the matter and move on,
but you won't listen to me!
I told you to spend the remaining time here in peace,
but you won't listen!
Then promise me this one thing.
I promise.
You have promised then.
Seriously, if you break this promise...
Then I seriously won't see you again!
From this point on, this conversation is recorded.
Do you agree with this?
Yes, I agree.
Let's start.
On the day of Ms. Han Yoo Ra's death,
The person in the picture from the cruise
is me.
Please continue.
Mr. Beom.
- Yes?
I have to learn my lines. Would you practice with me?
Now?
Mm. Don't want to?
No! Which scene?
Scene 17.
"You should let me go. The detectives will be here soon."
"Shut that mouth of yours."
"I loved you."
"Love? You didn't love me."
"You loved my decent face and wealth."
"But..."
"I will hear such excuses in hell."
"Bye.  Zài jiàn." ("Bye" in Chinese)
POW!
Where is "Bye. Zài jiàn."?
Ah, I'm sorry.
It was an ad lib. Was it weird?
Why do you think she recommended you for this role?
She wants to show you that she's the main actress now.
She wants to brag about it in front of you.
Her mom's like that, but I thought she was nice. But she's worse.
Mom. I have to memorize my lines.
There are not many lines to memorize anyway!
Exactly 3 words.  "Stop right there!"
There are still so many actions!
Looks like Se Mi gets to taste all the romance
and you'll get to kick to your heart's content.
I mean, these people!
There's no one bringing a chair for you?
Today, it's Cheon Song Yi's treat!
♬  We will be together for all times.  ♬
Indeed. . .
Please put them in front of Ms. Cheon Song Yi.
Cheon Song Yi
♬  I've been saving up my moments,
but I'll spend them with you now.  ♬
♬  You are my love forever.  ♬
- You came, Mother.
-- Yeah, welcome.
How is it you came here?
Did you tell him, Mom?
What?
He asked me where you were shooting, so. . .
What's. . .all this?
You might catch a cold.
For sure, people who've spent quite a sum of money
know how to use money. Anyway, thank you, Hui Kyeong.
My Song Yi can keep her head up now.
Of course she should.
If Cheon Song Yi keeps her head down,
is that still Cheon Song Yi?
I should go tell them to come eat.
Why go this far?
I have to suck up to the staff to film you well.
Ah, right. Who is the actress you are working with?
Noona.
- Unni.
So, it is Se Mi. The actress you are working with.
Yes.
Actually, I know it also. That Se Mi likes you a lot.
But why is the mood like that?
I should let her clean up her feelings
as fast as possible, right?
I should've done that too, right?
For you, it's too late.
You are going to do that today?
Yes. If you have time, watch me and then leave.
I am going to make new history in the action movies.
Can you try raising this?
Director, you were hungry, weren't you?
Please come eat.  Enjoy the food!
Cheon Song Yi is treating you today!
- Thank you!
Song Yi Will Treat You Today
Enjoy the food!
--Eat a lot, Director.
--Thank you!
Why aren't you eating?
Don't bother.
Really? Then, do so.
But wait,
isn't it too much?
What is?
The main actress is staying still,
but the supporting actress is acting out.
What, how childish.
Are you trying to win favors through food?
You might not know this because it's your first time,
but do you want to know how to
really  make her into a main actress?
What?
Just because she has more lines,
doesn't mean she's the main.
Loosen up.
If you are that anxious, everyone can tell.
Your daughter is not good enough for the role,
but you put her there anyway,
and now you are nervous to the core
because people might realize that.
Omo. Director Jo.
Go and eat up.
I think we need to get a tight shot here.
Aren't you scared?
I am scared.
But in the worst case scenario, I will just die, right?
Hey, how can you say that?
Don't you worry. I won't die.
Let's have dinner later. I will treat you to something good.
Raise her.
Lower.
- How is it? Is it okay?
- Yes.
Once you fall about half way,
they will start pulling the wire.
And we'll do the landing when we're taking full shots.
The important part for this shot is that
you have to look very cool when you jump off, okay?
Okay.
Hey. Get it controlled.
There's no danger of that being leaked out, so...
Hyung!
What?
What are you doing,  pull!
What's happening? Why is this happening?
What's going on?
Hui Kyeong!
Emergency Center
Oh, why? Did something happen?
Really? Did she die?
Daebak!
Actress Cheon Song Yi Hurt In Fall While Filming.
Life in Danger.
Se Mi. What is this?
What happened to our Hui Kyeong?
Mother.
Do not act so rashly. A lot of people are watching.
Central Surgery Station
Why can't my Song Yi go into surgery?
Because of splenic rupture, there is copious bleeding.
She also has an external injury, so we need to secure a transfusion.
But, her RH antibody screening test result
came out as positive.
What?
RH E-type blood was confirmed,  a specific kind of blood type.
This is a very unique and rare blood type,
and our hospital does not have it.
We are going to try to look more.
Because we are such in an emergency state
we'd like all family members to get their blood type tested.
Is there any other family member?
No, what happened?
How did this..?
Wow, even on these articles, people curse her off.
I know right?
I should just..
-Let me go. I am going to sue all those people.
-You can't. Hold it in.
No.. Why are you doing this? Stop.
Hey. Cheon Song Yi got into an accident.
Serves her right. I didn't like her.
Hey. Are you guys human?
Get out!
You guys are banned from this comic book store. Get out!
Hold it in. Just look at me and hold it in.
Oppa, Cheon Song Yi got into an accident.
A wire was cut when she was filming.
I guess she was seriously hurt since her life is in danger.
Where?
Where is the hospital?
What are we going to do if both you and I don't match hers?
Our Song Yi... What is she going to do?
They say they're going to look into other hospitals.
Song Yi's dad..
Song Yi's mom.. Where's our Song Yi?
What's this? It's too easy.
He says he did everything without us interrogating.
If this is true, then wouldn't we have to
arrest him right away, Prosecutor?
A lawyer follows in but just sighs.
Please say something.
Can we take a break?
Let us.
Would you like some drinks?
It's okay.
Do Min Joon.
Yes.
Do you have a secret that you want to keep?
Or, do you have a person you want to protect?
What is the reason for coming up with
the perfect lie pointing to yourself?
I don't know for what or for whom you are doing it,
but because of you, someone else's crimes can be covered up.
Prosecutor.
Something happened.
It says Cheon Song Yi had an accident while filming.
She's in critical condition.
Look at this. The number 1 search keyword
is "Cheon Song Yi critical."
That's right, you are close with Cheon Song Yi.
How could something like this happen?
This man! A person's still talking, yet he runs out.
Mr. Do Min Joon!
Did Do Min Joon already go?
Pardon. Who?
Do Min Joon, the one that was just interrogated.
Didn't he just leave?
No, he didn't.
What are you saying? He came bolting out of that door.
No, no one came out before you, Detective.
I have been watching constantly.
What are you saying?
He opened that door and just came out.
No, I'm telling you that no one came out.
Have my eyes turned weird?
Did Do Min Joon come in just right now?
No. He just went out, remember?
I know, right.
He went out, but he's gone.
He was there just a while ago, but gone.
But why does this strange situation seem so familiar?
Hey! Do Min Joon!
Prosecutor, even if I get called a lunatic,
I need to confirm this.
Here. Here.
Here, he came out here.
Here. . . But he doesn't come out there.
Hey, it's not even ...
It's like something out of a Hollywood movie. . .
Wow!
Look at my hair standing up here.
What is that bastard?
Is he Harry Potter? Is he Harry Potter?
Is he playing around with us?
Please tell us.
What is it? Magic, is that it?
High level of trickery. Is he a friend of Lee Eun Kyul or what? (Lee Eun Kyul is one of the famous Korean magicians)
If not, how are you going to explain this situation?
You must have seen wrongly.
You must be kidding! It was caught by the CCTV.
He opened that door to go out,
but he didn't appear on the other side.
He disappeared. Just like magic!
The CCTV must have been malfunctioning ...
or it's a faulty one.
Are you really going to be like this?
Try calling him. Ask him where he went
to see if he went to Hogwarts, the school of magic.
It feels like I'm in a dream right now.
He's gone crazy.
Crazy.
The father's results came out to be a match
for Cheon Song Yi's RH.
Please prepare for the surgery.
- Okay.
Father, please go directly to the Blood Center and prepare
for the transfusion.
Yes, yes, I will be going.
I will be going. Don't worry.
Breaking news. Actress Cheon Song Yi
injured at shooting site. Condition critical
What's the matter? By this time...
Shouldn't you be meeting with the prosecutor?
According to our agreement?
What do you think I will do to you?
You. . . I will kill you.
Me? You will?
You dare to?
That's right. I will. Right now.
You. . .
I will kill you the same way you did to Cheon Song Yi.
DIE!
You can't kill me.
I. . . know...
That if you kill me. . .
you will also die.
You couldn't be thinking about that, right?
You can't do that.
If ever you kill someone with your abilities,
you said you will also die.
That's why you haven't interfered with anything, held back, and lived this far, isn't it?
No matter how much you hate him,
you should never let that thought become reality.
You can't die just to kill that inhuman bastard.
Could it be that you are risking your life just to kill me?
Did we have such a special relationship?
I know everything about you.
Your secret, who you are. . .
where you came from, and. . .
what your fatal weakness is. . . everything.
It's not like you have many lives,
even if you are an alien.
Perhaps, are you going to use that one life...
on me?
If killing you...
can stop you,
I'm fine if I die.
Cheon Song Yi will die too!
If I die,
Cheon Song Yi, who's in the hospital now, will die too.
Do you think I didn't set up any safety device
while playing a game with a guy like you?
Even if you kill me,
you can't stop me.
If I die, you die!
Then,
there will be no one to protect her.
Are you...
still okay with it?
Pray that Cheon Song Yi will be safe.
If something happens to her,
I'll be back to kill you.
You said you have much to lose.
I'll let you taste the feeling of losing something one by one.
Eventually, I'll make you lose everything.
Destruction!
I'll let you know what that is, distinctly.
- You dare to...?
- Whom you dared...!!!
to mess with. I'll let you know that, too.
The surgery was successful,
but there was copious bleeding.
Pulmonary edema developed, so until she
breathes normally, she needs to use the oxygen respirator.
And we need to observe the progress.
What about her life? Will she survive though?
Let's watch her for a little.
If she breathes normally in 2 days,
you won't have anything to worry about.
It's still very fortunate.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
I'm thankful.
Our Song Yi,
you saved her.
I'll be going now.
Call me when something happens.
Go after seeing her wake up.
She won't want to see my face.
That's always the problem with you!
You really don't know how people feel?
Our Song Yi...
Do you know how much she missed you?
Even if I said not to appear again,
how can you really not appear. Not even once!
The one who is worse than me
is you.
Aren't you going to greet your father?
You said I didn't have a father.
It was you who didn't even leave a single picture, then now...
Dad.
When I was young, I called you whenever I got scared.
Cue!
Dad...
But now,
I call out a different name.
Do Min Joon.
For the first time,
I have a person whom I love more than you, Dad.
From morning till night...
I've got a person with whom I want to do everything.
♫ The person who called out to you like that is me  ♫
♫ My tears which flow  senselessly are love ♫
♫ You were always at my side but ♫
No matter how much that person keeps pushing me to go away,
♫ I didn't know it was you and ♫
I can't take a step.
♫ Why you, who were waiting, knew and ♫
♫ and just told a sad story. ♫
Even if I try so hard to hate him,
♫  Today how many more of the same tears are left. ♫
I can't hate him.
Again and again,
♫  Today how many more of the same tears are left. ♫
I keep on dreaming sad dreams that he loves me..
♫ Will you tell me I don't know love and farewell? ♫
♫ Rain drops keep turning into tears, blocking my vision ♫
♫ Where are the tears the same as today's going? ♫
♫ How much more? I don't know ♫
Again and again,
I'm dreaming a sad dream.