[English subtitles are available.]
Who is she?
Why do you take my photo without my permission?
I have to answer you?
What are you doing?
Are you crazy?
Who
are you?
Who are you? I feel curious
because you can stand in the air,
with weird clothes and strange hairstyle.
And the strange object floats down from the sky.
Everything is strange.
What is your real identity?
I won’t be shocked no matter what.
Don’t look down upon me. I like reading
the collections of bizarre stories.
Mother often said it’s ridiculous,
but I don’t think only mankind exist in the world.
There probably be things like ghosts, monsters,
nine-tailed foxes and emissaries.
Which one do you belong to?
You don’t have anything to say?
Then do you have a place to go?
Where are your families?
No matter who you are,
you are my savior.
In that case,
mother-in-law may allow you to stay.
So, please go with me.
Follow me!
I will help you.
What an unlucky thing!
Madam Seo hanged and killed herself
last night at the foot of the hill.
In memory of her virtue,
we’ll apply to the court for the title of paragon.
The funeral is held tonight.
Find out the kid and kill her.
She is conferred upon and can’t be found alive.
Yes.
This
is my grave.
What am I now?
What will happen if they find me alive?
What should I do now?
I’ll visit the parental home in Kangneung
and tell all this to my father.
He may tell me the way to survive.
Thank you for all your help.
I don’t know where you were from,
but I hope you can return safely.
I don’t know your identity.
But you seem to have superpower.
Anyway, please don’t worry about me.
Leave here
together with me.
Let me
protect you.
Are you asking who I am?
You still don’t know me? I’m Cheon Song-yi.
Yes, you are Cheon Song-yi.
You can’t be her.
Who is she?
She and I are alike?
Right, many people in Cheongdam-dong
want to have my face via surgery.
But fake ones
are never better than the real one.
Hey, what are you looking at?
The shoes
are yours?
Of course.
This is the only pair throughout the country.
I will never use casual brands.
[My Love from the Star Record 3]
Is it rebirth
or doppelganger?
You are not superstitious.
How can you make an illogical speculation?
Please be logical. It’s impossible.
An alien exists, so rebirth is also possible.
As for logics, your existence is illogical.
What’s your plan?
What?
I mean the shoes you mentioned.
Will it be like 12 years ago?
You are foreseeing the accident later on?
The owner of the shoes may die?
Will you get involved like 12 years ago
or just let it be
as usual?
What did you do with Han Yoo-ra
in the beauty room?
Everyone is talking about it.
I don’t know. She always tries to piss me off.
Who is the man
held your hand and took you out?
The man lives next door.
Your professor?
Yes.
Why did he come for you?
Gave me my wallet back.
He said I’m alike with someone else.
Who?
There is no doubt.
Maybe first love. Maybe deceased mother.
We know the feeling.
He gets close to me on purpose.
What’s wrong?
I had a stomachache since last night.
You didn’t eat anything for the shooting?
-Hello, Ms. Cheon.
I’ve watched the award ceremony for you.
Congratulations.
The evening dress is fabulous.
Where did you buy it?
Miss Yoo, time to the next scene.
Okay.
Hey, do you know Yoo Se-mi?
-Yes.
Then why didn’t you say hello to her?
Where did you learn the bad habit from?
I will watch you.
If you make her awkward again,
I won’t forgive you easily.
You’ve heard about my hot temper, right?
It’s not a rumor but the truth.
Goodness, I forget my lines because of you.
Is she kidding?
She can only realize the problem
while being in the worst situation.
Everyone is looking forward to something bad.
Then Cheon Song-yi is screwed.
If she is really that popular
and great,
how can I trust you and let you take her away?
It seems
I saw the guy somewhere.
Six o’clock.
It’s six o’clock. Let’s call it a day.
I’m leaving now.
Leaving now?
Yes.
Hey, the new guy.
Listen carefully.
I don’t want to…
Please calm down.
I will solve it.
Mr. Lee Hee-kyung.
Are you here to play?
I’ve finished my job, so…
You can never finish your job before seniors.
The new one should be helpful.
How can you use that photo as the background?
She’s my girlfriend.
Shut up!
My wife is Kim Num-ju, will you believe it?
You are decadent.
Workers only put work things on the desk,
or use a family photo as the background
to remind themselves
of working hard.
Do they?
Stop asking questions.
Go change your background
and buy everyone a cup of coffee.
Quickly!
It’s hard to stand in the society.
Yes, sir.
What’s wrong?
Mr. Yoo.
Did he go for the coffee?
I taught him a lesson.
Why bother? Mr. Yoo.
He used a family photo as the background.
I asked him to do that.
Is this our chairman?
And Director Lee?
What do you think?
Lee Hee-kyung is chairman’s son
and little brother of Director Lee.
Mr. Yoo.
I lost my temper in front of Lee Hee-kyung?
Yes.
Mr. Yoo.
Why did I do that?
Here is your coffee.
I didn’t do it well.
Although I finished my job,
I should wait for you and get off together.
Mr. Yoo already told me all that.
Did I?
Yes.
Have you finished your job?
I’ve finished.
Yes, right.
We should finish our job on time.
Then let’s get off together.
Okay.
Thank you for the coffee.
It’s hot.
How is it going? Did you reveal yourself?
Of course not. Nobody knows.
Come in.
Director Hwang.
Hee-kyung, nice to meet you.
How are you?
Fine.
I heard you’re back. Let’s have dinner together.
Sure, but it’s your treat.
I don’t earn much because I just begin to work.
Okay.
And…
Hee-kyung, go back first.
Okay.
Director Hwang, I will visit you.
What’s the matter?
I once said it before.
It’s about Im Se-ug.
He joined land procurement of the shopping
center and died of car accident not long ago.
Oh, yes.
It seems we have to conduct an investigation.
During the funeral, the family said
something weird happened before the accident.
It’s said at that time
this is beyond our control.
The police will handle it.
But I feel it’s weird.
It’s said he met someone of our company
on the day before the accident.
We should conduct an investigation in detail.
Fine.
Go ahead.
Okay, I see.
How’s your diabetes?
I measure glucose and take insulin regularly.
It’s stable now.
I like you so much. Please take care.
Okay. Thank you. See you.
My stomach!
What’s wrong with it?
Beom.
Song-yi.
I have a stomachache
in the right side.
I’ve told you it’s because of great pressure.
It’s different. Come quickly.
It’s my dad’s death-day. I’m in Chun-cheon.
Call an ambulance!
It will become news in that case.
Call your mom. Or I will call her.
Don’t call her.
I will go by myself.
Stomach on the right side. It may be appendix.
It’s none of my business.
My stomach. Remain conscious.
I’m a star.
Star of Asia.
National Goddess.
There are so many shoes.
This one.
I should keep fashion even go to hospital.
Excuse me.
Where are you going please?
Me? Seong-min University Hospital.
But it’s two a.m.
I have something to do.
Forget it. That’s great.
I feel extremely terrible,
so would you please take me with you?
Began to feel uncomfortable at nightfall.
Have a fever.
Feel painful on pressing
and worse without pressing.
From all these, I think it’s appendicitis.
[Appendicitis]
What are you doing?
You have one year of experience, right?
Give the records to the doctor
and prepare for surgery.
Okay.
But who are you?
What?
What’s your relationship with the patient?
He’s my manager.
Me? God!
Why did you ask me to do all that?
There are too many operas recently
related to stories in hospital.
Why am I your manager?
I am a star.
If I came to hospital with a strange man,
there will be rumors.
Pregnant or trying to kill myself.
Very ridiculous.
You still can’t say I’m your manager anyway.
Are you Cheon Song-yi’s manager?
Please apply for admission.
If it’s really appendicitis,
do I have to have the operation?
Of course. You don’t want to?
There will be a scar.
I still want to wear bikini.
Please tell the doctor to pay attention to it.
Why me?
You agreed to be my manager.
When did I agree?
Cheon Song-yi’s manager.
Yes.
Is this the number?
There is a person using beeper today.
Please wait a moment.
Hey, Manager Do.
What’s wrong?
Don’t leave.
You can’t leave. Stay beside me when I wake up.
Don’t go. Wait here.
Time to enter.
Hear me?
Manager Do. Don’t leave.
Guardian?
Yes.
Because of the surgery, the air in the stomach
has to be released.
You can see the green signs in passage.
Help the patient to walk there for several circles
so that she can fart quickly.
I won’t fart.
You can’t leave hospital before farting.
It’s impossible.
-I will inform you after that.
-Okay.
God!
Oh my! The hospital gown is cheesy.
Only slim clothes fit my beauty.
Ask them if they have some in red.
Red ones are better for me.
Are you serious?
Keep walking.
The lady must be extremely beautiful, right?
Who?
The one like me.
You even got confused,
so she must be an epic beauty.
I made a mistake.
You are not alike
in details.
Is she your first love?
No.
I owe her.
In this case, you may owe a lot of people.
Think of it carefully.
You are kind of man easy to be hated.
You should change your manner.
Alright now.
It’s not me.
Nurse.
Hey. It’s not me.
It’s snowing.
The first snow.
It’s the first snow.
You know?
In Joseon,
any lies can be forgiven during the first snow.
Even lying to the emperor won’t be blamed.
Sir,
I have something to tell you.
Actually, I
love you.
So I want to grow up quickly
and then you can see the beautiful grown me.
I’m lying.
Are you scared ?
I’ve said
any lies could be forgiven today,
because it’s the first snow.
How can we have the first snow
without chicken and beer?
Beef intestine and liquor sound good.
I want to have seafood pie and dense wine,
noodles with fried sauce, sweet and sour pork.
-Hey you…
-And raw cuttlefish.
It’s really amazing to bite alive little things
with some sesame oil.
Was it an appendix operation or brain surgery?
I can’t remember when I ate things at will.
1,395 calories of noodles with fried sauce,
sweet and sour pork.
900 calories of seafood pie and dense wine.
My favorite chicken and beer
has 1,522 calories.
I can have nothing.
Wait a second.
Since I have my appendix out,
I should have lost some weight.
You’d better stop talking nonsense and go sleep.
Will you leave after I fall asleep?
People now know you are my manager.
They will doubt if you leave.
I mean…
I won’t leave.
What’s your constellation?
Aquarius. Why?
Will you take a boat recently?
Boat?
It’s not suitable for Aquarius to get on a boat.
You’d be careful of water.
Really?
I don’t believe that.
Better safe than sorry.
Am I right?
[Patient: Cheon Song-yi
Doctor: Park Jeong-min
Seong-min University Hospital]
No entry for externals.
I’m not an external.
How to explain?
Please keep it a secret.
I am Cheon Song-yi’s boyfriend.
No.
Then I will prove it to you.
The subscriber you dial is power off.
Power off?
I’m really her boyfriend.
There are a dozen people
called themselves a boyfriend this morning.
I’m different from them.
Where is Cheon Song-yi’s manager?
He knows me.
Here he is.
This said he’s Cheon Song-yi’s boyfriend.
Really?
Why are you here?
He isn’t the manager.
Of course he is.
He is the one took Cheon Song-yi to the hospital
and stayed overnight.
What? Overnight?
Overnight?
What should we do?
The patient needs to rest absolutely quietly.
-Nobody is allowed to enter.
-Yes.
Hey. Hey you!
Cheon Song-yi and you are known as friends.
It’s said it started from junior high school.
Yes. We were always together in high school.
We met in everywhere,
so we became friends.
It’s said she had the appendicitis surgery.
Will you go for a visit?
I will see her after this interview.
Next question. When Cheon Song-yi was a student…
-Miss.
-Yes?
-Don’t you have any questions about me?
-I…
Of course we have.
Miss Se-mi, do you have a boyfriend?
I’ve carried a torch for him for a dozen years.
So many lines. It looks boring.
It’s about Jang Hui-bin’s childhood.
Yours is better.
Not many lines.
Not to fall into the water in such a cold day.
Lee Hee-kyung is coming. Oh my god!
He’s really handsome.
Hey, Cheon Song-yi.
You know me, right?
I’m Lee Hee-kyung.
I don’t know you.
You took the chocolate AD,
then became popular and got a play, right?
My dad is the chairman of the company.
So?
I’m not here to show off.
But I’m the one who asked my dad
to invite you to film the AD.
You are here to thank me?
Why should I thank you?
As the model,
I help you sell the chocolate well.
So you are here to show your appreciation?
I’m here…
-I don’t mean that.
-Forget it.
I have no time on you.
-What is she doing?
-Why is she so arrogant?
Hey, Cheon Song-yi.
You can’t be so popular without me.
My dad was unwilling but I persuaded him.
I didn’t ask you to do that.
He’s never really looked at me.
I don’t understand why I was attracted by him.
-No.
-I’ve said many times
that I’m Cheon Song-yi’s boyfriend.
-Yes, I see.
-Yes, right.
Hee-kyung.
Hey.
You could call me since Beom can’t come.
Why did you ask him to come?
He would come to this hospital for something.
But it’s two a.m.
He had something to do.
It must be a trick.
He is a stalker, right?
Think it over.
He lives next door and is your professor.
Seoul is so big.
He must come for you on purpose.
Stop making up stories.
It’s me who moved to his next door.
It’s me who applied for the class.
How about I move to your next door?
Is his house bought or rented?
Se-mi.
Take Hee-kyung home.
Yes, let Song-yi take a rest. Let’s go.
Leave yourself.
I will stay and sleep here.
Stop.
It’s dangerous here.
You are the most dangerous one.
Have you called your mom?
Maybe I should wash my hair so as to
keep good in the cameras on the way back.
She may worry you.
Please give me the newspaper.
I will read the horoscope for you.
Horoscope?
Where is it?
I’m Aquarius.
It reads that I should be careful of water
and not to take a boat.
What’s it?
It’s not here.
What did he do?
There is no horoscope here.
I made up story about horoscope
and warned her against water.
Is it useful?
She would never listen to others.
So will you let it be?
I’ve did all that I can.
Getting involved more is improper.
Then why did you call me here?
What?
To be honest,
I also have my life and work.
But you just called me like this.
You said you would never get involved,
then do it.
Why are you mentioning it again?
Actually you care very much.
You thought I was hard to deal with.
Now you say I’m calling you at will.
It’s OK since we are friends of 30 years.
Remember,
we look like father and son.
Anyway, I feel at ease in my mind.
What?
You completely forget the respect of seniority.
I’ve seen a lot of changes in this world.
Is your beeper ringing?
Should I be the only one
who knows your beeper number?
It’s the first time I meet
your beeper rings.
Call her.
Professor Do Min-joon.
What a surprise!
You really use a beeper?
This is Cheon Song-yi.
How did you get my beeper number?
You left it as the contact of my guardian.
What’s wrong?
Nothing. I’m just asking for the horoscope.
I cannot find it on the newspaper.
It’s there.
You called me for this?
Request?
I’ve agreed all your requests I can.
You think I will agree with this request?
What is your plan for tomorrow?
It’s cold.
I want to go for sauna.
-It’s a pity.
-What’s wrong?
I’d invite you to my house
and play table tennis with Tiger.
Jobs came to my house yesterday.
If something wrong with the computer,
let the one who made it repair it.
Jobs is deceased, okay?
No kimchi?
The instant noodles only takes 800,
so I can’t offer you kimchi of 1,000 for free.
You are going too far.
-You are so mean.
-You can just leave.
Thank you.
Welcome.
May I help you?
I’m here to borrow some books.
Okay. Good.
What kind of books?
Deacon for A Single Room.
Brilliant Seduction from the Man Next Door.
Staying in the Office with Tactful Superior.
Love Contract with the Potent Man.
Oh my.
Why?
What’s wrong?
Deacon for A Single Room.
Does a single room need a deacon?
Why not to get a two-room with the money?
Of course it’s not a single room.
Please use your imagination.
Staying in the office with tactful superior?
Is it worthy of imagining?
Listen.
The books are for my life.
Don’t humiliate them.
You have a higher taste?
Books for my life is
Goo Eun Mong.
What?
Isn’t it a book of the Joseon Dynasty?
You are really old-fashioned.
You think old books are old-fashioned?
Goo Eun Mong, a new fantasy book in Joseon.
It’s 400 years earlier than but as good as
Harry Potter.
Kid,
I’ve been curious all the time.
Which year were you born in?
Hey. Naughty boy.
Where have you been for all these days?
What’s wrong with her?
The “her” is your elder sister.
All in all, let’s get in quickly.
Wait a moment.
Mr. An.
Here.
Hello.
Madam.
Director and workers of Song-yi Special.
Thank you for your hard working.
I’m Song-yi’s mother.
This is his younger brother Cheon Yun-jae.
Cheon Song-yi is as beautiful as mother.
Thank you so much.
However,
we don’t use a reflector?
What?
Is this the only thing for lighting?
Oh, yes.
I believe you are clear
about today’s arrangement.
You haven’t met each other for a long time.
You came once hearing of the surgery.
It’s about different concepts of family.
Mr. An.
Good idea.
Let’s begin from the moment I get off the taxi
when I’m crying.
I’m good at acting crying.
Good idea.
Right?
Call a taxi first.
Get me out of the camera before I destroy it.
Okay?
That bast…
You know the senior year syndrome?
I’ve heard of it before.
Even the alien would be afraid of it,
so they give up the invasion of the earth.
Madam,
it’s about concept of family.
Let’s film me at first.
I will try my best to show the uniqueness.
Okay.
To be honest, I’m better than Song-yi in acting.
Cheon Yun-jae.
You are still alive?
So,
why didn’t you pick up my phone.
Mom said you often ran away from home.
Don’t talk.
It’s good to see you are alive.
Hey.
We haven’t met for one year. You just leave?
-Come here. I will give you some money.
-Forget it.
I can support myself by working.
You are not allowed to work.
Why don’t you behave well in studying?
You know?
I ran away from home
because I don’t want to use your money.
Can you
stop talking to me like that?
stop sending money home?
The family became like this for the money.
If it weren’t for you,
dad wouldn’t become like that.
-Hey, Cheon Yun-jae!
-Song-yi.
My daughter.
What’s wrong with you?
I’m coming.
Oh. My son.
He is so sad to heard his sister is  ill.
They love each other so much.
Hey.
Over there.
Song-yi.
Please stop!
Get out. Mom!
Everyone, please get out.
What a bad girl!
She has such a bad temper.
As beautiful as me, but not the good temper.
You are right.
Mrs. Cheon.
The contract will expire next month.
Will you renew it?
You are always the one who signs it.
I’m not sure.
Je-guk and Panton called me many times.
Song-yi has worked for you when she was a child.
Maybe she can make some change now.
Why bother?
It’s good to stay.
There is a saying goes
“Friends are old and good.”
Mr. An.
For me,
I like the new ones.
Mrs. Cheon,
it’s been a long time. Let’s go shopping.
There are many new things.
It’s said Cheon Song-yi is in this hospital.
Really? What’s wrong?
My daughter.
Dad.
Come here.
It’s cold. Why don’t you wait at home?
Did you buy it?
Of course.
Chicken eater.
It’s real.
Snowing day
should have chicken and beer.
You are a little kid.
You can’t drink beer.
Only cola.
Okay. I see.
Drink beer with me when you are grown up.
What’s going on?
[Director: Hwang Ui-gyeong]
Hello?
Director.
Can you come to my office?
Yes. I’ll be there soon.
What?
What’s wrong with Director Hwang?
It’s a sudden death of hypoglycemia
because of excessive injection of insulin.
What’s wrong?
Why did that happened?
He didn’t have diabetes for the first day.
He isn’t the person who will make that mistake.
Call Secretary Zhang for me.
Let’s go to the mourning hall.
Yes.
A bit weak and weary-looking
but not looking down.
Yes.
Take a look.
Is it too obvious?
Make it like the feeling of just getting up.
Unruly with sexy beauty.
A bit soft.
I’d re-blow it.
Song-yi, the shoes are missing.
Why?
I wore them to the hospital.
Your stuff were taken away by Professor Do.
Only the shoes are missing.
The shoes
are yours?
I can’t believe he’s that kind of person.
Love is the slave of sexual pleasure.
Love is the sweet fantasy getting from sex.
You may think if love is forever.
I’m sure it’s not.
Expiration date of love is ruled by nature.
Human will never go beyond the limit.
Why love is great?
It’s only because
it keeps the species going.
So, please don’t exchange
your most precious thing
for the short fantasy.
I’ve told you not to call me frequently.
Let me make it clearer.
Please delete my number.
Tell me.
What?
Are you jealous?
Shoes?
I have no idea.
My shoes are missing, but other things are there.
Helping you once means nothing.
I really don’t know.
Will you insist?
Actually, I appreciate your help.
But how can you steal my shoes?
I thought you were a good person.
But you cheat me.
I don’t understand.
The shoes for women are useless for you
I didn’t take it.
It’s said Hee-kyung is still chasing Song-yi.
Can you stop him?
Why?
What?
If I marry you and Song-yi marry him,
we two become sisters-in-law.
But I hate her.
Will I marry you?
Won’t you?
We’ve dated for one year.
People don’t know because we dated secretly.
It seems Dispatch doesn’t work hard recently.
They even give up such big news.
So you want everyone to know?
So you don’t want to get married?
Then break up.
Marry me if you don’t want to break up.
Is it for the sake of your ex-wife?
I’m different from her.
You know it.
And
I will never tell others about what I know.
I received Lo Soo-yeong’s wedding invitation.
Is the second son of L Group your friend?
Yes.
So you received the invitation, too?
Let’s go together.
Okay.
Go together.
You are suffered a lot from the surgery.
You are thinner and more beautiful.
Really?
I always become more beautiful during a wedding
and was scolded as a contrast.
Really?
Do I need to make you not that beautiful?
Going the wedding like this
I will be a contrast to the bride.
Why does Lo Soo-yeong
hold the wedding on the cruise?
People have to wear evening dress in a cold day.
It’s said to maintain secret.
Some people get in secretly
even in special hotel.
Get the shoes?
Yes.
They don’t have your size.
This is the only one
urgently carried from other places.
There is no way.
The proper ones are missing.
Give me the phone.
Okay.
Here.
Press one for calling. Press two for message.
Professor Do.
This is Cheon Song-yi.
I bought a new pair of the shoes
at a large sum of money.
I owed you last time.
So I will let it go.
I will apologize to you when there is a chance.
But I don’t know why you took away the shoes.
Over.
You.
I told you not to appear in front of me.
I told you I don’t.
What’s more, we will meet at the wedding.
Kindly remind you not to come tonight.
What’s wrong?
You dressed up but only my photos in the news?
You’ve made great efforts.
So you should be confident.
Hey.
By the way,
I received the scripts from Director Ma.
It’s said you wanted to get it so much.
But I don’t want to miss it,
so I accepted it at a lower price.
It seems I have to enter Cannes to avoid you.
You bad girl!
I will kill you.
This is Cheon Song-yi.
I bought a new pair of the shoes
at a large sum of money.
I owed you last time.
So I will let it go.
I will apologize to you when there is a chance.
But I don’t know why you took away the shoes.
[Wedding of the Century]
It’s the wedding
of actress Lo Soo-yeong
and Jang Jun-yeong, son of Jang Hae-cheol.
Being well guarded,
many tycoons and stars are entering.
Do you see the media?
Now, actress Cheon Song-yi is arriving.
This way.
[All the stars participate in.]
[Non-public Wedding with Only Dignitaries]
Why don’t I trust love?
Absolutely trust.
In the past,
many people trusted love above the station.
They risked their lives and eloped,
but it ended within three years
because the man with lower grade played women.
Make a proposal?
Sing a song for me
and kneel down.
The woman asks for kneeling down and singing
for proposal is childish.
Being childish is what I need.
That’s love.
Love will never overcome time.
Love can overcome everything.
I will meet it soon.
I will marry after I meet it.
I’m at the age of getting married.
-=Next=-
She wore the shoes to the boat at last?
If something really happens,
you sure you’ll let it be?
Song-yi is missing.
It’s unbelievable.
Cheon Song-yi was missing with the man.
I really saw something weird.
Did you go there that day?