♪Where does the moon shine
in the dream of ages♪
♪Grudges endure the longest along the way♪
♪The anger in blades' shadows♪
♪Wild youth in bright clothes♪
♪Intoxicated in the moment♪
♪May I tread skies, cross seas♪
♪Gallop with wings at dawn♪
♪My heart for the sword never withers
despite the fire♪
♪Every move challenging the heavens♪
♪Luckily, there are a few true friends♪
♪With hearts bound♪
♪Drinking, the autumn moon never ages♪
♪Let us roam freely together♪
=Blade's Dance with You=
=Episode 14=
All the people in the villa are unreliable now.
Dismiss them all.
Yes.
I'll handle it right away.
Wait.
After this,
take some money
and go home
to enjoy your old age.
Mr. Mo.
Thank you
for all these years.
Go ahead.
Thank you
for your care all these years.
The villa guards are being replaced.
So what?
We're leaving today anyway.
Where's Xiaoren?
Last night, she said she wanted to say goodbye
to Jun Mo and didn't come back.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
Isn't it normal?
They like each other.
Maybe they've reconciled by now.
Impossible.
She said she'd leave this time.
Don't be silly.
When a woman really loves a man,
it's hard to let go.
No matter what you do,
she won't feel it.
But
she promised.
The three of us
would travel the world
and fight injustice together.
Actually,
I have to part with you too.
Why?
Because she
did something against you.
Mo Wei.
Zhao Xiaoren spared you,
but we won't be nice to you.
Really?
Did you tell Zhao Xiaoren
that your father
is Zuo Feng?
Xiachan,
what does he mean?
So you found out.
Your father
framed Zhao Xiaoren's father.
How did my father frame him?
They're all dead.
Who knows if Zhao Li
colluded with the enemy?
I know.
I know everything.
Then tell us the truth.
Alright.
But first, tell me
the real reason
the Empress sent you here.
Nonsense.
We weren't sent by the Empress.
Getting old.
My movements
are slow now.
You're awake.
You're here.
Hungry?
I made you glutinous rice balls.
Silly.
How could you give me
your meager inner strength?
Do you know
you almost died?
I won't die.
From now on, I want to eat
these delicious rice balls every day.
I'll find out
what happened to Master
and clear his name.
But
that means
you'll face the Emperor,
Empress, and Crown Prince.
I didn't fight
before because I didn't want
to involve more innocent people.
I know the pain
of losing family.
Besides, Master left me,
and you weren't by my side.
My only reason to live
was to find you.
What about now?
Now,
I understand
only by taking the initiative
can more people live in peace.
And...
What else?
Now I live for you.
Alright.
Then from now on,
I live for you too.
Now eat.
Rest well after you finish.
I need to go out for a bit.
You can't go.
Wherever you go,
take me with you.
I need to interrogate Zuo Xiachan and Li Wei.
Do you think
they poisoned you?
They are the least suspicious,
but I need to confirm their identities.
Identities?
What do you mean?
Tell me.
Zuo Xiachan's father is Zuo Feng.
Li Wei's father
also died 16 years ago.
Zuo Xiachan.
Zuo Feng.
Yao,
I don't want you to go.
No.
I must go.
Zuo Xiachan,
stop pretending.
The needle is still in your mouth, right?
I didn't expect it to be you
to come here.
I didn't expect you
to be Zuo Feng's daughter.
Want to avenge your father?
Then kill me.
Spit it out.
Come on, kill me.
Jun Mo said
you work for the Emperor
or the Empress.
Nonsense!
Zhao Xiaoren,
don't let Jun Mo
frame me.
Kill me if you want,
but don't insult me.
Don't overthink it.
It's because you and Li Wei
stole my father's notes.
I stole them.
It has nothing to do with Li Wei.
Who ordered you?
The Chief.
So, you said
you came to rescue me
and killed for me.
Was it all fake?
No.
If Li Wei wasn't injured,
it would have been his mission.
I found Li Wei after I got the mission
and asked him for help.
In return,
I had to protect you from the assassins.
I feel like you're lying to me.
Why would I lie?
After my father was killed,
my mother drowned herself,
and I was sold to a brothel.
Do you know what that place is like?
Your Highness,
all the guards in the villa
have been replaced
with soldiers from the border.
From now on,
there won't be any problems.
A few pages are missing from here.
It's alright.
I've seen it.
Those pages
recorded Zuo Feng's
corruption.
Zuo Xiachan probably
tore them out
to hide her identity.
Do you think they poisoned me?
It's hard to say.
The guards in the villa
didn't react
to the assassination attempt.
There might be drugs
in their food.
The assassins
were long-time servants in the villa.
They
must have been planted
years ago
by the Empress
or the Crown Prince.
Their actions
were coordinated,
so someone was directing them.
This is over now.
In the future,
if you want,
the army will enter the city.
Half of the officials
in the court
support you.
Don't act rashly.
I don't want a river of blood
unless absolutely necessary.
Seize the moment, Your Highness.
Enough.
Got it.
I mentioned the brothel
and you felt sorry for me.
What if I'm lying?
Jun Mo said
if you had no reaction
when I mentioned him,
then you aren't the one who poisoned him.
He's poisoned?
When?
None of your concerns.
He's my husband.
Such a possessive dog.
That's because this bone
is too tempting.
Some vixen
won't leave him alone.
Come on.
Where's Li Wei?
I was about to see him.
Do you want to come?
He's not working
for the Empress or the Emperor.
He's too naive.
With a friend like you,
he can still be like this.
It's really not easy.
Mo Wei's martial arts are very good.
I'm no match for him at all.
You must be careful of him.
Though he only killed my father under orders,
I will never forgive him.
After this is over,
I will seek him out for a life-and-death duel.
♪Drifting back through the snow♪
♪Dreams end, seeking the unseen mountain♪
♪Slowly walking away♪
♪Dust and frost cover your eyes♪
♪Cold plum blossoms blaze like fire♪
♪Farewells etched in glances♪
♪We can't have what we want♪
♪Stop missing♪
♪That sword strike♪
♪Lovers are far apart♪
♪With dreams unfulfilled♪
♪Thoughts of you, how to let go♪
♪Your eyes unchanged♪
♪Yet you're beyond reach, amidst clouds♪
♪Only the sword's edge leaves the story blank♪
♪The heart's chessboard♪
♪No one to play against♪
♪Only regrets remain♪
♪It's not about winning or losing♪
♪Promises waiting for someone to hear♪
♪Mountains and seas unseen♪
♪Moonlit nights unremembered♪
♪Only regret cannot be measured in years♪
♪We were once so close♪
♪Countless meetings♪
♪Like seeing you anew♪
♪A meeting agreed upon, yet also a parting♪
♪Drifting snow refuses to return♪
♪Better to step into a spring♪
♪With you♪