♪Where does the moon shine
in the dream of ages♪
♪Grudges endure the longest along the way♪
♪The anger in blades' shadows♪
♪Wild youth in bright clothes♪
♪Intoxicated in the moment♪
♪May I tread skies, cross seas♪
♪Gallop with wings at dawn♪
♪My heart for the sword never withers
despite the fire♪
♪Every move challenging the heavens♪
♪Luckily, there are a few true friends♪
♪With hearts bound♪
♪Drinking, the autumn moon never ages♪
♪Let us roam freely together♪
=Blade's Dance with You=
=Episode 24=
Li Wei, when will you visit me again?
Whenever I have time,
I'll come to see you.
It's this answer again.
My Lady,
please teach me
how to stay young
forever.
Zuo Xiachan, what are you doing?
Poison Queen
is already 68 years old.
Master, please accept me.
Do you think I did wrong?
If it was for me,
then it's a big mistake.
If not,
then you're foolish enough to believe
that a person who stops at nothing
to achieve their goals
can ensure peace for the people.
I think she can.
A blood-stained bun
can indeed fill the stomach,
but would you eat a bun stained
with your parents' blood?
Zhao Li.
After my death,
did the border wars cease?
Yes, yes. They ceased.
Then I can rest in peace.
Your Majesty, you had another nightmare.
Are you a human or a ghost?
Do you wish for my death so badly?
Jun Mo, are you alright?
Crown Princess, are you unharmed?
Acted all your life,
you can't stop acting now.
Ministry of Rites.
Here.
I want a decree drafted
to pass the throne to Crown Prince Jun Mo.
Yes.
Father,
you're not passing the throne to me
but to the Empress.
Impossible, absolutely impossible.
Letting you draft the decree
is to give you a chance to survive.
Otherwise, you'd be dead now.
I...
I've been weak and useless all my life,
always controlled by others.
At this point,
I will never pass the throne
to a woman.
How can I face
my ancestors?
- Jun Mo, protect me.
- Your Majesty.
I'll pass the throne to you.
Enough.
You want to go back on your word?
I'll help you fulfill that wish.
Put on this royal robe,
and you'll be the new ruler of this world.
(Funing Hall)
The weather is so nice today.
What did the Poison Queen give you?
Why is it more effective than mine?
I didn't use anything
from the Poison Queen.
I'm going to buy a roast suckling pig.
Going to see the Poison Queen,
I'm leaving now.
Looks like I need to find a partner too.
Wait. I'll go with you.
I want to get something from the Poison Queen.
The Empress seems foolish.
Not using inner strength
means she wouldn't die.
Did you know earlier
the Empress didn't want to live?
From the moment she said
she wanted me to help her ascend the throne,
I knew.
Why?
The Empress values power the most.
What keeps her going
is power.
But all her close relatives are dead.
So she knows
even if she can secretly control the court,
she can never sit on the throne.
So,
the Empress was asking you
to help fulfill her final wish.
Now that the Empress is dead,
what do you plan to do?
You know the answer.
Am I to become the new Empress?
Being the Empress isn't that easy.
It'll be easy for me.
Why?
Because I'll be the only one
in the harem.
If you dare marry again,
I'll kill them all.
Then I have to reconsider
being the Emperor.
I want to return to Jasmine Villa.
I still want to experience being an Empress.
♪Drifting back through the snow♪
♪Dreams end, seeking the unseen mountain♪
♪Slowly walking away♪
♪Dust and frost cover your eyes♪
After putting on the royal robe
and wearing the imperial crown,
your body
won't be yours anymore.
♪We can't have what we want♪
What are you going to do as the Emperor?
Observe the lives of the people,
uphold the law,
and eradicate treachery.
I understood that sentence,
but what if you're too busy
handling state affairs in the future
and have no time for me?
To one doth pledge with true heart,
I shall be generous with everything to thou.
I didn't quite understand that one.
♪Promises waiting for someone to hear♪
In this lifetime,
I will only love you.
♪You walk barefoot in the wilderness
before our meeting♪
♪The word love hangs in my heart♪
♪This one glance outshines everything♪
♪The spring wind should be envious of me♪
Let's go.
As your husband, I need to govern the country.
♪Who folded the kite♪
♪Falling into the abyss with the wind♪
♪Innocent youth♪
♪Fulfillment in dreams, yet still lacking♪
♪Lovers are far apart with dreams unfulfilled♪
♪Thoughts of you, how to let go♪
♪Your eyes unchanged,
yet you're beyond reach, amidst clouds♪
♪Only the sword's edge leaves the story blank♪
♪The heart's chessboard,
no one to play against♪
♪Only regrets remain♪
♪It's not about winning or losing♪
♪Promises waiting for someone to hear♪
♪Mountains and seas unseen,
moonlit nights unremembered♪
♪Only regret cannot be measured in years♪
♪We were once so close, countless meetings♪
♪Like seeing you anew♪
♪A meeting agreed upon, yet also a parting♪
♪Drifting snow refuses to return♪
♪Better to step into a spring♪
♪With you♪
♪Lovers are far apart♪
♪With dreams unfulfilled♪
♪Thoughts of you, how to let go♪
♪Your eyes unchanged♪
♪Yet you're beyond reach, amidst clouds♪
♪Only the sword's edge leaves the story blank♪
♪The heart's chessboard♪
♪No one to play against♪
♪Only regrets remain♪
♪It's not about winning or losing♪
♪Promises waiting for someone to hear♪
♪Mountains and seas unseen♪
♪Moonlit nights unremembered♪
♪Only regret cannot be measured in years♪
♪We were once so close♪
♪Countless meetings♪
♪Like seeing you anew♪
♪A meeting agreed upon, yet also a parting♪
♪Drifting snow refuses to return♪