♪Where does the moon shine
in the dream of ages♪
♪Grudges endure the longest along the way♪
♪The anger in blades' shadows♪
♪Wild youth in bright clothes♪
♪Intoxicated in the moment♪
♪May I tread skies, cross seas♪
♪Gallop with wings at dawn♪
♪My heart for the sword never withers
despite the fire♪
♪Every move challenging the heavens♪
♪Luckily, there are a few true friends♪
♪With hearts bound♪
♪Drinking, the autumn moon never ages♪
♪Let us roam freely together♪
=Blade's Dance with You=
Don't move.
Father.
Master.
Master, please stop.
If you continue,
many people will die.
Father,
I will definitely avenge you.
Master.
Don't come over.
Yao.
Yao died
sixteen years ago.
=Episode 1=
(Ten days ago, Bamboo Forest,
Outskirts of the Capital)
(General Chain from Twelve Generals)
(Zhao Xiaoren, Earth Killer from Flash Sect)
Where are the other two people?
I won't say anything.
Then don't speak.
(Father,)
(I will soon send these two down)
(to see you.)
So cute.
What a pity.
Come here. Come.
(Serene)
The winding path, misty marshes.
Step by step ascending gracefully.
In dreams, there should be
smiles as radiant as flowers.
Bright eyes and beautiful brows.
Good.
Bring another pot.
You're still in the mood to recite poetry.
Aren't you going
to marry the ugliest woman
in the entire capital city
and spend your wedding night with her?
If it were me, I definitely couldn't stand it.
But it doesn't matter.
Today, I specially brought
the top courtesan Fuxiang to serve you
to please you before your marriage.
My Lord,
how can such a joyful day
be celebrated with a cup?
Let's use a pot instead.
You can't.
You just arrived here.
If you finish a whole pot now,
I'll have to carry you home.
Let go.
No.
Bravo.
Impressive.
Great.
What's going on here?
Someone's been killed.
(Aside from Flash Sect,)
(someone else wants to kill him.)
(How many bad things has he done?)
What's this all about?
They were just decoys.
You're the real killer.
They're not worthy of teaming up with me.
Still defiant.
Let me see who you are.
This way,
you can't use hidden weapons anymore.
Shameless.
Surviving
isn't shameful.
Then don't blame me.
- What are you doing?
- Let me go!
Or I'll bite your ear off.
How dare you?
Try me.
Count to three. Let's let go together.
- One, two, three.
(Father's jade pendant.)
Why didn't you
catch her?
Let's go home.
Why is your ear so red?
Wait for me.
(Jasmine Villa)
(Three days later)
All the guests have left.
Stop standing here.
It's time to enter the bridal chamber.
Right.
Whether
the bride
is beautiful or ugly,
just
put this on.
Get lost.
Yes, My Lord.
It's getting late.
You should rest.
You can't
stand here all night.
I'm waiting for someone.
It's so late.
No one will come.
He's already arrived.
Jun Mo.
Congratulations.
On this auspicious day,
let me join the celebration.
Thank you.
Where's the bride?
Let me see her.
Your Highness,
today is Mr. Jun Mo's big day.
Disturbing the bride
would be against the etiquette.
Who are you to stop me?
Get lost.
It's okay.
This ceremony
was all prepared by my brother.
You're reasonable.
Did you hear?
Lu Zuo's daughter
is naturally extremely ugly.
She's over twenty years old now
and no one dares to propose to her.
Unexpectedly,
you're in luck.
My dad said,
"An ugly wife is a treasure at home."
My mom is ugly.
What's your name?
Zhu Dabao.
Zhu Dabao?
Indeed a pig.
Want to get promoted and rich?
- Yes.
- Yes?
Guards,
castrate this fat pig
and send him to the palace to serve me.
- Jun Mo.
- Your Highness.
Didn't you want to see the bride?
Let's go.
Consider yourself spared this time.
Next time you dare to interrupt,
I'll castrate your entire family.
(Happy)
Jun Mo,
she's a criminal's daughter.
Now that you've married her,
behave yourself
and stay here for the rest of your life.
It should be so.
You've always been like this.
I can't tell if you're angry or happy.
Good.
Then look at her.
See if you can smile or not.
♪Drifting back through the snow♪
♪Dreams end, seeking the unseen mountain♪
♪Slowly walking away♪
♪Dust and frost cover your eyes♪
♪Cold plum blossoms blaze like fire♪
♪Farewells etched in glances♪
♪We can't have what we want♪
♪Stop missing♪
♪That sword strike♪
♪Lovers are far apart♪
♪With dreams unfulfilled♪
♪Thoughts of you, how to let go♪
♪Your eyes unchanged♪
♪Yet you're beyond reach, amidst clouds♪
♪Only the sword's edge leaves the story blank♪
♪The heart's chessboard♪
♪No one to play against♪
♪Only regrets remain♪
♪It's not about winning or losing♪
♪Promises waiting for someone to hear♪
♪Mountains and seas unseen♪
♪Moonlit nights unremembered♪
♪Only regret cannot be measured in years♪
♪We were once so close♪
♪Countless meetings♪
♪Like seeing you anew♪
♪A meeting agreed upon, yet also a parting♪
♪Drifting snow refuses to return♪
♪Better to step into a spring♪
♪With you♪