Little ones,
Wow.
You’re here.
Here.
Save one more for me.
It’s so cool.
Wow, it’s huge.
What a big boat.
It’s so big.
A Lai said,
Aunt Gui calls you the Five Tigers.
The Five Tigers.
We also heard about your brother.
Brother.
We made it.
After we finish with Tang Cheng and get the gold,
good days will come.
Xiao Jiang said,
once we have the gold,
we can live a good life.
We got the gold,
but lost the people.
You police,
searching everywhere for the truth every day.
Where is the truth?
This is the truth.
There is a truth.
The truth we police have found is
you are all victims.
Give it to me after you pick it up.
Come on, come on, come on.
Pick up anything you find.
Alright, let's go.
Mom.
Look.
I found a bag.
Such a big basin.
I picked up a bag.
That's great.
Really great.
Scrap.
Coming.
-Come here. -Time for buns!
Time for buns!
Buns.
Want to eat?
Yes.
Of course I do.
Who wouldn't?
Do you have money?
No.
You can trade things for it.
Really?
Here.
Mm.
This one.
Trade for a meat one.
Come.
Here.
This one.
Trade for a vegetarian one.
Is this okay?
This one.
It can't even be traded for a bun.
Can anything be traded?
Of course.
If it's a thing, it has a price.
I don't understand.
What I mean is,
as long as you have the guts,
there's nothing you can't trade for.
If you come empty-handed,
then you'll just go hungry.
Then,
do I have a price?
Everyone has a price.
I'm not some victim.
You killed Yang Dong.
Yes.
Brother Hai.
Since we've started,
don't stop.
Definitely don't
let them go.
Brother.
Come on.
Finish me off.
Fourth Brother.
You go first.
You killed Liu Kui too.
It was me.
Xu Honglai and Zhang Guiping were your targets too.
If you had come a few minutes later,
I would have succeeded.
If we had come a few minutes later,
what about Xiao Gu?
Can you protect her?
She's my daughter.
Do you want your daughter to end up like you?
She's not like me.
She will have a lot.
A lot.
You have a lot too.
Luo Haixiao.
Even though you are orphans,
that is not an excuse for your crimes.
You can see your daughter.
Why don't you cherish it?
Why?
Dad, Dad, my gorilla is missing!
It must have gone out to play again.
Please help me find it quickly.
Does it still hurt?
Yeah.
It won't hurt for much longer.
I've made a lot of mistakes in my life.
Dad is a bad person.
You're different.
You should be a good person.
Remember that.
Are you sleepy?
Yeah, I am.
Go to sleep.
Then I'll really sleep.
Go ahead and sleep.