Every time one is born, one dies.
You're a jinx.
Do you know that?
You bring misfortune only to our family.
Why don't you just die?
What's the point of you being alive?
My grandson!
Heavens!
Why did you take my grandson away?
Take this woman away.
Take this jinx away.
Please, take this jinx away quickly.
I'm begging you, heavens.
I'm begging you.
Take her away.
Take this jinx away.
Heavens!
Heavens, I'm begging you.
Sorry.
Looking for a nanny, looking for a nanny.
Looking for a nanny.
Miss, do you want to be a nanny?
Just help take care of a child.
Just one child.
Why not give it a try?
Is Xiao Hai dead?
Yes, dead.
In the end,
I couldn't keep a single one.
Human trafficking.
Home invasion robbery.
Organizing and leading a criminal gang.
Inciting minors to commit crimes.
Intentional injury.
Premeditated murder.
Zhang Guiping.
You're the best actor I've ever seen among suspects.
Enough.
Start from the first child you abducted.
I got married at eighteen.
I had two children.
One lived for forty days.
The other died right after birth.
A fortune teller said my fate was too strong.
My life was too tough.
I had to bring in a child from outside to raise one successfully.
Only then could I suppress my fate.
So I went and took one.
What year was that?
1982.
The first time I worked as a nanny,
I took A-Lai away.
This baby is so cute.
What's the baby's name?
His name is A-Lai.
A-Lai, A-Lai.
Later, I raised four of them.
A-Kui.
Xiao Hai.
Xiao Jiang.
And Dongzi.
My five tigers.
I can't understand, I just can't.
Come, give it to me.
Go play.
Help!
A Kui
Open it and take a look.
This is what you got in exchange today.
That lady
When she got up and ran
She kept crying and screaming.
Very
scary.
Don't worry.
No one will know it was you.
That lady
won't know who you are either.
Tomorrow, you all go together.
Remember this,
no one is smarter than you.
You'll understand once you have the skills.
In this world,
there's nothing
you can't get.
Got it.
How did you forge their identities?
Twenty years ago,
at the county health clinic,
there was a nurse named Li Xia.
At that time,
I paid some money
and bought birth certificates from her.
But later, she died of cancer.
I never went back after that.
You also planned for Dai Qi to kidnap Li You, didn't you?
Yes.
I hinted to her
to kidnap Li You
so she could take revenge for Wang Ziyan.
This young man is pretty good.
That's rare.
Someone like me, I've only ever been a nanny my whole life.
But I'm a woman too.
That year,
when my husband passed away,
it really felt like the sky was falling.
Just think about it,
who could have killed him?
Li You
That's right.
Let him taste the pain too.
Wouldn't you feel much better then?
To be honest, about this matter...
If that's the case,
you caught Dai Qi,
and I took Mu Mu away.
Wouldn't that be much more convenient?
If I hadn't gone to the station today,
how could you possibly have caught me?
Zhang Guiping
On the day the task force was formed,
you were destined to be caught.
Speak.
How many people did you abduct in total?
A dozen or so.
I can't remember exactly.
Those under three were sold.
The older ones
were kept by my side to work for me.
Tang Cheng's gold
was also stolen by you, right?
I worked at the villa for half a year before.
I knew.
That gold
wasn't clean anyway.
Giving it to them
wasn't as good as giving it to my kids.
We can't make a big scene.
After entering the house,
one person controls Tang Cheng and the bodyguard,
the other opens the safe.
Who will go?
Draw lots.
We made it, brother.
I'll go with you.
You ordered Huang Jiang and Luo Haixiao to commit the robbery.
Then you wanted to kill them to silence them.
Is that right?
Are we lost?
Where is this place?
Once we cross this mountain,
we'll reach Wusu.
Trust me.
Let's go.
What's wrong?
Mom.
You are all my children.
What my children are thinking,
would I not know?
Go ahead, say it.
Why are you leaving me?
Is it because of Su Yun, that mute girl?
Mom.
This has nothing to do with Xiao Jiang.
It was my decision.
It was all my idea.
I'm sorry, Mom.
I'm sorry.
Since you want to leave,
then go ahead.
I'll watch you leave.
A Kui.
Mom.
Give us a chance.
Xiao Jiang.
I am their mother.
They're the ones who don't listen.
Then they're not your children.
Yes.
They never were.
They are.
If it weren't for me,
they would have died long ago.
Zhang Guiping.
In your whole life,
you've never saved anyone.
Every crime you've committed,
every injustice suffered by your victims,
the law will hold you accountable for all of them.
Nothing will be overlooked.
This child.
Have you seen them?
I don't know them.
Did you look carefully?
Look again.
I said I don't know them.
Look at this photo.
I'll ask you again.
In 2005,
on May 6th,
in the afternoon,
at the Qing family compound,
this ten-year-old child,
this child,
is yours.
Have you seen them?