Hurry up, hurry up!
Put some effort into it.
Didn't you eat enough?
All of you, put some effort into it.
My stomach hurts.
Hurry up, hurry up.
Okay.
Don't cry, don't cry, don't cry.
What is this?
Didn't you say you didn't know her?
What did you do to them?
You took the gold.
And you even hit me.
How should we settle this?
Let them go.
Otherwise, you'll never see the gold.
Take your filthy hands off.
Second Brother,
The five of us brothers,
Big Brother, Little Jiang,
Dongzi,
are all gone.
Only the two of us are left.
Can the two of us
still be good brothers?
Let's get the gold back.
Mom will give it to you.
Mom.
You still can't wean off your mom?
You all act so tough.
But I only have Mom.
Let me tell you,
where the gold is.
Where is it?
Come here.
I'll go.
Let them go.
Then you might still get to see the gold.
Little girl
That mute aunt of yours
I've already sent her back
Do you want to go back?
Dad
He still hasn't said where the gold is
Let's have a talk, just the two of us
What are your terms?
Mom
How would I know where your mom is?
Weren't you picked up from the mine?
Your mom
Do you know why your dad wants to find her?
Do you understand?
You made a mistake
What?
Will also be
You want to see my mom
Kid
When making a wish
Be careful
Luo Haixiao
Hello
Brother Lai
Luo Haixiao stole a car and ran away
Brother Hai ran away
Turn right.
Turn right again.
Stop.
Turn off the lights.
Coming. Who is it?
Open the door.
Coming, coming.
Hurry.
This is killing me.
What is it now?
Hey.
Old Zhao.
Let me tell you.
You should go to the hospital for a checkup, seriously.
I think you,
might have hyperthyroidism.
This is...
If you're sick, you need treatment.
Stop bothering me.
Is it still about Tang Cheng?
Back then, there were so many of you.
Nearly ten years of effort.
It's impossible there are no clues at all.
It's not that we don't have skills, do you?
Cut the nonsense.
Let me tell you, Qian Laosan.
Now people have died because of these gold bars.
If you know anything, say it now.
You go first.
I'm listening.
What is this trying to say?
Didn't you say there was a maid at Tang Cheng's house back then?
Take a look.
Does it look familiar?
The maid disappeared.
At that time, Tang Cheng
specifically looked for a photo of that maid,
but couldn't find any.
How would I know where she is?
His name is Liu Kui.
Xu Honglai.
Yang Dong.
Luo Haixiao.
These might not be their real names.
But they are likely part of a criminal gang.
Who is he?
You don't know?
I know.
His name is Huang Jiang.
Huang Jiang.
That's right.
Did you see him again after the gold bars were stolen back then?
No.
No, I really haven't.
Not bad, Old Zhao.
Could it be him?
He's just skin and bones.
How much more do you know about Huang Jiang?
How much could I possibly know?
I've only interacted with him a few times.
The kid is pretty good.
He's quite handsome.
He told me
Told you what about him?
He and a few of his brothers
were raised by a woman
by the railway tracks.
Who is that woman?
I don't know.
Never met her.
Third Brother.
Think carefully.
What for?
You have a lot of connections.
Go, go, go.
Old Zhao
Look at me
Do I look like
a computer to you?
Huh?
One moment you ask where this is,
the next you ask where that is.
Am I in charge of household registration?
If the neighbor's dog goes missing,
do you have to ask me too?
You know,
where would I...
I remember now.
She's called Aunt Huang.
Aunt Huang.
Which Aunt?
No, that's not right.
Gui.
Gui as in osmanthus, Aunt Gui.
Aunt Gui.
Alright, I got it.
If I need anything else, I'll ask you.
Thanks, Old Qian.
No need to thank me, I owe you anyway.
Exactly.
Aren't you still owing me two hundred?
Come on, hand it over.
It's been so many years.
I still haven't given you any news about Qiqi.
I haven't found her for you.
I'm sorry.
I don't know this person either.
It seems they've never shown their face.
She is the
mother of these five people.
Where was Daiqi on the night of the 5th?
The van.
Wasn't she sick that day?
Then take this.
The van.
Where's Daiqi, Auntie?
She
isn't here.
Take the kids home first.
-Qianqian  -Mumu
Mom will be back soon.
Say goodbye to your mom.
Be good.
Bye-bye.
-Let's go, let's go  -Goodbye
Master.
Hmm.
You do it.
It's finished.
She
This
This is
the nanny at Daiqi's house.
Who is it? The child is sleeping.
Police.
Is Zhang Guiping here?
Please cooperate.
Stop.
Who are you?
You just barged in.
Who let you in?
Aunt Zhang isn't here.
She quit yesterday.
Where did she go?
Do you have her phone number?
I don't know, I don't have her number.
Then you must have the agency's number.
We now suspect Zhang Guiping.
What else can you suspect?
My daughter and son-in-law have already been taken by you.
Now you're saying our nanny has a problem.
Are you done yet?
Is your child okay?
I already told you.
He's sleeping.
Go, go, go.
Knocking on the door in the middle of the night.
Do you have any manners?
Mom
The police are watching us now.
And also Brother Hai's side.
Taining is very unsafe right now.
You're worried.
Yes.
You should leave the country the day after tomorrow.
Go to Man Ni Island first.
Wait until I get the gold.
Then I'll bring you back to Wusu.
Little Fa Lao is also waiting for us to return.
You make the decisions this time.
I won't interfere.
Don't worry.
I've arranged everything.
I've also sorted out your exit route.
This group of children
will all be sent away the day after tomorrow as well.
Add one more.
Add one.
Mumu
I want Daiqi's son too.
Okay.
Understood.
I'll find another good kid to be his friend.