(antifan_act, hashtag anti-fan, follow)
(Choi Tae-joon)
(Choi Soo-young)
(Hwang Chan-sung)
(Han Ji-an)
(Kim Min-gue)
(So I Married the Anti-Fan)
(Episode 6)
(Only If I Hadn't Met You)
You're late. Start running.
It must be uncomfortable.
We had to switch flights,
and those were the only seats.
And nothing in the business class?
Can you put your arm down?
Sorry.
I'm sorry we missed our flight
because of me.
Will you keep causing trouble?
Well, something kind of came up.
What was so important
that you had to stall everyone?
-I said I'm sorry.
-Exactly.
So what made you do this to feel sorry?
I had to hang the laundry, okay?
Fine. It couldn't have been a big deal
if you can lie about it.
But if you're going to bail like this,
just say that you're out now.
Why didn't you leave me behind?
Why did you let me tag along?
He nags way too much.
Are you two newlyweds?
We were like that when we were your age.
Ma'am, we aren't in any relationship.
We were like them once, remember?
I don't understand
why we fought so much back then.
We aren't like you two.
How come In-hyung went to Japan alone?
Well, I said I'd follow her,
but she felt bad for taking her manager
since she's just an extra.
Yes, so I asked why is she in Japan?
To shoot an ad.
Didn't you know?
It's In-hyung, so I figured you knew.
An ad? What ad?
The ad for SP Group I mentioned before.
They just needed anybody to come,
then In-hyung volunteered to go.
You didn't say you gave that gig to her.
Did you?
What's the product?
Why is it done in Japan?
It's for this coffee drink.
Who-joon is the main model.
They just needed anybody
to be there as his partner.
You didn't say
it's Who-joon's ad.
I was going to report back,
but you told us
to manage something like...
No, I'm sorry.
Does she know who the main model is?
Yes.
-Get out.
-Sorry?
Get out of here now!
I'm sorry.
Enjoy your meal.
Excuse me. I'm a huge fan.
Could I have an autograph?
Sure.
Can you hold this?
Here. Thank you.
Aren't you going to eat?
You can eat that too.
Hey, I heard Who-joon had this.
We can probably sell this
at a hefty price online.
That's why top stars
never touch a thing even at a hotel.
It's tough to be a celebrity.
Did you see Who-joon?
It's tough to be that good-looking.
I need to use the restroom.
Oh no.
My gosh. Come on.
I'm sorry.
My gosh. Are you crazy?
Why didn't you lock the door?
Look at this. My phone.
Man, that was shocking.
Goodness, you two don't want to stay away
even for a second, you newlyweds.
Goodness,
you must be tired from the travel.
Glad to have you, Geun-young.
You're finally here.
I was really anxious
that you wouldn't come.
Are you sure you didn't go, "Oh well"?
Come on, what do you think of me?
I went, "We won't shoot
if she doesn't come."
Goodness.
You can unpack your stuff later.
Why don't we head over there
and have a talk?
-Let's go.
-This way, please.
I'm sure Who-joon has been to Japan a lot,
and it's not your first time, is it?
My gosh, everyone has been to Japan.
It's barely foreign now.
Sounds great, then.
Geun-young, you're going to be
Who-joon's guide today.
-Me?
-Yes.
Who-joon, you haven't been
out on the street in Japan
since you were
probably only here on business.
-I guess.
-So today,
you're going to stroll around
like a regular tourist, not a top star.
-Doesn't that sound great?
-Don't you think people will swarm in?
No one would recognize him
if he puts on a cap and walks around.
He stands out even more
when he covers up like a celebrity.
Right. I shouldn't have said that.
People would think there's no way
Who-joon would be out here in the open
-without a disguise.
-Yes.
-Don't you think?
-Exactly.
Will you two go with them?
-We'll be behind...
-Right.
We have to go find
the next place for our shooting.
What? We already have...
-Okay, then.
-Wait, we aren't...
-Shall we?
-Where are Ra-ra and Kang-yeon?
We asked the advertisement staff
to help him out.
-I see.
-Let's go.
Geun-young, say hi to the camera.
Hello.
Where do you usually go first
when you're in Japan?
Well.
I always stop by Shibuya first.
Shibuya is in Tokyo.
Exactly.
I was saying
it's a shame that Shibuya isn't here.
I see.
Okay. You must come to Japan often.
Where should we go?
Since we're in Japan,
we should eat sushi first.
-Sushi sounds good.
-Yes.
Then I'll put my trust in you
and follow you.
Okay.
Shall we?
Darn it.
-Let's go.
-Okay.
I'm on a tour of good restaurants
with Geun-young.
Do we go this way or that way?
-That way?
-Yes.
Everything still looks the same.
I don't think this is it.
-This way?
-To the tasty restaurant.
Hey, I think it's over there.
This way?
Do we go down this way?
Wait, I don't think this is it.
-How much longer will it take?
-Soon enough.
Are we going back this way?
-This place must be great.
-Yes.
Goodness, I wonder how great it is.
I'm really looking forward to it.
-Where in the world...
-I thought something might be here.
She has zero sense of direction.
Geun-young. Geun-young?
It'd be easier to find
if we can spot something nearby.
Why don't we look it up on the map?
Right. I can't seem to remember very well.
My gosh. I'm so sorry.
It's all right.
Hey, I think it's that place.
You said it seemed right before.
-Over there.
-That's the fourth time you said...
No, this time, it's real.
Just ask her for the name of the place.
She just came across that by chance.
Then let me try a bite.
Wow, this is unbelievable.
Hey, turn it off.
-Turn it off.
-Why?
Whenever you turn this off,
turn this one in the back off too.
Our voices are getting recorded.
You've never been to Japan, right?
I can tell by the way you're eating.
You sound like people
who eat sushi for the first time in Japan.
We walked miles to eat this? Man.
Whatever. I just have a big appetite.
You're right. I almost fainted in shock
when you ate two servings on the flight.
And it's your first time here, right?
Stop pretending.
No, I'm a regular here.
I ate that in-flight meal for your sake
to not put you in a spot.
For my sake? When you were done,
you went, "May I have two more?"
You're unbelievable.
-You weren't asleep.
-Aren't you full?
Goodness. What on earth am I doing here?
This is great.
Japan is all about local beer,
and the essence of business trips is
skipping work.
Yes, drink up.
So did you hand over our first episode?
The first episode?
Wait, did you edit it in a weird way
behind my back?
No, I'm sure you'd love it too.
What did you do?
It's a secret.
Why are you making me so curious?
If this show goes under again,
you won't see me for another ten years.
Come on. Didn't you return
because you missed those days?
I made two mistakes that day.
First, setting that dove on fire.
Second, setting the night on fire
with you.
I can't believe it.
Why is the sun so burning?
I'm going to get tanned.
Let me see. Did you get tanned?
Look. I already turned darker.
You darned sun.
Ms. No, when you get tanned,
-you'll look sexy.
-I know.
-Very much.
Why don't we head over there
and get tanned?
You have a knack
for keeping yourself in peace.
I hate you.
I wonder if our two heroes are in peace,
just like us.
-Should we go in here?
-Sure.
There are lots of cute stuff.
There are lots of stuff.
-What's this?
-It's called "mikuji."
You get to pick out your fortune.
You should pick one too.
My fortune?
How is Geun-young's fortune today?
I have no idea what this says.
Let me see.
I see. "Full bloom."
(You're a late-blooming flower.
Your true love is before you,)
"You're a late-blooming flower.
Your true love is before you, but you..."
(You're a late-blooming flower.
Your true love is before you,)
"You're a late-blooming flower.
Your true love is before you, but you..."
(but you do not recognize your love,
just like a lunar eclipse.)
"You're a late-blooming flower.
Your true love is before you, but you..."
(You will go through
many tunnels of trials,)
"You're a late-blooming flower.
Your true love is before you, but you..."
(and tribulations
before you recognize each other.)
"You're a late-blooming flower.
Your true love is before you, but you..."
Hey, I guess you can speak some Japanese.
What does it say?
Well. "Even after much trouble,
you will not find your true love."
"You should continue
to choose work over love."
Really? Does it really say that?
Yes.
"However, if you keep this fortune strip,"
"you will be able to find
your true love later in life."
"But if you lose this fortune strip,
you'll never find love."
Something like that.
You have to keep it well.
-Give it to me.
-Keep it well, okay?
-Okay?
-All right? Okay.
-Give it back.
What? Hey, give it back.
Come on. Give it back!
-You better keep it well.
-So give it back to me!
-Catch me if you can!
-Why did you take it?
Fine, I'll give it to you.
Here, take it.
Hey! Come on! What's with you?
(Jae-joon)
Why won't she pick up?
She won't pick up her phone?
Yes, I'm unable to reach her all day long.
Anyway, what have you been
reading all day?
Gu told me that specialty crops are
very popular these days.
A life where nature and humans become one.
Enough.
-Farming is very...
-That's enough, please.
Let's just keep living like this. You are
the biggest specialty crop in our family.
Specializing in what now?
Just grind the ink stick.
I love December Bright the most
among all of your works.
I'm a December Bright.
I can't be a part of Seotda,
and I'm not considered
as a Bright card in Go-Stop.
Today, I'm going to show you
how you do your brows.
Now, draw your brows in a straight line.
-Yes, Ms. Jang?
(-Hey, Mi-jung.)
I haven't been able to reach Geun-young
all day long.
(Really?)
I'm not really sure either.
I haven't seen her for a few days.
For a few days?
I thought she was at your place.
Right, she's living with a senior
because of work.
A senior? Who?
Wait, is that little brat
living with a man?
Ms. Jang, no. That's not the case.
People don't think it's a big deal
to live together before marriage,
(but you kids can't do that, okay?)
Babe, open up.
Yes, Ms. Jang.
I'll find out and call you back.
Goodbye. Okay.
Babe, are you okay?
Are you all right? I'm sorry.
-I need... I need water.
-Yes, water. Here.
That feels much better. I almost died.
-This is why we shouldn't live alone.
-Gosh, stop it.
(The phone is turned off.
Please leave a message)
(-after the tone.)
-Why won't she pick up her phone?
Did she go on a trip with a guy?
We have to be at a meeting
with the advertisers.
Okay. I'll tell Mr. Han about it.
You should go.
-All right. Bye.
-Bye.
Bye!
Gosh, I'm finally free.
What should I do?
Was that a raindrop?
No. No, please don't rain.
Hello.
Mr. Seo, I'm sorry, but the advertiser
only wants to see the models.
-I'm so sorry.
-What?
He wants to have a casual dinner
with the models before the shooting.
Well, we weren't told ahead
of this situation, so...
I understand. Let's do that.
You must be tired too. Go get some rest.
And get me the ramen from that place.
You don't have to worry
or take this the wrong way.
Okay, then. Call me if anything happens.
Please look after him.
Let's go.
-Good luck.
-Okay.
Hey.
Come on in, Who-joon.
-Nice to meet you.
-Nice to meet you too.
I wanted to have a casual dinner
with the models,
-so please don't think too much of this.
-Sure.
This is... Right. Ms. Oh In-hyung.
She'll be your partner.
I heard you two are acquainted.
Yes, you're right.
-Long time no see.
-Yes, it has been a while.
-Take a seat.
-Okay.
One of our subsidiaries is
an entertainment agency,
and I asked them to send
whoever they can as your partner...
I mean, I asked them to send a model,
and In-hyung came.
I heard you two are acquainted,
so I had a good feeling
about this advertisement.
Come out.
I said come out.
He's the second son of SP Group.
If it's all right with you,
may I go out for a second?
Sure.
-I'm sorry.
-Don't mind me.
Let's eat.
-Why are you here?
-What are you doing?
Didn't you see that I had an ad gig?
Anything but this!
How can you leave without telling me?
Did you do this because you knew
you'd be in it with him?
Hey, tell him that you're out.
No, go tell the advertiser
that you want another partner.
That way, everything will be over.
Let's get this over with.
Jae-joon!
If I asked him to switch her,
will that be the end of this?
How will that resolve anything?
Who-joon, stop that.
Stop minding us.
Just get back in there
and ask him to switch her out.
Who-joon, I really want this gig.
You don't mind having me
as a partner, do you?
I mind. I care about this.
I don't care
who plays my partner.
You better sort this out now.
Stop making a scene here.
Did you hear that?
He said he doesn't care
if you don't play his partner.
Do you want to destroy your pride
to do this job?
They wanted just anybody for this job.
When I offered to take it up,
I had already thrown out my pride!
What about my pride?
Okay, Jae-joon.
I'm sorry I didn't tell you.
But I want to start over
by using this ad as my chance.
Who cares if Who-joon is the lead?
I'll get my break, then...
Are you sure you didn't volunteer
because it was him?
No? Fine.
I'm sure you thought this through.
You probably thought it'd be better
to do an ad gig with him
than someone who isn't as popular.
But is that all?
See?
Your eyes say otherwise.
Your eyes won't lie for a minute
or even a second when you look at him.
That's why I'm saying no!
I said
that isn't the case.
Forget the American Village and whatnot.
Look at how pouring it is.
-I'll get it.
-Thanks.
Hey, you came back early.
Some advertisers
want to see the model alone.
I see. Really?
He wanted some ramen,
so I'm going to get some.
I wanted to get some for the crew too.
You'll have some, right?
Ramen on a rainy night sounds great.
-So you two are in, right?
-Yes.
Let's see. Then the production crew are...
You ran out of fingers.
Don't you think you need another hand?
I knew it.
In-hyung.
You can't fool me.
Who do you think knows best
about how you came to be with me
and why you're still here?
Me. It's me.
How can you be like this?
Have you ever thought about this
in my shoes?
I feel awful about myself too.
Whenever you get
jealous, annoyed, and angry,
I tell myself that it's fine, that
it's the price I pay for living off you.
Do you know how dreadful that is?
That's why I'm telling you this now!
I don't care
even if you came to be out of need.
I don't care even if you're
still sticking around out of need.
So please!
Stay away from doing anything
that reminds me of him.
I also
want to win recognition.
You of all people
should've given me your trust.
Darn it.
(I'm glad I came today
to meet a chicken like you.)
Why won't anyone pick up their phone?
(I'm glad I came today
to meet a chicken like you.)
Mi-jung, why did you want me so badly?
(I'm glad I came today
to meet a chicken like you.)
Mi-jung, why did you want me so badly?
So I came.
Geun-young can't be reached.
You're acquainted with that reporter
who writes for Who-joon.
Call that guy and find out
what's going on.
She's in Japan on a shooting.
-Really?
-Yes.
Then why won't she pick up her phone?
It's her first time in Japan.
What if she gets lost?
Hey, she's not a kid.
Don't be worried about her,
and get me a glass of cold beer.
You must love fried chicken, Shin-hyuk.
All of Mi-jung's men are
crazy about fried chicken.
"Men"?
Well, it was great
back when she worked at a yukhoe place.
Right, and the pork belly place.
(I'm glad I came today
to meet a chicken like you.)
Right, and the pork belly place.
(I'm glad I came today
to meet a chicken like you.)
And the raw fish place.
(I'm glad I came today
to meet a chicken like you.)
You must like all kinds of food.
I heard you have lots of women too.
Gosh, you'd make my girlfriends sad
if you put it like that.
I'm, you know, a guy with lots of love.
You have that much love,
yet you visit me here very often.
I'm grateful to death.
You don't have to die.
That hurts.
Doesn't it smell great?
This is a really great place.
Everything seems the same.
You'll be surprised once you try it.
Here you are.
-Thank you.
-Sure.
I've only seen this in Japanese dramas.
Actually, it's my first time in Japan.
You thought he'd make fun of you.
Yes, you know what he's like, right?
I thought he might take me as a joke
if I said it's my first time.
Well, he already does.
I think he does that
because he's comfortable around you.
No way. Around me?
I'm sure you were angry with him today,
I haven't seen him
pull a prank like that for ages.
There's a need for someone
to mess with him from time to time.
I see. Right.
I'm glad you're here for him.
Now that you put it like that,
I feel like I'm pretty useful.
Do you know
what people used to call me at work?
Just Geun-young.
They always said,
"Just make Geun-young do it."
There's something different about you.
You have such a gentle way of talking.
Anyway, you seem to adore Who-joon a lot.
Back when I was the youngest manager,
I took the highway back to Seoul
from Busan.
But the car suddenly stopped midway.
I called the insurance company,
and that's when I realized
we were completely out of gas.
I was a total idiot. That's what.
-So what happened?
-We didn't make it to his next schedule,
Then the CEO lashed me out
with all kinds of vulgar words.
I figured I'm done working with him.
Right. But how are you still here?
On my way out,
I saw Joon there waiting for me.
I apologize to him,
then he said, "Why are you sorry?"
"That can happen when we get busy,
and you're just a rookie."
"Why is he making
such a big deal out of this?"
Really? Who-joon said that?
Yes, the same Who-joon.
He said he could catch a break
thanks to my mistake.
He said he was very happy
on his way back in the towing truck,
then thanked me instead.
And he asked me to stay with him
and be his manager to the end.
I'm having a hard time believing you.
You can't make up
heartwarming stories about your singer.
He's a good kid.
He debuted while he was still young,
so the first thing he learned was
how the world was cold
and he always had to weigh stuff.
He never got a chance
to be his gentle self.
But he's a kind-hearted kid.
I know that.
Just...
Just stay here.
I'm doing this so you feel hot.
You're late. Start running.
You should eat before it turns cold.
Isn't it good?
I just shared all kinds of stuff.
Hey!
(She's...)
(I think she's the same woman
from that time.)
You broke his heart!
(What are they talking about?)
(She was crying back then,)
(and she's crying again today.)
You're back.
I'll go give these out.
That smells great.
You should've told me.
Why did you do that with people around?
-Who is it?
-I'm here with the ramen.
Mr. Seo, you don't look so well.
I gave these out
to everyone who wanted ramen.
-And these were left.
-Yes, thank you.
Is Geun-young getting some rest?
She must've been tired.
I think she's asleep.
-Goodnight.
-Yes, goodbye.
-Bye.
-Thank you.
It's probably cold and soggy,
but if you want some, eat it.
Get some rest.
I have to let you go,
but I can't do that yet.
And I...
And I still...
(Your message has been sent.
Thank you for using our service.)
need you.
(And I...)
(And I still...)
(Your mailbox is full.)
(Father)
Yes, Mr. Chairman.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I will
figure everything out.
Let me go!
Hey!
Are you an idiot?
I told you not to see her.
Why did you bring her here?
Stop that, Ji-hyang.
Don't call me by my name.
How long will you do this?
How long will you lurk around him?
It's a misunderstanding. Stop that.
I asked him to come out.
-If he didn't, I was going to visit him...
-If you left him
for a jerk like that, then it's over.
He only had you in his heart,
but you broke his heart!
The least you can do is let it mend.
Why do you keep coming back to break it?
That's enough, Ji-hyang.
In-hyung, if you really care about him,
please just leave.
Yes, you're right, Ji-hyang.
I didn't think this through.
I'm sorry.
Don't go after her.
Good morning. You got up early.
-Hey.
-Morning.
Hotel breakfast is
the best part of traveling abroad.
-Eat up, everyone.
-Okay.
Who-joon, you don't look so well.
Did you catch a cold?
Goodness.
And Geun-young,
you don't look well either.
You didn't get enough sleep.
Goodness, you're all in bad condition.
What's going on?
-Hey, let's go get some food.
-I just did.
-Eat some more.
-More?
Why?
Did you eat that ramen last night?
No, I didn't.
You should've had it since this is
your first time in Japan. Why not?
It was all soggy.
Did the noodles get soggy
in the heavy rain?
Or was it people who got soggy?
Eat up.
I'm sorry, but you can eat that.
Sorry for the trouble.
I'll go upstairs and get some rest.
Don't mind me and eat up.
What's wrong? Was he mean again?
-He's always the same.
-He probably feels embarrassed.
Anyway, who's that woman...
Who's who?
Don't be surprised. I won't be curious.
Goodness.
Mr. Seo, will you go with him
to shoot that advertisement?
Yes, of course.
Aren't you going to go?
-Director.
-Hey, you're here.
Yes.
-What do you think?
-Everything is going well thanks to you.
You're an expert, after all.
-One second.
-Okay.
-Where's the partner?
-Not yet.
Isn't she a rookie? Call her.
This is funny.
What kind of a rookie dares
to make the top star wait?
She's here!
I'm sorry.
-I'm sorry.
(-It's her.)
I'm sorry.
All right.
Let's get ready and keep it moving.
It's all right. You can relax.
Thank you.
(Who-joon's partner is)
(that woman?)
Hello.
-I'm the CEO of her agency.
-Hello.
-I see.
-Why is Jae-joon here?
-Hello.
-Please take good care of her.
We'll do our best.
-Isn't that Oh In-hyung and JJ?
-Then let's start from here.
-Please take a seat.
-I see.
-What an odd group.
-Why?
They used to be in the same agency.
I see.
My gosh, you really don't have
good information.
Fine.
I need to go check that out.
Here's the script.
So you're going to walk along the beach.
-That thing?
-Yes.
-Geun-young.
-Hello.
What brings you here?
His partner is in my agency.
I see. Is she the one
I met at the TV station?
Yes, the one you wouldn't recognize.
-You haven't seen her, right?
-No.
Where could I have seen her?
It's really windy.
(Special Cafe Latte Storyboard)
They look great.
Of course, it'd be great.
What a sight.
It must be tough to face each other.
-Sorry?
-What?
The sun is really bright,
so wouldn't it be tough
to face each other?
I guess so.
What would that feel like?
Like you're head over heels.
Sorry?
No, I mean that the sand is so soft
that their heels are probably stuck.
-I see.
-Yes.
Do you like her?
I mean, the sea.
Not really. It's way too windy.
A windy beach can get annoying.
Even if it looks beautiful?
There are beautiful landscapes
that can be an eyesore to you.
It's a bit sad, though.
It's getting hot.
-And a bit icky.
-Tell me about it.
Is it because it rained yesterday?
What's with this weather?
I'm sure there's a reason.
-I'm sure there is something.
-There is something.
What did you just say?
Me?
I didn't say anything.
I must be hearing things.
I think the shooting is almost over.
Geun-young, I'll see you later.
Okay.
What's going on
between Jae-joon and that woman?
Geun-young!
Let's get ready to shoot our show.
-Right, okay. Finally.
-Yes.
(I need to start
by solving this guy's mystery.)
Let's get started, Geun-young.
(So what exactly happened
between him and her?)
Like this.
You haven't done this a lot, right?
Is this how you'll be?
All right, now.
Goodness.
(What is this?)
(My heart must have gone crazy.)
Goodness.
What are you doing?
I told you not to satisfy your needs here.
Okay, now. Let's do this again.
My goodness.
-Oh no.
-Wait, don't rush out.
Gosh. Oh no.
Keep shooting. Keep rolling.
Geun-young, no!
Geun-young!
That's it. Who-joon, carry her out.
This is why I said
we shouldn't go in the water!
Are you okay, Geun-young?
I told you not to do this!
-Geun-young!
-No, I'm fine.
Be quiet. Geun-young, are you okay?
-Get her out.
-Are you okay?
Geun-young. Geun-young!
-Geun-young! Keep your eyes closed.
-I'm fine.
Geun-young!
What am I going to do?
Wake up.
Geun-young. I'm so relieved.
I was really shocked.
I'm so relieved.
Shouldn't I be awarded
as a brave citizen or whatever?
Do you want this towel?
I'm fine.
I need to talk to Mr. Han.
You need to stay focused.
Your mind was somewhere else
as soon as we began.
-Why did you fall in there?
-It's not like I wanted to.
You pushed me really hard.
You better stay focused on me from now on.
You're the one who overreacted.
Goodness. That two-faced jerk.
(Who-joon)
I thought he was gay.
But he's not.
(Who-joon, gay)
Then is that woman...
(That woman)
(Who-joon, gay, that woman)
The tteokbokki?
Like this?
Then where does JJ stand?
(JJ)
It's not like I'm a detective.
Whatever.
Goodness.
You look like you slept very well.
Did you catch a cold?
You can worry about others?
Did you?
I feel fine after getting some sleep.
Just don't let me catch it.
What did I expect?
Geun-young, there's no shooting today.
Do you want to come to town with us?
Where is everyone?
Ms. No was gone
by the time I woke up late.
They both went out to shop.
Are they here to work or travel?
Today is the premiere,
so they wanted to watch it together.
You can come out with us.
She doesn't want to come. Let her stay.
Why are you pestering her?
He must be feeling better.
He's grumbling again.
Come with us. It's our last day.
Okay, Mr. Seo.
I left my wallet in the car.
You two can head over to the udon place.
I'll make a quick trip.
Goodness, he can be very sloppy.
I guess you don't realize who causes that.
-What did you say?
-Let's browse as we wait.
My gosh.
This is cute.
These come in all kinds of colors.
I guess it's a local character in Okinawa.
I'll get one and hand it out.
We don't have this in Korea, right?
What? Where did he go?
I can't believe this guy.
He should've said he's leaving.
-Hey.
-Yes?
May I help you?
-I'm sorry.
-Oh, all right.
Oh no.
Why didn't you go? Where's Geun-young?
-She was just here.
-What? You were here with her.
I left for a second...
Where did she go?
She's such a troublemaker.
She said it's her first time coming here.
Her phone doesn't work right now.
Man.
Darn it.
Where is she?
This is driving me insane.
It's okay.
I just have to get back to the hotel.
Okay.
But what is the hotel called?
I want to go home.
Why did I tag along anyway?
Look at this mess.
Mom...
Found you.
I told you to stay focused on me.
(You're embracing your anti-fan.)