Did you know it has already been ten days since we became date mates?
Already?
Time really flies, doesn't it?
You're right. Time really flies.
How is it so far?
Not so bad, except for the couple t-shirt.
What about you?
That's my answer.
I heard you were preparing a new proposal.
Wow, you're so well-informed.
So what are you planning?
It's a secret.
Tell me. I'm curious.
So you can trash it again?
Maybe.
I might be more critical if it sucks.
I'll have to do well to avoid your criticism.
But did I make you feel that insulted back then?
Yes. It was the most humiliating day ever since I came into the company.
I apologize. Please forgive me.
Let's toast to that.
- What a beautiful weather.
- Yeah.
[Seo Yi Jun, Team Leader]
[Played by Cho Hyun Min]
[Jeong Ha Ram, Team Worker]
[Played by Cho Han Gyeol]
[Are you looking for true love?]
[Love Mate]
[Episode 6]
[True love is having a welcoming heart, whenever, wherever, without any change]
What the... Didn't you go home?
I did. I did, but... you wouldn't leave my mind.
You didn't eat dinner yet, right?
It's a hassle.
Do you mean that I'm a hassle, or that it's a hassle for me?
Both?
So aren't you happy to see me?
I'm very happy.
With words only? I want you to express yourself.
Oh, right.
Look at this.
Okay, I believe you. It's so funny.
Oh? This!
[True love is having a welcoming heart, whenever, wherever, without any change]
Isn't this what I said?
So what?
I'll need to collect royalty fees.
What are you saying?
Let me join the proposal. I'll give you my share.
You're kidding, right?
Working late with the person I like is on my bucket list.
I'm merciless. You're out as soon as you lose focus.
Of course, I'm just going to work. What are you imagining?
I'm just saying.
Hurry and eat so we can get to work.
Are you serious?
I'll help you. It's too much to do alone.
But if I suck, you can mercilessly criticize me, too. Deal?
Deal.
Did you choose a title for your new proposal?
It's too early. I don't even have a draft yet.
Really?
It's always easier for me when I begin with a title.
Just like...
a sprout grows from a seed, ideas sprout from my head.
I see. It would be nice to begin with a title.
Bucket list?
Jeong Ha Ram.
Jeong Ha Ram. Don't sleep here. Go home.
Are you done?
I still have a little more left.
Let me know when you're done. I'll take you home.
I can take a taxi home.
Go home before the last bus.
Then I'll just take the taxi with you to your house.
My house?
There you go again with your dirty thoughts.
Anyway, just wake me up.
I worked too hard today, so I'm out of it.
Hand.
Hand!
Why?
Let's hold hands and sleep.
I can hear your heart really well.
Should we just take the day off tomorrow?
I'm suddenly wide awake.
What will we do instead of sleeping?
What you kept thinking about.
I did not think anything like that.
Then what I kept thinking about.
Let's go to sleep. We'll really be late tomorrow.
All right.
Good night, Hyeong.
[What is true love?]
[Objective]
Is it midnight already?
Jeong Ha Ram.
What's that?
Happy birthday.
How did you know?
I was too indifferent, wasn't I?
You should have told me in advance.
My heart feels like it's going to explode.
Make a wish before it explodes.
- Happy birthday!
- Thanks.
So... what did you wish for?
For your proposal to be accepted.
You made that up to cheer me up, didn't you?
Tell me! What did you wish for?
No. Wishes aren't meant to be shared.
Then let's clean up here. It's late.
No gift?
Wasn't the event enough? What more do you want?
Our secret late nights at work continued, and in the end,
the new proposal was complete.
[True Love]
♫ I can't help but look at you to my heart's content ♫
♫ When you call me, I get flustered for no reason and blush right away ♫
Next, Team Leader Seo will present his new proposal.
Applause.
I present my new proposal.
The title is "True Love."
We ambitiously prepared a healing dating program
that heals the wounds of breakups through new people and finds true love.
Team Leader Seo, you did really well!
We finally passed!
Leave the rest up to me.
I will pour my soul into writing the script.
- Fighting.
- I'll put my trust in you.
Shall we have a celebratory party later? It will be my treat.
I-I'm sorry, but I have plans later.
Is it a date with the person you're seeing?
Yes.
Oh, well, it can't be helped. I'll back off today.
- Let's set a date soon.
- Sure.
Do you at least want to get a drink with me?
I also have plans.
Yes? Today must not be the day.
Anyway, great job, everyone.
- You did well, too.
- Thank you.
Hey, what are you up to?
Thanks.
What did I do? You did all the work.
Gosh, you constantly stayed by my side.
That's not easy.
I'm honored, Team Leader Seo.
By the way, where are we going later?
It's a surprise. You can look forward to it.
A surprise? What is it?
It's a secret.
Aigo, you did so well.
Unveiling your body isn't the surprise, is it?
I rented this entire place... for you.
Here?
I'm joking. I asked the director for a favor.
Hand.
Hey, wait, wait!
Give me a second.
One... two...
Surprise!
This is for you.
What do you think?
The mood is so nice.
I always wanted to come here... with the person I like.
What is my next surprise?
His name is Yun Do Kyeong.
He's a former swimmer, currently modeling under the stage name DK.
[Name: Yun Do Kyeong]
I just tossed them the "True Love" proposal. I simply tossed it. But...
They caught it. They reached out to us, saying they wanted to do it.
What do you all think?
Team Leader Seo, what's with your expression? Don't you like him?
With his looks, he'll be... a huge help with viewer ratings.
I agree with you, Manager.
I see star potential.
I'd like to proceed. From what his agency says,
they also have a strong intention to support him.
And they said that he's willing to do anything we ask.
Let's take the easy road. The easy road.
Let's think about it a bit more.
Sure. The proposer's opinion is most important.
Please decide as soon as possible and give us a positive response.
My ex-boyfriend who made me miserable.
He showed up in front of me out of the blue.
Why now...
♫ So I just like you ♫
♫ Just stay as you are now ♫
[Are you looking for true love?]
[Love Mate]
♫ You don't need to realize it ♫
♫ You're the most brilliant person to me ♫
♫ Just like you ♫
♫ My heart still flutters when you call me ♫
♫ Your soft voice... ♫