Are you busy?
I asked if you were busy.
The call is not going through. Please leave a message...
Hey!
- Do you know Assistant Manager Park?
- Why aren't you picking up?
Assistant Manager Park will... Let's go.
What's with him all of a sudden?
[Seo Yi Jun, Team Leader]
[Played by Cho Hyun Min]
[Jeong Ha Ram, Team Worker]
[Played by Cho Han Gyeol]
[Are you looking for true love?]
[Love Mate]
[Episode 5]
He didn't say a word to me all day
and treated me as if I was invisible.
Ah, I am upset!
Was I too harsh on him all this time?
He's not doing this to tease me like a kid, is he?
Hey, why are you ignoring me?
[Ha Ram]
Is this too straightforward?
Did I do something to upset you?
Why do I get such a bad feeling?
It's probably nothing.
Whoa, hold on! Hold on!
You feel restless, don't you?
Me?
Your eyes give it away.
Now you know how I felt all this time, right?
I'm not sure.
You asked for some time to think.
I didn't want to disturb you.
Gosh! I'm so glad to talk to you after a whole day of evasion.
- It was just one day.
- What do you mean by "just"?
Every minute, every second with you is like an hour.
I'm done thinking.
Already?
There wasn't much to think about.
I'm so excited and nervous... about what you'll say.
Let's talk during lunch.
Just tell me now. Don't make me restless again.
Wait.
[Quiche Mignon]
I'll get straight to the point.
Let's be date mates.
Date mates?
Yeah. Rather than starting to date right away,
let's decide after getting to know each other better.
How should I put this...
It's somewhere between flirting and dating.
When we've already crossed the line?
I know it's out of the ordinary,
but...
I'm unfamiliar and cautious with these emotions.
I'm also scared I might mess up if I rush into it.
- Because...
- Because?
I'm a relationship virgin, like you said.
And I am fragile when it comes to emotions.
I really want to do well.
And I also want to get to know you more.
Then let's do it, Date Mate.
Really? Thanks.
How about we set a duration of a month?
Sounds good.
But... what if we both don't think we're right for each other?
It's better than hating each other and regretting it later, right?
For now, let's set some rules.
- Rules?
- Yes.
Next month...
Let's keep it a secret at work.
Excessive touching is off limits.
♫ I can't wait to know, Baby ♫
♫ I want to know how you feel ♫
♫ Your heart is fluttering like mine ♫
♫ I can't wait to know, Baby ♫
♫ There's never enough time for me to love you ♫
♫ I can catch a star for you if that's what you want ♫
♫ If you're afraid of the dark, I'll make it bright like your smile ♫
♫ No matter how hard I try ♫
♫ I can't imagine not having you by my side ♫
♫ Honestly, looking at you ♫
♫ I think I know how you feel ♫
♫ This feeling I can't hide, it's love ♫
♫ I can hear it louder than the ticking clock ♫
♫ My heart, please hold back ♫
♫ Even if I pretend I don't like you ♫
♫ A smile naturally appears when I look at you ♫
♫ I can't wait to know, Baby ♫
♫ I want to know how you feel ♫
♫ Your heart is fluttering like mine ♫
This was tiring, but it lifted my mood.
You like it more because you're with me, right?
Do you need to confirm it every time to feel satisfied?
Team Leader, I want to set a rule, too.
What is it?
Let's choose pet names for each other and speak comfortably.
You've never called my name even once.
You always call me "hey" or "you."
Well, that's...
By chance, it's not because you don't know my name, right?
As if I didn't know your name?
Then call my name now.
What's the big deal?
Ha Ram.
I can't hear you.
Ha Ram. Jeong Ha Ram.
I'm touched.
I want to set that voice as my ringtone.
It takes little to move you.
You can drop the honorifics.
But you... not at work.
All right, Yi Jun Hyeong.
(T/N: lit. "older brother" of a male, but is also often used in close friendships or relationships)
But "hyeong" sounds a bit cringe.
But you say it so naturally.
Of course. I've been calling you that in my heart.
It's so you.
Did you know?
Polar bears and penguins can never meet.
That's why this moment is so unbelievable to me.
Wow...
This feels so nice.
[Single Heaven]
[Single Heaven Proposal]
[Empty Recycle Bin]
Before I knew it, a small change reflected in me.
It was a bit unfamiliar, but I decided to trust it.
I'd like to change the Single Heaven proposal.
Team Leader Seo, what?
You want to change the direction of the proposal after all this time?
What's your reason?
I think we were a bit too hasty with Single Heaven.
I don't think that's the only reason.
You can't fool these eyes.
To be honest, I'm seeing someone.
Daebak! Have you succeeded with the training?
- Is that why you changed your mind?
- I can't say you're wrong...
Anyway, I'll send you the draft soon.
I'm sorry for the inconvenience.
Of course, it's what you want. I am with you.
Seeing you full of confidence eases my heart.
You must have found the answer, huh?
I'm not sure yet, but I'll do my best.
Let's pick ourselves back up and do our best.
Gosh! I'm honestly a bit envious of you.
Gosh, why be envious?
What's with the tumbler?
What else? It's a couple's item.
Couple's item?
What's with that reaction? It's disappointing.
We agreed not to be like this at work.
I'm doing this because we're at work.
- Seriously, you're...
- Why?
Stop being so reckless.
I know you like it, but you're just being shy.
I'll just use this at home.
I knew you would be like this. So I prepared one more thing.
What? What is it? Spill it!
I ordered couple t-shirts too.
What? Couple t-shirt?
I'm sorry.
You were so cute just now.
Cancel it this instant!
I don't want to.
Doing this without consulting me is unfair.
Team Leader Seo, "A couple t-shirt"? What was that? Are you dating someone?
No, I was just working on the proposal.
You're not buying couple t-shirts with the newbie, are you?
- Pardon?
- I'm kidding. Look at this.
The newsletter cover draft is out. Daebak! Look at those eyes.
Hearts are shooting out. Pop, pop!
Come to the rooftop garden immediately.
Why did you react like that if you like it?
We agreed to keep this a secret. You're not cooperating.
I'll let the tumbler slide, so cancel the couple t-shirts.
They're already being shipped.
What?
Should I return them?
You don't even mean that. Oh, right.
Here.
Hyeong, you came out nice.
Especially your gaze.
What about my gaze?
It's out of the ordinary. It seems like you've fallen for me.
You're right. To be honest, you shook my heart a bit at the time.
Is that why you fainted?
No.
I fainted while holding my breath because I didn't want to breathe the same air as you.
I guess I'll just have to believe that.
Oh, let's take a picture.
What picture?
To commemorate our first couple item.
Aren't you tired of taking pictures with me?
As if. Don't be shy and get close to me.
The couple item.
Lift the photo so it's more visible.
Like this?
Yes.
Make pretty faces. I'm taking it.
One, two, three!
What the... What are you two doing here?
Oh, I was showing him the cover.
Team Leader Seo, something is going on here, isn't it?
You two seem to be hanging out a lot recently.
No way. You know we're not on good terms.
You're really suspicious.
Exactly. You used to argue all the time.
♫ So I just like you ♫
♫ Just stay as you are now ♫
[Are you looking for true love?]
[Love Mate]
♫ You don't need to realize it ♫
♫ You're the most brilliant person to me ♫
♫ Just like you ♫
♫ My heart still flutters when you call me ♫
♫ Your soft voice... ♫