I fell in love with you...
at first sight.
What?
[Seo Yi Jun, Team Leader]
[Played by Cho Hyun Min]
[Jeong Ha Ram, Team Worker]
[Played by Cho Han Gyeol]
[Are you looking for true love?]
[Love Mate]
Hey.
Even if I seem like a pushover to you,
[Episode 2]
you should know when to stop.
I provoked you intentionally. Shock treatment.
Since you don't believe in love, Team Leader.
So? You fell for me. So what?
I want to
date you.
What?
You're definitely drunk and out of your senses.
I'm very serious right now.
- What is 8 times 9?
- 72. See? I'm fine, right?
Dream on.
Why?
Why should I date you out of all the people?
Do you think you're special?
I'm tall.
I'm reliable.
And most importantly,
I'm handsome.
I might look like this, but I'm top-notch when it comes to blind dating.
That's what you think. I don't think so.
Which aspect of me?
That ridiculous shock therapy
and a confession out of the blue.
You probably thought it was the perfect plan.
But right now, you're being rude.
I am super offended right now.
I'm sorry, but you better give up on your feelings.
Gosh.
Oh, wait!
Aren't you curious... why I like you?
Not one bit.
Really?
As you already know, I don't date.
I don't like to. Relationships are too bothersome.
Getting caught up in mixed emotions is the worst.
Then why do you meet people through apps?
You're so tenacious. How did you know?
I vaguely heard it from the writer.
Yes. I meet people through apps.
That's simpler and nice. Why?
Since there aren't expectations or a need for unnecessary emotions.
Not because you're afraid?
Let me say one thing.
You're... not my type. Period.
Hold on!
I'll make sure... you date me.
"He fell for me"?
That's absurd.
He'll lose interest on his own.
[Title: Runaway Penguin]
This crazy psycho—
That hits the spot.
Yes. I meet people through apps.
That's simpler and nice. Why?
Since there aren't expectations or a need for unnecessary emotions.
I'll install them all.
What's this?
No thanks. I don't get hangovers.
Pardon?
Didn't we clear things up last night?
Things like this won't work on me.
Team Leader, are you still drunk?
Wasn't it you?
What makes you so sure?
Was this really not you?
Give it to me if you won't drink it.
Good. I was suffering from a hangover anyway.
No matter how busy you are,
you should take care of your looks.
Looks are more important to me than you think.
I don't just like anyone.
You're crazy.
I'll really drink this.
[Quiche Mignon]
Yes, Writer.
Yes, I'm inside.
Yes, all right. Okay.
Team Leader!
Did you enjoy your lunch?
Have a seat here.
I've already ordered everything.
What are you doing right now?
What are you scheming?
I changed the route a bit.
Now that I have confessed to you,
I will pursue you head-on.
Wow. Sudden brake.
Stop fooling around and change lanes.
What's with you two?
Writer, what do you do if you get bitten by a rabid dog?
There's no cure for that.
Let's go over there.
Have a seat here.
Assistant Manager! Here. Over here!
- Hurry, hurry, hurry.
- What's this?
I ordered everything already. Did you enjoy your lunch?
It was okay.
Have this. Have this!
Gosh, the stress.
What is it? Huh?
It's nothing. Don't worry about it.
Anyway, when will you start the training?
I have to do it, right?
If you trust me completely.
I'll think about it some more.
Writer, what would you like to drink?
An iced vanilla latte for me.
- Okay.
- 130 cm?
It dosn't look like it.
But you're 180 cm tall.
That's a 50 cm difference...
Ajeossi!
Ajeossi, stop!
Team Leader. Look at this, another coincidence!
I'm worried you might fall.
Hurting the same spot twice is unfair.
I'll give you three seconds to take your hands off.
One, two, three!
♫ I can't wait to know, Baby ♫
♫ I want to know how you feel ♫
Did you know?
Playing hard to get is your charm.
Passing through.
♫ At first, I couldn't help my fluttering heart ♫
♫ I can't help but look at you to my heart's content ♫
I should ride the subway from now on.
I couldn't even imagine at the time...
that misfortune could also become destiny.
Manager. Did you look at the draft?
Yes, I got it. It looks fun! Good luck!
Thanks.
He only meets people through apps?
Then I'll find you, no matter what.
Hey. Aren't you working?
Aigo, so strict.
I was taking a short break.
What would you need a break for?
I brought the actors snacks and set them up.
I got the draft and delivered it to you.
I helped the props team organize the props.
I helped carry the lights for the lighting team.
What else did I do?
Newbies are supposed to gain experience by doing this and that.
And don't just wait for orders. You should look for things to do.
Take a look at the snack table.
A lot of people took things.
All right, I understand.
Could you two help me out a bit?
Sure, how can we help you?
Please fill in for the test shots.
Excuse me? Isn't it the newlywed concept today?
Oh, good.
Let's use this chance to take official couple photos for you guys.
Manager...
I am sorry, Writer, but I can't do it.
The female model is really tall.
She's about your height.
- That's still a bit overwhelming for me—
- No!
We'll do it.
This is part of our job.
Isn't that right, Team Leader?
Of course, of course!
The team leader should set a good example for his workers.
That's right. Please do me the favor, Team Leader Seo.
Don't think too hard. Let's go.
Letting personal feelings influence work is a bit pathetic.
Let's go.
Can you put your legs on his?
My l-legs?
Good, that's it.
Okay! Just like that.
What are you doing?
This is a pose from the draft.
You checked it yourself.
Let's just get it over with quickly.
That depends on you.
This is in the draft.
Ha Ram, very good.
Can you put your arm around his waist?
Yes, just like that. Good, good!
Okay, okay. I'm going in.
Why are they so good?
You know we're supposed to kiss at the end, right?
Can I do it for real?
Oh, my! What's wrong with him?
Team Leader! Team Leader!
[Photographs and Outings]
He's making me worry.
Team Leader.
Is he dead?
What did you do to me?
That's what I want to ask you.
♫ So I just like you ♫
♫ Just stay as you are now ♫
[Are you looking for true love?]
[Love Mate]
♫ You don't need to realize it ♫
♫ You're the most brilliant person to me ♫
♫ Just like you ♫
♫ My heart still flutters when you call me ♫
♫ Your soft voice... ♫