THE PLACES, CHARACTERS, ORGANIZATIONS, AND
INCIDENTS IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS.
Hey, guys. It's me.
Did you see the woman
who stabbed Kim Gukho?
Wow.
She stabbed him in the side.
Then in the chest!
This is it. Fuck!
I'm finally getting my money's worth.
The poison arrows and bomb were too much.
Kim Gukho's in a coma now.
If he dies,
will the 20 billion won go to her?
Will Kim Gukho die...
or live?
13 YEARS AGO
Minjin?
Let's go. You have work tomorrow.
Hey.
Fuck, I'm screwed.
Did you hurt yourself?
What do you mean?
Your clothes are ripped.
The sleeve.
It must've gotten caught on something.
Don't talk to me. I'm tired.
DONGHA TAEKWONDO
Dongha, are you excited to go to the zoo?
Dongha,
there's a real tiger over there.
Let's go see it.
Let's go see the tiger.
Mr. Kim Gukho?
You're under arrest for the murder
of Lee Minjin.
Don't move.
Stay still.
Let's go.
You bitch!
How dare you sell your husband out?
You bitch.
Dongha.
Dongha!
It's okay. Mommy's right here.
THE 35TH VIENNA INTERNATIONAL
MUSIC COMPETITION
First prize
goes to Seo Dongha.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
Congratulations on winning
the first prize.
Let's give him a round of applause.
NO WAY OUT: THE ROULETTE
20 BILLION WON FOR NOTORIOUS CRIMINAL
MASKED MAN'S TARGET, KIM GUKHO
WHO'S THE MASKED MAN BEHIND THE HIT?
I heard you
first picked up the violin
at a local cultural center at a late age.
Why do you think
you were able to progress so quickly?
Well...
I was lucky enough
to meet a great teacher.
I think that helped me progress faster.
You're getting offers
from top music schools around the world,
including the University of Music
and Performing Arts Vienna.
What are your plans for the future?
I'm so grateful.
I want to go to all of these schools.
I'm going to decide
after discussing it with my teacher.
Things have been noisy
since Kim Gukho's release from prison.
How does it make you feel?
We will only take music-related questions.
Do you plan on apologizing
to the victims?
Why do I have to apologize?
That's the end of the interview.
Let's go.
Goodbye.
You didn't have to come here.
I missed you.
Great job.
You did well.
He only got two notes wrong.
I'll make you omurice for dinner.
You should come too.
Sounds good.
- Hey.
- What?
Isn't that him?
Kim Gukho's son.
You're right. The genius violinist.
I don't believe it. It's him.
Disgusting.
That asshole is probably a pervert too.
The apple doesn't fall
far from the tree.
- So freaking creepy.
- Why is he here?
Hey.
- What did you just say?
- What's it to you, lady?
Why would you compare my son
to that bastard? Why?
Let go of me!
- What the hell?
- Hey.
My son is different!
He's different from him!
And he's different from the likes of you!
Dongha...
KIM GUKHO'S THE DEVIL
SEND HIM TO HELL
WIPE OUT SEX OFFENDERS
CAPITAL PUNISHMENT
Mirroring Seo Dongha's
musical performance.
I don't need a new television.
I need a new boiler. Damn it.
It'll be here tomorrow.
There's only one boiler place
in this neighborhood.
It's so fucking cold.
It's the busiest time for them.
Here you go.
Your body will heat up in no time.
I promise...
to bring your son to you.
Of course.
He was mine to begin with.
Thank you!
Daeun, wait for me!
We're late. Hurry up!
Be punctual!
Hey, he's here.
What time is it?
He's fashionably late.
He doesn't even care that he's late.
Why the hell
does he always look so gloomy?
Would you be
smiling if you were him? Think about it.
He put his headphones back on.
He must have heard us.
Hey, look at your texts.
GROUP CHAT
TAEHUN: DID YOU HEAR ABOUT HIS DAD?
NAMGYEONG: YEAH, EVERYONE'S AFTER HIM!
Hey,
where's Seo Dongha, that bastard?
Well?
Where's Seo Dongha?
Move out of the way.
Come on.
Your dad's fucking awesome.
He's worth 20 billion won! Fuck.
Must be nice.
You're rich.
I was curious about something.
Why is your last name "Seo"?
Shouldn't it be "Kim"?
Did you change your identity or something?
What the hell?
Where do you think you're going?
Get lost.
You dirty little fucker!
You asshole!
Have you lost your mind?
That's enough!
What wrong did Dongha do?
You fucking bitch, are you crazy?
You punks!
- Don't move!
- Let go!
What should we write
on her face?
Who's good at drawing?
Grab her tight!
She's so strong.
Hey, write "bitch" for me.
- What's he doing?
- What?
What is that?
What are you doing?
Fuck, is this gasoline?
Asshole.
What?
What the fuck are you doing?
Let's all die here.
Stop bluffing, you bastard.
What?
You don't think I'll do it?
Hey, it's fire! Run! Get out of here!
- He's crazy.
- Hey, wait for me! Hey!
Thanks.
From now on,
don't act like you know me.
This is the place
where Kim Gukho's son lives.
RAPE GENES
GET LOST, SON OF A MURDERER
Stop it.
I have to erase this.
Erasing it won't change anything.
People will see it.
I'm okay, Mom. You can stop.
Let go of me. I have to erase this.
I'm fine.
Let's go home.
Okay?
KIM GUKHO
20 BILLION WON
KILL
Guys, I'm about to be pissed.
Do you think this is right? Do you?
I told you to kill Kim Gukho.
Did I tell you to set off a bomb
where people were gathered?
Is this a war?
Someone will fire missiles at this rate.
Starting now,
any injuries to civilians
will be considered a foul, got it?
Come on, guys.
I'm not asking you for much, am I?
Let's keep it clean and straightforward.
Lieutenant Baek, you need to see this.
What is it? I'm busy right now.
Now, the Masked Man
has broadcast five times,
and each person was mentioned here before.
That goes for Yoon Changjae too.
Among the petitions submitted
to Open Newspaper,
they're criminals
who weren't properly punished.
Do you know who the last person is?
It's Kim Gukho.
Wait.
I did this, but it gets cut off here.
What's wrong with this?
Like that?
Mi... Church?
It looks like Midian Church.
- Midian Church?
- Yeah.
This church is really famous.
Thank you so much.
This is Professor Rebecca.
The String Department dean at the
University Royal Conservatoire of Music.
- I see.
- Say hello.
It's so nice
to meet you, Dongha.
The concours was amazing.
Your gorgeous and dynamic music
always inspires me.
I hope you can find your dreams fulfilled
in our school.
I can provide all that you need.
Thank you, but...
I need some time to think about it.
Oh, what are your concerns? I can help.
What are you saying?
Dongha will go.
Tell her that he'll go.
There's no problem here.
Let me talk to him.
No problem.
Okay. Good.
Read it.
Mom...
I talked it over with your teacher.
Go abroad.
What about you?
Well...
I need to take care of some things.
I'll be there soon.
I won't go without you.
Dongha,
just go first. I'll be there soon.
You know I can't be persuaded.
Please.
Let's eat.
MIDIAN CHURCH
Members of the congregation,
during a counseling session yesterday,
a deacon came to me and said,
"Pastor."
"I pray every day and every night."
"I even attend early morning prayers."
"So why does my son
play video games instead of studying?"
"It's hard raising a child."
So I asked her this.
"Deacon, did you only study
when you were in school?"
If prayers could send
our children to college,
then our presbyter's children
would've gone to Harvard.
Now, beloved members
of the congregation...
You shouldn't pray alone.
Teach them God's words so they can
take responsibility for their lives.
Let's bet on it
with our lives.
- Hallelujah.
- Amen.
Pastor, have some water.
You're spilling again.
MIDIAN CHURCH
Yes?
Ah.
Yes, hello.
Thank you.
Elder,
please give the pastor a meal.
Thank you. I appreciate it.
There's a system where
we can post petitions?
I had no idea.
I know people don't trust the law
these days...
...but wouldn't it be safer to stay
within the boundaries of the law?
That's what God would want.
I'm just curious.
Do you watch YouTV?
Of course, I do.
I love mukbangs.
Ohh. Yes, I see.
This is made at the church. Try it.
Yes, thank you.
So how can we help you, Detective?
No, I just came to check some things.
Okay.
Somi!
Give this to your dad on your way.
I have to go straight to the library.
Your dad hasn't changed
his underwear for days. Look.
That's disgusting.
No, it's not! Here.
Bye!
This stop
is Hosan Police Station.
Hosan Police Station.
Damn it. Where is she?
Hello? Hey.
Did Somi leave?
But I didn't ask you to send me underwear.
That's strange.
She left a while ago.
Okay.
YEEUN
- Yeah...
- There's...
- Yeeun, what...
Wait...
Honey!
Honey?
Yeeun? Yeeun!
Yeeun!
- Honey.
- Yeeun.
Hello, Detective!
- What's this?
- I'm here for my money.
You little...
Honey, go inside.
- I'll...
- Lady, stay right there.
She should hear this too.
Your daughter's life is at stake.
What? Somi's not home?
What? She's not here.
You asshole.
You son of a bitch!
- Where's Somi?
- Let go of me.
Where is she, fucker?
She's very smart.
- You asshole.
- You raised her well.
Motherfucker.
I'll kill you.
So why did you steal
my precious money? Huh?
Look at what happened.
You brought this upon yourself!
- I said I'd return it.
- Do you even have it?
I'll come up with it at all costs!
Fuck, do you think I'm stupid?
I told you I was watching.
Detective, I gave it some thought.
You're protecting Kim Gukho.
I have 20 billion won in front of me.
Why settle for a billion?
Bring Kim Gukho to me.
We can make an exchange.
Him for your daughter.
A clean swap. I swear.
Don't you know
- the police force is there?
- Bring him alive.
Got it?
I have to kill him. That's the rule.
How can I bring him now? Damn it.
That's your problem.
I feel kind of sorry for Somi.
Oh, right.
If the cops come after me first,
- you'll get a can of her fingers.
- You piece of shit!
I'm going to kill you today! Just die!
Can she play the cello
without fingers?
- How will she play?
- If you touch a single hair,
I swear I'll kill you then. Got it?
Yeah.
I'll get going now.
I'll call with her phone.
Don't follow me out.
Honey?
- Honey...
- Honey.
It'll be okay.
Nothing will happen to Somi. I'll...
I'll take care of this.
- What do we do?
- Don't worry. It's fine.
Our Somi...
What about Somi?
Somi. What do we do?
- Somi...
- Honey.
Yeeun, calm down.
It'll be okay.
Oh.
Who are you?
Ah, yes, hello.
I'm Kim Gukho's attorney.
And?
I have something to discuss with you.
Can you open the door for me?
- I have nothing to discuss.
- No, wait.
It'll just take a moment.
Mom?
The documents you left behind.
I looked over them.
An uncontested divorce will be difficult
with these conditions.
The issue regarding custody
is indeed something
that can be negotiated
between both parties,
but a unilateral written statement
of relinquishing custody will have...
no legal effect.
Don't tell that to me.
You can speak with my attorney.
Your son is...
He's a genius violinist.
But lately, it seems
he's more famous as Kim Gukho's son.
If this drags on,
you'll get mixed up with him
over custody issues.
Are you okay with that?
HUMAN ANATOMY II
Don't you mess with my son!
I'll kill him and everyone else.
There's something I didn't tell you.
I'm recording this.
Call me if you change your mind.
Your son's innocent.
OFFICER PARK
Yes, Lieutenant Baek.
Hey, Officer Park.
I have a favor to ask.
Track the location of a phone for me.
It's urgent.
Yes, that's not difficult.
Who is it?
Yeah, it's my daughter.
Don't ask anything else.
Can you just do it quickly?
Yes, I understand.
Can you text me the number?
TO HOSAN
Is that it?
Where did it go next? Find it.
- It's Route 59.
- Keep playing it.
What's wrong with that?
I think the security cameras
here are broken.
There isn't a bypass road here.
Fuck.
Enforce it! Enforce it!
Kim Gukho threatens
public safety! Execute him!
Execute him! Execute him!
We can't live with the anxiety!
Ensure public safety!
Ensure it! Ensure it!
Castrate sex offender Kim Gukho!
Castrate him! Castrate him!
Give Kim Gukho
the death penalty! Execute him!
Execute him! Execute him!
Ban sex offender,
Kim Gukho, from Hosan City!
Ban him! Ban him!
We can't live with the anxiety!
Ban Kim Gukho!
Ban him! Ban him!
Castrate sex offender Kim Gukho!
Castrate him! Castrate him!
You may go in.
Lift your arms, please.
You may come in.
I am...
Kim Gukho's son.
- Excuse me?
- I'm his son.
I'm here to see my dad.
Kim Gukho's son is here.
His son is here? Send him in.
Go inside.
Mr. Kim, your son is here.
My son?
My son is here?
Send him in! Now!
He's going in now.
Kim Gukho, you bastard!
Leave Hosan City right now!
You scumbag!
My son...
You've grown so much.
So much.
Get in here.
Let your dad hug you. Come on.
I'm glad you're here.
I'm so glad you're here.
Let's go inside, okay? This is your house.
Come on in. Come on.
You punk.
You're so frail.
This won't do. Come here.
Let's get you something to eat, okay?
I have a lot of money.
I'll buy you everything you want to eat.
- Alcohol.
- Alcohol?
I want...
to drink with you, Dad.
You want to drink with me?
Really?
Yeah!
You're old enough to drink.
That's right. Yeah!
You should learn how to drink from me!
Wait a second.
Hang on.
Hey, Mr. Lee.
My son's at my house right now. Yeah.
It's not that.
Can you order in a nice whiskey
and dishes for us?
Korean, Chinese, Western, Japanese.
Order every land, sea,
and sky animal there is!
Come if you have time. Okay.
Yeah, okay. Bye.
Dongha, come here.
Look at what I did.
Thinking about you,
I folded each one by hand.
Do you remember?
You loved tigers.
Dad, I...
Yeah? What?
Can I see my room for a second?
Your room?
I didn't clean up.
Yeah, of course.
This is your house.
Go ahead.
Dongha!
I have beer. Do you want some?
Well...
Let's drink when the food gets here.
Okay, go ahead.
Ah.
Dongha, come out!
The food is here!
I'll be right there!
Mom,
it seems we have forgotten
the emotional pain we've been living with
for some time now.
I thought we could live happily
without that jerk in our lives.
Here you go.
But because of this incident...
I'm paying you handsomely.
I realized we'll have to live
with this label
and be in pain for the rest of our lives.
I'm okay with people
pointing their fingers at me...
- Goodbye.
- ...but I can't endure seeing you
in pain any longer.
You've carried the pain for me
all this time,
so now,
I'll bear that pain for you instead.
I'm sorry, Mom.
Come here.
Sit down.
This is a fine whiskey.
Son, let me pour you a glass.
Here.
There you go.
Are you okay?
Are you?
Mr. Kim, your wife is here.
Yeah.
It's nice to gather like this as a family.
Search her thoroughly, okay?
- Father.
- Yeah?
I'll pour you a glass too.
Yeah, sure.
Here.
I feel great today!
You little punk!
How dare you! You little bastard!
You bastard!
How dare you swing a knife at your father?
Did your mom put you up to this?
Did she put you up to this, you shit?
You little fucker...
Damn it...
Dongha.
Dongha?
Honey...
She's coming out!
Didn't she just go in?
What's that? Is that blood?
- She must be hurt!
- I...
I killed Kim Gukho.
I did it!
I killed Kim Gukho!
Translated by Suyun Mounce