Hei Ba
You're really amazing
I knew my taste wasn't wrong
What are you doing?
There are so many people here
Behave yourself
So what?
You are my idol
The man who appears most in my dreams
I want to
give you a surprise
Don't tell me it's about Chairman Li
Sort of
This...
This isn't appropriate
What's inappropriate about it?
For this matter
my dad and I
talked until our mouths were dry
How about
we talk in private
Ten years
For this matter, I
worked tirelessly for ten years
Hei Ba
I...
I know
Don't say it
It's bad for your reputation
Reputation?
You don't think I'm going to...
Everyone
Today
in the name of the Billiards Association
I want to clarify something to everyone
Please welcome Mr. Cheng Ye to the stage
Ten years ago
at the Chaoli Cup
National Youth Championship
the champion, Cheng Ye
due to suspicion of match-fixing
had his results cancelled
It has now been verified
that this was a frame-up by his opponent
Lang Jiu
Therefore
on behalf of the Chaoli Group
I apologize to Mr. Cheng Ye
And in the name of the Billiards Association
clarify to the public
that we revoke the penalty against Cheng Ye
regarding his ten-year ban
and restore his
champion title
Good, good, good!
Good! That's great!
Hei Ba
This moment
we have all waited ten years for it
I'll be waiting for you at the new Chaoli Cup
Go for it
Hei Ba
Many people ask
what our relationship is
Tell me
how should I answer?
Best buddies for life
Get out of here
You...
You today
did you think I was going to confess publicly?
Of course
not
If I said yes
would you accept?
Don't say anymore
I already know everything
I wouldn't stoop to forcing you
But getting a reward from you
isn't too much, is it?
You're at it again
You're here
Seems I came at a bad time
Then
let's drink this wine another day
Don't
Don't go
I owed you guys a bottle of wine last time
Now
I'm here to fulfill my promise
So
You left early
to go get the wine?
Yeah.
Salon-Boli
Champagne House.
Why is it exactly the same as the one I brought?
Special Series:
Innocence Speaks for Itself.
Ah.
You two really are on the same wavelength.
Congratulations.
Champion.
Hei Ba.
You're so handsome.
Don't touch.
Drink.
Keep drinking.
Where is Missy?
She went back.
As for Jiang Nanshuo,
what do you plan to do?
Right now, he
has his hands full.
I want to make things even worse for him.
Hei Ba,
I want to release that video.
Let public opinion completely crush him.
Crush him so he can never rise again.
We'll hand the evidence of Liheng Group fixing matches
and Nine Heavens Media's illegal deals to the police,
to bring him down instantly.
Jiang Nanshuo has always, in front of the media,
maintained a facade of being a dashing gentleman.
Only by letting the truth
be fully exposed to the light,
forming a tsunami of public opinion no one can suppress,
can we completely destroy him.
I must make him
tear off this disguise with his own hands.
Make him personally destroy
everything he has painstakingly built.
I want to settle this once and for all.
But that is...
Wei Wei's bloody scar from ten years ago.
But uncovering this scar
can protect countless other girls from bleeding.
For my ten years,
I had you and Lin Lu to clear my name.
For Wei Wei's ten years,
it's time someone stood up for her.
I want everyone to know
that Wei Wei's death
was never an accident.
It was Jiang Nanshuo's
premeditated murder.
Hello
This is Hao Dai
Do you need loan services?
President Jiang
When will you give me the money you promised?
You have a final 24 hours
If you fail to pay off the debt in time,
you will be blacklisted for dishonesty.
Trash
You're all trash
What "Five Little Dragons"?
Just a bunch of lowly reptiles
I will crush you all
I will never hand over Liheng Group to anyone
Never
Boss
Bad news
Liheng Group involved in major illegal activities
Exposing Nine Heavens Media's pornography ring
Get out
Liheng Group acquired
Brother Nan
Revealing the truth buried for ten years
Inside story of the female college student's death
Jiang Nanshuo suspected of
Where did you go?
You want to leave me too?
Here is ten million
It's all the money I could raise
Worthy of being my woman
Different from that bunch of trash
What?
You raised money for me,
so you've grown wings?
Do you dare to leave me?
I wouldn't dare
You know what's good for you
Tell me
Next,
what do you plan to do?
The most important thing right now
is to quickly refute the rumors for Liheng
We can launch a charity livestream
to restore the Group's reputation
Hei Ba
I will make the nightmare of ten years ago repeat itself
And drive you out of the billiards world for good