Everything you did back then,
I'm paying it all back.
Don't you want to know the truth about your ban?
That report of yours...
was actually mine.
What did you say?
Let me go,
and I'll tell you.
Speak.
Don't be in such a rush.
Actually, you only have yourself to blame.
Who told you back then
to refuse to fix the match?
So,
Jiang Nanshuo ordered me to perjure myself
and report you for match-fixing.
Hei Ba,
I really should thank you
for taking that ten-year ban for me.
So it was you all along.
You bunch of scumbags!
You jerks!
Don't get angry just yet.
I have another wonderful show
prepared for you.
An even better show.
Wei Wei...
Hei Ba...
Jiang Nanshuo!
You jerk!
Are you even human?
Why get so worked up?
Didn't my woman sleep with you for a night, too?
As Wei Wei's ex-boyfriend,
you really are a failure.
To not know what she went through before she died.
Go to hell!
Kill me if you have the guts!
Nan-ge!
Don't do it here.
Come with me.
Let go of me!
Take him away.
Move!
Wait.
You want to play with me?
I'll destroy you.
It's as easy as crushing an ant.
Throw him out.
Let's go.
I'll see myself out.
I've found the recently world-famous
Five Little Dragons of the East.
Rumor has it,
aside from Captain Jack,
no one can beat them.
Wouldn't it be better to just get Captain Jack?
After the Inescapable Net Tournament,
Captain Jack never appeared again.
What if he suddenly shows up?
Why don't we
set a threshold for the competition?
Require a substantial deposit
to receive an invitation.
That way,
all the contestants
will be under our control.
However...
However what?
The Five Little Dragons have a big appetite.
With Liheng Group's current cash flow,
we can't satisfy their demands.
No matter how big their appetite,
I have a way
to make them spit it all out after the match.
How much are we short?
At least half.
This is 40% of Liheng Group's shares.
Pledge it to the Chaoli Group.
Qujiang's wealthiest, the Chaoli Group?
Isn't that too risky?
Chaoli Group has always wanted to acquire Liheng.
Nothing ventured, nothing gained.
Do as I say.
Understood.
You're crazy!
You...
What do you want?
What are you doing?
Kidnapping a woman in broad daylight?
You've got some nerve!
You dare touch the boss's woman?
I'm taking you away.
Recently, Jiang Nanshuo
to revive the group's finances,
is organizing the Five Little Dragons of the East Tournament.
I've lain low for years
just to send him to prison with my own hands.
You go compete.
Defeat them.
Sever all of Liheng's financial arteries.
I just need to win.
Right.
You need to win a match.
I'll handle the rest.
Okay.
Ever since I took over Nine Heavens Media,
I found that recruiting streamers is just a front.
Some of them
are sent to the Red House,
while others
are sent to Kaye Mountain
to perform stripteases
and engage in the sex trade.
Jiang Nanshuo is full of tricks.
After doing so many evil deeds,
he still manages to get away scot-free.
You are someone even more important
than myself.
So no matter what,
I will help you get revenge.
Kaye Mountain must be hiding
even more shady dealings.
The Red House is just one of his bases.
Unfortunately,
I haven't found solid evidence yet.
I have to go there again.
I'll go with you.
Okay.
Let's go.
Who's there?