Your Highness, are you… okay?
What happened, Your Highness?
Well, you see,
there was just a minor accident.
Oh, dear. What happened?
I'll get someone
to clean this up right away.
But what are you doing here,
Royal Tutor Jung?
Royal Scholar Yang wanted me
to escort His Royal Highness.
I just told him that His Royal Highness
would not be able to attend the lecture.
I should attend the lecture today.
Go tell him I changed my mind.
Your Highness but…
JWAJEON
Your Highness.
EPISODE 6
"Spring is born in spring."
"Spring grows in summer."
"Spring is harvested in autumn."
"And spring is treasured in winter."
That is correct.
Oh, Royal Tutor Jung.
His Highness is already here.
I thought you went to go and get him.
Where were you?
Well, there… was a small accident.
Accident? What happened to your finger?
Why… why did…
And you also look like
you have a terrible hangover as well.
"So the scholar said,
the best of the four morals is similar
to the best virtue of the five, sympathy."
"If we decide
to look at the moral values individually,
there are many values."
"But if we look at them as a whole,
one value includes all four moral values.
And this is the truth."
"All these moral values
make up the truth."
"And the universal truth
will be clear as day."
Do you understand?
Why are you staring at each other?
I… wasn't staring at him.
And I see your face is
the very same color as red wine.
What is it, Your Highness?
I… forgot to get my book.
Your book is here.
The one for the evening lecture.
Oh.
Please, will you excuse me.
Don't trouble yourself.
Please stay here.
Don't worry, I will take care of it.
Royal Tutor Jung.
Yes?
You must have time on your hands today.
No. I have a lot of work to do.
Okay. Whatever. Go get a book
from the Crown Prince's office.
His Highness needs it
for the evening lecture.
Go now. Hurry.
DAEHAKYEONUI
JWAJEON
Oh, no.
What… what is it?
Your Highness!
Where on earth are you going?
Your Royal Highness!
Did I do something to upset him?
JWAJEON
Your Highness.
Why do you have this particular book?
JWAJEON
What are you doing with that book?
That is not the one
you were supposed to go get.
I have it because that book belongs to me.
But this book is Dam-i's. No?
See, I transcribed this book myself
for a girl I liked.
I have no idea
what you are even talking about.
I will look for the book myself.
I want you to leave now.
You really don't remember
a court maid named Dam-i?
Back when your grandfather
was still alive,
I had a private audience with you.
And you personally gave me
the present she left for me.
The palace is full
of countless court maids.
How can I remember something
that happened so long ago?
But what about…
you did remember me.
When we first met at…
at the courtesan house, you remembered me.
Well…
I only remembered you because
I thought you were good at flattery,
even for a brazen boy.
Does that answer you?
JWAJEON
Dam-i?
When I was young,
she was a court maid that I liked.
Oh.
The girl from the banquet
who you fell in love with at first sight?
The Crown Prince had
the book I gave to the girl.
The Crown Prince?
Why do you think…
Dam-i just disappeared like that?
She didn't say goodbye to me.
If she's still alive,
she's probably already married, right?
And she must have kids
who look just like her, right?
What a surprise.
I never would have guessed that
you could be a hopeless romantic too.
Didn't you tell me
that you went to off to Ming
because the women in Joseon
weren't good enough for you?
What about you?
Is there someone you like?
Someone I like?
You're very handsome,
and you're wealthy too.
Plus, you're a member
of the royal family with a heart of gold.
There is.
There is? Who is it?
Which clan is she? Is she a relative?
Is she pretty? Is she kind?
Don't say…
you already set the wedding date.
She's very beautiful.
She's warmhearted.
How come you didn't say anything to me?
So when will you introduce me to her?
I'm a good judge of character
with the ladies.
I'm not sure.
I don't even know
if I'll get the chance to do so.
Don't tell me…
that your love is one-sided.
You had a very long week,
and you seem quite fatigued at the moment.
Your Highness, would going
to sleep early be a good idea?
Wait.
Your Royal Highness, what is it?
Do you know how my record…
No.
Do you happen to know how Dam-i's record
has been settled?
Why are you asking me that?
It is my understanding
that your mother had it taken care of
when she was alive.
DAM-I
DAY 21 OF MONTH 4
LEFT THE PALACE DUE TO ILLNESS
What is this regarding?
Why did you come
all the way here this morning
to meet an imprisoned physician?
I'm embarrassed to ask you for a favor,
but my daughter
made a promise to the physician.
So I came here to ask for your help
despite my shame.
I hope you understand my situation.
I thought you were so sure of yourself
even before His Majesty and Lord Sangheon.
But even you, the Minister of Personnel,
need help when it's your child.
Please wait over there.
I'll bring out the physician.
I apologized to that girl.
I didn't only do it
because you told me to.
I also know what is right and wrong.
I came by to tell you that.
Are you surprised to see me here?
Or touched that I came to see you?
Who are you?
What are you doing?
Where… is that physician?
What are you doing here?
LIST OF COURT MAIDS
What is this, may I ask?
I might have been
a bit curt with you the other day.
That court maid…
in fact, she died.
It happened
right after she left the palace…
due to an illness.
DAM-I
LEFT THE PALACE DUE TO ILLNESS
I see.
That explains
why you couldn't remember her.
That girl…
must have been someone special to you.
She was my first love.
She helped me become a better person.
I wanted…
to thank her…
if I ever saw her again.
I guess I won't be able to.
I didn't mean to make you concerned,
Your Royal Highness.
My apologies.
NOKUNGAK
Goodness. What are you doing?
I'm helping you with the laundry.
Do you know the story
behind these deserted quarters?
What story?
A long time ago, a court maid loved a man
who lived outside the palace.
She couldn't overcome
the sadness of unrequited love.
So she hanged herself here in this place.
Afterward, people stopped coming here.
And the deserted quarters
became an eyesore.
So the Kings tried to demolish
this place over generations.
But anyone who tried
either got sick or died
as if they'd been given a terrible curse.
That's what I heard, anyway.
After that, they weren't
able to tear this place down.
So instead, they just closed it.
Well…
aren't you scared
to be alone in a place like this?
Why would I ever be scared?
I like that no one comes here
thanks to that story.
NOKUNGAK
A ghost!
You startled me!
Stop. Wait up!
Wait until I catch you!
Come on, wait up! I'm scared!
I thought you'd be busy
with the reception. What brings you here?
I heard the Crown Prince
ended the lecture early today.
So, is there something wrong then?
Oh, he went to his usual spot.
You know, the spot he always goes to
when he has a lot on his mind.
This place is a true gem.
You'll never find a breeze
more refreshing than up here.
Hyun.
I thought you'd be in Ganghwa
for the reception.
You haven't left yet?
I postponed it to tomorrow.
I have a more important matter
to take care of today.
A more important matter? What is it?
You mentioned you wanted
to have these the other morning.
I happened to remember what you said.
I hope…
you didn't delay your trip
because of this.
Well, it was one reason.
You always told me
that you wanted to run free.
So why do you always stop… here?
Because I have to go back to the palace.
And this is…
the extent of the path I know.
You told me once
that you had traveled
some place far, right?
What all did you find far away from here?
If you keep going
straight past the gate,
is it true that you'll see the ocean,
which is longer and wider
than anyone knows?
Does that really exist?
Yes. It does.
And there is also
a sturdy ship with a big sail as well.
Once you get on the ship,
you can go anywhere.
Even if it's very far.
If you ask me for directions,
I will give them to you.
You can count on it.
You only have an hour left out here.
Unfortunately, in an hour,
the sun will be set.
So until then, why don't you enjoy
the refreshing breeze
and the beautiful view.
I have been working hard lately.
So I can't stop dozing off.
Flowers for
the Crown Prince's quarters?
I wasn't informed about this.
Can you tell me what they are for?
Well, you see…
The thing is--
If I may ask, can I get some flower seeds?
Well, I'm done planting the flowers,
and I do have some left.
Just a few, hmm?
Can't you give me some of the flowers?
Hmm?
Why do you have those?
Oh, these? I want to plant flowers.
I've got a spot picked out.
Mm.
I see.
Thank you…
for looking into her court record.
Yes.
I heard that
you are attending lectures again.
I know you've been busy lately.
Hey! Royal Tutor Jung!
What on earth are you doing?
You have a big problem!
What problem?
Well, the Minister of Personnel
lodged a demand for your resignation.
My resignation?
Royal Tutor Jung Ji-un of the Crown Prince
is in fact Samgaebang's real physician?
Unfortunately, yes, he is, Your Majesty.
If what you're telling me
is the truth,
who is the imprisoned physician
at Hanseong Magistracy?
He used to work at Samgaebang
as a mere assistant, Your Majesty.
Left State Councilor,
I need you to explain this.
You were the one, Councilor,
who recommended Royal Tutor Jung.
Everything that the Minister of Personnel
has presented is true.
Then are you telling us
that you recommended
a lowly physician from the street
to be the royal tutor of the Crown Prince
despite knowing his history?
He may be a lowly physician
from the street,
but he does have wisdom to share.
Your Majesty,
didn't you compliment his wisdom
during the last exam?
Jung Ji-un displays an excellent character
plus, great literary talent
compared to other tutors.
This good-natured man
ran a pharmacy to share
his medical knowledge with the people.
Samgaebang is its name.
You cannot possibly hold
this act of kindness against him.
His history running a pharmacy
isn't the problem.
Hiding this from His Majesty
and the Crown Prince is a crime.
I'm sure that you would all agree.
On top of that, if the Inspector General
went and ordered the closure of Samgaebang
for corrupting public morals
within the community,
then I am confident there must have been
a far bigger issue than meets the eye.
I resented the Minister of Personnel
for not siding with me.
Now he's tipped the scales my way.
He's a difficult man to decipher.
It's too early to celebrate.
You know the Left State Councilor.
He'll probably try to make this go away
by reprimanding a lecturer.
That's why we must help him.
His Majesty expects
extraordinary things from Prince Jehyeon.
Don't you think
it's time for us to finally step up
and weaken the position
of Lord Sangheon and the Crown Prince?
Why did you allow them to live?
I'll explain everything in person
to the Minister of Personnel.
Do you think
you can so easily hold sway over him?
I practically spoon-fed you,
but you couldn't even handle that
and made a mess.
I'm sorry, my lord.
I will do whatever it takes
to handle this.
Of course you will
because your precious son's life
will depend on it.
Let me through,
I must talk to the Minister of Personnel.
-I only need a moment.
-No.
He said he wouldn't meet with you
until His Majesty approves it.
Please leave.
Wait. I only need a moment of his time.
How dare you!
I want you to release them now.
I'll take responsibility for everything.
You will take responsibility?
You've deceived the royal family,
so now your life is in danger.
How will you take responsibility for it?
You could have just punished me
right from the beginning.
Why do you insist on torturing my friends
and putting everyone in danger?
His Majesty will decide
in three days at the morning assembly.
Do whatever it takes
to secure your position until then.
If you fail,
those friends you cherish,
as well as the two of us,
and your dear mother
will not live to see another day.
Your Highness.
Tell me. What has happened?
It looks like
matters have gotten pretty serious quick.
His Majesty will punish Royal Tutor Jung,
and he will also punish his father
for turning a blind eye to his son.
I very much doubt that
Inspector Jung Seok-jo was acting alone.
Everyone must know that he was only doing
what my maternal grandfather
had told him to do.
Anyway, I say it all worked out.
You weren't exactly keen on them.
So driving them out of the palace--
It's getting late.
You can go now, Bok-dong.
Yes?
Oh. Yes, Your Highness.
Are you bothered by the scandal
with Royal Tutor Jung?
You know he's Jung Seok-jo's son.
The one responsible
for murdering the Prince.
And also, the one who tried to kill you,
Your Royal Highness.
I know.
I do.
You must not forget that.
Not ever.
So please do not forget.
It's all my fault that he's in trouble.
The Minister of Personnel
scared me out of my wits.
Maybe… maybe it's not too late?
If I say
I'm the real physician at Samgaebang,
Yeong-ji and Ji-un will live, right?
What nonsense is this?
The Inspector… No.
Ji-un's father told me that…
that if I recant it all,
everyone will be okay.
You idiot. Do you seriously buy that?
Once he hears that, he's more likely
to find a nice place to bury you.
-You dimwit.
-What am I supposed to do?
Ji-un is about to die because of me.
Chief Gu!
You've got to get out of here now.
I'll tell Royal Tutor Jung everything.
So don't do anything stupid, okay?
Say you know nothing.
Stick to that. Got it?
Come on, hurry up!
You know nothing.
My lady!
-My lady.
-Father.
Wait!
-What are you doing?
-They are about to get hurt because of me.
Father.
Just please would you look the other way.
They aren't bad people.
I'm sure it wasn't their intention.
How can we be certain that
they are not bad without any evidence?
I will only see them
as either innocent or as guilty.
Father. Father, please no.
That's enough.
I already reported it to His Majesty.
For now, the decision is in his hands.
Father! Father!
His Majesty will issue a royal order
at tomorrow morning's assembly.
It's unfortunate, but I believe today
will be the last time that I see you.
You haven't been here long…
but I'll remember your lectures
as somewhat useful.
I cannot leave the palace yet.
I'm in need of your help.
You're the only person
who can help me now.
Why do you think that I would help you?
Did you forget that I wanted you gone
more than anybody else
when you first arrived here at the palace?
I know that. That's why
I'm asking you for your help.
You knew from the beginning
that I was a physician at Samgaebang.
But you still accepted me
as your lecturer, anyway.
That was because I lost the wager.
I did promise after all.
Could you keep
your promise to me
just for one more time, Your Highness?
Unfortunately, there's nothing
that I can do for you.
So I advise you to stop asking.
Royal Tutor Jung…
There you are.
Where on earth have you been?
I looked everywhere for you.
What about Jil-geum? He's okay, right?
It's about your father.
I think he's going to
just go and pin the whole thing on him.
I don't know what to do.
I can neither stop him nor support him.
Chief Gu! Chief Gu!
What do you mean, "pin it"?
That fool wants to save you and Yeong-ji.
You don't think
that he'll kill them, do you?
I mean, you cherish them
like your family. Right?
No… Jil-geum. No!
Hey, wait a minute. Tutor Jung!
Tutor Jung, wait!
Your Highness,
Prince Jaeun is here to see you.
You're back.
Was your trip to Ganghwa pleasant?
Yes.
I have something to tell you.
What is it?
Royal Tutor Jung ran Samgaebang
with the sole purpose
of helping poor kids from the slums.
That's what you're telling me?
Yes, Your Royal Highness.
He only accepted
the position at the palace
to save his friends from Samgaebang.
He never wanted the title at all.
-Why are you even telling me all of this?
-Because--
I know Jung Ji-un
is an old friend of yours.
I understand that
you want to help him out.
But this is pointless.
Whatever the reason,
he still broke the code of morals
and deceived our family.
His actions will not be forgiven.
He may be my good friend,
but he's also your tutor.
I'm very tired.
I'm sure you're exhausted
from your trip as well.
We should talk some other time.
I cannot leave the palace yet.
I'm in need of your help.
You're the only person
who can help me now.
What did you wish for?
Do you remember the slum
we passed by earlier on our way here?
Hmm?
I wished that the kids in the slum
would be well fed
and grow up in good health.
That is what I wished for.
What?
It's a parents' job
to take care of their children, though.
Wouldn't you say?
But most of them are orphans.
I grew up there as an orphan too.
My heart breaks for them,
but I don't have the means to help them.
So if I make a wish for them,
perhaps, maybe someone
might help them out one day.
So, tell me. What did you wish for?
Oh. That?
Uh, I don't…
Just a second, Dam-i, hold on.
Young Master.
Why did you do that?
Well, after hearing your wish,
my wish just sounded
so petty and extremely selfish.
-Oh?
-So I changed mine.
My wish is to actually become that someone
who can help those kids.
Should I have not mentioned it?
No.
If I didn't, Jil-geum would be framed
for everything and end up dead.
I couldn't let that happen to him.
Of course, not.
Right!
Royal Tutor Jung is on it.
I'm sure he has come up with a plan.
I doubt that he's gonna kill
his own son. Right.
No. No way, no way.
What if Royal Tutor Jung gets killed too?
The Inspector is capable of doing so.
This is driving me crazy!
What do I do? What do I do now?
Who exactly is going to get killed?
Who are you?
Who… who are you?
Wait a minute.
Where are we going?
Where are you taking me?
Oh. Oh, sir.
-Yeong-ji!
-Jil-geum!
What is this?
-Ji-un!
Are you really…
-going to kill them too, father?
-Step aside.
How much more
can you possibly disappoint me?
I said, step aside.
Are you really going to kill me?
Please let them go.
I beg you.
They will live some place else.
Tell yourself that.
That is the only thing you can do.
-Ji-un!
No!
-What are you doing?
-If I do this…
you have no reason to kill both of them.
If you dare lay a finger on them,
I will never forgive you.
Even if you are my father!
Ji-un!
Lock him up until I return.
-Ji-un!
Take the girl away for now.
Jil-geum!
-Jil-geum!
-Yeong-ji!
Write down what I say.
You were scared, so you lied.
And you are the physician at Samgaebang.
You were scared of your punishment,
so you bought off
guards and escaped. Got it?
No…
Please spare me.
Please let me live!
It's my fault. Please don't kill me.
I heard that Ji-un saved you and that girl
when your lives were in danger.
You can…
pay him back now.
Yeong-ji.
Please spare me…
Yeong-ji…
Please spare me.
I AM THE PHYSICIAN OF SAMGAEBANG
I ESCAPED
BANG JIL-GEUM
Wait. As you promised,
please spare Ji-un and Yeong-ji.
Please don't kill them.
Please…
Please let them live.
I see some crooks
secretly took the prisoners
from Hanseong Magistracy.
As the Crown Prince, I demand
give the prisoners to me.
If you do,
no one will shed
one drop of blood here tonight.
Did Lord Sangheon approve of this?
Was I unclear?
I ordered you
as the Crown Prince of Joseon.
Unless there is a royal command,
no one may dare to disobey.
Your Highness.
Is that what you truly believe?
You must not agree with me,
seeing how you aren't
laying down your weapon and submitting.
If he so much
as moves his hand even one inch,
then I want him dead
and bring his head to me.
What? Don't think
I'll go through with this?
I doubt that my grandfather
will punish his dear grandson
for killing his dog.
What is going on?
Tell me what happened.
Your Highness.
You even took the royal guards with you.
Won't you please tell us
what on earth you were doing?
And what if Lord Sangheon finds out…
Why did you do that?
Why…
why were you so very arrogant,
Your Royal Highness?
Those men took away the prisoners.
I understand that it was on your order,
but it seemed unjust to me.
So I only did
that which I felt must be done.
You're wrong,
Your Royal Highness.
Your moral convictions will not be allowed
to influence your actions.
There is only thing that you must do,
and that is listen to me,
your grandfather,
and never challenge me.
That's it.
Do you understand?
Do not forget.
Whatever path ahead that I choose…
will also be your path.
And if you deviate from that path,
I will never forgive you,
no matter how much I love you.
Get up.
It's time for the assembly.
Where are they? What about my friends?
I need you to tell me
if they're both safe first.
You'll see for yourself
after the morning assembly.
Are they still alive?
You didn't…
kill them, did you?
Let me sum it up.
This man here, Jung Ji-un,
recommended and prescribed
only expensive and rare medicinal herbs
under the pretense of treatments.
Is that true?
Yes, that's true.
There is more.
When I visited Samgaebang,
not only did he make me wait
with the people of low birth,
he also humiliated me
by turning me away
at the gate in front of them.
Jung Ji-un neglected
the custom of our class
and tarnished
the authority of the nobility.
Inspector Jung Seok-jo protected his son.
I ask you to punish them, Your Majesty.
Please punish them,
Your Majesty.
Is everything they said true?
Yes.
It is true.
Here is the punishment…
for Royal Tutor Jung
and the two prisoners.
Royal Tutor Jung Ji-un
of the Royal Institute
ran a clinic called Samgaebang
as a nobleman.
He exploited people and tarnished
the prestige of the nobility.
Moreover, he deceived
me and the Crown Prince
and disgraced the royal family.
So his sentence will be quite severe.
Therefore,
he is no longer a lecturer
for the Crown Prince
and will be banished
after facing 50 lashes.
And those who helped him
to run Samgaebang
will be forced into do manual labor.
If you decide this is the punishment
I deserve, I will accept it.
But without the prisoners,
the punishment can't be executed.
My assistants from Samgaebang are missing.
Please tell me where they are.
What are you talking about?
I thought they were imprisoned
at Hanseong Magistracy.
Your Highness, someone took them away.
Allow me…
to answer that question.
Your Highness.
You turned out to be a
a man of outstanding generosity.
Please allow me to be
in charge of receiving the envoys.
Put your faith in me this time.
I'm truly grateful
for this grand welcome.
That is enough.
You are in the palace of Joseon.
I've asked you to come
so I could show you something interesting.
What the hell do you think you're doing?
Your Royal Highness.
I put my faith in you.
And you disappointed me.