This is all
Prince Wonsan's doing!
I just wanted to confirm
His Majesty is actually a woman.
Really?
The truth you have discovered…
will be buried alongside you.
He is not here. Let's go.
Yes, Commander.
I have something
I have to tell you.
I am…
going to get married.
I do not want to lose you, Your Majesty.
And this is the only way I'm able to…
be sure I can make that happen.
Stop, don't you dare leave!
I didn't say…
that we were finished here.
You can't leave.
Stop now!
I am ordering you.
Forgive me,
Your Majesty.
I'll agree to get married.
I will do whatever you tell me to.
As long as
you keep His Majesty's secret in return.
No matter what happens…
you need to keep it.
EPISODE 18
Oh, my. How gorgeous!
Commander Jung's wife clearly
put a lot of thought into these gifts.
My lady.
Your Highness!
So-eun, hello.
You didn't have to bring anything.
Thank you, Your Highness.
I wish you the best.
And all the planning, how is it?
There are many things left to arrange.
And it still doesn't feel real. Not yet.
I hope you're not tiring yourself out.
Is there something the matter?
No, it's nothing.
Are you upset because of that rumor?
About Lord Jung and His Majesty.
I heard it as well.
Don't worry about it, Your Highness.
You know that it is not true at all.
The rumor will be gone
after he and I are married.
Don't you think about it anymore.
As you instructed earlier,
I talked to the Ministry of Works
about renovations
at the Royal Confucian Academy.
We still have
some leftover rice bags from before.
And we have an excess of roof tiles.
Thus, the materials and workers…
I do not want to lose you, Your Majesty.
And this is the only way I'm able to…
be sure I can make that happen.
So the renovations
can proceed, Your Majesty.
Oh, yes. And Scribe Jung of Seungjeongwon…
Ah. Scribe Jung. Come over here.
Ah. Join us.
Come here, now.
Scribe Jung, he has
some very good news, Your Majesty.
He will be
getting married soon, Your Majesty.
He must make preparations for the wedding
and so he will be very busy.
So would it be all right
if Scribe Kim brings you
the daily reports for the time being?
Yes. Sure.
Then we will take our leave, Your Majesty.
All right, let's go.
I'm still looking for the poisonous herb
we discussed previously.
When we are able to locate it,
we will be able to prove that
all the records from the Royal Secretariat
are entirely fabricated.
Your wedding plans,
how are they coming along?
Well…
That's good.
Thank you for your work.
You are now dismissed.
So were you able to find Lord Changun?
I wish to have a word with His Majesty
about the impending event.
I know. It's coming up soon.
And also, Scribe Jung's marriage
is happening soon too.
What do you think of that?
Marriage? He's getting married?
You haven't heard?
I thought that the two of you
were best friends.
Does His Majesty know?
Are you all right, Your Majesty?
It's nothing.
I really think
that's enough practice, don't you?
You could get hurt
if you're not careful, Majesty.
I said it's nothing.
Your Majesty.
I just need to have
at least this right now.
Let me, please.
Marriage?
What is this nonsense?
It's not nonsense, though.
A stupid rumor
has swayed you to act to drastically?
How could you make her care for you
when your feelings
are completely shallow and selfish?
Okay. You're right about me, all right?
These shallow feelings were all I had.
Okay?
What?
We never had a chance
to be together forever, anyway.
I had to do this.
Bastard!
Why… are you doing this?
You must have a good reason, I know.
There's a strange rumor circulating
at the courtesan house in the Capital.
A man resembling Lord Changun
has been claiming
His Majesty is part of a set of twins,
and may also be a woman.
I was told you wanted to see me, Lord.
Yes.
I called you here because
there was just something I had to ask.
Your Majesty,
your herbal tonic is ready.
You can enter.
Fortunately, Your Majesy,
the swelling will not persist.
Oh, your royal physician is here.
Eunuch Hong, what have you done?
F-forgive me. I don't know what happened.
-Check to see how badly he has been hurt.
-Yes.
-Court Lady Kim.
-Let me see.
No, wait, I'm fine.
-I told you I'm fine.
-My goodness.
-Hold on, stop it.
-Did it hurt you at all?
Oh, no.
Thankfully, it wasn't too hot. I'm--
Well, that's good. You may leave.
Yes, Your Majesty.
I feel awful about this.
His Majesty
hurt his hand while training.
I was just there to examine it.
I see. And is he okay?
Yes. I also took his pulse,
and it seems strong.
That means he can share
his bed with the Queen.
Mm. I see.
Keep an eye on him.
Report everything, no matter how small.
Yes, my lord.
See. As we expected.
Busohwa.
Was it really necessary
to search everywhere just to find that?
Use your brain sometimes
and not just that body of yours.
I thought you were smart.
Did you look into the sonangcho?
Today, I have an appointment
at the pharmacy to buy
-so-nang-cho.
-Really?
What did I tell you?
I told you I could find it.
Are you sure, though? When? Where?
It'll be dangerous,
make sure that you go there with Eun-seo.
Eun-seo? Not here.
He is really busy.
He said His Majesty gave him a task.
He left for Pyeongan Province.
By the way,
you are about to get married,
and your face looks terrible.
How did you bust your lip?
You need to take care of yourself.
I know it was your father's idea,
you can still try
to show a little interest, you know.
Ji-un, the Inspector General's daughter
she has a kind heart
and also, she's a nice lady.
Ji-un. Ji-un.
And don't forget that
she also takes such good care of us.
I just thought that I would come over.
I did not know that you would be here.
We have received the wedding gifts.
It must have been difficult
to choose them.
And I heard that your mother
selected everything on her own.
Yes.
What happened to you?
Oh.
It's nothing.
Please use this.
Lord Jung, tell me.
Do you not want to get married?
It's just that…
I am sorry.
And…
I will try to do better.
It's just going to take a while.
So-eun will be marrying Jung Ji-un,
the first-born son of Commander Jung.
Your Highness.
You must prepare for the evening.
All right.
So, Your Highness.
I was summoned
by the Chief State Councilor, so I went.
And so then, what did he want?
Your Highness, please forgive me.
Yu-gong.
I couldn't help but tell him everything.
That you and His Majesty
use two sets of blankets.
What?
How could you disobey
my direct order like that?
I was terrified
when Lord Sangheon was questioning me.
Beginning tonight,
we will be sharing one blanket.
What are you saying?
There are awful rumors
going around the palace.
And if we are to put an end to these lies,
then this has to be done.
Those rumors…
they are nothing more than rumors.
I will tell them
to bring another set of blankets.
For a husband and a wife,
there cannot be two sets of blankets.
My Queen.
I don't know everything, but I think
I know what a Queen is meant to do.
She needs to be the mother of the state
and that means let her subject then become
like her very own children to look after.
But without having carried
or given birth to a child of my own,
how could I understand what being
a real mother even means and cherish them?
Producing an heir
so we can continue the royal lineage,
it's the reason I exist and
the Queen's most important responsibility.
Help me to fulfill my duty
as the Queen, I beg you, Your Majesty.
Please stop what you're doing.
I don't wanna hurt you
more than I already have, My Queen.
Why won't you embrace me?
Can't you just hold me?
Please, My Queen, you must stop.
You must.
Is the problem your preference?
Is it that you prefer
to love men, Your Majesty?
Or is it because your heart
already lies with another woman?
Please answer me.
Is it that you don't desire me?
Or is your behavior for another reason?
-No, it's not you.
-Well, then, if that's truly the case
why won't you allow us to sleep together?
I really need to know what's wrong.
I would rather you select another.
If this is something
I cannot fulfill…
choose a royal concubine
to produce an heir, please. You must.
Listen to me.
This has nothing to do
with how I feel about you.
And I know…
how strange all of my actions look to you.
But soon
I will tell you everything.
I swear that I will explain exactly
how there was simply no other choice.
I promise you this.
I'll make sure you know.
I swear.
My father found out about…
His Majesty's secret.
What?
I would do anything
to protect this secret.
No matter the cost.
Hyun…
you must pretend to know nothing.
I beg you.
Sir, someone came to the pharmacy
asking about sonangcho.
Father.
Why are you here?
Sonangcho, is that the reason
you came here?
Did you also know the truth about
how the late King was poisoned?
What are you trying to do
by unearthing this now?
I will get to the bottom of his death.
If you reveal the truth
about all that's happened,
then you will also expose your own father.
If this is your crime then,
you must face the repercussions also.
Lord Sangheon
watches this pharmacy closely.
His eyes are always on it.
You mean…
we're being ambushed?
Jil…
Jil-geum is on his way.
It's too late for him, all right.
You better just let it go.
So he should… suffer again because of me?
When you hurt me,
I thought my life was done,
so friends were
the only things motivating me.
If it wasn't for them,
I would have been full of despair…
and ended it.
Excuse me,
but how much farther must we go?
Do you even have sonangcho?
We are almost there.
I cannot sell
such a rare herb out in the open.
Of course. Yes. It is quite rare.
By the way, why are you
looking for such a deadly herb?
Oh, well,
I have my reasons. You don't wanna know.
Oh! What is this?
He is the man looking for sonangcho.
If you wish to remain breathing,
I suggest you tell me the truth.
Why are you looking
for the herb sonangcho?
Well…
I heard it was a rare,
and I couldn't find it…
Spare me, please.
Now, you're going to tell me
who sent you here.
It was me.
Ji-un, help!
I sent him here.
Ji-un.
We should go, Jil-geum.
Get them!
Stop!
What brings you here tonight?
I will take care of this now.
You can step back.
Lord Sangheon ordered us to find the man
looking for sonangcho
and bring him back at any cost.
I said step back!
Do you understand?
I will report this to Lord Sangheon.
Stand down.
Ji-un.
You were not here this afternoon.
So I picked them out for you myself.
I wanted to thank you
for your offer to help out.
Well, of course I would.
You do not have to get me anything.
I heard that Lord Jung cherishes you
and your brother like his own siblings.
Could I consider
you two my siblings as well?
I really want to get along with you
and your brother like my own family.
Of course.
Yeong-ji! Yeong-ji!
Ji-un!
-What's wrong with him?
-He's bleeding. Get something!
Oh, no. Ji-un!
Ji-un, please wake up.
Ji-un, come on!
What happened here? How did he get hurt?
Well… I don't know.
Has the news
reached Lord Sangheon?
A number of people heard Lord Changun
discussing the twins while he was drunk,
that could easily spread.
And… I assume no one's found my uncle yet?
If Lord Sangheon can make my uncle talk,
it means that my life is in danger.
Go find my uncle first.
Yes.
Were you really behind this?
I want to know what it is you're plotting?
I told you to find my uncle, didn't I?
You must end this.
Our uncle is dead.
Are you certain?
Did you see who was responsible?
How could you have done something so evil?
I don't understand
why you're doing all of this.
You don't, huh?
It all makes sense.
I did always wonder
why you were so loyal to His Majesty.
Hyun, you always knew, didn't you?
That His Majesty was a woman.
Your heart has been leading you
down this road for too long, Hyun.
-Find him!
-Yes!
I didn't expect that Lord Sangheon
would be so quick to seek me out.
You cannot go like this.
Come with me to see His Majesty.
If you give up and ask for forgiveness,
I will look for a way
to keep you alive, brother.
It is too late. Now stand down.
Look at you. You'd betray
your own flesh and blood, brother.
And all because of this girl.
And what will be next,
after you meet Lord Sangheon?
I will take what is mine.
You can't, please!
A true King is not a woman, Hyun.
Escort him back.
Please have a seat, Lord Wonsan.
You faked Lord Changun's death
to dethrone His Royal Majesty
when he was Crown Prince?
It seems that you still haven't let go
of your vain desires.
You've seen
the umbilical cord already and…
you think my desires are in vain?
You are the one harboring vain desires,
and still pressing onwards,
while knowing how poor your situation is.
The palace is quiet.
So you must not be aware that
His Majesty was attacked by assassins.
His coat string was ripped
during the attack.
And Commander Jung
was also present at the scene, I heard.
I wonder why he hid it from you.
You must be feeling quite anxious.
A young king is infatuated with a man
and refuses to sleep with the Queen.
I'm sure you're aware by now
that the recipient
of His Majesty's passion is a man.
Unless, for some reason,
you want to end your life tonight,
I don't think you will benefit
from provoking me by telling evil lies.
Do you remember?
Ten years ago,
shortly after
the royal preceptor was killed,
His Majesty acted almost like he was
a whole new person for quite a while.
Back then, we thought
it was he was just in shock.
But… think about it.
It wasn't even His Majesty anymore.
How dare you!
How dare you ridicule His Majesty
with such a violent, ridiculous claim?
For that I should
rip your tongue right out!
There's still
an opportunity to keep your power.
Listen. You can let me be of use to you.
What do you say?
Join forces with me, Lord.
Lock him away right now!
I will leave on my own.
Soon, there will be no choice
except for you to come over to my side.
What, are you saying that he knows?
My uncle was sent to attack you
on my older brother's order.
I believe that he plotted this
to find out if you are a woman.
He is on his way to tell
Lord Sangheon about it right now.
What will we do? Oh, dear!
Court Lady Kim! I'm right here.
Your Majesty.
What should we do?
We need to be the first ones to act.
What Lord Wonsan knows
is still only a speculation.
So my grandfather
won't be rushing to move just yet.
Have you had
a restful night's sleep?
Yes.
Chief State Councilor,
what brings you here
all the way to my quarters?
Last night,
foolish thoughts consumed me
and distracted me from my sleep.
I have been hearing talk
that things between
His Majesty and you are not well.
It is…
so much foolishness.
His Majesty cherishes me,
I assure you, my lord.
Soon, there will be good news I'm sure.
So please don't worry about it, my lord.
Ji-un.
You okay? Can you sit up?
What happened, huh? Where's Jil-geum?
You should worry about yourself.
Jil-geum is going to be fine.
Don't worry about him.
Lady So-eun
looked after you all night.
She actually just left.
Your Majesty, I…
miss you so much, Majesty.
So much.
I wanna be by your side always.
The sonangcho,
have you heard anything else?
Well, it seems
they are still looking for it.
I'm sure Physician Seo obtained
the herb and gave it to my grandfather.
We must go and capture him
and get him to confess.
But what if he does not
make a full confession?
You will only be making
Lord Sangheon more suspicious.
You're completely right, Your Majesty.
He has already begun
to have suspicions towards you,
and I think he's going to find out
about the truth soon.
Whatever we do, we need to hurry, Majesty.
Get Eun-seo and send him out right away.
Why did you not tell me
that His Majesty was attacked
by Lord Changun?
We were coming back
from Officer Yoon's grave.
And so, His Majesty
did not wish for it to be known.
You followed royal orders?
But then, when I tasked you
with bringing me Lord Changun,
why didn't you say anything then?
Forgive me.
I thought it would not be
too late to inform you
after I had confirmed it
and captured him first.
I see. You may leave now.
Commander Jung,
I need you to keep an eye on him.
Yes, my lord.
Your Majesty.
Eun-seo, where is he now?
He just arrived at Seonwonjeon,
the Royal Portrait Hall.
What brings you here
at this late hour?
Where were you going
at this time of night?
I just thought I'd go get some fresh air,
because I was feeling a bit lonely.
Well, then if you don't mind
I would like to have
a little chat with you.
I have many very interesting things
I wish to share.
Yes. That sounds quite nice.
Your uncle was presumed
to have killed himself,
but he is actually alive,
and he appeared
to make an attempt on your life.
But it turned out
he was not trying to kill you.
He was trying to confirm
if a ridiculous rumor was true.
What rumor is that?
That the King was born a twin in fact.
Also, that the King
shared the womb with a sister.
That, in and of itself,
would make things difficult
for you to keep the throne.
But he also claimed
the siblings had secretly been switched,
and that the girl twin now
sits on the throne as the King of Joseon.
How about that?
Come now, Your Majesty,
it's quite amusing.
Yes, it's amusing, but you know,
people from outside the palace say
that a flesh-eating monster
lives deep inside the palace.
When I was young,
I was afraid of meeting it face to face.
So I never left my chamber at night.
But after a while,
I realized those people
were actually telling stories of you.
Well…
it seems all these rumors
get thrown around
and absurdly exaggerated.
They can be.
But Your Majesty…
the rumor is not a completely untrue one.
It's true that when you were born,
you did have a twin sister.
And when I was informed
of what had happened,
I ordered her to be killed that night.
You had my twin sister killed?
Yes.
And the people who knew about
your sister they are all gone as well.
I made sure they were killed.
But why did you do that?
How could you take
such an utterly cruel action, my lord?
It was all done for you,
Your Majesty.
At the palace,
it is not like with the commoners.
Witnessing the birth of twins
is considered an omen here.
The late King who ascended
the throne after murdering his nephew
was more afraid than anyone else that
people were going to find out about them.
Therefore, I was
in an impossible situation.
I had two choices,
I could kill you and also your sister
or I could choose
to kill your sister alone and keep it…
my secret.
And why are you choosing this night
as your chance to tell me this?
If anyone else were ever
to find out about this,
I will see to it that they are all killed.
Rest assured, if anyone tries to hurt you
I will have them killed.
I truly do hope that…
you acknowledge
my loyalty to you, Your Majesty.
As long as you continue to do so,
I will…
have no regrets for what I've done.
They can call me a monster.
You must leave the palace now.
Go and gather your things.
You…
Your Majesty.
I can't go, Majesty.
You can't just make both of us go.
I will never leave you!
I'm going to stay right here by your side.
I understand, but it's too dangerous
for you to be here.
My grandfather will hold you both,
so he might get me to tell the truth.
But what about…
What will you do now?
I will reveal that my grandfather
ordered my father killed
and plotted treason.
I have the ledger from Yeoyeon,
and if I can find sonangcho
through Royal Physician Seo,
I know I can do it.
Everyone, the entire royal court
is under Lord Sangheon's thumb.
You were the one who said
that it isn't enough to bring him down.
After everything, I must try.
You will not stay away for long.
I will make this work. I don't care how.
I will get you back.
You need to be right here at my side when
I pass on the throne to Gyeom.
-No.
-Your Majesty.
Trust in me, okay?
I will…
I will not die.
You two know better than anyone…
all that I have endured to get here.
We've become
a hindrance to you, haven't we?
Forgive us, please.
I understand
you have the body of the girl.
Show me her body at once.
Do you not trust your man,
Jung Seok-jo anymore?
Ten years ago, shortly after
the royal preceptor was killed,
His Majesty acted almost like he was
a whole new person for quite a while.
Commoners play
with childish toys like this.
So why might you have it?
That's mine…
Crown Prince,
what is your opinion?
Is marriage what you desire?
Please be more considerate of them.
Could we wait a little to start
making our plans for this wedding?
What I mean
is that you were wrong,
and you should not have gotten involved
in the murder of a lowly girl.
You think that girl's life was petty?
There is no such thing as a petty life.
And not a single person
deserves to die for no reason.
Please take care of them, Hyun.
I will come back right away
as soon as they are safe.
Bok-dong.
Take good care
of Court Lady Kim, all right?
Yes, Your Majesty.
I will take good care of her.
Do not worry yourselves.
Once this is over,
I'll come and get you right away.
Oh, you had better.
Even if the hour is later than midnight.
We will wait for you with the lanterns on.
You need to come to us.
Come on. Follow me.
I don't know
what His Majesty plans to do alone.
There's a place…
that we need to stop at.
It's very late.
Why would you come here?
We're here
because I've got something to say.
YEON-SEON
His Majesty he was
at one time a court maid in the palace.
And for a long while,
the King used the name…
Dam-i back then.
Commander Jung pursued
and killed the Prince, thinking he was
Dam-i, since he was wearing her clothes.
It was His Majesty's wish
that you'd never be told all this but…
I think that your father
is the greatest threat
to His Majesty at this moment.
So I'm asking you
to keep His Majesty safe.
Protect His Majesty,
I beg of you.
Lotus flowers
brought me to you,
so I thought that
the name would be fitting.
Yeon-seon.
She said to give these to you
if I ever met you.
LONGING, NOT
She told me they would help you
stay strong when things get hard
just like they had been helpful for her.
That court maid…
LIST OF COURT MAIDS
…in fact, she died.
That girl must have been
someone special to you.
She was my first love.
We were born twins.
Me and my brother,
the son of the Crown Prince.
After my brother died…
I suddenly had no choice
but to take his place.
I may not be able…
to tell you everything.
JWAJEON
YEON-SEON
Dam-i.
Is it you, Your Majesty?
Dam-i?
I think we
should break off our engagement.
One who covets
the crown must be coldhearted.
-I am sorry, Hyun.
-No! Jaeun!
Forgive me, I couldn't.
Is this the kind of life
you want to live?
No. Kill me instead!
He didn't do anything wrong!
The Crown Prince's twin sister
did not die that night.
I'm his twin sister.