Take it.
No, don't!
Commander Yoon…
Where is he?
He didn't make it.
But he told me
to make sure this was delivered to you.
Commander Yoon said that…
you two were friends.
He's resting peacefully by the stream…
that leads from Yanghwajin
right to Mount Jeoldu.
You should visit him.
Uncle, how are you even…
Your Majesty.
Father.
Get them!
Stop him!
Protect His Majesty.
What? Damn it.
Are you all right, Your Majesty?
Were you injured?
I'm okay.
What about the assassins, where are they?
Please forgive me.
My uncle. I'm sure he's responsible.
Wait, but…
Lord Changun died by suicide months ago.
It would be wise to keep this between us
for the time being.
Even if we say
my uncle is behind the attack,
no one would believe us anyway.
Of course, Your Majesty.
I will scout up ahead.
Follow me and stay alert.
EPISODE 17
Well, is His Majesty a woman?
I don't…
It seemed like it, but…
I don't know. Maybe not.
What?
Don't scare me like that.
Uh, well, you see,
Commander Jung came out of nowhere.
What do you mean Lord Changun
attacked His Majesty?
That's impossible.
We all know that he died.
I was thinking about that too.
It's not like he can come back to life.
Are you sure that you are
not injured at all, Your Majesty?
Mm-hm.
Why was Commander Jung there, though?
But wait. Do you think it's possible
that he's aware of your secret?
I don't think so… yet.
Even if he saw anything,
he wouldn't be able to tell anyone.
The fact that I exist
could very well be the thing that
brings him down as well.
He'll stay silent for no other reason
than to cover up his mistake.
I see.
Your Majesty,
Lord Jaeun shall enter.
Word is an assassin attacked
at Officer Yoon's burial site.
Yes.
However, the public can't know.
It will only lead to panic.
I understand.
Still, they say your uncle led the attack.
Is that true?
I know it seems impossible,
but I am certain of it.
I will look into this matter.
Lord Changun and my brother
have always been close,
so perhaps he is already aware.
Thank you for looking into it.
Were you also there
visiting Commander Yoon's grave?
Mother told me that you two
have been friends a long time.
Is His Majesty well?
Yes.
Let him know that I will report back
once I find out more.
Then will you also…
be informing Lord Sangheon?
You expect me to believe that
a man coming back from the dead?
Once I look into it,
if anyone has more to inform
the Chief State Counselor about this,
it should be His Majesty.
How was your conversation?
Does Commander Jung…
He was his usual calm self, so it's
probably likely he didn't see anything.
I see. Hmm. That's good to know.
Here you go.
The attack must have alarmed you.
This will help with that.
So, uh, I wanna ask about Kang Eun-seo.
Would it be all right if I suggest
that he stay at Samgaebang?
Samgaebang?
Yes. From what I can gather,
he needs time to heal.
There is no better place for that.
While he's there he can also help my
friends to look into the poisonous herb.
I have been worrying a lot
about him lately,
so that would definitely ease my mind.
Mm.
Have we met before, huh?
I was born in the Year of the Snake.
So I'll drop the formalities, okay?
No?
Uh, it was Ji-un who sent you here.
It was, wasn't it?
So you can make yourself at home.
Yeah?
I brought this for you.
The tea is sure to warm you up--
Oh!
Are you all right?
Uh, please let me know
if you like any more.
I've brewed an extra batch.
That'd be great.
Are you kidding?
Yeong-ji, this tea is not cheap!
Well, hurry up and drink.
It's time you earn your keep.
Okay?
Hurry. Come on. Now, now. Let's hurry.
Aah! Anyway, the palace
has lots of herbs suppliers,
but this is the largest.
Welcome. So what can I get for you today?
Oh, well…
From what I hear, you sell the good kind.
Isn't that right?
Good kind? For what?
The liver or for the eyes?
No, that's not what I mean.
You know. The sort of herb that's rare…
My lord, it is good to see you.
Have you brought in
the herbs that I requested?
As if you need to ask.
Uh, this way, my lord.
So, are they for the royal infirmary
or are they for Lord Sangheon?
They are actually for me this time.
Ah, I see. Well, we have a fresh batch
of dried foxglove and barberry root
which are of good quality.
Please take a look.
The umbilical cord of twins?
I happened to stumble on His Majesty's
while moving his placenta chamber.
According to the physician
who examined it,
it undoubtedly came from twins.
Are you saying that you
were not aware of this at all?
But that is preposterous.
The physician must be mistaken.
Twins within the royal family?
He should pay with his life
for even uttering those words.
You have him brought to me right away
and he will be punished severely
for insulting His Majesty.
Your Highness, please forgive me.
I did not mean to cause any disturbance.
It would be wise of you not to speak
of such preposterous matters either.
One might think you are hoping to lead
a rebellion against the King.
I would never hope for that.
I wish to see you
because I have been away for a while.
I apologize if this unnecessary concern
has troubled you, Grandmother.
The girl is dead, then?
His Majesty has ordered
the death of everyone
who knows about the twins,
so please bear that in mind.
This secret must be taken to the grave.
Why are you visiting
with the Grand Queen Dowager?
I would think you would know.
I have been away from the Capital,
so it is my duty to greet her.
I hope all is well with you.
Has His Majesty also been
in good health lately?
No. No, wait.
He's a woman. I'm certain of it.
Rather than attacking me,
the man took His Majesty in his arms.
Don't you think that's a little odd?
Unless he has a serious death wish.
-I need to get to the palace now.
-Are you out of your mind?
His Majesty was almost assassinated.
The palace must be on full alert.
Do not draw attention to yourself--
What if everything is quiet at the palace?
It would prove he is what you say he is.
Because he'll want to keep
today's attack a secret.
Anyway, what did you mean
about being able to
return to the Capital sooner than planned?
Uh…
Well, it seems as though things
will go better than I was expecting.
Ha.
By the way,
did you hear the rumor?
What?
No. What rumor?
His Majesty and the royal scribe,
someone saw them returning together
just before dawn.
Just before dawn?
-Together?
-Uh-huh!
Oh? Where did they go?
Who knows?
Probably a secret rendezvous point.
-Are you serious?
-No way! No way!
My goodness. Two of them together?
Hey, you know, that may be why he's been
avoiding sleeping with the Queen?
My gosh!
Right. I can't believe it.
-I thought so too. I know.
-I think that's pretty weird…
-So weird.
-No wonder.
Get back to work.
Are you saying that His Majesty
has been seeing Scribe Jung in private?
Someone saw them again
returning to the palace together.
They were spotted very early this morning.
But they seemed like more than
just a monarch
and his loyal servant.
That is because…
it is natural that a scribe should serve
His Majesty in close proximity.
Yeah.
Is it not odd that he requests two sets
of bedding when you sleep together?
Is it possible
His Majesty prefers men to women?
Quiet. You know I told you
about that in confidence.
But--
I have been fond of you
since before I came here.
But you should not relay
such ridiculous rumors to me.
No, that is preposterous thinking.
His Majesty obviously
cares about me a lot.
You saw for yourself, didn't you?
He sent refreshments
to enjoy with my friend.
Well, Scribe Jung was also there.
That was…
If you ever mention
absurd rumors like this again,
I will have you dismissed,
do you understand?
Wait? What? Prefers men?
The rumor has spread like fire
among the court maids
that he and Scribe Jung
have been intimate with each other.
That's enough of that!
Where you heard such a rumor is beyond me.
Lo… Look over there.
Look! There they are!
It looks like the rumors
were true after all.
There must be
something between them.
But a man with another man?
Rumor has it
they wander off together every night.
I wonder
what made him that way.
Wha… Uh…
What if this leads to more trouble?
Let me think.
Scandalous rumors regarding His Majesty
and a royal scribe?
This must be stopped.
We'll be done for
if this rumor spreads any more.
This must be stopped!
Jil-geum sought out
an herbal shop he suspected.
Kang Eun-seo will inform you
of their findings tonight,
so I will escort you to the shrine.
Your Majesty!
Your Majesty.
Chief Royal Secretary, what is this about?
Is there urgent business?
No, Your Majesty.
Uh, you must be out for a walk.
Uh, well, I…
What…
The weather is excellent today.
It is the perfect day to go for a walk.
Oh! Scribe Jung, did you not say
you had some business to attend to?
I have yet to conclude my report--
Scribe Jung, we need to speak with you.
-Wait, I…
-Yes, we should go talk now.
You see, the thing is…
So from the provincial city…
You know, it's so nice out,
we should do something…
Let go of me! What are you doing?
I haven't finished giving my report yet.
You need to stay away for your own good.
Wait. What are you talking about?
Salacious rumors about you
and His Majesty's relationship
are spreading all over the palace.
They say that the two of you are together.
-Together?
-You know, intimately.
I did not think too much of it
and just considered it gossip
that would fade away.
But if the Chief Royal Secretary knows,
it means that
all of the other officials do as well.
I think it would be a good idea
to stop seeing Scribe Jung for now.
If any of these were to get back
to Lord Sangheon somehow,
you and Scribe Jung will both be
in serious danger, you know that.
You are headed to the King's quarters
unannounced, Your Highness.
What do you plan to do?
Are you going to inquire
about the rumors--
I told you not to speak of that!
I just…
wanna see him even if it is from afar.
It will put my mind at ease.
What do you mean he's not here?
He said he wanted to go out
walking for a little bit.
I see.
Do you know which way he went,
by any chance?
Sorry. I don't.
At the herbal shop,
I saw the man
who was dressed as a royal physician.
Was it the man you spoke of?
The one who killed Eunuch Cho.
Yes, he's a royal physician
who goes by the name of Seo Seung-gyu.
I saw the scars.
The ones on his wrist.
On Seo Seung-gyu?
If we can find sonangcho there,
we can be certain
Lord Sangheon was behind it.
For now, I'll keep looking into it.
Seo Seung-gyu is the one responsible
for your well-being.
He must be stripped of his position
and arrested immediately.
If I were to actually do that
my grandfather would know
that something is going on.
For the time being,
I will keep a close eye on him.
Doing that will definitely be beneficial.
-However--
-Do not worry.
I will have Eunuch Hong find whatever
information he can about his whereabouts.
We should go.
I would like to do some digging
into the herbal shop,
the one that supplies the royal infirmary.
You should head out first.
I will stay here and leave
after a few moments.
It's not because of the rumors, is it?
I have caused you so much
unnecessary hostility.
Please forgive me.
Why would you think
you're responsible for any of this?
Silly rumors like this
don't faze me anymore.
So please do not worry.
When I said I'd endure
the consequences, I meant it.
Still…
it'd be wiser for us to be cautious
for the time being.
Uh…
Hold on. Why are you taking
this path at night? It's dangerous.
Which department do you serve anyway, huh?
Come on. Follow me.
I will escort you to a safer path.
-This way.
-Thank you…
Stay close, ladies.
My Queen, this is not--
Sorry, Your Majesty.
I should really be heading back
to my quarters now.
I am sorry to say,
but the Queen is already in bed.
Should I request
that she wake up to see you?
There is no need.
In the morning, would you
please tell her that I came to see her?
Yes, Your Majesty.
Yu-gong.
What happened today should never
be repeated outside these walls.
Understand?
Are you feeling all right, Your Highness?
I truly believed…
that I really did not need that much.
All I wanted was for His Majesty
to hold my hand…
and have him acknowledge
the love I have for him.
I mean that was all I thought
that I needed.
Your Highness.
I just…
don't know what I should do.
What should I do?
Ooh!
A wicked rumor has been circulating
in the palace recently.
I have no idea how it even surfaced
in the first place.
However, I believe it has something
to do with there still being no heir.
Are you distancing yourself
from the Queen because
her father is loyal to Lord Sangheon?
Of course not.
I see. Well, I am sure
you are well aware of this,
but the Chief State Councilor
is a terrifying man.
If the rumors spread
while you remain childless,
he might suddenly turn against you.
So I urge you to proceed with caution.
Just keep your head down as they say.
GWAJEONBULNAPRI: DON'T DO ANYTHING
THAT CAN RAISE SUSPICION.
It will not do you any good
to keep Jung Ji-un by your side,
so I would suggest that you
find an excuse so you can
have him removed from here.
I do apologize for concerning you,
Grandmother.
However…
I will manage what goes on
in my own residence,
so please do not worry.
I gave orders to have
tea set up for you and your Queen.
Being seen together often
should help to make
these petty rumors subside.
You should go see her.
My Queen,
last night wasn't what--
I will not ask you to tell me
what is happening.
I will not pester you
for your affection anymore either.
Just…
allow me to produce your heir.
My Queen--
I am the Queen of this nation,
Your Majesty.
And as a wife and as the Queen,
let me at least fulfill
my responsibilities.
Additionally,
I would also urge you
to fulfill your responsibilities
as the King of this nation.
If you give me your word, I will…
not question anything ever again.
You must fancy a woman.
What is the meaning of this?
A bizarre rumor about His Majesty
and Scribe Jung has spread all over.
I know Jung Ji-un
is an old friend of yours…
so I say this out of my concern.
A man in love with the King.
How can one even comprehend that?
If you came here
just to relay a ridiculous rumor,
I would rather you leave.
I have no interest on absurd speculation
spread by clueless people.
I also heard a rumor.
A man resembling Lord Changun
was recently seen in the Capital.
You wouldn't know
anything about that, would you?
I mean, you were the first
to inform everyone of his passing.
Come to think of it,
no one actually confirmed
that the body was Lord Changun's.
The funeral was quite rushed as well,
which makes me wonder
if it was just to cover something up.
Now look who's being ridiculous.
How can a dead man come back to life?
You say speculations don't interest you,
but I guess that's not absolutely true.
I would very much like…
to someday meet the woman
that ring is meant for.
Lord Wonsan,
I have news about Lord Changun.
It appears he snuck out
of the safe house again.
Go find him right this instant
before he's recognized.
Yes, my lord.
You have no idea
how much I missed this place!
Mm.
Do you want to hear something amusing?
Mm?
So what if…
Just what if
the king of this nation…
was actually a woman?
-No way!
-A woman? You've lost your mind!
Hold on! What if the prince
was born twins and swapped later?
-My gosh.
-And now we have a woman for a king.
That's absurd.
But it's the truth.
Pour me a drink, will you?
What is your name?
-It's So-wol.
-What?
-So-wol?
-Lord Changun.
I had too much to eat.
How is a dead man…
Hey!
Lord Changun died from falling,
did he not?
Yes, my lord.
Apparently, he was spotted alive recently.
Look into it and get back to me.
Yes, my lord.
That reminds me.
Your son must be incredibly loyal
to His Royal Majesty.
Being seen so often
by his side in close proximity…
could easily cause the spread of rumors.
My trust in you is the only reason
I gave him that position.
Do not disappoint me anymore.
I will keep that in mind, my lord.
Is it him?
-He's here.
-Are you sure it's him?
-I honestly thought he would stay away.
-But he's here.
Shut your mouths right this instant.
Allow me to take those
to His Majesty tonight.
Your Majesty, the reports have arrived.
Could we perhaps talk?
It'd be best if you just stay away
for the time being.
Last night, Her Majesty the Queen…
Well, there was an issue.
His Majesty is feeling troubled as it is,
so it's best if you…
if you refrained
from visiting his quarters.
That I will.
I have to… leave?
The Grand Queen Dowager and
the royal elders have sent me to tell you
after they had voiced their concerns about
the… the rumors of you and His Majesty.
I am well aware
that I have no right to even say this,
but…
if your love for His Majesty
is truly built upon loyalty,
please…
leave the palace on your own accord.
Your Highness, but I--
His Majesty can no longer be
frowned upon by his elders
all because of the rumors
that you have caused to circulate.
You're home later than usual.
I had work at the palace.
Really? You were only there for work?
Huh?
Yes.
Why do you ask me that?
It's nothing. Just get some rest.
A marriage proposal, you say.
With my daughter, you mean, Commander?
Yes, that is correct.
You should leave us.
I'm sure you're aware of the fact that
she participated
in the Crown Princess selection.
Which is why I do not understand
why you're before me
suggesting this marriage.
Actually, that is exactly
why this matrimony
could benefit both of our families.
Was this suggested by Lord Sangheon?
If you intend to use this
as just another pawn
in your political game, then I--
Absurd rumors…
regarding my son had been circulating
within the palace.
With this marriage,
we can put these rumors to bed.
Father.
I…
want to join his family. Commander Jung's.
I have loved his son for a while.
My feelings I have for him were
strong enough to make me wanna give up…
on ever being the Crown Princess.
So-eun…
Please just let me marry him, Father.
I will ask my husband
to write the marriage letter soon.
Please take care of the rest.
Yes, my lady. Please do not worry.
I will prepare only the best gifts
the Capital has to offer.
Care to tell me what this is about?
You should get going.
Shall we?
A marriage letter?
Your father told me the news.
The bride's family also approves of you.
They will ignore it all,
so please do this.
I don't know what you heard about
the situation, but it's not true.
That is not who I am.
I swear to you.
Uh, then how can you…
explain how such a rumor exists?
Start a family of your own.
So people will forget.
Marry the young lady, have a child.
And just live a normal life, all right?
You were the person who always told me
to follow my heart.
Yes, I did.
But I didn't mean this.
This could cost you your life.
And for what?
I can endure the ridicule
and the humiliation that I received
because of what you've done.
But I can't watch you suffer.
I can't do it and I won't.
Mother.
Follow me.
You will not have to write
the marriage letter.
For I…
will not do it.
Your opinion is irrelevant.
The girl's family has agreed
to the marriage already.
I swear to you, it's only a rumor.
Why are you being so extreme about it?
Are you sure…
it's just a rumor?
I know that…
His Majesty is…
actually a woman.
What do you… mean?
There is no need for you to lie to me.
I already know about everything.
So do as I say.
If you choose to disobey,
then I might not be able to keep
this secret buried.
And what is that supposed to mean?
-You'll what?
-I will kill her.
Because that is the only way
to protect you and our family.
To protect us…
Are you saying
you will commit treason, Father?
How can it be treason
when His Majesty is a woman?
You will go through with this wedding
because you have no other choice to make.
Lord Changun has been found, my lord.
-Uncle, stop now!
-Would you stop if you were me?
I'm dead if I get caught!
Damn it!
Spare me, please.
This is all Prince Wonsan's doing!
He said faking my death
could bring down His Majesty.
The attack on His Majesty
was also orchestrated by him.
I swear it wasn't my idea.
I just wanted to confirm
His Majesty is actually a woman.
Really?
Uh… Ta… take me to Lord Sangheon instead.
Okay? I'll tell him everything, huh?
What… what are you doing?
Why are you doing this?
I'm hurt.
Just wait! Wait!
Don't you know who I am, huh?
I am His Majesty's uncle!
Please spare me.
Let me live this once
and I will do whatever you ask.
Tell me to do tricks
or to crawl on my hands and knees.
Look, watch. Look, see? I'll do anything.
Please.
Please let me go just this once. Please.
The truth you have discovered…
will be buried alongside you.
What?
Do you think that I would not
be able to kill His Majesty?
Father. Father, please.
After the wedding,
you will leave the Capital.
You can be a physician
or whatever you want.
And I will not interfere. I promise.
Don't you think
you're taking this all too far?
Couldn't you…
just let His Majesty's secret…
stay buried forever?
Do you honestly not know what will happen
once Lord Sangheon finds out the truth?
Just do as I say.
And if you don't,
I will not be able to protect you
or His Majesty anymore.
Who is the wedding for?
So-eun will be marrying Jung Ji-un,
the firstborn son of Commander Jung.
No way.
It's not possible.
I was wondering…
why did you not come by today?
You didn't deliver the royal reports.
Do you have any idea how worried I was?
I have something I have to tell you,
Your Majesty.
I am…
going to get married.
Why, though?
If it's because of the rumors
that are going around,
don't go through with it.
We knew that this was
going to be difficult and--
This is the choice that I have made.
Then…
that's what you really want.
How can you just lie to me like that?
Why on earth
are you going through with this?
Please just tell me
why all of a sudden you have
a complete change of heart.
We've been able to stay strong
through so much until right now.
So what is it?
Is there a reason why…
you cannot just tell me then?
I do not want to lose you, Your Majesty.
And this is the only way I'm able to…
be sure I can make that happen.
So what are you saying then?
If you don't wish to lose me, why--
This is…
I think this is where
I should say goodbye, Majesty.
Stop! Don't you dare leave!
I didn't say…
that we were finished here,
you can't leave.
Stop now!
I order you.
Forgive me,
Your Majesty.
Your wedding plans,
how are they coming along?
Well…
How could you make her care for you
when your feelings
are completely shallow and selfish, huh?
How dare you!
Your Highness,
please forgive me. I told him everything.
What? How could you disobey
my direct order like that?
And what would be next
after you meet with Lord Sangheon?
A woman cannot be King.
I will take back what's rightfully mine.
Sonangcho,
have you heard anything else?
I will do whatever is necessary
to protect His Majesty.
Trust in me, okay?
-Your Majesty.
-I will not die.