How could this happen?
Your Highness.
LONGING
What are you doing here
by yourself without any accompaniment?
Well… um…
I… wanted to get some fresh air
after my reading,
so I came out for a walk.
Does this perhaps belong to you?
What?
That, um…
NOT
Yes. That's mine.
Commoners play
with childish toys like this.
So why might you have it?
There you are, my lord.
So tell me.
Were you… able to see her off?
Yes, I was.
I recommend you return to your quarters.
His Majesty made it clear
that you were to stay there, did he not?
He… did.
Hold on.
Huh?
Why are you in such a hurry?
You forgot this.
Oh.
Right.
NOT
Hey, you're not supposed to be here.
We must go back, Your Highness.
I have been looking all over for you.
Escort him
to his quarters now.
He is not to leave his room
for the rest of the day.
-Understand?
-Huh?
Yes, my lord.
NOT
I'm… sorry.
I really was going to come back
right after I gave these to him.
I'm telling on you
once His Highness comes back.
I am going to tell him that you snuck out
when he told you to stay inside.
Hey, Bok-dong.
Bok-dong.
Mother, I… wasn't told you'd be here.
Who else… knows about this?
Sorry? What…
what do you mean, Your Highness?
That this child…
swapped their clothes
with the ones the Prince wore.
Who else knows about this?
Please spare us.
The Prince, Dam-i, and I
are the only ones who know.
Please forgive me.
I was just following the Prince's order.
From now on, you are…
the Prince, okay?
Listen to me…
you can never share
what happened today with anyone else.
You must… take this secret to your grave.
Tell me you understand.
EPISODE 2
My dear Prince…
Your Highness, where are you going?
Your Highness.
Your Highness!
Your Highness, what are you going to do?
Go back where I belong. Okay?
It's the Crown Princess.
Come on.
I understand
you have the body of the girl.
My only daughter
was taken away because of you.
And there's nothing more
that you, or anybody, can do to me.
-Show me her body at once.
-Why?
Do you not trust your man,
Jung Seok-jo, anymore?
I was under the impression
that if you asked him to,
he'd kill even my child without thought.
You can take her with you
if that will help you feel reassured.
I brought her into the world.
So naturally,
she must carry some of your blood as well.
So if you want to send her off yourself
then, father, do it alone.
No parent…
ever wants to hurt their child in any way.
Everything I am doing
is for you and our family's sake.
Find it in your heart to let this go.
PASSAGE GRANTED
Go ahead.
-I-wol, wait up.
-Yeah, wait up.
What took you so long?
I thought you left without me.
Anyway, did you hear about--
-Excuse me.
-Goodness me.
You're I-wol, right?
Do you know me?
Of course I do.
Dam-i works with you, isn't that right?
Can you give this to her when you go back?
I'm Jung Ji-un. Wait.
Tell her it's from "Jwajeon."
I can't help you out.
Please, I wanna give it to her in person,
but I can't go inside.
Can you please just give it to her?
It's not that.
Dam-i isn't at the palace anymore.
Wait, she isn't?
She disappeared.
And no one knows where she went, either.
Wha… what do you mean?
She left to attend
the banquet for the elderly,
but never came back.
And nobody has spoken to
or heard from her,
not even the court ladies or maids.
It's not like she has
any place to go outside the palace.
Father.
Were you at the palace again?
Uh, yes.
I wanted to see that girl.
The court maid girl?
Father, I need a favor.
Do you think you could
ask around about my friend
the next time you're at the palace?
She went to the banquet for the elderly
and no one's seen her since.
But you might have better luck finding her
as an inspector and all.
Do you really think tracking down
some girl is my responsibility?
-That's not what I--
-Enough.
Don't you ever bring her up
in front of me again. Understood?
Did you really
not eat anything at all today?
Eat.
Eat even if
rice tastes like sand in your mouth.
And drink water
even if it tastes like you're…
drinking bitter medicine.
I don't want to.
And I… hate everything.
If you give up and stop trying,
it will mean death
for everyone around you.
For you and me.
For everyone.
Are you awake?
We have brought some water for your face.
From now on,
Court Lady Kim and Eunuch Hong
will be taking care of you.
So do not worry.
Maids will bring water and help you
-wash yourself in the morning.
-Please stop.
You don't have to do a thing.
-Let the maids handle everything.
-Your Highness.
Your schedule is fairly simple.
Every morning,
you will go to the King's quarters
as well as the Queen's quarters
to offer your greetings.
And then, you will come to our quarters
to say hello to the Crown Prince and me.
The Prince is here.
I was concerned when I heard that
you hadn't been feeling well for a while.
Are you feeling better now?
Yes. Sorry to have made you
worry about me.
You don't sound as strong as before.
Is it because you've been dealing
with this sickness recently?
No, Your Majesty. I am perfectly fine.
This isn't good.
I will have one of the court physicians
deliver some tonics to you.
To energize you.
Make sure to drink it every day.
Yes, Your Majesty.
It's time for the morning assembly.
This is enough for morning greetings.
You may all leave now.
I keep stepping on my robe
because it's too long.
And this is also big.
I will have them altered for you today.
We'll go ahead, come with me.
No, not there.
It's around the other way.
Your Highness,
I have the herbal tonics from the Queen.
It is hot. So please be careful.
Hot!
Oh!
Sorry. My fault.
Oh. Oh, no.
I'm sorry, Your Highness.
I'll get another bowl right away.
Are you all right? I'm so sorry.
No. It's fine. I'm all right.
Don't worry about that.
Bok-dong!
You asked for me?
Get some ointment from the royal pharmacy.
-Huh?
-Go on.
Your Highness.
Please forgive me.
It was my mistake, Your Highness.
All of you may leave now.
It looked like a deep cut.
Please call her a physician.
There's no need.
It is not your place to worry about her
even if her finger is cut
or completely severed.
She was hurt because of me
because I dropped the bowl.
No.
It was her fault.
You are never to apologize.
You are not to worry about other people.
You can only think of yourself.
You are not to care
about what others might think of you.
Because you…
are the Prince.
There's no need to show respect to others
or even feel bad for them.
There are two people
you will show respect to, the King
and the other is the Crown Prince.
Do you understand?
But…
why do I have to do that?
That's not how I want to live.
It is only fair that I apologize
to whoever
deserves my apology when I'm at fault.
No matter what my title may be.
They must know their place.
You have to make them fear you.
Which means
you can't let them get close to you.
Or you won't survive.
Even your shoulders.
And widen your stance.
Who are you?
It's me, Hyun.
Hyun?
What's going on?
You two aren't training together, are you?
What? Does it look like training to you?
Well, since the Prince's good cousin,
Prince Jaeun, is here,
I'll get some refreshments right away.
No. Don't worry about it.
I'm sorry. I may have been
out of line with my prank.
By the way, what brings you here?
Isn't it obvious?
Your birthday is fast approaching.
So I came to ask
what you'd like me to give you
for a gift.
My birthday?
He's the brother of the King
and the son of Queen Consort An,
Lord Hyeonun.
Congratulations, Your Highness.
Lord Geumjeong of the Sinbin Kang clan.
They are the sons
of the late Prince Dohyeon.
They are Prince Wonsan
and Prince Jaeun.
You've met him before.
Congratulations to you.
Thank you very much.
Well, I hope you aren't confused today.
It's me, Hyun.
I was just playing around before.
What were you confused about?
So good to see you.
Congratulations.
This fine weather must be proof
that everything on earth
is joining together today
to celebrate your birthday.
Thank you so much.
It is truly an honor to witness
such magnificent growth in you.
I understand
you have the body of the girl.
Everything I am doing is
for you and our family's sake.
Find it in your heart to let this go.
Please remember that you
shape the destiny of Joseon.
We rely on you.
I will devote my life to serving you
as I've been doing
every day before this one.
Anxiety is getting to you.
You saw enough guests.
It's best if we stop here for now.
I can handle it.
The son of Jung Seok-jo,
from the Office of the Inspector General,
asks for an audience, Your Highness.
Okay.
My name is Jung Ji-un, and I am
the son of the Inspector Jung Seok-jo.
Thank you for granting me
a private audience with you.
I heard that
today is your birthday.
This may sound presumptuous,
but after hearing about
how amazing you are from a girl I knew,
I decided that I wanted to meet you
and wish you a happy birthday in person.
From what she told me,
you aren't authoritative
or arrogant,
but a generous prince
with a loving heart for his subjects.
Ever since then,
I have been hoping that one day,
I would be able
to serve by your side, Your Highness.
Soon I will be
going to Ming for my studies.
And I will do my best while I am there
to keep this promise to you and to return
as a subject you will be proud of.
Please stay healthy until I return.
Wait.
Was the girl who you spoke to
named Dam-i, by any chance?
That's right. Do you know her?
LONGING, NOT
She said to give these to you
if I ever met you.
LONGING, NOT
She told me they would help you
stay strong when things get hard
just like they had been helpful…
for her.
Do…
do you happen to know where she went?
I do not.
Please let me escort you out.
LONGING, WAIT
Your Highness!
Aren't you the inspector
who was looking for Dam-i
the day she disappeared or…
Please excuse me.
Since the day of the banquet
Dam-i hasn't been back to the palace,
I was wondering
if you met her that day, sir.
I did not. And I haven't since either.
I see.
Thank you for your time, anyway.
Wait.
Do you think you could do me a favor?
Sorry?
I was actually looking
for someone to help me out.
That girl…
Where exactly are we headed to, sir?
The court maids
will be looking for me.
I should be getting back to my post now.
We just arrived.
Why?
Why are you… Why are you doing this?
Can't you spare me, please?
I'm sorry. I'll try to make it quick.
No!
No, father. Please, stop.
Ji-un, what are you doing here?
Why are you trying to kill her?
What did she do?
This has nothing to do with you.
Now move aside.
Stop it!
Father, stop it. Please!
Move!
Father!
No!
Your Highness!
-Your Highness!
Where is the Prince?
I don't know. I searched everywhere
in the Prince's quarters,
we're looking, but nothing yet.
We must find the child
before anyone finds out.
I will never forgive myself…
if something were to happen
to that child as well.
Your Highness, please do not worry.
Everything will be all right.
No!
No, father. Please, stop!
Why are you trying to kill her?
What did she do?
This has nothing
to do with you. Now move.
Stop it!
Father, stop it. Please, father!
Move!
No!
-Your Highness!
-Your Highness, where are you?
Eunuch Hong, go check over there.
-Where are you, Your Highness?
-Your Highness!
-Where are you?
Your Highness!
Where are you?
Why are you sitting here doing nothing?
Go and help find the Prince, won't you?
My heart breaks for the young Prince.
She must have been so scared.
I wouldn't have lasted a day
if I were in her shoes.
The Prince's own grandfather
had him killed.
Being forced to live around those people
must have taken a toll on her.
But I couldn't do anything
to lessen her burden.
All I did was cry
in front of her out of fear.
You have to be brave now, Bok-dong.
Especially for the sake
of the young Prince.
The day the King finds out the truth,
it will be the death of everyone.
I'm here.
-Your Highness!
Where on earth
have you been, Your Highness?
It's all my fault.
Everything.
The Prince and I-wol were killed
because of me.
Please stop crying.
This is not your fault.
None of this,
Your Highness, is your fault.
The moon is certainly bright tonight.
When I was pregnant with you,
I had a dream.
A very big moon slid underneath my dress.
And soon after the moon split
into two beautiful pearls.
One of the pearls was your brother.
And the other
was probably you.
I was happy…
when I had you and your brother.
I was…
I was truly happy.
Why…
aren't you scolding me?
I ran away.
Why are you not scolding me?
Because you came back.
Because you came back to your mother.
I-wol…
is dead.
I cannot…
forgive…
the man who killed her.
And now, that boy…
I won't be able to forgive anyone now.
Then don't.
Be it hatred or resentment.
No matter what it is.
Learn to live with it.
As long as it gives you the will to live…
that is enough.
I promise
I'll be responsible for everything.
And you…
I want you to live.
Even when it's hard…
just live your life.
Mother.
You said mother…
you called me Mother after everything.
Thank you.
I am truly grateful.
Never forget…
that you are the Prince, all right?
You are so special.
Your life is important.
You are the chosen one.
Mother.
I'm sorry.
I had promised to always protect you.
But that's a promise I can't keep.
I failed you as your mother
and made your life…
harder than it had to be.
And thinking…
about how you have been forced
to live in this endless anguish…
I am filled with so much regret.
But I believe in you.
And if anyone…
can do this, I have no doubt it's you.
Remember what I told you?
You are…
very special.
Don't forget that.
My beautiful…
daughter.
Mother.
The Crown Prince
shall now enter.
Your Highness.
Everybody out.
I wanna be alone with the Crown Princess.
Mo… Mother. Please, Mother…
Mother. Please.
I have one wish, Your Highness.
Please protect
the Prince…
our child.
-Your Highness.
-Mother…
Mother.
-Your Highness!
-Mother…
All who are present!
Bow down four times!
10 YEARS LATER
Move!
Get out of my way!
Clear the way!
Open the door! It's very urgent.
JASEONDANG
Your Highness, it's Bok-dong.
Bok-dong, did you find any?
Yes. Here you go. Yes.
That's silk.
Is there a reason you brought me silk?
Yes, Your Highness.
I looked for it everywhere, I swear,
but I couldn't find the cotton one.
Would you please forgive me?
I'm sorry, Your Highness.
My room was cleaned by a new maid and…
Well, she threw out
all of the cotton covers.
Only do the tasks assigned to you.
If you aren't sure of something,
don't do it.
That's the rule here
for the Crown Prince's quarters,
understand?
SAMGAEBANG
Do you know
how Samgaebang came about?
How, exactly?
You see, we've got
a remarkably important man from here.
Oh.
This distinguished man
passed the state exam at the age of 15!
He is the legend who saved
the Vice Minister of Rites of the Ming
-with his miraculous touch.
-He saved the Vice Minister?
How'd he do that?
-How did he do that?
-Yeah, how?
-Allow me.
-Of course.
This even took place
in the most famous inn in Yanjing.
The Vice Minister
played a major role
in the Emperor's succession to the throne.
And one day when he was having his meal…
-Oh!
-…some food got stuck
and he began to choke.
Goodness.
Sir, what's wrong? Are you okay?
Sir, what's wrong?
Sir!
I think something's stuck in his throat!
Someone help!
Hurry! We need some help!
What is stuck in his throat?
What are you doing? Do something!
Sir!
Who was that?
Get him!
Knock him down!
Who sent you?
He survived.
Wait.
Are you from Joseon?
I am, yes.
I'm from Joseon also.
I don't know how to thank you for this.
Don't thank me.
I just did what anyone would do.
The man you just saved
is the Vice Minister of Rites.
You saved an important man's life.
I'm sure the Emperor
will give you a generous reward.
Everyone's life is important.
I would have done the exact same thing
if it turned out
he was a sad beggar on the street,
and not the Vice Minister.
Goodbye.
Yup. "I would have done the same thing."
All right. Okay. Now, do you all
wanna know who this man is?
Tell us.
-It's…
-Tell us.
Physician Jung!
Physician Jung! Physician Jung!
Where is Physician Jung, huh?
Where is he? Where has he run off to?
Just calm down. What's wrong?
The Minister of Personnel,
we went to his house.
His daughter's face is totally ruined.
It's a disaster.
Physician Jung! Physician Jung!
Move out of the way.
Step back!
Be quiet.
Tell us at once where the physician is.
What's going on out here?
What?
-Uh, help.
-What's going on?
There's always a chance of side effects.
It's rare, but it happens.
So I'm just unlucky?
Don't worry yourself.
With the medicine that I provide you,
it will be gone in half a day.
Okay. Now, let me see.
Where is the herb for a rash?
-Jil-geum.
-Yes.
What… what do you need from me?
Go out to the herb storage and fetch me
those dried blackish yellow flowers, okay?
Uh, those flowers?
We don't have any.
We do. Just go check
the third shelf over on the right.
We don't.
We don't?
Just give me five days.
Once I get the herbs,
I'll bring you the medicine right away.
-Yeong-ji.
You have until the end of today.
And if you should happen to fail in this
I can't promise that your shop
or that girl will be safe.
Is that clear?
Damn it!
Bullseye!
Sure is one arrogant Crown Prince,
don't you think?
He wouldn't be
if my arrows weren't defective.
Or if he didn't have
his grandfather to thank.
You know without him,
he never would have been the Crown Prince.
The Queen has the King
wrapped around her little finger.
So he only adores Prince Jehyeon.
That explains his need to compensate.
Please watch your tongue, Uncle.
We're not in private.
What? So they hear.
I wasn't making up any of it.
You know what? I should catch
one of those deer for myself as well
so that I can also benefit
from the graces of Lord Sangheon.
Who knows? He might be someone who prefers
a man like me who is full of vigor,
to someone
who looks like a delicate flower.
Hey!
Who did this?
What crazy bastard…
You said you wanted
to catch something for my grandfather.
The next time
you're impetuous with your words,
I will not be as forgiving with you,
even if you are my uncle.
So you wanna play this game, huh?
Huh?
What on earth?
He looks like a woman.
What is going on?
The Crown Prince has vanished?
We must find
the Crown Prince before anyone else does.
-Jump.
-What?
A court maid at the royal hunting?
An assassin?
An assassin attacked the Crown Prince?
She had a delicate face,
porcelain skin and dark brown hair.
Hyun?
Why did you spare
that young the man?
The one who saw you
there in the woods at the royal hunting?
I must kill him. I will.
What is your name?
-Jung Ji-un is my name.