Social assistance.
[English subtitles are available]
No. 124, Begonia Garden.
A child's head is stuck in a gap between railings.
[English subtitles are available]
Dispatch Truck 2.
Social assistance.
[English subtitles are available]
No. 124, Begonia Garden.
What's wrong?
A child's head is stuck in a gap between railings.
Dispatch Truck 2.
Take a rest.
Liu, take a rest.
[Fire Services]
Be careful.
Look who's back.
Come on, stop playing.
Let's give a big round of applause
to welcome the firefighting hero,
Comrade Liu Ruyi.
Nice.
-Nice.
Comrade Liu
took the lead and risked his life
and got injured in glory
to set an example for the team.
Right?
So
the station has unanimously decided
that until he recovers,
everyone will cover
for Comrade Liu's tasks within the station,
right?
Okay.
First of all,
thank you to all my comrades.
You are all my family.
Secondly,
didn't I successfully challenge an old team member before?
I request for an exclusive rule for me, the sixth...
rule to be added!
I agree.
I agree!
Okay.
[Special Division's Five Rules]
[Special Division's Six Rules]
Article 6:
you can’t be in the restroom for more than five minutes.
-Okay!
One sows
and another reaps.
-Okay!
[Special Division's Six Rules]
♫Yesterday in circles♫
♫Wind and frost carve out my side face♫
♫Advance against the looming light♫
♫Reminding me that tomorrow's a brand new day♫
♫Let the vow echo in my ears♫
♫I'm determined to go further♫
♫Move forward bravely against the light♫
♫Smoke and fog blot out the sky♫
♫Fly higher against the wind♫
♫Beyond the skyline♫
♫After dusk and before dawn♫
♫Go through countless trials♫
♫Break through that wall to touch♫
♫The boundary between the rising sun and the sea♫
[Bright eyes in the Dark]
[Episode 4]
[Misfortunes Never Come Singly]
Who can tell me
[China Fire and Rescue Team Combat Training Safety Manual]
what the premise of fire rescue is?
Shao Yijiu.
Yes.
The premise is
that only by ensuring one's own safety
can one effectively help others.
Did you do that?
Qin Shiquan.
Yes.
Did you do that?
Sir.
No.
Liu Ruyi.
Yes.
If it were you,
what would you have done?
Sir.
Since I'm aware that someone's trapped,
I'd have prepared and brought one more safety mask with me.
Sit.
Yes.
Yu Qilei.
Why should Liu Ruyi prepare an extra safety mask?
Then, there was a lot of smoke at the scene of the fire.
Assistant Liu is adjusting the rescue plan
according to the situation at the scene.
Sit.
Yes.
At the thought of rescuing others,
have you forgotten everything about how we carry out our mission?
Such a stupid mistake.
Let me tell you.
The Fire Rescue manual
only states the base line.
On the basis of the base line,
if you want to do things faster and better,
you must
observe more,
think more,
and learn more.
What were you two doing?
Did you want to sacrifice yourselves?
If you can't even keep yourselves safe,
how can you save others?
Like this,
how can the other brothers trust you?
Let me repeat.
Fire rescue
is not an outlet for you to show off.
If anyone does anything stupid,
you'll have to get lost immediately.
If you have something to say, just say it.
Sir.
Director.
We know we were wrong.
We just wanted to save the people.
Just like how you saved us in the earthquake back then.
Please give us another chance.
You two...
Go back
and copy this Fire Rescue manual
three times each.
Yes.
Sit.
[China Fire and Rescue]
Are you studying?
Deputy Yu.
This is a summary of my work experience over these years.
It includes some of my insights.
Keep it.
It might be useful.
Thank you so much.
Deputy Yu.
I know you have a high level of expertise
in structural engineering.
I hope you can teach me.
I will try my best to learn well.
Take it one step at a time.
Yes.
How is the copying going?
-Instructor.
Instructor Yang.
You're here too?
Okay.
I'll leave you to it then. I'll get going.
Come here.
Let's talk.
You got scolded today.
Do you feel bothered?
Here.
Sit.
Actually,
it's normal to be emotional.
But looking back,
you two
should also understand your director's stance.
Today,
when you asked him about the earthquake back then,
do you know why he didn't say anything?
There are some things
you two don't know.
That earthquake
was a big blow to him.
You can even say
that it completely changed his life.
After that earthquake,
there was a long period of time when he couldn't get back to his usual self.
You two...
reminded him of it again today.
You two are still young.
You have the spirit and desire to be a hero.
It's commendable.
But when I look back,
being a hero
is definitely not about individualism.
Don't forget
that you two are firefighters first.
You must follow the discipline
and complete your assigned job.
That's the most important thing.
As for the rest,
don't think about them first.
Thank you, instructor.
I get it now.
What about you?
All right.
Go on with the copying.
-Yes.
[Supply Depot of Blue Friends]
Director.
What time is it?
[Supply Depot of Blue Friends]
You're eating so much cold food in the middle of the night.
Aren't you afraid of diarrhea?
Zheng Yang told me that it's about to expire and he couldn't finish it,
so he asked me to come...
You have to eat everything that's about to expire?
That entire cabinet is filled with foods that are about to be expired.
Will you finish them all?
Director. Why don't you have a taste too?
Take it away.
Hurry up.
Go back to sleep.
Stop eating.
Stop eating. Throw it away.
Enough.
Stop eating.
By the way, director,
the instructor left something for you in the fridge.
Remember to take a look.
You're back.
Is it good?
This restaurant is average.
It's not as good as
the one at the intersection.
You're really something.
You got free food and you're complaining about the taste?
You should be thankful you get to eat it.
Have a bite.
No.
I don't like sweet food.
Let me tell you.
I bought this for you with my own money.
You'd better finish it.
Don't worry.
Whenever I eat this,
have I ever not finished it?
Going back to the topic at hand,
I need to talk to you
about Yijiu and Shiquan.
Yijiu is interesting.
He reminds me of you when you were younger.
As for Shiquan,
he's smart
and insightful.
I think he has the potential
to be a commander in the future.
They're still kids.
They're good kids.
Right?
They're eager to join the firefighting field.
Don't you agree
that it's normal
for them to be impulsive
sometimes?
Right? You have to understand their perspectives.
These two kids
were saved by firefighters.
So, they always feel like they owe their lives to firefighters.
That's a scary way to think, you know?
Yes.
Speaking of which,
I think it's necessary to find them a master
who can guide them well.
How about
you step up to the job?
I have to take care of the two of them alone?
The greater the capability, the greater the responsibility.
Do you think I'm very idle every day?
No.
Even if they have to be taken care of,
it has to at least be one for each of us.
That won't do.
They need you as a guide for professional matters.
Besides,
they may not
want to be instructors in the future.
Also, what can I teach them?
Right?
Besides, you've already eaten the cake.
You can't turn me down
for such a small matter.
The thing is, I have other concerns.
I'm not in the mood for this.
Let's keep them here first and talk about it next time.
What do you mean by keeping them?
Aren't they already staying in the station?
Forget it. The conversation's over.
What's wrong?
Is something bothering you?
Talk to me.
Lin Luxiao.
The relationship of a director and an instructor
is like a married couple.
There shouldn't be any secrets between them.
Enough. Stop nagging.
Hurry and go to sleep.
You're always acting like an old lady.
Wait...
Just tell me what's wrong.
Where are you going?
To take a walk.
What for?
What time is it already?
I'll take it that you've agreed to the matter about the two kids.
Halt.
-Director.
You're here.
I called you here
to...
Director, we were wrong.
Yes, director.
We were really wrong.
When I was copying the manual,
I discussed it with Shiquan.
I think you're right.
Luckily, nothing happened this time.
Otherwise, not only would we not be able to save them,
but we would also be in danger
and even become a burden to others.
Director.
I was reckless in this mission
and even implicated Yijiu.
I realized my mistake.
It's good
to acknowledge your faults.
I called you here to tell you something.
There is a tradition
at our Special Division Station.
The experienced members guide the rookies.
Generally,
an old team member will guide a new team member.
But considering
that you two are in a special situation,
I’ve discussed it with the instructor.
So I've decided to personally guide you two.
From now on, if you have any questions,
just ask me directly.
It's the same when you're on a mission.
Follow me closely
and do as I say.
Understand?
Yes, Director.
Yes, Master.
Thank you, Master.
Alright.
Go back.
Yes.
[International, Hong Kong/Macau/Taiwan, Departure]
Mr. Jiang.
Sorry I'm late.
Welcome home.
It's good to be home.
What's so good about it?
I'm not happy at all.
Whatever. I've returned anyway.
Why did it take you so long?
Where's the car?
There's no car.
I came by subway.
What do you mean?
Mr. Jiang.
After your incident in Milan,
the chairman was very angry.
He thinks you need to hone
the way you do things.
Mr. Jiang.
What happened to you in Milan?
I've told you a million times.
I was just drunk.
The police took me to the police station.
After I sobered up from a night's worth of alcohol,
I was released the next day.
Nothing else happened.
It's that simple.
All right.
Stop lying to me.
They're all saying online
that when you were in Milan,
you were gambling,
involved in fraud,
and even used your looks for gains.
Who told you that?
That's what they say online now.
Find out
who was the one to spread those rumors.
Find them.
Okay.
Get a taxi.
Mr. Jiang.
I...
I need to take this call first.
Hello.
Mr. Ma.
I've checked out your artists.
It's...
too complicated.
Well,
you can learn more about our business first
and organize your artists.
That's it.
Bye.
Mr. Ma is really hard to deal with.
He doesn't understand what others are saying.
I'll call a taxi.
I've already done it.
Why is our company hiring artists?
It is for an event?
Mr. Jiang.
The traditional industry is not doing well now.
The chairman wants to transform the company
and enter the integrated entertainment business.
He even started a company for this.
Now that you're back this time,
I'm sure he wants you to take over.
What's integrated entertainment?
It sounds boring.
I won't do it.
Wait, Mr. Jiang,
you have no idea.
The company is really different now.
Two days ago,
they've just finished laying people off,
and now we're getting a pay cut.
We're just taking it a day at a time.
Let me see.
One really can't avoid one's enemies.
[Genius violinist, Lin Qi]
So your name is Lin Qi.
Nan Chu.
The rehearsal ended so early today?
Yes.
My friend found a good place.
It's an open-air stage.
Let's go practice dancing together.
Wait for me. I'll be right back.
Let's go.
Sorry, we're closed.
The door is still open.
Are you Chinese?
I'm sorry.
We're closed.
I just want a Laobing.
I'm sorry.
We're an Italian restaurant. We don't have Laobing.
Don't lie to me.
Don't you think I know
that Laobing is just the Chinese pizza?
Right?
Sorry, I can't make it.
If you don't make it for me,
you're looking down on me too.
Just like my dad.
You all look down on me.
It's fine.
I don't need you.
I can make the Laobing myself.
-We really can't make it.
-You can't go in.
We really can't make it.
I just want a Laobing.
Auntie, you're so mean.
Do you know him?
I don't just know him.
If you find him,
tell him
that we have a cooperation to discuss with him.
Okay, no problem.
[Fude Group]
What do you think of this form?
Look at this part.
Mr. Jiang.
By next week,
if the performance figures does not improve,
you can all get lost.
You're here doing the bare minimum every day
and dozing off at work.
The performance figures are bad.
What do I still need you for?
Dad.
You've only been abroad for a few years
and you already forgot that you have to knock before entering.
Why did you insist that I come back?
You can eat prison food anywhere.
It's the same if you have it here.
Don't listen to the nonsense.
I did nothing wrong outside.
I slept in the police station for a night and they let me go.
Really?
Then why don't you think about
why they only made up stories about you?
Why didn't they make up stories about others?
What happened to your hand?
Explain yourself.
I fell when I was canyoning.
I'm almost recovered.
Just keep wasting your time.
Don't always look down on me for canyoning.
In order to play well,
I even studied geography
and vegetation-hydrology interactions,
and learned how to survive in the wild.
I've won two swimming championships and three rock-climbing championships,
and even got the High-altitude Rescue Training certificate.
Really?
Then you can totally support yourself.
Put your feet down.
Put them down.
When I was your age,
I would rather go to the factory to twist screws
than ask for a penny from my parents.
It's boring if you keep saying the same thing.
Times are different now.
There are many people of your age
staying up to work late,
renting houses, and supporting their families.
Why don't you ask them
how the times are different?
Let me ask you.
Back then, why did you work so hard
and start such a big company?
I'm well-off enough
to choose to live in the way I like.
I'm not in the way of others either. Am I doing anything wrong?
Fine, even if I don't have money,
can't I pursue
my hobbies and dreams?
You...
Only those who are incompetent
speak with grandiose words.
Come over here.
Come over here!
You win.
Let me tell you.
The company is in its transformation phase.
I called you back
to let you take over a project.
Take a good look.
[Flaming Youth]
You'll be in charge of this project from now on.
The arrangements with the fire department
[Flaming Youth]
and the partner company
have been made for you.
A fire prevention educational special program?
I won't do it.
Even ten years ago, no one watched something like this.
Jiang Ge.
If you can't even do such a small task,
then you don't deserve my investment anymore.
Leave.
Leave!
Fine.
I'll do it.
But let me say this.
I'll do as I please
and approach it differently.
Say it.
Mr. Jiang.
I've made an appointment for you
with the violinist that you asked me to find.
Send me the address right now.
I'll be right there.
We've settled the rent for this year.
So we don't have to worry about money anymore.
Next, we'll focus on the preparation for the modern dance competition.
But we need to decide on the costumes for the competition.
Does anyone have any thoughts?
Why are you all silent?
What's wrong?
Nan Chu.
Are you
unable to dance with us from now on?
Of course not.
I'll come back whenever I'm free.
Nan Chu.
Remember us when you become famous.
About that, I can't promise you.
Look, she's already being obnoxious.
She's already being obnoxious.
How am I acting like a big shot?
-You are!
It can be considered that you've stepped into the entertainment industry.
You need to give me plenty of autographed photos.
Your celebrity crush changes every time you watch a different drama.
How do I know who you want to marry the most?
What I want is yours.
Your autographed photos.
I can sign it for you now.
Sign it.
Sign my shoes.
Then I will never wash my shoes again.
Sign it.
I want to take a photo with the future star.
Me too.
Hang on!
Nan Chu.
All right.
Remember to send it to me.
Okay.
I'll edit it for you.
I know you can't bear for me to leave,
but you know how resilient we dancers are.
Don't think of me signing on to a company
as suffering a huge injustice.
It's just a few years. It's decent.
Dancing will be my main job.
I won't give up.
Besides,
I have you guys
and Dream Dance Club,
so I feel very at ease.
We'll treat you to a meal then,
to celebrate you finding a side job.
What does everyone think?
That's good.
What do you want to eat?
I want to eat hot pot.
Hot pot again?
Me too.
You forgot to ask Nan Chu what she wants to eat.
I know, right?
Skewers.
That's good. We can have some beer with skewers.
Pick a restaurant.
Let's go to the place we went last time.
Let's have a look.
Here?
Is it this restaurant?
No, not this one.
I have to take this call. Carry on and pick a place.
This restaurant must be delicious.
Its rating is 5.0.
Hello, beauty.
I'm back.
Who are you?
Have you already forgotten about me?
Who treated you to Iberian ham?
Who taught you how to make Italian risotto?
Have you already forgotten about me?
Lin Qi?
You've come back to work in China?
Yes.
I happen to be at Jiangse Bar to discuss something.
I'll also be having a meal.
Why don't you join me?
Think of it as a welcome party for me.
Okay.
Come on.
This seat is taken.
I was the one who asked you out.
You may leave.
Don't you recognize me?
You are...
Let me help you recall it.
I asked you for Laobing in Milan
and you called the police.
I'm here
to have a chat with you.
What's wrong with wanting some Laobing?
Why did you make me
take the blame for those unfounded charges?
Back then, the police were just doing their job. We had no other choice.
That's it?
I... I have to get going.
W-What do you want?
I'm warning you.
There are surveillance cameras here. Don't act recklessly.
So what?
Is it illegal for us to talk?
Get out of the way.
This is a public place. Don't act recklessly.
It's been a long time since we've met.
I'll buy you a drink to catch up.
Look, how nice is this?
Have a drink and make Laobing for me.
What a great ambience,
right?
L-Laobing?
Do you know how to make Laobing?
No.
If you don't know how to make it,
-why are you opening...
-Stop it!
Everyone is here.
You can make Laobing together.
I've called the police.
Called...
Called the police?
I'm speechless.
I just want to eat Laobing.
Why do you keep calling the police?
Are you kidding me?
I'm wronged. It's just a misunderstanding.
I just wanted some Laobing,
but he insists that I'm from the mafia.
You don't have to explain it to me.
Just wait.
I'll let you know when the result is out.
W-When will you get the result?
What's going on?
They almost got into a fight because of Laobing.
Okay.
Lin Qi.
Lin Qi, when did you come back?
I didn't hear anything from your brother.
Sun.
You even know each other? Is that how it is?
I called your brother.
He'll pick you up in a while.
Thank you, Sun.
Just wait for a while.
Is it the especially handsome firefighter brother
whom you've mentioned?
Wait.
How are you talking about whether he's handsome or not at this time?
This is the police station.
So what?
We're the ones who're in the right anyway.
You have no idea how strict my brother is.
If he knows I came to the police station as soon as I came back,
how would I explain it to him?
You're right.
If I had known this would happen,
I should have just accepted to settle at the scene.
You finally understand what I meant.
Didn't I tell you
to just apologize to each other and end this matter?
Why did you have to blow things up and call the police?
Now you know to turn after you hit a car.
You should have just done that earlier.
Why should he apologize?
Why are you pointing your nose at us?
If it weren't for your attitude,
we wouldn't have come all the way here.
Listen up, auntie, you should shut up right now.
You won't understand even if I explain it to you.
-Mingyang.
-Look who's here?
If Lin Qi weren't here,
you would have forgotten about me,
your old classmate.
What are you talking about?
You should know it even if others don't.
I'm a firefighter. We're no better than the police.
Of course I know that.
I'm just kidding.
Don't always be so serious.
How is that brat?
He's fine.
It's just young people
getting into a conflict.
They had a quarrel.
I asked them to come to the station to calm down.
Did he fight with anyone?
No.
Just sign him out
and he can leave with you.
I have something to attend to.
Let's eat together later.
Okay.
Thank you for going through all the trouble.
It's nothing.
Oh no.
He looks angry.
What should I do?
Is he your brother?
Yes, who else could it be?
Brother.
Impressive.
You just came back
and you want me to meet you at a place like this?
Brother, you misunderstood.
It's all their fault...
Shut up.
I can testify for him.
We didn't do anything.
He bullied us.
Exactly, it was all..
Don't talk nonsense.
Who bullied you?
Talk to the police if you need to.
Don't point your finger at us.
Who the heck are you?
Officer.
Jiang Ge.
Be good and sit down here.
Listen up.
I'll let you off just this once.
Officer.
I'm here to pick Lin Qi up.
Brother.
Sign here.
And her.
And Nan Chu.
How do you know each other?
He saved me...
twice.
Twice?
[Police]
Are you crazy?
How can you go in there?
[Police]
It's fine. I'm already out.
Don't come out.
The paparazzi are waiting outside.
Why would there be paparazzi waiting for me?
You're thinking too much.
They
are targeting Mr. Jiang.
Mr. Jiang?
Jiang Ge?
Forget it.
I can't explain everything on the phone.
Anyway, remember this. Jiang Ge
likes thrills and pursuing extreme sports,
and his family runs a business that's involved in the entertainment industry.
He's sort of like an Internet celebrity.
He's being watched by the marketing accounts every day.
You just signed the contract.
At this critical moment,
you must not cause any trouble.
Understand?
Yes.
Nan Chu.
Rush back to Dream Dance Club now.
The pipeline next door is leaking.
If you don't come back soon,
the place will be ruined.
Do you want me to take you home?
No.
Well,
do me a favor.
There are paparazzi outside. I can't be photographed.
You're even being watched by paparazzi?
No, I'll explain it to you next time.
Brother.
Come on.
Thank you for today.
Since it's fate,
treat me and my brother to some supper.
I have something to do today. I really can't.
Next time.
Brother, please treat me then.
Brother.
Is it this one?
No. Jiang Ge isn't there.
Why isn't he coming out?
Let's wait a bit more.
What are you doing here?
That's Jiang Ge, right?
Yes, it's him.
Take more photos.
Y-You two can go back first.
Okay.
Bye.
How could you do this?
Stop taking photos.
Let's go.
You like taking photos, right?
Get out of the car and take the photos.
-Mr. Jiang.
-Come on. Take the photos to my face.
What are you doing?
Are you taking photos secretly?
Are you filming videos for a marketing account?
Come on. Film me.
I'm right here. Film me.
Are you crazy?
Who are you calling crazy?
Forget it.
Don't run away if you're not crazy.
Calm down.
I'm crazy.
Do you have medicine?
Calm down.
Forget it.
We're in front of the police station.
Your shoes.
You're really something, Jiang Ge.
Dad.
You're so capable now, aren't you?
You played your way to the police station.
Is the police station fun?
Wait...
How is it?
It's really a misunderstanding. Let me explain.
Was it the chairman?
I'm speechless...
Forget it.
Let's go.
We're in front of the police station.
The car is over there.
Eat something, brother.
It was really a misunderstanding
that your brother ended up in the police station.
How could someone like me
do something bad?
It'd better be this way.
You just came back. You should live honestly.
Just this once.
Next time, if you run into any problems,
call Dad.
No, no, no.
Dad would have scolded me if he came.
How did you
get acquainted with that lady?
Nan Chu?
Back then, she was studying modern dance in Milan.
We're all Chinese.
After spending some time together, we became good brothers.
Brothers?
We're not dating.
Who knows what you've been doing?
Your brother has been focused on his career since he came back.
How could he be distracted by romance?
Okay.
By the way,
I'm going home to visit Dad tomorrow.
Do you want to come along?
You go ahead.
Well,
there are a lot of things to do at the station.
Wait.
You always say you've things to do when I ask you.
If you don't visit home,
you should at least call him.
I call him every week.
Every time,
he just nags.
You know Dad's temper.
Although he nags at you every day,
you are still the most important to him.
Unlike me.
He can't be bothered to care about me.
If you want to be scolded,
go and stay with him for three days.
See if he scolds you then.
No way.
Three days will be a disaster.
There are three men in our family and two of them are firefighters.
It's too intense.
If only Mom were still around
to balance things out.
Since you're back,
I'll take a few days off work.
Let's visit and tidy up Mom's grave together.
Sure.
It's just right.
I haven't seen Mom in a long time.
You've grown up after staying abroad for a few years.
Of course.
I know that you care about me.
Now that you're back,
what's your plan?
Didn't I tell you?
I signed a contract with a company
and they're planning to hold
a solo recital for me.
A solo recital?
I didn't provide for you for nothing.
You're starting off at a very high point.
Didn't you just win
the Best New Artist Award abroad?
Now you're having a solo concert right after coming back.
You've made it.
Here.
[Lin Luxiao transferred 5,000 yuan]
[Mom: I heard that you've signed a contract. For the follow-up work, I hope you can...]
[Children's Dance Competition
First Place]
[Beixun City Fire and Rescue Brigade]
A program team came to us
and said they want to film
a special show.
The brigade wants to establish this model.
After much pondering,
I've decided on your station.
[Flaming Youth]
This...
is good news.
Captain Meng.
This is great. Think about it.
Not only
can this show showcase a good image of firefighters,
but also help us
broaden our promotion of fire safety measures,
and even help the general public
understand fire safety knowledge.
It's killing three birds with one stone. Of course we'll do it.
You can count on us for this.
We will complete the task.
No.
We don't have the time to do that.
Captain Meng.
Give the task to another station.
We can't handle it.
Why not?
The area under our station's jurisdiction is already big
and we're short-handed.
It's so hectic all day.
You should know that too.
Besides, we are firefighters.
We should just focus on our work earnestly.
Why are you
dabbling in such illogical publicity work?
Is it helpful to our work?
If it's even a little helpful, then I wouldn't be against it.
Right?
D-Don't be in a rush to reject it first.
All right.
Professional capability is important,
but promotional work is also equally important.
By letting the general public understand
fire safety measures,
the pitfalls are fundamentally eliminated.
It's more effective than us being dispatched every day.
What are you promoting?
Can they put out the fire?
It's a waste of time.
And they'll all come to the station for filming.
It'll be a mess.
Can either of us handle it?
I really don't understand.
You're so narrow-minded...
Don't be stubborn with me about this.
Captain Meng.
We really can't accept the task. Give it to another station.
One's a director and the other's an instructor.
You can't even agree on an opinion.
Let's do this instead.
Go back
and have a meeting to unify your thoughts.
I'm not in a hurry.
I'll wait to hear from you.
Go back.
Yes.
[China Fire and Rescue]
Deputy Yu.
Are you playing Jenga?
Yes.
Yijiu.
Do you know how to play it too?
Are you any good?
I know a little.
A little?
That's good enough.
How about
you challenge our Deputy Yu?
You have to play a proper game with Deputy Yu.
Yu hasn't been challenged for a long time.
D-Don't...
D-D-Don't...
Don't worry.
You're not favored based on seniority in our station.
How about this?
If Yijiu beats Yu,
I'll be on duty for the entire week.
Nice.
But if Yu wins,
you'll have to be on duty for two days.
Okay?
I think that's good.
Then I'll be on Yijiu's side.
No problem.
No problem, right?
-Come on.
Anyone wants to follow me?
I'm on Yu's side.
Yijiu.
How about you
listen to me?
Forget about it.
Yes.
Yijiu, d-don't...
Everything will be fine, brother. Don't worry.
Come on.
Look at how sensible he is.
It's inappropriate.
Dagang.
Change the tools.
Okay.
I can't stand it anymore.
Hurry up.
Good luck.
Okay.
One! One!
It's fine.
Not bad.
One. Come on.
Slowly.
That one?
Is that one okay?
Be careful.
Just take it.
Let's check out my luck.
Six, please! Yu, get a six.
Teach him a lesson.
Six...
-Six!
The game's practically over!
Yijiu, it's game over for you.
-It's not over yet.
Careful.
I told you not to play. It's over.
Go on.
Thank you for your hard work.
My two little comrades,
did you forget about something?
Let me take you two to review something.
Look carefully.
Article 5 of Section 9.
You mustn't play Jenga...
[Special Division's Nine Rules]
With Yu Qilei.
It's your fault for not having it memorized.
Deputy Yu.
Have you never lost in this game?
Picking one wrong wood block
or one wrong brick
could cost
one or even many lives.
I can't afford to make a mistake.
Deputy Yu.
When you're free,
can you teach me structural engineering?
Yes, please teach me.
Liu.
Yes.
Director Lin.
Have you written the report for eating the lunch box at the roadside?
I'll do it now.
Let me emphasize this.
Everyone is very busy.
We don't even have time to eat.
I don't have time to do anything else.
Yes.
Keep playing.
Look at you guys.
You have potential.
Come and take over. I can't beat him.
[Milan]
Hello?
Hello. Milan?
[Tips for Fire Safety]
Students.
What are the precautions for campus fire safety?
Do not randomly connect wires indoors.
Don't use high-voltage electrical appliances like electrical rice cookers or immersion heaters.
Turn off the switches when there's no one in the room.
In classrooms and laboratories, please strictly comply with all safety management regulations,
safety operation regulations and other relevant regulations.
All experiments should be conducted under the teacher's guidance.
Chemicals should be stored in their specified safe places.
Do not carry flammable or explosive products outdoors on campus.
Here's the last reminder.
The more you learn about fire prevention,
the better you can protect your lives.
♫Lament how people come and go♫
♫Dust drifts before it disperses♫
♫Have the passion for love♫
♫While pain can only be buried deep♫
♫Promise that you can rely on me tomorrow♫
♫Reversers bear light♫
♫To light up our lives♫
♫Life is burning hot♫
♫Fate was once burnt by ideals♫
♫Not afraid of hurting♫
♫Bright eyes in the dark♫
♫Hold the radiance in the dark♫
♫Illuminating the insignificant existence♫
♫Tear the darkness apart and illuminate the sky♫
♫Get rid of the darkness and run forward♫
♫Courage condenses into spots in the sky♫
♫Travel in time♫
♫In an instant♫
♫Reflect the dazzling light♫
♫Reversers bear light♫
♫To light up our lives♫
♫Life is burning hot♫
♫Fate was once burnt by ideals♫
♫Not afraid of hurting♫
♫Bright eyes in the dark♫
♫Hold the radiance in the dark♫
♫Illuminating the insignificant existence♫
♫The clouds in the sky♫
♫Will always disperse♫
♫For the rising sun♫