[English subtitles are available]
Have you read the script
I sent you the other day?
Yes.
What do you think?
I think many lines are not necessary.
The male lead
likes the female lead
and she likes him too.
They can just tell each other
instead of keeping beating around the bush.
Then what should they say?
Just say I like you.
Say what?
I like you.
I like you too.
The stars are dazzling.
We met at the best age
and reunited at the right time.
We were once lost
but fortunately, we didn't miss each other.
We traveled thousands of miles.
♫Are we destined to meet?♫
We searched in a heavy fog.
You're the one who keeps me going.
♫Are we destined to meet?♫
When the clouds scatter and the sun shines through,
♫Will we miss each other?♫
it's the most beautiful view I've ever seen.
My glory
♫The vague memory becomes clear again♫
is you.
♫I accidentally realized that♫
♫We never brought it up♫
[Bright eyes in the Dark]
[Episode 24 New Identity]
Come on!
Pull!
Pull. Pull.
One, two, three, pull.
God.
What did you do?
That's my question.
Your drone ran into mine
when you took a turn.
Did you do that on purpose?
Why did you do that?
You did it on purpose, didn't you?
Did you mean it?
Look around. You can't argue now!
Quit if you can't fly a drone.
You didn't play along either when we pulled the hoses.
-Let's go.
-The superiors are watching.
Stop arguing!
Calm down.
What do you mean?
Tell me.
Don't fight.
Don't yell at me!
What should we do now?
Can't you see that it's a match?
What?
You've been doing this since the training.
Enough!
You can't fight
here and now!
You're brothers!
What are you doing?
The superiors are here for the match,
not your fight!
Break it up.
They're watching.
Two fools.
Fall in!
Hurry!
Can anyone tell me
what happened?
Report.
Director Lou.
During the 100-meter multi-barrier drill,
Lei Dagang didn't check the hose.
How could you blame it on me?
We never needed to do that during the training.
It's not my fault that you couldn't keep up.
You ran before the hose was connected.
Lei Dagang.
That was because you rushed me.
Because of me?
It's your fault!
Shut up!
They're all just excuses.
From today on,
all leave is canceled.
You need more training on the basics.
Run a 10K with weights now.
Reflect
on your mistakes!
Who's the one needing reflection?
Don't stop me!
Lou Mingye.
Aren't you the one
who should reflect on why we've become like this?
Since the day you came here,
our nightmare has begun.
Caring for your subordinates
and helping them solve actual problems
are your duties as the director!
In my opinion,
you don't deserve to be the director.
Run the 10K
if you like.
I'm not running!
Stop!
You're defying your director!
If you dare to leave this playground,
I'll report to Captain Meng
to remove you from duty!
Go ahead.
[China Fire and Rescue]
Wait, Shao Yijiu.
What's your problem with me?
I have no problem with you.
Then can you stop giving me that face?
If you're still angry about what happened during the day,
we can talk about it.
You're also responsible for the accident.
I had the right of way.
Don't you know that?
It's a basic rule.
I'm not angry.
Then what's your problem?
You're upset.
Don't think I haven't noticed
that you've been acting weird lately.
You were snarky when I talked to you
and sometimes simply ignored me.
Tell me if you have a bone to pick with me.
Okay?
I've got nothing to say to you.
Wait.
What did I do?
Stop pretending.
I already know that you're Lou Mingye's apprentice.
Have you forgotten
who saved us
from the earthquake
and who has never
taken any apprentices except us?
Although I apprentice with Lou Mingye,
I've never said
that Director Lin is not my master anymore.
What's the difference?
There is a big difference.
Director Lin is brilliant.
We both know that.
No one doubts it.
But Director Lou has his strengths too.
New equipment.
New concepts.
Especially drones.
He inspired us, didn't he?
Shao Yijiu.
Don't forget
why we came here.
It's because we want
to become great firefighters.
That's why I'm driven
and keep learning.
What's wrong with that?
Don't give me that.
Lou Mingye is competent
but not qualified as the director!
Have you ever thought about
why our station
has ended up like this?
The competition he encouraged
has turned us against each other!
Have you forgotten
what Master told us?
We firefighters
should trust each other
and have each other's backs!
Have you forgotten the stories
we read in the award room?
You've changed.
You've become such a utilitarian.
Have you ever thought about
how we can work as a team
when we go on missions
if we see each other as rivals?
You're taking it too far
and mixing things up.
Lou Mingye is my teacher.
Director Lin will always be my master.
A teacher is a teacher.
A master is a master.
They can coexist!
We can learn something from everyone!
If possible,
I even want to learn structural engineering from Deputy Director Yu.
Don't change the subject.
That's a whole other bag.
You're just being mean!
You're biased against Director Lou!
Believe whatever you want.
Assistant Liu.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I'm just…
I'm just a bit out of breath.
Gosh.
You look pale.
Are you feeling unwell?
I'm fine.
Don't play tough.
Go to the hospital now.
I'll tell Director Lou about it.
Yu, don't mention him.
It's making me feel worse.
Put your feud aside
at least for now.
All right.
You need a check-up.
Let's go.
Let's find out what's wrong with you.
-Let's go.
It won't take long.
[Outpatient Department]
Inhale.
Are there any other symptoms?
The test result is fine.
Maybe you're just under too much pressure at work.
There have been a few sudden deaths
in the E.R.
and the dead were all fitness buffs.
I feel great now.
Dr. Xia.
I was just too angry just now.
Don't worry.
I'm
right as rain.
Has something happened at the station?
A really annoying guy
came.
He's obsessed with new equipment
and new technology.
Everyone at the station
feels so overwhelmed.
He's also made us compete with each other.
I'm worried
that in the end,
even someone like me will wash out.
Try to find solutions
instead of keeping complaining.
You can prove your abilities to him
to shut him up.
Yeah.
Dr. Xia.
I'll get going.
Wait.
This is for you.
I've never received any gifts from girls.
Dr. Xia.
Our bottles…
It was a two-for-one sale.
What a bargain.
I like it.
Leave if there's nothing else.
I'm working the night shift later.
Okay.
I'll leave you to work.
Have a good rest.
I called you here today
to talk to you about something.
My application to work in administration
has been approved.
The appointment has been announced.
Finally.
Great.
When are you supposed to report?
Next Monday.
Okay.
I'll send you there on Monday.
What?
Are you unhappy
about your new post?
No.
I'm glad that I can keep working
in the fire department.
But I can't stop worrying
about our station.
What are you worried about?
You were there during that assessment.
I think something has gone terribly wrong
at the station.
They didn't perform well
in that assessment
just because
drones were new to them.
And perhaps they haven't got enough training.
After they blundered in the first test,
they kept making mistakes in the following tests.
They were too nervous.
Right?
It's no big deal.
Do you believe what you're saying?
You
don't want to interfere with Lou Mingye's work.
I understand.
With reformation
comes pain.
And it needs time.
But come to think of it,
reformation can't be achieved overnight.
We've just left for a few days.
But you know what?
Lou Mingye has filed a complaint against Liu
and asked to remove him
from his position.
What's the beef?
I don't know.
If I did, I wouldn't be so worried.
We've worked at that station
for so many years.
It's like our child.
Now that our child is in trouble,
we can't just sit by.
Yang.
You should
talk to Lou Mingye about it.
After all, he's the director now.
He arranges all the work at the station.
I don't work at Heping Road Station anymore
and have no position there.
What right do I have
and who am I
to intervene?
So,
here is my solution.
Since my accident,
Yu has taken over my place as the instructor.
Now that I'm going to work in administration,
the station needs a new instructor.
So,
I hope you can take the baton
and return to the station
as the instructor.
I just got transferred out.
The superiors won't agree.
It's not suitable.
How come?
Captain Meng was transferred in and out of
administration three times
for the best interest of the firefighting teams.
That was how our team was formed.
Lin.
We're both veteran firefighters.
As the old saying goes,
I'm a brick in the revolution
and will go wherever I'm needed.
Let me think about it.
Okay.
Five, six, seven, eight.
Two, two, three, four.
Well,
sorry.
Stop for a sec.
What's wrong?
Nan Chu.
I don't understand the moves the choreographer designed.
They can't show
the pain of losing a child.
I think the moves are fine.
In performance,
constraining emotions works better than letting them out.
Think about it.
If you were in great pain,
you wouldn't want anything to know it, would you?
So,
concealing your feelings
can arouse more sympathy in the audience.
Nan Chu.
You should lead this dance.
Yes.
Nan Chu.
If you dance with us,
we'll have a higher chance of getting chosen.
You're just too nervous.
You can make it.
Okay.
[Lin Luxiao]
Hey.
Coach Lin.
What's wrong?
The rehearsal didn't go well?
Yanzi and Sha
have been practicing very hard
but still can't meet the expectations.
They're anxious about it,
but I can't help them on the stage
and don't dare to say much.
I don't want to affect their mood.
This is a rare opportunity.
I don't know what to do now.
You don't need to rehearse again today, do you?
No.
I'll go back and figure something out.
Don't go back.
Come with me.
What are we going to do?
Just walk around.
It's a weekend.
What do you want for dinner?
Anything will do
as long as I'm with you.
When you weren't in the Fire Investigation Department,
we were on different schedules,
and even when we both had free time,
either Lin Qi or someone else got in the way.
Yeah.
Now that I think about it,
actually,
this is just our second date.
Right?
When will you be on leave next time?
Why don't we go on a trip?
There are so many things I want to do with you.
How about we go hiking
and watch the sunset?
We can also go surfing by the beach
or skiing on real snow.
Sure.
You agree?
Nan Chu.
There's something
I need
to tell you.
What's it?
I met Yang
and he said something.
In short, he hopes that I can go back
to Heping Road Station
as the instructor.
What do you think?
I…
I don't know what to think.
There's too much going on.
Neither Yang nor I
work at that station now.
I heard that a lot has happened.
I've worked with people there
for so many years.
Every one of them
has been through thick and thin with me
and fought alongside me.
To be honest,
I'm worried about them.
But
if I go back,
things will go back to the way they were.
I'll be very busy
and won't have much free time.
I know.
I haven't made up my mind yet.
I want
to ask your opinion.
I'm at a loss now.
Don't worry about me
and don't overthink.
If you want to go back,
I'll support you.
I told you
that you belong at the front line.
Let me sleep on it.
Nan Chu.
What's wrong?
Can't sleep?
Did I wake you up?
No.
Is something bothering you?
Coach Lin is going back to the Special Division Station as the instructor.
He's going back to the front line.
Then is he going to be so busy
that you can barely meet him?
I don't know.
Maybe.
Sometimes,
I hope
he can spend more time with me.
But I'm used to it anyway.
It's not a big deal.
But as you know,
many firefighters died
in the explosion at South Bay Harbor.
Instructor Yang lost a leg in it.
I see.
You're worried about Coach Lin's safety.
I never fully understood how dangerous his job was.
But after that accident,
I do.
I can't help but think
that after he goes back to the front line,
something similar will happen again.
What if he didn't survive next time?
Why don't you tell him about your worries
and talk him out of it?
Xi Gu.
I've become so strange.
Am I too selfish?
No.
It's understandable.
I know I should respect his job.
I also know
that he has duties to fulfill.
But I just can't get rid of
those selfish thoughts.
I really hope he can stay in the Fire Investigation Department.
That way, we can spend
lots of time together
and have lots of fun.
I want him to go back,
but I also want him to stay.
I feel so torn.
Is that why
you acted cool in front of him
during the day
but mope under the covers at night?
What is love?
Even death becomes an easy choice in front of it.
Alright. Stop thinking about it.
Sha and the others will come to practice tomorrow morning.
Actually, I don't think you should feel torn.
Because in the end,
you'll still support Coach Lin's choice.
You're right.
I'll always support him.
If he can't make time to see me,
I'll make time to meet him.
Alright.
Stop thinking.
Go to sleep.
[Beixun City Fire and Rescue Brigade]
Are you used to it now?
I'll get used to it
eventually.
It's not like I have a choice.
When are you going to the Fire Investigation Department?
In just a few days.
If you have any requests,
tell me.
No requests.
We just came to see you.
We missed you.
I'd buy it if Zhengang said it.
But it came out of your mouth.
I have to doubt your intentions.
Captain.
Give me some credit.
How about this?
If you just want to catch up,
we can talk after work.
I need to attend a meeting now.
-Wait.
-Captain Meng.
Well,
we're not here
just to see you.
We have a small request.
Get to the point.
I don't have all day.
Have a seat.
Sit.
Spill.
Here's the thing.
We were there
during the last assessment.
After going back,
we both felt bad about it.
Ever since we took over Heping Road Station
from the previous director,
we've excelled in every aspect.
But now…
You know.
Actually,
we can't blame it all on Lou Mingye.
He's new there
and unfamiliar with many things.
He needs some time to adjust.
Right?
That assessment
was a hell of a mess!
Yes.
It was.
What do you two think?
Here is
my opinion.
The other day,
I talked with him.
Since I left,
there has been no instructor at Heping Road Station.
So I hope Lin can go back
and replace me
as the instructor.
You? Instructor?
When he brought it up,
I refused at first.
I thought I couldn't be an instructor.
Later we discussed it
and had a deep conversation.
I agree with one thing he said.
It doesn't hurt
to give it a try.
Compared with someone
who's transferred from somewhere else
and is unfamiliar with the situation,
I'm a better choice.
I used to be the director there
and still have a deep bond with those firefighters.
I'm also familiar with everything at the station.
If I talk to them as their instructor,
they'll listen to me.
If you have the confidence,
I can give you a chance.
But let me make it clear.
You have to
promise
to improve things greatly
after you go back.
Don't let me down
or let others think
Heping Road Station is under poor leadership.
I know.
Thank you, Captain Meng.
This is the complaint
Lou Mingye
filed against Liu Ruyi.
After you go back,
your first task
is to settle their feud.
Captain Meng.
Rest assured.
I give you my promise.
After I go back,
I'll solve
all the problems like this.
Bring people together
at Heping Road Station.
I need to see
a united team.
Yes.
Three things.
First,
besides more training every day,
I've applied to the Command Center
to notify us first
when assistance is needed.
It'll be training in real emergencies
and a good chance
to learn from the other fire stations.
If anyone wants out,
you can apply to transfer away.
We don't need idle hands here.
Second,
I have an announcement.
Before we
get our groove back,
no one is allowed to take leave.
I'll abide by this decision too.
I'll cancel all my leave.
I hope the leader of every unit
can abide by it too
to set a good example.
Director Lin.
Hello, everyone.
I'm Lin Luxiao,
your new instructor.
The official appointment
will be announced this afternoon.
Instructor.
Have I allowed you to talk?
Sit down.
Third,
Mr. Lin Luxiao,
the former director of this station,
will be back as our instructor
from this day on.
Let's welcome him.
Great!
He's finally back.
Hey.
Milan.
I'm busy. What's it?
Well,
my leave
has been canceled.
I'm afraid I can't come home for Miaomiao's birthday.
I mean,
can you explain it to her
for me?
[Yu Qilei]
Hello?
If you don't want to come back
or can't come back,
just be honest with us.
Don't give us hope and then shatter it every time.
The new instructor
canceled everyone's leave.
[Yu Qilei]
I have no choice.
Anyway, Miaomiao is waiting for you to come back every day.
Explain it to her yourself.
I don't know what to say.
Shiquan.
You need more training.
You're too thin.
Instructor.
Come on. I miss eating with you.
Sit here.
Come.
Lower your voice.
I missed you.
Instructor.
Please.
Don't shout in the canteen.
Come on.
Have a seat.
Welcome back.
Have some meat.
Alright.
Dig in.
Shiquan.
Sit here.
Don't mind me, Master.
It's a small table.
I'll eat somewhere else.
Don't mind him.
Lin.
You're finally back.
We all looked forward to this day.
You have no idea
how insane Lou Mingye is.
Don't talk about him.
Let's talk about you first.
What's wrong with you?
What do you mean?
What do I mean?
Captain Meng has received his complaint.
Stop playing dumb.
Lou Mingye.
It doesn't matter.
It's just a complaint.
He can complain all he likes.
I don't think he can do anything to me.
Liu.
What kind of attitude is that?
Tell me.
Do you still want to be the director's assistant?
If you want to resign,
let me know.
I have the complaint letter.
You scared me.
You have it so I can be relieved,
can't I?
Alright.
I haven't decided what to do with it.
Then what will you do?
First, it depends on your performance.
Second,
I need to find out who's at fault.
Master.
You don't know.
-He...
-Now let's talk about you, Yijiu.
I've seen what happened in that assessment.
I'm so disappointed in you.
You've been here for a long time.
Have you learned nothing at all,
Yijiu?
What have you been doing every day?
Luxiao.
What's wrong?
Nothing big.
Enjoy your meal.
I'll wait for you outside.
Eat.
Eat your fill.
Work out more.
You're so thin.
I've lost weight too.
That's great.
Yu.
What's wrong?
Nothing serious.
Well,
I've been saving up my leave.
I want to go home to see Milan and Miaomiao.
Go.
You don't need to tell me.
The problem
is that no one is allowed to take leave now.
I…
I could've been fine with it,
but Miaomiao's birthday is coming up.
If I missed it,
I'd feel so bad about myself.
I understand.
How about this?
I'll go talk to the director.
Really?
Yes.
Thank you, Director Lin.
Thank you.
I can't guarantee that he'll agree.
Calm down.
One more thing.
I'm the instructor now,
not the director.
Oh, right.
Thank you, Instructor.
Alright.
I'll go talk to him now.
Wait a minute.
Okay. Thank you.
Director Lou.
I have something to discuss with you.
What's it?
Yu Qilei
has been saving his leave for a long time
and wants to go home to see his wife and child.
Can you let him go?
I just canceled all leave
yet you came to ask for leave for Yu Qilei.
Who will take my words seriously in the future?
I know Yu Qilei
very well.
He's been working here for a long time.
He won't make such a request
unless he has to.
And he hasn't taken leave for a long time.
His daughter's birthday is coming up.
Please give it a thought.
He deserves a break.
We should manage this station in a humane way.
I'll think about it.
Okay.
You have the complaint letter against Liu Yuyi.
What do you plan to do?
Let him work as usual for now.
I'll finish the tasks
Captain Meng assigned to me.
Liu Ruyi used to be my unit leader.
I didn't file that complaint to drive him away.
I just think given his current state,
he's not qualified to be the director's assistant.
I understand.
I'm back to help you.
We'll work together
and have a clear division of labor.
I'll follow your plans at work,
but I need time for other things.
Okay.
[Heping Road Fire and Rescue Special Division Station, Binxi District, Beixun City]
[Dorm Room]
What are you so happy about?
I'm going home.
Go home?
Yes.
I thought we were not allowed to take leave.
I talked to Instructor Lin
and he helped me.
Lou Mingye just agreed?
It's so sly of him.
Once Lin came back,
he began to rally people to his side.
Good for him.
Liu.
Listen to me.
Lou Mingye
is just a bit serious
and sometimes too stern with us.
He's just too rational.
But
he's not unreasonable.
Maybe he's just
too focused on technology
and how to improve our performances.
I know him well.
Don't defend him.
I'm not defending anyone.
I'm just telling you what I think.
Okay.
Let's not talk about him.
I'm annoyed at the mention of his name.
By the way,
I bought chocolate for Miaomiao.
I'll go get it for you.
For today's warm-up,
run a 10K
and practice the dual pumping operation once.
No lunch until you finish them.
Come on.
Hurry up.
Join me.
Let's go.
Keep up.
Faster.
How's it?
It's good, isn't it?
Yeah.
Look.
Although the living room is not big,
it has a sofa.
In the future,
we won't have to watch movies on the floor anymore.
One, two, three.
Is the rent expensive?
Don't worry about that.
Zong said
the company
should do this for you.
It's great.
By the way, Nan Chu.
Come.
I have a surprise for you.
Close your eyes for a sec.
What's it?
You're being so mysterious.
Follow me.
Mind your step.
Keep walking.
Careful.
Three, two, one.
[China Fire and Rescue]
I know it's too far away,
so I prepared this for you.
Look.
This
is my gift to you.
When Coach Lin doesn't have time for you,
you can see him with this.
Thank you, Xi Gu.
Nan Chu,
as you know,
you have the perfect love in my heart.
No matter what happens,
you and Coach Lin must be happy.
We will.
It's Mr. Han.
[Beiyao Entertainment]
Mr. Han.
You asked to see me?
[Beiyao Entertainment]
I heard
that you've been working on choreography for Dream Dance.
I haven't been assigned any work recently,
so I…
Why we haven't assigned any work for you?
You should know the answer.
Alright.
It's been months.
Your acting classes are close to the end.
Don't you think
it's time for you to come back and make some contributions?
I know.
I'll try my best
to complete whatever tasks you assign me,
but when I'm off work,
I hope I can…
From now on,
your work is dancing.
You'll keep dancing when you're off work.
I don't understand what you mean.
We've decided to support Dream Dance.
You'll be the lead
and try to get on the stage of Beixun Theater.
Really?
Do I look like I'm kidding?
Zong, what are they talking about?
Zong.
Stop guessing.
It's good news.
Really?
What's it?
Zong, did I do anything wrong?
I asked you to find a house in Sunshine Garden Community.
Why didn't you do it?
That's because
it's too far away from the Special Division Station.
It'll be harder for Nan Chu to meet Coach Lin.
I…
Yeah.
You have a point.
I do.
What you did before
disappointed the public
and disappointed me.
I've been thinking about
what kind of persona you should adopt
to be back under the spotlight.
A few days ago,
Shen Guangzong
showed me a video of your rehearsal.
It inspired me.
I have an idea.
I think
maybe you can make
more people like you
just by being who you really are.
[Tips for Fire Safety]
Pay attention to fire prevention and eliminate fire hazards.
[Johnny Huang as Lin Luxiao]
Treasure your life and avoid disasters.
Fire safety is of great importance.
In daily life,
we should all take fire safety seriously
and start with small things around us.
Integrate fire prevention
into every aspect of our lives.