[English subtitles are available]
My homework!
It's gone.
[English subtitles are available]
My homework.
My homework was burned to ashes.
[English subtitles are available]
I spent the whole summer vacation on it.
It's all gone.
What's wrong, kid?
My homework is still in there.
Don't worry.
I'll find it for you.
No.
It's not mine.
There's only one bag in there.
See if you recognize the stuff inside.
This is definitely not my bag.
Here is your homework.
Look.
[Student Card of Beixun Sunshine Primary School
Name: Wang Xu
Gender: Male]
It's you.
Mr. Firefighter.
Thank you for being so helpful.
You're welcome.
I just did my job.
[Bright eyes in the Dark]
[Episode 21 It's Show Time]
Assistant Liu.
Because you are
a veteran firefighter,
I never criticized you.
But today,
I have to get it straight.
I don't know
and don't want to know
how Lin Luxiao used to run this place.
Now that I'm the director,
you all have to follow my orders,
including you.
Your orders
are all about taking exams
and doing test papers.
Can we save people
from fires
with your scores?
But in both the simulation training
and exam recently,
you ranked last in the station.
It means that you don't know
how to do your job.
I don't know how to do my job?
Lou Mingye.
When I was your master,
I assessed your abilities with those standards!
Tell me.
What's wrong
with the stuff I taught you back then?
If you underperformed once,
I'd just think you had a poor understanding of the fundamentals.
But now I realize
that you have an attitude problem.
Is this how you used to do things here?
Is this the team Lin Luxiao once led?
What are you getting at?
Keep it between us.
Don't get Lin Luxiao involved.
Listen.
I'm a firefighter.
I don't save lives by talking.
If you've only got theories but no practice,
it's just empty talk.
If you practice without knowing theories,
you're flying blind!
The proof
is in the pudding.
Assistant Liu.
Your lack of theoretical knowledge is your biggest weakness.
You don't save lives by talking,
but by thinking!
I hope you can face your problems.
You guys.
Run ten laps around the playground.
Submit self-criticism essays to me tomorrow.
Yes!
Let's go.
Let's go, Assistant Liu.
Don't be angry.
[Heping Road Fire and Rescue Special Division Station, Binxi District, Beixun City]
Lin.
Come back now.
[Heping Road Fire and Rescue Special Division Station, Binxi District, Beixun City]
Hurry.
What's wrong?
I'm busy right now.
Just tell me what happened.
Can you find a way to get transferred back?
I can't stand it anymore.
What's wrong?
It's Lou Mingye.
He insists on having theoretical exams
every day!
And you know what?
He's always nitpicking.
I don't understand.
We've been firefighters for so many years.
When have we ever needed that?
Besides…
Wait.
You...
Hello.
Everything is fine, Luxiao.
Don't worry.
Wait.
Okay. I'll hang up now.
No, Yu, you...
Okay.
You…
Why did you call Luxiao?
He's been transferred to the Fire Investigation Department.
Why did you bother him with this?
Then you tell me what I should do
with the new director.
Enough.
Enough, Liu.
I know you mean well
and have no bad intentions.
But I think in the future,
when we're with him,
we should try
to control our temper.
Just keep your mouth shut.
Fine.
I won't argue with you.
Yu, I'll do you a favor.
I'll do you a favor
and let it slide today.
Okay?
Okay.
But wait and see.
This is not the end of it.
Trust me.
Okay.
Don't dwell on it.
Just remember.
Keep your mouth shut in front of him.
Okay?
Director Lou.
It's late.
Why are you still washing the tender?
If they sent you to persuade me,
save your breath.
I believe in my judgment.
Don't make assumptions.
I just had nothing to do
and dropped by.
This is the team you led.
They can't even handle the basic details.
You're the director
of this station now.
You can adjust the rules
and training methods
as you see fit.
Every tender
must be kept spotless
to prevent equipment aging
and the inestimable losses it could cause.
I criticized them
because I know
how serious the consequences
of overlooking these details can be.
I know you attach great importance to discipline.
Since you became the inspector,
you've been emphasizing
discipline
and regulations.
I understand.
But don't push them too hard.
It'll backfire.
It's precisely because you've never paid attention to these details
that the management has been so lax.
That's why I'm here
to correct your mistakes.
I demand everyone
to be meticulous
in order to eliminate
all the security risks.
Maybe you think I'm too stern.
I reformed the training methods,
applied for a load of new equipment,
and required them
to focus on high-angle rescue.
I know.
Many people think I'm unrealistic.
But let me tell you.
This is just my first step.
My goal
is to build a cutting-edge
firefighting team capable of using
high-tech equipment.
And I'm sure
that is the future of firefighting.
If you need my help,
call me anytime.
Qin.
We're not right for each other.
Let's break up.
No.
I don't agree.
Wrong, wrong.
You two are not in the right mood.
Don't you know the circumstances?
You're terminally ill
but didn't tell her
and want to break up with her.
Don't you feel torn at all?
You acted like a robot.
No emotions at all!
And you!
You've been with him for seven years.
He suddenly wants to break up with you today.
Aren't you going to ask him why?
You two can be fools
but the characters are not!
Guys.
There are numerous ways
to act in this scenario.
But they
showed us the worst way.
Come on.
Tell me.
Can you do it?
Can you take it seriously?
One more time.
Wait, wait.
Let's try someone else.
You, go up.
Me?
Yes, you.
Do you hear me?
Hurry.
Start.
Qin.
We're not right for each other.
Let's break up.
No.
We…
Oh my god.
What are you doing?
What are they doing?
Do you know what acting is?
Come on, tell me.
If you still don't know
what acting is,
I can tell you this for sure.
Acting
requires talent.
Go home and think
if you have the talent.
What's wrong? Do you have objections?
No.
I'm thinking about what you said.
Class dismissed.
I can't teach you!
Standing here
is really nerve-racking.
I shouldn't have called you here.
It was so embarrassing.
That teacher was harsh.
Are you frustrated?
Do you think I'm not cut out for acting?
I don't understand acting.
But when I sat there
and looked up at you,
I knew
you should be the female lead.
Even if I'm not cut out for it,
I'll stick it out.
The tuition is so expensive
and not refundable.
I'll stay the course.
Stay the course.
That's great.
I'll visit Yang this weekend.
Can you go with me?
Yes.
Then I'll pick you up
and go together.
Will that take up too much of your time?
No.
I work in the Fire Investigation Department now
and have regular work hours.
I have plenty of time.
You're just on loan to it.
It's temporary.
You'll definitely go back to the front line.
Why are you so sure?
Because you belong at the front line.
You're just on loan to it.
It's temporary.
You'll definitely go back to the front line.
Because you belong at the front line.
[China Fire and Rescue]
[Nan Chu]
I'm learning to act
but don't know how far I can go,
[Nan Chu]
but I'll try my best.
[Nan Yueru: I see.]
[How to Act]
Three, two, one.
Start.
Stop!
Do you know what your role is?
You're an undercover agent
who's on a mission with your husband.
But when you acted just now,
you basically had
"Look into me.
I'm an agent" written on your face.
I don't think you can make it to the second episode.
Why are you scared?
I thought you were going to hit me.
Did I say I wanted to hit you?
No.
Then why did you think so?
Because…
Louder!
Because you look fierce.
You all saw it, right?
This was the real reaction.
Do you know why?
Because you empathized with the character.
You knew what he'd do next,
so your reaction
was real.
If we
can't empathize with the characters,
how can we expect the audience
to be convinced
by our performance?
Becoming the character
is fundamental to acting.
It's not my theory.
Stanislavsky said that.
What's the basis of acting?
Live your life
and observe others' lives.
Nan Chu.
You started dancing at a young age.
You must've performed on stage
many times.
But why are you so unconfident
when you're acting on the stage?
Did you dance
only for yourself?
Tonight, each of you
needs to bring an audience here.
I'll ask you
to act in a given scenario.
I wonder
how bad
your performances can be
when this place is full of people.
Class dismissed.
[Outpatient Department]
Hold the bars.
Slow down.
I can't hold the bars forever.
I have to walk by myself eventually.
But you're practicing now.
Well,
I'm doing much better than I imagined.
Captain Meng said
this is the best prosthetic leg on the market.
It's so kind of him.
Thank him for me.
Take a rest.
It's okay.
Careful.
It's tiring.
Captain Meng has told me.
He's arranged rehab for me.
It'll start next week.
And
Li Lei will come to help me.
You don't have to come here every day.
You can't keep bringing your girlfriend
to my ward for dates.
It's weird.
And I feel bad about it.
Besides,
the girl won't be happy about it.
Instructor Yang.
I've found videos in which dancers shared their experiences about rehab.
See if they can help you.
Okay. Thank you.
It's Yanzi.
I need to answer it.
Okay.
Stop looking.
Your eyes are glued to her.
Why don't you follow her out?
I'm just wondering if something has happened in her dance club.
Don't give me that.
Stop pretending.
I know you so well.
Don't I?
The way you looked at her…
Enough.
Stop talking about me.
How are things going
between you and Li Lei?
Just the same.
I should focus on the rehab now.
Keep practicing.
I'll take you out
during my vacation.
Sure.
Instructor Yang would prefer to go out with someone else.
I know.
We'll bring Li Lei
with us.
Okay.
I can use a trip.
Alright.
Leave now.
Keep practicing.
I'll watch you.
There's nothing to watch.
You…
Go on practicing.
Okay.
Take a seat, Nan Chu.
I got it. Take a seat.
I can do it myself.
Hello, Xi Gu.
Nan Chu.
Sorry.
Zong wants to meet me.
I'm afraid I can't make it tonight.
Okay. I'll find someone else.
What's wrong?
The acting teacher
asked us
to bring an audience over tonight.
I invited Xi Gu
but she can't make it tonight.
That's great.
I'll go.
No.
I'm so bad at acting.
I don't want to make a fool of myself in front of you.
You're still learning,
so don't be afraid of making mistakes.
Have some confidence in yourself.
The teacher said that too.
When is it?
Are you really going?
I need to be there for you.
Good evening, Mr. Jin.
Trainees
and the audience,
good evening.
Before we start today's acting session,
let me elaborate on it.
During this session,
the trainees
will act
with the person
they brought here
in a certain scenario.
I'll offer you a random scene
and you can improvise.
The goal
is to help the trainees
overcome embarrassment
and mental barriers
by acting with someone they're familiar with.
It's a very important part
of studying acting.
Liberate your nature.
On behalf of all the trainees,
I'd like to thank everyone
who's been invited here.
I believe
you're the people they trust the most.
I'll give you ten minutes.
We'll begin after you're ready.
Go make preparations.
Does that mean
I have to get on stage too?
Yes.
You have to act with me.
I can't act.
You don't need to lead it.
Just reply to me
when I say something to you.
There are so many people here.
I…
Well,
I'm afraid if I go on stage,
I'll affect your performance.
You won't.
Just stand there
and think of yourself as a log or a tree.
A log?
Or a hydrant.
Please?
Okay. A hydrant.
Don't be nervous.
You're blushing.
The first group.
Nan Chu and her partner.
What's your relationship with him?
He's my boyfriend.
What does your boyfriend do?
I'm a firefighter.
Okay.
The scene you need to play
is that he once saved you
and now you meet him again.
Okay. Start.
Mr. Jin.
Is there a limit to the form of performance?
No.
Just show the right emotions.
Can I play some music?
Sure.
♫I wait for you in the crowd♫
♫Time flies after the storm♫
Plus this time,
♫The pain never stops♫
I've been saved by firefighters twice.
♫The light shines through the shadow♫
My name is Nan Chu.
Lin Luxiao.
♫Time stops when I'm running to you♫
Hello, everyone.
I'm Lin Luxiao, the director of Heping Road Special Division Station.
♫Time stops when I'm running to you♫
I'm also your chief coach.
♫Lament how people come and go♫
♫Dust drifts before it disperses♫
I think
he's like a hero.
♫Have the passion for love♫
No matter what happens,
♫While pain can only be buried deep♫
as long as he's with me,
I feel safe
♫Promise that you can rely on me tomorrow♫
and at ease.
♫Reversers bear light♫
♫To light up our lives♫
♫Life is burning hot♫
♫Fate was once burnt by ideals♫
♫Not afraid of hurting♫
I think this girl
♫Bright eyes in the dark♫
is very kind
♫Hold the radiance in the dark♫
and has a soft heart.
♫Illuminating the insignificant existence♫
I'm going to find the man who saved me five years ago.
You said he was dead.
♫Lament how people come and go♫
I'm not sure about it now.
Especially these days,
I have a lot of questions.
♫Dust drifts before it disperses♫
♫Have the passion for love♫
♫While pain can only be buried deep♫
♫Promise that you can rely on me tomorrow♫
♫Reversers bear light♫
♫To light up our lives♫
♫Life is burning hot♫
♫Fate was once burnt by ideals♫
♫Not afraid of hurting♫
Nan Chu.
Five years ago…
♫Not afraid of hurting♫
♫Bright eyes in the dark♫
Five years ago…
You saved me.
♫Bright eyes in the dark♫
♫Hold the radiance in the dark♫
♫Illuminating the insignificant existence♫
♫Tear the darkness apart and illuminate the sky♫
♫Get rid of the darkness and run forward♫
♫Courage condenses into spots in the sky♫
♫Travel in time♫
♫In an instant♫
♫Reflect the dazzling light♫
♫Reversers bear light♫
♫To light up our lives♫
I don't need you to be everyone's hero.
♫Life is burning hot♫
You protect the world.
♫Fate was once burnt by ideals♫
I protect you.
♫Not afraid of hurting♫
♫Bright eyes in the dark♫
From now on,
my life belongs to the country.
♫Bright eyes in the dark♫
♫Hold the radiance in the dark♫
my life belongs to the country.
But my heart
♫Hold the radiance in the dark♫
belongs to you.
♫Illuminating the insignificant existence♫
♫The clouds in the sky♫
♫Will always disperse♫
♫For the rising sun♫
Nan Chu.
I'm impressed by your performance today.
I think you don't need me
to tell you
why you did so well today.
Because I empathized with the character?
Yes.
You didn't say anything during the whole performance,
but from the way you looked at each other
and your tacit cooperation,
I felt
the love between you.
It's real.
That's why it's touching.
I think
you must've experienced it yourself
to have performed so well.
I hope
you can be a happy couple forever.
Thank you, Mr. Jin.
I've got carried away.
Back to my point.
This is why I emphasize empathy repeatedly.
You must be thoroughly immersed in the scene
to show the most real reaction
so that everyone can be moved by you.
Your performance today
showed me your potential.
However,
besides sympathy,
confidence is also very important.
You looked very confident just now.
Because of your confidence,
you showed a sense of faith in your performance.
It's a kind of power
that can make you more immersed.
I hope you can remember
how it felt to be confident on stage.
I will.
You did a great job too.
Thank you.
Bye.
You did a great job too.
Let's go, Miss confident.
Here.
Get prepared.
You're going to take dance classes
[Proposal for New Youth, a Large Talent Show]
and get on this show.
Dance?
No. It's not suitable for me.
Give it a try
before you draw the conclusion.
You look like you're born for it.
No, Mr. Ma.
I don't want to spend my energy on this.
I just want to play the violin
and let more people know my music.
So young, so naive.
Don't be childish.
Are you famous?
No.
No one knows you, right?
You need to be famous first
before we talk about your dream.
Okay?
But I don't want to be a pop star.
Neither do I want to make quick cash.
There's nothing shameful
about being a pop star and making money.
Not everyone can do that.
I know.
But that's not how I want to make money.
Enough.
Do you really think
the company spent so much money on you
because of your musical talent?
Don't be ridiculous.
It's because of your face.
Understand?
Do what you're told.
Start taking dance classes tomorrow.
Lin Qi, listen.
As a young man,
you must know your place.
Sorry, Mr. Ma.
I can't do it.
What do you mean?
I won't learn to dance.
Do you still want your job?
Guess I have to quit.
[Mr. Ma from Heaven Music]
[Demand Letter]
Lin Qi.
You signed a ten-year contract
[Demand Letter]
with us.
If you want out of it early,
you'll have to pay for 30% of the losses incurred.
Since you came back from Milan,
the company has provided you with ongoing training.
If you leave now,
you'll have to pay for all the training sessions
and costumes during this time.
Yang did the math.
It's about five million yuan.
Bring the money to me first.
Then we'll move to the next step.
Hello.
Hey.
What are you doing?
What's up?
You miss me?
Drink with me.
Enough.
Don't be so upset.
I think it's a good thing.
You finally stood up for yourself.
You're a free man now.
Don't mention it.
I regret it so much.
Do you want to be a pop star
or play gigs?
You want neither of them
and don't like your company's plan for you.
You have to terminate the contract eventually.
So it's better sooner than later.
I regret listening to you,
of all people.
I was too impulsive.
I have to school you on this one.
What's wrong with being impulsive?
Isn't that what being young
is all about?
It's no big deal.
Do you rich kids
always talk like this?
Do you think everyone can do
whatever they please like you?
Now they want to sue me for breaking the contract
and make me pay for their losses.
What should I do?
I don't mean to judge,
but it seems like they offered you a pie and you dug in
without checking if it was cooked or not,
or if it was even edible.
Then they set a trap in the contract
and you walked right into it.
Didn't you read the fine print back then?
Shut up.
At worst,
I'll learn to dance.
Learn dancing?
That's too much.
Where are you going?
I got you.
Stop worrying about it.
I'll help you out.
You haven't paid for the drinks.
You pay.
Mr. Jiang, wait.
I'll inform Mr. Ma of your coming.
Mr. Jiang.
What brings you here?
Mr. Ma.
Have a seat, Mr. Ma.
-Be my guest.
-Sit.
Have a seat.
There's something
I need to talk to you about.
[Beixun City Fire and Rescue Brigade]
Luxiao.
Captain Meng.
Nothing serious.
I just want to know
if Zhengang's rehab has been approved?
It just got approved.
You're going with him.
Escort him, look after him, and cheer him up.
Spare no effort.
Okay. Rest assured.
I'll do my best.
Captain Meng.
I heard Lou Mingye
is pushing for innovation and reformation at the station.
Yes.
He's proposed a lot of constructive suggestions
and just did a simulation training.
What's wrong?
Are you worried?
No. I'm just asking.
You have his number, don't you?
You can call him.
Who am I to call him?
He has his plans.
He doesn't want me
to tell him what to do.
If you're willing,
I can relay your message to him.
Okay.
That's great.
Thank you, Captain Meng.
Listen.
I hope both of you
can look at the big picture.
You're both devoted to firefighting
and should communicate more with each other.
Understand?
Yes.
Don't worry, Captain Meng.
Okay.
Captain Meng.
What brings you here?
Speak of the devil.
What do you mean?
Nothing.
Don't bother.
What's up?
Why have so many of my requests
for equipment been denied?
Good equipment is in high demand.
There's the budget to consider.
How many requests have you made
since you became the director?
The last one alone
already exceeded our brigade's annual budget.
But good equipment is essential.
To do a job well, one must have the right tools.
If we want to save lives in emergencies
and reduce firefighter casualties,
we can't cut corners on hardware expenses.
How about this?
After you go back,
list the equipment that is in the most urgent need.
I'll bring it up again
at the brigade meeting.
Does that work for you?
Yeah.
Thank you, Captain Meng.
Also,
the National Firefighting Competition is about to kick off.
It's getting a lot of attention from higher-ups.
They've already selected a few teams as candidates.
The provincial authorities will send people
to determine which team
will represent Beixun.
Okay.
I'll step up the training after going back.
I'm leaving, Captain Meng.
Starting today,
in addition to emergency responses,
we'll do more training every day.
You guys are either unit leaders or deputy unit leaders,
which means a heavy workload.
Do you have any objections?
The National Firefighting Competition for this year
is just around the corner.
Things are different this year.
It's going to be a brand-new multi-skill competition.
I trust you
to excel in the traditional skills.
But my expectations for you
go beyond that.
Heping Road Special Division Station
needs to showcase
our latest training achievements
in terms of the usage of new technology and equipment.
It's not a request,
but a must.
The training for this competition
will focus on Combat Unit 1
and Combat Unit 2.
I'll come up with a specific plan.
During this period,
your performances will be part of the evaluation.
I'm hoping for your full cooperation.
No problem.
We'll cooperate.
Do you have anything to say, Assistant Liu?
No.
You can speak your mind.
This is good.
Do you think we drivers can participate in it?
You've never participated in it either?
No.
It wasn't held the year I came here.
You two are lucky.
It's held soon after you came.
The drivers can participate.
But let me remind you.
This competition
is not a walk-in-the-park kind of event.
If you decide to participate in it,
you've got to go all out
and must not be dead weight.
Got it.
Don't worry, Deputy Director Yu.
Jiu and I won't hold the team back.
Yeah.
Don't take what Lou Mingye said
too seriously.
It's just a small competition.
Don't stress yourself out.
I'm not stressed out.
We've already got enough training tasks.
I'm afraid I can't handle more.
Qi Huo.
Unit Leader Fang wants to meet you in the garage.
Okay.
[Old Man]
What?
What…
What's taking him so long?
Yu.
Did you see Qi...
Qi Huo?
He's out there.
Okay.
Your mom is on a mission.
I'm going on a trip soon.
Your grandpa arrived today.
Come home
when you're off duty
to spend some time
with him.
Do you hear me?
Yeah.
I'll hang up if there's nothing else.
Hang on.
I heard
that Director Lou
has rolled out this competition thing
which has high standards.
Step up your game.
Why are you so sure that I can't rise to the occasion?
It's an opportunity for me.
I'll give it my all.
Just stay down to earth,
whether it's an opportunity or not.
Enough.
Captain Meng.
We're not in your office.
Can you stop giving me orders?
Go about your business.
I'll go back to see Grandpa in a few days.
Alright.
Keep it in mind.
Don't worry, Dad.
I'm hanging up.
D…
Dad?
[Tips for Fire Safety]
Hello, I'm Jin Kexi.
[Li Fei as Jin Kexi]
I'd like to talk about safety awareness today.
When you're in a crowded place like a theater,
you should pay attention to safety exits
and evacuation signs.
When there's a fire,
stay calm
and head for the exit following those signs
in an orderly manner.
If you're in a crowd,
find a safe way out immediately
and hold onto something sturdy
to stay on your feet.
Don't go against the flow,
or you may trip up.
If something unusual happens, don't stand around watching.
Call the police immediately
and stay away from the scene
to avoid further harm.