[English subtitles are available]
Li Haoyu!
Are you leaving?
Why didn't you tell me?
Are you afraid that after you leave,
you'll never come back?
Say something!
You can leave.
You don't have to tell me either.
But I will wait for you here forever.
I'll wait for you to come back and apologize to me.
[Prosperity, Joy]
Okay. Stop.
[Lin Luxiao]
Mission completed. Returned safely.
[Bright eyes in the Dark]
[Episode 29 Nothing a cup of milk tea can't solve]
I've been told about Fang Xiangqian's matter.
I'll report to the station and apply
for a special case discussion during our team meeting.
Don't worry.
Okay.
Thank you, Captain Meng.
Anything else?
Did you have some problems at work?
I want to apply
to leave the Heping Road Special Division Station.
Some things happened at the station recently.
I didn't manage them well.
Because of me,
conflict broke out
among members of the station.
I think the members do not
acknowledge my ability as the director.
Neither are they convinced.
I was unable to lead the team well.
And I'm really not suited for this role.
Since I can't do it,
you should replace me.
You were the one who proposed yourself for this position.
Now you're giving up.
Where's your pride?
I've received your request.
Go back for now.
I hope you can consider it carefully.
Before today’s training,
I'd like to say a few words.
I know.
Since I came to Heping Road Station,
you have some opinions about me
due to the way I do things.
As the director,
because of me,
some problems arose in the station.
I take full responsibility.
I've reported to Captain Meng
and applied for a transfer.
For the time being, station matters will be
handled by Instructor Lin
and Deputy Yu.
Take these cups of milk tea
as my last apology to everyone.
Wait.
You're leaving just like that?
About Fang,
let me give everyone a quick rundown.
Matters with the hospital have been resolved.
Fang's mother
can be admitted today.
On top of that,
Fang’s firefighter’s family support
allowance has been dispatched as well.
Future medical expenses
and various expenses
can all be reimbursed.
Captain Meng
has also contacted an expert.
Fang Xiangqian's mother's surgery
should be done in the next two days.
So you don't have to worry anymore.
But what I just said
was not done by me.
It was Director Lou who
tackled the paperwork bit by bit.
He went to see Captain Meng.
He contacted the hospital.
He helped Fang Xiangqian
apply for the best savings and convenience.
He always does it.
But he never says it.
That's your station director.
During this time,
many things happened at the station.
I was aware
of some problems.
Some of you had opinions.
Some of you
were upset.
Conflict broke out among you
because of these things.
I'll ask everyone a question today.
I'm asking you too.
Are we still a team?
Yes.
If the team
loses face,
everyone in the team loses face.
We still have one chance
to qualify for the Firefighting competition.
But you're just going to give up?
You're all planning to give up?
In so many years,
the Heping Road Special Division Station
has never been in a more sorry state than this.
Look at you.
Now you're all messing around
and refusing to put in effort.
And you're just going to leave?
Let me ask you.
Your pride is on the floor.
Do you want to pick it up?
Yes!
Do you want it?
I'll stop here.
Next,
Director Lou, please say something.
All of you.
Listen to my order.
Take your milk tea.
Didn't you hear the director's order?
Do you want to redeem yourselves?
Yes!
Can you redeem yourselves?
My brothers!
Cheers!
All of you.
Run to the training ground
at full speed.
Go!
Instructor, clean up!
♫Yesterday in circles♫
♫Wind and frost carve out my side face♫
♫Advance against the looming light♫
♫Reminding me that tomorrow's a brand new day♫
♫Let the vow echo in my ears♫
♫I'm determined to go further♫
♫Move forward bravely against the light♫
♫Smoke and fog blot out the sky♫
♫Fly higher against the wind♫
♫Beyond the skyline♫
♫After dusk and before dawn♫
♫Go through countless trials♫
♫Break through that wall to touch♫
♫The boundary between the rising sun and the sea♫
♫Move forward bravely against the light♫
♫Smoke and fog blot out the sky♫
♫Fly higher against the wind♫
♫Beyond the skyline♫
♫After dusk and before dawn♫
♫Go through countless trials♫
Can you do it?
♫Break through that wall to touch♫
If you can't, switch out.
♫The boundary between the rising sun and the sea♫
There's still time.
Alright.
♫The boundary between the rising sun and the sea♫
Don't talk nonsense.
Who else can lead you
♫The boundary between the rising sun and the sea♫
except for me?
Comrades of Heping Road Station.
Congratulations.
On behalf of Beixun City,
you will compete in the National Firefighting Competition.
Guys,
do us proud.
Yes.
How is your practice?
You'll know.
Do your best.
Show your real skills.
Don't worry.
I won't embarrass you.
If anything, I'll only embarrass myself.
Anything else?
I'll leave if there's nothing else.
You should have been the leader.
What are you talking about?
You are the station director.
Of course you should be the leader.
Thanks.
What are you thanking me for?
You just don't get it, do you?
When I was working with Yang,
he said that
the relationship between
a qualified director and his instructor
is like a close couple.
Understand?
That's enough.
We're leaving.
Get in.
Do your best
and get a good result.
Do you hear me?
Okay, don't worry.
Go.
Bye.
Come on.
[China Fire and Rescue]
Okay, stop.
Don't use your fake feelings
and tears to fool the audience
and us, okay?
I want true feelings.
Only true feelings
can move yourself
and the audience.
I want true feelings.
One more time.
Don't stop until we get a good shot.
Come here.
There was another girl who auditioned for Ya last time.
Call her
and ask her to come here.
Okay.
Hurry up.
Do you want to ask me
when I can come back?
When the jasmine flower you bought last year blooms,
I should be back.
Li Haoyu.
I water it every day.
Will you come back
when the flower blooms?
It's okay even if you're a little late.
I'll wait for you
until you return.
[China Fire and Rescue]
The ten comrades on the stage
represented the Beixun City Brigade
and won second place in the competition.
They have gained great honor
and set a good example.
I thank you
on behalf of Beixun City Brigade.
Applaud.
Nice!
[Certificate of Honor]
Have a seat.
These ten comrades
brought about honor and merit
to our brigade.
I have an idea.
Can I give them a day off?
However,
other comrades
have contributed a lot too.
As for the reward,
you decide.
How about treating us?
Yes! Treat us!
Treat us!
No problem.
Okay, everyone.
Well,
Instructor Lin and I discussed this on our way back.
The competition rewards from the brigade
are all at the Supply Depot of Blue Friends.
You can use that to buy any
food and drinks you want.
On top of that, today,
I'll treat everyone with my own money.
Nice!
Listen.
Cherish this opportunity.
This is not Director Lou's usual style.
I learned well from Instructor Lin.
Report.
I, Fang Xiangqian, have returned!
Captain Meng.
You're back.
How's your mother?
She's fine.
The surgery went well.
The test report is out.
It's positive.
The doctor said
she could be discharged after some rest.
Great.
It's great news.
This is double the joy.
Shouldn't we further celebrate?
Right?
Yes!
We'll celebrate.
And...
Thank you for helping my mom, Captain Meng.
You too, Director Lou
and Instructor Lin.
I'm just glad things are well, Fang.
You don't have to rush back to work.
Captain Meng just gave all the
participants of the competition a day off.
Lin and I plan to take everyone to camp.
Everyone, bring your family.
You can bring your wife too.
Spend some time together.
Yes.
As the old saying goes,
don't be arrogant or impatient.
Keep working hard.
Yes!
Did you say Supply Depot of Blue Friends?
Yes.
I want to take a look.
Can I?
This is also a feature of our station.
How about this, Captain Meng,
Qi Huo.
Yes.
Take Captain Meng to the supply depot
and give him a tour.
Take the chance to introduce our work
and life experience to Captain Meng.
Yes.
Okay.
I...
I'll go first.
Goodbye, Captain Meng.
Go.
Hurry up.
Hurry.
Go.
Look at his dainty steps.
This is it.
Not bad.
Good.
Aren't you going to introduce it to me?
This is a good venture.
The station can promote it.
What do you want?
Just say it.
Nothing.
I'm just looking around.
What do you think?
You must have gained a lot in this competition.
Didn't you announce it just now?
The second place.
Yes.
I mean,
you got second place.
There's still
room for improvement.
What's wrong?
Are you still not satisfied with second place?
Did I say that?
Didn't I give you all a day off?
Am I very annoying in your eyes?
I'm your dad.
I can't even talk to you now?
Sure.
Go ahead.
I'm listening.
Look at you.
I...
I mean...
Well...
You did well this time.
You mustn't
be proud and impatient.
I said that already.
Anyway, work hard at everything you do.
I have a question.
Are you saying this as my leader
or as my father?
What's the difference?
If you said it as my leader,
I'm grateful for your recognition.
What if I said it as your father?
I want you to know that
everything I have
was earned by my own efforts.
Yes.
You got it yourself.
I'm not denying your efforts.
Back then, when you applied to be
a firefighter behind my back,
I made you change your name.
Why did I do that?
I did that to tell you
what firefighters rely on.
We rely on strength, persistence,
and real skills.
Am I
a qualified firefighter now?
Yes.
Have I always relied on myself
and not on anyone else?
Yes.
Have I ever embarrassed you?
No.
Then, can you praise me
as my father?
Son,
I'm proud of you.
Please say it again.
Say what?
What you said just now.
You weren't even looking at me when you said it.
Say it again.
I won't repeat the same praise twice.
Just say it again.
Look at me so I can feel it.
I have a lot of things to do.
Just say it once.
It won't take long.
Just once.
Next time.
Say it again, just once.
Well...
[Supply Depot of Blue Friends]
If you're really embarrassed to say it,
you can post it on your Moments instead!
[Supply Depot of Blue Friends]
This is more like camping.
When the lights are on at night,
it will be even more atmospheric.
Let me tell you.
I saw Director Lou
at the garage just now.
He brought all the old tents we replaced last year.
At night,
others might think something happened.
Lou Mingye.
I'm not blaming you.
But it's been so many years.
Can you be more fun?
Lighten up!
You're more stingy than me.
Both of you are stingy.
Okay, good enough.
Aren't Milan and Miaomiao coming?
They are.
They'll be here later.
That's good.
Although Milan and I are divorced,
I’ve discussed it with Milan.
We'll still meet once in a while.
No matter what,
we can't let the child suffer.
That's right.
Although
I can't be a good husband now,
at least I still have a chance
to be a good dad.
Miaomiao is so cute.
You can't bear to upset her.
Are you busy?
You're here, Yang.
Who is this?
Let me ask you one question.
When are you two getting married?
When?
Soon.
Why don't I know that?
Wait, this is important.
Do you need a best man?
Best man?
We have enough best men.
We need one more bridesmaid.
Why don't you fill the spot?
What's the meaning of this?
I'm your best friend.
I want to be the best man.
Best man!
You guys talk. I'll go there and help.
Okay.
Let's go.
Have a seat.
Okay.
Where's Nan Chu?
She's not here?
Nan Chu
is filming with the crew.
She can't make it today.
I'll sit for a while.
Have a seat.
Sergeant Lin!
Why are you back?
I'm done filming.
So soon?
I miss you.
I miss you too.
Hurry, cover the kid's eyes.
Enjoy yourselves.
I'm leaving.
Play with us.
No thanks.
I have to deal with Shen Guangzong.
His occupational hazard is acting up again.
I took her out secretly, you know.
By the way,
It's cold at night.
Take this.
Just in case.
What treasure is it?
Okay.
Take care of Nan Chu.
Don't worry.
I'm leaving.
-Off you go.
-Bye.
Bye.
Let's go.
I have so much to tell you.
Me too.
What?
You go first.
You first.
Who is this?
Long time no see.
Long time no see, superstar.
Let me ask you two a question.
When will you get married?
Why do you have so many questions?
Wait, this is important.
Do you need a best man?
What?
Is being the best man your side gig?
You want to be the best man all the time.
I like being the best man.
Dad!
Dad.
Who is this?
Miaomiao.
Sister-in-law.
Hello, Sister-in-law.
Say hello to your uncles.
Hello, uncles.
Hello.
All right, everyone is here.
Hurry.
Say hello.
Let's start.
Okay.
Sit here, sister-in-law.
I'll go there.
I'll take you there.
Honey.
Leader.
What would you like to drink?
Is it cooked?
Hungry?
Wait.
Coming.
Eggplants.
Put it here.
Slice the inside up.
Where is the knife?
Where is the knife? Use the knife.
It's okay.
Use...
[Xia Wan]
I'm busy today.
I can't make it.
[Xia Wan]
Dagang's job
is tiring
and doesn't pay well.
His phone needs to be on standby 24 hours a day.
Every time I want to talk to him,
he's either in a meeting,
on a mission,
or training somewhere.
It's hard to ask him for help.
I still remember when I was pregnant,
I handled everything myself.
He was no help at all.
Exactly.
When I went on a date with Qi Huo,
he ran as soon as he heard the bell.
And then I had to yell at him that
it was the end of the school next door.
This is called conditional reflex.
Mine does that too.
From what you said,
we have two firefighters at home.
How will we live?
You two are actually fine.
You're in the same system.
You can understand each other.
Why don't we make a forum online?
The title is...
"Complaints of a firefighter's family."
The title is good.
Are they all sent by one of us?
What's wrong, Liu?
Are you unhappy because
because Dr. Xia isn't coming?
She's not coming.
Don't think too much.
Right?
She's just ambitious.
She's busy with work.
She still loves you.
Don't think too much.
Let's wait and see.
If she cares about me,
she will come sooner or later.
That's enough.
She's just busy with work
and couldn't make it.
Stop complicating it.
Okay?
Good for you.
Do you think you're the tragic male lead?
Why are you sitting here?
Prepare the skewers, Drama Queen.
Okay.
You keep creating drama for yourself.
Drama queen.
Yes, she doesn't love you.
Actually, living together as a couple
means holding and supporting each other.
If something happens,
we can only bear it together.
To be honest, regarding my mother-in-law's illness this time...
If not for the help of the team,
Fang and I wouldn't have known what to do.
You don't know
how bad Fang is with words.
He doesn't like talking about his problems,
so he keeps them to himself.
Once,
I saw him
hiding away, secretly wiping his tears
because he couldn't afford the hospital fees.
My mother-in-law even said,
if push comes to shove,
she would just not get treated.
I really...
It's all thanks to his team
and his team leaders.
They helped us get through this.
I used to joke with Fang
that
he is much happier with his team
than when he is with me.
He said these are his family.
I didn't understand it before.
But now I understand.
Yeah.
We are already sitting here.
We can't change our options now.
Dagang also said
the special nature of their industry
is to hand over their backs.
As family members,
we should be more considerate.
As firefighters, they should take time
to take care of the family.
Isn't that enough?
In my opinion,
we should get together more often.
They are a family.
Then we're family too.
-Yes.
-You're right.
Nan.
If Lin Luxiao makes you unhappy,
just tell us.
We'll hold a meeting with him for you.
Of course.
Yes.
If you want to know his whereabouts,
you can ask me anytime.
I'm counting on all of you.
No problem.
Here are the skewers.
Here you go.
It's done.
It's all done?
Why is it burnt?
Is it still edible?
Of course it is.
We made so many.
They're only good for putting out fires.
You can't eat this.
Did you barbecue this?
Did you take it from someone else?
Don't eat it.
It looks like it.
It's salty.
How did you barbecue it?
We had a great chat.
Look at Dagang.
He must get beaten by his wife often at home.
And Unit Leader Fang
probably can't beat his wife in a quarrel.
Miaomiao.
Miaomiao!
Daddy is going to chase you.
Miaomiao, I'm going to catch up with you.
Slow down, Miaomiao.
Miaomiao.
Sister Milan.
Have you ever regretted it?
Back then, they all advised me not to divorce him.
They said I would regret it.
They said I had to be considerate.
Firefighters
sacrifice their families for everyone else.
It's really sacred.
But
I can't be that great.
I tried many ways
and tried to tolerate them.
But after a while,
it became hard to persist.
I don't want
to face everything
all by myself.
I'm just one person.
A woman.
An ordinary woman.
But you,
you're a superstar now.
And Luxiao is so busy.
Do you even have time to meet?
Also,
What have you done for the future?
I don't know.
But I don't think I can figure it out.
No matter what,
I will protect Lin Luxiao.
Protect?
Nan Chu.
You're so brave.
Actually,
Yu and I divorced
not just because he's a firefighter.
More importantly,
I don't think we suit each other.
Nan Chu.
I wish you and Luxiao all the best.
You must be well.
Everyone is so enthusiastic.
The lights
make it so atmospheric.
You used the emergency rescue tents.
How did you come up
with the idea of camping in the emergency rescue tents?
What, you have a problem with it?
Are you upset?
I'll punish you.
Bottoms up.
Hurry up.
Since everyone is here,
let's take a group photo.
-Okay.
-Come on.
Wait.
Today is a special day.
I need to use the toilet.
Don't you remember?
Today?
I don't know.
What festival is it today?
What milestone?
What anniversary?
I don't know.
Never heard of it.
Today is Sergeant Lin’s birthday.
Happy birthday to you.
Thank you.
I forgot about it.
Then you can't forget it from now on.
This is your first birthday celebration
since we got together.
I won't forget it again.
We'll celebrate every birthday together from now on.
There are kids here!
Don't let them see.
What are the kids afraid of?
Make a wish.
-Make a wish.
-Wait.
I have a question.
Did you prepare all these by yourself?
No, I was afraid I couldn't make it in time.
Instructor Yang and Assistant Liu helped me.
The cake!
Director Lou picked it!
Right?
I knew only he could choose
such a small cake.
Who swore
to never celebrate my birthday?
Screw you!
Am I that petty?
Shut up and make a wish.
Make a wish.
Stop.
What did you wish for?
I can't tell you.
I'll take it as becoming a father soon.
Let's wish Instructor Lin
happy birthday again!
Cheers.
Let me position everyone.
Family members sit in the front.
The rest of you stand behind your partners.
Yijiu. Shiquan.
Liu.
We'll
sit on the ground.
Sit on the ground.
Come on.
Can you fit all of us in?
Yes, wait.
Ready. I'll start.
Ten, nine, eight...
-Hurry up.
-Seven.
Six.
Come on.
Slogan.
One, two, three!
Be safe!
(Six months later)
One more.
Enough.
You've taken so many.
Come on, take one for him.
Coming.
Okay.
-Let me see.
-Next.
Nice.
Why am I so handsome
in this new outfit?
Alright.
My turn.
Come on. Three, two, one.
Cheese.
Let me take a look.
Take a good photo of me.
I'm going to send it to Xia Wan.
You look so proper.
Aren't you a born firefighter?
He smiles like a chihuahua.
Not bad.
Okay, I'll take this one.
Okay, I'll send it to you right away.
Okay.
Good.
Take a look.
Where is Instructor Lin?
Didn't he come back with us just now?
He asked for leave as soon as he came back.
A leave?
What?
Instructor Lin asked for a leave?
Have you forgotten
what day it is today?
What day?
Right!
Today is a big day.
No wonder.
Warrior Li Haoyu
asked me to tell you something
before he died.
["Waiting for You in My World" premiere]
[Starring: Zhang Huaming, Li Runqi, Nan Chu]
Alright.
["Waiting for You in My World" premiere]
[Starring: Zhang Huaming, Li Runqi, Nan Chu]
Let's give a big round of applause
["Waiting for You in My World" premiere]
[Starring: Zhang Huaming, Li Runqi, Nan Chu]
to welcome the main creation team of this movie
["Waiting for You in My World" premiere]
[Starring: Zhang Huaming, Li Runqi, Nan Chu]
to the stage.
Let's give them a round of applause.
Nan Chu did a great job.
They loved each other, but they couldn't be together.
Even a man like me is touched.
I have good taste.
The premiere is so popular.
Nan Chu will be a big hit.
Nan Chu.
I love you as before.
[Tips for Fire Safety]
Let me share with everyone
[Liu Junzihe as Fang Xiangqian]
some anti-fraud know-how.
We firefighters
[Liu Junzihe as Fang Xiangqian]
never produce, operate,
or sell any firefighting facilities, equipment
or tools.
Don't believe in anyone
who claims to be from an establishment
and try to sell you firefighting equipment by force.
If you encounter such problems,
you can report them to the police.
Please purchase firefighting equipment
from legal and reliable sources.
Use them correctly
and cherish them.