I sent you DMs and called you, too.
I'm sorry.
My teacher had my phone.
Mark, what do you think?
Are you happy we're taking a walk?
He's cute.
But you got your phone back after class.
I went straight to play basketball.
I'm really sorry.
Are you suspicious of Chan Seong?
If you know anything, be honest.
Thank you.
San.
Don't spread rumors.
Is Ji Yu here?
I told you I'll see you, didn't I?
How do you two know each other?
("What Do You Like?")
We bumped into each other
on the way to school...
and he cracked his phone.
Do you really think
I expect you to buy me a meal?
It was an excuse.
Nam Do Ha? Just you two?
Then you wouldn't have told me
if San hadn't caught you.
What?
This is so upsetting.
Chan Seong.
You haven't even been around me.
- Hey.
- You're hiding something from me!
What am I hiding?
You would know better than I do.
Hey, Mi Na!
- Hey!
That face again.
Why do you always play the victim?
You still like Chan Seong, don't you?
That's why you only do this to Ji Yu.
What do you know?
I'll do something about the rumor.
It's not my first rumor.
Su Jin was a friend I really liked.
Nam Do Ha!
Why did you do that to me?
You two are silly.
I was just being nice,
and you fell for me.
I've never met girls as easy as you two.
You really are trash.
Stop it.
Give it a rest.
It's embarrassing.
By any chance, is the one you like...
Then is it...
Yes.
(Fragile)
(Chapter 45
Monday, October 14th, 2024)
(Slut container)
(Did you let Do Ha do you?
I heard you'll do with anyone. How much?)
(I'm next. I put myself on the list.)
(I feel bad for Do Ha.)
(You can't live without boys
since you have no father.)
(They're all attention seekers.
That's why they hang together.)
(Dirty slut)
I didn't touch that.
What? Is something wrong?
Ji Yu, why don't you read our group chat?
I know.
This is a serious offense.
You're ignoring your fellow warriors
who crushed Nam Do Ha with you.
What do you think about this?
Well...
Those crazy bastards.
They've gone insane.
- Ji Yu, are you okay?
- Yes.
Mi Na, you didn't get any messages?
Then that's a relief,
but I didn't expect it to be this bad.
Did we go overboard?
It must be me.
It's not you.
We made a scene,
but the kids who send
these types of messages are just crazy.
You're right.
I've only heard about this.
I'm just a bit shocked
since I've never experienced this.
It's okay.
How is this okay?
Then should you make a new account?
Avoiding it won't resolve this.
Let's take screenshots first.
This is a crime.
Hold on.
(You can't even see my eyes
face to face.)
(You bastards can't even look at my eyes.)
(You just run your fingers
like losers behind the screen.)
(I can tell how ugly you'd look,
you rotten bastards.)
(If you send me messages like these again,
I'll ruin all your lives.)
(Get ready to be investigated.
I've screenshotted your DMs.)
You can't stay quiet.
They'll go even wilder if you ignore them.
Thanks.
I wanted to curse them, too.
If anything like this happens again,
don't hide and tell us right away.
They must have nothing better to do.
It's okay. Forget about them.
I'll get over it.
Don't pretend like you're okay.
I feel reassured.
I'll beat them up if I see them.
Beat who?
Is it me?
Since we're on the subject,
did you send Ji Yu those stupid DMs, too?
Stupid DMs? What do you mean?
If not, never mind. You can go your way.
Why? Is someone bothering you?
What?
I don't know what it is, but it's not me.
Aren't you being biased
just because Do Ha's my friend?
Besides that,
you're buddying up when you're taken.
How can we think you're good?
Who said I had a girlfriend?
I've seen things. Don't play dumb.
I see.
I broke up with her.
I'm serious.
A Ra, let's just go.
About that time...
I'm sorry.
Okay. Reflect a lot on it.
On page 101, look at Sentence A.
In front here on "In the light,"
with "of" in the back,
it means "to consider."
It can also mean "to reflect on."
(Hi!)
(You just read it, you crazy slut.)
(Did you think I'd be scared?)
(Is it because you only have your mom?
You're so pathetic.)
(Does your mom know?
You bring home boys when she's away.)
If we look at Yi Yuk Sa's life...
in retrospect to reflect on it,
we realized that doubts are caused
by experiences sometimes, right?
That's why the memory
that triggers doubt...
is always held by people,
which we can understand from him.
Then if we look at the choices,
"A" is doubt, "B" is experience,
and "C" is memory...
Why are you still up?
I'm just watching lectures.
Really?
Should we talk?
How is it studying by yourself?
- It's okay.
- Isn't it hard?
Do you want a tutor?
If you're going to nag, just leave.
I'm sleepy.
Ji Yu.
I told you I'll handle it myself.
Fine, I'm not trying to nag.
I'm worried about you.
I want to do whatever I can for you.
I should've been more attentive.
I feel bad.
Can't you tell me what's bothering you?
Please?
Do you want to move schools?
What?
I talked to your dad.
He's fine with taking you.
If you want, I'll think about it, too.
Mom, it's not like that.
That time, I was just so...
I mean...
I really don't want to go.
I'm really serious. I want to be with you.
Okay, I got it.
Whatever is bothering you lately,
you're just not ready to talk yet, right?
But when you're ready, please tell me.
No matter what people say,
I'm always on your side.
You know that, right?
Yes, Mom.
(Chapter 47
Wednesday, October 16th, 2024)
We're going home.
What's wrong? Need to use the bathroom?
No, it's not that.
Are you sick?
Mi Na.
What is this?
For crying out loud. Let's go.
- Let's go.
- Bye.
Have a good time.
Sorry.
- Bye.
- I'm jealous.
San, just a moment.
Did Chan Seong leave already?
He left early today.
What? Why?
He hasn't been doing well lately...
since that time.
Call him.
It's so small. Look at its coat.
I know. It's so cute.
Where is it going?
It's Su Ho.
I didn't expect that from him.
Come on.
He wouldn't be human
if he's mean to animals, too.
Let's go.
(Can you come out for a second?
I'm in front of your house.)
Are you doing better?
Yes, I'm feeling better.
Did you wait long?
No, I didn't wait that long.
- Sorry.
- What?
I shouldn't have avoided it.
I was embarrassed
for letting you see me like that.
No, I'm sorry.
Because of you, you had to...
No, it's not because of you.
I was just angry.
Still, I hit him first.
- You know, right?
- Yes, I know.
- Ji Yu.
- What?
People make mistakes,
just like you and me.
But at this point,
we're both a bit...
Then...
how about we give it some time?
To figure out what to do.
To see what's better.
Okay, let's do that.
You study during break time?
That's not right.
I know.
A Ra, do you feel an urge to study?
Do you think about it?
We have a test coming up soon.
But am I the only one taking it?
So? What do we do after the test?
Isn't it too early?
- That way, we can have the best time.
- The best?
Then how about coming over to my house?
My mom will be away on a business trip.
- Really? We can sleep over?
- Yes.
Let's have a pajama party.
All of you bring your pajamas.
I should tell Ye Ri, too.
- What?
- Get off me.
What?
Mi Na looks after Ye Ri the best.
I know.
I'll bring something better than pajamas.
What is it?
- It's a secret.
- What?
- What is it?
- Hey.
(Slut container)
Don't block my way.
Aren't you going too far?
You should seriously stop.
Let go.
You stop before I report you.
- What?
- Did you think I don't know?
This is you.
(You crazy slut. You left your friend
for a boy. You can't live without boys.)
(How ridiculous you are.
When I send you DMs, you read them.)
Are you shocked that you got caught?
(Don't make me angry.
You don't know what I'm capable of.)
No, it's not that...
What is this?
Then who...
What is this? Why did you bring me here?
Why is she here?
Did you two make up?
Why?
Tell me.
Si Jung.
(Calling alclssus0330)
Was it really you? Why?
Are you crazy?
Su Jin, getting involved with Ji Yu
was hard for you, so I...
What? Do you know what you did?
You two hate each other's guts anyway.
- What?
- I was ending things once and for all.
Is that so bad?
- Si Jung.
- You only feel bad for Su Jin, right?
Have you ever given me
so much as an excuse?
You two don't know.
When we hung out,
you two were inseparable.
Do you know how awful it feels
to be a third wheel?
Ta-da!
- My gosh.
- What's that?
Where did you get it?
My dad made this plum wine. I stole it.
That's wild!
We can't drink. We're still minors.
Why not? Seniors drink 100 days
before the CSAT.
This can be our drink
before the exam, too.
Do you even know how to drink?
No, but we can find out by drinking this.
Our youth is...
- Now!
Bottoms up!
It's sweet.
- I can feel it running down.
- I know.
How strong is this?
You don't eat but drink well.
I guess I'm cut out for it.
Let's have another.
- Hey, Mi Na.
- Yes?
What's going on with San?
Yes, give us the scoop.
He likes me. It was love at first sight.
Look at you, Mi Na.
Cut that out.
Are you two going out then?
We're not at that point yet.
I'm just meeting him since he likes me.
Since we're at it, tell him to come.
- Right here?
- Send him a DM to tell him you miss him.
Would he come right away if he likes you?
Hey, this is my home.
Sorry, I'm drunk.
Ignore her. Her switch is off.
Okay.
- Why are you here?
- Me? Well...
Mi Na said he missed me, so...
And you don't miss her?
What do you like about Mi Na?
She's just pretty.
She's really kind and mature.
How far did you two go?
Stop it. You'll suffocate him.
- Are you okay?
- I'm okay.
Mom's calling me.
- Let me answer this.
- Okay.
- Wake Ye Ri up.
I said I'm fine.
Don't worry. I'll sleep soon.
Okay, Mom. Bye.
I feel tipsy.
- Lean on me.
- Okay.
- San.
- Yes?
Next time.
When you're sober.
(Fragile)