They've gone crazy.
You can't stay quiet.
They'll go even wilder if you ignore them.
Did you send Ji Yu those stupid DMs?
Aren't you being biased
just because Do Ha's my friend?
- He went home early today.
- What?
He hasn't been doing well lately.
But at this point, we're both...
Why did you bring me here?
Did you two make up? Why?
How far did you two go?
Next time. When you're sober.
(Fragile)
No more candidates, right?
So are we going with them?
Me!
I have one! Basketball jerseys!
Class Five is already wearing it.
If these are it,
we'll go straight to voting.
We have to decide on one fast.
Do you like basketball?
No, it's not like that.
She's dating a guy who likes basketball.
Hey!
We'll go with a taekwondo uniform then.
Finally.
We're ordering them this week,
so check your sizes and let me know.
Also, we need to decide
who will participate in what.
You all have to participate in
at least one.
I don't feel like it.
Why not?
I'll get burnt.
Wear sunscreen.
A Ra, can you participate
in one more for me?
No, and I was going to
participate in everything.
Anyone for the race?
We need two boys and two girls.
- Me!
- Okay, A Ra.
Any boys? Quickly.
Okay.
Any more girls?
Hurry up. I'll take recommendations, too.
Ji Yu, do you want to run, too?
No, I want to recommend someone.
Who?
Han Su Jin.
- Su Jin?
- Yes.
Su Jin is good at running.
She would always win races
back in middle school.
That's a relief.
Will you be okay with it?
Yes, I'm fine with it.
Okay then.
Now let's pick out for dodgeball.
(Chapter 51
Tuesday, October 22nd, 2024)
We need to talk.
About last time,
I didn't know Si Jung would go that far.
Me, too.
I'm sorry I doubted you.
No. I doubted you, too.
Hey, Su Jin.
I'm really sorry.
About hurting you.
It'll sound like an excuse,
but I had a huge crush on Chan Seong.
I'm sorry.
It wasn't just anyone.
I shouldn't have done that to you.
I get it, so you can stop.
I'll stop hating you,
so you stop being sorry to me.
But how did you know before?
About me wanting to run.
I saw your fingers.
What?
When you're thinking about something,
you crack them.
Right.
(Chapter 52
Tuesday, October 22nd, 2024)
Have you thought about a phrase?
- Yes.
- What is it?
- Guess what this is.
- "Titanic?"
The free hug.
That's classic. What about you?
"Count on me, sister!"
"Victory for Class Three."
I'll upload it on my Instagram
to get more followers.
Will that work?
- But do I have to do this?
- Of course. You all have to.
You have to since your friend
is serious about sports day.
I haven't thought of what to use.
- Should I recommend one?
- What?
"Class Five, the cuties."
- That's cute.
- Are you crazy?
You expect me to go with that?
- "Cute girl?"
- No.
"Cool girl?"
I'm not doing this.
Then do other things.
Something like sunshades or fans.
Never mind. I'll find something.
I can do it.
Okay.
Look at them.
Are you done?
- You didn't forget.
- I didn't forget.
Do it again.
You're in Class Three, too.
I can't believe you came up
with something using your name.
Make me one with my name, too.
With A Ra.
"I know you, A Ra."
That's too lame for sports day.
You're so good.
- You have a knack for it.
- Really? Is it good?
Yes, you're good.
Ye Ri, what are you doing?
What is that?
- Is it that bad?
- Yes, it is.
It's so hard.
Give it to me.
- That's...
- This is a lost cause.
- I'll have to do what I can.
- Forget about that.
- What do you think?
- It's pretty.
It's pretty, right?
(Class Five, cuties)
(Chapter 53
Wednesday, October 23rd, 2024)
It didn't say it was going to rain.
It must be a passing shower.
Should we just run to the bus stop?
Hey!
"I hope you fall!"
That sounds a bit rough, right?
I guess.
Should we just use it then?
I guess we should.
This is great.
- I think he likes you.
- Stop it.
- Seriously.
- No, he doesn't.
Superhero
Ayy, zip-zap zoom, come on, comе on
Hold me tight, just here we go
No, you don't have to be scared
Never give up
- Baby, trust you and me
- Is it San?
- Yes.
How is it? Is it going well?
(Chapter 54
Thursday, October 24th, 2024)
- You're so good.
- You're good.
She must not be coming.
She's busy. She's full of love and all.
It's the best time.
I'm seriously reflecting.
All of a sudden?
I didn't know San felt that way.
In a way,
he's good at keeping a poker face.
How can you know everything,
even if you're close friends?
That's true.
Why are you here without San?
San and I decided to just stay friends.
- What?
- Why?
He wasn't my boyfriend. Why so surprised?
Then what was he?
I thought about going steady
since he liked me,
but I think we're better off as friends.
You've matured in a way.
I know. Something is different.
Are you really okay?
Yes, I'm really fine.
Anyway, I'm in, too.
Cancel this round!
Hey!
- I was winning.
- I'll shuffle it.
That's good. I was losing.
(Chapter 55
Thursday, October 24th, 2024)
Ji Yu is here. Isn't she looking for you?
What is it? Are you looking for Ye Ri?
- Is San here?
- San?
San is at the teachers' lounge.
Is this urgent?
No, I'll send him a DM later.
The bell will ring. I should go.
Are you free later in the evening?
Hey, you were looking for San, right?
Yes.
Why San? Have you messaged him?
No, I should talk to him in person.
Is something wrong?
Don't you think San is acting differently?
I can't see a big difference,
but something does feel different.
Why did you want to see me?
Let's get off and talk. We should get out.
Let's just keep going.
What?
Let's just go to your place.
I'll walk you home.
You brought me to my home a lot.
I'm glad it stopped raining.
Yes, it must have been a shower.
I worried that it might rain until late.
You didn't bring an umbrella either?
We could just buy one.
It's just...
we might not be able to talk for long.
I thought about it a lot.
About what?
About being with you.
About understanding you
and resolving our issues.
About what to say first
and things like that.
It was hard.
- But...
- Chan Seong.
It was so hard to be with you.
What?
I betrayed my best friend.
I felt so uncomfortable.
I gave up my friend to be with you.
I had to ignore those feelings
to be together with you.
When you're smiling, having a good time,
I somewhat got annoyed
even if I was laughing with you.
Once I had that in my mind,
it was endless.
I kept doubting you and Su Jin,
and kept obsessing over it.
Then I think I slowly lost myself.
Do you regret being with me?
No. I don't regret liking you.
But my behavior hurt someone.
And moreover,
I couldn't look after myself.
I think I know what's important to me now.
I...
So this is why you brought me home.
Let's break up.
I'm sorry.
Me, too.
Here you go.
Bye.
(Chapter 56
Friday, October 25th, 2024)
How do I look? Do I look okay?
Yes.
What's the point of asking?
You're dressing up for sports day.
Even so...
- Am I cute?
- Yes.
You're cute.
- How can you be okay?
- What?
It didn't work out between Mi Na and San.
Ji Yu and Chan Seong broke up,
but she's so alive.
We should have fun when it's a fun day.
And we have you guys.
Eun Su, you don't seem to know.
I, Jeon Mi Na, learned so much.
I see.
Also...
Never mind. Anyway,
you told me to be careful
and now you want me to cry?
Never.
Here's the money.
Ji Yu, just stay there.
It's so crowded.
Please don't push.
- What?
- Do you like cats?
- All of a sudden?
- It's not all of a sudden.
I asked you on a DM before.
I see.
Why don't you read my DMs?
I know you can hear me.
Do I have to answer that now here?
I'd rather just answer it.
- Why do I have to read them?
- I'm just asking you to accept me.
Why do you hate me?
I also don't understand
why you're so interested in me.
I like you. Isn't that enough?
I'll pay for everything.
Thank you.
It's on me, so enjoy.
See you later.
Also, answer my DMs.
Are you okay?
Well, it's free food.
Let's go. The girls are waiting.
Over our heads, please.
A little further up.
What are you doing?
Thanks.
- What?
So you ordered food, too.
Ji Yu, this must be ours.
They look so good together.
What are you talking about?
The rice cake and chicken
go together so well, right?
- You're right.
- Try it.
- They do go together so well.
- Yes.
I've never seen you with braids.
The girls did it for me.
It suits you.
Thanks.
My goodness.
- What?
- My gosh.
- Did you drop it?
- Do you have a tissue?
No.
- Hi.
What got on your clothes?
The girls and I had rice cakes.
Do you want to eat with us?
No, my stomach doesn't feel good.
Are you nervous?
What?
Good luck at the race.
Are you going to root for me?
Of course.
Sorry.
I'm okay.
Nice shot.
Let's go, Class Three!
- Class Three!
- Let's go!
Class Three!
- Class Three, let's go!
- Let's go!
- Hey!
- San!
Are you okay?
- Are you okay?
- Are you okay? Where does it hurt?
This is bad.
- This is bad.
- He must be hurting.
Be careful.
This is bad.
- He needs to see the nurse.
- Are you okay?
(Nurse's Office)
- What's going on these days?
- What?
What's with you?
Look at your handsome face.
You're completely out of it.
Why would you get pushed by that?
It's nothing.
Is it because of Mi Na?
What?
You must have liked her a lot.
Is it hard because it's not working out?
Is this a post-breakup breakdown?
Shouldn't I be getting it?
I broke up with Ji Yu.
Stop it. It's not that.
So I'm saying
you should tell me
so that I can help you as a friend.
What is it?
Do you really want to know?
Yes.
(Fragile)