[This series is a work of fiction.
All characters, locations, and events are entirely fabricated.]
[Previously]
Besides this drug,
the disease can also be transmitted
through blood.
Technically, those people are already dead.
If I become one of those rage things one day,
please kill me.
Let's get to know our neighbors.
Do you suspect anyone in particular?
Everyone seems suspicious.
What's the point of this meeting?
Shouldn't we find a way
to protect ourselves from them?
Can you please take care of your grandson?
You're probably believing
those rumors in the group chat.
Zombies only exist in movies.
He posted it himself!
See? See? See?
Beam?
It's me, Run.
This is my senior from high school.
This is Prach. He's my--
I'm Run's husband.
Get to the Get Hi pub right away.
Yayee!
Da, I'm home.
Okay.
The Next drug is spreading in a new form.
Traces of Next have been found
in supplements and vitamins.
We've also discovered that
the new version of Next,
when mixed with water,
changes from red to clear,
like plain water.
[Psytaline]
Yes, sir.
Ah, I've received it.
Just a moment, sir.
Kai…
Don't shoot Kai! If you shoot him,
he'll really die for real!
This isn't Kai, Inspector.
He's already dead.
He can recover.
Kai has to recover.
Kai! Get a hold of yourself!
Kai! Get a hold of yourself, Kai!
Kai!
[Happiness]
You're awake?
Why did you tie me up? Let me go!
Do you even realize what you've done?
What did I do?
I didn't do anything! Let me go!
How did you get infected?
Infected with what?
Were you bitten or did you take the drug?
I'll be right back.
It must be chaotic downstairs.
But don't worry, Beam.
The Special Control Unit will take care of it.
You said he was infected from
being bitten or from that drug.
What do you mean by that?
To be honest, I don't know much either.
I only know that…
this drug can cause people to become violent.
I see.
I wonder who else is infected down there.
That's what I'm wondering too.
You need to get checked
along with the others.
This way, please.
Run called to report another case
at The Breathe Condo.
I've sent a backup team.
You can return to the center now.
Chief, please come this way.
The infected has escaped.
Spread out and search. Be careful.
Try not to alarm the residents.
Captain, collect this evidence.
[Prach]
Thank you so much, Beam.
No, I should be thanking you.
Thank me?
For what?
Well…
That was the first meal in six years
that I've had with someone.
You live alone like this.
If you ever need help, let me know.
Thank you.
[Where are you now?
Are you coming home yet?]
[Prach]
Yayee…
Yayee, we're here.
Okay, you're awake. Carefully now.
Okay.
Okay…
Thank you for walking us.
You should go inside now, Run.
I'll be leaving now.
Yayee, you're sleeping with me tonight.
Your mom probably won't be back yet.
Thank you, Dr. Beam.
Sure.
Come on.
Stop!
Found him!
Please let me go!
I didn't do it! I didn't do it!
There's an emergency at The Breathe Condo.
We've found a large number of
infected individuals.
The officers we sent have become infected
along with a number of residents.
Hey, you two! Don't fight!
Stop!
Initiate the emergency response plan.
Yes, sir.
- So what now?
- Now what?
- How do we get home now?
- We need to go to work.
- Yeah, we have to go home.
- We still have to go to work.
- You're responsible for this.
- We're already late.
- You can't do this to us.
- Yeah, this is a waste of time.
Excuse me,
I don't live here. Can I leave?
No, you can't.
We can't let anyone through.
We have to quarantine everyone
in this condo.
What?
Attention, residents of The Breathe Condo.
I am Yutthasak Suwannasiri,
Director of the Special Control Unit.
I regret to inform you that, at this moment,
there is an outbreak of a new disease
in The Breathe Condo.
Relevant agencies do not yet have
definitive information on this disease.
Therefore, for your own safety
and to prevent the spread of the disease,
we ask for your cooperation
in remaining in your residences.
And without absolutely necessary,
please do not leave your condo phase
for at least
7 days.
This is to avoid contracting
the infection.
If there is any further information or changes,
the Special Control Unit
will promptly inform you.
We hereby ask
for your cooperation at this time.
[Lockdown]
Run…
I couldn't reach Yayee's mom,
so I left a note on her door
so she knows Yayee is with me.
Where have you been?
Let's talk inside. Come on.
You know, I almost died last night.
Luckily, Beam saved me just in time.
Well… Are you alright?
I'm fine. I wasn't bitten by the infected.
But Beam and I captured him.
In the fitness room.
Don't you dare… disappear like that again.
Run, is my mom back yet?
How about this, Yayee?
I'll go check if your mom is back,
but for now, stay with Run, okay?
Good girl.
Are you hungry?
You must be hungry.
Hello. Welcome.
Please change your clothes first.
Do you have any water?
Yes, the water is over there.
Help! Help! Somebody help me!
Please, help!
What's going on here?
I found the dealer.
If you catch him, this is over, right?
It's too late.
The infected are now spread
throughout the entire condo complex.
We tried to send in forces
to control the situation,
but the number of infected here is
increasing rapidly,
and it's more than our personnel can handle.
All we can do is seal off the phases
with the most infected.
Fortunately, we know that
light can disrupt their perception.
I need you to warn the residents
not to leave their rooms at night.
Leave a team here to monitor the situation
in case there are infected hiding in the condo.
Report any updates.
If you find any infected,
we emphasize that
you must capture them alive.
Do not kill them.
Yes, ma'am.
The rest of the team, stand by at the unit.
And we still haven't found the trainer.
You have to help us deal with this.
But we only agreed to find
the drug dealer, didn't we?
The infected are spreading
throughout the building.
That's not even including the people
who took the drug,
and we don't even know
where they got it from.
Soon, all these people will turn
into rage monsters.
But isn't that your job?
That trainer often comes to this condo
before going out to sell the drugs.
I believe that if he can do this,
he's not working alone.
Either way, I have to
seal off this entire condo.
If you disagree,
you can leave this area right now.
But if you're willing to help,
we need to find out who's behind this.
And we might even find a cure
for this disease.
Hello, residents of The Breathe Condo.
I am Arisara Kaewrod.
I have been assigned to oversee and
coordinate the quarantine within this condo
to ensure it runs smoothly.
The man who was restrained
that you all saw earlier
is a suspected infected individual.
This disease is called Rage Disease.
It is not transmitted through touch,
saliva, or any bodily fluids.
Therefore, everyone can continue their lives
in the condo as usual.
The initial symptoms of this disease
include dizziness,
rapid breathing, abnormal sweating,
dry throat, coughing, intense thirst,
rapid heartbeat, tremors, and seizures,
leading to a loss of self-control.
If you experience any of these symptoms,
please contact the staff
using the contact information on the card
you are about to receive.
And to prevent the spread of the disease,
please quarantine yourselves in your own units.
As for food and other management,
we will take care of it.
There you go.
Well… If anyone has any problems,
contact them.
That's for all three of you.
How are we supposed to work?
Yeah, right.
Did you hear the announcement?
They will take care of everything.
All we have to do is stay calm
and quarantine ourselves.
Who said we had to?
They just asked us to cooperate.
I'm telling you to quarantine.
Hey, excuse me,
but where are we supposed to quarantine?
You can stay in the maid's room
downstairs for now.
What?
Oh, about the garbage, please take it to…
the common area floors.
That way, there won't be any odor problems
in the residential floors.
Stock up on food and supplies.
The minimart in our condo is still open.
It will probably stay open
at least until the supplies run out.
Just go stock up.
Then who will be the representative
to go pick up the food?
I will.
Is that a good idea?
Sending a woman?
I can handle it myself. Is that okay?
I'll go too.
Then we have enough volunteers.
Thank you.
Actually, you don't have to come.
Hey…
I'm worried. I'm afraid you'll get tired.
I'll be fine.
We can help each other
if anything happens.
Okay.
Thank you very much
for helping Run the other day.
But from now on,
you don't have to worry about her.
I'll take care of Run myself.
It's no problem.
I'm happy to help.
Okay.
Which building?
- Building C.
Please give us a lot.
It won't be enough. Please give us more.
I'm afraid it won't be enough.
Bring us a lot!
Hurry up!
Divide into groups and as periods of time,
instead of turns.
In case someone wants to escape from here.
Which building?
Building B.
Move closer.
- Yes, sir!
Quickly, quickly.
Hurry up.
We need to gather more information
on the residents.
I brought you some food.
Supplies delivery.
Hello, Doctor.
Hello. Just the two of you?
Yes.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Jeu and Fah…
I saw Fah getting out of the trainer's car.
The trainer.
Don't forget that I saw the trainer
being close with Yoshi.
Sophida might be involved too.
Hey, Run.
Are you interested in becoming
a member of the condo committee?
It's not really my thing.
I'm more of an action person.
Alright. Thank you.
Sure.
These two are obsessed with their positions
in the condo management.
They might be taking advantage of it.
There're instant noodles, canned fish,
and paracetamol.
- Rice…
- Rice?
- We all have the same things.
- That's all?
To eat for so many days?
I'll be bored to death.
We have free food for many days.
We'll save so much money.
I could stay quarantined
for a whole month like this.
Oh, Grandpa…
If we have to eat like this for a whole month,
I can't take it.
I can only make 2-3 content videos
before it gets boring.
Jee… Don't complain so much.
It's better to have food to eat.
This kid…
I can't handle him.
Just this much? How is this enough
for three people?
Come on, honey.
We have other things stored away.
And I have to cook for your secretary too?
Rangrong helped me
with urgent work all night.
She's stuck here because of me.
Have some sympathy for her.
Does she really need to eat, sleep,
and work in her boss's room all day?
Honey,
don't overthink it.
You're the only one for me.
Everyone else is just an employee.
I don't see them as anything more than that.
Babe…
I miss you so much.
If you miss me so much,
why don't you just leave that Auntie already?
How long do you want me to wait? Huh?
Babe, you know that I still need her money.
I don't care.
Just break up with her.
Even if we starve, I won't care.
I'll break up with her,
but please wait a little longer.
Trust me, okay?
Okay.
But you must break up with that Auntie
for real.
Where have you been?
I went out for some fresh air.
You don't tell me
where you're going anymore.
I won't go anywhere.
Don't be mad at me, okay?
Here you go.
Thank you.
These are all of Miss Run's test results.
There's nothing unusual.
Here we go…
Wow…
Whoa,
how long will this take to finish, Yayee?
Help me put these together.
Okay.
Yayee… Your mom is calling.
Mommy!
Yayee, I heard the news about the condo.
It must be very chaotic, right?
Come back soon, Mommy.
Stay with Run for now, sweetie.
Don't be naughty, okay?
Where are you, Mommy?
They've closed off the condo.
No one can enter or leave.
If I could get in,
I would go to you right away, sweetie.
Mommy…
Mommy loves you, Yayee.
I miss Mommy.
Please bring her back to me.
I'll bring her back to you.
Come on. Keep playing.
It's okay. I'll take care of it.
You and our child will get better.
I'm close to finding the solution.
You and our child will be okay.
Run, did my mom call again?
Let me check.
Yayee, your mom hasn't called yet.
She's probably trying to find a way to get in.
Should I try calling her again?
Okay.
Hello?
Hi, Dad.
Oh, Run? How are you?
I'm going on an official trip
to another province.
You might not see me for a while.
Well,
you always make your own decisions
about where you want to go
and what you want to do.
And if you need anything, just call me.
If I can't answer, I'll call you back.
Okay.
Hey.
Are you asleep yet?
What?
You can't sleep?
Yeah.
You see,
the dream home I imagined
now seems to be out of reach.
How about this?
Just think of it as a scout camp.
With mentors guarding outside.
That's not helping at all.
Come on, we will get through it.
Will we really get through this?
Yeah, we'll get through this together.
I'll protect you.
That gave me goosebumps.
Go back to sleep.
Miss Run's blood test results are back.
Her blood only temporarily inhibits
the disease's progression.
The lab needs more blood samples
to repeat the test and confirm.
If you need it, then go get her.
Yes, sir.
Here it is.
I've prepared the most delicious breakfast
in the world for you.
The egg isn't burnt, I promise.
Come on, Yayee…
Yayee?
Yayee, what's wrong?
Yayee!
My inhaler is out.
You have asthma?
We need to do another blood test.
We've changed to new equipment,
which will give us more accurate results.
Okay, I can do the test, but I can't be there.
If you want to do the test,
you have to come here.
Oh, and if you do come,
please bring 3-4 Ventolin inhalers.
There's someone here with asthma.
If my blood is so important,
then come right now.
And another thing, find someone for me.
Da…
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
Come in.
Director, the lab team reported
on Miss Run's blood test.
She might have antibodies in her blood.
There's a 10% chance.
I'll take it, even with a 1% chance.
Go get her here.
She refused to come.
Hello? Yeah…
Yayee has asthma.
What?
But don't worry.
I've already given her first aid.
But I need you to look after her for a bit.
I'll be back soon.
Where are you now?
I'm waiting for Joy.
Joy? Who brought her in?
I have to go.
Yutthasak is here.
Hey, Run. Wait--
How are you doing, Yayee?
Where did Run go?
Run is doing a security check.
Be strong, okay?
You'll feel better soon.
Where is Joy?
She's with us now.
She's been with us
since before you asked for our help.
What do you mean?
Why are you doing this to me?
How can I go back to my daughter now?
Stay with Run for now, sweetie.
Don't be naughty, okay?
Mommy loves you, Yayee.
Yayee, you're my only happiness.
So she's still alive?
She's alive for now.
And because of that, we need your help.
We need you to give us more blood samples.
[Prach]
Alright. Now rest well.
Run?
We need you to give us more blood samples.
But I said I needed two days, didn't I?
But we don't have time.
You have to come with me now. Let's go.
- Then let me call Prach first.
- Run…
Okay.
Hey!
Run?
Run!
We need you to give us more blood samples.
Then let me call Prach first.
Okay.
Open the gate.
Thank you.
Hey!
Just now…
I found something covered in blood.
Calm down and tell us.
What did you find in the condo?
Is it a movie promotion?
Open up!
Just open the door for him.
He's making a big fuss right now.
Help me! Help me!
Back away!
Just like what I saw.
Monster!
Even if they bring food tomorrow,
who would dare go out and get it?
I'll go.
How much per person would be appropriate?
Someone's desperate for money.
We have to do something.
They probably…
have their own reasons for not announcing it.
If they won't say anything, we have to.
Clear everything out.
Director,
we found the trainer
who is suspected to be infected.
He's dead.
So you lied to us?
I did not lie.
I just didn't think you needed to know
because even if you did,
it won't be of any use.