Here.
Find a page that tickles your fancy.
We're using this?
I thought you'd bring me
a textbook for kids.
It's best to learn
with what you're interested in.
You're sounding like a teacher.
I am a certified teacher.
That's true.
Wow. This is great.
Wow!
This one!
The Keikyu train.
Yeah, that's the one.
When I was younger,
I often rode this train to Miura Beach.
How have you been?
My mom used to take me
so she could see a guy.
I didn't like the reason,
but the sea was beautiful.
I went there on a school trip
in elementary school.
- Really?
- Yes.
Maybe we crossed paths then.
I don't think you were born then.
I guess not…
Sorry.
Okay, let's begin.
Please feel free to use this.
Let's try writing what it says there.
May I?
Look here,
"Ride the Keikyu line
and experience summer at Miura Beach!"
What was it again? The Keikyu…
"Ride the Keikyu line."
Keikyu…
By the way…
What is the point
of learning how to write?
If you learn how to read and write,
you can read books, write letters, and…
it'll broaden your horizons.
You think so?
Not being a good student
made me a smooth talker,
which proved helpful
in the service industry.
RIDE THE KEIKYU
How's this?
They all make that face.
I told you it was impossible to teach me.
I don't think it's impossible!
Let's start with the simple stuff.
So listen…
The vertical lines are written
from top to bottom
and horizontal lines
are from left to right.
This is the same for any kanji.
Try it.
- Me? Now?
- Yes.
Top to bottom and left to right.
Exactly!
With this kanji for "Kei" in Keikyu.
- There's a square box.
- Yes.
The left side is just
a straight vertical line
but the horizontal line goes left to right
and then straight
into the next vertical line.
Straight in. Okay.
And then write the line
from left to right to close the box.
Try it!
Ready?
- Top to bottom…
- Straight.
- Yes.
- And then left to right.
- Yes!
Then…
- Straight down like this!
- Straight.
To finish it off?
Left to right.
There you go! Very good!
- Yeah, right.
- I mean it! You're a natural!
You're good at flattery.
Oh, I know!
You should work at a hostess bar!
I have some connections.
No, thank you.
I get awkward talking
to people I don't know.
I was only joking.
We're complete opposites.
Everything's a joke to me.
TRAIN TRAVELS
I envy you.
I take everything seriously…
I have false hopes and get shocked.
And then you get mad and bite people?
Exactly! I'm a chihuahua, after all!
A customer requested me, so I need to go.
Okay.
I need to prepare for my classes.
How about this Saturday at this time?
I'll give you an assignment then!
An assignment?
Please practice writing this sentence.
ASSIGNMENT
Okay…
Understood.
Thank you.
See you.
No student of mine
had ever thanked me before.
It made me happy that I was able to help
someone even though I'm a bad teacher.
- Hey! How's it going?
- Hey!
- Don't be too eager.
- Okay.
- Hey!
- Hi.
My parents said our families
should meet as soon as possible.
What do you think?
Yeah.
My dad said to invite your family to ours.
He was rolling his shoulder, but…
But?
I'm worried because he can be rude.
Is he?
He seems a little strict,
but he's a very good dad.
You haven't seen it all yet.
He's got such high expectations
for who I marry.
Then, I'll think of it
as a job interview with an executive.
It feels a bit sudden,
but how about this Saturday?
Yes, that would…
Sorry, I have plans this Saturday evening.
How about Sunday?
Yeah, I think that works.
Can I ask what you're doing?
What?
This Saturday evening.
I have a student
who's falling behind in class,
so I'm helping with their assignments.
Oh, private tutoring!
- You're so devoted!
- No! Not really!
Hey. Were you working late?
No, I was having dinner with Mr. Kawahara.
Really? Any progress?
We're arranging for our families to meet.
Wow.
Okay, let me tell you as a divorcee,
how not to screw it up.
Whatever you do, don't put on an act.
- It'll make your life easier.
- Here.
Thank you. You're my rock.
By the way, how did it go with the host?
What was his name… Kaoru?
Why?
Our show's doing a special feature
on the host murder.
And I want to interview him.
You don't have to run it by me, you know.
I'm not running it by you.
I just wanted to ask what he's like.
You called him about your student, right?
Yeah, but it was a quick interaction.
Never mind then. Let's meet up next week.
See you.
I hadn't lied to Momoko in a long time.
I don't have the desire
to tell my friend everything, but…
it was an unnecessary lie.
The submission
of the career path survey is due soon.
Have you decided on your path?
If you're struggling to decide,
please come talk to me!
I felt lost too when I had to decide.
Why did you feel lost?
I…
I wanted to work in publishing.
So I wanted to study literature at
a university not attached to this school.
However…
My parents…
Well, mainly my dad said,
"Girls shouldn't go through hardships.
No need to take an exam for university."
That's unbelievable.
Isn't that sexism?
What he said is unthinkable now, right?
I knew he was just worried about me,
and my grades weren't great.
So, I chose the university
affiliated with this school.
You gave in.
I felt frustrated.
But because of that,
I tried very hard while job hunting
and got a job at my dream company.
Sorry for going on a tangent.
Anyway, as I just mentioned,
after many different experiences,
I finally decided to be a teacher.
What I want to say is,
it's okay to make wrong decisions.
It's never too late for a second chance.
Class dismissed!
Stand up.
Bow. Goodbye.
Goodbye.
Your family is kind of similar to mine.
You think so?
Parents who want to control
their daughters,
and daughters who give in to them.
That's why you're rebelling?
A bit childish, huh?
I thought you were much more mature
than me when I was in high school.
Are you seeing someone recently?
What?
Everyone's saying
that you've been different lately.
I do have someone I'm engaged to.
Don't tell anyone, okay?
Miss.
I…
I'll go to a university in the US.
If I want to change, I need to leave home.
So I need information on scholarships.
Okay.
And about Kaoru…
I'm over him.
What?
I…
I guess I wanted to escape
from my parents and my studies.
But I know we live in different worlds.
Different worlds?
No matter how good-looking or kind he is…
He is a host.
There's no future for us.
I'm going to study hard,
go to a good university,
date someone who's a catch,
and have an amazing campus life.
See you.
She's right.
But…
My heart ached a little
by how an 18-year-old girl
talked about different worlds.
This is Kaoru. Do you remember me?
I guess you can't forget,
I'm too handsome!
Hey, can we meet soon? I miss you!
I've made it into the top ten
so come see me to celebrate!
Hey, stop!
Really? Thank you!
Ms. Ogawa.
I heard today's homeroom went well.
- Oh, I think so.
- Nice.
Wait, Mr. Sakura!
You did your master's
on learning disabilities, right?
Yes, I did.
How come?
I want to learn how I should interact
with such students.
What?
There are different kinds
of learning disabilities.
Also, I doubt any
of our students have any.
Just in general terms is fine.
What if they struggle with literacy?
Can they understand sentences
if they hear them?
Their communication skills
when conversing is…
possibly better than an average person.
But they can hardly write any kanji.
I see…
Some people have difficulties
connecting the sounds to letters.
They tend to struggle in school.
How do you teach someone who grew up
that way and is already an adult?
You should avoid forcing them
as you could end up hurting them.
But there must be a way!
Why are you so eager
if we're speaking in general?
I guess it doesn't matter.
Anyway, it's important
to get used to reading and writing first.
Also good stationery.
Stationery?
Ballpoint pens can make
them nervous as it's unerasable
so I heard pencils are better.
- Pencils.
- Yes.
FOR A BEAUTIFUL WRITING FORM
TAIGA TAKAMORI
They didn't have it…
- Oh! This is the one!
- This one?
This is what I wanted!
- How about this one?
- No, definitely this one!
For sure!
- Looks nice to write with.
- Right?
He didn't come.
I felt a little relieved.
Ms. Chihuahua!
Sorry. Did you wait long?
You're 18 minutes late.
I was making these. Here you go.
That's considerate.
I am a host.
Okay. Cheers!
Let's begin.
Yes, Miss!
I like the enthusiasm.
TRAIN TRAVELS
Very well.
I shall gift you some learning materials!
Ta-da!
Ta-da? That's kind of lame.
And this is for me?
Open it.
It's inexpensive, but it writes nicely,
use it to practice.
The lead comes out if you press here,
and there's an eraser in there too.
It's so cool.
I was lost for words for a second.
Yeah, right.
No, I mean it!
No one's ever given me a pen before!
Okay, let's check your assignment.
I see, this is how it works.
And if I press here, it goes back…
Show me your notebook!
The color's great.
And this is the eraser I see.
Mr. Takamori! Your assignment?
I was going to do it
but work was busy and…
As a host, you should come up
with a better excuse.
It's true!
Right now,
the battle for first place is intense.
First place?
A spot all hosts aspire to.
Especially this month,
as it's the tenth anniversary of the club.
Everyone's trying but…
I'm so close to winning.
I can't go to the club!
Teachers can't go to host clubs!
Many do actually.
I'm not trying to force you to come.
Are you relieved?
Or are you sad?
Sad?
If I force you to come,
you'll have an excuse.
Even teachers must have some desire
to go to a host club.
Not at all.
I'm sure any woman would have
the desire to be pampered by young men.
At least I know I don't!
- So boring.
- What?
You're so boring.
You're a really boring woman.
So self-conscious and nervous.
What?
Miss.
You might be academic,
but I don't think you're smart.
What do you mean?
You can't enjoy life
being scared of everything!
You know, like…
Go crazy and just have fun!
It's not that easy!
Is it not? I think it is!
For example, try this right here.
Just by dancing around a bit
things look a little brighter!
I trained as a dancer at a cabaret once.
Pretty good, right?
Spin…
Stop it.
I'll leave if we're not studying.
Fine by me. Goodbye.
You're not obliged to teach me.
And to be honest,
I wasn't really feeling it.
Taking lessons
to learn writing at this age?
Who does that?
It's okay for an idiot to stay an idiot.
Oh really?
Why didn't you tell me sooner, then?
If you're so popular and busy,
why did you take the time to come?
Oh my…
It's because I wanted to see you.
Don't mock me!
It's true.
I will not fall for a host's sales talk!
Miss, you're so cute.
Lesson over!
Oh, you're actually leaving. What?
So I was forcing him to learn.
I wanted to feel good
by doing something teacherly.
I guess I also thought
we lived in different worlds.
No more. That's it.
"There"… No, that's not right…
15 YEARS AGO
"Went there and
I found a cat"…
and a poop suddenly attacked!
Everyone got covered in poop!
- Gross!
- What are you saying?
Takamori!
Read it properly!
Show us your notebook!
You've nothing written!
- You're so dumb!
- Dumb!
Dumb! Come on, let's go!
KANJI TEST
EAST
Stop breaking it.
Why can't you write normally?
Only one horizontal line here.
How are you so stupid?
How's it going with the teacher?
What?
You said she'll become your customer.
Yeah, soon, I think.
- It's taking quite a long time.
- Our boss always says not to rush it.
The longer it takes for her
to let her guard down,
the better the outcome.
And how do you do that?
I make her angry.
Very angry.
Really?
Women tend to make excuses
after getting mad at someone
because they don't want to be disliked.
So you just need to take
that opportunity to be nice to them.
Impressive!
As expected of our future number one!
Thank you for teaching me!
Future? Don't you mean
the next number one?
Oh, sorry.
But knowing that much about women
must make dating quite boring?
I don't date.
Really? But you must've fallen
for someone before?
No, I haven't.
- You must have!
- I haven't!
- Tell me! Please!
- Stop. Oh, someone's calling.
HAG
What?
Hey, Taiga.
Something wrong with Yuki?
No, he's fine.
Thanks for the other day.
Don't be so wary.
I just called to say thank you.
Can you wait a minute?
Yuki, your brother.
Taiga! Thank you for helping us!
Are you better?
I've been fine all along!
Hey, Taiga. When will you read me a book?
Next time.
Okay!
So yeah…
I will return the money when I can.
It's fine. I'm just glad Yuki's okay.
Thank you.
You take care of yourself, too.
A host got stabbed, right? I'm worried.
See you.
How was that?
He is a host.
Deceiving people is part of his job.
It's a necessary preparation.
Regarding your question…
The answer's no.
I've never truly fallen for a woman,
and I'm sure I never will.
RIDE THE KEIKYU LINE
AND EXPERIENCE SUMMER AT MIURA BEACH
PIETAS GIRLS' HIGH SCHOOL
Good morning.
- Good morning!
- Morning!
Good morning.
What's that about?
It looks like a ransom note.
It's nothing.
MS. MANAMI OGAWA
TAIGA TAKAMORI
You're so boring.
Cheers to our families'
bright future together!
Cheers!
I bet people
at the Japan Business Federation
will be amazed to know
that we'll be related soon!
I still can't believe it!
What a surprise!
Stop it already!
You're stealing the spotlight!
Sorry! I got carried away!
I heard you teach
at Pietas Girls' High School, Manami?
I do. I teach Japanese.
I see.
Please teach our son some Japanese.
It was his weakest subject in school.
Although he was often
at the top in math class.
Don't brag like that.
Manami wasn't good at math,
so I think they'll be a good match.
- They can help each other.
- So… Hey.
What kind of family do you want to have?
Well…
It might sound boring,
but I want to build a happy home.
Everyone wants that.
What I mean is that whatever issues
we have, I want to face them with a smile.
Shouldn't you face your issues
in a serious manner?
Well, yes. I think it depends
on what the issue is, and I meant it as…
Bankers work in such
a demanding environment
so you said you want
to take it easy at home, right?
I did. In order to devote myself to work,
I think a good
work-life balance is needed.
That's a good mindset to have, but…
it mustn't be your priority
if you want to succeed.
I recommend working
until you sweat blood at least once.
Yes. Sweat blood?
Sorry, my husband's
not very good at making jokes.
It wasn't a joke.
You know nothing about
the outside world, so zip it.
- How about it?
- Please start.
Thank you.
- I'll get more tea.
- Sorry!
Thank you!
Please don't worry too much.
My son is ambitious.
With Manami's support, he can do anything.
Manami is humble but also very determined.
That's why I became
even more attracted to her.
Oh, aren't you smitten!
I wish I could be young again!
I'm envious! It's lovely to see this.
- Please eat!
- Yes.
Kaoru. You have a customer at Table K.
- Thank you for choosing me!
- Kaoru!
By yourself today?
Is that bad?
Not at all! I'm happy to see you!
Yay.
Has Ms. Chihuahua been here lately?
I can't tell you
about other customers, sorry!
But we're friends.
Does that mean
you're a school teacher too?
- Thank you for the drink.
- Sure.
I hate sneaking around,
so let me get straight to it.
JBC TV PROGRAM DIRECTOR
I'm interviewing hosts
about the host murder.
Oh, that?
Have you or any other hosts
you know been in danger before?
No need for names.
Well, Ms. Momotaro…
This is where you come to have fun!
If you're not here for fun, please go.
I'm trying so hard to become number one.
Even if I could be killed,
I need to take first place once.
That's my assignment.
Assignment? That word does not suit you!
- Ms. Chihuahua wouldn't mock me like that.
- Hey!
I can take his place.
An interview sounds interesting.
Great. Please have a seat.
Thank you.
I'm Machida.
I'm Tsubasa.
Ms. Momotaro?
Gosh! That went well!
Well done!
- Oh, sorry.
- Oh!
- Oh! Yay!
- Yay!
- Sorry.
- It's fine!
- I'm embarrassed about my dad.
- What?
Forcing his opinion on promotion…
Oh no, I respect your dad a lot!
I mean, I would like to be promoted.
Oh really?
Why?
You said you want to prioritize
your private life.
Oh, that wasn't a lie!
I do think that way sometimes.
It's not a problem! I sometimes
change my mind about things too!
Friday next week, I finish work early,
so let's check out venues.
Okay.
On the way back,
why don't we stay a night in Yokohama?
I want to redeem myself from last time.
Oh, I'm sorry! I'm not free that Saturday.
- Oh…
- I have plans.
Private tutoring again?
What? Oh no, not that!
I have plans with Momoko.
I see. That's a shame.
I'll compromise.
Oh, no, the horn.
I guess this isn't a good place for that.
And I ended up drinking quite a lot.
Hey stop! Why would you do that?
The interview flopped.
- Any overcharging?
- Yes!
I paid 50,000 yen!
Kaoru didn't want anything to do with me.
Really?
He didn't even tell me
if you've visited lately.
Why would I?
Well, he seems to be interested in you.
Even if I could be killed,
I need to take first place once.
That's my assignment.
Assignment…
It is dangerous, though.
It means they'd do anything for money.
I'm not surprised that incidents
happen in such an environment.
- How did the family meeting go?
- Yeah.
It went well.
My dad made me anxious, though.
How did Kawahara what's-his-name do?
On the way back,
he suggested an overnight trip.
- Oh, so it's going well!
- Yeah.
- Very well.
- Good!
Oh there… there she is!
How do I close this window?
I can't close it!
She's struggling…
You can do it!
Are you relieved she wasn't lying?
Yeah.
You thought she was cheating?
Uh…
I didn't doubt her.
Oh, yes, you did!
What?
Liars tend to think
that others are lying to them too.
We're getting married!
Of course, I worry about who she meets!
If she has an affair,
my reputation at work can be ruined!
I see.
Oh, there she is!
Oh? Why is she…
What? She's coming this way!
Get down!
- The seat's not reclining.
- What?
Isn't the station the other way?
What?
- Where did she go?
- That way.
What?
Hey! Are you going to follow her?
He's already obsessed…
PIETAS GIRLS' HIGH SCHOOL
Her workplace…
What am I doing?
COMBUSTIBLE TRASH
RIDE THE KEIKYU LINE
AND EXPERIENCE SUMMER AT MIURA BEACH
Thanks! See you soon!
- Get home safe! Thank you! Bye!
- Bye!
Oh, Miss! Are you here to see Kaoru?
No, I…
Come in.
Come on! It's so cute,
how you're squeezing my hand!
Tsubaki! Ijuin! The teacher's here!
- I can go in by myself.
- Come on! It's okay!
Escort her in!
Good evening!
- Excuse me.
- Come in!
- One by one, okay?
- One by one!
I'll take your bag.
We have an anniversary event today.
Welcome!
How's Ms. Momoko?
- She's good…
- She never contacts me.
- Watch your step!
- Okay.
- Here's your seat. Please enjoy.
- Thank you.
- I never get a reply from her.
- She's bad at texting.
Oh, is she?
Here is your wet towel.
Ms. Chihuahua! Welcome.
Oh? What's with that look?
I received your assignment.
Oh, yes.
It was very well written. You did so well!
I'm not in kindergarten.
I'm sure a lot of effort went into it.
- Next time we can try a longer sentence…
- Quiet!
Let's not talk about it here.
You should have fun.
Help your student.
Your nomination is already a great help.
Fine. But I can't stay too long.
That's okay! Thank you!
First drink, please.
Okay!
What would you like, Miss?
- I…
- Don't force yourself to drink alcohol.
Teachers tend to worry
what others might think.
Oh, true.
So?
- Huh? You want to go home?
- No!
I would have some champagne!
- What?
- Wow. Champagne?
I'm capable of having fun.
"Capable"? You're such a square…
Are you sure?
It depends on the price.
Here's the price list.
- Right here.
- Have you decided?
Quite a few choices.
This one, please.
Sure!
50,000 yen?
50,000 yen!
Oh my, Miss!
- Thank you!
- I'll get it ready.
- Thanks!
President Akina is here!
Welcome!
Welcome, Ms. Akina.
I'll be back.
Hi! It's me, Kaoru!
Oh, you're wearing it!
Of course, I am!
I'm so happy!
I'm glad!
- It's my first time trying it on.
- Really?
- You must have known I would come.
- Also, look at this…
TSUBASA / HIROTO
KAORU
Kaoru…
Can I have some too?
Thank you.
Oh, and the steak!
It's good, right?
Excuse me.
Ms. Akina. Thank you, as always.
- Happy tenth anniversary.
- Thank you.
I knew you'd do well
as a legendary ex-host.
It's nothing.
I heard that you've been successful
in the real estate
and cabaret club businesses too.
Fortunately, yes.
I'm sorry I changed my nominated host.
I thought I'd get banned as a penalty.
No way!
JOKER couldn't have succeeded without you.
Excuse me.
Staff members!
Please gather around Ms. Akina's table!
- Gather around!
- What's happening?
What's going on?
What is this?
- Guess what?
- What?
The wonderful and lovely President Akina
and our charismatic Prince Kaoru's table
has ordered ten bottles of champagne
worth three million yen!
- No way!
- Thank you very much!!
- Thank you!
Let's ask a few words from Ms. Akina!
Three, two, one, go!
- Yeah!
Are you all ready to aim
for first place at JOKER's
Kabukicho branch?
- Yeah!
I promise here and now
to make my newly nominated host,
Kaoru, number one!
- Wow!
- Yeah!
Thank you, Ms. Akina!
- Yes!
That's all? That's not enough!
- Thank you, Ms. Akina!
- Yeah!
That's not enough!
I can't order more for that!
Do more!
More? Wait, hang on. I know!
Thank you so much!
Be careful!
Not even close.
Stupid ones need
to show sincerity if they want to win.
You're so dumb!
Dumb!
How are you so stupid?
Yes, you're right!
Everyone got covered in poop!
What should I do?
Hang on…
- Hold this, will you?
- What?
Let me think.
- Ms. Akina.
- That's risky!
- Be careful!
Thank you so much!
Woah!
Are you okay?
Ms. Akina, I love you.
Gosh! Miss, are you okay?
Hey, you.
You're leaving?
But it's this club's special day!
We meet again, huh?
Anything you'd like to say?
Kaoru is not stupid.
She said you weren't stupid.
Right! Let's have some champagne!
- Let's have an amazing time! Yeah!
- Yeah!
- Are you ready?
I'm very sorry about that.
Please come again.
I'm sorry. I shouldn't have said anything.
- No, it's fine.
- However…
That shouldn't be allowed
even if she's a paying customer!
A host club is a place
that allows all customers
to have fun in their own ways.
To people who come to these places,
I guess I'm the one who's out of place,
clueless, and immature.
What assignments are needed
for me to become a proper adult?
BEWARE OF SUSPICIOUS INDIVIDUALS
Miss.
The biggest idiot
is me.
He followed you and saw you go into JOKER.
Before you act, think hard
about what's most important for a host.
You really are a host to your core.
THIS DRAMA INCLUDES BUSINESS PRACTICES
THAT COULD BE CONSIDERED VIOLATIONS
Subtitle Translation by: Emily J.