=Her Trajecting=
(Every Trajectory Is You)
=Episode 8=
Shu Yan.
What's the matter?
You look so pretty today.
All of the men were staring at you.
I'm getting angry.
I should be the only one
who can admire your beauty, right?
You're mine.
Sorry about that. My hand slipped.
Hey,
you're drenched.
Get yourself sorted out in the restroom.
Shen Weizhou,
what are you up to?
I can do it myself.
Aren't you going to view houses today?
I can join you tonight.
I...
I'm busy tonight.
What about next time?
Mr. Shen.
Alright.
You can go ahead, then.
Okay.
See you next time.
Shu Yan.
Why did you leave without
hearing my explanation?
I don't know why they did this either.
You know this too.
I'm perplexed myself.
It occurred so many years ago.
I have a terrible memory as well.
Maybe
I said the wrong thing.
Initially, I was quite angry.
However,
after I gave it some thought,
I figured that you had
no reason to deceive me.
After all, we're best friends.
That's right.
We're best friends.
Why would I do that to you?
All those people
tried to bully me
using all kinds of bizarre reasons.
Now,
it seems like your turn.
If so,
what should we do?
Now, we mustn't let them bully us again.
I'm going to meet Chu Chen.
We'll clarify things in person.
You're going to meet Chu Chen?
Will Tianyu be upset, then?
That won't happen.
The stocks he bought appreciated a lot.
He made a huge fortune.
The stocks he bought appreciated?
He told me
that he was going
to buy the things I liked.
It's the expensive handbag
I saw before.
I liked it,
but I couldn't afford it.
He even said
that he would take me to view houses.
I assume
he wants to propose to me.
Really?
Alright now. I'll stop here.
I need to go on my date.
Shu Yan,
I won't let you
lead a life happier than mine.
- This is great. I finally obtained it.
- Be gentle.
You'll attract
people's attention, you know?
- What if people recognize me?
- I'm so happy.
I'll never forget
that you bought this limited-edition
handbag for me.
Alright now.
Let me send you home. Let's go.
Okay.
(So,)
(he's Shen Jiao's boyfriend, huh?)
Hello, Baby?
Why didn't you wait for me?
Where did you go?
I had another appointment.
That's why I left first.
Don't tell me you're going on
a date with Shen Weizhou.
That's not it.
I'm meeting my classmate.
That's fine.
You have to be wary of Shen Weizhou.
He's definitely interested in you.
Don't spout nonsense.
He has a girlfriend.
That's my hunch as a man.
So what if he has a girlfriend?
All men will cheat.
Even if he's married,
he'll have an affair outside.
He'll definitely target you.
(All men are just like you.)
I can tell
that Shen Weizhou is a playboy.
You're gullible as well.
He'll definitely target you.
You won't do this to me, right?
Me?
Of course not.
I'm no ordinary man, you know?
I'm very faithful.
Alright.
I have something else to do.
I'll hang up now.
Wait.
Hello?
Don't tell me she discovered
my affair with Ye Wei.
We didn't do anything.
We just kissed a few times.
You can't blame me for that.
Ye Wei is indeed charming.
I wonder what she's doing now.
Hello?
Where are you?
- Grandpa.
- My granddaughter is back.
Grandpa, look.
Weizhou bought me a lot of stuff.
I wanted them for so long.
You look so happy today.
Grandpa, you have no idea.
He looked so handsome
walking the runway today.
He had plenty of female fans
shouting his name down the stage.
Is that so?
Yeah.
How was it?
Did your work go smoothly?
Yeah.
I'll arrange for you
to be Weizhou's assistant for now.
You should start from the basics.
Try and understand
the nature of our business slowly.
After that,
I'll arrange
an official position for you.
Once
Weizhou takes over the company,
you can assist him.
Grandpa,
I don't want that.
- What do you want to do, then?
- I just want to get by.
I'll go and organize my things.
Remember to tell me
when dinner is ready.
Of course.
Go now.
Look at that lass.
Weizhou,
- Meng Ya will return to the country soon.
- Why is she returning to the country?
She's an international model.
Once she joins our company,
she'll serve as a good promotion
for our company across the world.
I hope that you can differentiate
between public and private affairs.
I'll make a move first.
- Aren't you going to join us for dinner?
- I need to maintain my figure.
You...
Chairman.
Were you looking for me?
Did you find out anything
about that woman?
Don't worry.
I've placed her profile
in your study room.
Alright.
Go now.
Okay.
Here.
I made this especially for you.
Give it a try.
It looks delicious.
What do you think?
It's really delicious.
I'm glad you like it.
I'll make it for you in the future.
You don't have to.
By the way,
did you bring the letter here?
(Stop annoying me! I hate you! By Shu Yan)
Look.
(Ye Wei can actually
forge my handwriting.)
It does look like my handwriting.
But it wasn't me.
You didn't write this?
If so...
Maybe
your crush is pulling a prank on me.
It's all in the past now.
It no longer matters.
Let's talk about something else.
Sure.
(So, Ye Wei tried to sabotage me
in secret in the future.)
(To think that I actually trusted her.)
In order to be at my best on stage,
I never took any food today.
Now, I'm finally having some food.
Thank you for
keeping me company. Ye Wei.
Isn't Yan keeping you company today?
She dolled herself up.
I thought
she went on a date with you.
It's fine.
She loves me very much.
She can't escape from my grasp.
It's hard to say for sure.
Everyone says
that women are unpredictable.
When Yan's mother was young,
she ran away from home
for the sake of a man.
Speaking of which,
Yan is truly pitiful.
So, her mother had an affair?
Don't you know about that?
You...
So,
has anyone
tried to court you lately?
Chu Chen,
I have a boyfriend.
Are you...
Are you referring to
the celebrity Shen Weizhou?
Of course not.
Why would you think
that he was my boyfriend?
He was the one who told me
to meet him at Jiangning Restaurant.
He pays a lot of attention to you.
I thought he was your boyfriend.
(No wonder Chu Chen
went to the restaurant.)
(But why did Shen Weizhou do that?)
I have no idea about that.
Let me send you home
after you're done eating.
Don't worry.
I won't pester you.
You don't have to.
You have plenty of customers today.
You can resume your work.
I can head home by myself.
I'll come and try
your dishes again next time.
Okay.
I'll make a move first.
(Han Tianyu)
Take care, then.
Goodbye.
Han Tianyu?
What are you doing here?
What's wrong?
Were you expecting another man?
So, you tailed me?
Who said you could skip my calls?
I merely wanted to give you a surprise.
You dolled yourself up today.
Which man did you seduce today?
An apple doesn't fall far
from the tree indeed.
What do you mean by that?
I'm sure you know
what I'm talking about.
Everyone knows
that your mother had an affair.
Did Ye Wei tell you
about my mother's affair?
Are you afraid of something?
Are you afraid that she might
tell me about your affairs as well?
Tell me.
Where did you go after work?
Let go of me!
You're hurting me!
Did you go and seduce another man?
Tell me!
No! Let go of me!
Listen.
Don't ever think of escaping from me.
Even if you were to die,
you can only die by my side.
Which scum did that?
Shen Weizhou!
Shen Weizhou! Stop hitting him!
Shen Weizhou, stop hitting him!
I knew it!
You two were having an affair!
Scram!
You're hurt.
Are you okay?
Wait. Why did I run away?
Why did I do that?
Darned Shen Weizhou.
I would've beaten him up
if I weren't...
Shu Yan,
you'll never escape from me.
What are you doing here?
I was worried about you.
Why were you worried about me?
You didn't answer my calls.
I was worried
that you might be in trouble.
Even so,
it's none of your business.
Who said so?
I was worried
that Han Tianyu might harm you.
Why would you think so?
Shu Yan, certain people and things
will never change.
What will happen will happen.
I won't allow anyone to harm you.
Shen Weizhou,
what do you mean by this?
I have a boyfriend.
You have a girlfriend as well.
Stop doing things
that'll cause people
to misunderstand us.
What is Shen Weizhou doing here?
I thought Han Tianyu
could show me something exciting.
(Han Tianyu)
I hate people
who cheat on their partners.
Cheat?
I didn't cheat on anyone.
I've already handled my affairs.
Handled?
Were you referring to your girlfriend?
Girlfriend?
What do you mean by that?
I never expected you to be this despicable.
Listen,
Shen Jiao
is an important friend of mine.
She's gentle and kind.
I won't allow you to hurt her.
How did Shen Jiao
encounter a playboy like you?
She's so unlucky.
Shen Jiao?
Are you saying
that Shen Jiao is my girlfriend?
You don't say?
Don't tell me that's not the case.
I saw everything.
Shu Yan, I do fancy you.
But do you actually know the truth?
♪You became a soft glow
that lit up my heart♪
♪When I was sinking into the sea♪
♪It was you who showed me the way♪
♪How I long to walk beside you♪
♪To guard the light
and shadow of every dawn♪
♪You always calm my storm inside♪
♪You are my one and only answer♪
♪You're the light I reached for
but never touched♪
♪You lit up my path
through the darkness♪
♪The time we lost was too long♪
♪I'll hold onto every second ahead♪
♪You're the light
that breaks through my endless night♪
♪You make the stars
burn brighter in the sky♪
♪I see you across time and space♪
♪I fall for you all over again
at our reunion♪