=Her Trajecting=
(Every Trajectory Is You)
=Episode 26=
Hello.
Yes.
Yes, that's me.
Vice President Lin is still in the US.
I think
it's possible
to match his schedule.
But first,
I must confirm it with my boss.
Han Tianyu?
What are you doing?
Shu Yan.
How ambitious you are.
You knew all along
that Shen Weizhou was
the heir to Norran Entertainment.
You dumped me just to him, didn't you?
Let go of me.
Stop wasting my time.
Shu Yan.
You must've started liking him
when I proposed to you, right?
That's why you fought with my mom.
You pulled that underwear stunt
to embarrass me.
Right.
Everything makes sense now.
Tell me.
When did you two start cheating?
Tell me!
So what if we did?
What can you do now?
All you do is act like
a barking stray dog.
What else can you do?
I'll kill you!
Security!
Calm down, you.
Let me tell you one last thing.
If you're still missing one dot
in the whole story.
You cheated with Ye Wei.
None of this
would've happened otherwise.
Cursed you!
Stay still.
Out!
Leader.
Han Tianyu. Are you coming or not?
Come now, or get replaced!
Wait, no! Don't replace me.
I'm on my way.
Miss.
Those insufferable fools.
It seems
I have to get it done myself.
What kind of crappy brush is this?
You're scrubbing my face off!
If my face
gets ruined, you're done for.
You're just
a third-rate performer doing tiny gigs.
You really think you're a superstar?
Take it or leave it.
Do you even have any work ethic?
Don't start throwing a tantrum.
You want to talk to me about work ethic?
A big shot like you
is beyond my league.
Han Tianyu,
what are you doing?
What's your deal?
Do you think
you're an A-lister now?
Get lost.
No, sir.
Please calm down.
I'll do an extra dance for you, okay?
Take it off.
Get lost.
Sir...
Long time no see, Han Tianyu.
How'd you end up as a street performer?
What?
Is the superstar here to mock me?
Of course not.
I'm here to work with you.
Work with me?
Yeah.
We have a common enemy.
What do you mean?
Shu Yan.
She stole my fiancé.
So what?
She has nothing to do with me anymore.
Are you really okay living like this?
Do you want to be looked down
by every random street troupe?
Do you want to be some homeless guy,
wandering around for shows?
Nothing I can do about it.
That Shen Weizhou has power,
influence, and money.
Now that Shu Yan's with him,
she can live worry-free for life.
People like me are nobodies.
I can't change anything.
Do you think Shu Yan is the only one
who can change her fate overnight?
What are you getting at?
Don't tell me you're into me.
Whatever Shu Yan has,
you can have it too.
A cheap woman like her
had no right to steal my man.
I've decided to teach her a lesson.
If we're lucky,
we could even
take over Norran Entertainment.
Then,
you get to punish
the woman who betrayed you,
and become
a world-famous superstar.
Doesn't that sound tempting?
So, how do I make it happen?
I'm all ears.
Why don't we
talk somewhere else?
I've taken care of the tax issues.
Shu Yan unknowingly
became one of the country's
top real estate tycoons.
Do you really think this is okay?
There's nothing wrong with it.
This is
the group's overseas
equity transfer agreement.
You really want to
transfer it to Wu Mengya?
You're not even going to
check with the old man?
(Overseas Equity Transfer Agreement
Party A: Shen Weizhou, Party B: Wu Mengya)
I'm the heir to the group.
Grandpa is already retired.
He has no right to interfere.
Trying to make changes
with your new position, huh?
What exactly are you trying to do?
If your physical report
didn't say everything was fine,
I would've thought you were dying.
You and Shu Yan have already broken up.
Her future happiness
has nothing to do with you.
I just want what's best for her.
I hope even long after now,
she can still be happy.
The person who sent Ye Wei
those files
about Shen Weizhou's identity
was you.
That's right.
But, she didn't get what I meant.
She made a few pointless decisions.
So, I hope you'll get it.
What do you want me to do?
Shu Yan has some real estate
under her name.
Buildings,
land,
apartments.
They are worth eighty million.
Eighty million?
Shu Yan?
Are you sure?
This...
What do you want?
Help me with something.
Once it's done,
you'll get more than
a hundred times that.
A hundred times?
By the way,
your wife's connection to Shu Yan
is pretty interesting.
They're not just best friends.
They're also stepsisters.
Where have you been?
You didn't answer your phone.
Look at the time.
You're hiding something from me.
What?
You went to Shu Yan's mom to scam her,
and you failed.
How do you know that?
The people who sent you those photos
didn't ask you to go after her mom.
What matters now
is that Shu Yan has eighty million.
What?
Shu Yan has that much?
Shen Weizhou gave it to her.
What charm did she have
to make him so obsessed with her?
Shu Yan...
This might actually be good for us.
If Shu Yan were to die,
her only family,
which is her mother,
would inherit everything.
If Shu Yan dies,
and the money goes to her mother,
why would she share it with us?
Didn't you tell me
your dad had passed away?
Keeping that bottled up
must be hard, huh?
From what I heard...
your dad is actually alive and well.
Buddy,
you can't do this.
You borrowed money.
You should pay it back.
You have a business now. You're a boss.
Why wouldn't you have money?
What do you expect us to do?
For the time being,
I don't have any money.
Give me a little more time.
Give me one more month,
and I promise I'll pay you back.
Pay us two hundred thousand first.
The rest
can wait.
I really don't have it.
I don't even have ten thousand.
Then, you have this coming.
No, wait!
What are you doing?
You only need one kidney
to live.
Relax.
It won't hurt too much.
No!
Buddy!
This is illegal!
Please, I'm begging you!
Stop!
Ye Wei?
Why are you here?
Where's the woman you live with?
Oh.
She...
Ye Wei is here!
The debt collectors are gone!
Here's one million.
Use the money to save your skin.
Once everything is done,
I'll help you clear all your debts.
And
you get to live a high life.
One million?
This is a lot of money.
Where did you get this?
Save your curiosity.
The one who gave you this money
could make you disappear
without a trace.
Just do what you're told,
and this miserable life
will be over soon.
Otherwise,
we all die together.
Can you do it?
Yes, we can do it.
We'll do it.
This is the overseas equity
transfer agreement from Norran Entertainment.
It's been fully separated
from the group.
You now have control over it.
You really think
this pathetic little agreement
is enough to send me away?
To make me give you my blessing
and leave with the money?
There was never any love between us.
My family owed your father a debt.
I broke off the engagement.
So, I owed you compensation.
This money
is enough for you to live comfortably.
But I had the chance
to become the lady
of Norran Entertainment.
If it weren't for Shu Yan,
we would've been married long ago.
We wouldn't care about each other,
and live our separate lives.
Wu Mengya.
Whatever you're planning,
stop it right now.
What else can I do?
I just want to win you back.
It's fine.
While you still can,
enjoy this love of yours.
Love always ends sooner or later.
When it does,
you'll come back to me.
Do you think he knows our plan?
What now?
Do you know
how much the stuff he gave me is worth?
How much?
Forty million.
Forty million?
Does he think I'm a beggar?
He really thought
that would get rid of me?
Han Tianyu.
Kill Shu Yan for me.
When it's done,
you'll get everything
you've ever wanted.
I'll clean up the mess.
As for me,
Shen Weizhou will come back for me.
And then,
I'll make him regret
ever trying to brush me off.
Mr. Bai.
Help me look into something.
Thank you, honey.
We have to make sure
nothing goes wrong.
Got it.
Everything is ready.
Should we start right away?
Yes.
I believe you'll do great.
Wait for me.
I'll be right back.
(Here lies Shu Moshan)
Mengya hasn't made a move.
But Shu Yan's mother
illegally rented a gravel truck.
You mean...
It means
if Shu Yan dies,
all the real estate you gave her
will go to her mother.
Where's the gravel truck?
According to the global GPS tracking,
it's currently driving on Highway 404.
Shu Yan!
(Do you know?)
(Ever since the moment I was reborn,)
(I've been ready to face everything.)
(No matter what fate has in store,)
(I won't let anything happen to you.)
(I'll keep you safe.)
(I'll face it for you.)
Shen Weizhou!
♪You became a soft glow
that lit up my heart♪
♪When I was sinking into the sea♪
♪It was you who showed me the way♪
♪How I long to walk beside you♪
♪To guard the light
and shadow of every dawn♪
♪You always calm my storm inside♪
♪You are my one and only answer♪
♪You're the light I reached for
but never touched♪
♪You lit up my path
through the darkness♪
♪The time we lost was too long♪
♪I'll hold onto every second ahead♪
♪You're the light
that breaks through my endless night♪
♪You make the stars
burn brighter in the sky♪
♪I see you across time and space♪
♪I fall for you all over again
at our reunion♪