Mel, you have to see this.
You should post
a video to prove everything's fine.
That would clear things up fast.
Really, Anton?
How can you smile after
being beaten up by your wife?
You react to one video.
You don't know the whole story.
Your brother called me.
He said he saw Alice, Beth, and Mel on TV,
and he felt the need to call me.
That's why I needed to go and talk to him.
We needed you to talk
14 years ago but you didn't.
I'm re-investigating Louisa's murder.
Don't you want to know the truth?
You're 14 years too late.
Try to go near my brother again,
you'll have to face me first.
[tense music playing]
[Edong] Have you been able
to sleep soundly these past 14 years?
[eerie music playing]
Your friends were smiling for the camera,
but their eyes said otherwise.
[eerie music continues]
They aren't happy.
They aren't at peace.
Did you see it too?
How about you? What do your eyes say?
Maybe I'll get to see them soon.
[music becomes suspenseful]
[suspenseful music continues]
[theme music playing]
Oh, by the way guys,
this has been going around.
We finally want to address this…
"husband beating" issue.
Um… are you actually
serious, guys? [chuckles]
- Yeah.
- [both chuckling]
My wife is beautiful as ever.
And soft-hearted.
She can't even hurt a fly.
- [chuckles]
- How could she hurt me?
Yeah, to clarify,
I only punched his arm jokingly.
It was an affectionate gesture,
but it caused this huge misunderstanding.
And that black eye you saw in the photo…
- Which I actually got from surfing.
- Yes.
Before that photo was taken,
I had an accident in the water.
My surfboard hit my eye.
I know you're all concerned,
but, [chuckles lightly]
Mel and I,
would never hurt each other.
Even if you asked anyone close to us,
they'd tell you this whole issue's a joke.
Mm-hmm.
We're happy.
And we love each other.
So much.
[smooches]
- [Mel chuckling]
- [mysterious music plays]
Uh, so h-how exactly do I get a gun?
The first step is getting a license.
There are several requirements,
including a DNP clearance,
a drug test,
and a neuro-psychiatric evaluation.
You'll also need to attend a seminar
on gun safety and responsible ownership.
The rest of the requirements
are easy to complete.
Don't worry, we'll assist
you throughout the whole process.
So, how long will it take?
[store clerk] Two weeks at most.
Two weeks?
Yes.
Why do you need a gun?
[mysterious music continues, fades]
[man] Isn't it a bit
early for a drink, Attorney?
[man chuckles]
Do I know you?
[man] Well…
I saw you on TV.
And I always see you here too, so…
I asked around about you.
You know…
a smart woman like you turns me on.
[man chuckles slightly]
[Erica scoffs]
Good for you.
They say you're
a defender of the poor and the innocent.
And who told you that?
Pretty much everyone I asked.
[sighs heavily]
Well, I can assure you I'm not a saint.
In fact,
I can think of two
people who absolutely hate me.
- [pensive music plays]
- [man] Good.
Good.
Because,
in all honesty,
I'm not looking for any saint.
[man chuckles lightly]
[pensive music continues]
Well, we expect that there
will still be negative reactions.
What's important is
that many support and defend you.
Good thing you both
have a strong following.
As long as you stay lovey-dovey in public,
I'm sure this issue
will die down eventually.
But please, no more black eyes.
It's really stressful.
Please, let's not go through this again.
Oh… [chuckles]
You should tell my wife
to stop being so moody with me.
You guys know I'm such a simp for her.
[chuckles]
[Anton inhales deeply]
[Tom] I love Mel.
But gosh,
that girl's just so problematic.
Did you see how bitchy she was to Anton?
Imagine, pulling that kind of attitude
when her husband's
been nothing but patient with her.
And she's the one refusing to have a baby.
And did you hear the way
she talked to her mother-in-law?
I wouldn't be surprised
if it turned out
that Mel really punched Anton.
Babe, we cannot judge them.
You know that.
And it's so obvious
that they're lying to us.
- [tense music playing]
- [heavy footsteps]
[Beth] So, what's up?
You know I'm not going
to stop bugging you, Alice.
You really think I wouldn't notice, huh?
First, you freaked
out over some random car
and ran like something
bad would happen to Seth.
And now you're buying a gun?
Hey, tell me. What's really going on?
Hey, Alice, you better tell me the truth.
You're a terrible liar.
- [cup rattling]
- [pensive music playing]
[Alice clears throat]
[sighs heavily]
Scott and I,
are getting a divorce.
What?
Why? What happened?
We thought you were doing great.
[Alice] Don't lie to me, Scott!
I know you were with her!
My friend saw you,
and you guys were at a hotel.
You were with her!
Yes, we were,
but there were other people too.
Our college friend group met there.
You know that I love you, right?
And I would never cheat on you, okay?
[huffs] I knew this would happen.
Your family never liked me.
They've always wanted you to marry her!
Is this it?
Is this you giving them what they want?
What? You're talking crazy!
Alice, will you please just listen?
I'm not cheating on you!
I want a divorce.
- What?
- You heard me!
What do you want?
How many times do I have to apologize?!
I don't need you to apologize!
I said, I want a divorce!
Well, I don't!
Stop treating me like I'm your enemy.
I thought we're going to fix this.
I'll go to therapy with you.
Couples' counseling?
I'll do that too, just please…
- Please, don't do this.
- No.
I'm leaving, Scott.
- Alice, please!
- [whimpers]
[breathing heavily]
[tense music playing]
You're not taking Seth with you.
And if you insist on doing this,
I'll sue you for full custody.
- [breathing heavily]
- [tense music continues]
[breathing heavily]
[music fades]
I think he's having an affair.
Seriously?
- But what's the gun for?
- [Alice sighs]
Are you scared?
- Is your husband hurting you?
- [exhales deeply]
Look, I'm just scared that
he'll take Seth away from me.
You know his family's really powerful.
He can,
sue for full custody and win.
I'm just scared that once
he gets his hands on Seth,
I won't see my son ever again.
But I won't let that happen.
Over my dead body, okay?
[Alice breathes deeply]
Please,
don't tell Mel.
She has problems of her own and…
I don't want this getting around.
Even Uncle Edward doesn't know.
Is that why you're
still wearing your wedding ring?
[solemn music playing]
I just don't want people
finding out about my problem.
[chuckles bitterly]
[solemn music continues]
- [music fades]
- [sighs]
[Anton] Do you need anything?
The helpers have gone home.
Want me to make you a sandwich?
- [file thumps]
- [huffs]
Well, I guess our problem's solved.
[Anton sighs]
[breathes deeply]
Are you still mad
because I went out with a black eye?
If I can forgive you for giving it to me,
why can't you forgive me for that?
[morose music playing]
You know what?
Tim's right.
I have a strong following.
I have brands and clients who trust me
even before I met you.
I'll do fine without you, Anton.
[breathing shakily]
Let's end this.
I want out.
Out?
Out of this marriage!
Out of this whole thing!
Anton, I'm done.
I'm done.
[Mel breathing shakily]
Mel, please?
You know I love you.
And no one will love you like I do.
[Mel scoffs]
Why can't you appreciate that?
Why is it always me
willing to work on this relationship?
Shut up!
[breathing shakily]
Just… shut up!
[morose music playing]
[sighs]
You'll lose Grace & Glam.
What?
You heard me.
You don't control Grace & Glam!
I have a solid deal with Reema,
and we have a good relationship.
[Anton] Reema is
just the Creative Director.
You seem to forget that my family
is friends with the owners. [scoffs]
And they're actually
really mad and hurt, Mel.
They can't believe
you would do this to me.
In fact, Aunt Millette is just waiting.
One text from me
and she'll call Reema to drop you.
And find a new face for their brand.
You can't do that!
[breathing heavily]
I don't want to, Mel.
But you leave me no choice.
You always do this.
You go crazy and try
to sabotage our marriage.
You don't even know what's good for you.
[slaps]
You're a monster!
[morose music resumes]
[line ringing]
- [exhales deeply]
- [ringing continues]
Why do you always hurt me, Mel?
- [huffs]
- [morose music continues]
"I" hurt you?
You need help, Mel.
You have issues.
You punched me a few days ago.
- You gave me a black eye.
- Fine!
Yes, I punched you.
But you fucking know why!
[upbeat dance music playing]
[overlapping chatter]
[man 1] He's a winner.
- [man 2] Hey!
- [Anton] Oh, speaking of that…
- …we should be celebrating.
- [man 2] Of course!
- [man 2] Next week!
- [Anton] Can you still surf?
- [Anton] Next week?
- [man] Sure, what about you?
- Come on!
- Come on, dude!
- [Anton] No!
- [overlapping chatter]
- Cheers!
- Cheers to your promotion!
[upbeat dance music continues]
- [man] See you guys later!
- Oh!
I'm so sorry!
- I didn't mean to!
- [sighs]
No, it's fine. It's fine.
You sure?
You look like
you could use a better drink.
And maybe someone to talk to?
[both chuckle]
Richard.
Mel.
I know you.
I've seen you on a billboard on EDSA.
Which one? There are two.
You look great in both.
- Hey, replace my drink.
- I'll get you another one.
- You spilled it all over the floor.
- I'm so sorry.
Babe!
- Hey, babe.
- Is there a problem?
Oh no! There's no problem.
He's just
apologizing for spilling my drink.
Bro, find someone who's not married
before you get yourself in trouble.
Okay.
Babe, what is wrong with you?
[Mel] Hey, ow!
Hey!
Anton, you're hurting me! Stop it!
- Ow! Let go of me!
- [Anton grunts]
- What the hell?!
- I turn away for one minute,
and you're already flirting with someone?
That guy was harmless!
Why does it even matter, huh?
You've been ignoring me the whole night
because of your friends!
[Mel grunts]
Are you doing this on purpose?
You want to push my buttons?
- Anton…
- You want to make me angry?
And now you try
to humiliate me in front of my friends?
- Huh?
- Let go of me!
[choking]
- [kick lands]
- [Anton grunts]
[Mel grunts, breathing heavily]
Come here!
[Mel grunts] Let go! Let go!
Stop it! Let go of me!
- [Anton grunts]
- [camera shutter clicking]
[menacing music playing]
- [music fades]
- That's your problem, Mel.
You never take accountability.
[huffs]
If you hadn't flirted with another guy,
you wouldn't have gotten hurt.
It wasn't my fault!
Just like it wasn't my fault
what happened at the bar that night!
- [tense music playing]
- [Mel breathing heavily]
Help me! Help me, please!
- Ma'am. Sir.
- Keep him away!
He's hurting me!
I'm not drunk!
You're more drunk than I am,
and it doesn't even matter!
Because even when
you're sober, you still hurt me!
I told you not to take any drugs!
Especially not with alcohol!
I did not take drugs!
How dare you!
[Mel] I was protecting
myself from you, Anton!
And you told all the staff
I was out of my mind because of drugs!
[screaming hysterically]
[Mel] And weren't you the one
who spread those rumors about me and John?
Because you were petty and jealous?
It's not my fault, Anton.
I'm not the problem here.
You are!
You're the monster!
And the best thing for me to do
is get the hell away from you!
Go ahead. Leave!
Let's see if anyone
still supports you after that.
Once I go to town telling everyone
how you've been cheating
on me and abusing me for years!
[sobs]
This last incident?
It's the perfect setup, don't you think?
Let's see how many people believe me.
I'll tell all our friends,
all my family's friends.
And when I'm done…
no one will ever
want to work with you again.
Not Grace & Glam.
- Not anyone else!
- No!
- You'll be ruined!
- [sobbing] No!
You can't do that to me!
I can.
You know I can.
I'm Anton Montenegro.
I can do anything I fucking want.
[sobbing]
[dark music playing]
You're always so hardheaded, Mel.
You think you can leave me.
That you can survive without me.
But you need me.
[sniffles]
You'll be nothing without me.
[dark music continues]
I hate you!
I fucking hate you!
[screaming hysterically]
I hate you! Get away from me!
[bawling]
- You keep making me hurt you!
- [crying]
If you were a good wife,
we wouldn't have ended up like this!
- [blow lands]
- [Mel groans]
[sobbing loudly]
- [blow lands]
- [Mel groans]
[dark music continues]
[Edong] Did you see what I saw too?
Aah!
Edong was right.
It's easy to be better,
but it's harder to forgive others.
Ester's disappearance and
Celestino's death were not coincidences.
Don't worry, Attorney. We'll meet again.
He's the one behind it.
He's going after
everyone who sent him to prison.
And we're next.
Me, Mel, Alice, and Beth.
Santiago is in Bagumbayan.
Unless someone's acting for him out here.
Maybe he has an accomplice.