[mayor] I know your brother's story.
He's been through a lot,
but he turned out to be a good person.
[Erica] Is that true?
- Been here long?
- No, just ten minutes.
Why didn't you go in first?
So we could all go in together.
That Rodrigo Celestino,
the lead police
investigator who put Edong in jail?
He was found dead the other day.
Were you and your brother involved
in what happened to them?
I don't know what you're talking about.
[unsettling music playing]
[theme music playing]
[all singing]
♪ Let us all raise our hands ♪
- [young Beth] Wiggle your hips!
- [all giggle]
[young Beth]
Group Four members, come here!
Group One?
Me.
Jeez. Erica and Louisa are in our group.
Lucas makes it worse.
Wish us luck!
[young Alice] Shh! They might hear you.
That Lucas is often absent
because he's always
worried about his junkie brother.
Erica barely talks, always low on energy.
And Louisa?
- Boys are all she thinks about.
- Keep it down.
Why?! It's true! [sighs sharply]
[melancholic music playing]
[young Louisa] Erica!
[pants]
Come on, hurry!
I'm so thirsty.
- Goodness.
- It's so hot.
Yeah.
[melancholic music continues]
[truck horn blaring]
[foot stomping]
- [horn continues blaring]
- [truck engine revving]
[unsettling music playing]
[horn blaring]
Papa!
Aah!
- [loud crash, glass shattering]
- [tense music playing]
[loud thud]
[glass shattering]
[heavy thud]
[tires screeching]
- [loud crash]
- [glass shattering]
[tense music continues]
[all breathe sharply]
Hurry!
[young Louisa] Sir?!
Sir.
- Sir!
- Sir?!
[young Mel] I'm calling an ambulance.
[young Beth] Don't touch him!
I saw that on TV!
Let's help him!
Mister Mike?
You know him?
He's Alice's father.
Alice?
Alice!
Alice! Alice!
[panting]
- Alice! Alice!
- [young Mel whimpers]
- Alice!
Alice, wake up!
[breathing heavily]
[grunts]
- Alice!
- Wake up!
- [fire crackling]
- Ow!
Move back, kids! You might get hurt!
- Alice!
[woman] Move back, kids!
- We need to save her!
- [loud thumping]
[young Mel] Alice!
- My god!
- [sobs] Alice!
- [young Beth] Alice!
- We need help!
- Alice!
- Call for help!
- Wake up, Alice!
[cries]
[panicked breathing]
[young Erica] Alice--
- What will you do?!
- We need to save her!
[woman] The car's about to explode!
Goodness, it's about to explode!
Move back, please!
- [pounding on window]
- [grunts]
- Oh, no!
- Alice!
[young Louisa] Alice!
Alice, wake up!
Unbuckle her seat belt!
[grunts] I can't!
- Hurry up!
- Come on!
- [young Louisa grunting]
- [loud thudding]
[young Louisa pants, grunts]
[young Mel] Alice!
[fire crackling]
- Alice.
- [young Mel] Alice!
[young Louisa] Alice?
[young Beth coughs]
[young Mel] Hey, Alice.
- [young Mel] Alice.
- [young Beth] Alice!
Alice, you're alive.
[young Beth] Thank God you're alive.
Alice, Alice.
[young Mel and young Beth sobbing]
- [electricity crackling]
- [women screaming]
- [screams]
- Alice!
- [woman 1] Help them!
- [woman 2] Get out of there!
- [woman 2] No one helped.
- [woman 1] Oh no!
[woman 1] It's going to blow up!
[young Alice and young Louisa grunting]
[young Beth] Alice! Support her head.
- [coughs]
- [screaming indistinctly]
- [young Beth] Alice!
- [young Alice grunting]
[young Erica] Louisa!
[grunting]
- [young Mel] Get Louisa! Hurry!
- [young Erica] Careful.
[young Erica] Let's go. Are you okay?
- [explosion]
- [passersby screaming]
[woman] Oh my!
[young Alice crying]
[sobbing]
[sobbing] No…
[sorrowful music playing, fades]
I want to thank you all again.
My daughter's alive because of you.
I don't know what
I would do if I lost Alice too.
Please, look after her.
She really needs friends right now.
We went to Alice's but…
she wasn't there.
Flowers?
[somber music playing]
Didn't her dad die in this very spot?
You think…
[young Louisa] Alice!
[somber music continues]
[young Alice]
I haven't actually thanked you.
Thank you.
Mama said,
there were grown-ups there
but they were scared to help.
But you guys,
you risked your lives for me.
Why did you do that?
[young Beth] Maybe because
we knew it was you inside that car.
[young Mel] It just happened.
These two,
they were the first to help,
even as the fire grew stronger.
I just followed Louisa.
[somber music continues]
Bestie, are you okay now?
[music becomes gentle]
What?
You said it too nicely so,
It doesn't sound like you at all.
So what are you trying to say?
That I'm usually not nice?
- Yes.
- [chuckling]
Hey, you can't start a fight with me.
- [Edward] Good evening.
- [Louisa] Hello, Uncle!
- [Edward] Hi!
- [Louisa] Good evening.
Have you eaten?
- Come in.
- Hello, Auntie.
This is for you.
We just wanted to say hi to Alice.
Have you eaten?
Join us!
Oh no, it's fine, Auntie.
No, I'll get you all plates.
Oh! Can we? [awkward chuckle]
Sinigang is my favorite!
- Is it okay, Alice?
- [woman] Have a seat, girls.
Eat some more, Alice.
This is my all-time fave.
- [chuckles] Have some more!
- [hushed] Hey!
Are you that hungry?
[all chuckle]
[young Alice] We should name our group.
- MABEL?
- It's not MABEL (mah-bel),
- it's MABEL (may-bel).
- MABEL.
- [music fades]
- [birds chirping]
[young Lucas] Edong, get up.
- Edong.
- What do you want?!
[groans softly]
Why are you here?
Go home. I'll follow later.
Will you stop this?!
Mama's been gone for a long time.
Look at yourself.
Do you think she'd be
happy if she saw you like this?
She loves me no matter what.
Right, Ma?
Go home.
[young Lucas] Where are you going now?
Going to get some stuff again?
The people call
you an addict and a thief, you know.
- Don't you even care?
- Move!
- I lost my mother too!
- [morose music playing]
Did I end up like that too?
- I said move!
- Listen to me, Edong!
[young Erica] Lucas!
[morose music continues]
[music fades]
[sniffles]
You're really nice to your brother.
He wasn't this way before.
He took care of me like
a dad should've because ours didn't.
I get it.
[somber music playing]
Even my mom, who's failed at being one,
I haven't given up on her.
[somber music continues]
[sniffles]
[young Erica] Sometimes, I wonder…
Maybe if I leave Amurao,
I can reinvent myself.
Then Mama will finally be proud of me.
I don't want you to change.
That will make me sad.
- [both chuckle softly]
- [music fades]
You're celebrating your birthday, right?
Take this.
So, it'll be like I'm
celebrating with you.
Thank you, Lucas.
I'll get the cake and
balloons before the shop closes.
I'll bring it to the boardwalk.
You said you'd tell me on your birthday,
if you liked me too…
So, do I pass by your store tomorrow?
Don't bother.
[romantic music playing]
I already have my answer.
I like you, too.
[romantic music continues]
Does everyone have a gift already?
I don't have one yet.
We should've just gotten a group gift.
Erica deserves to get a lot of gifts.
I'm sure her mom won't get her anything.
That's why I've been
reminding you since last week.
Well then, I'm sorry.
Help me find her a gift.
What should I get her?
Clothes? A bag?
A boyfriend?
A boyfriend for Erica?
[laughter]
[unsettling music playing]
So, are we official now?
Erica!
- Come here!
- Wait!
Get away from her!
Erica, seriously?!
Don't yell at her!
Shut up! I'm not talking to you!
Erica, his brother
is a junkie and a thief!
He has gone in and out of prison!
That's his brother, not him.
What's the difference?!
[young Edong] Hey! What are you saying?!
- [tense music playing]
- Edong, let's go.
You're one to talk!
Wasn't your mom a mistress?!
What about you?!
- Beth!
- Your father is so vile…
he killed your mother!
- How dare you!
- [young Erica] Beth!
- Let me go!
- Beth!
[blow lands]
[young Louisa] You bastard!
- How dare you!
- [blow lands]
- You bastard! I'll tear out your hair!
- Enough!
You're going to regret that!
Mark my words, I'll kill you!
- Damn you!
I will kill you!
You're dead!
- Erica, let's go!
- [young Edong] I'm not done with you!
You should've stayed away from Lucas!
Look what happened!
She didn't know this would happen.
Of course, she did!
[young Erica sniffles]
She knew it was wrong!
That's why you were
keeping it a secret, right?!
Listen to me, Erica!
Lucas may be different from Edong.
But if you choose him,
you'll be close to Edong, too!
You saw how violent he was!
Erica, I don't want you to get hurt!
Because you can't protect
me anymore when you leave?!
[tense music playing]
You're leaving?
I'm not the only one keeping secrets,
Louisa is, too!
She's leaving Amurao.
Were you ever going to tell us,
or you would just disappear?!
[tense music fades]
[young Mel] Louisa, is it true?
Louisa! Answer the question!
- Hey!
- Why won't you answer us?
I was going to write
you when I get to where I'm going.
[young Beth] Where the hell are you going?
Why won't you tell us?
[young Mel] Yeah. I don't get it, Louisa.
How long have you been planning this?
Didn't you think we deserved to know?
Did you even consider how we would feel?
You're all leaving, too!
Why are you acting so surprised?!
I'm not.
I thought we'd always be together.
Good thing you have Lucas, huh, Erica?
Stop it!
Let's, at least,
hear out why Erica likes Lucas.
Let's not be so judgmental!
But you shouldn't have kept it a secret.
You know what this feels like?
It feels like you don't trust us!
That we're not really your friends!
Because true friends don't
keep secrets from each other!
And do you think
it's easy for me to leave?
When Papa died,
it was like my world fell apart.
[somber music playing]
Then I met all of you,
and things made sense again!
But now, everything will change.
I'm worried that if we're not together,
everything will fall apart again!
Then you would just
leave us without a word?
Do you have any idea
how much that hurts, Louisa?!
I didn't even get to say goodbye to Papa!
- [young Alice sobbing]
- [somber music continues]
Alice!
[young Alice] You lied!
[young Mel] At least,
they don't blame us anymore.
We'll graduate from
Amurao High with our names cleared.
[young Alice] I did that for Louisa!
So she could finally rest in peace!
[young Beth]
We did the right thing, okay?!
[young Erica] If
that was the right thing to do,
why do I feel like this?!
It makes me sick!
What you did was wrong!
[young Beth] "You"?!
Why?! Did you even speak up?
You said nothing, Erica!
You're one of
the reasons Edong will rot in jai!
Stop playing innocent!
[young Alice] Erica!
[poignant music playing]
[young Erica] Lucas, I tried!
I told them the truth but
they wouldn't listen to me!
[young Lucas]
I thought you were on my side!
I thought you were different, Erica!
But you're just like them!
What are you doing?
[poignant music continues]
[music fades]
Erica.
[Mel] What do you want with Lucas?
The Santiago
brothers are planning something.
Esther Castro is missing,
and Celestino was murdered.
What I heard is that Esther's been hiding
because of her fraud case.
And Celestino was killed
by a syndicate he crossed before.
So, after 14 years,
it's just a coincidence
those two incidents happened?
Both were involved in Edong's case.
Wait, so you really think
Edong and Lucas are behind this?
I don't believe it's just coincidence.
You don't even have proof.
And still, you came here
and ambushed Lucas with that accusation.
You're concerned about
the lack of evidence now, Beth?
[Mel] I know Lucas.
He would never do what you're saying.
You know him that well?
[tense music playing]
[tense music continues]
[Erica] I have a strong feeling.
And my instinct is rarely wrong.
If I'm right that Esther and
Celestino's cases are connected.
it only means one thing.
Edong is coming after
everyone who wronged him.
So that means…
That includes us.
We're next.
[tense music continues]
But he's in prison.
But Lucas isn't.
And it's entirely possible
that Lucas is acting for him.
That's impossible, it's not Lucas!
[tense music continues]
Mel's right, it's not Lucas.
You know how I know?
Because you love connecting things
that were never
connected in the first place.
You should know.
You did the same thing.
What's up with you?!
Are you still hung up
on what happened before?
Aren't you?
You expect me to believe
that you sleep peacefully at night
after what we did to Edong?
Yes, because what we did was right!
And even after 14 years,
that will never change.
Because we did nothing wrong!
[tense music swells]
[music turns suspenseful]
[suspenseful music continues]
[inmate] Santiago! You're being summoned.
- [men grunting]
- [blows landing]
When a law is broken,
there's punishment.
Why do you think
your mother never told you
about what happened to her friend?
Stop!
Louisa!
It's all in the past,
but she's still digging it up!
If you're right, good.
But if I'm right, at least I warned you.
We didn't do anything wrong!
When something's wrong,
it needs to be made right.
[grunts]