[Locsin] Looks like
your hand got hurt pretty bad?
I do not even know
how I managed to face him.
All I could think about
was getting Seth back.
You should not have faced him alone.
You should have called Uncle Edward.
Or at least asked for help.
He was holding Seth, Erica.
I didn't even think--
He's a murderer.
Be grateful that's all
that happened to you.
Althea? What happened?
You have to leave.
You and Seth need to go back to the US.
We cannot give
that monster another chance at our son.
[Beth] We need to work together.
All our lives are in danger,
including the people we love.
We need to stop Edong now.
[suspenseful music playing]
[theme music playing]
[sinister music playing]
- [man] Edward!
- [music fades]
- [rooster crows]
- How are you guys?
I heard what happened. That was terrible.
How's your grandson?
Luckily, he didn't get hurt much.
[exhales] He's okay now
but, of course, the child was traumatized.
I'm glad you got him back.
But what you did was admirable.
You were able to fight that person.
When it comes to family,
we do anything we possibly can.
[rooster crows]
Good thing
our village added more security.
[rooster crows]
Who knows,
Edong might attack our neighbors again.
It's worrisome.
[Erica] You heard that?
I was behind Cornelio when he was talking.
[tense music playing]
It was probably Travis.
He is Kyle's number one apologist.
When we went to see him,
he was defensive for Kyle.
Cornelio warned him
that you guys were coming.
They were talking about something
that needs to be kept secret from you.
[tense music continues]
[Marco] We need to monitor them.
Even Kyle's mother.
Do you think that will reveal anything?
Kyle is currently in the US.
They are our only physical link
to what happened 14 years ago.
[Marco] What's clear is
we got a reaction from them.
We just have to wait
and see what they do next.
[car door opens, closes]
[tense music continues]
- [Marco] I have spoken to the police.
- [music fades]
They don't want
to panic the people of Amurao,
like what happened before.
They're worried
it might bring bigger trouble.
But they will search every
area where Edong could be hiding.
Even Louisa and
Liezel's spot by the woods.
Since Edong knows about it,
the cops will search it too.
Erica and I went to our old home.
There's no one there.
[uneasy music playing]
We still need to get it checked.
Like I said,
they will do everything to find him.
You said… that's what you wanted, right?
[tense music resumes]
[car engine revving]
[tires screech]
Hands up!
Sir! Please don't!
[tense music continues]
Take a look at this.
Go around the area.
[Lucas] Like I told Erica,
my brother won't ever go to our old house.
Because that's where
my father killed my mother.
But if you want to waste your time…
Then go.
[uneasy music playing]
Amurao isn't that big, right?
Maybe the police aren't that stupid
and catch him right away.
- [phone buzzing]
- [music fades]
Hello?
[sighs in relief] Thank you.
The prosecutor found
something for us to continue
our case against Anton.
[stirring music playing]
[Mel inhales, exhales heavily]
You said you had
influence at the Justice Department!
They did speed up the resolution,
but they'll still sue me?!
I don't know what happened.
I've been calling Secretary,
but he's not answering!
This shouldn't be happening.
Okay, but don't worry.
Attorney Artillero will--
It shouldn't have come to this
if you just did what you promised!
Hey! I told you from the beginning.
That woman was no good for you!
But did you listen? No!
Now look at what's happening!
So you shouldn't be mad at me
'cause this is all your fault!
[Barbara huffs]
[tense music playing]
Son, I'm sorry. You didn't deserve that.
I'm sorry. I'll fix this. Okay?
I'll fix this.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, okay?
I'll fix this, don't worry. I'll fix this.
[tense music sting]
[Alice] We were all there.
We saw how he tricked Mel,
and purposefully separated her from us
just so he could hurt her.
Luckily, we arrived right away.
Because if not, he might've killed Mel.
And Mel was telling the truth.
Don't just fall
for the charming smile, the handsome face,
and the edited and
spliced videos of that man.
This is not an online fan war.
This is about a woman's life.
We will stand by Mel's side…
…as she fights
to finally hold Anton accountable
for all the abuse
that he has inflicted on her
all of these years.
[poignant music playing]
[music fades]
Are you sure about this?
If you post this online,
you'll be going
through the same toxic bullshit
that I've been going through.
I'm used to toxic, Mel.
Don't worry. I know how to handle this.
Besides, is there anything more toxic
than our current situation?
What's the difference
adding another one, right?
[Erica chuckles wryly]
It's not even a choice, Mel.
[Alice sighs]
We may disagree on a lot of things…
But this?
We're a hundred percent on this.
Right, Beth? Erica?
There are men really like that.
Kyle did this to Louisa back then.
[Erica] Anton did it to you.
If we don't fight back,
we'll just keep letting them do this.
This won't end.
[somber music playing]
[Mel sniffles, sighs]
I- I don't think I've thanked you yet.
Like, really thank you…
…for jumping in and
physically protecting me from my husband.
[Mel] You got hurt, too, but…
But you didn't think about that.
Thank you.
Thank you, guys.
And you're right.
We're not the same.
And we will never be after Louisa's death.
She will always connect us.
[Mel sniffles, cries]
That night…
That night will always connect us.
[somber music continues]
[Alice] How are you and Ryan?
[music fades]
We're going to be okay.
[sighs] Beth, I'm sorry. I…
I didn't mean to cause any
conflict between you and him.
We can handle it. We'll be okay.
Like I said, you're right.
I was just thinking of myself.
I realized it after
what happened to Chloe.
I'll help you find Edong.
And if it's necessary to look back
at what happened to Louisa in the past,
so we can catch him,
then okay.
What about…
admitting to what we did?
I thought we were done with that option?
Because of Mel's situation, yes.
However, since there
is a case against Anton,
we might be able to convince her to do so.
What?
Are we going to get in front of the camera
and say it all on social media?
[Erica] No.
We are going to hold a press conference.
That's where we'll admit everything.
A press conference?!
A simple video won’t be enough for Edong.
You’ve seen how he’s been torturing us.
The bigger the spectacle, the better.
[huffs] You really
just want to humiliate me?
Beth, I don't want
to humiliate or hurt you.
This is nothing personal,
but it involves all of us.
[melancholic music playing]
Do you know how proud I am of my daughter?
She’s just a kid,
but she understands how the world works.
She is not afraid to speak up,
especially when she knows what's right.
Everyone says she takes after me.
I believed it.
But that's not true.
She doesn't take after me.
Chloe is so much better than I am.
[melancholic music continues]
If she were in my shoes before,
she wouldn’t have
bent to Celestino’s will.
She wouldn't lie about that goddamn watch.
[melancholic music continues]
Fuck!
Damn it, here's the truth.
I lied before because…
I thought I had to do that…
…to put Louisa’s killer behind bars..
[melancholic music continues]
But…
when I think about saying that to Chloe,
I know she'd be
disappointed in her mother.
[sobs]
I know that her trust
in me would be shattered.
Just thinking about it now hurts so much.
[sobs]
Beth, like you said, Chloe is smart.
If you explain it to her,
she will understand.
You don't understand!
You'll never understand
because you don't have any kids!
You don't even have anyone in your life!
You're all alone!
Beth.
[melancholic music continues]
I'm sorry.
Sorry.
I don't want to fight anymore.
I'm here, aren't I?
We may not need to do that anymore.
Maybe they'll catch Edong soon.
[melancholic music continues]
- Beth--
- I said I can't, okay?!
I can't do what you want!
Beth!
[melancholic music swells]
- I need to stay here.
- [music fades]
We still have to talk to the prosecutors
to prepare our case against Anton.
[Tom] Whatever you need.
Babe, just say it.
Have you thought about what I said?
There's a case against Anton now.
[Tim] And those videos
you have proving he's abusive?
Those will ensure your win in the case.
I already told you I don't want
those videos to come out, right?
[sighs]
Okay.
If you need us there,
just tell us.
No!
Don't come here.
It's not safe.
Oh my god, babe.
You're going through a lot of hardships.
You're fighting against an abusive spouse
and a serial killer at the same time!
That's why I told my mom
not to follow me here either.
I don't want you guys
to get dragged into this.
Edong's also
targeting everyone close to us.
[suspenseful music playing]
There he is.
[reporter] TV host Anton Montenegro
gets provisional release
after the court allowed him
to post bail for the three cases
filed against him by his wife,
Mel Barrera Montenegro,
Attorney Erica Melendez,
and another one of her friends.
[camera shutters clicking]
Anton, what do
you think of the judge's decision?
"ANTON MONTENEGRO, PROVISIONAL RELEASE,
GREETED BY SUPPORTERS"
I'm disappointed, of course.
Like I said,
I just defended
myself that's why they got hurt.
And I believe the prosecutors…
made a grave error in judgment.
But I'm ready,
to prove my innocence in court.
Have you talked to Mel?
- [camera shutters clicking]
- I've…
actually reached out to my wife.
Many times.
- [suspenseful music continues]
- [cameral shutters clicking]
Mel…
I don't know why you're doing this.
But we can still fix this.
Despite everything that has happened,
I just want to let you know…
I still love you, Mel.
[camera shutters clicking]
[Anton's supporters cheering]
- We love you, Anton!
- Whoo!
- "WE BELIEVE YOU, ANTON"
- We love you!
[reporter] Based on what we saw today,
there are still many
who support Anton Montenegro
despite the cases he is facing.
Supporters of so-called
Golden Couple are currently divided
and the issue is expected
to get even more controversial
in the coming weeks.
- Geez! Here we go again!
- "#WeStandWithMel"
This is why so many
women are afraid to speak out
because no one would believe them!
You're so cruel for victim blaming Mel!
And seriously?!
Just because Anton's
handsome and looks like a "green flag"
you're so convinced he can't hurt a fly?
Oh, come on, people!
Stop this toxic fanaticism! Please!
I stand with Mel.
- Oh, come on!
- "#BoycottMel #YourStylesTrash"
We're not born yesterday!
[scoffs] You can't fool us!
Hey, Celebrity Stylist Mel!
Your cover's trash just like your style!
Stop making stuff up just
because you got caught cheating!
You're making my blood boil!
"@SintaOfficialPage
WORKS TO PROTECT WOMEN'S RIGHTS
AND AMPLIFY THE VOICES OF SURVIVORS
WHO HAVE LONG BEEN
SILENCED BY FEAR AND STIGMA."
- It's so unfair! Mel's so mean!
- "BoycottMel #AntonNotGuilty"
What if Anton ends up in jail?
No, I can't take it!
I've been losing sleep, guys.
Because what if
Anton really ends up in jail?!
I can't take it!
[music becomes ominous]
[screaming] Aah!
- [thudding]
- [grunts]
Why?! Why?!
[laughing]
- [objects breaking]
- Why me?!
Why?!
[laughing maniacally]
[manic laughing continues]
Why did you let them stop me?
[fake crying]
[laughing maniacally]
[eerie music playing]
- [objects thudding]
- [laughing maniacally]
Is this another trial?
[laughing maniacally]
[objects cracking]
[screaming] Argh!
[laughing maniacally]
[eerie music continues]
[music turns unsettling]
Why must you always test me?!
[laughing maniacally]
Why did you even let me live,
if you were only going
to put a stop to my mission?
[laughing, crying]
[unsettling music continues]
I just want to correct their mistakes.
That's my mission.
[dramatic music sting]
[dramatic music stings]
[unsettling music intensifies]
[screaming]
[ominous music sting]
Ma, when I saw
the dead cat, I was so terrified.
Why is he doing this to us, Ma?
We're surrounded by villains.
I don't want you to get hurt.
I don't want you to be involved, Uncle.
We are surrounded by
people who wants to punish us.
You're nothing
without me! I'll destroy you!
And I feel like we're just waiting
to see which one of them strikes first.
The demons may send
angels to protect sinners,
I won't stop until I complete my mission.