She's so disappointed
in me.
I will never forget
the way she looked at me.
Let's just talk
to Chloe again.
- Love, go home.
- I will, love.
Argh... Ugh...
F**king untie me!
I don't like your wife.
But you know
what I dislike even more?
Men like you.
- Argh!
Are you going home?
It's almost morning.
Love... Anton's dead...
- Put your hands up!
- I didn't do this!
- Love, what's happening?!
- I didn't do anything wrong!
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[PHONE BUZZING]
Hello?
What?!
[FOOTSTEPS]
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Ryan! Ryan?! Ryan!
[RYAN] Love! Love! Love...
- What did they do to you?
- [LOCSIN] Oh, Beth!
W-Why are you full of blood?
- Did they hurt you? Why are--
- [LOCSIN] Beth! Beth.
Why is he handcuffed, Locsin?!
What did you do to him?!
What did you do to my husband?!
We didn't hurt him, Beth.
But he's a suspect in the death
of Anton Montenegro!
What?! Is this a joke?!
Locsin, you know my husband
could never do that!
I'm sorry, but this is my job.
We found him all bloody.
He was right next
to the murder weapon,
and right in front
of the victim's body!
Even if it's the corpse
of the most corrupt politician,
he'd never do that!
My husband is not a killer!
Love... It's fine.
- We can fix this.
- What do you mean it's fine?!
Remove his handcuffs!
Let's just talk
at the police station.
[BETH] Locsin, you know
my husband could never do this!
Get my husband out of there!
This isn't him!
You know he didn't kill Anton!
What's with you?!
- Beth, calm down.
- Calm down?!
How, when they're going to
imprison my innocent husband?!
[BETH] Locsin, remove
his handcuffs!
Beth... Please.
[MAN 1] Her husband's dead.
They could make
more sex videos now!
- [MAN 2] Yeah.
- [MAN 3] Look at her.
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATION]
[BETH] Locsin.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATION]
[ALICE] Beth, let Erica
fix this.
You know she'll help you.
[ERICA] Did you read him
his rights?
Yes.
Ryan, don't talk
until I'm not there.
I'll follow you to the station.
Love...
Everything will be okay.
We'll get through this.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[ENGINE HUMS]
[PHONE RINGING]
Hello?
[EDONG] How's your husband?
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
You bastard!
How does it feel, Beth...
to be accused of a crime...
...you didn't do?
You did this, didn't you?!
You did this!
You did all of this,
didn't you?!
Why are you doing this?!
[EDONG LAUGHING]
Wow, ma'am is
acting innocent...
...and pretending to be stupid.
[EDONG LAUGHING]
I want to make you feel
what you made me feel, Beth.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
You're a liar...
Beth.
You want to imprison
and punish others
like what you did to me.
You want to destroy lives...
and separate them
from their families...
...like what you did
to me and my brother.
Don't you teach this
to your students, Beth?
That what you reap, Beth...
...is what you sow.
Now...
The man you love...
[EDONG CHUCKLING]
...will also suffer.
He'll be hurt the same way
you made me feel.
There's nothing
you can do, Beth.
you can do, but watch.
You know it yourself, Beth...
that it is all...
It is all your fault!
You d**n b**tard! D**n you!
Why are you doing this,
you b**tard?! You demon!
You're a demon!
[BETH SOBBING]
[BETH] Why are you doing this?!
Why not me?! Huh?!
[BETH SOBBING]
[ERICA] You've already taken
a lot from them!
Why don't you take revenge
on me?!
[EDONG] But I've been doing
that to you
for a long time now...
Attorney.
You want to save people, right?
But you didn't save anyone.
Not a single one...
...from me.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
You couldn't do anything,
Attorney... [CHUCKLES]
But watch them cry...
...and get angry,
while they lose everything.
You're useless, Attorney.
You are worthless.
[ANNETTE] Die!
[EDONG] You're not
a savior, Attorney.
[ANNETTE] You shouldn't have
been born!
You shouldn't be alive!
You'll just become
like your father.
I should have killed you!
D**n you! Die!
[EDONG] You know what you are?
You are a fake hero.
Fake...
...hero.
[EDONG CHUCKLES]
Just like the pity
you gave me before.
You didn't do anything
to help me, Attorney.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
I've been taking something
from you for a long time now.
I'm slowly destroying
everything
you think you stand for.
Don't you feel it?
Attorney?
[EDONG INHALES]
I am destroying you.
[EDONG CHUCKLING]
When are you going to stop?!
What else is there, Edong?!
What more do you want,
so we can end this?!
I'm not going to stop
until I've ruined everything
you want to save.
Everything will be ruined,
nothing will be left.
Not even one.
You all built your lives
because of a lie.
You ruined my life
What did you think, Attorney?
That your lies
could protect you forever?
I'll get my revenge.
And you will pay.
Accept it now, Attorney.
You won't save anyone.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
- You were cheating on me?!
- Ouch, ouch.
- What?! How dare you!
- [MAN] That wasn't me!
[WOMAN] I don't care!
Bebang reported you!
- [MAN] She's just accusing me.
- [WOMAN] Accusing you?!
She saw your hand
on Marie's thigh!
- How dare you...
- I'm not cheating on you.
Edong called you?
[BETH] Edong talked to me,
but he also talked to Erica.
It's like he already confessed
to killing Anton, right?
[BETH] He wants to get back
at us! You know that!
You even gave us
a protection detail, remember?
It's unfortunate the shop
isn't part of our surveillance.
I only remembered
when we were on our way.
If you were monitoring it,
this wouldn't have happened!
[ERICA] Wait, you said
a tipster messaged you.
- Do you know who that was?
- It was an anonymous tip.
It only said there was
a murder in Ryan's shop.
That was also Edong.
If they have the same number,
we have circumstantial proof
that can help
our frame of theory.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
It's the same!
Did you record the call?
No! But shouldn't
this be enough evidence?
Ryan should be acquitted!
[LOCSIN] It still needs to go
through the proper process.
When he arrived,
just after 6AM,
that began his 36 hours
under inquest detention.
So, before
it turns 6PM tomorrow,
we have to take him
to the prosecution,
along with the police report
and possible evidence
against him.
Only then will
the prosecutor decide
if he should be charged
or not.
[BETH] Is it possible
for him to be sued?
Huh? Is it possible?
What if...
- Erica, what if...
- It'll be difficult for them.
The prosecution now looks
for heavy evidence,
not just probable cause.
They'll only take it to court
if they think
there's a realistic chance
for Ryan to be found guilty.
If the evidence is weak, they
will release Ryan right away.
Does that mean he'll stay here,
while we wait for the decision?
Yes. And while we're moving,
only medico-legal can prove if
Ryan's injuries are consistent
with the fact
that he was unconscious
before the police arrived.
If that's put in the report,
we can question
the validity of the arrest.
Is there still no medico-legal
officer available?
Negative. They were all
deployed in Liwayway
because of a group ambush.
But we're reaching out
to other medico-legal officers
in nearby towns.
I hope someone's available.
We'll have them picked up
right away.
Alice and Mel are also
in the hospital.
They're talking
to Mel's family friends.
They're checking if
there are medico-legal doctors
available in nearby towns.
I hope
they have some good news.
The injury on the back
of Ryan's head,
shouldn't that be evidence?
Evidence that he was set up!
[ERICA] That's right, Beth.
But that all depends
on the findings
of medico-legal.
But don't worry.
Marco already began
an independent investigation.
Lucas is helping, too.
Everything they can get,
along with our sworn statements
about Edong's call...
I'll use those in the inquest
to weaken their case
against Ryan.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- Love!
- Beth. You can't touch him.
A medico-legal officer has
to check him first.
The evidence might be ruined.
Crime Ops cleaned only
a few parts of his body...
...to prevent him
from getting infected.
But everything was documented
before that.
You explain this
to Chloe, okay?
Tell her,
her father's not a murderer.
What's with you?
Even if they show
millions of evidence,
she'd never believe
that you could kill someone.
Love, we're going
to fix this, okay?
We'll get you out of here,
I promise.
You can do it, love.
You push down everyone
who stands in your way.
And now you're
with your super lawyer friend.
They'll all be ruined.
[EDONG] Everything
will be ruined,
nothing will be left.
You won't save anyone.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[LOCSIN] You can count us.
We'll be fair.
I know this isn't Ryan's doing.
- This isn't Ryan's doing?
- Sir!
Lieutenant Locsin...
Our job is to look
for evidence,
not to make allies!
There's no such thing as
friends here! Not on my watch.
Bring all the case files
of this Ryan
to my office.
I'll be on top
of this investigation.
Sir, yes, sir.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
That was Lieutenant Colonel
Kian Delos Santos.
Our new station commander.
He's from Manila.
He's too... by the book.
We can't do anything.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
If Anton was really
killed here...
There should be more blood.
So why is there so little?
Why is it all over the place?
[MARCO] Look at those.
If he was killed here,
there should be more of that.
That means...
He was killed somewhere else.
He couldn't have been killed
in our old house
because I was there last night.
It's possible that Anton
went here to Amurao,
and he met Edong by chance.
That is the most possible.
But how did he bring
the body here?
He could've used Anton's car.
But I already circled
this area earlier.
I can't find the car.
Your brother could've ran
away with it.
If there was any evidence
that could point to him,
I'm sure he already
disposed of the car.
We need to find him.
Crime Ops will stay here
until later.
For now, let's...
go house to house.
There might be a CCTV
that caught what happened.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[MARCO] The crime scene
hasn't been released.
But there's not enough blood
to say Anton was killed here.
That has to be included
in the police report.
Only then can we match
it to the blood stain pattern
analysis and toolmark exam.
[ERICA] The forensic report
will surely be in our favor.
But when will that be?
The problem is that
even preliminary
medico-legal findings
might not reach
tomorrow's hearing.
They're understaffed,
and have a huge backlog.
- [MARCO] D**n.
- Well, d**n it is!
Ryan's injuries were only given
first aid!
He hasn't even been checked
by medico--
Erica?
[ERICA] By the way,
have you reached
Ryan's two mechanics?
We need them, Marco.
We can get something from them.
[MARCO] I'm done
with Art Lacuña.
But I can't reach Edgar Mata.
I'll look for him.
I'll call you again.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[MEL BREATHES SHAKILY]
[ERICA] Mel.
I'm sorry, I didn't even think
to ask you.
How are you?
I know Anton's your abuser,
but he's still your husband.
I'm not even heartbroken by it.
[MEL BREATHING SHAKILY]
[MEL] I-If anything, I...
I feel relieved, that's why...
That's why
I feel guilty because...
You're right, Erica.
Anton was my husband.
I shouldn't just be feeling
shocked now, right?
[MEL BREATHING SHAKILY]
Think about it, Mel.
[ALICE] Why did he come
here last night?
Probably to confront you
about the video, or...
about the fact that...
He's not in control
of the house...
Or even
his bank accounts, right?
I mean, who knows
what he could have done to you?
Remember, he was so angry
at the coffee shop.
When you didn't want
to go back to him.
What more last night?
[MEL SNIFFLES]
He probably came here
to hurt you.
So, no.
You don't owe
that f**king man anything.
I'm sorry.
[ALICE SIGHS DEEPLY]
[BETH EXHALES DEEPLY]
I was too defensive.
I told Chloe
what I had done.
A-About the watch
they found with Edong.
I told her that...
I lied to the police
that the watch was Louisa's.
[MEL SNIFFLES]
[BETH BREATHING SHAKILY]
I knew she was going
to be disappointed...
[MEL CRYING]
But... I was still defensive.
[BETH] I'm defensive
even with my daughter.
Even with you.
[BETH CRYING]
Do you know why?
Because even though
I told the truth...
It's still not the truth.
[BETH SNIFFLES]
It's not the whole truth.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
Back then, I always said...
that I lied because...
I believed
that Edong killed Louisa.
That he should be imprisoned.
- [MEL SNIFFLES]
- [BETH SNIFFLES]
But the truth is...
I did it for myself.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
I just believed
in what Celestino said.
That I would lose
my scholarship...
that all my plans
would be ruined...
That d**n bastard.
- [GLOOMY MUSIC PLAYING]
- [BETH SOBBING]
I had no choice but to lie.
[SNIFFLING]
And I forced all of you
to go along with it.
I didn't feel a shred of guilt
sending Edong to prison.
[BETH SNIFFLES]
Even when you got mad
and left us.
Even when our friendship
was ruined
because of what I did.
Because...
I had to do it for myself.
[GLOOMY MUSIC CONTINUES]
But...
[SNIFFLES, BREATH SHAKING]
Even before Edong could
get back at me,
karma struck first.
I thought...
I could lie and live
the rest of my life
like nothing had happened.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
Yet it feels like I've never
done anything right in my life.
[TIME TICKS BACKWARD]
[BETH] Maybe it's because...
I've always been ashamed.
That guilt has been
eating me alive.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
Even though I couldn't
admit it to myself.
[TIME TICKS FORWARD]
[BETH, ALICE CRYING
AND SNIFFLING]
I got left behind
during college.
I was way too full of myself
when I said...
that I could make it.
That I could make a name
for myself.
But when the moment came,
I couldn't keep up
with the others.
Everyone assumed...
I regretted having a child
so young.
But the truth is,
I was relieved.
At least I had something
to blame
for being such a failure.
- [EMOTIONAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [SOBBING, SNIFFLING]
A flop.
The biggest flop.
Elizabeth "Flop" Sevilla-Mora.
I didn't want to be stuck
in Amurao.
Honestly,
I could've gone to Manila
and resumed my studies
after giving birth to Chloe.
But, I guess...
I just wanted to ruin my life.
[WHIMPERS]
Erica...
Erica, I'm sorry.
[SOBBING CONTINUES]
Every time I accused you
of being selfish,
I was really aiming at myself.
I'm sorry for looking down
on you back in high school.
I'm sorry that...
when you became successful,
all I could feel toward you
was anger and envy.
Because honestly,
that was all I had.
Pride.
I felt so small.
Clinging to pride was the only
thing that kept me standing.
Erica, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
But now, Erica,
I'm giving up all my pride.
Erica.
Erica, I'm begging on my knees.
Erica, free my husband
from prison.
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Erica, please, help us.
Help my husband.
Erica--
Help us.
My family doesn't
deserve this, Erica.
I do. Every bit of it.
Erica, please...
We need your help.
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[BETH SOBBING]
Erica, please...
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Thanks, Marco,
but I'm not sure about this.
We can make it work.
So, what's the plan?
I know you.
You don't give up easily.
You should've never...
You're no hero.
You're worthless.
I couldn't promise to help him.
What if Edong was right?
You killed my son!
- Get out!
- You killed my son!
It's all her fault!
You and your friends...
You all deserve to die!
Will you help me finish this?
I still have a score to settle.