We're taking statements
from Mrs. Mora's daughter.
It's possible they saw the suspect.
Do you have CCTV installed at home?
I can give you access.
The guy was about to kill us,
and you still took a video?!
Are you the G.O.A.T, or are you cringe?
Instinct, bro!
I heard Esther's staying there for now.
She's helping look after her sister…
Just keep an eye on Esther.
We'll get there before she leaves.
If we were wrong about Esther,
we could've been wrong about Lucas too.
- You don't need me anymore?
- Ow!
[MAN 1] I feel bad for Esther.
Did you see her face? All beaten up.
Had to be rushed to the hospital.
[man 2] Damn. I bet she was followed.
She was on her way to the bank
to deposit money when she was robbed.
[man 3] Good thing they didn't kill her.
They just took the money.
Money can be replaced. Life can't.
[man 1] And she cried like crazy.
Just imagine. She lost the money
her classmates pooled together.
I heard they were
planning to renovate our church.
[man 2] Yeah.
And Esther's super into church.
She probably feels like
she let God down by getting robbed.
Poor woman.
[somber music playing]
[Esther sighs]
What a day.
- I'm so exhausted.
- Same here, sister.
- I agree.
- But…
Father will be even more pleased if…
Miss Esther! Miss Esther!
Maybe you just got it wrong.
I know Edong didn't hurt Louisa.
Please take back what you told the police.
I'm begging you.
[somber music continues]
Instead of calling me a liar,
perhaps you should
pray for your brother's soul.
- Absolutely.
- Isn't that right, sister?
Help him repent of his sins.
And you should repent too.
For covering up your brother's wrongdoing.
- That's a sin.
- Yes, sister.
You saw someone else!
[young Lucas sniffling]
I'm sure of it! It was dark!
The police would
understand if you made a mistake!
Oh no, I don't like
what I'm hearing right now!
We're church ladies.
Sinning isn't something we do!
- Step aside!
- We can't do that!
My goodness!
- He's a lost cause.
- Poor boy.
[theme music playing]
[Chloe panting]]
Seriously? You were taking a video
while a lunatic was chasing you?
I was in my journalist mode, Ma.
[chuckles]
Huh? Journalist mode?
I'll take your phone away, just you wait.
[Chloe] But why, Pa?
What if some other
creep tries to chase us again?
How many times does this have to happen?
It's like you're
wishing for it to happen again.
What's up with your daughter?
She's debating me again.
[Chloe] Just speaking facts, Pa.
[Ryan] Speaking facts?
How about you finish your food?
Here. Want a slice?
[unsettling music playing]
[Joshua] What makes you say that?
- He was wearing a hoodie.
- No! He wasn't!
He was! It was a dark one!
No! I know what I saw!
[Mel] Don't you find it strange?
After Erica warned us
about Edong and Lucas,
this happened all of a sudden.
According to the kids,
the man who followed them
was wearing a cap and a hoodie.
Isn't that also what
Louisa's killer was wearing?
He was laughing…
He was laughing like he enjoyed it.
Like he was playing games with us.
[dark version of
"Sabay Sabay Tayo" playing]
[utensils clink]
- I need to go somewhere.
- Huh? Where?
We're still eating.
And we're not done
talking to our daughter.
She won't listen to me if you're not here.
I won't take long. Give me your keys.
- Drive carefully.
- Mm-hmm.
Take care.
[unsettling music continues]
[music becomes suspenseful]
[music fades]
[sniffles]
[breath quivers]
[dogs barking distantly]
Thank you.
Your mom called me.
She told me what happened.
[sighs] Why did
you leave your husband, Alice?
[inhales shakily]
Did he hurt you?
[morose music playing]
Don't lie to me, Scott!
I know you were with her!
My friend saw you at a hotel!
Yes, we were!
But there were other people too!
- A group of us from college met there!
- Ah…
I would never cheat on you.
Y-You know that I love you, right?
I knew this would happen.
I knew it.
Your family never liked me.
They wanted you to marry her.
Is this it?
Is this you giving them what they want?
You're talking crazy!
I am not cheating on you!
Please, Alice!
Let's just talk, Alice!
[grunts] Argh!
[vase shatters]
[panicked breaths]
- No…
- Alice…
- [breathing shakily]
- Alice, I-I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Alice. Are you okay?
It was an accident.
I have never hurt you, and I never will.
But the way you've
treated me these past months,
like I was some kind of monster.
[breathes deeply]
Alice, I don't know
what's happening anymore.
Please, just talk to me.
[breathing sharply]
I want a divorce.
- What?
- You heard me.
What do you want?!
How many times do I have to apologize?!
I don't need you to apologize!
I said I want a divorce!
Well, I don't!
Stop treating me like I'm your enemy.
I thought we were going to fix this?
I'll go to therapy with you.
Couples counseling.
I'll do that too. Just please,
please, please don't do this.
I'm leaving, Scott.
Alice, please--
- [breathing shakily]
- [tense music playing]
You're not taking Seth with you.
And if you insist on doing this,
I'll sue you for full custody.
[Alice exhales heavily]
[tense music continues]
- [music fades]
- [crickets chirping]
[sighs heavily]
So…
do you think…
that Scott really wanted to hurt you?
What if…
he was telling the truth?
That he didn't want that to happen?
Believe me, Uncle.
He's a monster.
[pensive music playing]
So you think that he has something to do…
with the trouble
that happened at your house?
[scoffs] Who else could it be?
Maybe he doesn't
even want to wait for the trial.
[sniffles] Maybe
he wants to take Seth away from me.
But if that were true,
why didn't the person go inside the house?
Why didn't he take Seth?
We hid in the bathroom.
Hurry! Hurry!
Let's go inside!
[unsettling music playing]
Maybe he came in while we were in there.
But you didn't hear anything
outside the bathroom, right?
He didn't even try
to force himself in there.
[pensive music continues]
[Christina] Hon?
Edward?
Just a minute.
- I thought someone was going to get shot.
- Ma'am, hold on.
- Me too.
- Hold on.
- We should always stay alert.
- Ma'am, hold on!
Locsin, have
you checked the CCTV at Alice's house?
Hold on. Dalimit.
Have you checked the CCTV footage?
Not yet. We're just about to do so.
What do you mean?
You had it since earlier!
- Why haven't you checked it?
- Beth.
Just so you know,
something bad happened here earlier.
Some of the cops were
even sent to the hospital.
So please be mindful of your tone.
Well, my friend is getting paranoid.
So I'm hoping you can
speed up your investigation. Okay?
You really are something.
Yes, ma'am. Sure thing, ma'am!
I'll tell you when
something comes up. Okay?
Just please be patient.
We'll call Mrs. Miller after
we're done checking the footage.
Fine.
- [suspenseful music playing]
- [engine revving]
[suspenseful music continues]
- [winces softly]
- [suspenseful music fades]
[Anton] Babe?
- How are you feeling?
- [Mel exhales deeply]
Leave me alone.
[unsettling music playing]
[Mel breathing shakily]
Babe?
That's okay.
I'm not going to touch you.
I didn't know you were injured earlier.
[Anton] I'm so sorry.
Uh, Mrs. Montenegro?
[sighs awkwardly]
The results of your tests are back,
and you have a bruised liver.
Fortunately, it's only a grade 1 injury.
It could have been much worse.
So now, you really need to rest well
and allow your body to recover.
Please avoid alcohol and
non-prescription medications.
[unsettling music continues]
[doctor] Next time, be more careful, okay?
And you also mentioned, you slipped
and hit the edge of the table?
[music becomes tense]
- [stabbing sound]
- [Mel screams in pain]
[groans]
[Mel sobbing]
[coughs]
[breathes heavily]
[tense music continues]
Mrs. Montenegro?
Babe?
That's not true, Dr.
[tense music continues]
[music becomes foreboding]
[car door closes]
[music fades]
Ma'am Esther.
Do you remember me?
[crickets chirping]
I'm Lucas Santiago, Edong's brother.
[ominous music playing]
[music becomes tense]
- What my wife means, Dr.--
- Slipped…
is an understatement.
[Mel giggles softly]
I've walked a lot of runways,
but the truth is,
I'm really clumsy. [chuckles]
Sometimes,
I even trip while just standing still.
[Anton exhales deeply]
That's true, Dr.
This isn't the first time
my wife's been hospitalized.
She's uncoordinated.
Thank you, Dr.
Tonight was supposed
to be a night of celebration.
And it still is.
Because you saved Mel.
[doctor] You just have
to be extra careful, okay?
If the hit
to your liver had been stronger,
it could have been
a severe or even a fatal injury.
It'd be a shame to waste
your big billboard on EDSA
if something happened to you.
It's already up?
- [breathes softly]
- [tense music continues]
[chuckles softly]
My wife will be more
careful next time, Dr.
She has so much she wants to protect…
with everything she has now.
[tense music continues]
- [music ends]
- [engine revving]
The police are unbelievable!
They still haven't
checked your CCTV footage.
[faucet running]
[sighs]
When did they say they'll do it?
They said they're starting soon.
But didn't you just
share access with them?
We can still check the footage ourselves.
[curtain slides open]
- [eerie music swells]
- [screaming]
[Alice breathing heavily]
We have to go! We have to go!
[breathing heavily]
Let's go, baby!
[door clicks]
[Seth] Mom, I'm scared.
- [breathes sharply]
- [Seth] Mommy…
- [Alice screams]
- [Seth cries]
I'm calling the police!
[glass shatters]
[Alice screaming, breathing heavily]
[unsettling music playing]
[huffs slightly]
Sorry. Did that stress you out?
I know you don't want
to see whoever broke into your house,
but this way, we can identify them faster.
You'll all be safer, and so will Chloe.
You're right. [exhales shakily]
Where are you?
[sighs]
We're checked in at
Parkland Hotel right now.
We'll stay here
until the house gets fixed.
Okay, I'll come see you.
[unsettling music playing]
[inhales]
[Edward] Do you believe…
Scott meant to hurt you?
What if he's telling the truth…
that he didn't mean for it to happen?
[unsettling music continues]
[Christina] Hon? Edward?
Oh, wait.
[Christina] Edward?
- [somber music playing]
Sweetheart.
Edward…
Why did you leave me?
I don't want to be alone.
Sweetheart, I'm right here.
I just stepped out for a while.
You were with Althea earlier, weren't you?
- [groans slightly] Yes.
- Oh!
[somber music continues]
Sweetheart, look.
I brought someone with me.
Do you still remember her?
[chuckles]
It's Alice.
Our niece.
[music becomes pensive]
Hi.
Hi, Auntie Christina.
It's me, Alice.
How have you been?
Sorry I'm only visiting now.
I missed you.
Who are you?
You're not Alice.
My niece is only 16 years old.
[somber music resumes]
Uh, sweetheart.
Sweetheart, you need to get some sleep.
[chuckles softly]
Go on, get some rest.
- [exhales]
- Go.
[Edward] Hmm.
[somber music continues]
[Edward grunts softly]
[exhales]
You have to make sure about Scott, Alice.
Love can be painful.
No matter how happy it feels,
it always comes with pain.
But that's not enough reason to give up.
I just want you to be sure…
before you throw away
something beautiful in your life.
[somber music continues]
- [somber music fades]
- [door unlocks]
[foreboding music playing]
[handbrake ratchets]
[Erica] Isn't this Lucas's car?
He might already be inside.
[Esther grunts]
[music turns suspenseful]
[suspenseful music intensifies]
- [Lucas] I just want to make things right.
- [Esther] Stay away from me!
- Miss Esther!
- [whimpers]
Just say you're safe and alive!
Admit you lied about my brother!
People like you and your brother
are the reason this
country is drowning in darkness!
Monster!
[Esther grunts]
What did you do?!
Edong, he was at my house last night!
That's impossible! He's in prison?
I'm sure we'll see each other again.
Edong Santiago has
been leaving the prison!
Is he escaping,
or are you letting him out?!