[Chloe] Is Aunty Mel going to be okay?
[Beth] It's going to be really hard.
But I know she'll get through it.
Because we're not leaving her.
[Scott] Are you
really okay with us leaving?
[Alice] It would be
so much better if you stayed,
but we have no choice.
We have to protect Seth.
People just laugh about what happened.
But my daughter can barely function
because of the shame and fear.
She's so broken.
[Erica] There are people
who are capable of
doing disgusting things to others.
I try to be a good person.
What I want to see in others,
I start with myself.
I'm so goddamn tired of being scared.
So I'm going to do
what my friends told me to do.
Now I can finally set these videos,
and myself, free.
[ominous music playing]
[whistling "Sabay Sabay Tayo"]
[whistling continues]
[music turns foreboding]
[foreboding music continues]
[foreboding music crescendos]
[theme music playing]
[club music playing]
Holy shit, dude!
He really got you.
What, dude? Should we get him back?
Let's do to them
what they did to your face.
Yeah. Should we hit back?
You think it was Mel
who told that guy to attack you?
I don't know.
My lawyer said probably,
to intimidate me over the case.
[scoffs] Your toxic wife
is really something, dude.
A cheater and an abuser!
I wonder if the guy she's with
knows she's like that.
- What a bitch.
- Hey!
Will you stop talking about her like that?
Don't tell me
you actually believe that cheater.
[huffs] All I'm saying is, if it was me,
I wouldn't want to be
a victim of a deepfake sex video.
After all, she's still a woman.
Show some respect.
Wait, so…
you believe it's fake?
Yes.
Then…
- you're stupid.
- [woman scoffs]
[tense music playing]
Hey, Anton!
And your lapdogs!
You guys might want
to watch Mel's channel.
Why? Is there a new sex video?
[Jennie scoffs]
[tense music continues]
[Mel] Help! Help!
Aah! Help me!
Dude, what the hell?
[Mel] Help!
[woman] So it's true?
Everything Mel said about you?
Oh my God. You're so disgusting!
No, no!
That video isn't real, okay?
It's not real. Relax.
Narcissist! Monster!
What did you call me, huh?
Fuck you!
- Bro! Bro!
- What the hell?!
- Stop!
- Hey, dude!
- Anton, stop!
- Bro, stop it already!
- Get out!
- Stop it!
- What's wrong with you?
- Come on, bro!
- I'm going fucking to kill you!
You fucking bitch!
Get off me!
[crowd murmuring]
[tense music continues]
[Mel] Lately,
I've been feeling so exposed.
It's like my skin was peeled off.
This made me feel naked,
vulnerable, and afraid.
You fucking monster!
So it's true you'll
hurt any woman you want?
Mel was right.
No one is safe with you.
Asshole!
Get the fuck out of here.
Get out!
Fuck you!
Fuck you all!
Fuck you! Fuck everybody in this room!
- Fuck all of you!
- Get out!
- Asshole!
- Leave!
- Don't ever come back here!
This is all your fault!
You useless fucking bitch!
I should've finished you off before.
I'm going to fucking kill you, Mel.
[tense music continues]
What the fuck are you looking at, huh?
Are you taking a video of me? For what?
Are you going to post that? Go ahead!
I'll sue you both, bitches!
I'll sue you! I'll sue you!
[scoffs] Yeah, that's right.
Run!
You think I'm scared of you?
You should all be scared of me!
I'm Anton Montenegro!
None of you can destroy me!
Not Mel, not you, not any one of you!
What?! Who are you looking at?
What's your problem, huh?
[Mel] It's done.
[music fades]
I just ruined my life.
[inhales, exhales sharply]
But why does it feel
like a weight's been lifted?
[poignant music playing]
For the first time in a long while…
I'm free.
[chuckles] Is it weird?
I don't know,
that's how I feel. [chuckles]
[poignant music continues]
I'm so proud of you.
[sobbing]
[music becomes tender-hearted]
[music becomes unsettling]
[cicadas chirping]
[cane scraping]
You think you can outsmart me?
[both grunting]
[unsettling music continues]
[Edong] I'll get you, Alice.
You and your executioner.
No one is escaping.
Not one of you.
[unsettling music continues]
- [music fades]
- [whistling "Sabay Sabay Tayo"]
- [whistling fades]
- [ominous music playing]
[ominous music sting]
[Alice] Mel?
[music fades]
[water lapping]
[Mel sighs heavily]
[Alice] So…
What made you decide
to finally put out the videos?
[Mel scoffs]
Louisa.
I had a dream about her.
She told me to…
let it all fall apart.
Then, just start over.
Sure sounds like Louisa.
What's your plan?
Well, right now…
Honestly,
nothing.
I know I'm going to have
to start from the beginning.
I know it's going to be
a long and difficult battle, but…
I know one thing is for sure.
I will not break.
I heard your conversation with my mom.
You're right, Erica.
Anton expects me to break.
So I will not.
Yeah. Maybe that's the whole plan.
We're here for you.
We've got you.
[Mel chuckles softly]
You know what's funny?
Louisa said the same thing.
That I can get through all of this.
Like how she overcame
everything she went through
during and after her issue with Kyle.
[pensive music playing]
She said she made it through that
because we were there for her.
And she said that
you would do the same for me.
I said a lot of things have changed.
But,
if I can restart my life,
then why not our friendship too?
Right?
[Mel sniffles]
We can.
- [music fades]
- [water lapping]
I'm sorry.
[somber music playing]
You will need a lot of
patience when it comes to me.
All my life,
it's just been me and Marco.
No friends.
No family.
[somber music continues]
[Mel] Well,
for someone with no friends or family,
you still didn't think
twice to come to our rescue.
You've always been like that.
You and Louisa.
You were always
MABEL's first line of defense.
Always the first to jump into danger.
Without even considering your own safety.
[Erica sniffles]
Uh…
About me and Lucas…
[stirring music playing]
[phone buzzing]
Oh, I missed a call from Beth.
Let me call her back.
[stirring music continues, fades]
[shovel thudding]
[Edong grunts]
[whistling "Sabay Sabay Tayo"]
[foreboding music playing]
- How is she?
- [whistling, music fades]
[Alice] Considering
how life-changing that was?
[chuckles softly]
She's actually okay.
[Alice sighs heavily]
She said she felt relieved.
Like, she's…
free.
[melancholic music playing]
Just like you,
when you told me
what you were going
through in your marriage.
Your issues with Scott.
Yeah.
It felt like a weight
was lifted from my chest.
[melancholic music continues]
Maybe that's what I'll feel too.
What do you mean?
[melancholic music continues]
[Erica] What I said was true.
Lucas and I…
Erica, you don't--
You don't have to.
To be honest, I have no right to know.
That's between you and him.
[music fades]
I just wanted to be clear.
[sighs softly]
I was wrong.
I don't think I still feel
the same way for Lucas.
[chuckles softly]
I guess I was just hanging on to the past.
Because…
I was scared.
[Mel exhales heavily]
I was scared to be alone.
I was scared that…
no other guy like him
would ever choose me.
[melancholic music resumes]
And that's my problem, you know.
I always want a man's validation.
From…
My dad.
To Anton.
And even Lucas.
[melancholic music continues]
You've always known my dad was,
always so toxic.
He…
wanted me to believe that,
I was nothing.
Nothing without his approval.
And…
That led me to ignore all of
Anton's red flags when we were starting.
Until…
Nothing.
I couldn't get out. [sobs]
[melancholic music continues]
[sniffles] And Lucas…
[Mel sniffles]
Lucas will always be that one light,
during the darkest time of my life.
[Mel sniffles]
He became my support.
A temporary pain killer.
He made everything bearable.
[melancholic music continues]
And…
Yeah, we had our shot.
But…
It just didn't work. [scoffs]
It's over.
As for what you had together, Erica.
Yours was cut short.
So…
If you think this is the right time
for the both of you,
I'll be fine with it.
[melancholic music continues]
From now on,
I'm going to stick to the plan.
To not break.
And…
- I can only do it if I do some intense…
- [music becomes hopeful]
Self-care
and self-love.
[hopeful music continues]
To hell with men, right?
[both chuckling]
I'll pull an
Attorney Erica Melendez attitude.
[chuckling]
I don't know if that's a compliment
- [laughing]
- or an insult.
- It's a compliment!
- [Erica laughs]
You're the patron
saint of strong, independent,
and emotionally unavailable women.
[both laughing]
[music fades]
[Marco] Erica.
[tense music playing]
[monitor beeping]
[Marco] Kyo flatlined.
[tense music continues]
Oslo is singing like a canary.
[file thuds]
The digital forensic report just came in.
The videos on the USB?
Verified. Authentic.
No tampering, no edits.
- It's crystal clear that you were present
- [music fades]
when they were killed
and thrown into the river.
As we speak,
the complaint affidavit
to be submitted to the DOJ.
In a few days,
your arrest is imminent.
And you'll end up here.
You'll only get
bombarded with the same questions
so if I were you,
as early as now,
I'd start talking.
[investigator breathes deeply]
Tell me in detail
what happened to all of them.
Were they all dumped into the lake?
- [Oslo breathes heavily]
- [suspenseful music playing]
[Oslo] If I…
Tell you everything,
will you grant me immunity?
You'll put me in witness protection?
Whatever you think
you know about Laurence Kyo,
I'm sure that… [exhales deeply]
It's only this much.
He may be dead…
But the organization he handles?
It's too massive to dissolve.
I'm certain someone else
has already taken up his position.
And I'm also certain that,
it was him who ordered,
to have me killed.
Sir, I beg you.
I need protection!
I will give you all of the information
of the entire organization.
Even their connections
outside the Philippines.
Okay, okay.
We will put you
under our protective custody.
But…
That's if you give us good information.
Then we'll talk about your immunity.
Lost beauty queens.
[dramatic music playing]
[music turns suspenseful]
- Don't!
- Move!
- No!
- [gun cocks]
[gunshot]
[Oslo] Herlene Guinto.
Shot in the head. Tossed in the lake.
Janina Locsin.
Also shot in the head.
Lake.
As for LJ,
she was stabbed front and back.
Also in the lake.
- [shovel thudding]
- [dirt shuffling]
[suspenseful music intensifies]
[music becomes ominous, fades]
[birds chirping]
[foreboding music playing]
[dramatic music sting]
Do you ever feel like
you're living on borrowed time?
That you've got what you have,
at the cost of others.
That at any time,
it could all just fall apart.
[screaming]
Help… [crying]
What happened?
Is it true that they found a body?
[Edong] Did you all think you got past me?
He did this on
purpose to rub it in our face
that he won't let our dream
of growing old together come true!