Erica's theory is
that Louisa had a secret boyfriend,
that guy's Angelo?
My father died, then
Louisa followed after. Then, you left.
How could I ever forget my friends
who I thought were
different from my mother,
but also made me
feel that I didn't deserve
to be heard and believed in?
- [door creaks]
- [crickets chirping]
[groans, grunts]
These kids, really!
Every day it's like this!
Jeez.
[faint crying]
[woman] What's this? [grunts]
Oh. Where did it go?
[unsettling music playing]
[woman gasps]
[woman screams]
- [woman] Ah! Oh my god!
- [Alice] Huh? What…
[woman breathing rapidly]
[woman gasps]
[woman] Aah!
[woman breathing heavily]
- [Alice crying softly]
- [unsettling music continues]
[Alice sobbing]
[theme music playing]
[rain pattering]
[door shuts]
Why don't we just ask them?
You really think they'll the truth?
[rain continues pattering]
Why would they do that if
they have something to hide?
What if they're not hiding anything?
You're too loyal to our friends.
That's not how investigations work.
Why? Who's investigating?
Not me.
Didn't I tell you that I wouldn't do it?
[uneasy music playing]
"FYI. THE POLICE FOUND EDONG LAST NIGHT.
HE FELL INTO
THE SAN DIMAS RIVER AFTER GETTING SHOT.
THEY HAVEN'T FOUND HIM.
THE POLICE BELIEVE HE'S DEAD."
[uneasy music continues]
[phone pings]
[line trilling]
[phone ringing]
[phone pings]
[ringing continues]
[line trilling]
[phone rings]
[phone pings]
[disconnected tone]
- [Lucas] Any updates?
- [music fades]
[Yuri] Boss, we searched this area,
but we found nothing.
Negative.
We'll search this area next.
[unsettling music playing]
"WHY IS SHE STILL IN AMURAO?
DID THEY BREAK UP?"
"MAYBE THE RUMORS ARE
TRUE THAT THEY'VE BROKEN UP."
"MAYBE ANTON COULDN'T TAKE IT ANYMORE.
MEL PROBABLY GAVE HIM ANOTHER BLACK EYE!"
[unsettling music continues]
[music fades]
Rose, where's Alice?
I didn't hear her come home last night.
Ma'am, you have visitors.
[foreboding music playing]
[Mel] Mom. Dad. Uh…
[foreboding music continues, fades]
Hi! [chuckles]
- [Margie] I missed you so much!
- [Mel chuckles]
[Margie] Oh my!
We heard so many things happened to you
while we were in Europe. Are you okay?
Uh, yeah! Yeah, Mom, I'm perfectly fine.
Alright, that's good. [chuckles]
When I found out
you were home, I knew right away
- I had to take you both here.
- [Margie] Mm-hmm.
- You know us very well, Anton.
- [uneasy music playing]
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
[Cedric] Mel, why are you still here?
Go back home to your husband.
- [uneasy music continues]
- [chuckles] But, Dad,
Alice hasn't been back in
the Philippines for so long.
I'm just making up for lost girl time.
[Cedric scoffs]
Ever since you were a little girl,
you've never had any sense.
Go back to Manila with Anton.
Today.
We're not here to visit you.
We came to fetch you.
- [uneasy music continues]
- [Margie] Darling…
Mel has a husband now.
She's not a little girl anymore.
And if Anton is fine
with her staying here then,
it's none of our business.
It is our business!
Just a month ago,
there were rumors
going around that our daughter
is a husband beater.
She can't be making rash decisions.
Aren't you a celebrity?
Don't you check online
to see what people are saying, huh?
People are speculating
that you and Anton are fighting,
that you don't live in
the same house anymore.
[music becomes morose]
[music fades]
[Alice] Oh!
Oh my! Is that
Uncle Cedric and Aunt Margie?
- Hi!
- Hello, Alice.
- Hi, Uncle!
- [Margie] Hi!
Your stay in the US treated you well.
You keep getting prettier!
Oh, Auntie,
I will never be as beautiful as you.
[all chuckle]
Oh, and Anton,
thank you so much
for letting Mel stay here.
I've missed her so much.
You know, Uncle, Auntie,
after this whole Edong escaping thing,
Mel and I haven't found time to hang out.
- [Mel] Mm-hmm.
- Actually, in two days,
we're going to be visiting
the house we're renovating.
- [Margie] Ooh.
- We've only been there twice.
[Alice] We've been
so focused on being safe
and secure from Edong,
so we haven't gone out much.
[chuckles] Oh.
Why wait two days?
Can't you go there today?
[Alice] Um…
Actually, Uncle, Auntie, we're planning
to make a whole thing out of this.
Mel, Beth, and I, we want to reminisce
and celebrate our friend Louisa.
[Cedric] Oh.
[chuckles] Of course, of course.
[tense music playing]
[Alice chuckles]
[music ends]
Chloe!
Chloe, I'm sorry.
It's not right to forbid
you without an explanation.
But can't you trust Mama for now?
[melancholic music playing]
[door closes]
- Hey, you!
- Hmm?
Don't ask Angelo anything.
But you said
you wanted to know what they know.
How would we do that without asking?
- But, love…
- Tsk. Oh, you.
Have we learned
nothing from those shows on TV?
Trouble starts when
the main character keeps secrets.
- Hmm.
- The solution is easy.
They just need to talk.
And what if Angelo is the killer?
Are you going to let him
know that you're onto him?
Do you want me and Chloe to get hurt?
Tsk. Is that why you're
stopping her from going?
Do you really think
Angelo is going to hurt Chloe?
Didn't I tell you?
Angelo is not a killer, okay?
You defend Angelo like he's your endgame.
Aww, you're so cute! Let's go. Come on.
[foreboding music playing]
[Margie] Where's our driver?
What have you told
your friends about me, huh?
Did you say bad things about me?
You really think I would tell them
that I married a monster, Anton?
I would rather die than
humiliate myself like that.
But you…
You don't seem to feel any shame.
Are you not embarrassed that you had to
call my dad just to bring me home?
Gloat all you want.
We both know
that you'll come back to me.
[Mel grunts]
[tense music playing]
Do you remember that time…
when I asked you to wear a costume?
And you kept saying no,
because you said it was degrading.
But no matter how many times you refused,
you still wore it.
For me.
I have tons of those videos, babe.
Videos that show
what a liar and what a tease you can be.
Your 'no' always ends up being a 'yes.'
[tense music continues]
[smooches]
[music fades]
Alice, I was worried about you earlier.
When I woke up, you weren't there.
I'm okay. I'm okay, Uncle.
You left the house barefoot, Alice.
[Edward sighs]
Is it because…
the lights were out, that's why…
you went outside?
I- I'm sorry, I forgot.
You don't like the dark.
It's okay. It's okay, Uncle.
It's not your fault. [chuckles]
I'm okay.
Umm, don't worry about it.
Alright, I'm just making sure
you're okay.
Yeah.
I have to go.
Talk to you soon, Uncle. Bye.
[unsettling music playing]
[woman screaming]
- [water gushing]
- [unsettling music continues]
- [inaudible chatter]
- [unsettling music fades]
The police are issuing a statement.
[inaudible chatter]
- It's starting. I'll call you back.
- [reporter] Let's go.
[police] It's been two
days since our encounter
- with Edmundo Santiago,
- [morose music playing]
the convicted murderer
who escaped Bagumbayan Prison.
He was armed and dangerous,
so our officers were forced to shoot him.
He fell into the San Dimas River.
Based on witness accounts
and consultations with our experts,
we believe that Edmundo Santiago is dead.
The search and retrieval operations
for his body, are still ongoing.
[reporter] Sir, a question?
Is that your explanation?
Why don't you tell the truth?
That you shot my brother,
even though he was unarmed!
- Get away from me!
- [inaudible chatter]
I was there! "Armed and dangerous," huh?!
He didn't have a weapon on him!
- Nothing! He had nothing!
- "POLICE: ESCAPED PDL DEAD"
Now you're saying my brother's dead?
You don't even have his body!
Nothing!
Now you're giving up, huh?!
- [dramatic music playing]
- [reporters chattering indistinctly]
[dramatic music continues]
[music fades]
- Now you're giving up, huh?!
- [woman] Poor guy.
Why do you feel sorry for him?
That's how it should be.
His brother Edong is
a criminal. People like Edong
- deserve to die.
- You're the murderers! You!
[man] I agree.
If they bring in Edong alive,
he might escape again
and come back here to kill more people.
The police did the right thing.
[Lucas] You're the murderers! Murderers!
[pensive music playing]
[pensive music continues]
They said the search is still ongoing.
But…
[music fades]
they're reducing
the size of the search party.
Expect that by day five or day seven,
they'll issue a statement
that they're halting
their search for Edong
until they receive new information.
[distant traffic noise]
If you need anything,
you have our number.
[ominous music playing]
[ominous music continues]
- [music fades]
- [crickets chirping]
Love?
[foreboding music playing]
[door creaks]
[foreboding music continues]
[engine rumbles, stops]
[phone buzzing]
"LOVE"
- [buzzing continues]
- [foreboding music continues]
[buzzing ends]
- [crickets chirping]
- [foreboding music continues]
[panicked breaths]
[glass shatters]
[foreboding music intensifies]
[foreboding music continues]
[metal rattling]
[music becomes sinister]
Why was he holding a bloody knife?
And who owns
the bloody clothes that were in his bag?!
- Ah!
- I couldn't save Louisa then,
and I couldn't save Edong now.
You did everything you could.
Tell that to Lucas.
Do you still have feelings for him?
Edong!
Sir, Ma'am Mel just
left a condo in Manila.
- What are you doing here?
- I was worried about you.
You know how I feel about you.
Find out who she met with.