[Angelo] You really think I killed Louisa?
I didn't kill Louisa!
All our time together,
you thought I killed someone?
You married me, Liezel.
I can't believe Louisa had a secret life
we knew nothing about.
[Alice] She went through so much.
Why didn't she tell us?
We could've helped her.
I'm Bianca Seropon. The missing student.
It was my decision to leave Amurao.
I heard about
the accusations against Miss Liezel.
Beth, who were you protecting
when you hid
your suspicions about Angelo from us?
I didn't say anything
because I wanted to be sure!
But you know I was
looking for answers too!
Do you know how scared
Chloe was for you when she called me?
Ma!
- I'm sorry. I have to go.
- Where?
Hey, Alice!
[drums thumping]
[cheerleaders chanting indistinctly]
[whistling "Sabay Sabay Tayo"]
[whistling continues]
[ominous music playing]
- [hiphop music playing]
- [dancer] One, two, three, four.
[whistling continues]
[ominous music continues]
[car horns honking]
[theme music playing]
[Joshua]
So, it was just a misunderstanding?
You didn't attack Miss Beth, Papa?
No, son.
I didn't hurt anyone.
Even adults can have misunderstandings.
[Liezel] We're like that, too.
Sometimes,
our emotions get the best of us.
What about Bianca?
Uh…
It's true that I knew
about Bianca's disappearance.
But I kept it a secret to protect her.
I was just helping her.
And Bianca texted me, saying that
she's at the police
station to give a statement.
[Joshua sighs]
I was so scared.
My classmates kept making up stories.
And you were even fighting.
But… It's okay now.
You two are okay.
Everything's okay now, right?
[somber music playing]
Everything will be okay, son.
Get some rest. We all had a long day.
Good night, Ma, Pa.
Pa, good night.
[somber music continues]
Go on, go to sleep.
Mm. There we go.
[somber music continues]
[beer bottle thuds]
[music fades]
[door closes]
My hoodie…
I went back for it the next day…
but it was gone.
[unsettling music playing]
[unsettling music continues]
- [Liezel] I took it.
- [music fades]
And then I threw it away.
To protect you.
[Angelo breathes deeply]
So, you thought I killed Louisa, but…
you still chose to protect me?
[sniffles] I thought that if--
if you did that, then it was my fault.
Because I deceived you.
Because I hurt you.
And I thought that when,
when you found out about me and Louisa,
your anger…
made you kill her.
[morose music playing]
I couldn't do anything to protect Louisa.
But now, I can protect you.
Ah. So you felt guilty?
- That's why you married me?
- No!
[stammers] Yes.
Yes, I feel guilty but…
It's not just because of what happened.
I love you, Angelo.
[sniffles] And that never changed.
It's not the same as
the love I had for Louisa, but…
But I love you.
[Angelo sighs heavily]
It's what I held on to.
And it's still what I'm holding on to now.
[morose music continues]
S-- Sorry… [sniffling] Sorry…
Sorry.
Sorry for the lies.
Sorry for the secrets.
[morose music continues]
I'm sorry I was scared of you.
You kept all of that from me.
I kept what I knew about you and Louisa.
Why didn't you tell me?
Because I'm scared, Liezel.
[music becomes somber]
I'm scared to hear directly
from you what I already know.
No matter what I do,
you will never love me
as much as you loved Louisa.
[sniffles]
I don't know what I'll do
if I hear it directly from you.
I might just lose my mind.
I don't know what I'll do.
I won't be able to handle it.
- [somber music continues]
- [both sniffling]
Is there a reason still?
[somber music continues]
For us to stay together, Liezel?
[both crying, sniffling]
[somber music continues, fades]
[cicadas chirping]
Hey. What's wrong?
I was worried after your call.
Are you okay?
Is Seth…
He's fine.
Okay… Um, then…
Wait, what's going on?
Why did you ask to meet?
I just…
I just watched
a couple fall apart… [sniffles]
because of things
they couldn't tell each other for years.
I couldn't help but think,
had they chosen to trust each other,
to talk about it,
maybe it wouldn't have destroyed them.
They wouldn't be
hurting for so much, for so long.
And I…
I realized, Scott…
That's what I've been doing to you.
And I… I don't wanna do that anymore.
Alice--
I said… I said I'd figure things out.
And, no, no,
I have not. Not completely but…
I realized…
[sighs] I don't wanna do
this alone anymore, Scott.
[hopeful music playing]
I am choosing to trust you.
Because after everything,
I still love you and…
And I still do. I still love you.
And… [cries]
[sniffles] I haven't stopped.
[hopeful music continues]
Please tell me I haven't lost you.
Please tell me you can still forgive me.
Please. I'm so sorry.
[breathing heavily]
I know I don't even
have the right to ask you.
I-- What I did is
just so horrible, it's…
I don't have the right to ask you
after everything I did.
Alice…
I still love you.
[crying]
[Scott] Come here.
[Scott] Shh…
I'm sorry, I… [sobbing]
I hope you can still forgive me.
I, I hurt you. I called you a monster.
- No. Hey, hey, hey.
- I took Seth away.
- It's okay. Shh, it's okay.
- [crying, breathing heavily]
We're gonna figure
things out together, okay?
[Alice sighs heavily]
You're choosing to trust me.
So trust me.
Trust me when I say
that this leap of faith, it's enough.
It's more than enough for me.
Okay?
[emotional music playing]
Yeah.
[music fades]
[woman] Where are you taking my husband?
Sir, have mercy, please.
He didn't do anything wrong.
Where are you taking him,
sir? [whimpering]
Mrs. Seropon,
you know what your husband did.
What did my daughter tell you?
Don't believe in Bianca. She's a liar.
What she's accusing him of isn't true.
Joey didn't do anything to her!
Your husband is a rapist, Ma!
[crying] He defiled me!
Why won't you believe me?!
Because you're a liar!
You want to ruin my
life and make me miserable!
Then why did you still look for me? [sobs]
You even made a story
out of my disappearance.
It wasn't because
you were worried for me, right?
You just didn't want
everyone to know the truth.
[sullen music playing]
You even blamed Miss Liezel.
You don't care if someone's life
gets ruined as long
as it isn't your husband's!
You take that back!
Drop your complaint if
you want to come back to this house!
Do you understand?
I'll forget I even had a daughter!
Do whatever you want, it's your life.
As long as we understand each other.
Once you walk out that door,
don't expect anything from me anymore.
[dramatic music playing, swells]
[music fades]
[Beth] Chloe.
Did you hear us in the hospital?
[refrigerator closes]
[sighs]
You don't want to tell the police.
That's why Papa said
to tell Attorney Erica instead.
- [morose music playing]
- But…
You don't want to either.
What's going to happen now?
[Ryan] Chloe.
Don't worry about it. It's fine now.
Your Uncle Angelo didn't hurt your mother.
And he had nothing
to do with Louisa either.
Yes! I was worried about Joshua.
- I'll text him right now.
- [Beth] Mm-hmm.
[morose music continues]
[sighs]
Chloe.
Why did you have to call…
your Aunt Erica?
We could have handled it on our own.
I didn't want
to make a big deal out of this.
Ma.
I was scared for you.
You could get hurt again.
I tried calling Aunt Mel,
but I couldn't get in touch with her.
I know you don't get along,
but I was desperate, Ma.
[somber music playing]
Are you mad at me, Ma?
Don't get mad, please!
[somber music continues]
- [smooches]
- I'm not angry, Chloe.
And I understand why you did it.
[somber music continues]
[music fades]
[upbeat music playing]
[indistinct chattering]
Enjoy your food.
[Marco] I spoke to Loquere.
He confirmed Angelo's statements.
On Louisa's time of death,
Angelo was involved in
a fight in a different neighborhood.
The police arrived
to arrest everyone fighting,
but Angelo had already escaped.
The next day,
Angelo arrived at the station with his dad
to file an incident report.
I've made a request.
And if his statements match,
he will no longer be
a suspect in Louisa's case.
Now that Bianca's back,
her case has been dismissed, too.
[upbeat music continues]
He'll also be cleared of sending
the text messages Beth received.
"THIS IS BETH. MEET ME AT
OUR OLD HANGOUT SPOT IN THE FOREST."
Whoever the killer is,
he knew Liezel and Beth
were at odds because of Bianca.
He texted Beth and Angelo
because he wanted them to fight.
He wanted them to hurt each other.
Are you sure
Louisa's killer was behind it?
[sinister music playing]
[Erica] Whoever he is,
we know how twisted his mind is.
What he's capable of.
[sinister music continues]
- [traffic noises]
- [sinister music continues]
Do you have…
other persons of
interest in Louisa's case?
[Erica sighs]
We always end up back
to square one in this case.
[music fades]
But this just shows there's a lot
we still don't know
about what happened to Louisa.
[whistling "Sabay Sabay Tayo"]
- [foreboding music playing]
- [whistling continues]
- [foreboding music intensifies]
[Mel] I thought once Edong dies,
we won't go through
these crazy things anymore.
But here we are again.
- [woman] Who hurt you?
- No--
I know you have problems.
They wouldn't shoot you for no reason.
You can stay here
until you can stand on your own
and you know where to go.
You escaped from prison?
You killed a lot of people?
I'm only killing those who deserve it.
There are people who deserve to be killed?
Four more.
Just four left. My mission continues.
[Erica] Be careful, okay?
Louisa's killer hasn't been found yet.
I'm sure he's just around. Watching.
[cackles]