[Isla] Your husband's there?
I don't know what to do anymore.
[eerie music playing]
Alice, oh my god.
This is private property!
- What the…
- Oh my gosh!
- [Alice grunts]
- [young Alice crying]
When you were five, and you went missing,
you mentioned something
about two trees facing each other.
Mama….
This is where they found
you when you went missing.
[Beth] Alice is not going with you.
I would have already
reported you to the police,
and you should have
a restraining order by now!
[Scott] You said that one day,
it'll be my turn to save you.
So if saving you now means stepping back
and letting you figure
things out, then I'll wait, Alice.
And I'll keep waiting
until you realize that I'm still me.
And we're still us.
[theme music playing]
[unsettling music playing]
[breathing heavily]
[grunts]
- [Scott] Alice.
- [Alice sighs deeply]
[unsettling music continues]
[Scott] Remember when we first met?
I was panicking.
But you calmed me down.
I tried to hide it,
but… you saw through me.
You saved me.
- [upbeat music playing]
- [traffic noises]
[elevator dings]
[Scott] Hold on! Agh.
Sorry.
[elevator dings]
[music fades]
[elevator whooshing]
[elevator thuds]
[Alice] Oh!
Oh.
Are we s-stuck?
Looks like it. Wait, I'll just call.
- [Alice clears throat]
- [woman on PA] Yes, hello?
Um, yes. Hi. We're stuck in the elevator.
Can someone please check?
[woman on PA]
We see you, ma'am. Sit tight.
We're dispatching a team.
Please remain calm.
Okay.
- [Scott whispering] Shit. Shit. Fuck.
- [Alice sighs]
[Scott inhaling sharply]
[tense music playing]
[Scott breathing heavily] Oh, fuck.
[music fades]
[Scott breathing heavily]
Are you okay?
[Scott inhaling sharply]
I'm great, yeah. Just great.
[Scott breathing shakily]
I'm sorry. I'm obviously not.
Claustrophobic, I guess.
"I guess"? So you-- you didn't know?
Not until now.
[inhales sharply]
I got trapped in one of these
when I was a kid.
Lights off for hours and hours.
I just didn't realize
it got stuck with me.
- [Scott exhales sharply]
- Now you know.
[Scott sighing deeply] Yeah.
[labored breathing]
[huffs]
[objects clattering]
[Alice] Here. Hold this.
Hold it.
Come on.
[light-hearted music playing]
Okay, so now, you close your eyes,
squeeze it,
and hold your breath for five seconds,
and then let go.
[light-hearted music continues]
[exhales sharply, chuckles softly]
How'd you know about that?
[chuckles softly]
I- I used to be afraid of the dark.
I am afraid of the dark.
And, um…
My dad taught me that trick.
Really helps when
things feel out of control.
[light-hearted music continues]
[Scott grunts, exhales sharply]
You're a life saver, you know?
I owe you one.
It's alright.
You'll have your time to save me.
Is that your way of asking me out?
[scoffs]
Are you seriously hitting on me
while we're stuck in an elevator?
[Scott chuckles] Okay.
Bad form. I give you that.
But how about once we're…
…rescued? Maybe?
Once we're rescued,
we can renegotiate.
[music becomes pensive]
[Scott] Deal.
- [sobbing]
- [pensive music continues]
- About"Bana"…
- [music fades]
There are no new developments yet.
[exhales]
These are the other files
on the missing beauty queens.
I need your help here.
I've already filed a Court
petition for habeas corpus.
And I told them to act on it immediately.
That's permissible under
section 6 of rule 102 due to the urgency.
- What did PBI say?
- They'll open the case.
They've been interested in
Laurence Kyo for a long time.
Because of drugs.
But they couldn't go after him
because he has a lot of connections.
But if we prove
that he has something to do
with the missing beauty queens,
that will break his protection.
[unsettling music playing]
[unsettling music continues]
[camera clicks]
- [music fades]
- [knocking on door]
What's up, dude?
Dude!
So, what's the plan?
Are you giving that to the police?
You'll admit
that your businesses are fronts
for my dad's money laundering scheme?
If you do that,
you're going down with him.
Are you trying to ruin your life?
Isn't it already ruined?
And you think he's
gonna let you get away with this?!
He's going to kill
you before you even testify!
[thuds]
Get out!
Leave!
[phone thuds]
[suspenseful music playing]
I think my dad did that.
"LOST BEAUCONERAS: MORE
BEAUTY QUEENS REPORTED MISSING"
You want to bring him down?
Don't drag yourself down with him.
That.
That's what you'll use.
[suspenseful music continues]
[music fades]
I'll call you.
Thank you.
I talked to your sister earlier.
[pensive music playing]
You're the guy who knows my sister, right?
Yeah.
[music fades]
Could you…
tell Erica that I'm sorry?
I'd like to apologize
for what I said last time I saw here.
And…
She's right.
Now I know the truth.
Do you think…
she'd like to be a part of our family?
[somber music continues]
[sighs]
Your sister is complicated.
She's hard to read.
She's used to being alone.
She's not used to
letting people into her life.
Even you?
[somber music continues]
Even me.
[sighs]
As I said before,
our ties end there.
The end.
I don't want to reconnect.
Your sister seems nice.
She's not like your mother.
She had nothing to do with that.
Are you going to punish her for that, too?
[young Erica] My father left you.
Blame him, not me.
Why would you punish me, too?
[Annette] You look just like him.
[somber music continues]
Do you know why I like working with you?
Because your life, is your business.
And my life is my own.
It's none of your concern.
[somber music continues]
It's sad to be alone.
Don't you feel lonely?
I'm used to it.
No one gets used to loneliness.
People who say that
aren't telling the truth.
[music becomes sullen]
[exhales heavily]
[music becomes uneasy]
[uneasy music continues]
- [flashlight clicks open]
- [Ryan squeals]
Chloe! What are you doing?
You'll give me a heart attack!
Why are you still awake?
Pa…
Why does Mama think Aunt Liezel
is involved with Bianca's disappearance?
Chloe, people just
made up stories about it.
It's all just gossip.
But Joshua's anger is real.
He won't talk to me, either.
- [sighs]
- So…
Did something happen?
Pa…
You know something, don't you?
You just won't tell me.
It's so hard living with
two investigative journalists.
Pa.
Chloe.
Let the adults deal
with the problem, okay?
But how will I fix things with Joshua?
[sighs] I don't even know the truth.
Chloe.
Can't you act like a kid for once?
There are other things to think about.
Think about your crush.
Wait, not that.
Come on, go to bed. You have school later.
And next time, turn on the lights.
You nearly gave me a heart attack.
- [huffs]
- [inaudible mumbling]
[unsettling music playing]
[unsettling music continues, fades]
[crickets chirping]
[tense music playing]
[tense music continues]
- [leaves rustling]
- [music fades]
[unsettling music playing]
[unsettling music continues]
[music becomes foreboding]
[leaves rustling]
[latch clicks]
[knives clinking]
[case closes]
[sinister music sting]
[foreboding music resumes]
[foreboding music continues]
- [knives whooshing]
- [gasps]
[suspenseful music sting]
[suspenseful music playing]
[suspenseful music continues]
[suspenseful music fades]
[ominous music playing]
[ticking]
[ominous music continues]
- [knife whooshes]
- [heartbeat thumping]
- [clock ticks]
- [knife whooshes]
[heartbeat thumping]
- [clock ticks]
- [knife whooshes]
[heartbeat thumping]
- [birds chirping]
- [music fades]
[flapping, chirping]
[leaves scraping]
[birds chirping, flapping]
You don't think I'm
that kind of person, do you?
Like what Alice said?
It wasn't you, right?
The Louisa in my dream.
Aren't we the same, Louisa?
We do what needs
to be done even if it's hard.
[wind blowing]
[unsettling music playing]
[unsettling music continues]
[footstep thuds]
[suspenseful music sting, fades]
[uneasy music playing]
Oh! [chuckles nervously]
Eat some more. Here you go.
Finish it, alright?
[uneasy music continues]
Ma, are you okay?
[chuckles softly] Of course!
Where's Papa?
Uhh…
He left early.
He just went somewhere.
Go on. Dig in.
[foreboding music playing]
[ominous music intensifies]
[footsteps approaching]
- [ominous music continues]
- [footsteps approaching]
[music fades]
[thuds]
Mrs. Mora, did you recognize
the person who did this to you?
I only saw that they were
wearing black rubber shoes.
Who would do this?
Who holds a grudge against you?
The list is very long.
You don't think Scott
did this to you, do you?
You were kind of hard on him last time.
- Scott?
- If your speculations are right about him
then most probably
he's capable of doing this too.
Angelo, come out!
Were you the one who beat my wife up?!
Why are you accusing him of
attacking you without any proof?
You have your suspicions
about your husband, too.