♪You wake up from the shadow♪
♪Jump onto the stage♪
♪Walk through the city neon♪
♪Stand out of the border♪
♪Time flies by♪
♪Joys and sorrows success or failure♪
♪At one place of the world once♪
♪The first ray of sunlight♪
♪Break through barriers of the night♪
♪Make my most beloved dream into shapes♪
♪Glory or quiet
There is the direction in the mind♪
♪Like a sunlight♪
♪In full bloom in the night sky♪
♪Not alone any longer
Stumbling along in confusion♪
♪No matter how
Break through bravely with a free hand♪
♪It’s the dream of love
Already lightened by you♪
=Go Go Squid 2: Dt. Appledog’s Time=
=Episode 36=
This...
Excuse me,
I didn’t mean to disrupt you.
It’s just Mr. Xiang said that
everyone back home is celebrating.
If we fail to interview you,
then there’s no need for us to go back.
We were about to interview you.
Can you say something briefly, Wu Bai?
I know you don’t like to
talk to the media.
It’s gonna be very fast.
Come! Come!
Here! Here!
OK.
Here, cameraman.
Dear audience,
now I’m at the backstage area
of Chicago Stadium
with the captain of our
champion team Wu Bai.
So, Wu Bai,
what do you want to say to your fans
and the audience?
Thank you.
Wonderful!
Anything else?
Thanks again, everyone!
What a wonderful speech!
Wonderful!
OK.
And now,
let’s listen to the K&K TEAM.
Come.
Come here.
Five energetic boys.
The last round
was very intense.
When we were watching...
You still remember
-Were you nervous?
-the AMC competition?
Very nervous.
Of course I remember.
We won the championship together.
But now,
I’ve retired.
You made a comeback.
And he
succeeded.
Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you.
Let’s go.
Coach,
we performed so well today.
Should you reward us with something?
Right!
You have to treat us to a meal!
Am I right, guys?
Of course!
Right!
I’ve already prepared a
celebration banquet for you.
Come back with me
to the K&K headquarters,
you can eat and drink your fill!
Till you’re drunk!
I want to eat pickled fish.
How about we
slip away?
Order whatever you like.
You can order anything.
Great!
We must eat and drink our fill!
Am I right, guys?
Yes!
That’s for sure!
The celebration banquet is ready!
What do you want to eat?
I owe you nothing.
Stop chatting, guys.
Let’s go!
-Go! Go!
-Let’s go!
Where’s Wu Bai?
Where’s Ai Qing?
I’ll give the coach a call.
No need.
There’s no need.
Let’s go. Let’s go.
Should I
hold back this time?
You sure?
I won last time.
Probably not this time.
Let’s see.
Lady first.
You held back
back in Singapore, right?
I didn’t.
Really?
I don’t believe you anymore.
After I learned what Assisting Genius
revealed about you,
I felt that I shouldn’t believe
everything you say.
I did pull some tricks
when I chased you.
But I really
did my best that time.
Because of your eyes?
After that match,
I received surgery.
And then,
you disappeared for three years.
When I was in the ward,
I always wanted to call you
and hear your voice.
But I knew
I wouldn’t be able to
promise you a happy life
even if I found you.
So I thought
when my eyes heal,
I must go look for you.
But what if
we didn’t meet...
What if
you failed to find me...
What if...
There’re no what ifs.
You so sure?
Then my eyes healed.
I thought
I should go to you
after I make some achievements.
No wonder you said
you wanted to win 300 competitions
to earn a chance to start over with me.
I haven’t yet told you
why it had to be 300 wins.
Why then?
Because Solo
had reaped 299 wins.
So I thought I must
win more times than him
to become qualified to profess my love.
But there were not many
robot fighting competitions
in our country,
so I forced myself to take part
in over 200 competitions abroad
before I came back.
People said you’re a little genius.
But how come I suddenly feel
you’re very stupid?
In fact, I also regret it.
Regret what?
I regret not coming back earlier
on that day you rejected me.
Now come to think of it,
if I come back earlier,
probably we’d have already got married.
Yes.
Rest early after you go back.
Good night.
Bye.
See you tomorrow.
What’s wrong?
I want to stay with you.
What are you thinking?
Nothing,
but you.
Why is your heart
beating so fast?
Now you know why.
Did you sleep well?
Why are you looking at me like this?
I thought I couldn’t
take my eyes off you.
I haven’t washed my face yet.
I don’t look good now.
You’re always beautiful.
I’ve already prepared the breakfast.
Get up and eat.
You got up so early
to prepare this?
Hurry and eat.
You must be very hungry.
Eat up.
Let’s eat together.
Eat this.
Yum.
Did you catch a cold, Bai?
I’m fine.
It’s not serious.
I happen
to have brought some cold granules.
I’ll mix some with water.
Hello, Mom.
Bai,
I watched the live broadcast yesterday.
I knew you were celebrating last night
so I didn’t dare to disrupt you.
How was it?
You won the championship.
Was your girlfriend happy?
Did you celebrate it together?
Yes, we did.
Mom,
I want to get married.
Really? You’ve decided?
Did she agree?
Great!
We’ll book flight tickets right away.
See you the day after tomorrow.
OK.
My parents will come back
the day after tomorrow.
The day after tomorrow?
I said I wanted to get married.
Then they decided to
come back right away.
Have some water.
It’s hot.
This is too fast!
The day after tomorrow?
So sudden!
Don’t make a fuss.
No.
I’ll ask my mom
to come to Shanghai, too.
You should pick another time.
Why would I?
Ai Jing is the elder sister.
I should meet her family first.
And then it’s Wu Bai's turn.
As his future brother-in-law,
I can’t fall behind.
Hello, Mom.
Yes, we won.
That’s not the point.
The point is,
I’ll book you a flight ticket now.
You should come to Shanghai
tomorrow morning
and meet Ai Jing’s father.
It’s indeed very sudden.
I didn’t expect it, too.
Things don’t always go as we expected.
You two are really interesting.
I’m still single.
But you’re going to meet
your father-in-law.
You should
work hard.
I’d better
play video games.
Oh man!
Come on.
Why are you still playing games?
Pack your things.
Easy. We still have time.
Hurry. We’ll leave
after you pack your things.
Move!
Oh man!
Tomorrow?
Yes, tomorrow.
Shen Zhe’s mother will arrive
in the morning.
Wu Bai’s parents will arrive
in the afternoon.
Why the rush?
I’m not eager,
but Wu Bai is very eager.
He wants to marry my sister right away.
Make dinner yourselves.
Dad, where are you going?
I’ll go buy some clothes.
I must look very decent.
Dad is even more
nervous than us.
Mom, listen to me,
you can’t bully Ai Jing again
when you see her today.
If I can’t be with Ai Jing,
I’ll jump down, you see,
from here!
I know.
Did I treat her badly
in the hospital last time?
Let’s not talk about the last time.
What I want to say is
Ai Jing really is
a very, very nice girl.
In terms of appearance, character
educational background,
and socializing skills,
she’s indeed
much better than you.
It’s just
she’s a bit too old.
Mom, I...
Could you please not always say things
I don’t want to hear?
I just like it this way.
Ai Jing’s three years older than me.
It’s perfect for me.
It’s a blessing to have an older wife.
My wife is older than me.
She knows how to
handle things better than me.
Sir,
we’re like-minded.
You heard that?
Ai Jing really is very nice.
You see?
Every time she scolded me,
I felt very convinced
and very comfortable.
Besides,
she’s mature and charming, right?
She’s an opera actress.
I know.
Then promise me, don’t bully her today.
So fussy.
Promise me you won’t bully her.
Swear it.
Swear what?
I’ll feel relieved then.
Is this the same outfit
you tried on last time
when we went shopping?
Yes.
I bought it on Vipshop.
It’s cheaper than in the mall.
It looks
very good on you.
This is a very formal occasion.
Dad, you ready?
One second. I’m ready.
Coming.
You can’t even walk now, Dad?
How do I look?
How do you think?
Very handsome!
How about this?
Turn around.
Except that
your belly is bigger, Dad.
This... This...
Dad,
they’re paying a visit.
Why are you so nervous?
How can I not feel nervous?
I have to meet two families in one day.
You do know how to torture me.
It’s not my fault, Dad.
Wu Bai arranged it.
It’s not my fault either.
Shen Zhe didn’t want to fall behind.
How can you...
Um...
When will Wu Bai’s parents arrive?
This afternoon.
We’ll go to Grandpa’s place first
to meet them.
OK. Ai Qing,
I’ll leave you alone then.
Your sister...
Let’s leave right away!
OK, let’s go!
-Let’s go!
-Let’s go! Go! Go!
Go for it! Go for it!
You shouldn’t have left in such a hurry.
Coming!
What did you forget?
Bai?
Didn’t you say
you’d come this afternoon?
I was afraid I may be late,
so I came early.
Come on in.
No one’s at home.
My dad and sister just went out.
You came at the right time.
Hurry. Hurry.
Help me pick an outfit.
Bai, Bai,
help me take a look.
Which one looks better?
What type do your parents like?
Long sleeves, short sleeves,
or sleeveless?
Dark color, or light color?
You can wear whichever you like.
No.
This is my first meeting with them.
I have to make them feel
I take this meeting very seriously.
You remember when you
went to see my grandpa last time?
You also asked me
to pick clothes for you.
But it’s different this time.
This is the first time
I’m going to meet your mother.
I can’t let her think
I have a bad taste in clothes.
Actually,
they saw you long ago.
They saw me long ago?
When?
The walls of my room
are full of posters and photos of you.
So they knew you long ago.
It’s still different.
They haven’t seen me in the flesh.
Don’t worry.
My parents
grew up together.
They’re each other’s first love.
So they’re very happy
that I’m marrying my first love.
Then,
this one.
Be happy.
Dad, Mom, Grandpa.
They’re here.
Ai Qing!
Hurry! Come here!
Grandpa!
I finally got to see you, Ai Qing!
Hello, Auntie.
Good.
This is our future daughter-in-law.
Don’t be so grim.
Hello, Uncle.
Hello, Ai Qing.
Ai Qing,
come chat with me.
-No, no, no!
-Come!
Ai Qing, chat with me!
Hurry! Hurry!
I haven’t seen you for a long time.
Come.
Now,
you and Bai,
and Han Shangyan and Nian
can get married on the same day.
You have to get prepared.
Did Bai propose to you?
Bai,
making a proposal is very important.
A girl will only be
proposed to once in a lifetime.
You should do it
in the most romantic way.
I already did that.
You already...
Grandpa, Bai already proposed to me.
Then...
Are you satisfied?
Yes.
That’s great. That’s great.
This is a very important matter.
It’s great you’ve done it.
Bai,
I heard Shen Zhe’s parents are coming?
Yes.
They’ll have lunch
with Ai Qing’s sister.
Wouldn’t it seem we fall behind
and are not proactive this way?
It’s not good.
I don’t think so.
There has to be an order.
It’s natural that they met
Ai Qing’s elder sister first.
Then we must
meet each other
more often in the future.
Sure. Sure.
Come visit us when you have time.
You’ll be in good health
if you’re in a good mood.
Right. Right.
Come to Guangzhou when you have time.
We can have morning tea together.
Will do.
Jing,
I got you wrong before.
Don’t take it to heart.
Not at all, Auntie.
Don’t think like that.
Alright.
Uncle, we’re leaving then.
See you next time.
OK. OK.
Take care.
OK. I’m off then. Bye.
Let me see you off, Auntie.
Sure.
Let’s go.
Take care.
Mom, I want to say something to Ai Jing.
Bye.
Come with me.
What?
What are you doing?
Now that you’ve met my mother.
Shouldn’t you reward me with something?
My dad and your mom are here.
I’ll come see you tonight.
Don’t say you don’t have time.
I have time.
My dad will meet
Wu Bai’s parents tonight.
I don’t want to go.
OK then.
See you tonight.
Uncle, I’m leaving.
I’ll visit you next time.
See you.
Take care of your mom.
OK.
Shen Zhe’s mother is a bit traditional.
And you’re hot tempered.
I’m afraid you’ll quarrel
with each other again.
You must get ready for that.
You should give in to her, you know?
OK, Dad. I won’t be like her.
Mind your words.
Bai’s parents should have arrived.
There’s enough time.
You can walk there.
No, it’s very urgent.
I need to change my clothes.
Change your clothes?
Aren’t you wearing a suit?
I bought two suits
for each of the meeting.
Hurry.
Hail a cab for me.
I’ll go change my clothes.
OK.
Dad, slow down.
OK. I know.
It’s so close. It’s hard to hail a cab.
How do I look?
Didn’t you change your clothes?
I did.
You did?
You bought two suits, right?
Right.
Two same suits.
Completely the same.
How do you think?
I’m not partial
to either of you.
Did you get a cab?
Yes. It’s downstairs.
I’ve got to go then.
Cheer up!
What’s that cheering?
Please enjoy.
OK. Thank you.
Grandpa, nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
Let me introduce you.
This is my son-in-law.
-Hello.
Nice to meet you.
This is my daughter.
Hello.
Let’s sit down and chat.
OK?
Please.
Grandpa, this way.
OK. OK.
Grandpa, sit here.
OK. OK. Here.
Sit here. Sit.
Here. Sit.
Sit down, please.
Bai.
Grandpa.
OK. OK.
This kid’s very polite.
This...
Thank you, thank you.
Well,
we’ve never
gone to a similar occasion.
We’re not experienced.
Please forgive us if we’re being
inconsiderate.
You’re too polite.
Don’t think like that.
They like each other
and want to get married.
Then they can go ahead and do it.
We can sit together,
chat and eat together,
and then we’ll become family.
Right. Right.
We want to buy a house for them.
Mom, I’ll buy it myself.
We can buy one ourselves.
How big a house do you want?
You should take your kids
into consideration.
Right. Right.
It’s very important.
They’ve decided.
They’ll have a boy and a girl.
Let’s talk about the marriage first.
Let’s do it step by step.
Right! Right!
It takes time.
Actually,
Wu Bai’s mom
wanted to give Wu Bai a gift.
But he wouldn’t accept it.
We’ve taught
Wu Bai to be independent
since he was a kid.
He’d get paid for doing housework,
which would become his pocket money.
So Wu Bai
has been very independent.
Wu Bai’s obviously
very well educated.
Your childhood was so miserable?
Not too bad.
I’m used to it.
You should keep up this
good habit of yours
after we get married.
What good habit?
Doing housework.
If you like,
I can do it every day.
Pinky swear.
I can finally stay with you
alone for a while.
Didn’t we just meet in the morning?
It’s different.
We were not alone in the morning.
It didn’t count.
How do you like my performance?
So-so.
How can you call it so-so?
My performance was obviously
perfect.
Since you already knew, why ask me?
It’s because
I wanted to hear you say it.
Should we speed up a bit as well?
Speed up what?
Getting married.
Wu Bai and Ai Qing are getting married.
What are we waiting for?
Wu Bai has chased my sister
for ten years.
So what if it’s 10 years?
I can chase you for ten years,
twenty and thirty years.
I can chase you after we get married.
How many candies did you eat today?
You’re so sweet.
You want me to agree
by saying some sweet words?
You got me wrong.
Honey,
my love for you is witnessed
by the sun and moon.
How can you say I’m hoaxing you?
You’re shameless.
I am, so what?
Not enough.
Still not enough.
Shouldn’t you go home now?
My dad will be back soon.
It doesn’t matter.
So he can be our witness.
Grandpa, slow.
Do you like the food?
Yes. Very good.
We need to talk about the house again.
Grandpa, you’re the eldest.
I’ll pay you a visit
personally another day.
I’ll be waiting for you.
OK.
Ai Qing.
Grandpa.
Come visit me when you have time.
Don’t worry, I will.
OK. OK.
Dad, get in the car.
Get in. Get in.
Let me help Grandpa.
Here. Let me help Grandpa.
See you.
OK.
See you, Ai Qing.
-Bye, Uncle.
-Bye.
Call me when you get back home.
Go now.
See you, Grandpa.
See you, Uncle.
Bye, uncle.
Goodbye.
See you.
Goodbye, Uncle, Auntie.
I’ve finally completed
this important mission.
Two tasks in one day.
Thank you, Dad.
Wu Bai is a nice kid.
You should cherish him.
Don’t bully him.
When did I bully him?
OK, let’s go home.
Let’s go.
Nice.
What are you playing?
What should I do now?
It’s so easy, Dad.
Just move it down.
Brilliant! Brilliant!
I won! I won!
I...
I thought about it all night.
How about
you get married together?
I’m not in a hurry.
You’re not in a hurry?
You’re one year older than Ai Jing.
But you’re not in a hurry?
I want to observe him for two years.
Right.
Shen Zhe
doesn’t seem as reliable as Wu Bai.
Let’s wait.
Dad,
Shen Zhe taught you
how to play this game.
Didn’t you say
you wanted to observe him?
Can’t I talk ill of him?
What about you?
How about you get married first?
I...
I think...
You see, we just met Bai’s parents.
Let’s take it slow.
Take it slow?
Bai’s parents,
especially his grandpa,
attach great importance to this.
How can you take it slow?
You must be quick!
Listen, Bai!
You’ll hold your
wedding ceremonies together!
In next month!
Next month?
What? You not happy?
No. Of course not.
Grandpa said
we should get married next month.
I’ll tell you face to face.
I wanted to wait
till your next birthday.
But Grandpa said so,
and he happens to be in China.
Let’s do it then.
So I’ll feel secure.
We have obtained the marriage license.
What are you feeling insecure about?
I feel insecure because
we’re not living together.
Bai, come on in.
Uncle.
Bai, come and sit.
Eat hawthorn balls.
Dad, give him a few minutes.
I need to talk with him.
You can eat first.
You just said
we’re getting married next month.
But,
are we moving too fast?
I’m not ready for it yet.
Grandpa said
we can get married on the National Day.
But,
we haven’t obtained
the marriage license yet.
I’ve brought the documents.
Let’s do it in a bit.
In a bit?
I checked.
They’re working today.
Let me take a look.
Dad, what are you doing?
Your sister is suspicious.
What is she plotting?
Dad!
How come this door is moving!
This door...
Um...
Bai and I will
get our marriage license later.
The marriage license?
Dad, what are you looking for?
You’ll need the household register.
Take it.
(Household Register)
Dad,
you carry the household register
with you all the time?
I prepared it after I met Bai’s parents
last time.
Thank you, Uncle.
Others don’t want to
marry their daughters off.
But look at you.
You can’t wait to marry us off.
That’s because Bai is excellent.
I wouldn’t do it
if it were another person.
Bai,
after getting married,
you’ll have
a whole new life to live.
Are you ready?
Uncle,
I’ve been preparing it for ten years.
Don’t worry.
OK.
I’ll entrust you with her then.
You really are ready?
I’ve been thinking about it
for a long time.
Let’s go.
(Civil Affairs Bureau)
(Freely Register Your Marriage
According to the Law)
OK.
On my count.
Smile.
OK.
Three, two...
Sir!
Again!
OK. Let’s do it one more time.
Three, two...
Sir! Sir!
Bai,
what are you doing?
Aren’t I supposed to make a gesture?
Who told you that?
97.
Wu Bai! Wu Bai! Wu Bai!
Do you know?
Now the wedding photos
are shot differently from before.
You should make some gestures.
Don’t just stand there.
Really?
Listen to me.
You’d been abroad for many years.
And then you were busy with competitions
after you came back.
I’m sure you don’t know
the latest trends.
Listen, if you don’t know what to do,
you can make some gestures like these.
Right, show your love
for her.
Go for it!
Sorry.
One more time.
Let’s do it again.
Just put your hands here.
Three...
Smile.
Two...
One.
(Marriage Registration)
(Marriage License)
Oh no.
I forgot to tell Wu Bai
he needs to go to a photo studio
to take new style photos.
He can’t take these photos
in the Civil Affairs Bureau.
He should know, right?
I think he knows.
So we have
the marriage license now.
Right.
(License holder: Wu Bai)
Is it too late
if I say
I regret it?
Don’t even think about it.
Let’s go.
(Civil Affairs Bureau)
Who’s calling?
My Dad.
Hello, Dad.
Hey, Ai Qing.
How did it go?
We have the license now.
Great!
I’ll go home with Dad.
You just got the license.
You should spend some time together.
There’s no need.
I’ll go back to the club
after I send her back.
Why are you going back?
Aren’t you having a holiday?
Wu Bai, stay in our house.
Don’t stand on ceremony.
Right. Right.
I’ve cooked
a lot of food for you.
You should eat them up.
We’ll leave you alone then.
Then...
Leave them alone.
Right. Right.
Let’s go.
We’re home.
My dad cooked so many dishes.
He even prepared wine for us.
(Till you’re drunk)
Till you’re drunk.
♪If you can see in my eyes♪
♪You’re the stars
Shining above the clouds♪
♪If you can see in my eyes♪
♪There are dreams of sea
My heart leaps♪
♪I don’t need you to see♪
♪Crossing the dark tunnels♪
♪Drowned in the crowds♪
♪There’s a shy boy♪
♪Waiting for you to step on the stage♪
♪Looking at your profile♪
♪To exchange an oath♪
♪One day you’ll look forward to♪
♪Maybe you’ll be surprised♪
♪Maybe you’ll stay silent♪
♪It’s fine I’m here I understand you♪
♪Until the end of the night♪
♪Until there’s no guardian left♪
♪I want you to know I’m there♪
♪Never let go♪
♪Ai Ai
Conquer the borderless white dream♪
♪Endure the scattering loneliness♪
♪Ai Ai
Until I become the champion♪
♪The gold medal is for you♪
♪If you can see in my eyes♪
♪You’re the stars
Shining above the clouds♪
♪If you can see in my eyes♪
♪There are dreams of sea
My heart leaps♪
♪Drowned in the crowds♪
♪There’s a shy boy♪
♪Waiting for you to step on the stage♪
♪Looking at your profile♪
♪To exchange an oath♪
♪One day you’ll look forward to♪
♪Maybe you’ll be surprised♪
♪Maybe you’ll stay silent♪
♪It’s fine I’m here I understand you♪
♪Until the end of the night♪
♪Until there’s no guardian left♪
♪I want you to know I’m there♪
♪Never let go♪
♪Ai Ai
Conquer the borderless white dream♪
♪Endure the scattering loneliness♪
♪Ai Ai
Until I become the champion♪
♪The gold medal is for you♪