♪You wake up from the shadow♪
♪Jump onto the stage♪
♪Walk through the city neon♪
♪Stand out of the border♪
♪Time flies by♪
♪Joys and sorrows success or failure♪
♪At one place of the world once♪
♪The first ray of sunlight♪
♪Break through barriers of the night♪
♪Make my most beloved dream into shapes♪
♪Glory or quiet
There is the direction in the mind♪
♪Like a sunlight♪
♪In full bloom in the night sky♪
♪Not alone any longer
Stumbling along in confusion♪
♪No matter how
Break through bravely with a free hand♪
♪It’s the dream of love
Already lightened by you♪
=Go Go Squid 2 Dt. Appledog’s Time=
=Episode 11=
My daughters are so beautiful.
How can’t they get married?
What’s more,
your grandma said
she will arrange a blind date for you.
-Blind date?
I don’t need it.
With my great charm,
many people are attracted.
Ai Qing can go for the blind date.
No, I don’t.
I don’t need it. I’m charming, too.
-OK.
-Let her go.
I will eat that since you don’t need it.
She should lose weight.
Seriously, you need a blind date.
The meat is for me.
Dad, look at her.
You need to lose weight, Jing.
You lose weight. You.
(New Model)
Boss.
Morning.
Please hold on.
The store isn’t open yet.
It’s been a while.
Nice to see you.
You’ve been back for years.
But you never contact
any old friends.
Ai Qing told you I’m here?
Yes.
Tell me.
What’s up?
I won’t believe
boss of the biggest Robot Fighting club
will come to me for a talk
on the early morning of a working day.
Same as Ai Qing,
I’m here to invite you to come back.
Come on, my friend.
The positions of Captain and Mechanic
of SP Team I
are kept for you.
(Personnel Employment Contract)
Tell me,
when should I report for duty?
(I never mentioned Han Shangyan
and I are cousins. Sorry.)
So,
Ai Qing doesn’t know
your relationship with Han Shangyan?
Don’t peep.
All right.
We all know you like Ai Qing.
It’s not news.
What’s wrong?
You made an apology,
but she didn’t reply, right?
I can see it from your face.
Now,
listen.
When you are given
a cold shoulder,
draw back distance with her.
You should be at a distance with her.
Give her some time for thinking.
Understand?
No.
Ai Qing is not that kind of person who
doesn’t reply after reading the text.
There must be something happened.
So?
I’m going to find her.
You…
It won’t be that easy.
I’ve reminded you.
She’s leaving like that.
What a pity!
Now you are leaving.
I’m alone here.
I will come back to see you.
Don’t forget that.
Here you are.
It’s the project report I wrote for you.
Keep it well.
You are the best.
Thank you for your hard work
all these years.
Feel free to come back
at any time you want.
Thank you, boss.
You may take some time to go
to the youth training camp
to say goodbye.
They may cry if they know
you are leaving.
I don’t want to leave, either.
I will come back to help
when I have some time.
Of course, feel free to come back.
I’m really happy for you.
When you came to Jiayi three years ago,
I knew you would return
to the team some time or other.
After all,
your love for it cannot be hidden.
Good luck, Ai Qing.
Good luck.
Ai Qing.
Hey, Ai Qing.
I can’t believe you are so great.
You will be the coach of SP Team.
Maybe we’ll have a chance to cooperate.
I’ve done something to offend you
before in working.
Please forgive me.
Good luck!
See you then.
Sure.
Well.
The car has arrived.
Let me take you downstairs.
This is heavy.
I got it.
OK.
I’m leaving now.
See you, Boss.
See you.
See you all.
Ai Qing.
Tomorrow
will be better.
(Seeking for Dreams)
I used to think
dreams fade over time
and become ordinary daily life.
Now I see dreams are like seeds.
They hibernate but never die.
Thank you for giving me a forget-me-not.
I don’t know who you are.
But because of you,
I never feel lonely
on the way of chasing dreams.
♪There are dreams of sea
My heart leaps♪
Dt. What brings you here?
I’m Lin Shan.
Let’s go upstairs.
How about a cup of
hand ground black coffee?
Excuse me.
Is Ai Qing in there?
Ai Qing?
Unfortunately, she just
resigned.
Resigned?
You don’t know it?
I heard she’ll report for duty
at SP Team next week.
Dt.
Dt. Dt.
Is there any message for me
from Mr. Xiang?
Xiang…
No.
I’m leaving.
Dt. You…
Can you think about it?
What kind of hairstyle would you like?
Cut it.
Cutting your long hair
would be a shame, isn’t it?
Miss, you may look very beautiful
if you have a permanent wave style.
No, thanks.
Please cut it.
You want to cut your hair
because you are crossed in love?
Miss.
Don’t take things too hard.
You wanna put the past behind?
No.
I want to return to the past.
Cut it.
OK.
♪You wake up from the shadow♪
♪Jump onto the stage♪
♪Walk through the city neon♪
♪Stand out of the border♪
♪Time flies by♪
♪Joys and sorrows success or failure♪
♪Really exist at one place of the world♪
♪The first ray of sunlight♪
♪Break through barriers of the night♪
♪Make my most beloved
Dream into shapes♪
♪Glory or quiet
There is the direction in the mind♪
♪Like a sunlight♪
Some people always have dreams,
being full of zeal in lifetime.
She will never give up without winning
a world Champion or the grand slam,
or without putting the national flag
on the project she likes.
Ai Qing.
You are this kind of person.
♪The dream of love
already being lightened by you♪
I will take you to see a person.
Don’t make me lose face, you know?
Who is that, Boss?
You will know.
Here she is.
Hello, Doggie.
Haven’t seen you for a long time.
Finally you are here.
It’s been a while.
Oh, please let me introduce.
Fu Yiwen, a senior of SP.
Hi, Senior.
We’ve met in Guangzhou.
Do you remember it?
Please allow me introduce myself.
I’m Fu Yiwen, mechanic engineer of SP.
Hello.
Welcome to SP.
That’s enough.
Go training.
I’m leaving now, Boss.
See you, senior.
Bye-bye.
Solo is waiting for us.
I will take you there.
Let’s go.
This is the leisure area.
OK, I will contact you.
Please.
Excuse me.
I just had a phone call
so I couldn’t pick you up.
Boss.
You cut your hair.
Please sit down. I’ll take the contract.
OK.
Well, take a seat.
Sit down please.
It’s been ten years.
Many things happened.
Finally we become comrades in team.
It’s my honor.
Actually,
I’ve always thought
the name Baona is a girl’s name
before I know you.
Not strange.
Everyone said so.
Then why did you come up with this name?
When I
first worked in the industry,
I always made mistakes in the rush
and couldn’t find my toolkit.
So I shouted at the competition site
that “Where is my toolkit?”
In that case,
people gave me that name.
After some time,
I got used to it.
You used to be a player, too?
You don’t remember?
You can’t figure out who I am
even if you rack your brain.
I entered the circle in 2006
and retired in 2008.
China wasn’t developed
in robot fighting at that time.
I chose to take a back seat.
Your team appeared one year later.
So
you attracted capital to form SP Club,
and Solo was the first on your mind.
In the year
when Solo Team was dissolved,
I intended to sign a contract
with you, Solo
and Han Shangyan.
But it didn’t come true
at that time.
What are you talking about?
Please read the contract first.
(Ai Qing)
It’s OK.
You can start working today.
About the social security…
Wait a moment.
Why do you become silly
once you see Doggie?
The HR will be in charge
of social security.
OK. Let’s talk about working .
OK.
Please assign the work, Boss.
Don’t call me like that.
I can’t get used to it.
Maybe you have to get used to it.
We will work together for a long time.
Guys,
please continue your talk.
I have to go to the HR department.
Ai Qing.
I’m very pleased
you can join us.
It’s my pleasure
to join SP, too.
OK. See you.
I will leave.
OK.
Can
I take a look?
Of course.
Thank you, Solo.
Thank you for giving me the chance.
Not at all.
It’s because you have the ability.
All leaders agreed with that.
The hero has just woken up.
You’ll create a glorious future with us.
When did you become so literate?
I’m the boss now.
So I should learn some phatic talk.
Your short hair
reminds me of the time
when we competed together.
I cut it on purpose
to get back the feelings
of playing games before.
Boss, I’m leaving now
if it’s OK.
Ai Qing, there is one thing.
What is it?
What’s wrong?
I’d like you to do me a favor.
The coach of Team II
will be on maternity leave next month.
Do you mind training
both Team I and Team II together?
OK.
No problem.
Then that’s a deal.
I will take you around.
There is a big surprise
for you.
-Let’s go.
This is our robot developing area.
-Hi, Boss.
Take a look.
All these devices
are the top in the world.
Come on.
This way please.
The 3D printer
is the best model as well.
We will print 3D models
according to the drawings.
It’s more convenient than that
in those days.
-Hello.
This is our working area.
Really good conditions.
It’s really much better
than that of our time.
Yes.
I will take you to the R&D Department.
OK.
This way.
Hi, Boss.
-Morning.
-Hello, Boss.
This is
the R&D area for our robots.
Now it’s more subdivided.
For example, this is responsible
for R&D and upgrade of mecha.
That is for upgrading
remote control and drive.
Come on.
I’ll take you to our training hall.
OK.
We always have our basic training
and practice game here.
You upgraded it well.
You played well.
Actually I think
we can be faster.
It’s already very good.
I’d introduce you our team members.
Goddess?
-It’s you.
You are the new coach of SP?
You’re Wu Bai’s girlfriend.
Yes, I’m the new coach.
But...
I’m not Wu Bai’s girlfriend.
Is that so?
What a pity.
It seems Wu Bai really likes you anyway.
You knew each other before?
Lin Yin is Wu Bai’s friend.
We met before in Suzhou.
I see.
Actually Wu Bai is also my idol.
I’d introduce myself formally.
Lin Yin just joined us.
He’s the youngest member of the team.
I’m already 18 years old.
We are all adults.
All are the same.
I’d introduce again.
Coach, I’m Lin Yin.
The operator of SP Team.
Nice to see you.
You have no idea
how many clubs
want this young genius.
Many people say
he’ll probably become the next Wu Bai.
I also think so.
What do you think, Coach?
I think…
Wu Bai is taller than you.
I’m still a kid.
I will keep
growing taller.
You just said
you are an adult.
I…
Well, let’s stop joking on him.
He may feel embarrassed.
Doggie.
There’s no need to introduce, right?
I’m back.
I knew you would come back.
You belong to this place.
I have to especially explain
that Ou Qiang is not an operator
but our software engineer now.
But a team
usually has two operators.
Who is the other one?
You may guess.
It’s been a while, Doggie.
Xiaomi.
When did you return?
When did you join in SP?
Why didn’t you tell me early?
There is no surprise in that case.
Ou Qiang.
You knew it earlier, right?
That’s his idea.
Boss.
Coach.
Thank you.
What’s wrong? Silly girl.
I promised you, so I surely will come.
Thank you all.
Thank you for coming back.
These are all the members
of SP Team I.
Welcome
back.
Welcome back.
♪A nobody Who am I♪
♪Don’t mind if you forget her♪
Wish all the new members
can overcome all obstacles
and be invincible
in the future games.
♪Maybe he’s tired and miserable♪
♪Maybe he’s humble
and has accomplished nothing♪
♪Maybe he could never be anybody♪
I feel like I’m back to Solo Team.
♪A nobody♪
Guys.
SP! Go for it!
Bibo, bibo. Wu Liao detected you’re
seriously lacks of happiness index.
Tell me if anything makes you unhappy.
That can make me happy.
Are you bored?
I’m not.
Alright.
I made the wrong estimation
of my emotional endurance.
I’m pleased she returned
to the armor circle.
But accordingly,
she has more time to be with Solo.
Searching the list of sad love songs.
Playing soon.
No, I’ve been in peace now.
Alright.
I admit
that I want to see her.
As you see,
SP’s hardware level
is second to none.
How about software?
Software?
Almost unbeatable.
Almost?
Is K&K comparable?
Do you know K&K very well?
Not much.
Then
you know Wu Bai very well?
Why do you ask so suddenly?
I found
that you think highly of Wu Bai.
I just feel time flies
suddenly.
When Han brought him
to watch the game for the first time
he was just a little boy.
Now he actually becomes
captain of the top team.
Yes.
We are getting old.
It’s their time now.
How about
inviting the members
to have dinner together tonight?
I’m afraid not.
Someone is picking you up.
Hi.
Short hair
fits you well.
Thank you.
How did you know I’m here?
Your ex-colleague told me that.
What are you doing here
today?
Ai Qing.
I wonder
if you came back for Solo.
No.
I want to take you to a place.
OK.
Where are we going?
Get on the car.
♪My love♪
♪My sweet love♪
♪I made you out♪
♪You and love♪
♪Are the eternal theme for me♪
♪I trust you♪
♪The rain The rain♪
I don’t know since when
♪It’s you♪
I’ve fallen in love with this boy.
♪My love All because of you♪
I know
I must like him very much.
♪I can’t leave you♪
Otherwise,
why would I feel
so reluctant at the moment?
But I know better
he’s Han Shangyan’s cousin.
He’s the captain of K&K.
These two points
together mean only one thing
for me,
same mistake.
Ai Qing.
I’d like to talk to you.
Wu Bai.
Can you listen to me first?
OK.
Do you remember you asked me a question
three years ago in Singapore?
Why did
Solo Team dismiss?
Yes.
Why did you mention that suddenly?
Now I’m telling you the reason
why it dismissed.
The real reason
was because of me.
I made
an impulsive decision
which caused the dismission
of Solo Team.
Meanwhile,
it caused an eternal regret
of Han Shangyan,
Ou Qiang and Xiaomi.
I want to find them back.
I want to rebuild the team.
Or
at least I can give them
the competition prize.
It’s like before.
We shared the prize together.
Even if it’s only one penny,
we would divide it into five.
So I kept playing competitions
until the Asian Championships.
Getting everyone back
is my greatest wish all the time.
I hope everyone of them
can live a very good life.
But
when I got SP’s contract,
I hesitated.
I almost refused their invitation.
But when I saw Slide later,
he said something to me.
He told me
he’s dying to return to the circle.
I was thinking
that must be the dream
of Ou Qiang and others as well.
So I have to spare no pains.
I must do that.
K&K and SP are competitors.
You are the captain of K&K.
If I become the coach of SP,
we two
will be the biggest rivals.
We take on our own team
and club.
We are no longer an individual.
So Wu Bai,
comparing to love,
something is more important
in my opinion.
♪Love will go go♪
♪The starry sky blurs my eyes♪
♪My heart will hurt♪
♪Looking at the sky
I miss you every second♪
Sorry, Wu Bai.
♪My tears♪
It’s all by bad.
♪Love will go go♪
♪My heart still hurts♪
I should tell you
today’s words earlier.
♪Star’s tears fall in my hands
at that second♪
But...
Do you like me?
I’m sorry.
You said
there is no need to say sorry
between us.
I have something to do.
I’m leaving now.
♪When I get used to the habit♪
♪Never thought we’d be apart one day♪
♪Feel sorry for
the most familiar stranger♪
♪The loneliest
in the liveliest environment♪
♪Love is about two people♪
♪I’m trying to get used to it♪
♪Still feel sad
when think of it sometimes♪
♪The most cherished memories
are the most common ones♪
♪The most regretful is perfect♪
♪I finally say goodbye to being upset♪
♪I can be brave♪
♪I’m not afraid of being alone♪
♪Let the memories
stop at the last good night♪
♪It’s a perfect end♪
♪I will remember your warmth♪
♪That’s my♪
♪Bravery that I never regret♪
♪The night missing you♪
(The chosen single dog)
♪Not all questions have an answer♪
♪But everyone is related to you♪
(Dare not to love too deep
Afraid of losing)
♪I can be brave♪
♪I’m not afraid of being alone♪
♪Let the memories
stop at the last good night♪
♪It’s a perfect end♪
♪I will remember your warmth♪
♪That’s my♪
♪Bravery that I never regret♪
♪Everyone becomes brave in regret♪
♪The eternal moment left in the past♪
Do you like me?
♪I can be brave♪
♪I’m not afraid of being alone♪
♪Let the memories
stop at the last good night♪
♪It’s a perfect end♪
♪I will remember your warmth♪
♪That’s my♪
♪Bravery that I never regret♪
Did you fix yesterday’s bug?
Yes.
But new problems appeared after that.
Boss is back.
Boss.
Here you are.
Thank you, Boss.
By the way, Shen Zhe is out for a date.
Captain still hasn’t come back, either.
Yes.
I see.
It seems Boss is in a bad mood.
Nonsense.
When does he
look in good mood?
Seems you are right.
Anyway, maybe not.
He is very kind
to Tong Nian.
Yes.
We haven’t seen her for a long time.
Have they argued with each other?
We can check
You Xiaoyu’s moments.
Then we will know.
Yes.
Let’s see if she posted new moments.
(You Xiaoyu)
Seems there is no new moment.
Let me see.
Hello.
♪Will you have dinner and walk with me♪
Don’t move.
♪On the streets you are familiar with♪
♪It’s hot dare not to breathe♪
♪Fearing of breaking it being careful♪
♪Your gestures and expressions
leave traces in my mind♪
♪Heart beating in front of you♪
♪Breathing beside you♪
♪Miss you once every day♪
(Choose the friend and listen together)
♪How much suffering to experience♪
(Garbage Sorting G)
♪Oh baby that’s just our luv song♪
Don’t be tough, be gentle.
You left your scarf at mine.
I got it a new home.
How is it?
Does it look good?
(Garbage Sorting G)
♪Imagine travelling in
all galaxies with you♪
♪Imagine travelling
through the time and space with you♪
It’s as coquettish as you are.
♪Feeling the same is more than fate♪
♪All things experiencing together♪
Don’t talk nonsense.
This is Wu Bai’s son.
♪Will we travel together♪
Finished your date?
Yes. I’m back.
Didn’t you go home for the new year?
Why are you still here?
We didn’t get the air tickets.
We’re leaving on the day after tomorrow.
We’ll go back several days later.
What are you eating?
Instant noodles.
Captain?
Wu Bai?
Wu Bai? Wu Bai?
What’s going on?
No idea.
Boss returned just now.
Boss is back?
He didn’t come out after getting in.
Will they fight?
I also feel the atmosphere is weird.
It’s the Chinese New Year.
Why are they so angry?
Go take a look.
I dare not.
Go if you want.
You go.
I dare not too.
You two cowards.
You go. Go ahead.
I…
I just want to have noodles.
You…
It tastes great.
Zhou Yi, make one for me.
If you like it,
buy it yourself.
Buy it yourself.
I have no money.
Why did you go on a date then?
I didn’t.
One more bite.
Wu Bai, I hope you are clear
that Ai Qing is Solo’s girlfriend.
No matter what happened among us,
Solo will always be my friend.
What about me?
♪When I get used to the habit♪
♪Never thought we’d be apart one day♪
♪Feel sorry for
the most familiar stranger♪
♪The loneliest
in the liveliest environment♪
♪Love is about two people♪
The multiple choices in the world
can be ridiculous and real.
I once thought
that not love is the only thing placed
on the other end of the balance of love.
But this kind of balance doesn’t exist.
Only my responsibilities,
my missions
and my dreams
are on my end of the balance.
It needs me to make a choice
between them and love.
♪I’m not afraid of being alone♪
♪Let the memories
stop at the last good night♪
♪It’s a perfect end♪
♪I will remember your warmth♪
♪That’s my♪
♪Bravery that I never regret♪
♪If you can see in my eyes♪
♪You’re the stars
Shining above the clouds♪
♪If you can see in my eyes♪
♪There are dreams of sea
My heart leaps♪
♪I don’t need you to see♪
♪Crossing the dark tunnels♪
♪Drowned in the crowds♪
♪There’s a shy boy♪
♪Waiting for you to step on the stage♪
♪Looking at your profile♪
♪To exchange an oath♪
♪One day you’ll look forward to♪
♪Maybe you’ll be surprised♪
♪Maybe you’ll stay silent♪
♪It’s fine I’m here I understand you♪
♪Until the end of the night♪
♪Until there’s no guardian left♪
♪I want you to know I’m there♪
♪Never let go♪
♪Ai Ai
Conquer the borderless white dream♪
♪Endure the scattering loneliness♪
♪Ai Ai
Until I become the champion♪
♪The gold medal is for you♪
♪If you can see in my eyes♪
♪You’re the stars
Shining above the clouds♪
♪If you can see in my eyes♪
♪There are dreams of sea
My heart leaps♪
♪Drowned in the crowds♪
♪There’s a shy boy♪
♪Waiting for you to step on the stage♪
♪Looking at your profile♪
♪To exchange an oath♪
♪One day you’ll look forward to♪
♪Maybe you’ll be surprised♪
♪Maybe you’ll stay silent♪
♪It’s fine I’m here I understand you♪
♪Until the end of the night♪
♪Until there’s no guardian left♪
♪I want you to know I’m there♪
♪Never let go♪
♪Ai Ai
Conquer the borderless white dream♪
♪Endure the scattering loneliness♪
♪Ai Ai
Until I become the champion♪
♪The gold medal is for you♪