♪You wake up from the shadow♪
♪Jump onto the stage♪
♪Walk through the city neon♪
♪Stand out of the border♪
♪Time flies by♪
♪Joys and sorrows success or failure♪
♪At one place of the world once♪
♪The first ray of sunlight♪
♪Break through barriers of the night♪
♪Make my most beloved dream into shapes♪
♪Glory or quiet
There is the direction in the mind♪
♪Like a sunlight♪
♪In full bloom in the night sky♪
♪Not alone any longer
Stumbling along in confusion♪
♪No matter how
Break through bravely with a free hand♪
♪It’s the dream of love
Already lightened by you♪
=Go Go Squid 2: Dt. Appledog’s Time=
=Episode 37=
We’re home.
Dad’s prepared a table of food,
and wine.
(Drunk as a lord)
Drunk as a lord.
I’m sure my sister wrote this.
Okay.
Now it’s only two of us here.
Eat something.
Ai Qing.
You first.
Please.
Why?
Wait for a while.
What’s up
your sleeve?
This is
my bank card.
The bonuses I got from
winning games are all in it.
My dear Bai,
are you gonna hand over
your financial rights to me so soon?
I was about to propose to you
when we were
at the City Street Garden.
But I was one step ahead of you.
Then please tell me
how would you
propose to me if I haven’t asked you.
97 and the others were just around,
each holding a box
like this.
97?
Were they all there?
What is this?
Your car key.
Car key?
I was thinking sometimes
I might be too busy
to pick you up,
so I’ve brought a car for you.
But first of all,
you need a driver’s license.
This is
the key of our wedding house.
Wedding house?
You have a wedding house in place?
The house...
It...
Bai,
I feel like
I was to marry
Doraemon.
I think I haven’t prepared enough.
It’s enough.
Actually,
I can do without these
as long as I get you.
No.
I’ve been imagining it for ten years
and I’ve been preparing for it
for ten years.
Could you tell me
what we will become in ten years?
We’ll be happier.
Bai.
Do you feel anything special?
For what?
Before and after we married.
Yes.
Such as...?
Such as tonight.
I’ll sleep soundly
on your bed.
Bad boy!
This is my right.
-I...
-Is that Grandpa?
Grandpa.
Hello Bai,
where are you?
In Ai Qing’s home.
Brushing my teeth.
For such a good day,
you should take her
to some romantic place.
I thought you would be
cleverer than your cousin,
yet you are as silly as him
when it comes to
such a critical moment.
Grandpa, you’ve misunderstood him.
It’s my idea.
Qing,
you can’t protect him like this
even before your wedding.
You should tell me
if he makes you
feel wronged.
Thank you, Grandpa.
Goodbye, Grandpa.
Did you hear it?
If you dare to bully me,
I’ll tell Grandpa.
I’m gonna bully you.
Can you stop me?
I’m calling Grandpa.
What are you doing?
Now, you can’t tell him.
(Mom)
My mom.
Mom.
Bai,
can I have a word with
my daughter-in-law?
Mom, it’s the first day...
Never mind.
Please speak, Auntie, I’m here.
You’re still calling me Auntie?
Please speak, Mom.
Bai,
what are you doing?
-Brushing teeth.
-Watching the movie.
What are you doing exactly?
Bai,
I have to blame you.
Even a man as straight as your dad
won’t do so unromantic things
like you.
Am I right?
Wu Bai, your mom is right.
You should be more thoughtful.
Hm...
Then I’ll hang up.
All right.
I’m sorry to bother you.
Goodbye.
-Goodbye.
-Bye.
Why not watch the movie?
Okay.
Which movie should we watch?
What about...?
You really want to watch the movie?
What are you working on?
The Champion Food we invented.
The more you eat,
the more champions you’ll get.
It’s the starter.
Gold shrimp and egg dumplings.
I’m gonna make
the winner’s oil-fried dumplings.
And the champion’s fried dumplings.
And...
I haven’t finished yet.
Though the name is strange,
it tastes good.
Shen Zhe!
Come and see
our championship display case.
Let’s go.
How is it?
What the hell are you doing?
We’re different now.
What’s different?
We’re the champion team.
Things should be changed.
Yes.
So?
What comes first to others’ eyes
when they come to visit us?
Of course, it’s the environment.
This is the “face” of K&K!
Isn’t it amazing? Look.
I’ll call all other teams
and ask them to
visit us.
Isn’t it...?
Although we’re champions,
we need to be low-key.
Am I right, Captain?
Since you’re all here,
we’ll have a meeting.
I’ve strictly examined myself.
Although we’ve got good results,
we can’t be arrogant.
Even though we have won
the world champion,
we still have many things
that could be improved.
Yes.
I bet that Naya
will upgrade their mecha.
But I think I might have
underestimated them.
So I will schedule
an upgrade of The Nobody,
just recently.
Shen Zhe.
I’ve thought a lot
after we’ve competed with
the world’s best players.
I... I will lock myself up
to do some practices.
Come on!
Fine.
A great team should never be
satisfied with victory
or be daunted by losing.
Captain, why I find you
smiling strangely?
Were you intimidating us?
I didn’t say anything.
You made the summary,
and that was good.
Captain,
you’re a bad boy.
Fine. Let’s get back to the point.
Wu Bai,
what were you gonna tell us?
Actually,
I have one thing to tell you.
What is it?
I get married.
Really?
You are married.
When is the wedding party?
Next month.
Buddies,
let’s buy some formal suits.
Let’s go.
Get it done.
Where is the Captain?
I don’t know. Where is he?
-Wu Bai.
Wu Bai.
You look good.
A fake gentleman.
A fictitious lord.
Mind your words!
Don’t worry.
We only speak good words.
Do you think
she will love it?
Of course.
You’re the most handsome man
in our team.
She should be satisfied with that.
Rest assured, Captain.
I’m sure Ai Qing will like it.
Come on!
Fine.
Grandpa,
these are all formal suits.
Yes.
Weddings nowadays need
more than one suit.
We need to prepare some
for our children’s wedding.
Yes.
Hello.
Hello,
do you need some formal suits?
Yes.
My grandchild is about to marry.
Please give your recommendations.
I’m the Grandpa.
He is the dad.
Here is a robot.
How do you like it?
Good.
I’ll buy them.
All of them?
Which payment method you prefer?
Scan it.
Okay, I’ll pack them for you.
Fine.
Grandpa, you’ll buy all of them?
Won't it will cost you too much?
Don't say that.
We’ll soon be one family.
Don’t be ceremonious with me.
Right.
A friend of mine
recommended an interior designer
to me.
Why not help our children
with their house designing?
That’s a good idea.
They are too busy
to look after that.
But you must not grab the bill again.
You... You pay?
I can share it with you.
Let’s go and have a cup of tea.
Fine.
It’s on me.
Please sit here.
I’ve looked
the floor plan of your house.
And may I know which style
you prefer,
the general style?
I hear that the newlyweds
are athletes.
Yes, they are.
Robot fighting athletes.
Sounds good.
Our children are working on high-tech.
Not only robots,
but artificial intelligence.
Just like this robot.
Hello.
Then should we have some
technological elements
in the house?
Please look at this.
This?
No, no, no.
I’ve been to their base.
It’s all copper and iron.
It would startle them
if they got up at midnight and saw this.
Not this.
Show me some loving designs.
Loving?
What about the minimalist style?
It’s popular among young people.
It renders a sense of the future
while being suitable for family living.
Minimalist?
I know this.
It’s just like
an empty house.
It is not
warm.
No. I don’t like it.
It's not suitable.
What if the traditional Chinese style?
Traditional Chinese style?
Isn’t it mahogany plus rosewood?
That’s old-fashioned.
Young people won’t like it.
And
it’s too expensive.
It’s not suitable.
Too expensive.
It’s not suitable, right?
What about this European vintage style?
Please look at it.
This one?
Isn’t it lace?
Lace or something.
This is absolutely not.
And this is also expensive.
This is not suitable, too.
Can you describe
the style you want
to me?
I’ll keep a note.
It’s like...
For example,
it should be simple but not plain,
low-key but a little luxurious.
Yes.
And then…
Some tech elements…
Some tech elements
in a loving environment.
Yes.
Also…
Some festive air...
Right.
Some festive air in an elegant manner.
Yes.
Mr. Ai,
do you have anything to add?
It's good.
You’ve spoken all I want.
The most important thing is…
The most important thing is?
A reasonable price.
Right.
Even if my client
embarrasses me a thousand times,
I’ll still treat him as my first love.
When one day I become the boss,
I’ll embarrass
all design institutes on earth.
Hush!
Bai, there you are. Come here.
Look what your grandpa
has bought.
What did you buy?
Isn’t it that
you and Ai Qing are married?
I know you two are busy,
so I’ve settled the deal
for your new house’s decoration
with Ai Qing’s dad.
Decoration for the new house?
Yes.
You’re married.
Soon or later,
you’ll need to furnish your house.
Have you finished with
my cousin’s house?
You should help him first.
Your cousin has been
very choosy.
I won’t meddle in his affair.
Come here and see.
I know young people
don’t like traditional things.
So I’ve chosen the smart home devices.
They said
it’s the color-changeable light
with voice controller.
How do you like it?
It is
special.
Yes.
It takes time before Ai Qing’s dad
and I settled on this one,
but I think the color
should be adjusted.
Grandpa,
I think the house
I am living in is good enough.
Isn’t it that my cousin
still needs a new house?
You should choose
a design scheme for him.
And his style should be
more festive than mine,
or he would complain that
you’re partial to me.
Yes.
You’re right.
Fine.
I should take this opportunity
to find a good design for him.
Then
I’ll leave it to you.
I’ll go now.
Congratulations!
You’ll soon have a new house.
-Bai.
-Grandpa.
Quick and help me.
It’s heavy.
There you are, Dad.
Grandpa,
what’s in it that makes it so heavy?
Mahjong.
Grandpa.
I’m bored staying at home alone.
So,
I’ve come
to play mahjong with you.
Mahjong?
That’s great.
I was thinking of playing mahjong.
Ai Qing,
can you play mahjong?
I saw my dad playing it,
so I knew the rules.
That’s fine.
You, me, and Bai.
We play mahjong.
Grandpa, I can’t play mahjong.
You knew that.
My grandson is so clever
that you should know the rules
after two rounds.
Mr. Wu, can you play mahjong?
I...
He can’t.
I totally have no idea of the game.
Right.
No more of it. We’ll start soon.
One, two, three, four.
We four play mahjong.
Hurry.
I should put it first
that it’s a real game.
Of course it is.
Fine.
Grandpa,
shouldn’t we talk about
the rules first?
Bai, don’t you have
the basic knowledge of it?
I don’t, but I can learn.
Mahjong is simple.
You must have a yaozi.
If you have all shunzi, kezi,
and jiangpai on your hand,
you win.
Yes.
Let’s begin.
Begin.
Let’s play mahjong.
Yi wan.
Xi feng.
I have a good hand.
Which one should I give out?
Does anyone like yi tong?
No, I don’t need it.
Wait, Grandpa.
I need yi tong.
Thank you,  Auntie.
I win.
It just matches.
Yes.
Wait a minute.
It seems I win, too.
Same color and neat.
A big win for you.
Brilliant. How smart you are!
Let’s go on.
Another round.
Er wan.
It’s mine.
I have three of it.
Liu tong.
Thank you, Grandpa.
Win!
Si tong.
I win.
Both of you’ve won?
Again, I win.
Grand slam!
You’re amazing, today.
Bai,
you’ve won the day.
Grandpa must have been tired.
Let’s stop here.
Qing,
let me buy some
wedding dresses for you.
Do you mean bridal gowns?
Let’s go. Bai, you’ll be the driver.
Fine.
Let’s go. Hurry.
-Grandpa, we’ll leave now.
-Sure.
Go.
We’re leaving.
I didn’t know you’re
so good at cooperating.
Are you happy?
Dad, you should
have told me in advance
so I can have some preparations.
You just made me nervous.
Don’t worry.
We still have many opportunities.
Because they won’t take
our money directly, will they?
We must find a method
to make them take our money.
Nice, give me five!
Yes.
Two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight.
That’s a lot.
Enough?
We still need some else.
We’ll go and buy shoes tomorrow.
Mom,
Ai Qing needs to work tomorrow.
She can’t go shopping with you.
Right.
Ai Qing has work to do.
How can she go shopping
with you every day?
Then you tell me
the size of your shoes.
I’ll buy them for you.
I shouldn’t bother you anymore, Auntie.
I can buy them myself.
Just tell her to fulfill her wish.
What’s her size?
36.
Okay, I’ll keep that in mind.
My dear,
don’t you think they are beautiful?
How did you know my size?
I know
all about you.
It’s time to go, Mom.
I’ll send Ai Qing home.
Wait.
Qing should stay one night with me.
You, too.
Qing will sleep with me.
Mom, what about me?
You sleep with your dad.
Is it okay, Qing?
I just want to chat with you.
I’m fine, Auntie.
Please, Auntie.
Bai,
come here.
What’s up?
What should I do? I’m nervous.
What do you think
your mom will ask me?
I don’t know.
You’re her son.
You should know something.
I didn’t have
any girlfriends before you.
I don’t know what she
will talk about with my girlfriend.
I have no idea, really.
What should I do?
I have an idea.
What is it?
Keep quiet.
When I was a kid,
if I didn’t know how
to answer the question,
I just stayed quiet.
They get used to it.
Keep quiet?
Isn’t it impolite
if I just keep quiet
when she speaks to me.
No worries. They’ve gotten used to it.
So I...
Auntie.
Bai,
why are you here?
You should go to bed now.
I... I will go to bed soon.
No worries.
I know you like her
since you were a kid.
I’ll take care of her.
Don’t worry.
I won’t tell her your little secrets.
Go find your dad
and have a chat with him.
-Go.
-Okay.
Quick.
-Go.
-Goodbye.
Do talk with him.
Let’s go to bed.
Yes.
Let’s go.
I’ve especially brought
his childhood photos.
Do you like to see them?
Yes.
Wait.
Come here.
Look.
Look at it.
It is when he was a kid?
Wow, cute!
He was fat back then, wasn’t he?
Was he cute?
He was five years old then.
His dad and I
had taken him to a park.
He was very happy then.
And this one.
This is when he was seven years old.
We took him for
an outing
and bought him a white hat.
He liked it
and couldn’t wait to put it on.
He was narcissistic.
What are you thinking?
Nothing.
Are you worried your mom
may embarrass your wife?
I’m afraid she might be nervous.
Bai,
your mom asked me
to give you a lesson,
a premarital lesson.
I think
marriage is
a holy ceremony.
So, you should...
Hm...
Wu Bai,
you’ve grown up
and you’re clever.
I think you should know.
So,
no more of it.
We’d better
have a nice sleep.
Fine.
(Wu Bai)
Living room.
Your mom is asleep.
You must be tired,
shopping with her
and chatting.
Can you adapt to it?
I’m fine.
Haven’t you been
following us for the day?
Yes.
Your mom gave me
a necklace this morning.
She said
she had put it in ready ten years ago.
She said giving me
was the same as giving it to you.
No wonder.
No wonder what?
Since they knew I liked you,
I haven’t received any birthday gifts.
Actually, they and my grandpa
all prefer girls to boys,
but they only had boys.
So they adore you very much.
By the way,
what did my mom tell you?
She has talked
a lot about
her and your dad.
I can tell that
she loves your dad very much.
They get along well.
It reminds me of my dad
after talking so much with her.
My dad and mom
get along well, too.
But
my mom passed away early.
After she died,
he’s paid all his attention
to me and my sister.
It’s obvious.
So,
he’ll be lonelier
after both of us are married.
We are his
companies.
For now it’s sure,
but what about the future?
The same.
We’ll be his companies like always.
We’ll live in Shanghai
and support him.
Bai,
thanks.
Earphone?
I didn’t see him
ever wear an earphone.
Zhou Yi,
what should I give Wu Bai
at his wedding the day after tomorrow?
We’re more than friends.
Your wishes to him
will be the best gift.
It sounds right.
Wu Bai doesn’t need anything.
What kind of gift can represent
our great friendship?
That’s a good question.
But I’ve already picked one.
Have an apple.
Thanks.
Can you tell me what you will bring?
It’s a gift
made by myself,
showing my regards.
What is it anyway?
I won’t tell anyone.
You won’t tell me?
Sir, what will you take with you?
I won’t tell you.
What’s yours, Zhou Yi?
You’ll know.
Where is your gift?
Why should I tell you?
-Morning, Captain.
-Captain.
Morning.
What’s up?
Who will be the first?
Me.
My gift has the most
significant meaning.
I’ll be the last.
The last one? Okay, you’ll be the last.
What gift?
Wedding gift.
Let me be the first.
Wu Bai,
I’m not eloquent.
I wish you happiness with Appledog.
Like the inseparable birds
and may you have a baby soon.
Have many children and grandchildren.
Coach,
I never saw you as rigid as this.
What did you know?
Though it might be old-style,
the meaning is good.
Thank you.
Okay, next one.
It’s my turn.
What’s this?
It’s handmade by myself.
Captain, please press this.
Press this.
(Happy Wedding)
(Forever Love)
That’s good.
That’s a good idea.
I know you don’t need anything.
It’s just a token of my wishes.
That’s why I made it.
I wish you a happy wedding
and forever love.
It’s thoughtful of you.
Shen Zhe, it’s your turn.
Didn’t you say you’ll be the last one?
Yes.
You should be the one
before the last one.
-Yes.
-Yes, you’re right.
Don’t you know it?
Of course I do.
I’m afraid you don’t know it.
What a joke!
Here you are.
What is it?
A hammer.
Isn’t it the one you
used for daily maintenance?
You give him a hammer?
You can save it.
You’ve been shallow.
This has meaning.
I’ve kept this hammer with me
for three years ago
since our team was still called DT.
It’s witnessed
many successes made
by me and Wu Bai.
It’s the lucky hammer.
Now I’ll give it to Wu Bai
and wish his marriage life
be happy and smooth.
Hammer away at it!
Captain, it’s yours.
That’s meaningful.
Sure.
Now, somebody can
stop laughing at me
and take out his amazing gift.
I’ve thought of many things,
but nothing will be more
meaningful than this.
(Reserve Fund)
Reserve fund?
-What is it?
-Reserve fund.
What do you mean?
You’re not serious about it, are you?
Why not give him
three massage coupons?
At least he can do
some massage with them.
You don’t know.
It’s a secret between Wu Bai and me.
When he asked me to join the team,
he promised that he would give
half of his wage to me,
which I have never used.
I let Su Cheng set up an account.
Now you’re married
and the money put into
this account increased.
It’s yours now.
What are you talking about?
I’m confused.
You can explain it to them, coach.
Wu Bai didn’t know about
the reserve fund account.
He thought he was depositing money
into Shen Zhe’s account every month,
but actually...
Anyway it’s Shen Zhe’s money.
He has the right
to decide the use of it.
It was yours
and I return it to you.
Half of the sum
will be used for team building
and the rest will be
bonuses for the future.
Are you serious?
Happiness suddenly comes.
I can’t breathe.
Enough of you.
It hasn’t fallen into your hands.
And you’re like you can’t breathe.
I don’t care for others.
Forget about the bonus,
but I must have a share
of the team building.
Why not use this opportunity
to hold a bachelor party for him?
Good.
I noticed there was always
a bachelor party
in TV dramas before
the hero got married.
We should have one, too.
Swimming pool.
A big house.
Beauties.
And champagne.
We should have one, too.
Bachelor party?
Swimming pool and beauties?
I’ll take you to some place.
Follow me.
You’ve arranged it?
Let’s go.
Today’s a good day. And tonight...
What about us?
You help pack the captain’s gifts.
We’re leaving.
This is a really good idea.
I also want to go.
Me, too.
(Happiness)
All right.
Well.
When will the dresser arrive?
At 6 a.m. tomorrow.
Okay.
Good.
This...
(Happiness)
Set it right.
Okay. It’s all right.
Go to bed early tonight.
Don’t drink water,
or you’ll get a puffy face.
Do you hear it, Qing?
I know.
Okay.
I’ll go now.
Dad,
won’t you stay here tonight?
No, I have gotten everything in place.
Don’t mess it up.
Now we can wait for tomorrow.
By the way,
the jujubes and longans
I put in front of the sofa
are with good meanings.
You must not touch them.
You must not.
-I know.
-Do you hear me?
I understand.
All right.
Well.
I’ll go now.
Okay.
I just said you must not eat them.
What the hell is in your head?
What’s wrong with you?
I won’t touch them.
That’s it. All right.
I’ll go now.
Dad,
can you change your suit tomorrow?
Well. Don’t worry about that.
Be careful on your way home.
Have a safe trip.
Hello.
Hi, my dear.
Wu Bai lied to us.
There is no bachelor party or anything.
I and 97 are in his room
watching him ironing clothes.
I’m bored to death.
I’m not bored.
Isn’t it good?
Save and conserve your energy.
I tell you,
he needs you and 97 to drink wine
for him tomorrow.
I know, but...
No more of it.
I need to talk with my sister.
Jing, I...
Damn it. My Jing won’t talk with me.
Be quiet.
I’m playing the game.
♪If you can see in my eyes♪
♪You’re the stars
Shining above the clouds♪
♪If you can see in my eyes♪
♪There are dreams of sea
My heart leaps♪
♪I don’t need you to see♪
♪Crossing the dark tunnels♪
♪Drowned in the crowds♪
♪There’s a shy boy♪
♪Waiting for you to step on the stage♪
♪Looking at your profile♪
♪To exchange an oath♪
♪One day you’ll look forward to♪
♪Maybe you’ll be surprised♪
♪Maybe you’ll stay silent♪
♪It’s fine I’m here I understand you♪
♪Until the end of the night♪
♪Until there’s no guardian left♪
♪I want you to know I’m there♪
♪Never let go♪
♪Ai Ai
Conquer the borderless white dream♪
♪Endure the scattering loneliness♪
♪Ai Ai
Until I become the champion♪
♪The gold medal is for you♪
♪If you can see in my eyes♪
♪You’re the stars
Shining above the clouds♪
♪If you can see in my eyes♪
♪There are dreams of sea
My heart leaps♪
♪Drowned in the crowds♪
♪There’s a shy boy♪
♪Waiting for you to step on the stage♪
♪Looking at your profile♪
♪To exchange an oath♪
♪One day you’ll look forward to♪
♪Maybe you’ll be surprised♪
♪Maybe you’ll stay silent♪
♪It’s fine I’m here I understand you♪
♪Until the end of the night♪
♪Until there’s no guardian left♪
♪I want you to know I’m there♪
♪Never let go♪
♪Ai Ai
Conquer the borderless white dream♪
♪Endure the scattering loneliness♪
♪Ai Ai
Until I become the champion♪
♪The gold medal is for you♪