I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Sister.
You're fine.
I'm fine.
I care about you and my two sons the most.
I owe you so much.
I can't forget.
When you were five years old, I was too willful.
I was pregnant with Ding Yi.
My parents abandoned me.
My parents bullied me.
I can never forget you.
You were chasing after my life.
Sister, come back.
Come back.
I want to come back.
But how can I?
All right.
I know.
I'm not as miserable as you.
Why are you doing this?
You can't do this.
Promise me.
Promise me to live well.
You have to be happy.
All right.
I know.
As long as you're happy, I'll be happy.
I don't care about all the grievances and hardships.
I'm sorry.
I came to Shanghai, but you went to a faraway place.
If you take a step forward bravely,
you don't have to bear the pain alone.
Thank God for letting me spend the last days with you.
The sky.
I want to go somewhere where I can love.
I want to love someone.
Where do you want to go?
Shangri-La.
The translation of the Chinese is the sun and the moon.
I heard that the sky is very blue and the scenery is very beautiful.
There are no worries and no sadness.
Will you go with me one day?
Yes.
Xiaorou, although you left,
you will always live in my heart.
I want to take you to the heaven you want to go to.
Shangri-La.
Will you?
I'm in front of the car. Can you take me there?
Okay, no problem.
Thank you.
Be careful.
Here we are.
This?
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Be careful.
This is good.
Youxi.
Hi, beautiful.
Hi.
I've never seen you before.
Nonsense.
Let's go drink beer together.
Okay?
You're free anyway.
No, I'm busy.
I'll give you this flash.
You may need it when you go back.
What about you?
It's okay, I have another one.
Oh, right.
This flash is very important to me.
So, I'll give you a call.
I'll go to you with it.
Youxi.
Let's talk later.
How about you two take my car?
I'll give you a ride.
Okay.
No need.
Bye.
You're good.
What are you doing here?
I'm afraid you don't have a flash.
So I came to give you a flash.
That's good.
That's good?
Of course.
Let's go.
Who are you going to eat with me?
No one.
I'm sorry.
Can you show me a balloon?
Love moments made with a young age is beautiful.
A naive and simple life at the Pike,
There's no fight, no deception, no hatred.
It feels like yesterday.
I've been reading the gossip.
Now I know
that gossip can be so meaningful.
I want to remember forever
that this person believes in love.
That's it.
I want to remember forever that this person believes in love.
Xiaorou,
I'll miss you
if you go well.
I want to remember forever that this person believes in love.
Fuck you!
It smells great.
If one of myé¾ Cannon Madrid masters were here,
I'd be theile of splendor.
I'm sure Ding Yi will make delicious food.
You're really good at cooking.
But remember to cook more delicious food.
Thank you, Chef.
I've learned a lot of dishes from you.
You're talented.
If I give you another month,
I think you'll learn all the dishes I've learned.
I can't help it.
Who told you to be so hard-working?
But I believe that with Ding Yi,
the business of our flower shop will get better.
Of course.
He has such a good assistant.
He's so sincere.
It smells so good. What is this?
It smells so good.
What new dishes did you make today?
This is the dish my uncle taught me.
Here you are, Ding.
Thank you.
It's delicious.
Mr. Kan, you'll be in charge of the restaurant.
You'll be a good student.
Mr. Kan, I'll leave the future to you.
Okay.
You two can go to the cinema with me on Friday.
I'll go with you as long as Uncle likes it.
Okay.
Come here.
Don't dress like this.
I'm not a man who can stand a man who is so handsome.
If you're handsome, you'll lose your life.
Can you talk?
What do you mean by losing your life?
What son?
How do you know it's a son?
You'll know when you go to the hospital tomorrow.
Mom said she would go with you.
If it's a daughter, I like her more.
I treat her like a little princess.
I'm sorry.
Youxi.
I've been thinking.
Maybe I'm not suitable for this child.
Look, I can't even take care of myself.
I think I'd better take the child away.
Can you say that one last time?
I'll take care of you in the future.
As long as you give birth to the child,
I'll take care of your consciousness and your mind.
I'm sorry.
Let her decide for us.
If you come to this world,
I'll hug you.
You don't have to cry.
I'll marry your mother right away.
Okay?
When you go out,
you should prepare clothes.
This way you won't catch a cold.
Put your hands here.
And you can go to the hospital.
Okay?
Let's go.
I finally know where the real charm of a man is.
I have to thank you.
You and Xiaorou's things.
Let her find her conscience and courage.
What's wrong?
Someone is upset?
Or someone stole it?
How could it be?
I'm not happy.
Because my brother is leaving me.
He doesn't even know where the future is.
I don't know.
Let's wait for the day to decide.
Finally, it's romantic.
I'm worried about them before I leave.
I hope their feelings are in place.
Don't miss me.
Have you ever thought about coming to my bar?
Or go to Dingyi's restaurant?
Think about it and stay.
Sister.
Let me go out for a walk.
See the world outside.
Okay, let's go.
I want to be born.
But you want to fly away.
Our children are like wings.
The farther you fly, the higher you fly.
I understand.
Left a little.
More, more.
Right, right.
Put it down.
Down.
Okay.
Li Lucy.
Ah, we are leaving.
Hey, Weiwei.
Why did you arrive early after class?
I came out of the classroom right before school.
I want to give you a surprise. How is it?
Are you very touched?
I am. I am very touched.
Let's go to the supermarket.
We have no fridge at home. Let's go buy some food.
We'll cook dinner at home.
Now?
Let's go.
But...
Yingdong sent a driver to pick me up.
He's been waiting for me at the door for a long time.
He only has an hour and 20 minutes to meet me.
Is Yingdong that important?
How long does he know you?
We grew up together. We are good friends.
No.
He introduced me to the art director of the gallery.
He saw my work.
You are so petty.
If you don't want to be a good girl, go home.
I'll make it up to you.
I'll give you a massage.
Do whatever you want.
I'm not doing it.
I'm not even in a balance.
I'm not going to be a good girl if Yingdong shows up.
A woman who is a pervert is so scary.
How about...
Today, I...
Okay, I'm playing with you.
Go ahead. Don't wait for too long.
That's the best you can do.
Bye.
I'll come back later. I'll cook dinner with you.
Look at the room.
No.
Where are you going?
I'm going to the supermarket to buy something.
Get in.
I'll drive you.
You are so good. I can't get in.
I can't.
I'm begging you.
How can you drive a motorcycle?
You scared me.
I'm begging you too.
If you don't let me drive, please don't give it back to me.
You call me every day.
You are like a mental health exam.
I'm going crazy.
Your mother told me to stop you.
I have to follow the rules strictly.
Do you understand?
When did my mother say that?
Let's go.
Hat.
Hold on.
I'll go.
Hold on tight.
Let's go, Mu Ze.
Don't be my boyfriend.
Sit down.
Amber.
Why are you alone?
Did Xiao Qiao go out with someone?
Who knows?
Her phone is off.
Why are you abandoned too?
Who says I'm abandoned?
Amber has always abandoned others.
No one has ever abandoned me.
Oh.
Brother.
I have something to talk to your brother about work.
I'm shy.
I'm not a good girl.
Bye-bye.
Darling, get in the car.
I'm sorry, Amber.
We have to go now.
If you are sorry, you should say more.
I think you should go to a relationship if you have time.
Otherwise, you will be alone.
You are so annoying.
Let's go.
Bye-bye, baby.
Hey, listen.
You are in a relationship.
It has nothing to do with me.
I don't want you to be with me.
Mr. Kang.
Brother Bing Yi.
You are the first one who left school.
You haven't left yet?
What's wrong?
Is first love really that important to a woman?
They have changed.
Do you think I'm unlucky?
First, my best friend was taken away.
Then, my motorcycle and my helmet.
Finally, my brother was taken away.
This case of a serial robbery
sounds very complicated.
This case of a serial robbery.
The police are rude.
Forget it.
I'll accept it.
Then, you go to the supermarket with me.
We will talk about the case on the way.
Okay.
Let's go.
Mr. Li.
I asked you to meet me
because I want you to be the producer of this film.
What do you think of this story?
Mr. Kang.
No matter how good your story is,
it can only be a little bit of artistic success.
Do you understand?
Look at it now.
Even commercial films are expensive.
Not to mention the so-called pure foreign films.
Look at the story.
It's a mess.
The heroine didn't even get on the bed.
She didn't have a date or a relationship.
She finally kissed him.
In the end, the heroine got a leukemia.
Mr. Kang, are you going to make a Korean drama?
That's too fake.
I knew you were the one who made this script.
You don't know, do you?
This is a true story.
The heroine's name is Hua San Mao.
The heroine's name is Ding Xiang Rou.
The story of the two of them getting together is very popular on Weibo.
Amber.
Uncle, you're not good at talking, are you?
How can you talk?
Kang Da Wan.
You're a tough assistant.
I'm sorry.
She's new here. She doesn't know the rules.
Don't mind her.
Actually, the idea of this story
was created by my assistant and me.
So I asked her to come with me today.
I'm not going to be your assistant.
The audience is very popular now.
They will never come to the cinema to watch your drama.
So your drama has no market.
Even if you make it, it's a waste.
No one wants to invest in this drama.
But films like The Tree of Shadows are also very popular.
From this point of view,
the audience still longs for pure love.
The Tree of Shadows?
Who is the director?
Zhang Yi Mou?
Who is Zhang Yi Mou?
The famous international director.
Dear Kang Da Wan.
To be honest,
you usually shoot MVs and commercials.
Why do you let the investors
have the confidence to invest in you?
It's just money.
I have the confidence to invest in this movie.
I have 100% confidence in Kang Da Wan.
You're a little assistant.
Do you know how much it costs to invest in a movie?
Kang Da Wan, how much did you say?
Don't make a scene.
You should know what I'm talking about.
I won't let you down.
12 million.
How much did I invest?
I'll invest in this movie. I'll be the producer.
Kang Da Wan.
You're quite a good assistant.
Actually, the place we're talking about
is run by his father.
The owner of this hotel is Wu Yuting.
So your father hates Wu Yuting?
That's right.
And Kang Da Wan is my boyfriend.
I knew it. I finally understood.
Kang Da Wan, you're really good at hiding things.
Don't talk nonsense.
Take away the heroine of this movie.
I want to find a heroine who knows love,
who has a girl's heart for her first love.
Brother Li, I'm going to go.
Take care.
Bye.
Be careful.
Brother Tian Yi.
How did Wan Jia talk to those girls?
She wants us to know.
She'll tell us.
You're not happy?
I'm not.
Are you afraid that Yingdong will change Wan Jia?
If she doesn't want to be changed,
who can change her?
I think Yingdong is too strong.
She must want to change Wan Jia.
Enough.
We're starting a business.
You're still busy with other things.
Get back to work.
You really don't care?
I only care about this movie.
Wan Jia.
Why are you here?
I missed you.
How was the food today?
It was good.
She brought me to meet some friends of her art exhibition.
She said that she wanted to arrange my works
for the exhibition of European artists.
Not bad.
She wants to support you.
Brother Li.
What are you doing?
What?
Aren't you happy for me?
No.
I'm happy for you.
Then, give me some advice.
I think Yingdong is a person who can create miracles.
If he really wants to help you,
you can do it.
Money.
Men's words are always more valuable than women's words.
No.
All I care about is your feelings.
Go back to the studio.
You can interview a popular idol in the eyes of young people.
The most sincere singer, Miss.
The listener you have dialed is busy.
Please leave a message.
Hello, everyone.
I'm Eddy.
I think many people are like me.
I want to know how you came to sing.
Actually, I was very ordinary when I was young.
Whether it's my appearance or my personality,
I didn't attract attention.
You know, little girls are a little bit inferior.
I always thought that I was inferior to others.
I was a little more loved than my classmates.
It's really hard to believe.
You're so good now.
So, should I say that singing saved you?
Because I'm not confident,
my classmates always mocked me.
They even gave me a name.
It's called Bao Ya Mei.
Bao Ya Mei.
Yes.
In my memory,
I spent my student years in college.
Then I went to Guangzhou to study middle school.
The winter snow is still cold.
It's hard to believe.
I feel like I know you.
I think you know everyone except me and Mei Bao.
You're a bad girl who never leaves anyone behind.
Yes.
You're so mean.
You're right. You're really rich.
I think your ideas are rich.
We're rich?
Then let's hear what you think about the poor.
You were talking about the annual concert.
You're worried about who should be the guest.
You're not...
Yes, it's her.
Ai Di is the hottest singer now.
She must be a hot topic.
If we invite her,
I'm afraid that the students won't pay attention.
Then the audience will be very excited.
What? What's wrong?
Am I not good at this?
You're talking nonsense.
Who doesn't know it's good to invite Ai Di to the concert?
But the problem is that she's so popular now.
Who can invite her?
Besides, Ai Di has always been a loud person.
She's never been on her MV.
She can't be invited to many concerts.
Let alone our school.
Who's so proud?
Right.
What does Ai Di look like?
Why can't she show her face?
She must be pretty.
She sings so well.
That's not necessarily true.
She's not a beauty if she's a sweet voice.
She might be a beauty.
It's no use guessing.
We can't see her face or her photos.
It's all nonsense.
Do you want to see her real face?
You're lying.
I'll help you.
Hua Xiao Xi.
We're all friends.
We know you're close to her.
Can you be a little more reliable?
It's a dream.
Wait and see.
I'll reveal her secret.
Hello, everybody.
Do you have time tonight?
Wei Bao and I want to have a farewell party with Wei Wei.
Okay. I'll inform him when I meet Kang Zirui.
I'll ask Yingdong.
He must want to attend the farewell party.
Wei Wei and I are going to watch a movie.
Let's go to the bar at 10 pm.
Okay. We have time to prepare dessert.
Thank you.
What are you drinking?
Just ask him.
I'll have a bottle of rice wine with popcorn.
I want a box of popcorn.
Mr Kang, you're too much.
You're just watching a movie.
You want popcorn with popcorn?
I'll call you Mr Kang.
It's none of your business.
Besides, you asked me what I wanted to eat.
Don't eat it if you don't want to buy it.
Fine.
I'm sorry.
How many are in the air?
13, sir.
How many can I carry?
4, sir.
Oh, wait.
Slow down.
Relax.
Heather?
I'm sorry.
What's going on?
Wei Wei, try the taste of the old man.
You've never tasted it before.
You don't understand, do you?
The taste of durian is sweet after it's eaten.
The old man is the one who has been in contact with it.
That's how you can feel its tenderness and kindness.
Do you understand?
I don't understand the taste of it.
You eat it.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
Xiao Jiu hasn't come back yet.
Xiao Jiu, I'm back.
You're back.
Let's eat.
Cook your favourite dishes.
Xiao Jiu.
Eat.
I'm too tired.
Why?
Why are you in a bad mood?
It seems that you've recovered from your sadness.
You can help me now.
I don't want you to be like me.
You're a good girl.
You'll regret it sooner or later.
Besides,
you might not be able to give the one you can give Wan Jia.
Yes.
I can't give it to her.
I know you're doing this for my own good.
Xiao Jiu,
I really don't want to be with Wei Wei
because I can't find Wan Jia.
Don't you think it's unfair to Wei Wei?
And every time I'm with Wei Wei,
I can't think of Wan Jia.
Besides, I...
Besides,
you're still waiting for her to change her mind, right?
Let me tell you.
Even if one day,
Yingdong really breaks up with Wan Jia,
she might not give up on you.
Then I still have a chance to wait, right?
I know I understand.
But I've also lost someone.
I just think
there are things that can be let go of.
You have to let go.
Why don't you look at the person around you?
It might be different from the feeling before, right?
Look.
It's like this dish.
I cooked something sweet before.
But now it feels different.
Come on, let's eat.
Let's eat.
Hello.
I want to eat.
Please come in.
Come on, try my new dessert.
It's called Miss You.
Thank you.
Come on, try it.
We're going to learn the hand-made hand-pulled rice.
You have to wait for a while.
The process is too troublesome.
Where are you going?
Xiao Xiao, let me give you a toast.
Okay.
Thank you for letting me learn
how to be a responsible man.
Learn from your brother how to be a responsible man.
Don't learn from me. I'm not a good example.
Xiao Jiu.
Next time you come back,
you two will have good grades.
You should make good restaurants occasionally.
Next time you come back, you will open a branch.
Are you here?
Hello.
The two beautiful men and women are here.
I saw them.
Come on, sit down.
Xiao Jiu, Amber specially prepared this.
We will drink it all tonight.
Thank you.
Don't you have to have a meeting?
You need friends to be busy.
Maybe one day my business will be in Shangri-La.
You will be able to get a hold of me.
You're angry again.
Thank you for arranging an interview for me.
Otherwise, I won't be able to see you.
I also want to thank you.
I learned a lot from you.
Handsome men, I'm starving.
Wait, mom hasn't come down yet.
My mom won't come down so early.
I don't like Xiao Jiu.
Then let me go up and persuade her.
Do women need to be coaxed?
No, I'll go.
You're too much.
Why are you so happy?
I'm coming.
Mom.
Where are you going? Sit.
I'm going to sing a song today.
It's for my dearest daughter.
A long, long time ago
You have me
I have you
A long, long time ago
You have me
I have you
I hope you're happy.
Go find your happy world.
Okay, you have to take good care of yourself.
I give you a video every day.
What's not happy?
Call back.
I'm always waiting for you.
I know.
Even in the next life
I also hope we are a family.
But I want to be your brother.
Because you are too much.
Okay, thank you very much.
Really, thank you.
Let's have a drink.
Don't shout.
Jiu Jiu, have a safe trip.
Have a safe trip.
Cheers.
I have you
Thank you three old men for getting me together with my brother.
Let him finally see my tenderness.
Today is the first time I watch movies with my brother.
Although he didn't invite me
But it was intended by the old man.
But I still feel very happy.
The old man is about to leave.
I hope that after she arrives in Shangri-La,
she can meet another Xiaorou.
She can live happily like a fairy tale.
You two, take good care of my sister.
Or else I'll beat you up.
Don't worry, Xiao Jiao.
As long as I have time, I'll be with you.
Xiao Jiao, don't worry.
Although I really don't want you to leave,
if I can let you come back and cook with us,
I'll be angry with you on purpose.
And then I'll tell you.
You're so angry.
It's not the time yet.
You're still not convinced?
You're kidding.
Are you going to beat me up?
You...
You're my only disciple.
You have to be grateful and considerate.
Remember that every dish has a name.
I remember.
If you have time, call us.
I will.
By the way, Xiao Jiao,
this watch with the girl's name on it
is a souvenir for you.
I won't do anything
that will hurt other people's feelings anymore.
One day,
I'll be proud of you.
Okay.
Thank you.
Okay, that's enough.
I'm leaving.
Take care.
Goodbye.
I'm leaving. Bye.
My longing for you
is like a kite that's broken.
An angel will come and love you for me.
I'll be by your side.
The most beautiful treasure in life
is those forgotten times.
Although we're poor, we only have happiness.
Wearing the old clothes.
We'll wait until the end.
We don't need any reason.
There's too much distance.
We can't be with you.
We'll wait until the end.
There's no excuse.
When you need it most,
you can always have it.
There's a saying
that you don't need to say.
You'll never hesitate.
You'll reach out your hand.
You'll be my wind.
You'll be my rain.
You'll teach me to stop and walk forward.
We've been hurt before.
There's a sorrow in the wound.
You'll be by my side.
We'll cry and drink.
We'll shout together.
We'll keep our mouth shut.
We'll stay on the street drunk.
We'll wait until the end.
We don't need any reason.
There's too much distance.
We can't be with you.
We'll wait until the end.
There's no excuse.
When you need it most,
you can always have it.
We'll wait together.
We'll wait.