You
Uncle
I'll take you to the villa for a visit
Okay
I'll take you to the basketball court of the school
You should be very interested
You
I'll tell you
Uncle, do you want to play basketball together?
Yes
Only one person left to play the game
I don't have clothes
Uncle, don't you dare?
What are you talking about?
Come on, come on
Uncle, come on, go
Come on, come on, come on
Come on, come on
Who is this?
That one, that one, that one
That's the uncle who is going to marry Hua Yuexi
How do you know?
I don't know either
Hua Yuexi is my boyfriend
Yes, he came to Shanghai to find a girl he likes
You are so handsome
You are so good at playing basketball
You are just like a passer-by
I didn't see you
Is that your taste?
It's a pity
A salary of one month for a shopkeeper
How many life jackets can you buy?
Just look at it
Come on, come on
Come on
Uncle, he is leaving
What's wrong?
Uncle
Come on, Xiaojiu!
How can I let Xiaojiu take it away?
She's the new girl I love.
Come on, Xiaojiu!
Jiu Yi!
What do you think?
Do you like it?
When did you become a male director?
I met a male director by chance.
When Zhu Chang chose the right one.
How will the picture be taken?
Next time, I'll watch you perform.
No.
Jiu Yi, come here.
How many did you get?
One.
I got one.
Yiping, your brother needs a towel.
Okay.
Thank you.
You're quite special.
Don't you remember?
I'm the limit.
Hua Youxi.
What were you thinking?
How could you put the matter of Xiaojiu and Ding Xiaorou
on the internet without the consent of the person?
What were you thinking?
No wonder all the girls are like flowers today.
They keep fighting with the outsiders.
You're the one who's to blame.
Mr. Tang, I'm just using the simplest way
to help my uncle find a new lover.
You're just playing around.
What are you waiting for?
No.
He's just doing it for the good of the world.
Uncle Kang understands me.
All of you misunderstand me.
If I were Ding Xiaorou,
I would be so embarrassed if so many girls like my boyfriend.
Look.
It's so popular on the internet.
There are many girls.
Mom, you have to see if Ding Xiaorou has replied.
That's too many.
Look, Xiaojiu.
What a famous girl, Ding Xiaorou.
The one who misses you every moment.
This is the most disgusting.
The one who can't forget her affectionate night.
It's not her.
She won't tell the truth.
Xiaojiu, don't be disappointed.
I posted the post on Weibo this morning.
Maybe she hasn't had time to read it this morning.
She should have searched it in three days.
Your method is too illogical.
I'll call Mr. Liao.
I'll search it on the school's list.
I agree.
What do you mean?
You didn't date and you didn't vote.
All right.
I know you're worried about me.
But who's wronged?
If there's a reason, we'll find it out.
Let's go.
You're not happy, are you?
She's just pretending.
Actually, she cares about her feelings.
She came to Shanghai just to find her.
Now she knows that she's in love with someone.
She must be very worried.
She's very worried.
Don't talk about Xiaojiu.
I'm telling you.
Go and check on Xiaorou.
Report to me in the afternoon.
Be careful.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
I don't know what happened to the brakes.
Let me check.
You should be fine.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Take it if you like it.
Is this a gift for me?
You can take it or not.
I don't want it.
Why?
You don't like it?
I've never received a flower before.
Is this the first time or not?
I don't know.
Well...
If you don't want it...
Forget it.
I'm leaving.
So soon?
I'm going to Shanghai.
I'm hungry.
I'm going to Shanghai to study.
Congratulations.
Have you ever heard of Wuhan University?
No.
But it must be a good university.
I've been learning painting for so many years.
I wanted to get into the art department there.
Now I can finally realize my dream.
That's great.
Have you ever been to Shanghai?
No.
I've never been there.
Will you go there?
I'll go.
I have nothing to do.
You can be a chef.
No.
Shanghai is a high-class place.
How can I go there?
Why not?
How can it not be possible?
For young people, there's nothing impossible.
I think you can walk out of the kitchen
and be a chef who is face to face with the guests.
Then you can see
the feelings of the guests when they eat your food.
You can communicate with them.
The more you do, the better.
Really?
You look so handsome in the chef's uniform.
It's a pity that you can't be seen by others.
Are you kidding me?
I'm serious.
I'm really serious.
Beautiful flowers.
Hey, let's go.
Mom, are you really going to stay up all night?
No matter how big the problem was,
you and dad never had a break.
My future son-in-law is going to eat at the restaurant.
Yingdong is a rich young man.
He must be eating at some high-class restaurants.
I'm afraid he's not used to the crowd.
You bought this new dress, right?
I bought it especially for Yingdong.
Did you buy it for Yingdong?
He has a lot of fashion brands.
He took me to one of the shops.
It's free.
You're so generous.
You're so kind.
Mom, what are you talking about?
I'm always close to you and dad.
Look at this.
How is this flower?
I bought it from the flower market this morning.
Jiajia's boyfriend is coming.
I want him to leave a good impression on us.
Look at your dad.
He's been raising his daughter for more than 20 years.
I hope you can be happy.
Find someone who really understands you and loves you.
After all, we are parents.
We have our parents.
I'm relieved that he can take care of you on behalf of us.
What are you talking about?
It sounds like you're married.
Jiajia,
Actually,
Mom and Dad don't want you to be filial to us.
We just hope he can love you with all his heart.
We just hope he can love you and not bully you.
Yingdong won't bully me.
That's good.
What time is it?
Can't you find him?
Call him quickly.
I'll be right there.
It's so late.
You should have called me if you didn't want to come.
He must have been delayed on the way.
You're late when you first met your parents.
I think he doesn't care about you at all.
It's okay.
It must be because he's too busy with work.
Mom and Dad can understand.
Let's wait a little longer.
I'm sorry.
Wanjia, did I bother you?
Yingdong, you're here.
Come in and sit.
We've been waiting for an hour.
Xiaoqiu, you're here just in time.
Help me with the opera.
Pretend to be my boyfriend.
Hurry up.
Please.
I'll go get some water.
Uncle, auntie, I'm sorry.
I just got in the car.
It's okay.
I'll go get you some food.
I'll help you.
How can that be?
It's okay to let a woman come in the kitchen.
You can sit here and wait for the food to be served.
It's okay.
Let's sit together.
Come on.
I'm so embarrassed.
Xiaojia, come here.
I didn't expect Yingdong to be so sensible.
He's not like the second-generation
I don't know if it suits your taste.
It's okay.
My family has always liked to keep things in their stomachs
and not say anything.
They're always happy.
Now that you're here,
we can rest assured.
If there's anything that my family doesn't say,
you can come to us directly.
We're a family now.
Right.
Actually,
there's something I can't say.
Just say it.
I'm not Yingdong.
Then who are you?
My name is Hua Shanmao.
I'm Meng Jun's brother.
I came to see you today
because I saw the magazine's report.
I didn't expect to meet you.
I'm so happy to see you.
I didn't expect to meet Wanjia.
Jiajia, what's going on?
I don't think Jiajia did it on purpose.
I'm sorry. I won't lie.
You didn't do anything wrong, Xiaojia.
You can't always replace Yingdong.
You'll be exposed one day.
Did he tell you the reason?
He hasn't answered his phone.
He set the date today.
He said he would come.
Xiaojia,
can you tell me why he did it?
Maybe he was trying to escape.
Men are afraid of
having a relationship.
Why didn't you ask him?
I don't dare.
I'm afraid
he might say something about my relationship with him.
Then it's over.
It's hard to be in love.
Sometimes,
you should be careful to maintain a relationship.
You should be honest.
You should be careful to maintain a relationship.
Don't worry about others.
Xiaojia,
have you ever thought about it?
Maybe Ding Xiaorou is trying to escape from you.
He knows you're looking for him, but he won't show up.
Will you give up waiting for him?
I'm a positive person.
Thank you.
The works crummy must still be in the store.
It's now or never?
I didn't go.
Why?
Jiajia is in a bad mood.
She went to the movies with her.
But she still can't smile.
How could she break up with Yingdong?
Who said I was going to break up?
I'm sorry.
I've spread my bad mood to you.
I'm not angry because of this.
Can you be a little bit more positive?
Yingdong doesn't even want to see her parents.
Why are you with her?
I'm sorry.
Wait.
I'll call Yingdong right now
and scold him for you.
It's okay.
Hello?
Little Yingdong.
Wei Wei.
I'm Wei Wei.
What do you mean?
Why don't you go to see your parents?
I'm telling you.
We're going to graduate soon.
After we graduate,
everyone will be able to be a handsome man
like Bai Fumei.
Don't regret it when that happens.
You don't have to explain it to me.
Wan Nian, let me...
Let me break up with you right now.
Right now.
No, no, no.
Kang Wei Wei.
You're good.
You're even playing with me, right?
Mr. He.
Just let her go.
Ding Yi.
You betrayed me.
She wants to marry you.
I didn't even go to the cooking class.
I just spent the first day with you.
You have no conscience.
Enough, enough.
Let's go eat.
Are you asking me to cook for you again?
Of course not.
I'm taking a class.
Wan Nian wants to try Xiao Qiu's cooking.
Let's go now.
Now?
It's almost 12 o'clock.
It must be closed.
That's right.
Xiao Qiu didn't go to work today.
As long as you believe,
everything is possible.
I can't let you be unhappy for another day.
Let's go.
Ding Yi.
Why did you bring us here so late?
You'll know soon enough.
Welcome.
Thank you.
You're still working at this hour?
Why are you like this?
Don't stand there. Come in.
I have news.
You wrote this night's performance.
For me?
Why, Xiao Qiu?
Because I want you to be happy.
I'm so happy.
Have a good wedding.
Don't be mad at me, okay?
I really didn't want to forget you.
I had a meeting this afternoon.
But my phone was in the car.
So I didn't have time to inform you.
I knew you were doing this for work.
You asked Ding Yi to let me come here.
I'm not afraid that you'll be angry and won't come.
I haven't eaten yet.
Let's eat together, okay?
Come on in.
I'll go set up.
I'm leaving.
Did you discuss this with Ying Dong?
You just arrived at the flower shop.
He sent me a note.
Romance is a game played by rich people.
Do you think this is love?
Isn't it good to be happy?
I think I'm a little hungry.
I'll cook you a meal.
Can I have a meal with you?
No problem.
You asked Xiao Jiu to kick me?
How is that possible?
I told you I was in a hurry.
I just ran into Xiao Jiu.
That's why I used this method.
Besides, Xiao Jiu denied it.
It's okay.
Who told me not to be handsome?
Next time I want to see your parents,
I'm afraid they won't recognize me.
No way.
As long as you're willing to believe them,
you're more handsome than anyone else.
Look at Xiao Jiu in this dress.
So handsome.
No wonder the girls on the school website
are all fascinated by him.
Yes.
Many girls in our school like him.
They say Xiao Jiu looks like a star.
I could tell when I played basketball that day.
Okay.
The dishes are ready.
Thank you, Xiao Jiu.
Xiao Jiu, you're so good at cooking.
You're better than all the flavors I've eaten before.
Have you ever thought of changing your work environment
to seek a bigger development space?
I think this is pretty good.
It's comfortable.
I'll be honest with you.
If you continue working here,
you'll always be a second-rate chef.
I'm very close to the owner of this restaurant.
I can help you build it
and make you a fashion star.
You'll be a star in the fashion and the catering industry.
You'll gain a lot of fame.
Xiao Jiu, think about it.
Yin Dong has a sharp eye in business.
So? Are you interested?
A thousand miles of horseback is necessary for a man to enjoy.
Trust me.
I know.
I hope the guests are not my name
because I cooked them.
I'm satisfied with your food.
I'm happy with it.
So...
I don't need it anymore.
Okay.
Xiao Jiu is so good at cooking.
It's okay if you don't like it.
I'm just a suggestion.
I know.
Thank you.
Thank you for looking up to me.
Okay.
Take your time.
Do you like this?
Are you giving me flowers?
Yes.
But you can also not.
This is my first time to receive flowers.
You can't count them.
I can't count them.
Then I won't.
Forget it.
Don't waste your time.
It's a bunch of flowers.
Come on, handsome.
Look here.
Okay.
Just like this.
La judge.
The other way is right here.
Okay.
That's it.
That's great.
Come on, handsome.
Look here.
It's a pity that you don't become a celebrity.
You're a good boy.
The beauty of the kitchen.
This is great.
It's great.
Thank you so much.
You're welcome.
I just don't like to hide talents.
It's great that Samo is almost done.
Do you want him to come and say hello?
No.
He doesn't like me.
You're so generous.
I just want to prove that my point is right.
I'll get this picture on different websites.
When this chef becomes famous,
you can change the list of new talents.
Okay.
Look at my brother. He's so handsome.
He's been on the magazine cover for interviews.
The beauty of the kitchen?
You've already told me that a dozen times.
You have such an excellent brother.
Can't I be more proud of him?
You can be proud, but there's a gap.
Come and take a look.
I'm sorry.
My brother was so excited when he saw me.
Let me tell you.
My brother is very, very good.
He's very good in every aspect.
In this big Shanghai,
you can't find a few people like my brother.
I think it's pretty good.
Sister.
Come.
Hurry up.
Sit down.
This is my brother. This is Sisi.
He's two years younger than you when he works in the bank.
Hello.
Why didn't you tell me about this?
I said I'd come here to eat.
You didn't tell me about this.
Your sister is also a good person.
That's right.
She's been single for so long, so...
Miss.
I'm sorry.
I really didn't know that today was our blind date.
I didn't want to waste your time.
I'm not suitable for you.
I hope you can find your happiness soon.
I'm sorry.
If I had known, I wouldn't have come.
Sisi, wait a minute.
Stop chasing.
How could you do this?
You abandoned a good girl like that.
You're so ridiculous.
The thing is, if you reject a woman in public,
she'll be very sad.
I don't want to be left out.
I'm telling you.
The school didn't even name Ding Xiaorou after the investigation.
Maybe even the name is fake.
I'm telling you.
You have to fall in love once before you forget your past love.
Do you know that when I was young,
I did this kind of thing a lot?
The men who chased me,
the cards I gave them,
they were all fake.
Wake up!
She's not like you.
What's different?
She's not the kind of girl you think she is.
Okay, okay.
I'm going back to work.
I...
I know.
Okay?
I'm leaving.
Bye.
He's so annoying.
He's so angry that he's making me angry.
And I'm the one who's not angry anymore.
I'm going back to work.
I'll call you later.
Okay.
Okay?
Bye.
Hi.
You are?
Can I ask you to give me something?
Yes, you can.
Look, he's just a handsome guy.
He's more handsome than the magazine.
Yes, he's really handsome.
If Dingding has a handsome guy like him
who can cook for me,
I'll be worth it in this life.
Eat up.
Xiao Xiao.
You don't like any of these?
What kind of girl do you like?
Look at my watch.
It's a little girl.
You have a name for yourself.
That's what you call a beautiful life.
I know.
You want me to read a book.
I'm not helping you introduce your girlfriend.
Are you annoying?
Are you a normal guy?
Xiao Jiu.
This time, I have to stand on the right side of the game.
And I've checked it out.
There's no one like Ding Xiaorou.
I don't believe it.
I can't find anyone with the ability to play games.
The only explanation is that
she's your fantasy.
You've been in love with a fantasy person.
You're just a delusion.
Why are you talking to Xiao Jiu?
What's wrong?
Xiao Jiu has her own secret.
There's no Ding Xiaorou.
Let's talk about it later.
Okay.
I'm tired.
I'm going to sleep.
I'm really doing this for you.
I've been looking for you for so many days.
You said you didn't have any.
Xiao Jiu, I know you're all being bullied by me.
I know.
I'm not going to let you go.
You've been bullying me for 500 years.
I'm going to teach you a lesson.
I'm looking forward to the best for you.
I will have a good ending.
When you need me the most,
I can be your guardian angel in heaven.
Da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da
Yi bai
We are the best, we don't need any reason
There are too many things in your heart, but you are the one I love
When you need me the most, you can always accept me
In our times, together
Thanks for watching!