I was thinking about what to do...
Normally I'm most attached to my life.
But I don't want to make my life more stressful.
Don't you want to go to the capital?
해요
I'm not done yet.
Yes, yes.
But I think we should stop those unnecessary messages.
This is the most painful thing for me now.
Yu Yi, maybe one of you brothers will be very happy.
I'll take responsibility for this.
You're not the kind of person to be nice.
You're not fair to you.
I think you should call your brother out and take responsibility.
Contact Youxi and ask her to come here.
It's okay. It will be okay.
Trust me.
What's wrong?
Your phone has a message.
Mr. Shi Liang is looking for me.
Let's go.
Okay.
Xiao Qiao, Hua Youxi is leaving.
Playing games like women.
Hua Youxi playing games.
Playing parallel games like women.
Playing games like women.
The The rope line is wrong.
I can help you to get out of there too.
What's wrong with you?
It's wrong but it is because you are losing contact with my characters.
Play games! Play games!
Mr. Yang.
I think before we start the discussion,
do you have something to say to Miss.
Eddie?
With sincerity.
I'm sorry.
I think the person you're most sorry for is not me.
Brother.
I'm sorry for making you and mom worried.
It's okay.
There's always a way to reduce the loss.
I've thought about it.
I'm a bad person anyway.
Do you think Hua Youxi is very good?
Hua Youxi!
What the hell are you playing?
I'm not as good as you.
Do you want to know why?
Because I never got pregnant.
Are you stupid?
Are you scared?
All your pocket money is with me.
Even your eyes.
You can only see my eyebrows.
Are you a man?
Hua Youxi!
I've been playing with you from the beginning to the end.
Hua Youxi, I'm playing with you!
I'm going to turn you into a piece of shit.
Today, all the people who were fooled by Hua Youxi,
I declare.
I'll help you double your pay.
I'm not sure if I can be the second.
Who dares to be the first?
Hua Youxi!
Let's go.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
You're so stupid.
Let's go.
How will you face the game in the future?
I have authority to decide the fate of my first love.
it's enough
Keep going!
explanation
The most beautiful treasure in life is the past.
Although the poor only have happiness,
the old clothes are still on my body.
The winter that is still hot and snowy
is singing three songs.
The summer night that is full of warmth
is floating in the wind.
Now we have changed,
we are busy with life.
But when you think of the past,
your eyes will shine.
Thank you, I don't hate games anymore.
Actually, a man who is emotional and willful,
and has poor management skills,
is not necessarily a bad person.
Otherwise, Mei Bao wouldn't treat him like this.
I really appreciate Mengjie.
Do you know why I will sing the songs she likes tonight?
Because she told me that
when she was young, she had expectations for love.
Although she was disappointed every time,
her heart was always full of tears,
and she was always fighting.
This is my mother.
She is a young girl who has not grown up.
Mengjie told me that
everyone makes mistakes,
but they have to be brave.
Even if it is a wrong beginning,
there will be a happy ending.
Sometimes the fate of two people is really a little bit worse.
But it is because of that little bit,
that there is a difference in nature.
I'm sorry.
Actually, I don't regret at all meeting you in Shanghai.
I don't regret either.
We used to know each other.
And because of my words,
you can become a revolution.
Monitor.
I have a request. Can you promise me?
Can I have a first love dream for you?
What is it like?
When you miss me, write to me.
Instead of texting and calling,
when we go out on a date,
hold each other's hands.
Even if you don't say a word, you can hear each other's heartbeat.
When you send me home,
give me a big hug or a kiss.
When I get old,
when I think of your eyes,
I will proudly say to myself,
I have a very happy first love.
Okay.
My new album is called Little Love.
This album is dedicated to the first love of youths in the world.
My first love is a young man who is a little girl.
I am a little girl.
My first love is a beautiful misunderstanding.
But the handsome monitor has always stayed in the heart of the spoiled girl.
Love has overcome all the noise.
Let the love of Jenny become the love of today.
Let me love again.
Even if he doesn't fall in love,
he can find his first love's dream.
It is the greatest happiness in my life.
Where isapped?
Where are you taking it, little, raccoon?
I am beginning to hate on you.
And you are not difficult.
Would youopa give me a kiss me?
What a видue!
Andrey,
Do you believe it?
Stop it.
If I were you, I would go to the treasure house and find her.
What she did for you is a man's pride, a woman's failure.
Hey, she lied to me.
I've been like a ghost for the last two months.
I haven't calmed down.
I'll make you feel bad.
Don't make a fuss.
Come to me.
Son, if you're not feeling well,
you can take my mother's medicine.
Enough, mom.
Stop it.
You've got it all wrong.
I'll erase it from my memory.
Women have a problem with love.
They have a problem with their brains.
Yes.
Some women are going through a lot with you.
They want to get back their first love.
What's wrong with you?
Are you in a bad mood?
No.
By the way,
how are you and Yingdong?
I'm fine.
Don't worry.
I'll talk to Yingdong later.
Let's see what he thinks.
At worst, I'll quit.
Don't worry.
I'm fine.
Mom,
can you give this to Xiao'ai for me?
I want to do something romantic every day.
This is romantic enough.
Mom will help you with the delivery.
I'm going to take a shower.
I'm going to work.
It seems that men have to suffer from setbacks at work.
That's why God made up for it in love.
Will you fall in love with a woman
for her first love?
Me?
How difficult it is for a man to fall in love with a beautiful woman.
I'm afraid that Yingdong is still a famous singer.
Why are you all looking at me?
I'm not that curious.
I'm afraid that Ding Yi
is afraid that he won't pursue other girls for Wanjia.
Isn't it good to change like this now?
And if Yingdong knows about this,
he may change his mind
and help our V-Live restaurant again.
So that everyone will be happy.
I'm happy for my brother.
What a good woman!
Good women are not fashionable at this time.
Good women are bullied by you boys.
Mom,
if you meet the person you loved,
will you adjust yourself
and fall in love with her again?
It depends on whether your mother is willing to do it.
Go.
Give me back the treasure.
Take it.
I haven't come to Li's house for two months.
So?
Hua Yuxin, don't you remember what you did?
No, mom, listen to me.
I really drank too much last night.
I don't know if I have any...
What is that?
Really?
I don't need you to be responsible.
I'll take care of you from now on.
I'll take care of everything.
Take a dress when you go out.
So you won't catch a cold.
Put your hands here.
Okay?
You have to rub it and hold it.
Okay.
That's a man.
It's the first time you've held my hand so seriously.
It's great to have you.
What did you say?
My boyfriend didn't say anything.
I can't talk.
My friend Hua Yuxin is very unhappy today.
So let's go to the bar and have a good bath.
We'll have a good bath tomorrow morning.
It's a good man, right?
Hua Yuxin, play games.
Play games until you're tired.
Yuxin, come on!
I'm tired.
I've been playing with you from the beginning.
I'm playing with you, Hua Yuxin!
Hua Yuxin.
I've never thought I'd remember this feeling in my life.
There are still many things I haven't told you.
Do you think Hua Yuxin will come?
What a good excuse, right?
She doesn't have to break up with me.
We can break up.
I'm sorry.
Daddy.
Why are you so angry?
Daddy, let's go to the movies together.
I haven't seen the movie with you for a long time.
Let's cultivate our artistic talent.
You want me to change my attitude towards movies?
I don't like your skills.
I won't agree to be a producer.
I'll make you breakfast.
Chenyin.
I'm coming.
You're always so cold-hearted.
Do you think the whole world is for your money?
Don't worry.
I'm not that kind of person.
When people fall in love, they become fools.
You have to believe your father.
You haven't been in love for a long time, right?
Do you remember me now?
Daddy.
The CEO of Chinese and American companies, Nisa.
The CEO of Chinese and American companies, Zheng Jing.
And the one I loved when I was ten years old.
Ma Yueming.
He's still texting you.
Why don't you talk to him?
Daddy.
I'll ask you to fall in love.
If you don't like mature women.
I can accept someone my age.
I'll be your matchmaker.
Don't be so dramatic.
Are you done?
For a Kang Zirui.
My daughter's quality and level.
Has already fallen to the bottom.
Victor.
Is Victor here?
Mr. Wu.
Didn't you tell me before.
That the lady was a producer.
It's too late.
What's the situation now?
You can't destroy my first love.
Daddy doesn't want you to fall in love.
But you can change your partner.
Break up with Kang Zirui.
Change another person.
Come back from the beginning.
With who?
Yingdong.
Didn't you like him before?
I've forgotten him.
You can forget Yingdong.
Then you can forget Kang Zirui.
Daddy.
Please respect my first love.
No one's first love can be broken.
You.
You have the right to correct your first love.
Start over.
Even if I start over.
I will choose Kang Zirui.
And I believe.
Kang Zirui is reluctant to leave me.
I tell you.
Don't force me to work with outsiders.
To deal with you.
Once I block your economy.
You are nothing.
Who is better?
Your breakfast is so bad.
I can swallow it.
Why can't you hear what daddy says?
Get out of the way.
This kid.
Hello.
Haven't you got up yet?
It's almost nine o'clock.
I came back at six o'clock in the morning.
What's wrong?
If you fall in love again.
Will you choose me?
What?
Who is the first person you fell in love with?
Why do you ask this?
I just want to know.
I know it's not me.
I don't remember.
But you are always my first choice.
Can you hear me, Kang Zirui?
We can't lose to daddy.
I'm sorry, something came up, I think.
I'm so sorry.
I wasn't mean before.
But what can you do in my current situation?
But my man brother i can listen to you.
And he is always my first choice.
But I do not understand that.
But I'm always your first choice.
Now i understand you.
I usually like this kind of compromise,
that they just want to met you.
But at the moment you are loving each other.
They usually love each other.
I'm not a friend of yours.
I don't want to be your enemy.
Why?
I'm not a friend of yours.
I know that you want to find a Ouyang Qiao.
But for me,
it's not easy to find another Amber.
I like smart and straightforward people.
Take this for me.
Don't worry.
I didn't put this on my mind.
Really?
You and Victor have proved your worth.
From now on, you can tell my father's opinion from his mouth.
And how he sees my emotional problems.
Amber, you're so generous.
You don't have to be so smart with me.
I will definitely make it up to you in the future.
Did anything happen today that has to do with me?
Yes.
Han Ding Yi has given the first love letter to the express delivery company.
He said he wanted to see me.
Is it possible?
Next.
I didn't get anything in return.
But Hua You Xi didn't get anything back.
So, Hua You Xi is smarter than Big Brother.
Who would want to get back the money?
Next.
And about the V-Log restaurant.
Han Ding Yi and Ying Dong are both stubborn.
They didn't find the way.
Han Ding Yi can't communicate with you.
Ying Dong can't communicate with me either.
I'm not a friend of yours.
Because you can communicate with me, Ying Dong can't communicate with me.
So, this game will be over sooner or later.
Next.
Eddie agreed to have a concert.
Hua You Xi is responsible for the publicity of this concert.
Hua You Xi is really lucky.
Yes.
I don't know what he has remembered in his last life.
Come on, let me help you.
Sit down.
I'll help you.
Come on.
It's too fast.
Come on, let me help you.
Okay.
Your father has a great idea today.
It's delicious.
Wei Wei, I've always loved to eat my food.
I made it with my heart.
That's right.
You can apply for a non-futuristic cultural heritage for every dish.
Then I'll eat first.
Jia Jia didn't come back today.
You should eat more for her.
Wei Wei.
Jia Jia and Ying Dong are fine, right?
Yes, they are.
Ying Dong even pushed her to the European Exhibition.
Really?
That's great.
You all have grown up.
You are flying further and further.
That's a good thing.
The younger people walk more.
The more you meet, the more you know.
The more friends you make, the more you know.
Don't worry.
Even if they all leave, I will stay here.
Because I have to eat the dishes that Wan Ba makes.
I'm afraid we don't have much of this opportunity.
The landlord here has to increase the rent.
And it's three times higher than before.
I called Jia Jia back this time.
I want to discuss with her about our future problems.
Now the restaurants are all on the path of the young people.
We don't know how to invest in this old book.
Thank you.
Xiao Ai, hello.
This is the first time I wrote to a girl in my life.
I grew up in front of the computer.
I'm too unwell.
Can we start dating?
I'm trying to find the impression of you in middle school.
I saw you eat soy milk and pancakes several times.
Can we start our date from breakfast?
I'm not sure.
I don't know.
Can we start our date from breakfast?
I'm not good at speaking.
I can't think of a blank paper between the paper and the brain.
I don't know what to write.
Let's meet and talk.
Waiting for your reply.
Monitor Han Dingyi.
Dear monitor Dingyi.
I imagined the feeling of receiving your letters in my dreams.
It's great.
As happy as I imagined.
I imagined how many times I had breakfast with you before going to school.
Or I went to the library with you after class.
You may say I'm stupid.
But can you take me as I loved you?
We went out together in school uniforms.
I want to find the feeling of being in the school.
That's the time I miss the most.
Love is invincible.
I want to buy a ticket.
Hello, 160 yuan.
Here you are.
Thank you.
Welcome again.
Dingyi.
This is the order of the big deal we discussed last month.
The harvest time is next quarter.
I want to confirm with you.
Should we cancel it with the other party?
Now I want to sell the fund.
Don't worry.
I won't give up until I'm satisfied.
I can't be like you.
I have everything here.
Dingyi, Xiaojian.
Mr. Sun.
What's the matter?
I have a good news and a bad news to tell you.
Which one do you want to hear?
Good news.
There are enough bad news.
The good news is that our vlog is saved.
Really?
What do you mean?
Mom and dad's rent is too high.
So they plan to rent out their restaurant.
The money will be used to invest in our vlog restaurant.
Really?
Really.
Weiwei, you're here.
I'm here to help.
Meng Zeyu is a good person.
He came in the afternoon.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Love really makes people do a lot of incredible things.
We're not in love.
Who told you to come?
Well, Weiwei.
I think you're busy today.
I'm afraid you can't get a job.
So I came to help.
I'm standing in front of you.
I'm holding the tools you usually use.
I'm sitting on the dishes you usually cook.
I can feel what happiness is.
Jia Yin, are you copying me?
No, but...
When I see you, I feel the energy.
There are so many flowers in the shop.
There are many peach blossoms.
Even the
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Hello, I'm Weiwei, the agent of V-Luv.
We will continue to follow the order of the European import flowering.
But the payment is not the British Group.
I will complete the
This afternoon, Yin Dong and his friends at the painting workshop
went to the museum to talk about selling oil paintings.
To meet all the success.
In addition to talent,
they have to depend on human relations.
Of course.
Now this business society,
if you have no value,
I don't want to talk to you.
Yin Zhou is so tired.
You seem to be in a good mood today.
I'm fine.
Your parents said they couldn't reach you today.
They'll come back tomorrow.
I was with Yin Dong at the club this afternoon.
My phone was out of battery.
What's wrong? Did they want to talk to you?
They came to see how Viola is doing.
They want to invest the money in Viola.
If that's the case,
we can continue to dream about Ding Yin.
What do you think?
I thought Viola would close down.
I didn't expect to convince my parents to invest today.
I think it's because of the opportunity
that God gave to Ding Yin.
I'm really happy that I can help him
keep his dreams.
I'm sorry.
I hope everything goes well.
Take care.
Why are you not talking so soon?
I'm here to return the car keys.
No more toilet fees.
I don't have to keep the car.
Oh?
In the wall?
That Loy, that guy from the
crime police brigade killed onerovchikov,
You are my friend in my heart.
I didn't expect you to care so much about your girlfriend.
You beat me for her.
And you gave up your flower shop.
I didn't expect you to care so much about Wan Jia.
Wan Jia is my girlfriend.
It's a man's duty to protect his woman.
I don't care what you think.
You invested in my flower shop.
And I managed it.
You are my trust.
I appreciate you.
Don't think too much.
I'm too busy.
I didn't have time to care about the flower shop.
The flower shop is too small for me.
I must find someone to take care of it.
Even without you, I will find someone else.
I know.
I'll tell you.
You don't have to come here in person.
Just ask someone to send you here.
It's okay.
I'm willing to come here.
I'm not as busy as you.
The most important thing is
no matter how much you miss me
I treat you as my best friend.
I don't want our relationship to be changed.
Dong Qing.
I didn't put the past in the past.
I'm too busy at home.
I didn't have time to care about the flower shop.
I'll take care of it sooner or later.
I understand.
I can't keep your dream.
It's my biggest regret.
Maybe I can ask the bank
to pay you.
No need.
I found my self-esteem.
The parents of the player decided to give up the restaurant
and put the money in my account.
I'm sorry.
Boss.
I'm sorry I'm late.
I want to find my dream.
I must get back to the way I was.
Will you go on a date with me?
Of course.
Because you are really extraordinary.
I'll treat you to breakfast.
I'm sorry.