Mr. Jiang.
Sign it,
and I'll make sure your position
at Lu Group is secure.
My dad is already old.
Fan, you are still young.
The Lu Group will be yours
sooner or later.
Why the rush?
Besides, Chairman Lu treats me well.
I won't betray him.
You need to know
which way the wind's blowing.
There isn't that much friendship
in business.
They...
Don't think I'm the same as them!
You want to take control of the Lu Group.
Win the Zhongyu bid,
and you'll have
my full support from then on.
Don't worry. Have a seat first.
Sit.
You.
Good.
Very good.
Good for you.
Thank you, Mr. Jiang.
The board wants to remove me.
You're behind this.
From today on,
I will take full charge
of the company's affairs.
Seizing power?
Good.
Lu Fan,
I am your father!
It's because you are my father
that I'm giving you this chance.
Cancel today's wedding.
Cancel it?
You can't just call it off.
What about the Lu family's reputation?
It's your wedding.
How you deal with it is up to you.
I won't do it for you.
Mr. Lu,
there's a problem
with the Zhongyu Group's bidding.
It's been ten years.
This is the price you're paying
for my mother's death.
If you don't cherish this opportunity,
think about
what else you have left to pay with.
Are you threatening me?
It's not a threat.
It's just letting you know.
Xia.
The wedding is about to begin.
Are you ready?
Ready for what?
To watch you put on
a show of sisterly love?
Xia.
There were things
I couldn't tell you before.
But now you need to understand—
I never did any of this
for myself,
and certainly not for wealth or status.
It's to end it,
once and for all.
I will finish this in my own way.
Remember.
No matter what happens today,
no matter what you hear,
protect yourself well
and stay far away from here.
Enough, Su Dong.
Stop your hypocrisy.
You are about to wear this dress,
go out to accept everyone's blessings,
and become the glamorous Mrs. Lu.
Finish it?
What a great excuse.
What a noble sacrifice.
It's just
a fig leaf for your vanity.
What you can't bear
to let go of is this immense wealth
and your title as Mrs. Lu.
Do you even realize
everything you have has come
at the cost of Dad's life?
And you still want me
to understand and thank you
from the bottom of my heart?
I don't need your instructions.
Look at your expression.
It's just like the wedding dress on you,
making me feel they
are both cheap and disgusting.
Since you've chosen to marry your enemy
and keep living your life of luxury,
I will walk my own path.
I don't need your hypocritical advice.
Have a happy marriage.
Welcome.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Please come in.
Mr. Zhang.
Thank you, Mr. Zhang.
Thank you.
It seems Lu Fan will
make a move before you do.
The result he wants
is different from what I want.
Looking forward to it.
Quiet, everyone.
I'd like to introduce someone special.
This is Ms. Liang.
She has taken care of the Lu family
for 20 years
and is like family to us.
Today, she
has specially prepared a piano piece
for our wedding
as a gift.
Xia.
It's fake.
Everyone.
It's fake!
What you are seeing must be fake.
You know,
this photo has been doctored.
Someone is trying to frame me.
Dong,
explain it to everyone.
Explain it clearly.
Tell them it's fake.
Say something!
Everyone,
I, Lu Zhen'an, have let you all down.
Su Dong and I
have been in love for many years.
My brother
entrusted these two sisters
to me.
I know her character.
She is not that kind of person.
Otherwise, we wouldn't have
been together for so long.
Please rest assured.
Someone fabricated all of this
to frame me!
The wedding will go on.
Sorry for spoiling the mood.
Emcee.
Xia.
Hello, dear guests.
I am Su Xia, Ms. Su Dong's younger sister.
Today, on this joyous day,
I'd like to offer
my heartfelt blessings
to my adoptive father and my sister.
Brother.
Do you love me?
Yes, I do.
What about you?
Mr. Lu, what exactly is the relationship
between you and your sister, Su Xia?
If you had known your father
would marry her sister,
would you still be with her?
Would you still sleep with her, Mr. Lu?
Mr. Lu!
Please answer.
Mr. Lu! Mr. Lu!
Mr. Lu, say a few words.
Mr. Lu, say a few words, Mr. Lu!
Mr. Lu, please say a few words.
Mr. Lu! Mr. Lu! Mr. Lu!
Mr. Lu Zhen'an.
Ms. Su Dong.
Do you take each other in marriage,
to love, honor,
and cherish one another,
in sickness
and in health,
for as long as you both shall live?
You...
Su Xia.
If you've got a problem,
take it out on me.
Why do you hurt yourself like this?
Su Xia.
Why did you do this?
Brother,
you're here.
Why?
Because everyone
in the Lu family is guilty.
My medicine.
Ladies and gentlemen,
today I'd like you to listen
to a few short stories.
Su Dong, what are you trying to say?
The first story
is about a patent—
High-Efficiency Lithium-Ion Battery
Anode Material Manufacturing Technology.
Its inventor was Su Minghao.
He was my father...
and Su Xia's.
Shut up!
It's him.
Lu Zhen'an.
You were blinded by greed
and drove our father to his death.
The data must be changed
right before Su Minghao
submits the final report.
The parameters.
Right, the key stability parameters.
That's a shameless forgery!
Lu Zhen'an, calm down.
The show has just begun.
The bank is taken care of.
The bank will call in the loan
the day the test fails.
The press headline we've prepared is:
Genius Engineer Su Minghao
Exposed for Fraud
as Billion-Yuan Project Collapses.