I was like a fool.
Like a fool! Like a fool!
Every day I have to face the man
who killed my father
and force a smile at him.
Do you know what I've been through?
And now you actually want me to marry him?
My father trusted Lu Zhen'an so much.
He treated him like a real brother.
When he was at his lowest,
my father helped him so much.
And him?
How did he treat my father?
Watch your mouth.
What do you mean "killed"?
It was your father
who couldn't handle failure
and chose to end his own life.
That is the police's conclusion.
Understand?
You guys killed him.
Give me what you promised me!
Give it to me!
Remember.
Lu Zhen'an forced your father to death.
It has nothing to do with me.
And,
Lu Zhen'an also slept
with the woman I loved.
He forced me to be like a dog,
wagging my tail
and begging him.
We are in the same boat.
As long as you listen to me,
I will help you.
Xia?
What interesting things did you hear?
Don't touch her.
Butler Jiang,
let me talk to her.
Xia.
Let's go. Come with me. Let's go.
Let's go.
Xia?
Look at me.
It's okay.
It's okay. Don't be afraid.
Listen to me.
What you just heard—
the things Butler Jiang
and I said—
were all nonsense.
We were lying.
We said it out of anger.
Do you understand?
Don't believe a word of it.
Nonsense!
Forget it.
Just pretend you didn't hear anything
and nothing happened.
Dad...
Dad was sick.
He was in too much pain.
It had nothing to do with anyone else.
It had absolutely
nothing to do
with Uncle Lu and Butler Jiang.
Do you understand?
It had nothing to do with them.
Promise me.
Forget everything you just heard.
Xia?
Forget it completely.
Never ever
tell anyone.
Okay?
Including...
Brother Lu Fan.
You especially can't let him know.
Do you understand?
Xia.
Come on, promise me.
Promise me.
Promise me!
Was Dad really killed by them?
Are you really going to marry Lu Zhen'an?
I must marry him.
Xia.
I must continue on this path.
I have no way back.
When you grow up, you will understand me.
Got it?
Su Xia.
What's wrong?
They are getting married soon.
What about us?
Don't worry.
Leave it to me.
I'll take you somewhere.
Brother, where are we?
This is where I've come to be alone
since I was little.
A secret base?
Starting now,
it's no longer a secret.
This is my childhood doll.
That's my drawing.
Brother.
So,
was I once your secret too?
Everything in my heart is right here.
What about you?
Your secret...
Is it a bad memory?
Behave yourself!
Are you scared?
There is no turning back
if you want revenge.
This path has just begun.
You still have a choice.
I heard someone say that
if you want to forget bad memories,
you have to overwrite them with new ones.
In the future, I...
don't want to think about
those rainy nights anymore.
Think about what?
Don't ask,
and I don't want to answer.
You just need to...
I don't want to mention the past anymore.
But from now on,
I hope you won't lie to me again.
What are you doing?
You must give me that thing!
I'm telling you!
Don't point at me.
Only I can point at you.
Jiang Dahai!
Let me go! Let me go!
Let me go!
Just this once!
Take your money and get out!
Alright.
I will get out right now.
What are you doing?
What are you trying to do?
Keep your voice down.
If you are any louder,
that old dog will know everything.
You said it.
You said after you get the money,
you would get out.
Okay, don't worry.
The thing you want—
I have already given it to you.
I'm guessing
that you'll use the wedding
to expose Lu Zhen'an in public.
If I tell this plan of yours
to Lu Zhen'an in advance,
then wouldn't your efforts over the years
be in vain?
You are shameless!
Let me tell you!
The money I gave you is enough
for you to find young women
for the rest of your life!
Alright, alright.
Keep it down.
Those women are not like you.
You
are a woman who grew up
in a prestigious family.
As long as...
you let me get what I want,
I will take the check
and leave immediately.
Be a good girl.
Mrs. Lu.
Mrs. Lu,
nice working with you.