(The Wind Blows from Longxi)
(The Nineteenth Strategy Steal the Firewood from under the Pot)
(Li Yan's Villa in Nanzheng County, the Shu State)
Clerk Feng,
are you saying
(Li Yan's Villa in Nanzheng County, the Shu State)
it doesn't have to be
a real invasion by Wu?
As long as Chengdu receives such news,
with Prime Minister away,
His Majesty
will order General
to take care of it?
Yes.
Absolutely.
In that case,
I can move
the provisions
to the front against Wu
in the name of the upcoming war,
stealing the firewood from under their pot.
That's an act of treason!
Please hear me out, sir.
This is the third step of the plan.
Sir,
your wisdom and leadership
are unrivaled.
Without supplies,
even a strategist like Prime Minister
won't be able to do much.
The Northern Expedition
won't go anywhere,
let alone succeed.
Prime Minister
turns a blind eye to Wu
but insists on battling in the north
at the cost of innocent lives.
Master,
after this,
your political ambition
will be realized.
Clerk Feng,
you'll be rewarded the most
for our success.
I'll go through fire and water
for you,
General!
Chief Xun,
you need to eat.
Other than Gu Zheng,
Gao Tangbing, as Zhulong, must've had other help
to communicate with Wei.
That's why they had to silence him quickly.
With that being said,
even if someone was there to kill him,
he'd definitely put up a fight.
That day, when I interrogated him without you,
he confessed how he killed Li Miao.
Take a look.
Once frozen,
you'll be hit
for sure.
I know
I'm making a mistake
by jumping to the conclusion
before finding the evidence.
Judging from your tone,
Chief,
are you suspecting
Clerk Feng?
He's too suspicious!
Think about it.
Who could
kill Gao Tangbing in the Agency silently
except for him?
The way Gao Tangbing died
reminds me of Li Miao's murder,
which was also
Feng Ying's idea.
Gao Tangbing didn't know he'd be next.
Now, I start to feel bad for him.
By the way,
when I talked to Feng Ying earlier today,
I noticed some dirt
on his sleeve
which could be from the wall in the cell,
but I'm not sure of it.
I'll go inside and check again.
Thanks.
Be very careful.
I will.
Feng Ying's deadly trap
will finish Prime Minister.
Take that as his way
to thank me for saving his life.
He was held accountable
for Zhulong's case
and he would've
ended up like Ma Su.
I was surprised
when you vouched for him.
Turns out
it's all worth it.
But he can't be trusted.
Don't lower your guard.
He's having no mercy
on Prime Minister
regardless of
their past.
It's to our advantage, though.
Once Zhuge Liang's force sets out,
we can take action in Jiangzhou.
Yes, sir. I'll go there to take care of it.
No, you stay in Nanzheng
to take the third step.
Yes, sir.
Good day, Clerk.
Chen Gong.
Yes, sir.
Look,
you're General's disciple
and his old acquaintance's son.
I'll have to rely on you in the future.
You're flattering me, sir.
Your plan
is the key to our success.
The court in Chengdu
will see new faces soon.
I'm going to need your help
to gain a foothold.
Chen Gong, you're wonderful,
but too tactful.
I'll try not to be.
Clerk Feng.
Clerk Feng,
it's Pei Xu.
Chief Xun!
Look!
Do you remember
the wood plank that killed Gao Tangbing is chipped?
I found this on Clerk Feng's sleeve.
It proves
that he was in Gao Tangbing's cell.
But it's illegally obtained
and can no longer be used as evidence.
Now, we know it was him.
We can keep digging.
That fox
will give himself away eventually.
Right.
I'll talk to Chen Gong
about it.
Sure.
According to Liang Jian of Intelligence Agency,
Zhuge Liang has been allowed to leave.
His troop will soon arrive in Hanzhong
while we're busy battling Wu.
Sima Yi will keep Wu at bay,
but our defense along Mount Qi is weak.
Once Feng Ying steps down
and Chen Gong takes his place,
we'll know every move
of the Shu Army.
No need to worry about them.
How many members are left in Wuxian Sect?
About 4,000.
Despite heavy causalities,
we're deeply rooted in Hanzhong
after being here for more than 30 years.
Once the Wei troops arrive,
we'll be ready
to join the battle.
Good.
I need you to return to Hanzhong.
No problem.
Chen Gong is determined to get rid of Feng Ying,
but his sworn brother,
Xun Xu, in the Agency,
won't let Gao Tangbing's death go.
As long as he's there,
Chen Gong can be compromised.
He also
destroyed Wuxian Sect.
Chen Gong is too important to our strategy.
We can't take any risks.
Go to Nanzheng
and tell Chen Gong to kill Xun Xu.
Why him
as he's too close to Xun Xu
and too important to us?
He needs to take this step.
Poison on these three golden arrows
is highly toxic and it'll kill instantly.
Yes, sir.
I won't let you down.
(Chen Gong's Residence in Nanzheng County, the Shu State)
Xun Xu?
Come on in.
(Chen Gong's Residence in Nanzheng County, the Shu State)
What's up?
Do you need anything?
Can't I just check up on you?
I need
someone to talk to.
Sure. I'm listening.
Guess what I'm thinking of lately.
I'm also thinking of Yue every day.
No.
It's something else.
I'm wondering
what's the point of
doing what we do?
It's meaningless.
We're all against each other.
No one can be trusted.
Innocent people get killed all the time.
I don't get it.
We're at each other's throats for what?
To restore Han.
We talked about it.
I hope that's not just all talk.
You know,
Feng Ying said the same thing
when sending me to Tianshui to kill you.
He killed Gao Tangbing.
Xun Xu,
I know you're suspecting him...
I've got the evidence.
Pei Xu found it on his sleeve.
At least it proves
Feng Ying broke the wood plank
in Gao Tangbing's hand.
I checked. It's a match.
I know
it's not enough to convict Feng Ying,
but he's definitely a suspect.
Keep watching.
Leave nothing out.
I'm going to pick up Chief Xun.
Chengdu reports
that Prime Minister and his force will set out
and arrive in Nanzheng in seven days.
Have the scribe room
notify all departments that we're in wartime.
The Northern Expedition
shall take precedence.
Intelligence Analysis and Operations shall stand by,
awaiting Prime Minister's order.
Got it.
And
make necessary arrangements
for my visit to Qingshi Valley.
Qingshi Valley?
A Taoist priest has been cultivating himself
for years at Mount Chiyan there.
He's known for fortune-telling.
That must be Taoist Qingyun.
He's been practicing Taoism there
for at least 20 years.
They say he's all too powerful.
The Agency is unstable. I need some guidance.
I'll make the arrangement.
With Chief Yang's return,
it's tough being caught
between him and General Li.
You could use his divination.
Yes.
Go ahead.
Close the door for me.
What do you need me to do?
I need more people who can be trusted.
With Ma Sheng and Liao Hui gone
and the renewal of Internal Affairs,
only the most trustworthy
can be put to watch the head of the Agency.
Right.
Besides, such an operation
goes way beyond my level.
I know you're new to your post
and this is too much to ask,
but I must get to the bottom
of this case
so that Yue will rest in peace.
I see.
I'll ask General Ma Dai
for a team of skilled guards
out of Feng Ying's reach.
Don't worry.
I also need someone reliable
and skilled at tracking others.
Can't Pei Xu do it?
He can only cover one side
and I need him, too.
What's the other side?
When returning from Tianshui,
I found a girl near Wudu.
Miss Liu?
Yes.
Why keep her under watch?
Something doesn't seem right.
I don't think she was there by accident.
Has she done anything strange?
No.
But that makes her even more suspicious.
Come on, Xun Xu,
you're being paranoid.
You have to believe me.
I asked her to help get Feng Ying out.
You know that.
Yes.
She did it too well
for an ordinary girl.
Only the highly trained
would be able
to perform so well without fear!
"The lowly tend to be loyal.
The educated end up ungrateful."
Can't a harlot
be brave and helpful?
Do you really buy that?
Given our experience,
we can tell when we see an undercover spy.
It's a trained instinct.
Plus,
Feng Ying gave her to General Li
and put her in a villa in the south of the town.
Don't tell me
you're suspecting General Li as well.
Oh, I get it.
You're jealous,
aren't you?
I'm serious!
As am I.
All those things together
can't be good.
Hey,
I've seen Miss Liu once.
She's gorgeous.
You're a player.
Of course you've seen her in Ziyan House.
But Feng Ying isn't that kind of person.
I bet he's using her to get to General Li
for something.
You two's first encounter is quite romantic.
Do you
have a thing for her?
Yes or no?
Yes? Yes?
You wouldn't believe it if I said no.
But the thought of her real identity
stops me
from going further.
Fine.
If you're right about
Feng Ying and Miss Liu,
then
he's definitely up to something big
by going to such great lengths
to plant her
around General Li.
What's more,
if he and Guo Huai
are trading with each other covertly,
they'll need a go-between.
You think Miss Liu is Feng Ying's messenger?
We need to find out.
How?
Put down bait to lure him out.
If I'm right about everything,
Feng Ying will try to sabotage
the Northern Expedition.
Alright, fine.
I'll do whatever you say.
Have someone we can trust
watch Miss Liu closely.
Do you remember Lin Liang?
He's in Nanzheng, too?
When my cover was blown up
in Tianshui,
he went to hide in the mountains.
After we caught Zhulong,
I had him come over.
He'll arrive tonight.
He's smart and loyal.
He'll be able to help you.
That's great!
Chief Xun,
I'm here to pick you up.
Pei Xu, hold him.
Be careful.
Xun Xu,
Prime Minister will set out soon. There's a lot going on.
You must be careful.
I will.
Xun Xu.
Don't forget about Miss Liu.
Go.
Be careful.
Mister Mi, it's been a while.
Now that we're in the same boat,
just relax.
What do you want?
I'm sent by Inspector Guo, Guo Huai,
to pay my respects to Zhulong.
I didn't know
until he told me
that Saint Lady was your wife.
I'm sorry about
your loss, Clerk Chen.
Are you settling old scores with me?
I wouldn't dare.
I killed Di Yue
while you destroyed my sect.
Let's call it even.
I'm here for something else.
Inspector Guo personally ordered me
to help you eliminate the threat
and kill Xun Xu.
I'm not speaking for Chen Gong
but
he's come this far.
If anything goes wrong
and he gets caught,
all our effort will be in vain.
People change all the time,
especially in this line of business.
We're playing a big game
and Chen Gong is the key to victory.
We must be extremely cautious.
Guo Gang,
in this world,
people are most fickle.
In order to succeed,
you cannot trust anyone
or let others take the lead.
Think about it.
Once Chen Gong gets rid of Feng Ying
and takes over Siwencao Intelligence,
he'll become too powerful
to be kept on a string.
We'll lose control of him.
I'm not surprised if he changes his mind.
Once he becomes another Feng Ying,
we'll be nursing a viper
in our bosom.
I understand.
Killing Xun Xu is
his final test.
We need him to be a lone wolf.
By killing his wife,
colleague
and sworn brother,
he'll have nowhere to go
except for here.
Chief Xun is too deep in Zhulong's case.
It's only a matter of time
before he gets to you.
Is there a problem, Clerk Chen?
If both Feng Ying
and Chief Xun are gone,
I'll be considered
a suspect.
You don't want to kill Chief Xun
because of your relationship, do you?
I think
it's a bad idea in any way.
Your opinion doesn't matter.
Inspector Guo demands
that Xun Xu be killed
by no one but you.
Poison on these three golden arrows
will finish him instantly.
You're known for your accuracy in shooting.
This is an easy job.
Leaders
should trust their followers.
Clearly,
Inspector Guo
doesn't trust me.
Don't get it wrong, Clerk Chen.
He cares
too much about you
to expose you to any danger.
Reckless moves will only ruin Qingping Plan.
It won't.
The operation is all set up.
It won't be in Nanzheng
or cause you
any trouble.
I'll see you outside Xixiang.
Look,
(Li Yan's Camp in Nanzheng County, the Shu State)
Zhuge Liang's force has left Chengdu.
They'll soon go through Hanzhong and take Chencang Road.
Then they'll ask me to send provisions.
There are two delivery routes
from Mount Dingjun.
The east one is longer
than the west,
but we have to go east.
Through Sanguan Pass, the Mian River, Xie Valley,
Wuzhang Plains to Chencang.
The south of Sanguan Pass is my territory.
Deliver everything there
and give it to Wei Yan.
Brilliant, sir!
Once we finish the delivery,
whatever happens after
will have nothing to do with you.
Wei Yan and the provisions
will have to go along
the Mian River.
Down the River,
we can have Chen Gong destroy the dam
and it'll flood.
At this time of the year,
the rain along Sanguan Pass never stops.
Natural disasters such as floods do happen.
Meanwhile, Wu is invading us.
I'll have to send the troops and the supplies
to the front.
My action is fully justified.
You've planned out everything, sir.
But we need a reason to go east.
General Ma Dai monitors the checkpoints along the way.
If he sends out a warning
that mudslides buried the west route
and it won't reopen soon,
then the east route will be the only choice
for delivery.
So,
we need to win Ma Dai over.
He's Ma Chao's cousin
and he followed him to leave Zhang Lu for us.
Ma Chao was a hero
but he chose to lie low with his cousin
before the late emperor over the last ten years for safety.
Six years ago, Ma Dai lost his cousin.
He joined Prime Minister halfway
and ended up abandoned,
so he's been unappreciated.
Sir,
the slightest gesture of appreciation from us
might be able to win him over.
I hope so.
I'll see to it.
(Chengdu, the Shu State)
(Zhuge)
(General to Suppress the North)
"Green the mallow in the garden,
waiting for sunlight to dry the morning dew.
Bright spring warms the land,
breathing life into all beings."
What a beautiful poem!
"People living in this world
come and go like dust."
As nice as it seems,
spring is fleeting.
You look preoccupied lately.
Is something bothering you?
No, I'm just a bit down.
I'll sit in the pavilion for a while.
Guard the entrance of the backyard.
I don't want to be disturbed.
General favors you the most.
No one would dare to disturb you.
Stop making fun of me!
I'll wait for you there.
Chief Xun,
this way.
Will she come?
She will.
Are we
moving too fast?
We're running out of time.
The Northern Expedition is about to begin.
We need to eliminate all the threats,
or there'll be another false intelligence case.
You're right.
Will Feng Ying be out of our hands?
No way. He's under our control.
Don't you find it strange
that Feng Ying would be that dumb
to leave such obvious evidence?
It seems that we've got dirt on him,
but actually,
we're being led by the nose.
Chen Gong is strange, too.
How could he miss
those loopholes I found?
Clerk Chen must've had his reason.
I guess.
-Pei Xu.
-Yes.
Stand guard for me over there.
Yes, sir.
See you later.
Long time no see, Miss Liu.
I knew you were injured,
but it's worse than I thought.
Or I would've gone to check on you.
Who told you that?
When Clerk Feng came to see General Li,
I asked him about you
and he said that.
I'm here
to tell you something.
What is it?
A while ago,
I had you
steal Clerk Feng's seal.
No matter what that was for,
I used you.
It shouldn't have happened.
I'm sorry.
I don't expect you to forgive me.
This is too much!
I'm not bothered at all.
But it bothers me deeply.
Hadn't it been for me,
you wouldn't have known Clerk Feng
or
been sent to General Li.
Xun Xu,
sometimes,
I don't have a choice.
You don't?
Right.
I know.
All that's happened
makes me realize something.
Like what?
That you, Miss Liu,
might be a Wei spy.
You must be joking.
(Siwencao Intelligence in Nanzheng County, the Shu State)
Please let me know
when the Wu Plan is launched.
Of course.
You'll be updated on every detail.
General Li needs me for urgent military affairs.
I'm entrusting everything here to you.
Take care, gentlemen.
We'll be working day and night
in the next six months.
Clerk Feng, I've got some fine tea
for you to taste.
That's very thoughtful of you. Let's go.
Let's go. Please.
Do you know Gao Tangbing?
Yes.
I met him in Ziyan House.
According to the account book,
he went there three times every month
only to see you.
What's wrong? He wasn't paid enough
to see me?
He had never been there
before you came to Nanzheng.
His real identity
was a Wei spy
called Zhulong.
A spy
visited someone three times a month.
What would you think about that person?
I don't know
what you're talking about.
Before he died, he told me
you were his partner.
I see.
You aren't bothered
by my involvement with
Clerk Feng and General Li,
but by the fact that I used you.
Is that so?
Do you think
all that's happened
since you found me outside Wudu
is all staged?
You tell me.
Do you know my feelings for you?
You must've felt something.
Is that also fake?
Despite your accusation,
you have no proof.
But that's not a problem.
Shu and Wei are sworn enemies.
You'll kill everyone if you have to.
If you think I'm a spy,
arrest me now.
I'm exhausted.
I'd rather rest in peace.
(The 24 Strategies of War, The Wind Blows from Longxi)
(Intelligence Agency in Longxi)
(The Nineteenth Strategy, Steal the Firewood from under the Pot)
I knew it.
Chen Gong and Feng Ying
talked Li Yan into
removing the provisions
for Zhuge Liang's troops
in the name of battling Wu
at the risk of treason.
As he said,
to steal the firewood from under their pot.
How evil that is
to obstruct the Northern Expedition!
And Xun Xu is still looking into
Gao Tangbing's mysterious death.
He found evidence
on Feng Ying's sleeve
and had people
watch his every move.
Meanwhile,
Liu Ying is his another target
as she could be the messenger
between Guo Huai and Feng Ying.
Poor Xun Xu
is caught in a dilemma
and he can only ask Chen Gong for help.
That's bad!
What's worse,
that cult leader, Huang Yu is back.
He showed up unannounced at Chen Gong's place.
You're freaking us out!
He said Guo Huai sent him
to help Chen Gong kill Xun Xu.
That's more threat
than help.
And Chen Gong must
get rid of his sworn brother
to prove his loyalty to Wei.
Guo Huai is such a snake!
Things are taking a sharp turn.
Here come the questions:
Will Chen Gong
kill Xun Xu?
Will their brotherhood
end there?
Will Shu stand no chance
against Wei?
Stay tuned.
Keep up with me
for the inside scoop.