(The Wind Blows from Longxi)
(The Twentieth Strategy, Rescue the Main Force by Sacrificing the Other)
Xun Xu, if you think I'm a Wei spy,
arrest me.
I'm exhausted, too.
I want to stop for a breath.
Everybody has to do something not out of his free will.
There are few people
like you and me.
Miss Liu, do you remember
that you gave me a bamboo flute?
I promised you
that I would always bring it with me.
It's my treasure.
But I've never given you anything in return.
With this token,
you can leave the town at any time.
I only beg you
to leave this dangerous place.
I hope
you will take care.
Chief Xun.
Chief Xun,
Lin Liang is very near.
Shall I ask him to follow her?
There's no need.
Shall I follow her personally?
I said, there's no need.
Don't
tell Chen Gong about it.
Fine.
Clerk Feng, I'm honored
by your gracious presence.
You invited me and I would come.
This is the new tea
of this year.
Please have a taste.
Good.
Nice tea.
When I was young,
I was quite busy
and all I cared about was
making contributions.
When I'm in my forties,
I get to understand
how great it is to be idle.
Clerk Feng,
you laid a strong foundation for Siwencao Intelligence.
There is no question
about your distinguished services.
Chen Gong,
you flatter me.
I don't.
Others may not be aware.
But I know it very well.
When Siwencao Intelligence
was first founded,
there were great hardships.
It was indeed you
who
spared no pains
to have created an unprecedented era
for battles
between agencies and spies.
Marvelous.
Keep this
between us
just for fun.
Don't say this in front of strangers.
When I was in Tianshui,
I gradually
gained trust from the Wei Army
so that I had access to the Document Chamber.
I checked
some documents.
It's clearly recorded
that you foretold things accurately in the past dozen of years
and gained the upper hand
in intelligence fights so many times
that the Wei Army failed to defend themselves.
So,
every time Guo Gang and Guo Huai speak of you,
they keep praising you
with a sense of awe for you.
They do?
What do they say about me?
They say you're extremely cunning
and vicious.
I don't deserve
such a serious comment.
The more vicious you are to Wei,
the more loyal you are to our state.
Clerk Feng,
when your enemies think so highly of you,
don't you feel proud?
Chen Gong, I think
you're suggesting something else.
I do have some confusion
that I want you
to enlighten me.
You flatter me.
The confusion you have
must be very serious.
I'm not sure
if I can help you out.
You can.
Because it was you
who did that thing.
Even if it happened a long time ago,
I don't think you would forget it.
Tell me about it, then.
In 218 A.D.,
General Li Yan garrisoned Zizhong County.
Instigated by Wei, Ma Qin and Gao Sheng rebelled.
They attacked Zizhong County with an army of tens of thousands of soldiers.
Unfortunately,
the number of enemies was gigantic,
but they couldn’t use tactics.
With fewer soldiers,
General Li Yan still gained the upper hand.
I remember this.
But it happened ten years ago.
I don't remember too much
about the details.
I don't need the details.
Just tell me
the rough outline.
Chen Gong,
what confuses you?
The rebel soldiers
failed many times.
But suddenly, as if God helped them,
they were thoroughly familiar
with the condition of our army.
First, they cut off the food route to Zizhong County.
Then,
a large army broke in.
I don't want to sit and do nothing.
I'd like to pioneer
and fight a way out
for you, General.
Once Zizhong County fell,
the rebel army would approach Chengdu.
As I remember,
to conquer the Hanzhong region,
the armies were kept within Yangping Pass
by the late emperor.
So, they couldn't go to Zizhong County for help.
General Li Yan was so unprepared
that he had no choice,
but to abandon the county and flee.
At that time, you were in Chengdu,
handling the military movements.
I guess
you know something.
Indeed.
I know something.
Then why?
Why?
Chen Gong,
I know what you mean
by asking this question.
When Chief Yang and I sent you to Wei,
I knew this day would come.
You did?
Your father Chen Fu
died in the battle of Zizhong County.
You're asking me
for justice.
If you say so,
Clerk Feng,
are you admitting the injustice you did?
I...
How shall I put it?
We can't
predict something when it begins.
Just like Di Yue.
When you first infiltrated Wuxian Sect,
you didn't know Di Yue would die.
All you knew was to complete your mission.
Am I right?
At that time,
letting the rebel army besiege Zizhong County
was a necessary step in our strategy.
What are you talking about?
The late emperor with his generals was confronting Xiahou Yuan
across the river at Yangping Pass.
Xiahou Yuan was
a genius general.
He had his place heavily guarded
and we failed
to infiltrate his army.
Just at that time,
instigated by Guo Huai,
Ma Qin and Gao Sheng rebelled.
Yang Yi
sent a very urgent secret edict
from the late emperor.
I was asked
to secretly offer the military condition
of Zizhong County to the Wei Army.
After Ma Qin and Gao Sheng
rebelled in Zizhong County,
the Wei Army on Mount Dingjun
misjudged as we expected
and attacked us rashly.
They fell into the Prime Minister's trap.
Xiahou Yuan
was killed in the battle by our army.
Then,
our army conquered the Hanzhong region.
I don't believe it.
I just don't.
I don't care
if you believe it or not.
This is just the truth.
Spy games are
full of deceptions.
Your father Chen Fu died in the war.
It was also unexpected.
I took the order from the late emperor.
I didn't fake anything.
I can swear to God.
(Ziyan House in Nanzheng County, the Shu State)
(Ma Dai, General Who Pacifies the North of Shu)
General Ma Dai.
Hu Zhong,
why can't I see
too many people here today?
General Li Yan is holding a private dinner.
Anyone irrelevant must stay away.
Why didn't you tell me
when we were back in the Agency?
It was a last-minute decision of General Li Yan.
I only found out about this now.
I hear there was a military emergency?
After receiving the edict from His Majesty,
General couldn't fall asleep.
He keeps thinking it over
in case he misses something
and let down
His Majesty.
The defense of Mount Dingjun is virtually impregnable.
General Li Yan can rest assured.
General Ma Dai,
your sword, please.
Come in, please.
Greetings, General.
General Ma Dai,
my friend.
Don't stand on ceremony.
Be seated.
Prime Minister starts the second Northern Expedition with 200 thousand soldiers.
Ma Dai,
you must be stressed out.
General,
the local granary is always equipped
by the standard.
Excluding the wheat after this autumn,
the grain reserve is sufficient for one year.
Under the command of His Majesty,
I have to coordinate the logistics.
Ma Dai,
hope you'll help me with it.
This is my duty.
I'm at your command, General.
Cheers, General.
Hu Zhong is my henchman.
He's worked for me for over a decade.
This time, I want to transfer him
and let him
be your assistant
for more experience.
What do you think?
Good idea.
If Hu Zhong stays
on Mount Dingjun,
he'll be a great helper.
Thank you for your patronage, General Ma Dai.
You're welcome, Hu Zhong.
General Ma,
what's your opinion about the dispute between the Northern
and Southern Expeditions?
General,
I'm a soldier.
A soldier
is bound to take orders.
Absolutely right.
But today,
we're having a private dinner.
You can
make your points.
Umm...
Jieting's failure happened
not a long time ago.
Again,
the Prime Minister overrode all objections
and stuck to his own plan.
He will fight the Wei Army
with all the soldiers we have.
If he fails,
we will suffer heavy casualties
and the national strength will be wasted.
Even though
he can win
by good luck,
the war will last for a long time
with a sheer waste of energy and money.
At present,
with existing human and material resources,
it's already hard to defend the properties
of the late emperor.
When the Prime Minister
remains warlike,
it is never
a good thing for our state.
General Li Yan,
the Northern and Southern Expeditions
both sound reasonable.
As a mere soldier,
all I can do is to strain every nerve
to repay His Majesty
for his patronage.
As for
the result of the war,
it is
out of my consideration.
Chen Gong,
the tea tastes great.
I just got to enjoy it.
You colluded
with Guo Huai,
sold the secret of Siwencao Intelligence,
and sacrificed fieldwork spies.
Were you also ordered to do that?
Yes, of course.
Am I a man
who betrays his state
for small profits?
Chief Yang will arrive in Nanzheng County with the army.
If you don't believe me,
seek confirmation from him.
I will.
Clerk Feng,
even if it's true,
should my father
and countless fieldwork spies
just get killed
for the national cause?
Should they?
No one deserves to be killed.
But between state interests
and personal lives,
I pick the former.
I firmly
believe this.
Chen Gong,
we've paid a huge price for this.
We must in no way waste the efforts already made.
Chen Gong,
please don't be my enemy
for what happened before.
Don't overthink, Clerk Feng.
I also care
about the national cause.
Gao Tangbing's suicide...
I arranged it.
Don't bother to ask anymore.
Remember,
you have nothing to do with this case.
Xun Xu is investigating you.
It doesn't matter.
Chen Gong,
go visit Chief Yang
and try to get a General's Token
of the Prime Minister's Mansion.
When drinking,
let's not talk about politics.
General Ma Dai,
you are conscientious and loyal.
You're indeed a model for soldiers.
Thank you, Hu Zhong.
The late emperor
entrusted His Majesty to me.
Before the late emperor
passed away
in Baidi City,
he summoned me secretly.
He urged
that if the Prime Minister wanted to betray His Majesty,
we should be prepared.
Your elder brother Ma Chao
used to be my close friend
before he died.
On this matter,
we had a few discussions.
He also agreed
with the late emperor.
General Li Yan,
I'm too humble
to talk
about politics.
You don't believe me?
General,
my brother has been dead for six years.
And I've never heard
about this.
Please forgive me.
Very well.
Off you go.
General Hu Zhong,
my sword, please.
General,
do you not want me
to leave this room?
It depends on
whether you'll change your mind.
General Li Yan,
I've made up my mind.
As for the fight for power,
you'd better
think more about it.
Wait, General.
Ma Dai, if General Li Yan has a secret edict,
will you still stick to your decision?
A secret edict?
General,
General Ma Dai is very upright.
We couldn't persuade him without the secret edict from His Majesty.
General Ma Dai, read the edict, please.
General Li Yan,
I was speaking
too rudely.
General,
please forgive me.
General Ma Dai,
will you fight the rebel army by the edict?
Now that you have the edict,
I will do anything I can
and shrink from no sacrifice.
Give him the affidavit.
Oh, I understand.
With the help of so many generals,
you'll enjoy popular confidence.
You don't need to worry about anything.
Let General Ma Dai
make his cross on it.
I...
I will.
Come on.
Let's make a toast
to General Ma Dai's joining us.
Thank you, General.
(Tianshui, the Wei State)
Inspector Guo, Governor Guo,
Zhuge Liang left Chengdu and entered the Hanzhong region
with the main force.
Wei Yan and his army are the vanguards.
They ride along Qinling Mountains,
towards
Wudu
and Yinping.
They're fast.
Scouts have found out
that a secret army is moving stealthily
towards Jianwei in the south of Mount Qi.
How many soldiers?
We're not sure yet.
About 30,000 soldiers.
What job are you doing?
Which one is exactly the main force of the Shu Army?
I'll go check it out.
Go.
Aye.
The Shu Army is attacking us
in a weird way.
I'll temporarily give up Wudu and Yinping
and return to Mount Qi Base Camp.
We shall strictly defend Shanggui
and Tianshui.
If we lose two towns before a war,
I'm afraid we can hardly explain.
When the Wu and Shu armies invade at the same time,
our army isn’t strong enough to defend separately.
Concentrated forces will do better in counterattack.
Generals, at my command.
-Here.
Strike all camps in Tianshui within three days.
Embattle along the Weishui River
and launch a frontal attack on the Shu Army.
Aye.
Chief Xun,
you're getting much better.
I'm still disabled.
Be contented, Chief Xun.
According to the physician,
only one out of ten men who are as badly wounded as you
could stand up again.
How do you feel today?
Clerk Chen.
I feel much better.
I can walk a few steps without the cane.
Good.
Be seated.
Be careful.
Slow. Slow.
All right.
You saw Miss Liu Ying today.
How did you feel?
We took the move.
Let's wait and see.
Lin Liang is keeping an eye on her.
He'll report to us if anything happens.
What about Feng Ying?
We have him spied on, too.
Nothing seems to be unusual.
However,
at noon yesterday,
someone drew a little circle on his door
with carbon dust.
Circle?
Yes, a very small circle.
If he hadn't wiped it off deliberately,
I wouldn't have noticed it.
Chen Gong,
this is a usual contact way of spies.
Do you still think he's clear?
I find something fishy today.
What is it?
He asked Sun Ling to arrange a trip
to Mount Chiyan of Qingshi Valley.
Qingshi Valley?
Why does he want to go there?
To have divination from a Taoist.
When will he go?
Early tomorrow morning.
I guess he won't arrive there
until nine o'clock.
The Prime Minister's army will be arriving tomorrow.
Everyone is busy with work.
Why does he want divination at this time?
According to him,
a lot of things have happened lately
and he wants to divine
if anything has gone wrong.
Nonsense!
If Feng Ying does anything fishy,
take drastic action.
Unfortunately,
I'm a mere chief of the Internal Affairs Department.
I don't think I can take him down.
Anyway,
we can't count on General Li Yan.
Feng Ying is already
his henchman.
What do we do, then?
Xun Xu, you mentioned it before.
So, I visited
Chief Yang
and got this.
General's Token of the Prime Minister’s Mansion.
This is great.
(Xixiang, the Shu State)
Welcome, Leader Huang.
Thank you, everybody.
This time I'm back
because Zhuge Liang is fighting against Wei with his main forces.
It's the time
to revive our sect.
Leader, issue an order.
To revive our sect,
I'm willing to take any risk
and shrink from no sacrifice!
We'll shrink from no sacrifice!
We've been waiting for a long while.
This is the day we're expecting!
Good.
Our sect is
the vanguard of the Wei Army
to destroy Shu and Wu.
Guo Huai sent me to the Hanzhong region
for two missions.
Tell me.
How many members
can we still gather from different towns?
Two or three thousand.
They're at your command.
Take two elders from the sub-bases
to gather our members
and sneak to the north of Sanguan Pass.
Get ready to cut off the food route of the Shu Army.
Aye.
Elder Cao.
Here.
Go with Guan Qi
to attack the pass outside Xixiang Town.
Outside Xixiang Town?
Isn't that the frontline battlefield?
It's just camouflage,
for Xun Xu of Siwencao Intelligence.
Aye.
Feng Ying.
I haven't
fought the enemies ever since.
You used to protect me all the time.
Feng Ying,
I've confirmed everything for tomorrow.
Taoist Qingyun isn't out for traveling.
Good, then.
Tomorrow,
we'll go there early in the morning.
The Prime Minister has left Chengdu.
He'll be arriving in Nanzheng County at three in the afternoon.
If you go to Mount Qingyun,
I don't think you can return in time.
Don't bother about this.
Just do what I told you.
Fine.
Go to bed early,
Feng Ying.
Wait, Sun Ling.
Mm?
Go to bed early, too.
Mm.
(Qingyun Hall in Nanzheng County, the Shu State)
We asked to meet Taoist Qingyun the day before yesterday.
Please inform him.
He's been waiting for you.
Come in, please.
This is the fee for the divination.
This way, please.
Chief Xun,
everything is ready in there.
Shall we arrest him now?
There's no hurry.
Let's wait until he comes out.
Chief Xun,
look.
Have someone follow him. Hurry.
Go.
Aye.
Keep a close eye on him.
So, you're an official.
I'm not wearing a uniform.
How do you know that?
The environment tempers people.
After being an official for more than twenty years,
you have official airs.
Don't you realize that?
Oh, I see.
I was being ignorant.
May I ask
what the divination is?
Does anything make you hesitate?
If you don't mind,
I'll get to the point.
I don't mind.
I'm all ears.
Within three days,
you will be in prison.
Nonsense!
Do you know who he is?
Don't be rude.
You sound optimistic.
You must be fearless of death.
Though a man's life is destined,
I still wonder
if I can get out of trouble.
As an old saying goes,
a man has to sacrifice something to get what he wants.
In this case,
nothing can help me out.
Nonsense!
What a bad Taoist he is!
This is my fate.
Why bother cursing him?
He's ridiculous.
He spoilt your mood.
I'll have some guards
break down his house.
He talked nonsense and made trouble.
That is unforgivable!
Don't monkey around.
We had wanted a good omen.
Unexpectedly, we got something disgusting.
-What the heck!
-Stop!
This is Clerk Feng Ying of Siwencao Intelligence.
Who are you?
Xun Xu?
What are you doing?
Clerk Feng,
you colluded with the Wei Army
and divulged our military secrets.
You're under arrest.
(Intelligence Agency in Longxi)
(The 24 Strategies of War, The Wind Blows from Longxi)
(The Twentieth Strategy Rescue the Main Force by Sacrificing the Other)
Something big happened.
Miss Liu Ying is involved
in the intelligence fight, too.
But Xun Xu
didn't want to blow her cover.
He even gave her a token,
asking her to leave this dangerous place.
Chen Gong
finally laid his cards to Feng Ying.
In 218 A.D.,
to defeat the Wei Army,
Prime Minister Zhuge
used the military information of Zizhong County
to divert their attention
from the battlefield at Yangping Pass
and misled them.
Finally,
our army won.
I'm bound to say
that Prime Minister Zhuge used a brilliant trick
to rescue the main force
by sacrificing the other.
Actually, Feng Ying didn't
frame Chen Gong's father on purpose.
Should my father
just die like this?
Feng Ying just had to complete his mission
for the interests of Shu.
No one deserves to be killed.
But between state interests
and personal lives,
I pick the former.
So, some people died accidentally.
They explained to each other clearly.
On the other hand,
Li Yan also did something.
He used the edict of the late emperor...
General Ma Dai, read the edict, please.
to threaten General Ma Dai for allegiance,
trying to draw more generals over
and deal with Prime Minister Zhuge.
I hate to say it,
but the late emperor's secret edict
can be used as a panacea.
Xun Xu is still
picking on Feng Ying.
He suspects Feng Ying is a Wei spy.
With the Prime Minister Zhuge's Token,
he wants to arrest Feng Ying.
Do you still think he's clear?
Chen Gong has returned.
We can then make concerted efforts
to fight against the Wei Army, right?
What is Feng Ying going to do?
Everybody,
so much for today's share.
I will go and get
some new information.