(The Wind Blows from Longxi)
(The Tenth Strategy If All Else Fails, Retreat)
Xun Xu, what were you thinking
by getting Clerk Feng out?
I knew he was framed.
Ma Sheng's will isn't solid proof.
If they task me
with this case,
I'm telling you,
the truth will come out in ten days!
It's not as simple as you think.
Things in Chengdu are changing.
Look,
the more there is to this case,
the less likely you're to be on it.
Don't you know that?
Tangbing,
Clerk Feng treated you well, didn't he?
You can't sit and do nothing
while he's going down.
-I didn't mean...
-Say no more.
It is what it is. Are you in or not?
You...
Fine.
What do you need me to do?
Get Clerk Feng
out of town tonight
and tread carefully.
Tonight?
Yes. That's right.
Aren't you aware
that Clerk Li has asked General Ma Dai
to impose a lockdown to seize the escaped?
Not even a bird can sneak out.
No excuses.
You're in charge of Intelligence Analysis.
There must be something you can do.
Can we trust Chief Gao?
Absolutely.
Tangbing and I go way back.
He knows what to do for the best.
I had him
go over to
sound Xun Xu out.
Actually,
there's a way out.
I'm listening.
General Ma Dai and the Madam of Ziyan House
are old friends.
He'd have her girls over
to entertain his men at the Yangping Pass
on the last night of every month.
And tonight is the night.
He's guarding Hanzhong
and the garrison in Nanzheng is
under his command.
How's this plan?
It's clever!
Terrific!
I know I can count on you, Chief Gao.
But,
to make it work,
I still need your help.
But how? I'm being watched day and night.
Hadn't Yin Ji sent you to sound me out,
I couldn't have gone to your place.
There's no legwork involved.
I just need you to send a message.
Where to?
Ziyan House.
I've never been to that kind of place.
Come on, liar!
You can't fool me.
That girl you found in Wudu has risen to
the top harlot there.
Don't forget what my department does.
What you did is logged in the system.
Don't you have
anything better to do?
Without such information,
I wouldn't be of help now.
Show this to Miss Liu
and she'll help you.
Is this a token of love?
Knock it off!
The Shu Army's garrison
has set up three lines of defense here.
There's only one path in and out of the col.
I wish we had the passwords and the tallies
to each post.
The guards and the tallies
are assigned randomly.
Even if we got them, they could be wrong.
Is there anything
Zhulong can do about it?
He's done everything he could
by giving us the map and the key.
Speaking of which,
this key is to the stone vault
keeping the design of the crossbow.
That gives us a better chance of success.
You'll have to jump off the cliff here.
I understand.
We've covered the entrance and the exit.
Now, let's go over the plan
once we get into the head office.
Have you rehearsed it?
Yes, many times.
Look,
Mister Mi.
The front gate leads to
five layers of courtyards.
The scribe room is
in the last one
with a secret chamber.
That's where the design is.
Is the scribe room guarded?
Yes.
As the main force is
lined up for defense,
guards outside the scribe room are only a few,
less than ten, I presume.
In that case,
we'll need a crack team.
Once you finish, leave through the back door.
The backyard is an open field
mostly used by the Shu Army for training.
And the cliff is right behind it
and left unguarded,
known as a natural barrier.
Leader...
Even if we have the crack team in there,
only two will be able to
make their way out alive.
Members of our sect aren't afraid of death.
Qingping Plan
concerns the future of our state.
Its success will come at a cost.
You two,
take the Bamboo Kites
and leave
with the design.
The thing is,
once we enter,
Shu soldiers
in the Military Technology Department
will be alerted.
We can get in and out quickly
with the design,
but once they find
that the design is missing,
the entire mountain will be sealed off.
And we won't be able to break out
with the design
even if we land safely.
That will be
Zhulong's concern.
All you two need to do is
grab the design from the head office
and put it at the drop spot.
Zhulong will pick it up
from Mount Dingjun
and send it to Tianshui.
Where's the drop spot?
I don't know
because he hasn't told me.
The last question is
if the Bamboo Kites
can fly Mister Mi and me
to that spot safely.
What if we're in the air and...?
Don't think too much.
The Bamboo Kites are our only option.
I'll fly with you.
You'll sacrifice yourselves for the great cause
and so will I.
Trust me.
You're a warrior.
If all goes well,
Qingping Plan will be a success.
Leader,
when shall we act?
In five days.
On Zhulong's signal.
Sure.
(Tianshui, the Wei State)
Liang Jian
pays his respects to you, Governor.
(Liang Jian with Intelligence Agency in Tianshui of Wei)
Liang Jian,
two updates for you.
One, Chancellor Mi
has arrived at Hanzhong
to gather together the Wuxian Sect.
He won't be back soon.
While he's away,
you'll be in charge of
the Intelligence Agency.
Yes, sir.
Oh, I almost forgot.
Uh,
Recorder Chen died
at the Yangping Pass.
He was
a hero.
What a shame!
One of a kind?
He was Baidi.
Yes, Chen Gong was a spy.
Chancellor Mi was right.
I was wrong.
Wrong and stupid.
Siwencao Intelligence of Shu
has declassified records about him
and it's corroborated by other sources.
Still, that doesn't affect the Qingping Plan.
It'll go on as planned.
Liang Jian,
work hard.
It's too big
a responsibility.
I'll do my utmost.
There's one more thing,
that is,
someone will replace me.
I'm leaving.
Where are you going, sir?
Commander Guo
has another plan for me.
I'll be escorted back to Chang'an
and deprived of my ranks.
So long.
-It's raining.
-Don't worry about it.
Come and join us!
Here?
Yes.
Miss Liu,
good day.
She's out.
The gate is right ahead.
Stop.
You're going out again, Zhang?
I'm taking General Ma Dai's friend
to the Yangping Pass.
You know it's a routine
once a month.
Please, Officer.
I heard General Wei Yan will be there, too.
Fine.
Let him out.
-Thank you, Officer.
-Wait.
Chief Yin.
inside is a guest of General Ma Dai's.
Whoever gets out of town
must be checked thoroughly.
Of course.
Greetings,
Chief Yin.
Miss Liu!
General Ma Dai
appointed her by name.
You aren't going to frisk her, are you?
Don't forget to check other carriages
for smuggling.
Yes, sir.
Let them go.
Thank you, Officer.
Let's go.
He let Feng Ying go?
(General Li Yan's Mansion in Chengdu, the Shu State)
Could Li Miao be more impotent?
Nanzheng is in lockdown.
The Agency, garrison in Hanzhong
and local forces of Nanzheng are all out.
Feng Ying won't be able to get out of their hands.
He won't?
He already has.
Luckily, I thought ahead
and didn't report his idea to His Majesty,
or we'd be in trouble
if the case got overturned.
You're wise, General.
What did His Majesty say
in court this morning?
Nothing new.
He's unpredictable.
The court will end tomorrow.
Whether we battle the north or the south
shall be decided then.
Zhuge Liang's supporters are many.
It's a tug of war.
Both sides
have a chance to win.
Will the impeachment fail yet again?
It's hard to tell.
General,
Feng Ying from Hanzhong is outside.
Who is it?
Clerk Feng of the Agency, Feng Ying.
Feng Ying is
smarter than I imagined.
Send him in.
But...
I'll have a go at him.
Yes, sir.
Feng Ying
pays his respects to you, Cavalry General.
Why
would a wanted criminal
ask to see me?
You should turn yourself in
at the Law Enforcement Office.
The missing of Baidi's code-cracking plates
and the murder of Liao Hui of Internal Affairs
were pinned on me by Li Miao.
Please bring justice to me, sir.
Oh?
Injustice is everywhere.
Why should I believe you?
I've got proof.
Proof?
Please read this.
Unbelievable!
Ridiculous!
Ma Sheng's statement and the case corroborate each other.
It's not fabricated.
Is there any hard evidence?
Li Miao is too noble
to go this low
and set up his colleague.
Turn this evidence over
to the Law Enforcement Office,
they'll get to the bottom of the case
and clear my name.
You're Yang Yi's underling.
Why not give this to him
and it's win-win?
I, Feng Ying,
am a decent court official,
not anyone's underling.
I risked my life to come here
to have a sincere talk with you, General.
Let's hear it.
With this piece of evidence,
I'll no longer be killed
but this whole incident
can go either way.
Is that so?
General,
you seized the chance of Prime Minister's loss of Jieting
and gained support
to halt the Northern Expedition
and clean the house.
Then you took over the Agency
to nip further threats in the bud.
That's remarkable!
But if Yang Yi
got hold of this evidence,
all your effort
would be in vain.
Keep going.
Yang Yi is
narrow-minded,
domineering
and a beast.
We're still battling poverty at home,
and the Northern Expedition
will cost us our future.
So?
I hate to see
your years of preparation
go up in flames.
(Xun Xu's Residence in Nanzheng County, the Shu State)
Chief Xun,
Clerk Feng should be
in Chengdu by now, right?
The curfew hasn't been lifted.
All is going well, I guess.
We should thank Chief Gao for it.
Without him,
it wouldn't be possible.
Sir,
how did you know
he'd agree to help?
Well,
what kind of person
do you think he is?
He's cautious,
logical
and a visionary.
Pei Xu,
you should work on your people skills.
Please
enlighten me.
He's cautious
about committing himself to anything.
You're right about that.
But by nature,
he only sides with the winner
in any circumstance.
Ma Sheng's last words
have guaranteed us victory.
The truth or the evidence
no longer matters.
It's only a matter of time
before Li Miao's downfall.
He held a grudge
against Yang Yi
and to get back at him,
he threatened Ma Sheng to slaughter Liao Hui.
That was a heinous crime!
Poor Liao Hui
always regarded us as brothers.
He died a martyr
for our state.
But the investigation on Zhulong
seems to have gone nowhere.
I have a feeling
that he's behind everything.
I'm swearing allegiance
to you.
Well then,
Clerk Feng,
I'll accept
your gift.
It's my pleasure to serve you.
There's one thing bothering me.
When I first landed in Nanzheng
and invited you over and over,
why did you
refuse to come?
Sir,
a fine fowl
perches only on a fine tree.
Only when you were in desperate need of help
would my talent be most appreciated.
What makes you think
that I need you
right now?
You and Prime Minister
have entirely different plans for the state.
Everyone knows it.
This time,
his loss on the battlefield
provided you with a golden opportunity to bring him down.
However,
he was too deeply rooted
and well-connected in court
to fall easily.
Then you had Li Miao
control the Agency.
As much as he tried
to win their members over,
he failed
to find his way in,
which left him no choice
but to cook up this clumsy trick
to set up an innocent man.
Sir,
I apologize
if my poppycock
offended you in any way.
Keep going.
You've had
the Noble Clans at your back
to gang up on Prime Minister.
It's too late to quit
and
it's life and death.
And?
If...
I mean, if I have
solid evidence that Yang Yi is colluding with
those bandits of the Wuxian Sect,
I suppose that'll be of great help to you,
General.
Clerk Feng,
please be seated.
Thank you, sir.
Our state
needs pillars like you,
loyal and dedicated.
I'm honored
and ready to serve.
(Wuxian Sect, Border of the Shu State)
Have some.
I can still drink.
(Wuxian Sect, Border of the Shu State)
Me too.
You... you don't respect me at all!
(Wuxian Sect, Border of the Shu State)
Am I right?
You know me.
I wouldn't dare!
I can drink more!
I...
believe you.
Let's go back and...
-Mister Mi.
-Keep drinking.
Elder Qin.
My lady.
Mister Mi,
let me walk you back with my lamp.
No need. I'll do it. We...
Elder Qin,
you look befuddled.
Go back and rest.
Yes.
I apologize.
Thank you, my lady.
Mister Mi,
you've had too much to drink, too.
I'll escort you back.
Do you and Xun Xu have a way to contact each other?
Yes.
The next time will be soon.
The day is coming.
We need his help
to capture Zhulong.
Sure.
I understand.
I'll fill him in on each step.
My concern is
Huang Yu's men
will be with you out there.
Will that be a problem?
Relax. I know what to do.
Mister Mi,
this is it.
I have something for you.
What is it?
I found this when Huang Yu tried to burn it.
Only half is left.
It was from Zhulong
with some numbers
that make no sense to me.
Uh... Thank you, my lady.
Mister Mi,
good night.
Good night, my lady.
(Prime Minister Zhuge's Mansion in Chengdu, the Shu State)
Prime Minister,
you're back from the court early.
Because the result is out.
So... did Li Yan withdraw his impeachment?
(Cavalry General Li Yan)
(Li Yan's Camp in Nanzheng County, the Shu State)
General,
Clerk Li with the Agency
has been waiting for you at the camp.
Is General-in-Chief back?
He's getting changed.
Please wait for a few more minutes.
Li Miao.
Hu Zhong.
Can I go and see him?
He's resting after his trip.
Hu Zhong,
help me, please!
I'm begging you!
What happened?
Feng Ying escaped and he's still on the run.
I'm afraid he's gone to Yang Yi in Chengdu!
I ruined General's plan!
It was all my fault...
Li Miao,
you're worrying too much.
Li Yan has submitted new evidence.
Against Feng Ying?
Li Miao is a lunatic.
Those charges he trumped up
are a joke!
They're full of loopholes!
Li Yan said
when you were head of the Agency,
the Wuxian Sect grew strong and insubordinate
under your watch.
What?
Files Feng Ying turned over to Li Yan
include a surveillance record
from November 26th
that you reviewed.
The record showed a man and a woman
with the Wuxian Sect
paid a visit to General Wang Ping.
Their conversation was unknown.
“Noted.
Report not.”
You wrote that
and the Agency followed your instruction
to not report it to the upper level
and filed it away.
Why?
General Wang Ping is
your right-hand man.
Such information could be used against you
if leaked out.
Li Yan didn't think so.
He believed
you were covering for the Army's secret contact
with the Wuxian Sect
and backed them under the table
so that it's gaining strength.
Intelligence Agency of the Wei
is in league with them, too.
You're
the cause of everything.
Prime Minister!
Feng Ying must've betrayed us,
or Li Yan couldn't have gotten hold of
such classified records!
His Majesty has ordered
an all-out strike on the Wuxian Sect.
As for you,
you're dismissed and demoted to a civilian.
Prime Minister!
You have your own merits
but you lack
a big heart
and patience.
Read more books at home.
You'll benefit from them.
Yang Yi has been dismissed?
That's like cutting off Zhuge Liang's arm!
Yang Yi has left office
and you've got your revenge.
An eye for an eye isn't enough.
I want more.
General speaks highly of you
for the good work
you've done.
That's nothing.
I'm just glad that I didn't hold him back.
The impeachment worked
not because of the failed Northern Expedition
or the Wei spy in the Agency.
On what ground then?
Yang Yi sponsored the Wuxian Sect secretly,
posing a threat to the state,
and kept expanding the Agency's influence.
And the evidence from General was strong?
Of course.
His Majesty ordered an elimination in rage.
And Feng Ying's case...
Don't worry
about that clown.
General had been aware of
the ins and outs of the case.
When His Majesty asked about it in court,
General
covered for you
and he specifically told me
to calm you down.
Li Miao,
he still needs you
to battle the Wuxian Sect.
His wish is my command.
I, Li Miao,
could never repay you
for your kindness,
General!
(Ziyan House in Nanzheng County, the Shu State)
With Yang Yi gone,
Prime Minister is under less pressure.
I want to help him
even for old times' sake.
You did what was best for everyone
even when stuck between two sides.
No one else in the region
could do what you did.
Stop flattering me.
I'm forced
to turn to Li Yan.
And
what's General Li
going to do with Clerk Li?
When Prime Minister let him go,
General Li took him in
and planted him into the Agency.
Were he found guilty,
General Li
would look bad, too, wouldn't he?
So a high-profile case
just goes away
like this?
That's absurd!
He's to wipe out the Wuxian Sect, isn't he?
He'll be remembered
for our victory.
Is that the plan?
I must say General Li is...
heartless.
Heartless?
The powerful
have no hearts.
I've recommended you to him
that you're the right one
for this job.
Me?
I'll be straight with you.
No one
can always
have a foot in both camps.
Get the job done
and Li Miao's mansion is yours.
You deserve it
with your seniority.
Generals.
Would you like a song
for entertainment?
Clerk Feng and I are here for business.
Maybe next time.
Have a nice day, gentlemen.
She saved my life last time, didn't she?
Yes, that was Miss Liu.
It's rare
to see someone
with her righteousness and courage.
Agreed.
Without her,
you would've been
in a tougher situation.
I'll give her a chance
to climb up the ladder
and show her that she'll be rewarded
for her good deeds.
Despite what she did for you,
she's nothing
but a street performer.
Why are you
so interested in her?
You know,
General Li has an elegant taste.
He's into music
and a professional himself.
If so,
this can be a smart move.
By the way,
what about Sun Ling?
He's tough.
He's been keeping his mouth shut for you
no matter how hard he's grilled.
Sun Ling
is impetuous.
Pain will help him grow.
He'll be fine
once my job is done.
Look,
Xun Xu isn't good with secrets.
Do not tell him the truth.
I won't.
If he asks,
tell him my whereabouts are still unknown.
Clerk Feng has left.
Would you like to have a seat inside, Chief Gao?
Sure.
(The 24 Strategies of War, The Wind Blows from Longxi)
(Intelligence Agency in Longxi)
(The Tenth Strategy If All Else Fails, Retreat)
Well done!
Thanks to Xun Xu,
Feng Ying made his way out
with Miss Liu Ying's help.
I knew
he could do it!
I'll also make my way
out of this dark cell soon.
But, Feng Ying,
I don't get this.
General Li Yan is sure that you're Yang Yi's man.
Will he still trust you?
I've got proof.
Are you...?
Proof?
Getting involved
in the power struggle, too?
Won't you
be betraying Chief Xun?
Over in the Wei State,
Guo Gang was told about
Recorder Chen's death.
Turns out, his best friend
was Baidi, a spy of Shu.
He lost his job because of it
while still in grief.
Actually,
it was Chancellor Mi who died.
Chen Gong is smart
and using his identity in the Wuxian Sect.
Qingping Plan is about to kick off
while Chen Gong and Huang Yu are
still working on the plan to steal the design.
Will everything go smoothly?
When will Baidi and Zhulong
battle each other head-on?
Keep up with me
for first-hand, exclusive intelligence!