♪An early or a perfect
or a destined love♪
♪It may start out like a prank♪
♪Love is so confusing♪
♪An isolated frozen island melts♪
♪And travels to the end of the universe♪
♪What words shall I use to describe♪
♪The long-awaited embrace♪
♪An isolated frozen island melts♪
♪My breathing becomes warmer♪
♪And travels to the end of the universe♪
♪What words shall I use to describe♪
♪The long-awaited embrace♪
♪An isolated frozen island melts♪
♪My breathing becomes warmer♪
♪An isolated island♪
=Dear Little Mermaid=
=Episode 8=
(Qingchuan People's Hospital)
(Outpatient)
(Comprehensive Department)
Systemic lupus erythematosus
is a type of disease caused by
low autoimmunity of one's body.
During the initial stage of it,
the patient will get
full body of skin rash.
Let's take a look,
two cases of transverse resistance,
the patients of systemic
lupus erythematosus
are all females.
During the entire treatment,
we are required to take
an effective approach
to maintain the permanence of the
patient's skin and mucous membranes,
lower the impact on
life caused by sore joints.
After checking your inspection report,
you're recovering well.
However, you still have to keep it up.
Dr. Bai,
Director Cao would like
to see you in his office.
Alright, got it.
You must rest well,
don't let your guard down.
I'll go first then.
Take good care of her for me.
Alright.
Miss Nurse, what happened to Dr. Bai?
Dr. Bai has been complained
by Urology department.
This patient named Su Zelin,
has his transfer procedure to
our Urology department carried out
through Dr. Bai three days ago.
According to schedule, he should
be having operation tomorrow.
However, during the
preoperative examination today,
we discovered that
he has high proteinuria.
It does not meet the
transfer criteria at all.
Not sure how would
Dr. Bai explain about it.
The procedure has no problem.
The patient has undergone
routine inspection before the transfer.
All indicator indexes are met.
Routine inspection?
How could you fool
us with only performing
normal routine inspection
for such a unique patient?
Dr. Xu,
Please mind your words.
We treat every patient equally.
Also clearly understand the
appropriate decision to make
in the specific situation.
Enough.
What exactly is the reason,
our department will investigate on it.
You can head back for now.
Alright, Director Cao.
I'll wait for your update then.
Alright.
Qijia,
do you have anything in mind?
Director,
I firmly believe that our
procedure and formalities
are perfectly fine.
I would like to apply
to speak to the patient.
Are you suspecting that
he had acted against medical
advice within these three days?
No.
I just want to talk to him about
follow-up treatment matter.
It's true.
Figure out relatively
what actually happened.
Patient's follow-up treatment
and psychological
counseling are more important.
Go ahead.
I'll assist you on any trouble.
Thank you Director.
Got complained!?
The patient is terrible.
He kept demanding to get another doctor
and ordered Dr. Bai
not to mind him anymore.
So what he meant was
Bai Qijia delayed his illness?
He actually said that.
Dr. Bai was even called
to the Director's office
regarding this matter.
(No wonder he didn't come to me today.)
Is Dr. Bai still in the ward?
Dr. Lu,
these are all bought for you.
Guru Bai Qi!
Where is Procrastinator Bai?
You both didn't actually
team up to prank me right?
Let me tell you.
I, Lu Tian, am a man with principle.
I would never lay my
hands on my brother's lady.
What are you talking about?
I have something to ask you.
Now I can rest assured.
Enjoy your food.
Have more.
It's delicious right?
Yes.
Dr. Lu,
I want to ask you something.
If a doctor is complained by a patient,
what would happen?
This will depend on what
is the complaint about
and the actual situation.
Actually medical industry also
belongs to the service industry.
Patient will request according to
their own requirements.
If the service is not
up to their standards,
they will find that
they were treated unfairly.
However, it's still subject to
specific circumstance.
What facts will it be
investigated according to?
Will any task force be set
up for the investigation?
How long will it approximately take
for the investigation?
It won't.
Don't tell me you're now
drawing doctors in your manga?
If you're really drawing us,
please draw those lifesaving works.
Boundless great love.
Rather than drawing about complaints.
Why are you talking so much?
I'm asking you, please answer.
The investigation results vary
across every department.
Is there something wrong?
I heard that
Bai Qijia was complained that he delayed
patient's operation.
Procrastinator Bai was complained?
Which department he was complained by?
By...
it seems to be...
Urology department.
Then it should be something wrong
during the patient handover.
However, by Procrastinator Bai's
personality,
he wouldn't voluntarily prove it.
About the complaint,
will it be serious?
He would get penalty.
Most probably, his
title won't be able to get
reviewed in the recent years.
I guess,
I would have to handle it myself.
Miss...Miss Bai Qi,
that guy at 10 o'clock
is exactly you wanted, Su Zelin.
(Nurse Station)
You're watching this too,
Railgun from some science manga?
Yes, the lightning
created by your fingertip,
is my everlasting faith.
Only I, Railgun,
- Will be immortal!
Nice! We are like-minded!
After all these while
being hospitalised,
finally get to meet like-minded peer.
Me staying in hospital for so long
that I think my dimensional
wall has broken.
I know, right?
Oh yeah, which ward are you from?
I'm Qin Ge from immunology.
Glad to meet you, I'm Su Zelin.
Glad meeting you too.
- Fellow patient.
Which episode you're watching now?
I'm watching this.
They talk about this summer festival.
This episode is really interesting.
Let me give you a quick idea.
This episode is about everyone
attending this summer festival, then...
Anyway, this episode
ended just like that.
I am not satisfied.
What a waste.
So you should
tell me about the
remaining plot tonight.
I find the way you tell it
is way more interesting
than it is in manga.
Tonight?
is your department not strict at all?
Policies comes from above,
counter-reactions from below.
I really envy you.
I can't be as free as you.
I'm facing an ancient girl
day and night.
Who is your attending doctor?
Who else could it be?
He is Dr. Bai, full name is Miracle Bai.
I think Miracle Bai's
full name is Bai Qijia.
I heard that he was
complained two days ago.
Maybe, I guess, probably,
must be...
Actually that's true.
Don't worry.
Who cares if it's
Bai Qijia, Miracle Bai,
Rice Cake Bai, Chicken Bai,
I will settle him for you.
Is it really okay?
Okay.
What time did you sleep?
This patient here,
not staying in your ward late at night,
who's your attending doctor?
I'm gonna report you.
Say your lines, say your lines.
You had lots of fun,
please let me go.
Alright then, I'll stop playing.
What are you doing here?
I...
I'm here to see you,
and bring you some snacks.
Heck, haven't seen you in two days,
you already start eating junk foods.
Isn't this turning yourself in?
This is called seeking leniency.
You...
Well, look at you.
You must be tired.
Alright ,I'll walk you
to your ward then.
I was on my way for ward rounds.
No, it's been very hard
for you these two days.
Go rest up earlier.
Bye.
(Nephrology)
You finally escaped.
I thought you were held on by Dr. Bai.
How is it possible?
By the way,
you can continue your storytelling.
Alright.
We were finishing
episode 22 right?
The following will be episode 23.
Due to the loss of
control in this experiment,
our four leads became unconscious,
that is,our group of main characters.
Meanwhile, the whole group
of main characters lie down
in the laboratory with
empty surrounding.
- Then four weeks...
- Zelin.
Actually I know Dr. Bai personally.
He was my friend in high school.
During school,
he was very conscientious.
Also,
he really likes his job as a doctor.
And he wouldn't justify for himself.
I'd hate to see his
hard work goes in vain.
So,
could you tell me
what's the truth behind your complaint?
I promise I would not tell anyone.
Actually...
Actually it's me myself
who couldn't stay on diet.
While the transfer doctors
was not being strict,
I...I went on a binge for three days.
Well...
I will surely explain
everything about this
to Dr. Bai.
Didn't Railgun say before,
I am the causation.
So,
I wanna solve it myself.
Am I right?
I'm really...
By the way!
There is one thing I
must remind you of...
No problem!
I understand, don't you worry.
What you told me today,
I will never them to Dr. Bai.
No!
You must inform him.
Why?
If you don't tell him,
how would he know that he owes me?
If he doesn't know that he owes me,
how could he return me a favour?
This is the modern age now.
Never do good deeds anonymously.
Lesson learnt.
Stinky Zelin, why isn't he back yet?
Did he forget it?
Please don't forget to tell.
Why are you so late!?
Xue...
Did I not come in at the right time?
Xuezhou, what are you doing here?
I'm here to help you
with your discharge
and bring you home.
Discharge?
You don't wanna leave?
No, I mean...
I mean...
Quit dilly-dallying, let's go now.
I haven't...
- I...
- Big sister,
why is it so messy here?
My favour.
The restaurant is here
, you can go in first.
I'll come after I park my car.
Good evening, Guru Bai Qi.
Good evening, Dr. Bai.
Come with me.
So this is the favour
that you prepared for me?
That's right, come on.
How is it? Do you like it?
It's actually pretty good.
Dr. Bai,
are you from a wealthy family?
No, why do you ask?
Look.
With your wage as a doctor,
how is it possible to reserve
such a big restaurant?
You should be a hidden
rich second generation.
When will your mum take five million
for me to leave you?
You think too much.
I'm absolutely not any of that.
This restaurant right here,
belongs to Su Zelin's family.
He offered to lend it to me.
The five million in
my hand is gone now.
Quit dreaming, let's start our dinner.
Is it good?
It's pretty good.
Let me guess.
You're here to pick me up.
Congratulations, you've guessed it.
It's quite late now,
where are we heading?
Where would you like to go?
I've been a puppet for half a day now.
My neck and lumbar hurt.
And I'm starving.
How about we...
Why don't you go to the
hospital for a checkup instead?
And work a shift after.
Not bad.
I will now stay inside
your car no matter what.
How can it be?
With your sore legs and lumbar,
what if you die in my car?
They don't hurt anymore,
I'm not starving anymore too.
Okay then.
For the sake of you
being helpful to me today,
I'll treat you a meal.
Can I choose the dishes?
Get off my car.
Comfortable.
How was it? Does it taste good?
This is the best restaurant
I've had in a few years.
Give me a moment.
I've prepared you a surprise.
What is this?
Break it open and you'll know, come on.
Me?
This is you.
Is it us during high school?
That's right.
You told me that
showing appreciation
should be ritualistic.
You said that in manga before.
This is really adorable.
I'm sad to eat it.
That's perfect.
I have something to tell you.
You can eat it afterwards.
You wouldn't be
trying to propose right?
No.
Good, that's good.
You scared me.
You made it so ritualistic
I thought
it was a diamond ring in the cake.
So if I really propose to you,
this would be your reaction?
No, it wouldn't.
I mean...
Well...
Anyway, what exactly were you saying?
Qin Ge.
I think, as we reunited not long ago,
we still need some time.
Also previously you have your secret
and your concern.
I could slowly approach you,
until you open your heart.
But now that there's no more
secret between you and me,
I hope that you could give me a chance
to pursue you once again.
Okay?
(How can anyone reject
facing such an expression?)
(But it's only three
months after we met again,)
(I'm already falling so deep.)
(I need to be more reserved.)
I would like to
use the toilet.
Watch out!
So this is the closest spot
with medication which you mentioned!?
Yes.
With those words you said to me
in the restaurant
and you're getting handsy with me now,
and your house is just nearby,
I'm now doubtful about your intention.
It was really a coincidence.
Su Zelin really lent me the restaurant.
And it's quieter staying here
in suburb.
It only takes 20 minutes for me to
head to the hospital
for work every time,
through the ring expressway.
You can ask me later
regarding trust issue.
Allow me to apply some medicine for you.
Done.
Watch out.
Those words you said to me
in the restaurant,
I'm not sure how am I
supposed to respond.
Do you plan to reject me?
No I don't, I mean,
I'm not sure what to reply.
I can't be sure now.
To be frank,
there's no need to rush
giving me an answer.
So long you don't intend to reject me,
I'm already glad.
Why are you being so
forgiving towards me?
The last time in Western Restaurant,
if I didn't show up,
would you be disappointed?
No I won't.
I'll try again if I failed this time.
And I'll still try again
if I failed the next time.
I will keep waiting for you.
Min.
Boss, are you done yet?
Do you want me to
come over and fetch you?
It's fine, I'm already home.
You should rest earlier, byebye.
Why are you lying to him?
This doesn't count as lying right?
If Min knows that
I'm at your place so late at night,
he will go crazy again.
He is very naive,
it will definitely scare him.
Naive?
Only you would think so.
What?
Nothing.
Why don't you stay here tonight?
Bai Qijia, I knew you
have bad intention!
Take a look outside,
it's almost morning now.
It's hard to order a ride here.
If I send you home and come back here,
it will waste a lot of time.
Why not just stay here for a night,
plus you should let your wound heal up.
I'm terrifying while sleeping, I
grind teeth, snore.
And I sleepwalk too, it's horrible!
It's fine.
Not like it's new to me.
Then I'll use the couch!
No, you can use my bed,
I'll use the couch.
No! No! No!
I'll sleep on the couch!
I...I'll sleep...
No need!
It seems to me that you
miss what happened last time
very much.
How about this time
we really make it happen?
You...
Bai Qijia.
I'm now a patient.
Please control yourself.
It's okay.
You just couldn't get too tired.
I won't let you get tired.
You...
Don't worry.
I won't make hickey on your neck
anymore.
Bai Qijia!
Good night.
Buzz off!
Morning.
Good morning.
Where have you been?
I've bought you breakfast.
You look pretty good in pink.
Really?
I'll put them on for
you more often then.
Go on, have a seat.
Go on.
After breakfast, I'll send you home.
You can take a nap.
I don't mean like that,
don't be too confident.
I'm busy, I'll get going now.
I've bought these
already, please have some.
Have some before you go.
Have you heard it?
Manager Xia gave an ultimatum,
demanding Editor Lin
to amend according to
Boss Qian Ye's solution.
If Editor Lin still wants to protect
Guru Bai Qi's work,
then we couldn't protect her anymore.
Right, even Editor Lin's
position to voice out
has been confiscated by Manager Xia.
Since Miss Bai Qi already
sold her works,
why can't she amend
following investor's idea?
I hope that you could give me a chance
to pursue you once again.
Okay?
Actually,
there's no need to rush for the answer.
So long you're not rejecting me,
I'm already glad.
What's for the lunch?
I'll deliver it to you.
Didn't you say that I
could take my time?
It's okay.
(Lunch time isn't much.)
(It takes a long time
for him to travel here.)
(But would it hurt if I
reject his offer?)
So fast?
Coming!
Boss.
Min.
King Bai.
(Doctor's Office)
(I've eaten already.)
(I'm taking a nap,
kindly not interrupt.)
I thought Su Lun and all
will accept such a compromised solution.
What on earth is Xia
Chuyun trying to do?
Why is she so against Xuezhou?
Xia Chuyun is sent from the
Group Editor-in-Chief Office.
Xuezhou's performance was
improved too quickly in recent years.
It must have pressured her.
And our collaboration
with Qian Ye this time
falls into a deadlock.
Even the group executives
who look up to her
see this as Xuezhou's
responsibility as editor-in-chief.
But Xuezhou didn't tell me any of this.
Xuezhou doesn't want you to worry.
However, I think you,
as the original author,
should have the
right to know all of this.
I understand now.
The biggest issue between
Qianye Film & TV
and us
is being stuck on the editing idea.
Min.
What if I told you,
I want to try again.
Would you help me?
You mean...
Without informing Xuezhou,
revise the idea according to Su Lun?
The sooner we could deliver it
Su Lun,
the sooner Xuezhou could escape
from Xia Chuyun's clutches.
Got it.
Boss, I will support you forever!
- Come on!
- Go! Go!
(Nephrology)
(Are you up yet?)
(Would you fancy a dinner together?)
(Fingertip Comics)
I knew I could meet you here.
I've sent you so many
messages, you ignored all of them.
Don't go.
What is it? Having a mood swing?
Yes I'm not in mood,
don't mess with me.
Be careful, I will vent my anger on you.
Don't keep it to yourself.
I'll take you somewhere to let it out.
What are you thinking?
Drinking is unhealthy,
fighting is illegal.
I'll take you somewhere that
you could relieve scientifically.
Let's go!
What are you doing?
(Are you awake? Would you
like to have dinner together?)
Am I pushing her too much?
Procrastinator Bai.
What are you doing this late?
So noisy around you.
It's a complicated situation.
Please tell quickly.
The thing is,
I asked Qin Ge out today,
twice.
She rejected me.
It's normal.
Hold on.
You can win.
Lu Tian.
Didn't expect this is
really your expertise.
Don't you need a break?
Stop talking nonsense!
Please! At least tell me why.
Because there is someone
trying to touch my people.
When did you have someone?
It's Qin Ge!
Guru Bai Qi.
Isn't Guru Bai Qi
with Procrastinator Bai?
Qin Ge is with me!
Okay she is with you.
But it's not necessary to
vent your anger on me right?
Let me tell you.
My four-year effort was gone.
It's my incapability.
Couldn't protect Qin Ge.
Who told you that?
You're the hardest working and
most excellent lady I've ever seen.
What a glib tongue.
It's true.
I've never seen anyone
works in private movie cafe.
You're literally the
business role model!
I'll believe you one time.
By the way.
Why are you not fighting back?
Are you letting me win?
I'm a gentleman, I don't fight women.
Aren't you a man?
Don't be afraid.
Fight if you're a man.
I'm afraid?
Look at you.
You know about K.O.
Come on.
♪Light shines through window
before a mirror♪
♪Incense smoke outlines your appearance♪
♪Enclosed in the vivid past♪
♪Those miseries
which I'm the sole audience♪
♪In the imagination of our future♪
♪You appear in every scroll♪
♪I think I have lost my mind♪
♪The world is blooming for you♪
♪Ignoring the flaws and truths♪
♪With you by my side, I have no fears♪
♪Light shines through window
before a mirror♪
♪Incense smoke outlines your appearance♪
♪Enclosed in the vivid past♪
♪Those miseries
which I'm the sole audience♪
♪In the imagination of our future♪
♪You appear in every scroll♪
♪I think I have lost my mind♪
♪The world is blooming for you♪
♪Ignoring the flaws and truths♪
♪With you by my side, I have no fears♪