All right. It's finally the last day.
At the end of every
season of "Love Catcher,"
I feel sad because it's over,
but it's also the day when
everyone's identities are revealed.
- I'll feel so light-hearted.
- I can't wait.
Yes, we'll be able to find out
the identities of all eight people.
Oh my goodness.
(Today's Question: Who
are the Love Catchers?)
Not the Money Catchers?
If we find out the Love Catchers,
the others will automatically be...
Money Catchers.
Is there anyone you're certain is a Love
Catcher even before we see the video?
Well, I believe we think
Won-jae is a Love Catcher.
- That's right. I agree.
- Won-jae is a Love Catcher.
- I think Su-won is a Love Catcher.
- Same here.
I think I'm pretty certain that
these two are Love Catchers.
Actually, I was sure that
Ha-neul is a Love Catcher.
However, when Su-won asked
her questions last time, she wouldn't
give him answers but instead
respond with questions of her own.
Why does she keep hiding her feelings?
Does she have something to hide?
So I kind of suspected her
of being a Money Catcher.
What do you think Jae-hyung is?
Like, his identity as a person.
Not whether he's a Love or Money.
If he's a Money Catcher,
he could've fabricated his profile.
He even has a building
that he built himself.
I wonder if that picture is real.
Last week, there was a new love triangle.
- Won-jae, Da-na, and Ji-min.
- That's right.
Do you want to ask him?
If it's okay, you can
spend one or two hours...
(Towards the end, the relationship of
these three people got really tangled up.)
- We didn't hear her answer yet.
- Yeah.
- I'm so curious.
- That's what I really want to know.
(Remaining time until the final selection)
There are about seven hours left.
Will they spend the rest of the
time with their current dates?
(Amidst fierce competition, Su-won and
Ha-neul are having a peaceful date.)
- Did you tell them we're coming?
- Yes.
- Where?
- Tell them?
Wow, I can't believe
I'm taking you...
to my restaurant.
Oh, really?
- That's right. Ha-neul runs a restaurant.
- What's going on?
My family will be there...
I really get along with parents.
Su-won is really nervous, isn't he?
If Ha-neul really is a Money Catcher, that
means her parents are playing along?
If she's a Money Catcher, once this is
over, they'll be like, "Hey, that was fun!"
Don't worry. I'll be good.
I'm really good at charming mothers.
I've never met a mother
who doesn't like me.
Su-won is really confident.
Does your older sister know your dating
history?
Do you share that
information with each other?
- She knows everything.
- She does?
- Yeah.
- I see.
Then I guess after we
meet, she'll evaluate me.
Totally.
(Nervous)
She probably will.
But my sister likes
good-looking people.
I see.
I hope she'll give me compliments.
They're like a couple
that's about to get married.
It's like they're fixing a
date for their wedding.
They really seem like Love Catchers.
- Is this it?
- Yeah.
Now that we're here, I'm
kind of getting nervous.
Oh my goodness.
- There are many wreaths.
- That means the restaurant just opened.
That's why she was described
as a "beautiful rookie owner."
- Hello.
- Welcome!
- Hello!
How have you been?
(Her mom and sister
welcome them with open arms.)
We have to see if they're awkward.
I'm checking if the restaurant is fake.
Come sit here.
- I bought this for you.
- Thank you.
Introducing him to her family must mean...
- How have you been?
- Good.
- Did you have fun?
- Yeah.
I see.
- Did you treat my daughter well?
- Yes.
She nearly spent the week with me.
- I see.
- Yes.
(Embarrassed)
What do I do?
- He said he's good with parents.
- Of course he's nervous.
What do you want to eat?
How about hot pot and rice balls?
- Two servings of hot pot and rice balls?
- Yes, please.
- I'll bring those to you.
- I can tell she's beautiful.
- Wait here.
- Okay.
Thank you.
(Ha-neul is uneasier
in front of her family...)
(and Su-won is clearly nervous.)
What do you think?
You said it just opened recently.
It's really clean.
There are a lot of plants.
It seems like a plant store.
- Aren't you nervous?
- Nervous? Kind of...
- I don't know what to do.
- Me neither.
Why am I so nervous today?
(The hot pot that will save them
from this awkwardness is here.)
- Thank you.
- Hold on.
(Will things get better
if they start eating?)
- Thank you.
- It's hot.
Okay. It's fine.
(Glance)
(Unlike usual, Su-won is really nervous.)
- Can I... sit down for a moment?
- Sure.
Su-won's getting paler and paler.
Moms can see right through you.
- She can tell if he's Love or Money.
- Right.
(How will her mom see Su-won?)
- It's hot, huh?
- How was it?
How was it?
- We... had a good time.
We spent the week together. - Really?
We were at the house together,
and it felt like...
Ha-neul and I knew each other for years.
I see.
You must like Ha-neul.
Fortunately, she responded to my feelings.
I see.
(Embarrassed)
Ha-neul seems bright and down-to-earth,
but she's very soft-hearted,
and she cries easily.
She's the youngest, so she's very lovable.
Right.
I like down-to-earth people.
Then that's perfect.
- That's wonderful.
- Yes.
Doesn't it seem like she approves of him?
- I hope it works out.
- Thank you.
She must like him.
- Enjoy.
- Thanks.
What do you think about him, Mom?
He's really handsome.
He seems like a very good-natured person.
- Oh, I do?
- Yes.
- You seem like someone with a
good heart, so I like you. - Thank you.
I'll make an effort so
that you will like me more.
- Yes, please do that.
- I will.
- Enjoy.
- Thank you.
- She gave me some compliments.
- Yeah, you made it.
(Relieved)
Her mother probably saw a lot
of things within that short time.
I'm curious what she thought.
Hang on.
Where... Where are you going?
To get some drinks.
(Ha-neul leaves for a bit, and
Su-won is left all alone.)
(Rice ball)
He looks uneasy. He
looks nervous and uneasy.
If you think he's okay...
- bring us Sprite.
- Okay.
If you don't think he's
okay, bring us Fanta.
- If I don't like him?
- Yeah.
(The sisters are coming up
with a secret plan in the corner.)
Do you like him?
(Ha-neul answers honestly.)
If she didn't, she wouldn't be
able to bring him to her restaurant.
(Ha-neul comes back.)
(Su-won gives her the
rice balls he rolled himself.)
Can you give me some w-w-water?
Oh no. He's shaking.
(Seems like he's still nervous.)
His throat is burning.
(So cute.)
(At last, Ha-neul's sister
appears with the drinks.)
(Please let it be Sprite...!)
(Does she like Su-won?)
(2nd Evaluation by
Ha-neul's sister: Approved)
Sprite!
(Trying to control her expression)
- This is hot. Hold on.
- Okay.
(Finally, the hefty clam hot pot is ready.)
If it weren't for COVID-19, we
could've eaten dinner there.
What was that place
called? Clam Gangster Lab?
"C.G.L."
What?
I was just abbreviating it.
Did you have a fun date?
Yes.
I mostly went on dates with Su-won.
Really?
- We danced together, too.
- What kind of dance?
It was like a sports dance.
We learned it for about two to
three hours and got assessed.
Assessed? What's your ranking?
- We didn't win.
- We didn't get first place,
but I think we beat
everyone in terms of looks.
Even though he's nervous,
he said that very clearly.
I think so. You're handsome, too.
- He's handsome, right?
- Yeah, he's really good-looking.
See? I knew my sister would like you.
I told him you like handsome guys.
Do you like to drink?
Ha-neul doesn't drink.
I'm not that good of a drinker either.
You two have a lot of things in common.
Yes, I think so.
(Nod)
Enjoy.
It might seem like she's carelessly
asking questions while cutting the food...
But each of those are barriers.
I can't believe we're having
the last date at my restaurant.
- But I think it's a meaningful location.
- Yeah, to me it is.
It's better than the common
places other couples go to.
I get to see your family.
I think it's great.
It kind of feels...
like I'm naked.
It feels like I'm showing you my true self.
It's not easy to introduce
your family members.
Right. That's a big deal.
We have to make our final
selection when we go back.
Right.
Don't you feel any pressure?
Even before...
we went on this last date today...
I already made up my mind.
I didn't ask you on a date
today to check your feelings.
I just wanted to spend
time with you today, too.
Oh my god. Woohoo!
I could see that...
you wanted to introduce me to your family.
So it gave me conviction.
I think he was touched.
(He honestly shares
his thoughts as always.)
That's how I feel.
What about you?
I think the biggest
thing I'm attracted to is
when the guy constantly
expresses his feelings for me.
I see.
From the first day until now,
I didn't feel have stronger
feelings for anyone...
than you.
It feels like we've
always known each other.
Yeah. It was comfortable
ever since the beginning.
Our conversations just flowed.
Right. They gave off couple
vibes ever since the beginning.
I didn't have a bad first
impression of her family.
Later on, if Ha-neul and I
become a true couple and I
see her family again, I
won't get on their wrong side.
Su-won must have felt awkward,
but he spoke very kindly
and tried really hard to get
along with my family, so
I felt really grateful.
- This couple is already...
- They'll pick each other.
At this rate, they're both Love Catchers.
- If they're not...
- There's no room for doubt.
(Remaining time until the final selection)
- I feel like you don't drink that much.
- Yeah, about once a week?
- I see.
- What about you?
Four days a week?
- Should we...?
- Hmm?
Once the sun sets a little,
should we go grab a drink?
Should we go grab a drink?
Really?
(Da-Na can't answer right away.)
They're getting to know each other.
So I think they'll be
curious about each other.
(Meanwhile, at Love Mansion...)
(Won-jae is endlessly waiting for Da-Na.)
(He's moving.)
(Rummage)
(Where is he doing?)
Won-jae changed his clothes first.
(Won-jae is ready to go out,
and Da-Na is still thinking.)
(Hesitate)
- Do you have plans tonight?
- Yeah.
Oh, really? Okay then.
What time do you have to be there by?
I think I need to reply to him now.
Oh, really? So you
haven't decided the time yet.
Yeah.
(They're together now,
but she'll be leaving soon.)
(And he'll have to watch that happen.)
It feels really strange.
- Of course it does.
- It's really strange.
The one you like is
contacting someone else.
(Thinking)
Do you want to ask him...
what time you're going to hang out?
If it's okay, you can
spend one or two hours...
Oh.
He's not giving up.
I was really nervous.
Her answer was going to
depend on who she likes more.
If she rejects me, then it's game over.
He changed his clothes first.
(Thinking)
(Ji-min? Won-jae?)
(Who will Da-Na choose?)
Gosh, it must be so hard for her.
(Remaining time until the final selection)
I thought I was going
to have a heart attack.
- The sound of the ticking clock...
- It's like Won-jae's nervous heart.
It really expresses that.
He's just holding onto his cell phone.
(Nervous)
(And Ji-min has moved locations.)
Oh, what's going on?
What's going on?
What's that?
They went to drink?
Did he go there alone?
Are there one or two plates?
There's something
in front of him.
- No, there isn't.
- There's no glass there.
He went to drink alone? What's going on?
That's so lonely.
(Sigh)
(A love triangle with one woman...
What is the fate of the two men?)
What happened?
What's going on? Who did
she go to? What happened?
Hurry!
(Won-jae?)
(Ji-min?)
(Da-Na has chosen Ji-min.)
See! Oh no!
Oh no.
Oh my god. This is actually happening?
Ji-min did it.
- All the food's here?
- They brought it just now.
What? Did you peel the peas?
(10 minutes ago)
(The sound of the phone
ringing is filling up the room.)
We thought she'd go to Won-jae.
He probably thought they
were going to meet up.
- Hello?
Hey. I called late, didn't I?
- What are you doing?
- Um, right now...
Ji-min said he made
reservations at an Izakaya.
- Okay.
- So I just got here.
- I can't watch!
- I don't want to hear it.
(Does he have to wait longer?)
Where is that restaurant?
- Samseong.
- Samseong?
Yes, that's right.
Then when you're done,
can you just stay there?
I'll go to you when you're ready.
Oh, you will?
This is hard. She's on a date, but
she also made a promise with Won-jae.
(Da-Na is standing at a
crossroads of decisions again.)
- Won-jae.
- Yeah?
I'll make sure to go to you by 8 o'clock.
Let's eat when I get there.
His expression...
Aren't you eating with him?
Hmm, I won't eat a lot.
Is that okay?
Yeah, alright.
What do I do? I can't
watch this. It's too sad.
I can't watch this! Oh dear!
Okay. I'm sorry I couldn't keep my promise.
No, it's fine.
- Okay, see you later.
- I feel like he's gonna cry!
He's angry and hurt.
(Da-Na pushed back the date with Won-jae.)
(He has to wait again.)
(Did Da-na's heart go to Ji-min?)
(Mixed feelings)
It's unfortunate. It could've been better
if he had gone on a date with her first.
He might have wanted to
end the day with her, but...
We saw that Ji-min and
Da-na's date went so well.
It went well.
- It's really good, right?
- Yeah.
- Shall we have a drink?
- Shall we?
- Cheers.
(Their second date started with drinks.)
- Just drink a little bit.
- Why?
So that I can drink more.
(Kidding)
It's too precious. Don't drink a lot.
- Are you tying your hair?
- Yeah.
I usually wear my hair up.
You look pretty with your hair up
and some loose hair down.
She definitely seems comfortable with him.
Isn't there anyone you
want to talk more with?
(Thinking)
(Curious)
I think I had the most fun
when we talked in the car.
It was so much fun.
Our conversation kept flowing.
I enjoyed it, too.
That was really cute. I
should do that next time.
When you slide down that wall.
Wouldn't it be charming
if I just slid right down
to the floor and crawled
out through the other side?
(That's hilarious!)
In that aspect, I'm
grateful to you because...
you enjoy the time we spend together.
It's a lot of fun.
(Really?)
It's all great.
While staying at
Love Mansion, I really
liked seeing your bright
and confident sides.
Da-Na seems happy but unsure.
(Ji-min is actively
expressing his feelings.)
(And then there's silence.)
Why is there so little time?
Would things have been
different if there was more time?
I don't know about you, but I
observe people for a long time.
I'm supposed to look at every aspect.
There really wasn't enough
time to get to know you.
I was a bit late, wasn't I?
It's difficult. There's limited time.
(They're more affectionate because
there's not that much time left.)
Why is she crying?
I think it would have been really hard.
Why are you crying?
She has to keep making decisions,
and the guys are waiting for her.
We've never had time to share things.
We only talked briefly.
We didn't spend time together.
It is unfortunate.
(There was limited time,
and their timing was off.)
Why are you crying so much?
Why am I so indecisive?
- Goodness.
- I think I know how she feels.
First off,
it's not like only one person
showed interest in me.
It feels like...
What do you think?
Are you glad you came out?
I'm glad.
Honestly, whether you're a Love Catcher
or a Money Catcher doesn't matter to me.
I'm grateful to you because you
enjoy the time we spend together.
It's a lot of fun.
I'm really grateful
for their hearts, but...
I don't know what I should do.
They didn't really have a
chance to talk or hang out,
but their conversations
are smooth and comfortable.
But she can't ignore Won-jae either.
(The regret of being one step
late makes his eyes tear up as well.)
(What will they choose?)
If you're a Money Catcher,
choose me to be safe, okay?
Oh my gosh.
Oh my god! This is like a movie!
What? I just got goosebumps.
The hair on the back of my neck stood up.
- Oh my goodness.
- What is he saying?
He's even crying. It's so sorrowful
and desperate. What do we do?
He's being sincere.
If you're a Money Catcher,
choose me to be safe, okay?
Okay?
What? He's getting that emotional?
(Are his overflowing
feelings flowing as tears?)
(Emotional synchronization)
Oh no.
(Are we Love Catchers?)
(Remaining time until the final selection)
I wish time would go by slowly.
I'm glad we made centerpieces.
We get to keep them like a memento.
We should show these off.
We went early in the morning.
We have to show them off.
I wonder if anyone's here.
- Change and get some rest.
- Okay.
Here.
- Oh, Won-jae.
- He keeps looking at his phone.
- Did you go on a date?
- What?
Why would you ask? Don't ask him that!
He doesn't know.
- Did you go on a date?
- What?
(Su-won has no idea what's going on.)
You didn't?
No way.
You were just here the whole time?
That's unexpected.
Su-won, just go inside.
Don't ask him anymore questions.
Yeo-min!
Yeo-min and Won-jae...
What's wrong?
- It's my fault.
- What's wrong?
This whole thing is annoying.
(At the sight of Ha-neul,
she's flooded with sadness.)
My small decision...
- I seriously...
- No one knew it would turn out like this.
I couldn't even go on a date with him.
Won-jae, what happened?
Yesterday, Yeo-min
texted me asking if we can
see each other at lunch and talk.
I told her, "I'm sorry. I
already made plans, so I don't
think I can hang out with
you. Let's just talk here."
He didn't make any plans.
I didn't know they were
going to leave this place.
I thought they were
going to talk here like me.
I see.
I thought she was
going to come back soon.
But when I realized that wasn't the case...
I felt so bad that I couldn't
look at Yeo-min's face.
I get it.
I thought I was going mad in here.
I thought...
Da-Na was interested in you.
That's how I saw it.
You probably don't have to worry so much
just because she went on a date with him.
Of course, I'm sure that's not how
you feel since she's with him right now.
All I can tell you...
is that from Da-na's perspective,
it's right for her to spend time...
with different guys.
Just keep that in mind.
When she gets here,
you can talk it out with her.
The best thing you can
do is try to win her heart.
(Remaining time until the final selection)
- They're here.
- Oh, Ji-min.
I had a great time.
Me, too. I had fun.
Yeah, same here.
- Go in.
- Okay.
(For some reason, Ji-min's
footsteps seem light.)
(Glance)
(Won-jae fell asleep while waiting.)
- That's so sad!
- He's going to get a cramp in his neck.
- Oh no.
- Oh gosh. What's going on?
(His desperate wait can be felt from
the way he couldn't even lie down.)
(Toss)
(Won-jae fell into such a deep sleep that
he doesn't even realize Ji-min is back.)
Hey!
I'm back.
Your cheeks are flushed.
Where did you go?
- Bongeunsa.
- She's really flushed.
Bongeunsa? Where else?
We looked around Bongeunsa and
went to drink at an Izakaya nearby.
But why didn't you come back early?
Weren't you going to go
on a date with Won-jae?
It seemed like he's been waiting for you.
It'd be a good idea for you to
call Won-jae and talk to him a bit.
They must've been curious about that.
He woke up.
- He keeps checking his phone.
- It's so hard.
(There's no word from Da-Na yet...)
He spots him.
Oh, he's here.
I just woke up, but it
seemed like she was back.
He sees that Ji-min is back.
Da-Na came back, but
she didn't contact him yet.
(Eventually, he calls her first.)
(Da-Na isn't picking up.)
I don't think it's a bad idea
for you to go there directly.
Wouldn't that be better?
I think it is.
There are only two hours left.
(There's no time to waste.
Won-jae goes to Da-Na first.)
(Da-Na just happens to be with Yeo-min.)
Hold on. Just give me five
minutes. No, three minutes.
(Yeo-min puts on a brave smile.)
Go on.
I want to give Yeo-min a hug.
Gosh, my heart breaks.
Go on.
(It's a game where the one
who loves more will lose.)
(Stumble)
This one day is more
intense than the first six days.
Right. It all just
comes crashing down.
This one last day of
the final selection is...
It's like a roller coaster.
It's full of twists.
(The moon is oblivious to his
heartbreak and shines brightly.)
(It's almost time for the final selection.)
(And these two don't have much time left.)
(Won-jae waited all day for
her, but he's not saying anything.)
(Peek)
- You can cover yourself with this.
- No, it's fine.
- Your legs must be cold.
- He's still taking care of her.
(But it's still hard to
say the first word.)
I'm sorry for making you wait.
I'm really sorry.
(Won-jae is still quiet.)
(Did his feelings change?)
Honestly...
I've been waiting for you to get
back and call me the whole day.
I didn't need anything else.
(Da-Na can't say anything.)
You should've told me
if you couldn't make it.
Hmm... I'm sorry...
I could've waited as long as you
wanted me to before the 24 hours was up.
Waiting isn't a problem.
I was just waiting...
for the call that you got back.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for making you come find me.
Nothing happened, right?
Did you get hurt or something?
No, it's nothing like that.
(While waiting, his nervousness
and worry had grown.)
You must've felt horrible while
you were waiting. I'm really sorry.
Honestly, I did feel horrible earlier.
But I feel better after seeing you now.
I'm glad that I can at least see you now.
He's really a Love Catcher, isn't he?
Why do you look so upset?
Smile for me. You look
really pretty when you smile.
Oh, Won-jae!
It's natural that she's in a predicament.
So did you make up your mind?
I'm not sure.
(After waiting a long time, the
only answer he gets is uncertainty.)
I think it really hit him for the first
time that Da-Na is in a dilemma. Right?
Yes, that's right.
(His heart crumbles at her answer.)
I don't know how Da-Na feels.
(Would it have been better not to ask her?)
No one knows your identity except for you.
Right?
But if...
if you're a Money Catcher...
If you are...
and you're really sure...
that I'm a Love Catcher...
Please don't do this.
Then choose me.
How can both of them say that?
How can they say the same thing?
- They don't care about her identity.
- It means nothing.
They're not interested.
They just like Da-Na.
This is crazy.
Then choose me.
(Close)
(That's what he's been wanting
to tell her after all this time.)
What are you saying?
I know. It's nonsense.
But I want you to at
least choose me for this.
You promised, okay?
Promise me one more time.
(He's expressing his
desperation like a joke.)
Gosh, Da-Na is in such a tough situation.
(Da-Na can't easily reach out.)
I'm sorry.
She didn't promise him.
She didn't do a pinky promise.
Did she decide to go with Ji-min?
I'm sorry.
(In the end, Da-Na didn't promise him.)
(She apologized instead of
promising him... What did she decide?)
(What results will they face...?)
I'm back.
Why are you so down though?
- Did you have fun?
- Yeah.
What's wrong?
I'm having a mental breakdown.
- Why?
I don't know where I should start.
Did she change her mind?
(Women's powder room)
Everyone is in complicated
situations for different reasons.
(Last time to get ready before
the final selection/Glance)
Da-Na.
Toss me over there.
What's wrong with you? You did fine.
No. Why is it so hard?
- What's hard?
- Exactly...
I can't choose...
(Da-na's feelings are
as complicated as ever...)
(Remaining time until the final selection)
God, I wonder what will happen.
I think she's gonna choose you.
That's what my hunch says.
- Even now?
- Yeah. I think she's gonna pick you.
That's how I feel.
What's wrong?
I really, really enjoyed the date.
It was really fun, and Jae-hyung
was funny and considerate.
But I feel really apologetic.
I don't know if I made
the right choice or not.
Isn't that what everybody thinks?
(It's hard to be certain
of anything right now.)
(Remaining time until the final selection)
(Men's dorm)
Did you make up your mind?
I have to decide now.
There's not much time left.
(Ji-min drops his gaze.)
I'm probably gonna go with the person
I've liked ever since the beginning.
The moment I was sure, I didn't
look at anyone else and decided that...
I was going to choose her.
It's a declaration of war.
Same here. The moment I was sure...
she was the only one for me.
(Whose heart will reach hers?)
It's so scary now.
I think I know your identity now.
There's a reason you must be nervous.
- What?
- Because she's a Love Catcher?
Because she's a Money Catcher?
Do you think that the
person you're going to
choose is a Love Catcher
or a Money Catcher?
I don't know.
- I think he's a Money Catcher.
- So do I...
If they're all Money Catchers,
then who are the Love Catchers?
- You think he's a Money Catcher, too?
- I have no idea.
I seriously don't know.
I really don't know. The
guys are ambiguous.
I have no clue, but I just
said he's a Money Catcher.
- It's ambiguous.
- I think Su-won is a Love Catcher though.
(Confused)
If I were you, I bet Su-won
has a lot on his mind.
- Because he's worried?
- Yeah.
Wow, if Ha-neul is really a
Money Catcher... then, wow...
I'm super nervous. Am I the only one?
No, of course we're nervous.
What about you? I'm curious about you.
I'm anxious.
God, I feel so weird.
(Remaining time until the final selection)
(Today's Question: Who
are the Love Catchers?)
Now it's time for the final selection.
Did everyone decide?
We have to decide, too.
What do you think?
- Who did I choose again?
- This is tough.
Was Da-Na sorry because
she's a Love Catcher?
(Sunny is quietly putting up her cards.)
Won-jae, Su-won, Yeo-min, and Ji-min.
I just picked the people I'm drawn to.
Aren't you drawn to someone
because they're sincere?
So I picked the ones
we are a bit more curious
about and want to know
what happens to them next.
That's who I chose.
I pick these three: Won-jae,
Yeo-min, and Su-won.
I just took out everyone who
seemed like Money Catchers,
and they were the ones left.
- It's pretty much the same for me.
- Really?
I pick Won-jae, Su-won, and Yeo-min.
- I'm thinking about Da-Na.
- Da-Na?
- I was stuck, so I looked at my outfit.
- Again?
I have three buckles.
I see.
- So there are three Love Catchers.
- Alright.
I pick Won-jae and Su-won.
Everyone's picking those two.
Ha-neul, Ji-min, and Dana.
I'm sure that Won-jae is a Love Catcher.
I think these participants
are definitely Love Catchers.
That's who I'm sure of so far.
I kept thinking that
Ji-min is a Money Catcher.
If you're a Money Catcher...
choose me to be safe, okay?
- Wow, I was... - He meant it?
- As an actor, you didn't think
he was faking it? - No, his emotions...
So I bet my all on him.
I think Ha-neul and Ji-min are...
a union of Money Catchers.
Seriously? Ji-min, too? I think
he's a real Love Catcher though.
Those who get it right
will get one coin, not two.
But you will get one coin per right answer.
- You could turn the tables.
- I'm sure I got at least one right.
Now, let's check the results
we were all curious about.
(It will be revealed right now!)
I just hope nothing scary will happen.
Please.
Matching rings?
- The Love Catcher couples will get rings.
- That's right.
I want to see them put those rings on.
(1. Each of the
participants will take the box
containing their identity
and stand in their position.)
I bet they're really nervous.
(2. They will go to their final
choice and deliver their identity box.)
(3. If they choose each
other, they will open
each other's boxes to
check their identities.)
(4. If they don't get selected,
they will deliver their
identity box to the person
they want and leave.)
- Who's going first?
- Who is it?
- Su-won?
- It's Su-won.
Gosh, he must be really nervous.
(Will Ha-neul choose Ha-neul as always?)
- He'll go to Ha-neul.
- I'm sure he will.
- Oh, why is he...?
- Why is he so slow?
He must be nervous.
Why did he stop?
What's going on?
This is very different from
the Su-won we've seen so far.
What's happening?
What is it?
I guess they get nervous at that moment
even if they know their choice.
(Ha-neul can't look at him.)
(Su-won is hesitating. Is he a
Money Catcher or a Love Catcher?)
(Jung Su-won has selected Lee Ha-neul.)
He really has eyes for only one person!
Ha-neul...
Thanks for making my heart
flutter while we were here.
I hope tomorrow's sky
will be beautiful, too.
(Giving the girls a heart attack)
(What's with that line?)
I kind of got goosebumps.
I hope tomorrow's sky
will be beautiful, too.
Why does my heart flutter?
(Su-won gives her the
box with his identity inside.)
- Su-won is a Love Catcher, right?
- Please.
(Does she feel the same way?)
Ha-neul has to choose Su-won
in order to know his identity.
If they're not Love Catchers...
It's Jae-hyung.
(This moment, he thinks about
all the memories at Love Mansion.)
I'm really curious about Jae-hyung.
Seriously.
(Who will be his final selection?)
(In-seong, the one he enjoyed
the final date with at the beach?)
(Or Da-Na, the one who made
him feel true nervousness?)
(Or is there someone
else on his mind?)
(Jae-hyung suddenly turns his direction.)
- Where is he going?
- What's happening?
(Seo Jae-hyung has selected...)
(Lee In-seong.)
I had fun today.
I want to have more fun with you.
- Oh my goodness!
- Thank you.
In-seong...
Why does her expression look so cold?
Gosh, I'm nervous.
(In-seong's expression is unreadable.)
(She can only check his
identity if she picks him.)
Won-jae, let's go
(He quickly passes by Ji-min.)
(Ji-min watches Won-jae's back.)
It's Da-Na, right?
Probably.
If only she had linked
her pinky with his...
If she had, he would've run to her.
Yes, that's like him.
He's not sure, but...
(He didn't get a clear answer
from the wavering Da-Na.)
(Does he still feel the
same way about her?)
Is he going to Da-Na?
- Yeo-min.
- I'm nervous!
I wish things worked out for her.
(Yeo-min isn't his choice.)
It's such a hard time for Yeo-min.
He's firmly heading towards her.
(Kang Won-jae has selected Jung Da-Na.)
(Ji-min is also watching his selection.)
Don't think about anything else.
Just know that this is my sincerity.
(You really are a Love Catcher!)
His words are sad, too.
Just know that this is my sincerity.
- He's the one we firmly believe
is a Love Catcher. - Won-jae...
(Is he a Love Catcher
who has come to find love?)
(Or is he a Money
Catcher putting on an act?)
(Did Won-jae's sincerity reach her?)
(On his way back, they
see each other again.)
(They avoid eye contact.)
(Are they choosing the same person?)
(He can't hide his nervousness.)
Won-jae is nervous.
Ji-min.
His expression is different from usual.
(Will he choose Ha-neul, the one
who he was always close with?)
(Or Da-Na, the one he cried
while making a confession to?)
(Who will Ji-min select?)
Su-won can't take his eyes off of Ji-min.
They both can't for different reasons.
(Ji-min stops in his tracks.)
What's going on? Why is he doing
that like he's a Money Catcher?
Don't do that! What are you doing?
He's pondering?
Don't do it, Ji-min.
(Who is the one that is
making him think so hard?)
(Ji-min continues walking.)
(Is he going to Ha-neul?)
- Really?
- For real?
(He passes by her.)
Oh, he passed by.
- He'll probably go to Da-Na.
- Yeah.
(The closer Ji-min goes to Da-Na,
the stiffer Won-jae's expression gets.)
Oh gosh, I feel bad for
Won-jae. This is driving me crazy.
(Da-Na was already chosen by Won-jae.)
(Ahn Ji-min has selected Jung Da-Na.)
If it's okay with you...
I want to see you again.
- Is Dana a Love Catcher?
- Is she a Money Catcher?
Thanks.
- I had fun.
- Thanks.
Da-Na has been selected
by Won-jae and Ji-min.
I can't wait to find out who she chooses.
(How will their love triangle end?)
Gosh, this is suffocating.
- The men are done choosing.
- Right.
- They're all done?
- Yes.
Everyone's identities will be revealed
after the women make their choices.
Here it comes. Something
big is going to happen.
- What do we do?
- Oh, Yeo-min!
(Yeo-min, the first one,
starts making her way.)
(She hadn't gotten selected by anyone.)
Yeo-min, give it to me.
- Won't she go to Won-jae?
- I think so.
Is it Won-jae, the one she
lost because of wrong timing?)
(Yeo-min slowly walks towards him.)
Why are you crying?
(Lee Yeo-min has selected Kang Won-jae.)
Thank you so much for coming
to pick me up on the first day.
I meant all the things I did
for you and the things I said.
Thank you for everything.
I want to thank you, too.
- Yeo-min is a Love Catcher!
- She's a Love Catcher.
She said she really
meant it and thanked him.
- Yeo-min is seriously so cool.
- She's awesome.
(She calmly says her goodbye and leaves.)
(Her last words that she was sincere)
- Is her identity being revealed now?
- Yes.
(I chose Yeo-min, too.)
Thank God.
(I'm the only one who
didn't choose... Yeo-min.)
- She's a Love Catcher, right?
- She is.
(He has to check her identity alone.)
Money.
(Won-jae stares at her
identity for a long time.)
What's with that reaction?
I'd rather she be a Money Catcher.
(Love? Money?)
(Lee Yeo-min = Money Catcher)
- Damn it.
- "Damn it"?
- For real?
- What's this?
Oh my god. I'm speechless.
My neck...
That's why she said everything
she did to him was sincere!
Because she's a Money Catcher!
- Or maybe because she really liked him.
- Precisely.
Oh my goodness.
(After checking her identity,
he's overwhelmed with bitterness.)
- Wow, but she really seemed like
a Love Catcher. - She did.
- I'm not off to a bad start.
- I think I'm doomed.
In-seong.
She seemed to have a lot on her mind.
(Will she choose Ji-min, the one she
had a good time doing the challenge with?)
(Or Jae-hyung, the one who
chose her after their last date?)
(They don't know each other's
identities, so she's more careful.)
Won't she go to Jae-hyung?
(Jae-hyung is to her right.)
(Ji-min is to her left.)
(In-seong, who had hesitated,
heads towards Jae-hyung.)
- For real?
- He can't hide his joy.
It's been a while since I've seen
the right corner of his lips go up?
He suddenly seems like a Love Catcher.
(Lee In-seong has selected Seo Jae-hyung.)
I truly had a great time today.
Me, too.
She said "truly." She's a Money Catcher.
"Truly."
- Don't say that word.
- "I truly had a great time today."
- If she said that, that means...
- She's a Money Catcher?
(It's time to check
each other's identities.)
Should we open it?
Yeah.
I hope they're both Love Catchers!
(What are their identities?)
At the same time?
- Look at their expressions.
- What? Why?
They're relieved!
I'm glad.
- I'm glad.
- I'm so glad.
Are they both Money Catchers?
Gosh, what a relief.
- They're either both Love
or both Money, right? - Yup.
- I'm glad.
- This is better.
This is actually better.
What's going on?
- Should we check one more time?
- Yeah.
They're Money Catchers.
They tend to check twice.
"Did I see it wrong?"
- Should we check one more time?
- Yeah.
In-seong is...
- She's a Money Catcher! Money, money!
- Yeah, it worked out better.
What about Jae-hyung?
- He's a Money Catcher.
- He's Money.
- They're a Money Catcher couple.
- Money, money.
I got it all right!
Oh my god. That's crazy.
- If the rest are Love Catchers...
- Won't you win first place?
There should be no more Money Catchers.
(The birth of a Money Catcher couple)
(They crack up at each other's identities.)
Gosh, this is better.
Jinx.
They're a couple.
- They're the most interesting couple.
- This is funny.
- It's interesting.
"It's interesting."
Now I know why Jae-hyung
looked so uncomfortable!
- That's because he's a Money Catcher!
- He had to hide it.
- He had to keep lying.
- He looks relaxed now.
I see now.
Good work, Jae-hyung.
I feel at ease now.
(The third one to go is Ha-neul.)
(Everyone is curious
about Ha-neul's choice.)
- What do we do?
- This is really important.
(Ha-neul walks without
a smile on her face.)
She's wearing the most
makeup today out of all the days.
Oh, did she perhaps
paint a mole on her face?
(Who will she choose?)
(Is it Su-won, like everyone wishes?)
(Will her footsteps reach him?)
(Or will she go to Ji-min,
who has always been by
her side whenever she was
going through hardships?)
(If she doesn't choose Su-won,
they will fail to become a couple.)
(What is her final selection?)
I thought I was going
to get a heart attack!
(Lee Ha-neul has chosen Jung Su-won.)
They both have to be Love Catchers.
They're our official couple.
(Nervous)
- You knew I would come, right?
- Huh?
You knew I would come, right?
I was... I was hoping you would.
Do I give it to you?
Thanks for coming.
She's not looking at him.
- I feel uneasy!
- No, it can't be!
No, no.
Thanks for coming.
Oh, what was that?
Their identities are important.
Yeah.
Please both be Love Catchers.
- Aren't you nervous?
- Huh?
I am.
Wow, this is really...!
(Are they nervous because they
don't know each other's identities?)
Please!
Why can't you look at me?
See? She can't make eye contact with him!
(Is it because she's nervous?
Or is it because she's sorry?)
Maybe it's because she's shy
since they're both Love Catchers!
Some people suspected
her of being a Money Catcher.
Ha-neul? No way.
- Is Su-won a Money Catcher?
- No, he's Love, right?
Should we reveal them at the same time?
(Nod)
Okay.
(Will they be able to smile together?)
(Please be Love Catchers!)
1, 2, 3.
(They opened the boxes!)
(Su-won and Ha-neul are checking
each other's identities at the same time.)
Didn't he just sigh?
Is that a good thing?
(They're not saying a word.)
Ha-neul shut her box, and
Su-won keeps staring at his.
- What's going on?
- Is she crying or laughing?
What's going on? What is it?
- Don't tell me.
- They're both Love Catchers!
They're Love Catchers,
right? Please say they are!
(Ha-neul = Money Catcher)
- I knew it!
- This is crazy!
- Money!
- Wow!
I got goosebumps.
But we thought he was a Money Catcher.
I think he's a Love Catcher.
(Su-won = Love Catcher)
(They were so shocked
by Ha-neul's identity
that they got shocked
by the coin's shadow.)
Oh, Su-won!
Oh my god, I think he'll be so heartbroken.
- Seriously.
- I knew it!
Poor Su-won.
Su-won was even thinking about how
they'll have a long-distance relationship.
Then was she playing hard-to-get?
Oh no.
Did you change your identity or...
were you a Money
Catcher from the beginning?
From the beginning.
(She was a Money
Catcher from the beginning.)
Wow, I got goosebumps!
It was so scary when
she said that and smiled!
From the beginning.
(Grin)
(We were totally fooled!)
Even though she had a
chance to change, she didn't.
She kept playing as a Money Catcher.
This is crazy.
(After checking her identity,
he can't bring himself to talk.)
I don't know what to say.
He can't believe it.
- Oh, man.
- This is nuts.
I'm sorry.
I really...
thought you were a Love Catcher.
Oh, Su-won. I feel so bad for him.
This is so shocking.
(He's even more shocked
because he trusted her.)
(Eventually, he starts to tear up...)
- My heart breaks.
- This is so sad.
I really don't know who's who anymore.
I'm sorry...
(Ha-neul, who was a Money
Catcher, walks away...)
Su-won, don't cry.
Su-won had felt really guilty
about going to Da-Na that one time.
Wow, but I think he
got really hurt this time.
This program is about the participants
playing as either Love or Money Catchers.
- Right.
- So she played a great game.
- She succeeded.
- Agreed.
- Oh, it's Da-Na!
- Da-Na.
She's the one I'm most curious about.
Whose box is that?
(This is the box of the one
who didn't get chosen by Da-Na.)
(Is it Ji-min? Or Won-jae?)
- Why does she suddenly
seem like a Love Catcher? - I know.
I suddenly feel that way, too.
I want to know who Da-Na will choose,
and I'm curious about the men's identities.
I'm dying to find out about Ji-min.
Were his tears fake or real?
(Her final selection)
- Are one of them Money?
- Are they both Money?
(The closer she gets, the
heavier her footsteps become.)
(She will go to...)
Who will she go to?
- Ji-min?
- Ji-min? Will she go to him?
(Or will she go to Won-jae, the
one who always looked at her?)
They both assured her of their feelings.
- That's right.
- They really did that.
They even told her that they
don't care if she's a Money Catcher.
She's passing by him.
Oh dear. This is crazy.
Oh no. Poor Ji-min.
(In the end, Ji-min wasn't chosen.)
Oh no. What's happening?
(Then she'll pick Won-jae, right?)
(Da-Na passes by Ji-min
and goes to Won-jae.)
Look at Won-jae.
(Smile)
(Jung Da-Na has chosen Kang Won-jae.)
Seriously, there are so many twists.
Ji-min and Da-Na looked so good together.
You really don't know until the end.
Wow, seriously.
- What's wrong with her expression?
- Why do you look so down?
I'll give you advice about your problems.
Sounds good.
- But why advice?
- She's saying she'll keep seeing him!
I see.
She's saying they should
get to know each other
slowly since she
observes people for a while.
(Finally, they exchange
their identity boxes.)
They must be so nervous.
Please both be Love Catchers.
What will they be?
There needs to be at least on Love Catcher.
(Now it's time to check
each other's identities.)
- Won-jae looks so...
- He's on cloud nine.
Please reveal your identities.
- I'm going to open it.
- Hang on.
What? Why?
(Why are you making me nervous?)
- Oh no!
- I hope they become a couple.
Yes, I hope they're both Love Catchers.
(What is Won-jae's identity?)
I hope Won-jae can be happy.
- I don't think I can check this.
- Why not?
- Huh?
- He must be nervous.
(Da-Na is holding Won-jae's identity box.)
Whatever you are...
I'm okay.
- Da-Na must be Love.
- Yeah.
This is awesome!
I think they're both Love Catchers.
Should we check now?
I hope they're both Love Catchers.
(Da-Na checks Won-jae's identity first.)
(She carefully opens his box.)
Please!
(After she checks it, her
expression looks kind of complicated.)
(And Won-jae gazes at her.)
- What?
- What is it?
He's not a Money Catcher, is he?
(Kang Won-jae = Love Catcher)
(Scared to death)
- I'm sorry! I doubted you!
- If he was a Money Catcher...
I almost got a heart attack!
(His pure love towards Da-Na was real.)
I feel like my health is worsening.
Please don't, Da-Na.
Don't frown. You're making me uneasy.
(What is Da-na's identity?)
(Love? Or Money?)
- He opened it.
- He saw it.
He has to smile.
- Don't tell me.
- Why did he close it?
(Her identity is...)
But I'm still grateful.
Is she Love?
I mean it.
Why is Da-Na so upset?
(Da-na's identity is finally revealed.)
(Please be a Love Catcher!)
I'm begging you!
(Jung Da-Na = Money Catcher)
- Oh goodness.
- Whatever!
(Someone save her!)
(Speechless 1/Speechless 2)
This is a horror program.
But this is what this program is about.
I'm sorry. I was too immersed in it.
Wow, but this is so shocking.
(The one Won-jae picked
is a Money Catcher.)
- I'm sorry...
- Oh dear.
I told you, it's okay.
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry.
I'm actually really grateful
that you kept your promise.
- I'm sorry.
- I'm truly thankful.
(She can't stop crying
because of his sincerity.)
Don't cry. Why are you crying?
(Da-Na can't bring herself to look at him.)
You're pretty when you smile.
Smile for me.
(We want to cry!)
Don't be like that.
- I want to send a DM to Won-jae!
- Seriously!
- I want to tell him to cheer up!
- Can we do a video message for him?
Goodness, he's trying not to make
her feel uncomfortable until the end.
But I think he'll struggle for a long time.
Bye.
(Eventually, Da-Na leaves
Won-jae and walks away.)
- This is so sad.
- This is really pitiful.
(Won-jae showed his
pure love until she left.)
This is what you
call "pure love," right?
- Seriously.
- Won-jae is so amazing.
He gave her his whole
heart in just seven days?
He's cool until the very end.
(There's another person who
didn't get picked by anyone.)
- Ji-min.
- He's smiling.
Ji-min is laughing in disbelief, right?
His eyes look sad though.
- I'm curious.
- Is he Money?
- He's a Money Catcher.
- Is he?
Money.
(Ji-min = Love Catcher)
He was a Love Catcher?
Ahn Ji-min was Love!
Those tears were genuine.
I want to send him a
message saying that I'm sorry!
He was a sincere person.
(One more coin!)
The most unfortunate thing was that
there were no Love Catcher couples.
- I'm so sad!
- This is really upsetting.
It's unfortunate.
(Final Results)
(Love Catchers: Won-jae,
Ji-min, and Su-won)
(Money Catchers: Jae-hyung,
Yeo-min, In-seong, Ha-neul, and Da-Na)
(Money Catchers: Da-Na & Ha-neul
Prize: $50,000)
(Amazing!)
Da-Na and Ha-neul won
the prize money of $50,000.
(Congratulations!)
Wow, it's shocking that no
one had changed their identities.
I expected some twists, but they
were so shocking that I'm dizzy.
How many did you get?
- I have four.
- Me, too.
They're tied.
What happens now?
What about that mini event?
If you're a Money Catcher,
choose me to be safe, okay?
I thought Ji-min was a Money Catcher.
Or maybe he said that
'cause he's a Money Catcher,
and he's saying choose
her so that she won't feel bad.
No, no, no. That's impossible.
- You don't say? How much you wanna bet?
- One coin!
Then I'll bet a coin, too.
(They had a mini event
where they bet coins.)
Ho-jun, you can't forget this!
(Since he won the mini
event, he got one coin.)
To Son Ho-jun, who got first place,
- I shall present him with a gold coin.
- Congratulations!
(Thanks to Do-yeon, he got the gold coin.)
Do-yeon, you're last place now.
I became a loser.
I shall accept that and live with
an apologetic heart towards Ji-min.
- Sounds good.
- The inference game is over.
How was it?
It was so much fun, and
I know this is just a game,
but I learned you
shouldn't trust people easily.
- Correct.
- I learned a lesson.
I also realized you shouldn't
grow weak at the sight of tears.
That's true.
It was so enjoyable, and
each and every one of them
was so charming that I
want to meet them in real life.
Right!
Then I'll sell this gold coin
and use it to pay for our dinner.
(Let's go party!)
I guess we're going to
Clam Gangster Lab then.
C.G.L.!
(Thank you for loving
"Love Catcher in Seoul.")
(After the final selection ended,)
(everyone's identities were revealed.)
(Revealing the Identities)
(Lee Ha-neul = Money Catcher)
(Jung Da-Na = Money Catcher)
(Ahn Ji-min = Love Catcher)
(Will you choose LOVE?
Or will you choose MONEY?)