(Seoul, the beautiful city
that represents Korea)
(A new love story that
will unfold in Seoul)
(The third "Love Catcher"
series: "Love Catcher in Seoul")
If I appear on "Love Catcher," I
might find someone I'm interested in.
I like a woman with a nice
smile who expresses herself well.
If we live together,
won't love find its way?
Honestly, I think everyone
will be beautiful and handsome.
My heart feels like it's about to
burst, and I think my ears grew red.
I believe in soulmates,
so I hope I find mine.
I'm curious what kind of
women will be on the show.
I'm very excited.
I think there might be someone
I'll fall in love with at first sight.
Won't there be some manly men?
I think there will be young people, too.
I'm sure there will be diverse people.
Of course, it'd be great if
there was a bearlike man.
I don't know how many people
are coming and what they'll be like,
but I'm hoping that
my ideal type will be there.
I hope there's someone who's
polite to others and takes care of me.
I'm sure everyone is good-looking.
I prefer someone tall.
I hope my ideal type will be here.
I don't care about age.
I hope there's someone who's
externally and internally my type.
Half of me is excited,
and half of me is scared.
There will be a bunch of strangers,
so I wonder what I'll have to say.
Aside from everything
else, I hope I can get
into a different
relationship than before.
(Young men and women came to find love.)
(They received a message.)
What's this?
It's a message.
(Check the profiles of
the opposite sex before
you meet the participants
for the first time.)
(Male. Age: 29. Job:
Researcher of a large company)
"Male God" of an
engineering college?
- Oh, their profiles!
- I guess their profiles are out now.
They can check the profiles first.
(I wanna see!)
- Do we need to write it down?
- Do we?
We're supposed to copy it?
(It suddenly turned
into a dictation contest.)
He constructed the
building himself. Oh my gosh!
There are diverse people. There's
even a 23-year-old college student.
It's obvious this person is handsome.
What makes you say that?
He's the ambassador of
Sungkyunkwan University.
He's the face of the school.
"Male God" of an
engineering college?
A lot of guys go there, and
he was the male god among them? Wow.
What's a "male god"?
- Man...
- God.
- Hang on. You know what
a goddess is, right? - Okay, I got it.
- So a male god is a man.
- Okay, I see.
- Wow!
- Whoa, a travel writer? That's cool.
Next up is the women.
Someone from California is here?
A dance teacher! Wow!
- So diverse.
- Dance is popular these days.
A novice beauty boss?
21 years old? She's the youngest.
She's the cover model of her school, too.
I can tell she's gorgeous.
That's it?
- Why don't the numbers match up?
- What's going on?
- There are five men...
- But there are four women.
- This actually makes it more interesting.
- Exactly.
- Someone could come later!
- Right!
Will there be any eliminations this time?
I'm sorry, Ho-jun, but
there's no one up there.
We have only ourselves to talk to.
Did you see a ghost?
- It's my first time.
- I see. That's fine.
If you have any questions,
you can ask Do-yeon.
(TVING Original: Love Catcher in Seoul)
'Charming men and women who
came to "Love Catcher" find true love.'
However, among these
"Love Catchers," there are
actually "Money Catchers"
who's here for the prize.
If two Love Catchers become a
couple, they'll achieve true love.
But if a Love Catcher and
a Money Catcher become a
couple, only the money
catcher will receive $50,000.
And if two Money Catchers become a couple,
they'll lose both love and the prize.
Will they be able to find
true love among the lies?
"Love Catcher in Seoul," a psychological
romance in a beautiful city, starts now!
Hang on. Can I ask this question?
What brings you here, Ho-jun?
I really like dating programs. I love them.
- You do?
- Yes, like "Transferring Love"?
- That was really fun.
- Yes, I saw that.
Of course, I saw the first and
second "Love Catcher," too.
There are so many amazing twists.
At the end when he...
When Chan-woo smiled.
- We felt the same way.
- It's really famous.
I know it's just a show, but I
remember being really immersed in it.
I think it's going to be
really interesting because
we have to guess who
the Money Catcher is.
You might get subtle
feelings, but it's hard to
tell if they're a love
catcher or a Money Catcher.
Are they Love Catchers pretending to be
Money Catchers? Or the other way around?
It'll be very thrilling.
And there's a new rule for Money Catchers.
I heard it's shocking. It will
be revealed in a moment.
I just hope I won't leave with disgrace.
I saw the results first and then
watched from the first episode again.
(So cool!)
- You studied.
- What a model student.
It seemed like Money Catchers
have their own concepts.
I'm going to keep an eye on that.
If he gets it wrong after
this, it's going to be hilarious.
I'm not good at hunches, so I was
thinking of going with your guesses.
- I see.
- But after listening to Loco,
I'm leaning towards him.
- You don't have a backbone, do you?
- No, I don't.
All right.
It's my first time meeting you,
but you guessed that right on.
I know. I have pretty bad hunches, but I
managed to hit bull's eye with that one.
That's hilarious.
- We can start guessing now.
- Yeah.
Wow, but five men and four women?
I bet they're super nervous!
(Love or Money? What is the first meeting
of those who came for love and money?)
(An enthralling love game of
young people who hid their identities)
(What will their first encounter be like?)
(The first participant)
Wow, he's really handsome.
To describe myself, I'd say I'm a
man with both brains and looks.
Of course, between love
and money, I choose love.
I can make money, but just because I have
money doesn't mean I can have that person.
I think it'll be fun and exciting.
If the one I like comes,
then I'll have to catch her.
(A bar in Seoul)
They're going to have
their first meeting at a bar?
(He's the very first one to
arrive at the lounge bar.)
This one seems like the Male God.
I think he's a businessman.
(He seems nervous.
He wipes his sweat.)
(Is he here for love or money?)
Personally, I think I have high standards.
Appearance-wise, I hope she has
double eyelids and a high-bridge nose
and is at least 167 - 168 centimeters tall.
(Clue: He has a fixed idea type.)
- He definitely gives off
"Love Catcher" vibes. - Right.
(The second participant)
- Wow!
- She's beautiful.
It's been a while since
I've been in a relationship.
I hope there's someone
here who gets along with me.
I'm somewhat like a fool.
I don't really get angry, and I cry easily.
- They both seem like they
just got off work. - Precisely.
It just feels like a blind date.
I've never experienced love at first sight.
I tend to open my heart if the
guy actively approaches me.
So I hope there's someone
who can take the reins.
(What will their first meeting be like?)
- Hello.
- Hi.
- You can sit anywhere you want.
- Okay.
(They sit apart from each other.)
(Peek)
(Smile)
- Oh my gosh!
- What was that? What was that smile about?
What's your name?
Lee Ha-neul.
- Lee Ha-neul?
- Yes.
- I see.
- What's your name?
I'm Jung Su-won.
- Su-won?
- Yes.
- Like the city of Suwon in Gyeonggido.
- I see.
- They already look good together.
- The atmosphere is nice.
Do you come to bars often?
- No, I'm a light drinker.
- I see.
- Same here.
- Are you good at cooking?
- No.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Are you good at cooking?
- No.
This is not good.
How tall are you?
I'm 171 centimeters tall.
171? You're tall.
- What about you?
- I'm 180 centimeters. Maybe 180.3?
Oh.
I think that's how tall I am.
(The third participant is here.)
She gives off different vibes.
I kind of feel like she's
the dance teacher.
- Hello.
- You can sit anywhere.
- Okay.
Where should I sit?
(She sits far away from Su-won.)
It's nice to meet you. Hello.
Hi.
My name is Lee In-seong.
- Lee In-seong?
- Yes.
On the outside, I seem calm and quiet,
but I'm lively, energetic, and bubbly.
- "Energetic."
- She's from California.
Okay, she's the foreign student.
What do you normally do? Like your hobbies?
- I recently started playing golf.
- Oh, really? Wow.
Rather than sports like that, I prefer
things like basketball and soccer.
- You play them?
- Yes, in high school, I played in teams.
Did you go to school
in another country?
I was born in America,
but I came to Korea when
I was six and attended
an international school.
I went to school here but
went to college in America.
I've lived in a different
country before, so I've
kissed someone who
isn't my boyfriend before.
(The fourth participant)
I think what's attractive about
me is that I'm honest and frank.
I've had this in mind for a while,
and I want to meet a girl who's like me.
Someone who's funny. Someone
I have great chemistry with.
- Hello.
- Hi.
- Can I sit here?
- Yeah.
(He sits between Su-won and Ha-neul.)
(Glance)
Have you been here for a while?
- About 10 minutes?
- 5 minutes?
- Oh, so you just got here.
- Yes.
He's good-looking.
- Where do you live?
- Me? I live in Pangyo.
Oh, Pangyo?
- May I ask where you live?
- I live near Itaewon.
- Oh, really?
- Yes.
- In Yong-San?
- Yes, that's right.
- I live in Yeoksam-dong.
- Oh, Yeoksam?
(Is this man who is leisurely leading
the conversation here for love? Or money?
(The fifth participant)
I've always liked sports cars,
so collecting them is my hobby.
I don't have any worries about money.
My flaw? That I'm too popular.
I've never had to try
to win someone's heart.
- Wow.
- Seriously, who is this guy?
Wow, he seems charismatic.
There's a high chance he's a businessman.
Hello.
Hi.
- Hello.
(He enters the bar with a strong aura.)
(He naturally sits in the center.)
(Awkward)
(Seo Jae-hyung)
Look at his expression. Wow.
- He's extravagant.
- Indeed.
(Glance)
- You must like accessories.
- Oh, me?
- I do.
- Really?
Yes.
That's a nice bracelet.
Thanks.
We all saw each others'
profiles. Can you tell who's who?
- I can.
- You can?
- Yup.
- Wow, already?
I think so, too.
- I'm so curious.
- I know. Can you tell?
- I have no idea.
- Right? Same here.
When I get to know someone,
I keep an eye on them.
Once I like someone,
that's when it all begins.
How many participants are there?
- I think there are 10 people.
- Five men and five women?
- Are there enough chairs?
- Oh, are there?
There are nine chairs.
How many profile cards were there...?
- I don't remember.
- There are five guys, right?
- That's why there are nine chairs.
- Oh, there are only four girls?
Yes.
It's an odd number.
(The numbers of men and
women don't match up?)
(The sixth participant hurries along.)
(Please pick your identity.)
That's right. They need to choose first.
Is it money or love?
(Money catchers may
fabricate their identities.)
No way!
This is something new
in this season, right?
- They changed it.
- They start with lies then.
That means your profile is a lie.
- You can lie or not lie.
- Yes.
Money Catchers can choose.
- Gosh, this is fun!
- This is getting interesting!
I feel like at the end,
someone will be like...
I'm excited!
(She's hesitating which one to choose. Is
she a Love Catcher or a Money Catcher?)
(Will you choose LOVE?
Will you choose MONEY?)
- Hello.
- She's cute.
- She looks young.
What's your name?
My name is Yang Ji-min.
Oh, we can't say anything else.
Right.
(Clue: Baby-faced. Is she
here for love or money?)
I totally want to get married.
It's been my dream ever since I was little.
I want a husband who's
sweet, polite, and loves kids.
But my dad said that's childish. He said
no one gets married before 30 these days.
I guess we have to go in order.
Do you have good memory?
- Yes.
- I'm Jung Su-won.
I'm Ahn Ji-min.
- You two have the same name.
- Oh, I see.
- I'm Seo Jae-hyung.
- I'm Lee Ha-neul.
I'm Lee In-seong.
Did you remember everything?
I'm gonna quiz you.
I don't think I remember all the names.
- Isn't my name easy to remember?
- Yes.
I remembered everyone's names but his.
Except for mine?
(The seventh participant)
I just want to show who I am.
I think I'm honest.
I don't like putting on a
facade, so I just act comfortably.
- Oh, hi.
- Hello.
(Yoon Jung-woo)
- Hi.
(Where will Jung-woo sit?)
(An empty seat between
Ha-neul and In-seong)
- May I sit here?
- Sure, go ahead.
It could be a bit burdensome
to sit between two women.
He could be the introverted type.
I learn face-reading, so I see
people from a different perspective.
I like women with round
faces with pretty cheekbones.
(Is there someone who caught his
eye out of the women with pretty smiles?)
If they have big cheekbones, you
can see their smiles more clearly.
It feels like they're smiling brightly.
(The eighth participant)
(He fixes his hair and adjusts
his clothes as if he's nervous.)
(Surprised)
- Hello.
- Hi.
(Won-jae sits between
In-seong and Ha-neul.)
(Glance)
Why do you seem familiar? Am I mistake?
Why does it feel like I've seen you before?
I'm not sure.
Currently, I'm studying physical
education at Inha University.
I'm Kang Won-jae, who is
training in physical education which
you can only get in if you
trained in military and martial arts.
Kang Won-jae...?
Oh, he's from "Steel Troops!"
The army!
- Oh, right.
- SDT.
No wonder his suit looked so tight!
Ha-neul recognized him right away.
(The ninth participant is
walking with excited steps.)
- She's the last one.
- The last one.
I think I'll give a
strong first impression.
I'm not someone who's in the shadows,
so I think I'll grab attention
during the first encounter.
Hello. Hello. Hello.
- Where should I sit?
- He's suddenly leaning forward.
(All eyes on her.)
(Lee Yeo-min)
- Is she from a beauty pageant?
- She's beautiful.
- Is she the last one?
- Yes, I think so.
But when I came in here, they gave me this.
- Hello.
- Hi.
- Should I take this?
- You can read it in there.
What's that?
- Could you read it?
- Should I read it out loud?
(Curious)
Tomorrow, come to the
lodging with the one you like.
We can freely start talking now.
- Tomorrow?
- So they're just meeting today?
- With the one they like?
- I guess they're not going there now.
Tomorrow?
The men are going to
pick up the women, right?
Right. He'll escort her, and
they'll go to the lodging together.
(Silence fills the bar after
the mission card is read.)
(Worried)
Honestly, I was very flustered.
There are four women and five men.
One person will have to go there alone.
I realized I could end up going by myself.
I'm worried that no one will
come pick me up tomorrow.
(The first meeting is filled with
strange excitement and worry.)
- Did you all eat?
- It looks so good.
- I'm starving.
- It looks delicious.
- They're too pretty to eat.
- Absolutely.
I have no idea what I should eat.
Oh, this looks
good. I pick this one.
(They pick the foods they want.)
The seats are too... separated.
- Everyone is...
- They're all anxious.
They can't eat.
If you like someone, do you sit
next to them or across from them?
Right now, shouldn't they sit across from
each other? So they can see each other?
I heard that it's better
to sit next to each other.
They say that you
should sit at the left side.
That's near their heart, and you
should whisper in their left ear.
That's what they say.
Oh, I see.
I think this is meatball.
(Ha-neul doesn't feel Su-won's
gaze and focuses on the food.)
Ha-neul?
(Su-won naturally moves near Ha-neul.)
Su-won already got his food, but it seemed
like he was waiting for her to find a seat.
- What's that?
- I'm not sure.
(There's something
subtle flowing between
them as they get to
know each other's tastes.)
He sat down first.
It could be because he's confident.
It's nerve-racking.
(Glance)
(With Su-won being the last one to
take a seat, all the men are at a table.)
Where do I have to sit?
It's really...
Who will muster up the courage first?
- Could this be seen as their choice?
- Yup.
(Who will be the brave
one to approach first?)
Should we sit here?
- Hello.
(Are Ji-min and In-seong
interested in Jung-woo?)
(Yeo-min and Ha-neul haven't decided yet.)
I'll go over there.
- Hello.
- Hi.
You didn't bring a lot of food.
I want to try some
before getting some more.
Yeo-min is an expert in this.
You have a dialect.
- I'm from Busan.
- Busan? I'm from Gyeongsang-do.
- Do you know Masan?
- I work there...
Where should I go?
I'll sit here.
(Ha-neul is still standing,
and Su-won is watching her.)
He keeps looking at her.
(Ha-neul sits with Won-jae and Ji-min.)
- Su-won seems interested in her, right?
- It's love at first sight.
At this rate, he'll spill all his food.
- What's going on?
- He's by himself!
- Jae-hyung is...
- He's Mr. Popular though!
This is bad!
(Unlike the others who are chatting
together, he's quietly eating alone.)
How do I put it? I'm observing.
When I get to learn
something, I tend to watch them.
I approach someone once
I get interested in them.
I'm confident, but this is how I am.
Everything's going according to plan.
- So that's his plan.
- It's going smoothly.
(She spots Jae-hyung.)
He's eating by himself.
- Should I tell him to join us?
- What?
Oh, sure.
- Jae-hyung, would you like to join us?
- Eat with us.
(Hesitating)
- Should I?
- yes.
- Eat with us.
- Come here.
He went.
I brought the most food.
Did you already eat?
I did, but it's been a while.
I think it'd be nice if
you become less shy.
- I'm shy around strangers, too.
- I'm really timid.
- Same here.
- Me, too.
- I'm shy, too.
- Is everyone here timid?
We'll be able to get
close by the end, right?
I wonder that, too.
I don't really talk a lot when I
meet people for the first time.
- I don't think that's true.
- You're pretty chatty.
I sweated a lot.
My hands were all sweaty.
- I feel like you're a good cook.
- Me?
Yes. Am I wrong?
- I feel like you enjoy it.
- I do, but I'm not that good at it.
But people who enjoy
cooking are good at it.
(The corners of his lips go up.)
- Do you drink alcohol well?
- No.
Two or three shots of soju
and I get red everywhere.
Right. I get red up to my neck.
What about you, Jae-hyung?
Oops, I'm sorry!
- Do you two know each other?
- Do you know me?
He looks like someone I know.
As soon as I entered the room, I
thought, "He really looks like him."
- That's why I naturally called
you by your name. - I see.
All of a sudden?
What if she did that on purpose?
What if?
(It's hot!)
What are your hobbies?
- I like bowling.
- Bowling?
I was in the bowling team in middle school.
I'm not good at it now.
Same here. I used
to score 150 to 160.
Wow, you're really good!
My score is 130, and I thought I was good.
- I think I'll score 100 now.
- I see.
Anything else besides bowling?
I love eating delicious food.
- Going to hot spots?
- Everyone likes that.
I love eating, too.
- I recently went on a diet
because of that. - I see.
- Do you like going for a drive?
- I love it.
Really?
- I love looking at the sky.
- I'm a cloud collector.
I took a ton of pictures today.
- The clouds are really pretty these days.
- Yeah.
- The sky during the sunset is beautiful.
- It's pink.
You get drenched in
those feelings for a moment.
- They're really compatible.
- Yeah!
Won-jae must feel a bit awkward.
What time do you usually sleep?
- Sleep?
- Yes.
- I sleep before midnight.
- Same here.
- Really?
- I tend to sleep early.
- Do you wake up early, too?
- Around 7?
I just got the chills! Me, too!
- I don't have an alarm.
- Me neither.
Right? This is scary.
- What do you do when you wake up?
- I really love music.
- Me, too.
- Really? What kind?
I turn on the LP when I wake up.
- I can't believe it.
- Wow, you must listen to music a lot.
- I try collecting them.
- I'm so envious.
Ji-min is in an awkward spot.
- But aren't you taken aback by tomorrow?
- Yes.
I can't believe we have to go back home.
What do we do tomorrow?
I have no idea what will happen.
I'll feel pathetic if I get rejected.
But on the other hand, no one
could pick up the girl.
- That's possible if a girl gets
more than one votes. - Oh no.
- What if I end up taking a cab there?
- Where do you live?
- You said you live in Gwangjin-gu, right?
- Yes.
(Will Jae-hyung go to
pick up Yeo-min tomorrow?)
I'm worried about tomorrow.
I think everyone is.
I'll just have to assume
I'll be driving alone.
- Just go to the lodging right away?
- Yeah, just be at ease.
- I'll have the music on.
- There are five guys though.
Right.
But won't one of us come to pick you up?
I think so.
Then we'll both end up
not going. Just kidding!
I'm pulling your leg.
I think he'll go get her.
Should we go? They
said we can go over there.
(Ha-neul's gaze follows Su-won.)
I think she's looking at him, too.
They seem to be conscious of one another.
- I think it'll be cold.
I get cold easily.
- The breeze feels nice.
- It's gorgeous!
- It's pretty.
- It's so beautiful!
Is this Changdeokgung? What is that?
- Isn't it Heunginjimun?
- Heunginjimun?
- Yes. - I see. I didn't know.
Where in Busan did you live?
Jingoo. Gaya.
I live in Seoul.
(Just then, Yeo-min bumps into
the fence and spills her drink.)
- It was too windy.
- I just have to wipe this.
- How's the weather outside?
- It's...
- Where's the restroom?
- I made a mess on the first day.
He seems like he doesn't care, but...
I think I was able to figure her out a bit.
I'll keep observing her and try to
get her to like me on the second day.
I'm confident.
But the more I see
Jae-hyung, the more I trust him.
- Oh, really?
- He's charming.
- If you think about it, he's
very innocent. - Right.
I think what he said will happen.
(Glance)
May I sit here?
Of course.
- Were you the second to arrive?
- The third.
It must have been very awkward.
Tell me about it.
But I saw you try your
best, and I was grateful.
I tried.
I had no idea what to do, so I
kept touching my glass of water.
But you made a lot of effort, too.
I think everyone's nice here.
Both the men and women.
I think you're really young.
Really? I'm not. I'm not that young.
Really?
(Their ages and jobs are under wraps.)
Is everyone sitting here again?
- Oh, your double eyelids!
- Me?
Is it past midnight, by any chance?
I'm not sure.
(Su-won, who was away
for a bit, comes back inside.)
- Are we back at the bar now?
- Yes.
- Did you guys talk a lot over there?
- Yes, we did.
It's an hour and a half past my bedtime.
- Please tell me if my double
eyelids appear. - Let me see.
They're here.
Oh my god. They're very noticeable.
I look greasy, right?
(He can't stop looking
at Ha-neul and Ji-min.)
Let's not bully each other.
(The two are getting along very well.)
- Su-won can't hide his emotions.
- Oh no.
Regarding first impressions,
I had my eyes on Ha-neul.
She has big eyes and a
sharp and high-bridge nose.
So I think she's all right.
If she's interested in
me, too, I dare predict
that we'll get into
a good relationship.
He seems like a Love Catcher.
- Right.
- He seems like a Love Catcher.
- I was amazed that we have the same name.
- Me, too.
Can you tell me the keyword? I'm curious.
Ji-min seems really proactive.
He goes to different places.
I feel like he's a Money Catcher.
So if they're proactive,
they're Money Catchers?
Can you tell me the keyword? I'm curious.
- Do you remember a keyword?
- Me?
Out of the women's keywords.
The one that shocked me the most was "21."
I think I know who that is.
- I won't ask you.
- Okay.
You look young, Ji-min, so I thought
that was you, but you don't act 21 at all.
- Right?
- You seem thrilled.
What? That's because you said I look young.
You really do look very young.
- I don't think she's 21.
- I think she is.
What do you usually see in women?
Honestly, I rely a lot on
first impressions and destiny.
What about you?
(The two men are waiting for her answer.)
Someone you can peg as
nice the moment they speak.
I'm trying to remember what I said.
I'm curious if everyone
already has eyes for someone.
I'm sure some of them do.
- I do, too.
- Really?
There's someone I'm curious about.
I wonder who it is.
Who is it?
What about you?
(She looks at the men at the other tables.)
- Hello.
- I'm Yang Ji-min.
- I'm Ahn Ji-min.
- You two seem to have the same name.
- We do.
I had eyes on him from the
first time I entered the room.
I like people who seem like
they grew up with a lot of love.
That's important for me, too.
I think you grew up with a lot of love.
Really? I'm glad. I was totally adored.
I think Ji-min's ideal
type is my ideal type.
He likes people who
are kind and considerate.
- Really?
- For real?
There's someone I'm curious about.
What about you?
(Ji-min looks elsewhere in
case he notices how she feels.)
Why are you looking over there?
I guess it's not one of us.
There is someone I want to have a
conversation in the car tomorrow morning.
(She can't meet his eyes.)
(Ba-thump, Ba-thump!)
- My heart is fluttering!
- Will he be able to notice it?
I think so.
But she looked somewhere else,
so I don't think Ji-min figured it out.
I wouldn't have been able to notice it.
She looked way over there.
But Ha-neul and Ji-min hit it off, too.
They giggled together.
- Su-won will definitely
go to Ha-neul, right? - Absolutely.
- He could go there tonight.
- He might get a head start.
He can't hide his emotions.
He's definitely a Love
Catcher, and he's into Ha-neul.
Totally.
Tomorrow, the guys will
have to escort the girls.
- Can you guess who will go to who?
- Ji-min will go to Ji-min.
I think he'll go to Ha-neul.
The way he was with her was a bit
different from how he was with Ji-min.
I feel like he was vibing with her as a
friend and not as someone he could date.
- So they're more like friends?
- Yes. They looked comfortable.
Jae-hyung will go to Yeo-min.
- Anyway, I hope it goes as he plans.
- I want to root for him.
- They probably didn't get any sleep.
- Of course they didn't!
(With the excitement of their first
meeting, the nine of them went home.)
(The morning where their
second meeting will occur
They're leaving.
Hello.
I'm the only one in a cab.
I regret not buying a car.
Coming together is what's important.
(Where are the men's
hearts heading towards?)
Wow, there Jae-hyung goes.
It's the first date.
I haven't decided
between them two, and I
think a date with either
of them will be fine.
That's when it all begins.
I think I could say
it's love at first sight.
Even if she likes someone
else, I'll do my best to steal her.
He's set on Ha-neul.
The one who caught my
eye the most was Ha-neul.
(That's unexpected!)
Really?
When I think about who matches
with me the most, it's Yeo-min.
- You live in Gwangjin-gu, right?
- Yes.
- I live in Nowon.
- That's close by.
I work out a lot at
Jungnangcheon.
I used to work out there, too.
I love jogging.
Seriously?
(The two of them are
heading to the same place.)
She has good vibes.
I think I'll go to the one
I want to talk with more.
They're in the same neighborhood.
I talked with Ji-min and In-seong the most.
I remember them the most.
(Will the five men be able to enter
Love Mansion with the woman they want?)
It seems like two men are
aiming for the same woman.
Yes, their interests are overlapping.
(Yoon Jung-woo)
(The second man arrives at the next place.)
(Kang Won-jae)
(And where are the
other men going to?)
I'm almost here.
It's right across that, right?
What if there are many other cars?
(These two picked different women.)
Oh no! The background looks the same!
(Covering her mouth)
This is driving me nuts.
- He's here?
- Oh no!
Where is this? The lot's full.
Aww, man.
Hello.
Oh my god!
Why did you come here?
- I guess we connected.
- Yeah.
- I think they're here for Ji-min.
- This is like a drama.
(The other two cars
come to different locations.)
I wonder who else came.
(Glance)
- The lot's full here, too.
- Good grief!
(Oh no!)
Won-jae and Jae-hyung.
(They're not pleased with the situation.)
I saw the Porsche and
got a bit disheartened.
I thought it's worth trying.
The war of nerves is tense here.
I hope at least one person is here.
Or else, my pride will be hurt.
Honestly, I thought at least
one person would come.
What will I do if no one comes?
I'm really worried that
no one will be here.
I'm kind of interested in two guys.
Su-won and Ji-min.
I don't know.
(Halt)
Wait a minute. I don't think there
was anyone in the underground lot.
(Synchronized)
(Please!)
(is the one waiting for her the
one she's been wishing for?)
(Jung Su-won)
Hello.
Goodness! That's wonderful!
- I hope they're both Love Catchers.
- Same here.
- Hello.
- Should I put your luggage in the trunk?
- Yes, please.
Hello.
- Wow.
- Did you sleep well?
You didn't get enough sleep, right?
Two hours? I think I
got two hours of sleep.
- I slept for about three.
- It's hot, right?
- No, it's cold.
- It is?
(The second meeting of the
people with hot-and-cold chemistry)
I connected with one person, and I
want to talk more with another person.
I think it's that spot.
(Two men are waiting for Yeo-min.)
(Are they the escorts Yeo-min had in mind?)
Goodness. Hello. Hello.
What do I do?
She has to choose.
Will you get in my car?
- Oh my gosh!
- Why is he doing that?
What do we do?
Will you get in my car?
(Compared to the proactive Jae-hyung,
Won-jae has a dim expression.)
What do I do?
What should I do?
She feels bad for having to
choose right in front of them.
I'll go with...
- I'm not sure who she'll pick.
- She's in a pickle.
- I'm sorry.
- It's fine.
(Yeo-min chose Won-jae.)
Oh no.
(One man is happy
while the other is sad...)
It's really heavy.
(Is this part of his big picture, too...?)
I wish this was part of his plan.
- Hello.
- Hi.
- Did you get some sleep?
- No.
Me neither.
This is driving me crazy.
God, I'm embarrassed.
Ugh, I'm humiliated.
I'm curious what will happen here, too.
I hope Ji-min, the one I
talked with the most, is here.
Between Ji-min and Jung-woo,
the one I want to get to know more is...
This means no one came to
pick up either In-seong or Ji-min.
(The one who disarmed
these two tense men are...?)
In-seong!
- Wow, what happened?
- This is unexpected.
I never expected this.
Is no one here? I don't
think anyone came.
Oh no...
Uh-oh...
- Please choose comfortably.
- Okay.
(In-seong can't avoid this
moment of decision either.)
- Who is it?
- Jung-woo.
- She'll pick Ji-min.
(Who is In-seong's heart leaning towards?)
I'm sorry.
- That's unfortunate.
- This is really bitter.
It's heavy.
- Should I put it in the back?
- Sure.
- You can get in the car first.
- Thank you.
(Stare)
(Bow)
(Is Ji-min not able to go because
he has lingering feelings for her?)
Sir, I'm alone. You can
take me there alone.
I can just go comfortably.
(At the same time,
Ji-min's taxi arrives.)
Hello, sir. I'm sorry,
but this luggage is
really heavy. Can you
help me load it in the car?
- On top of this, the luggage
is heavy, too. - Thank you.
There's one more.
This one is heavier.
- Should I get it from the other side.
- No, just get in.
Thank you, sir. Thank you.
(They head towards Love Mansion.)
(The seat beside him
feels strangely empty.)
I should've bought a car.
(Someone calls the upset Ji-min.)
Hi, mom. I'm heading to the
lodging in a cab all by myself.
I'm alone. The others are going in pairs.
It's okay.
- Did you get rejected?
- Yeah.
It could be because she doesn't like me,
but somehow, I'm disappointed
that I don't have a car.
You didn't tell her you don't have
one because you don't need it?
Mom, I didn't even have a
chance to explain that to her.
I couldn't tell her why I didn't have a car
yet and about how I'm a realistic person.
I'm just heading there by myself.
I need to buy a car.
I don't have a Porsche,
but I'll drive like this is one.
- I don't really know cars.
- I see.
It's fine.
I felt like we have similar tastes.
I thought you felt the same way,
so I kind of anticipated you coming.
- Really?
- Yes, I thought maybe you'd come.
We didn't get to talk a lot.
They look good together, too.
(What about Jung-woo and In-seong?)
- Thank you.
- For what?
- For coming.
- Oh.
Thank you.
When I first met you,
what caught my eye were
your glasses and that
ring on your pinky finger.
- Your glasses look really good on you.
- They do?
I brought another pair of glasses,
but I'll continue wearing these ones.
- For a week?
- Yes.
(Whatever In-seong likes!)
(The final couple: Su-won & Ha-neul)
Can I ask you this? Whose first
impressions did you like yesterday?
- You said there were two.
- Right.
Is there someone you're interested in?
- Yes.
- Really? What about you?
Same here. Two of them.
- Two for you, too?
- One for me.
Is one of them here?
(Flustered)
Is he the one taking you there?
Yes, he is.
- He did?
- Yes.
I see. Okay.
They're both very straightforward.
- Is the one you were talking about me?
- Yes, it's only one for me. You.
- They look good together.
- Yes, they do.
(Truth hidden within secrets and the youths
who have stepped forward to find love.)
- Wow!
- That's really nice.
There's a place like that in Seoul?
(Love Mansion)
(One cab arrives first.)
Thank you.
(First housemate: Ahn Ji-min)
Wow, that's really nice.
(What kind of story will
these nine youths make?)
(He walks through the
door and sees the first area.)
(Common dining room)
I wonder what kind of
things will happen in here.
Wow, I'm the first one here.
(Ji-min's heart is covered
with frustration and emptiness.)
(And one girl is shortening
the distance between them.)
- Hello.
- Are you alone?
- Yes.
I see.
- I think I'm the first one here.
- Really?
Why are you so breathless?
I rushed up here.
- Did you run?
- Yes, because it's raining.
We met yesterday, but it
feels like this is our first time.
- Really? We didn't talk that much.
- Yeah.
But because of the party
yesterday, it's not awkward.
- I think since he's here alone,
she sees some kind of hope. - Of course!
Is it here?
Is it?
I'm flustered.
Love Mansion.
Come in.
Did he drop the honorifics?
- They're coming together.
- I guess they came together.
- Hello.
- It's really nice.
- Yeah.
- Do I sit here? Can I sit here?
- When did you get here?
- More than ten minutes ago.
- Really?
I think it's great that we
didn't have to come here alone.
- Right. What a relief. - I was
worried that I'd have to come by myself.
It's good.
Oh, he thinks they came together!
Because they were here first?
Oh my goodness.
What did you guys do?
Did you just come here right away?
It took more than an hour to get here.
You had a conversation for an hour?
It wasn't too bad.
(Shy)
Ha-neul is really down-to-earth, so I
think it'd be comfortable to be around her.
Yes, well...
For some reason,
there's tension...
- This must be it.
- Yes.
- Hello.
(An uncomfortable love triangle
surrounding a man who wasn't chosen.)
In-seong feels bad.
(Feeling awkward for some reason)
(Another man is unfamiliar
with this situation.)
Gosh, I'm losing my mind here.
Did he laugh all the way here?
(Fifth housemate: Seo Jae-hyung)
He's trudging.
"Love Mission."
- Oh dear.
- He must be having a rough time.
Of course. He's in no right mind.
- Hello.
- You're all here.
- Yes.
- You look a bit brighter than yesterday.
- I do?
Yes.
You seem more at ease.
I kind of got adjusted to everything.
You have so much luggage.
How did you bring all this?
- I love things like this.
- You do?
Yes. I absolutely love
things like gardens and parks.
- I love grass.
- You must really like it here.
Yes, I love it.
They seem to have gotten a lot closer.
- Hello.
- It's really nice.
- Right?
I love how there's so much grass.
I love grass.
It's like a forest.
(Peek)
(All nine participants have
entered Love Mansion.)
Oh my god!
- I knew this would happen.
- That scared me!
- Oh my.
- Wow.
Amazing.
- Finally!
- I'm nervous. Why am I so nervous?
It has finally come.
(You will have seven
days to find true love.)
Oh, a week.
(Couples who win the
couple challenges get
enter the "Night Date"
or "Room of Secrets.")
It must be a date at night.
It says "or."
I guess you can choose.
Oh, you can choose.
(You can express your
interest only once per day.)
How do you do that?
So once a day, whenever
they want, they can put their
coin in the locker of the
one they're interested in.
If they change their
mind, they'll take it
out and put it in a
different locker, right?
Right. They'll put it somewhere else.
Then those who try to express
their feelings late at night may see
someone else's coin already in
that box when they open that door.
Right. So you have to do it very carefully.
(On the last day, the final selections and
everyone's identities will be unveiled.)
(Another message appears after that.)
(Please introduce yourself.)
That means the Money Catchers can introduce
themselves as their fake identities. Right?
- So we have to introduce ourselves.
- I knew this would happen.
I'm shaking.
I'm curious.
You can go first.
I'm...
32 years old.
I'm working as a freelance
travel writer right now.
I remember that profile.
I'm 30 years old.
And I'm working at a company in Pangyo.
- You're 30?
- Do I look older?
No! Why would you say that?
- Ji-min is him! - The ambassador
of Sungkyunkwan University.
- The face of Sungkyunkwan University.
- An elite.
I'm 29 years old, and I'm a researcher
of the LG Electronics development team.
I told you I'm from Busan.
That's my hometown, and
my workplace is in Changwon.
So I'm going back and forth.
Oh, he's the male god of
an engineering university.
I have a lot of jobs.
I'm in real estate, and I'm
the owner of a fashion brand.
Also, I have two cafe franchises.
- How old are you?
- I'm 32.
- You two are the same age.
- Let's be friends.
There's quite a gap with my age.
(Hesitate)
You can say it comfortably.
My name is Kang Won-jae,
and I'm 23 years old.
I'm a college student
majoring in physical education.
I was in "Steel Troops."
- Huh?
- You were?
- Which team were you in?
- I was the youngest member of SDT.
No wonder he looked familiar!
- You're really observant.
- I loved that show.
Wow.
I'm 26 years old, and I'm a dance teacher.
- That job suits you.
- Thanks.
I'm...
27 years old,
and I recently opened a restaurant.
What? Then you're good at cooking!
- I'm not the one who cooks.
- She's very shy.
She's the boss, not the chef.
I'm 21 years old.
- That was you?
- Yes.
I'm a college student
studying aviation tourism.
I'm trying to become a flight attendant.
It really suits you.
Thank you.
She's really 21.
I'm 26 years old, and I'm currently
studying at a university in California.
- So you're taking a break from school?
- It's all online classes now.
Yes, because of COVID-19.
- No wonder you have great pronunciation.
- Yeah.
You know suspenders...
(Is her English a habit? Or is she
purposely doing this to fool everyone?)
I knew it when I heard you
say a few English words.
- Who's the one with a franchise?
- The franchise?
- Here.
- Me.
- I thought it's unique.
- Yes, I remember it.
I built the building myself, and
I'm living at the very top floor.
The first floor is where the cafe is,
and the middle floor is for new residents.
- Do you make the coffee yourself?
- The employees do that.
Both of you are owners but
don't get involved in the work.
But at least you cook.
I have a few branches,
so I can't do it all myself.
There's one in Incheon and somewhere else.
And I have a fashion brand, too.
You're truly incredible.
I worked hard.
I had no idea you were 21.
Really? Who did you think was 21 then?
Let's talk about that now. Who did
you think was who based on the profiles?
- I think it will be interesting.
- Who did you think was 21?
I think I made a mistake.
(What's on Ji-min's mind?)
Ha-neul? I think she's 21.
I thought she was 21, too.
She's very beautiful and graceful,
but I felt like she's very young.
I tend to draw a line if I
think someone's too young.
I don't think I saw...
her as a woman.
I'm 27 years old.
- I love looking at the sky.
- I'm a cloud collector.
I took so many photos today, too!
That's right. They really got along.
He thought she was young
and drew a line between them.
I think I made a mistake.
Their interests may completely
change after the introductions!
I have no idea what he's thinking.
(The day before the final selection)
- What's going on?
- Who are they?
- Ji-min and...
- What's happening?
Su-won.
- What's wrong?
- And Ha-neul!
Things are serious.
Did they fight?
I'm gonna say it now since he's not here.
I think he was interested in you.
I feel like Ji-min was into you.
And you...
probably have some feelings for him, too.
You know you were selfish, too.
(It was a tsunami of an
unfathomable and uncontrollable scale.)
Why was he selfish?
Why did she say that?
I'm getting pissed off.
Why did things turn out like this?
- What's going on?
- Was he interested in someone else?
What's happening?
- This is it, right?
- That's the end?
You expect us to go
home like this? We can't!
- Wouldn't that be horrible?
- If you could just show us a bit more...
Just 30 seconds, please.
I won't ask for more.
Please do this for us.
Or at least give us soju.
I can't go home like this.
Prepare a dish for a date?
Are we each choosing one?
I thought of Su-won,
but I thought there
wouldn't enough time
to get to know the others.
I want to talk with someone else, too.
It's our first time, so it's not
bad to get to know others.
This is driving me nuts.
I feel like I'll be full
even if I don't eat.
I felt emotions I've
never experienced before.
Rather than feeling
interest, it was really warm.
It was warm food.
I thought at least one
woman would come to me.
I feel like the third wheel.
I can't intervene in their
conversation. It's hard.
She's here!
I got goosebumps!
This is what it's supposed to be like.
She's here now.
There were more men than women.
- I got a bit relaxed.
- I suddenly got happy.
- Hello.
Someone who's close
to my ideal type has appeared.
Her first impression wasn't bad.
- She's beautiful.
- It's the beginning.
My name is...