It's here.
So many people have passed away.
have arrived at the reservation. Please pick up the number 5807.
Gosh.
Wake up! Wake up!
He's here. He's here.
I'm here. I'm here. I'm here.
God of Car.
Get in the car. I'm the one you need to pick up.
Surpass him, God of Car!
We won!
When I was 17,
I saw the car god running on the arena with my own eyes.
The moment he stood on the winning stage,
he also lit the unbreakable dream of racing.
It's worth it to receive an idol.
Before the championship,
the doctor found out that I was terminally ill.
But I told myself I shouldn't have died in the hospital.
The destination of a racer is the track.
Idol, what do you think?
I learned how to drift from you.
I didn't run on the track. I'm not a real racer.
God of racing.
Can you do me a favor?
Don't be nervous. I'll show you the way.
Thank you.
The rain is too heavy. I can't see clearly.
Turn left at 50 meters, level 9.
Drive left.
Oh.
Full throttle passed. Delay the brake at the next corner.
Okay.
Don't think too much.
The biggest opponent of a person is yourself.
The highest level of a racer is the combination of human cars.
I'm at the end
This is awesome.
30 minutes until the life door closes. Please send the passenger to the life door immediately.
Thank you for helping me fulfill my dream.
A dream is important, but it's more precious than a dream.
is the person who loves you.
[We've reached the destination.]
Take care.
[It's a stone.] [It's a stone.] [It's a stone.] [It's a stone.]
The stone bridge
It may collapse at any time.
Sit tight.
Whether you can leave or not depends on your fate.
Did you have a nightmare again?
I received a passenger order. Please go to #705 Sunshine Community to pick up the passengers.
Isn't this my house?