Let's go. Let's go. Let's go.
Take me away!
Let's go! Let's go!
I want it.
It's... It's...
1405.
Hello. Hello.
It's not you! It's you! It's me! It's you! It's me!
You have deviated from your destination.
You're off the destination.
Young man.
Why did you leave without picking him up?
I didn't mean it.
How about
Get in the car.
Passengers in 1405 have arrived.
Please send to the Reincarnation Gate immediately.
Please send the passengers to the Reincarnation Gate before midnight.
After midnight,
The reincarnation door is closed.
You'll pay for it.
Hey, man. Let's go.
Can you do me a favor
can you do me a favor?
Granny.
My mission is to send you to the Reincarnation Gate.
I can't help you
I can't help you.
It's near the Gate of Reincarnation.
Granny.
We're almost there.
Get ready.
Get ready to get off.
Where did he go?
Don't do it. Don't do it.
If you don't want to be reincarnated,
I want to live.
The Reincarnation Gate is open.
The living must stay away.
Grandma!
Grandma, come out!
At the end of life.
The beginning of death.
The door is open! The door is open!
The boundary is gone
[Yin and Yang are intertwined.]
Life and death respond.
Ghosts are the guide.
Reincarnation.
Who are you?
Tell me your name.
Young man.
Let's go.
We don't have much time left.
Honey.
These are all your favorite.
Dumplings. Okay.
Here you go. Here you go.
Osmanthus cake.
Hello. Hello.
It's almost time.
Almost.
Soon.
We promised to come here
every year on this day.
The stars are not here.
You're not here either.
Honey.
Are you back?
Where are you?
Old man.
I'm here.
Granny.
We still have some time.
Thank you.
Young man.
60 years ago,
you made a promise to me
in the starry sky.
Now,
I used the fireflies
to say goodbye.
I'll eat well.
and sleep well.
Honey.
Wait for me there.