[This Thriving Land]
[Episode 2]
Let me iron
the groom's outfit for you again.
Sister-in-law.
Does our Fei family's ancestral rule
say that no guests are allowed in
before the bride arrives?
There's no such rule.
Then why hasn't a single person
shown up yet?
The auspicious time for the wedding
was determined at the Goddess Temple.
It's still early.
The tradition of waiting for the bride
means just staying put at home
and waiting for her to arrive.
No need to rush.
Let's go.
Madam.
Go burn the incense first.
Any news from the Ning Residence?
I heard from the villagers that
Master Ning scolded
that Mole Cricket away.
In a bit, go over to the Ning Residence
and deliver the betrothal gift list
we prepared
three years ago to him.
Tell him
I want a definite answer.
No more questions.
Go.
Father. Mother.
Dear ancestors.
The fact that I, Wendian, was able to
grow up and get educated,
and that the Fei family
is what it is today,
is all thanks to my sister-in-law's
care and management.
I'm about to get married
and establish a new family.
Please, ancestors, bless my sister-in-law
and our whole family with a good life.
I'll definitely honor my sister-in-law
and treat her like my own mother.
[Memorial Tablets of the Ancestors
of the Fei Family]
Master.
Steward Liu of the Fei family
wants to see you.
Master Ning.
Our Madam
asked me to give this to you.
What did Mrs. Fei say?
She said
she wants a definite answer from you
as soon as possible.
What's her intention in giving me
the betrothal gift list
at a time like this?
Does she want the betrothal gifts back?
Go back and tell Mrs. Fei
that I promise
to send
my pure and spotless daughter
to the Fei family before midnight.
He really said that?
Yes.
All right. You may leave now.
You and Qing must keep a close eye
on Young Master.
Don't let him go out, okay?
Yes.
Before midnight,
send his pure and spotless daughter
to the Fei family.
Before midnight,
send his pure and spotless...
Father, it's getting dark.
Why haven't you picked out
the land deed yet?
Mrs. Fei, you are so cruel,
trying to pull the rug out from us
at this critical moment.
Honey, what are you talking about?
Why haven't you gone to sell the land yet?
Stop making a fuss!
I'm trying to figure out a way, aren't I?
Get out. Get out.
-Father!
-Get out, you all!
-What are you doing, Father?
-Get out!
Widow Fei, you are so cruel.
The 50 mu of land in the betrothal gifts
is the best in the entire village.
It connects my family's
eastern and western plots,
like the lifeline of our land.
I've been growing it for three years,
pouring my heart and soul into every inch.
And now you say you want to take it back?
Mrs. Fei,
you're trying to rip my heart out.
you're trying to rip my heart out!
Rip my heart out...
Is anyone there?
Is anyone...
Why are you yelling?
I'm thirsty. I want some water.
Thirst won't kill you.
Wait!
Get me a bowl of water,
and you can have the hairpin I'm wearing.
Even if I don't get you water,
I can still have your hairpin.
Aren't you worried
I'll tell your boss?
Wait here.
Qing, Steward Liu!
Young Master.
It's so late.
Why hasn't a single guest shown up?
And the wedding procession.
Still no news?
The wedding procession...
Did something happen over there?
Is it related to Xiuxiu?
Well...
I'll go see Xiuxiu.
Young Master! Young Master!
You can't go out, Young Master!
What do you want!
Listen to me, Young Master!
Please, rest assured.
The Ning family said
they'd definitely send the bride back
before midnight.
Before midnight?
Why before midnight?
Tell me.
Tell me! Why is it before midnight?
I could tell something was off
with you two and my sister-in-law
the moment I came back.
Looks like something bad really happened.
I need to go see Xiuxiu.
Young Master, you can't go!
Let me go to the Ning Residence!
I need to see Xiuxiu!
Young Master, it's dark and
the road is slippery. You can't go!
Wendian!
Sister-in-law,
are you hiding something from me?
Sister-in-law!
Yes.
Xiuxiu
was kidnapped.
Kidnapped?
Who did it?
Big Nose Du from Chicken Ridge.
Young Master, Young Master!
Don't do that!
Don't stop me!
This knife of mine doesn't play around.
Step aside!
Madam, Young Master is...
Wendian!
Sister-in-law!
You really shouldn't have hid this
from me!
Young... Young Master!
Madam.
Still no news from down the mountain.
San.
I think this deal's going to be a loss.
Brother.
I don't think so. She's a bride after all.
They'll need to
have her back eventually, right?
If that's the case,
I'll give the Ning family a gift
and warn that Miser Ning.
Put your matters aside for a bit.
Tonight,
I'm receiving an important guest.
Don't embarrass me.
Brother, I won't.
Boss.
Second Boss.
Someone's coming up the mountain
with a weapon!
With a weapon?
I'd like to see
who has the nerve to do that.
Let's go!
San.
Leave yourself a way out.
You may meet again in the future.
Don't make it fatal.
Brother.
I'll listen to you.
My men!
Bring all the horses out!
Hurry up!
Yes!
Since someone has come up our mountain
uninvited,
let's grab our weapons
and make sure they don't leave here alive!
Hurry up!
Kill them all!
Let's go!
Hurry up!
Come on!
Guo?
Meat?
Try some.
It's so good.
How thoughtful of you!
Come on, sit.
I'll pour you a bowl of wine.
I'll pass.
I heard that Second Boss
kidnapped someone for quick money.
Quick money? More like slow money.
Where did Second Boss abduct her from?
She's the eldest daughter of Ning Xuexiang
from the Ox Temple Village.
I'll go take a look.
Don't look. Your soul will be drawn away.
All the more reason for me to go see!
So pleasing.
Boss, your guests are here.
Alright.
Let's go out to welcome them.
How many of them?
Four.
When Hu San comes back,
tell him to come over to meet the guests.
Got it, Boss.
Wendian.
Why are you here?
What do you think you're doing?
I know you feel anxious.
I'm worried too,
but...
But you are a scholar.
You haven't even been in a fight
since you were a kid.
So what?
I need to save Xiuxiu.
Those bandits use real weapons.
Xiuxiu's second uncle went to save her
but was driven back by a hail of bullets.
And those bandits have made it clear
that they only want ransom, not her.
As long as the ransom is delivered,
they'll send her back.
They won't kill her.
How about this, Sister-in-law?
Since Xiuxiu is alone
in the bandits' lair now,
she must be scared.
Take me there,
and I'll keep her company.
I don't know where the bandits' lair is.
Do you know?
Xiuxiu's great-uncle, second uncle,
and a host of other elders are all there,
trying to figure something out.
Beard Liu also brought news back,
saying your father-in-law said it himself
that he'd send the bride to our house
before midnight, right?
Yes, Young Master.
Master Ning said that himself.
Don't lie to me.
Why would I lie to you, Young Master?
Let's go home.
Listen to me.
I won't harm you.
I'm so useless.
Let's go back.
Let's go.
That deadbeat father of yours!
I think he won't cry
until he sees the coffin.
Alright then.
I'll cut off one of your ears
and send it to him,
to celebrate his daughter's wedding.
What are you doing?
If you dare to hurt me,
I...
I'll bash my head here and die!
If I die,
you won't have a good explanation either.
What,
are you trying to play tough with me?
Come on. Go kill yourself.
Come on.
My brother, Ning Kejin,
is the head of the Qingqi Society.
He'll definitely come to save me.
My father will, too!
Enough!
Still talking about
that worthless brother of yours?
Let me tell you.
I've beaten him down the mountain.
What a pity.
This pretty little face...
Don't! Let go!
My father will definitely come to save me!
Second Boss! Second Boss!
What?
Boss wants you to go meet the guests now.
Just a moment!
Second Master! Second Master!
What are you doing!
Second Boss, we can't break the rules
of the underworld.
Otherwise, it'll be hard to explain things
to Boss.
Keep a close eye on her.
You're quite something, you damn woman.
Trying to smash the bowl and cut the rope?
Let's see if you can cut it now.
Behave yourself!
My brother is back!
Do you want to die?
I was driven back by gunfire
before I even got to see Xiuxiu!
Father, why are you holding the land deed?
You want to use the land deed
to ransom my sister, right?
Mother, Father finally came to his senses!
There's no time to exchange it for money.
Kejin...
Father... Father's going to use
the land deed
to ransom my sister.
Father, how about this?
Father and son should fight together.
I'll go with you.
You'll take all the land deeds we have
and ransom my sister from Big Nose Du.
And when he opens the door
to greet you, I'll...
Why did you hit him?
Kejin.
Son.
Have you lost your mind?
Trying to lay a hand on the land deeds?
I'm not dead yet.
What's this all about?
I've told you long ago
since you were kids
that no one is allowed to touch
the land deeds. No one!
If you won't save Xiuxiu,
Son, let's go save her.
Let's go.
What are you doing?
Give it to me!
Mother!
W-What are you doing?
Why did you push my mother?
What are you getting all worked up for?
Instead of helping me settle things,
you just keep causing trouble!
Get lost!
Mother hit her head!
She's bleeding!
You're pressuring me, and so is Mrs. Fei.
Are you all trying to suck the marrow
from my bones and drain my blood?
Darling.
Here.
I was impulsive just now.
Mother.
I know you want to save Xiuxiu.
Of course we need to save her,
but we can't tear the Ning family apart
just to save Xiuxiu.
Kejin, what are you waiting for?
Go find a doctor for your mother.
Mother. Mother.
Father.
I'm begging you.
Please save Xiuxiu.
I don't want the family business
you left for me.
I just want you
to save my sister, Xiuxiu.
Nonsense.
Our ancestors passed it down
generation after generation,
and I've worked so hard
to build our family fortune.
Do you think it's something
you can discard just like that?
Let me ask you.
Can you come up with any good idea
without tearing the family apart?
I can't think of it now.
But Father, I know
I don't want any family business.
I just want you to save my sister!
Let me ask you.
Why did you take people up the mountain
without consulting me?
You even got in a fight with the bandits,
risking your life.
Do you think it'll still work
if we take the land deeds
to the bandits now?
Do you think those bandits will trust us?
Your sister would only suffer more
after you did that.
You mean
I made things even harder for my sister?
What use do you think those bandits have
for land deeds?
Do you think
they'd dare openly sell the land
or send people to farm it?
They dare not.
You are the eldest son of the Ning family.
Don't just come up with bad ideas
which will cost our family
like your mother and Susu.
Just get through tonight,
and it'll be alright.
Beauty.
I asked you if you wanted water just now,
but you declined.
Was it because
you want to have some wine with me?
What do you want?
I'll feed you with my lips.
What are you doing? Go away!
Who are you?
I'm your boss's guest.
Guest?
Guests should stay in the lobby.
What are you doing out here?
I'm looking for the toilet.
There are toilets everywhere,
aren't there?
Wait...
Keep quiet!
I'll kill you if you make any noise.
Where is the girl you kidnapped?
In... In the woodshed.
Keep quiet.
Go away!
Someone!
Let go of me! Someone!
It's me.
When we were kids, my mother worked
as a cook for your family.
They were like sisters,
and I was like a brother to you.
Do you remember me now?
Second Brother Guo?
It's really you!
Yeah, it's me. Why did they kidnap you?
If you don't save me,
I'll die here.
Alright, listen to me.
There're guests here tonight.
Maybe you can take the chance
to escape.
But this red outfit of yours is
too conspicuous.
Put on Jiu's clothes.
After you go out,
the stable will be on your right.
There are fewer people there.
Also,
Sis,
for the sake of
my mother's and my own life,
make sure you don't tell anyone
that I released you.
You must keep it a secret.
Come on, let's take off his clothes.
Here.
Here. Have some tea.
We're relatives by blood.
There's no need for such formalities.
The fact that
you let me visit your stronghold
shows you haven't forgotten me.
Of course.
When we were kids,
we practiced martial arts together,
and I often took
the master's stick for you.
Here, have some tea.
Try this wild tea from Chicken Ridge.
Hurry up and go.
Don't hurt him!
Don't hurt him.
-Dajiao! Dajiao.
-Xiu.
Why are you here?
Xiuxiu, I'll take you home.
We just held
a farmers' representative meeting
in Changqing.
Our Party specially sent me
to various places in Shandong
to organize and establish
farmers' associations
and farmers' self-defense armies.
When I received the mission,
you were the first person I thought of.
Du.
I want you to lead your team
out of the mountain
to form a farmers' self-defense army.
As for what happened in the past,
we'll let bygones be bygones.
Du.
I think I've heard the line
"let bygones be bygones"
that your man here said
in operas before.
Well, of course,
things like this still happen nowadays.
But things like
turned foes and burned bridges
can also be seen in operas.
Brother, why don't I understand
what this mister just said?
Is that some kind of bird talk?
What's this ridiculous association
or self-defense army?
Watch your mouth!
What's wrong?
I always talk like this.
Ridiculous association.
What, are you going to slash me
with a knife?
Do you think I'm afraid of you?
Young man.
You're here to ask our boss for a favor.
If you want to invite Boss out
to handle matters,
you must kowtow three times.
Come on.
Kneel before me first.
Let me see your true intentions.
That's going too far!
Put it down! Put it down!
Ge, put the gun down!
Put the gun down!
Ge.
That's not how you're supposed to talk.
Du.
We're just here to tell you about this.
As for whether you want to
proceed with it,
we can discuss it later.
I'm hungry.
I've been waiting for you guys
for a long time.
Let's go
have a drink.
We'll have to pass.
We still have to go to the next town.
Let me carry you on my back.
I'm okay.
-I'm okay.
-Come up.
Hurry.
Dajiao.
Take a rest.
It's okay. I can take it.
Take a break.
Okay.
Dajiao.
You saved my life.
I don't want to be some lifesaver.
Let's just hurry back.
Are you really the only one...
Are you the only one who came to save me?
So my father really wouldn't sell the land
to ransom me?
I just came as soon as possible
after I heard you were kidnapped.
I don't know
whether your father sold the land or not.
Don't think too much.
You'll know everything when we get back.
Let's go.
Or they'll catch up soon.
Does Du have something to say to me?
Dismount.
Mr. Du, Boss wants you back.
Attack!
There's a cliff down there.
They'll fall to their deaths.
Brother!
Check it out.
These three iron beasts
are real treasures.
Their firepower is fierce.
No matter the distance,
every shot is a kill!
Brother.
This is what really touches a man's heart!
San.
When will you learn
to consult with me
before you do anything!
Are you darn crazy?
Du Chunlin is the youngest son
of the Du family.
He has two older brothers,
both government officials!
He's the treasure of Master's family,
and you killed him just like that?
Brother...
He's the brother I grew up with,
barefoot and sharing the same bed
since childhood!
Brother...
You...
Today, I have to...
Brother!
Brother, please don't! Brother!
Brother! Brother!
Brother!
I was wrong, Brother.
Please don't, Brother!
It was because I was worried
you'd risk the lives of our men.
I was worried they'd betray us.
T-That's why I did it, Brother!
I was wrong!
No going down the mountain
for a whole month!
Brother, don't worry.
At that time...
Get lost!
I shot covertly.
No one would know!
Sister-in-law.
Any news, Sister-in-law?
I brought you some food.
You need to eat well to have energy.
Getting married is pretty exhausting.
Sister-in-law.
My mind's in turmoil.
I can't eat right now.
I want to go to the Ning Residence.
Once Xiuxiu comes back,
I'll bring her home immediately.
Sister-in-law.
I beg...
I'll go with you
and ask them for an explanation.
Get me a horse!
Hurry up and gather our men!
Second Boss.
Go!
Second Boss!
Listen to me.
Your quick-money kidnap won't work.
I guess she's already home by now.
You keep standing in my way,
and now she's run away!
Tell me what I should do!
Second Boss.
Boss also said you were not allowed
to leave the mountain for a month, right?
But she ran away—
that's 5,000 silver dollars lost!
Madam.
We're here.
Sister-in-law.
Is Xiuxiu back?
Xiuxiu!
Young Master.
Wendian.
It's inauspicious to see the bride
before the wedding.
Besides,
these are all relatives here.
Don't make a fool of yourself.
We have to follow the rules.
I understand your concerns. Listen to me.
I'll go and check on her for you.
Qing.
Take care of Young Master.
Okay.
Mrs. Fei.
It's not midnight yet.
Why are you here again?
You're truly impatient.
Wendian couldn't rest easy.
Today is his wedding day.
I can't let him suffer.
I promised you
I'd send my pure and spotless daughter
to the Fei Residence before midnight.
Xiuxiu is really back.
Xiuxiu...
Young Master.
Young Master. Just wait for a bit.
Mrs. Fei, think it carefully
whether you want the bride or not
before you lift the curtain.
As long as she's pure and spotless,
she can be Wendian's wife.
I'm relieved to hear that.
Wendian.
Sister-in-law.
Hurry up.
Let's go back
and prepare for the wedding procession.
Sister-in-law, is Xiuxiu back?
Didn't you hear it just now?
Qing.
After you bring us home later,
take a shortcut
to go invite the master of ceremonies,
Ning Xueshi.
Invite all the relatives and neighbors
along the way
and tell them
the bride has been delivered to our house
before midnight.
Got it.
Great, Xiuxiu is really back.
Wendian, let's go home.
Wash your face
and get changed into the groom's outfit.
Let's get ready for the wedding
and receiving the guests.
Sister-in-law, Xiuxiu is really back.
You have to listen to me now.
I promise
you'll have
a grand and honorable wedding,
proudly bringing
the Fei family's new bride home.
Sister-in-law.
I'll do as you say.
Let's go.
Let's go, Young Master.
Xiuxiu is back.
Be careful.
Beard Liu! Beard Liu!
Coming, Madam.
Quickly send someone to guard the door
and get ready to welcome the bride
and carry in the dowry.
No problem.
Sister-in-law.
What can I do?
Hurry up and get changed,
and tie the bridal bouquet.
Let's go.
Okay.
Congratulations.
Thanks. Thanks.
The bride is so beautiful.
Good luck.
Thanks. Thanks.
Come on in. Come on in.
Third Uncle.
What took you so long?
Thanks. Thanks.
You're welcome.
Come on in.
How do I look?
Let's go.
Your clothes are still wrinkled.
Better now?
Wendian.
This wedding hasn't come easy.
Soon you'll have to
perform the wedding ceremony,
the bride must enter the bridal chamber
to receive blessings,
and you'll have to entertain the guests.
None of these can be skipped.
I understand, Sister-in-law.
I'm not finished yet.
I just want you to know
that whatever I arrange
is for your own good.
You have to complete this wedding
with me.
So,
just do as I say, okay?
Sister-in-law,
why do you keep repeating these words?
I understand. Xiuxiu is back,
and this is our survival
after the calamity.
I will make sure the wedding
is decent, grand, and honorable.
Do as I say.
Do I look good?
Very handsome.
Young Mistress has arrived!
Sister-in-law, you're here.
It's late at night,
so let's skip the instruments.
Mrs. Fei.
Our Ning family has delivered
the bride here
before midnight.
Thank you for your hard work,
Young Master Kebi.
Please go in for a drink.
I won't attend the banquet.
Uncle is still waiting for me
to go back and report.
Sorry for the trouble.
Thank you, Madam!
Congratulations!
Thanks.
Hurry up.
Here comes the bride!
Bride.
Please get off.
We're home.
Come on.
Cross the threshold.
Step over the fire basin,
ward off evil and dispel demons.
Scatter the bran.
Bran scattered means
abundant descendants.
Scatter the bran this year,
and you'll have a son next year.
Now, step over the doorstep.
The auspicious time has come!
Hold the wedding ribbon tight!
Congratulations!
Groom and bride,
take your places for the wedding ceremony.
Hooray!
First, kowtow to Heaven and Earth,
and to all the gods and spirits.
First kowtow.
Second kowtow.
Third kowtow.
Rise.
Second, kowtow to the broom's parents
in thanks for their nurturing.
Since the parents are absent,
kowtow to your sister-in-law!
Alright!
No, no.
This won't do, Uncle Xueshi.
No, no, no.
You've maintained your purity
and upheld the proper way,
caring for your own integrity—
truly a person of great virtue.
You arranged the marriage
on behalf of your late ancestors,
ensuring the Fei family's lineage
continues.
You're truly a meritorious figure
of the Fei family.
You should be honored with this rite
to commend your virtue.
You deserve their respectful bow.
Please sit.
Mrs. Fei, you deserve this.
Kneel!
Xiuxiu. Xiuxiu.
First Kowtow.
Second Kowtow.
Third Kowtow.
Serve tea!
Take it. It's my gift for you.
Rise.
Bride and groom, bow to each other.
First bow.
Second bow.
Third bow.
The ceremony is completed!
Great!
May the newlyweds be blessed with
endless happiness.
May you soon have children
and enjoy health and harmony.
Now, enter the bridal chamber!
Great!
Enter the bridal chamber.
This way, please.
Be careful. Careful.
Don't push.
Wendian.
With so many people watching,
the bride must be shy.
Look at the bride yourself later.
You all must have waited long.
Let's start the banquet.
Steward Liu, go get the banquet started.
Great!
Time for the banquet!
Time for the wedding wine!
Wendian.
Those who've come to congratulate you
so late at night
are all our benefactors.
You must entertain them well.
Yes.
Qing.
Take Young Master to greet the guests.
Got it. Young Master.
Sister-in-law, wait a moment.
Xiuxiu.
You must be tired.
Have a good rest.
I'll come back to you later.
Don't worry, Sister-in-law.
I will make sure everyone's entertained.
Okay.
Qing, let's go.
Young Master.
Go. Go.
Watch the door.
Got it.
Susu, is that you?
Mrs. Fei.
How did you know it was me?
I...
I didn't mean to lie to you and Wendian.
Are you hungry?
I'm starving.
Take off your cloak.
Thank you, Sister-in-law.
Come on, eat.
I can eat all these?
They're all prepared for you. Eat up.
Mrs. Fei, you're so nice.
Susu,
what's this really about?
My father said
once I got on the bridal sedan,
he'd have time to save my sister.
When my sister comes back,
he'll take me away.
Mrs. Fei,
you won't blame me, will you?
I didn't mean to lie to you.
I'm doing this for my sister.
I know.
Susu, you're a good girl.
By doing this,
you did not only help your sister,
but also all of us.
I won't blame you.
Just stay here with peace of mind.
If you feel sleepy after eating,
you can sleep first.
But remember one thing.
Don't let anyone
know who you are,
including Wendian.
If anyone else finds out,
you won't be able to help your sister.
Understand?