[This Thriving Land]
[Episode 13]
How... Xiu...
I thought I was too late when I saved you.
But those bandits didn’t
lay a finger on you.
You're... unharmed.
What else could it be...
Back then, my father
left me to rot in that bandits' lair.
I made up those stories
just to see if he even cared.
To test whether he still
cared for  his own daughter.
Why would you humiliate yourself?
See what you've gone through for this!
Let me talk to them!
Lie down...
Lie down!
Who exactly are you going to tell?
Are you going to
stand on a stage and shout,
"My Xiuxiu wasn't harmed
by those bandits"?
Dajiao,
those who cared already showed it.
And those who don't...
no words will ever matter.
I just feel...
after all you've suffered,
we have to make them pay.
This isn't something revenge can fix.
Then why...
You always say
I'm the closest person to you.
But why didn't you tell me sooner?
You never once looked down on me.
It makes no difference
whether I tell you or not.
Besides...
I promised to keep it secret for someone.
Secret?
For whom?
When I was trapped in that bandits' lair,
it was Guo who risked his life
and snuck me out with the food deliveries.
That's how I came to you...
You've actually met him.
That night—
the man I kicked down...
Letting hostages escape from bandits' lair
means death by a thousand cuts.
So...
just drop it.
Xiu...
you've been through so much,
keeping everything bottled up.
In the future,
we ought to thank Guo the way he deserves.
I believe...
this is your mother,
no,
our mother's kindness
flowing through you.
From this day on,
I'll walk every step
by your side,
shield you from harm,
and protect you forever.
Dajiao, Xiuxiu—rise and shine!
It's second moon's second day.
It's time to circle the granary!
-Mother.
I'd have forgotten without you!
Today is second moon's second day.
That's right.
Here I come!
On Dragon's Day, we bang the pots.
Little mice, pack your lots!
Where to move? Don't you see?
To the rich man's granary!
Spare our crops; gnaw his gold.
Eat that miser's storehouse cold!
Mother...
Xiuxiu... you know how, right?
Have you done this before?
Can you manage it?
My mother used to circle it...
but the speech part was different.
So, what was your speech?
Come, come!
You will circle the granary.
Me? Do the circling?
But... you always lead it every year!
Things may change.
You're grown now.
It's time to shoulder the household.
No more gallivanting about.
You lead the circling,
and bring your wife with you.
If I'm to shoulder this household,
then my word rules.
Return the land to Tietou's family—
and I'll stay for good.
Suit yourself. Do it or don't—up to you.
Father never said no to returning it.
Let's stick to the granary circling today.
Fine, I'll do the circling!
Come, Xiu—
you lead the steps,
I'll follow you.
Here,
Xiu!
Bless the grain.
Let's go!
Easy there. Mind your arm!
Here.
Mother.
Say it.
Xiu.
You may proceed with your version.
Second moon's second day;
Dragon lifts its head;
Big barns brim full;
Small barns overflow;
Wheat piles high, grains carpet earth;
Gold and silver ingots sprout forth!
So nice!
Exactly!
Dragon's Day wakes the plow-oxen;
Spring tills, summer tends—earth's rhythm;
Hooves churn blessings through the soil;
Rains kind, winds mild—lucky season!
Granaries burst!
Harvests boom.
Granaries burst;
Harvests boom!
Granaries burst!
Granaries burst! Harvests boom!
Harvests boom!
Dragon lifts its head;
Big barns brim full; Small barns overflow;
Granaries overflow, fields drown in gold.
Coins sprout from the soil—
fortune unfolds!
Master,
you own so much land,
and we already have surplus grain.
Yet you still circle
such a massive granary.
How can you manage it all?
What nonsense!
I'm circling the granary here!
Besides,
who ever complained about too much grain?
If your jinxing words
reach passing gods' ears,
and come harvest
my granary isn't bursting,
I'll chop you up
and stuff you in with the wheat!
Oh mighty spirits!
All mighty spirits!
I was just babbling nonsense!
Treat me like passing wind!
I'm just a dumb child!
Don't let my master chop me up!
Thank you, sacred ones!
Thank you! Thank you, all gods!
Thank you!
You honey-mouthed rat!
All appetite and flattery!
I'm back!
Good heavens!
Father, why's the granary so huge?
Circling the granary was your job!
But you never came back,
so I had to do it myself!
I can't handle this job!
You know me.
I'm useless at fieldwork too!
Father!
Your son is meant for greatness!
See—
I've returned with glorious news!
Big talk again!
You vanish for days,
then swagger back with good news?
I should be thanking the gods
if you're not wanted by the law!
Look what I got you—
your favorite duck
from town!
Let's have a drink, just us two!
Kuangzi.
Whip up some dishes!
Come on!
Let's go, Father!
All this fuss
for the Qingqi Society
and that so-called Director—
what'd they pay you?
A few coins? Some land?
Learn from your old man!
That Feng Si's land—
how stubborn he was!
"I won't sell it! No way!"
Till I wore him down to nothing!
Father, can we please
stop measuring everything
in acres and coins?
That brain of yours—
always churning soil and silver!
What your son's doing now
will shake the heaven and earth!
Don't get cocky.
The winds aren't blowing our way now.
Stirring up trouble?
Watch your step—
back the wrong horse,
and you'll choke on the consequences.
Listen, Father—
the times are changing for real.
They say
when the Farmers' Association
comes to our village,
they'll demand permanent tenancy,
rent reduction, interest cuts—
maybe even land redistribution!
You need to take a stand.
What stand?
This land came from my ancestors!
You think some upstarts can just steal it?
Since when does the world work that way?
They won't debate ancestors with you!
They'll just say: "You stole this land".
What are you going to do about it?
Which of your muddled eyes
saw me steal land?
Can't you tell good advice from bad?
I'm trying to protect you!
Relax!
I went to the county seat,
and talked to all our old-timers
who once held influence.
The current situation is
just another power shift.
Like a gust of wind
that sweeps through the city outskirts.
It might not even reach us.
But you—you better watch out.
Now is not the time to stir up issues!
The Northern Expedition Army—
you know what their revolution really is?
Their battle cry is
"Smash the corrupt landlords!"
But who's corrupt, and who's a landlord?
That's up to them!
Don't think just
because you joined their cause,
you're safe from their lists!
True, you're right.
Listen here—
you'll do as I say.
Stay put and keep your mouth shut.
This isn't the time for adventures.
I've weathered more storms
than you've ever sailed through.
Yes, yes, of course.
You've eaten more salt
than I've eaten rice.
From now on, I'm your obedient servant.
What's so funny?
I'll need to
ask for a small favor from you.
Say it.
Have you ever
heard of a gun
called 20-round Mauser?
Fully automatic,
and so much better
than our crappy homemade rifles!
Director Du told me,
the Northern Expedition Army
equips a dozen per company!
That's why the Northern Expedition Army
dominate every fight!
It's all thanks to those guns!
Father—listen!
How much does it cost?
It's not expensive.
It costs
less than 10 silver dollars each.
I've got 20 guys,
You may equip me with 20 guns,
totaling to 200 silver dollars.
You mean, 200 silver dollars?
Two—Two Hundred?
200 silver dollars!
That gun is awesome.
How—
How many mu of great farmland
would this cost me?
You just flap your gums
like it's nothing!
Tell me! Do I look like
that 20-round thing to you?
Are you buying for me or not?
I won't buy it.
I don't have money.
What are you doing?
Did I scare you?
Come in here.
What's that in your hand?
Nothing at all!
You think I'm blind or something?
I was hungry,
so I grabbed a couple
alkaline steamed buns.
Pork belly stuffed
in refined steamed buns?
You actually have a good appetite!
Look at your waistline...
You've put on inches
after the New Year's celebration!
Don't pretend you don't notice!
How many times must I say it—
eat more alkaline foods!
I know.
Eat alkaline buns
and bear a son for the Fei family.
Fine. I won't eat it, okay?
I won't eat it.
Then take your medicine.
I know it tastes awful,
but I only want what's best for you.
This helps to warm your womb.
It gets your body ready
so you can conceive easier.
Finish it, and you can choose
lunch today...
plus a bowl of mung bean noodles.
Once you decide on lunch,
just tell the kitchen.
Beard Liu,
prepare more herbs for the Young Mistress.
Same prescription as before.
Five doses...
Actually, make it 10.
How am I supposed to live like this?
What's wrong with me?
I feel dizzy, with blurry vision.
Everything's spinning!
Does it still hurt?
See? It's already scabbed over.
I don't even need bandages.
This arm's never been
treated as precious before!
Back then, a cut here,
a stab there—
I never even noticed!
From now on,
these arms, legs,
hands, and feet of yours
are treasures.
They don't belong just to you anymore.
Then today,
I won't go anywhere—
these arms, legs, and hands
are all yours to keep. Deal?
Don't talk nonsense
What I mean is—
you've got to take care of yourself
before you can
care for our parents and me.
Alright, alright...
No more injuries,
no more worries.
Here—
gently now…
I've noticed that
this injury of yours
scared Father badly.
Let’s strike while the iron's hot.
I'll find Father later
to get back the land deed.
Why didn't you wait for me?
By the time you showed up,
the crops would've rotted.
Face it—you're half-crippled now.
Can't rely on you for squat.
This little bit of work?
I could do it one-handed!
You go rest—
You're good at nonsense!
One-handed is enough to handle it, huh?
You should be resting!
Why don't you go back?
Why don't you leave?
Look at you—
coming back bleeding.
Go ahead!
One wrong move
and next time it'll be your head!
We're farmers—
our duty is to tend the land.
That's the right thing to do.
Stop chasing pipe dreams!
Are you done yet?
Done.
So what?
if you won't leave, I'll quit nagging.
But take one step,
and I'll keep lecturing!
Father,
I mean it—I'll stay.
I'll work on the 18 mu of land with you.
If you want me to work more,
I'll explore new fields
to make it up to 20 mu,
for you and our family
But you must return Tietou's land.
If you still refuse to return it...
Director Du said,
once I'm healed,
he'll assign me to leave—
taking Xiuxiu with me.
And who knows
when we'd return?
Director Du even hinted...
when the movement grows,
he'll send me to the provincial capital.
Maybe even take trains
to the Forbidden City!
Do you think I'll get to see
the palace where the emperor lives?
Did that pot-bellied director say
you could see the Emperor showing?
Look at you, all grown up!
Why don't you go fly up to heaven?
To heaven, why not?
Go ahead!
Far away!
Out of my sight!
Then I'll leave now, for real.
Enjoy your 30 mu of weeds!
Sister-in-law!
Xiuxiu!
Look! Our land lease papers!
You said you'd get them back for me,
and you really did!
I was wrong about you.
Wait right there—I'm coming over!
Dajiao! Xiu!
Thank you!
I appreciate your help!
That two-faced monkey's got
the nerve to show up?
They may tolerate you, but I won't!
What breaks my heart...
is that land we tilled three times over...
Don't mention it, Auntie!
Tomorrow my mother, Xiuxiu and I
will come plant your peanuts
at Sesame Gully.
We can't wait until Tietou's back.
But I've sent word to Tietou,
urging him to return home faster.
Well...
Xiu.
I spoke out of turn the other day—
all that nonsense while I was heated.
Don't you dwell on my harsh words please
and don't stoop to my level.
I owe you a proper apology.
Honestly, Auntie...
I've been meaning to tell you too—
I shot my mouth off, same as you.
Hope you aren't holding that
against me either.
Of course not.
Alright then,
you all get back to work.
I'm heading out now—
See you later, Sister-in-law.
Wendian.
Should've sent word ahead—
we'd have Qing fetch you!
Here, eat!
No no...
She's got her own dishes.
This stays here...
Here.
This bowl's yours...
And this one's for you...
Here.
This...
You missed
the New Year's celebration at home—
so many dishes you didn't taste...
But I saved everything for you!
We'll have Qing cook it all for you later.
Sister-in-law,
this is too much—I can't finish it alone!
Let's all share it.
This is yours—no sharing!
Not a drop left!
Why?
For your health!
Now,
eat up quickly.
After this,
we've important matters to discuss.
And there's one more dish.
Where's the
Eucommia and Cistanche chicken stew?
Xiaoqin.
Susu.
How’s your sister been doing lately?
Has she got some kind of trouble?
My sister's fine.
But I've got a big problem now.
What's wrong, Susu?
Listen closely.
The only reason I came back
was a letter from your sister.
I know nothing!
If you want answers,
take it up with your sister-in-law.
My sister-in-law?
Never mind.
I'll go see Xiuxiu in a little while.
Where are you heading?
Sister-in-law,
I'd like to go for a walk after dinner.
Where you gonna go?
It's pitch black out there!
Whatever it is can wait till tomorrow.
Here—this is yours too.
And this...
Enjoy it.
Susu.
Drink this—
go on, drink!
After dinner, get to bed early.
Wendian's been traveling all day.
He must be exhausted.
Later, get Wendian's footbath ready.
And before sleep...
I know. I know.
Sister-in-law,
didn't you say earlier
there was something important?
What is it?
Well, Susu felt embarrassed.
Sister-in-law, I'm not tired.
I don’t need a footbath!
Who's talking about that footbath?
Wendian, listen.
I'll only ask one thing
from you during this visit.
That is to get Susu pregnant.
Once Susu's carrying your child,
you can roam wherever,
and return whenever.
I won't even lift a finger to stop you.
Sister-in-law,
the whole reason
I came back was to settle this.
this..
Pat her back, quickly!
What's wrong...
Beard Liu, bring a broom here!
What's wrong with you...
What's going on with you?
I've been feeling sick to my stomach...
I don't want to drink
this alkaline porridge.
Oh, Susu.
Sister-in-law, my period
hasn't come for two months now.
I'm afraid I might be...
What?
I'm afraid I might be pregnant.
My period hasn't come
for two months now.
P—Pregnant?
Come on, quickly!
To bed—immediately!
Why didn't you say so earlier?
I had no clue! You...
You...
How are you feeling now?
Lately I've been dizzy as hell,
nauseous too…
My belly's all hard and swollen...
But you keep saying I'm just overeating!
Saying my clothes shrunk in the wash!
I’m miserable.
Let me feel it...
Let me check.
Oh! It really is firm...
Firm indeed!
Then... most likely you're with child!
Oh, Susu...
I'm so sorry, I had no idea...
Hush now, no more tears... no more tears.
This is wonderful news, Wendian!
That's impossible...
Why not?
I'll let you know
if it's possible in a bit.
Susu!
You stay in bed now—don't get up!
I'll be back soon!
Beard Liu!
Madam, I'm here.
Stop sweeping! Forget the sweeping!
Prepare the cart
and fetch the doctor! Now!
Keep quiet!
Faster!
Hurry up.
Move it!
Get out of my way.
Second Boss.
The clothes and bedding are all silk—
I took everything.
But I couldn't find any silver.
Take all the farmhands outside—now!
Up! Move!
Faster, faster—
Move!
Move it!
Don't move a muscle. Stay put.
Standard rules.
Who scouted this place?
Step forward. Interrogate them yourself.
Spare me...
You think I don't know
whether your family has money?
Feng Si!
You landlords—
all slick talkers and sweet lies!
Cheating, stealing, scheming in shadows—
while we farmers
watch our ancestors' last coins
slip into your vaults!
Your fields devour ours,
gnawing our bones dry—
not even spitting out the marrow!
Everyone!
Shall I paint you a white gourd
or a red gourd?
I want red!
-White gourd.
-Red.
I'll count to three.
If red comes out—it's red.
If white comes out—then enjoy the white.
One.
Two.
Take it! Take it all!
Just give them the money—now!
Damn, he ran fast...
Just some worthless hired hand.
Whatever. Let him go.
Alright, let's head back.
Alright. Let's go.
This pulse…
It's chaotic.
Chaos?
Is it pregnancy?
A pregnancy pulse?
It resembles that.
It resembles a pregnancy pulse.
Resembles?
It is!
It is a pregnancy pulse.
A pregnancy pulse.
That's true.
It's a pregnancy pulse.
Wendian.
I feel sick.
Get the basin!
Here. Here you go.
Here—let it out!
Qing.
Madam.
The Young Mistress is pregnant!
At first light tomorrow,
go to the Ning's Residence
with the news.
And send word
to her elder sister's family as well.
Yes, understood, Madam.
Doctor Huo.
Write the prescription.
List everything
that she should eat or drink!
Certainly.
My poor Susu.
You've endured such hardship...
Miss Xiuxiu.
Dajiao.
Qing.
Miss Xiuxiu.
Mrs. Fei
asked me to bring you a message,
our Young Mistress is pregnant!
That's wonderful!
Susu's pregnancy is such blessed news!
The Fei family lineage
will now flourish and grow.
Since the younger sister conceives first,
you, the elder sister,
surely won't be far behind?
Mother!
Alright then, I'll be going now.
-Thank you.
Mother, I should go check on Susu.
Go, go see her.
Let me change clothes first.
Mother...
Shall we
have Xiuxiu bring those eggs to Susu?
Great minds think alike!
Come on, let's get the eggs.
Susu!
Come on here, quickly.
Susu, your sister's here to see you!
Susu.
Xiuxiu.
I brought you eggs—get your strength up.
How are you feeling now?
Xiuxiu!
Be careful.
Xiuxiu.
I feel so sick...
Why am I so nauseous?
This is all my fault.
Susu has missed two monthly cycles,
but I didn't even notice it.
But Xiuxiu, listen—
I swear
I'll care for her properly now.
Right now, she enjoys
the same level of care as our ancestors.
We might as well build her a shrine!
Xiuxiu,
keep watch on her.
Don't let her feet touch the ground!
First trimester's
the most critical period.
Ah! She barely ate during lunch.
I'll get her something for her.
You girls talk.
I can't swallow anything down right now...
You're not just yourself anymore.
You need proper rest and care.
That body carries two souls now,
no more reckless running about!
Our little Susu...
soon to be a mother...
If only our mother were here,
she'd be wild with joy.
Xiuxiu.
Is this...
really something to be so happy about?
Of course it is! You silly girl!
Listen, Su—
you rest well now.
Once the sickness passes,
I'll take you to my house.
I'll care for you proper.
Here, lie down.
I don't want to.
It suffers... right here...
Don't press it randomly.
Xiuxiu,
Wendian's return...
we owe it all to your letter.
I owe you deep gratitude.
Sister-in-law,
We still haven't thanked you properly
for helping with
Tietou's land dispute last time...
I keep my promises.
Qing.
Prepare the cart to send Xiuxiu home.
No need, I can walk...
Xiuxiu.
Wendian,
Since you're here,
escort Xiuxiu out properly.
I'll go check on Susu.
Xiuxiu.
Wendian,
I haven't gotten a chance
to congratulate you yet.
You're going to be a father now.
Susu's carrying your child.
I hope...
you'll treat her well from now on.
While you were gone...
Susu had it...
pretty rough.
She told me more than once
she couldn't bear the Fei family anymore.
I kept thinking—she's so young,
so unsure of herself...
so I urged her
to try harder with you.
So, this time...
don't leave so soon.
Susu's still a child at heart,
but her love's fierce,
and her intentions pure.
Wendian,
promise me this:
be good to Susu.
I'll go now...
but I'll visit Susu again soon.
Father...
I—I know I messed up...
Let go.
Father...
just let me keep this one bird?
I need... something to remember it by.
Take it.
Stew it with liquor.
But you don't have to—
Take it.
Fine. Fine.
Just this one, Father...
Let me keep it, please... for memories...
Get out.
Second Uncle.
Kejin.
How did it go?
That brat is finished!
They refuse to settle.
They say he's their only son,
not even married yet,
and now his leg's been broken by him!
Now they're taking it to court.
They want him rotting in prison!
Father! I know I was wrong!
Father, I can't go to prison!
Father, before Mother died,
you promised her
you'd get me a wife and kids—
to carry on the Ning family line!
You wretch!
Father.
When you were beating that man
half to death,
where was your conscience then?
Li.
Master.
Drag this wretched boy
to kneel
before his mother's memorial tablet!
Now!
Please come along, Young Master...
Don't inflame your father further.
Kejin.
is there any room for negotiation?
Useless as this fool is,
I must keep him from the gallows.
We can't let him rot in prison!
I'll try calling in favors...
See if any connections can intervene.
But Second Uncle—
you'd better prepare some silver.
Father.
You're back!
We were just about to bring you your meal!
No, no—
hold on!
Great news!
What news?
The heavens shut a door on me…
But opened a window!
We can forget about Tietou's land.
Now, we can buy your Second Uncle's plot!
He's desperate for help now.
That no-good cousin of yours
got into trouble!
What? Kebi's in trouble?
Wasn't he obsessed with those…
quail fights?
That's right!
Then Song family's boy from the town
had a quail
that pecked his bird's eye out!
Your cousin lost his temper,
beat the kid up—
and broke his bones!
Luckily, your brother stepped in,
and they barely agreed to
settle for 500 silver dollars!
Father,
I'll go assess the situation.
I'll go with you.
Wait—
hold up! hold up!
Are you planning to buy land?
You even got the money?
Listen up, everyone!
If you can actually help,
talk to my second uncle inside later.
If you can't?
Quit loitering around
and go back now!
What a mess!
So much money.
-Where to gather that much?
-Exactly.
Xiu's here!
Xiuxiu is here. Go inside.
Make way—Xiuxiu's here!
His niece is here!
Xiuxiu has arrived.
Kejin, what's the situation now?
You two got the news too?
Go check on Second Uncle, quick!
Xiu, you go in there first.
Where is Kebi?
He's locked in the woodshed.
That little brat's had it too easy.
Let him starve for a few days
Dajiao and I came
as soon as we heard about it.
What can I do to help?
Just you being here to talk with me
already puts my heart at ease.
Everything has been handled by Kejin.
I could never measure up to your father.
He raised fine children...
Second Uncle,
You'd rather sell your land
to save your son—
gave up everything
to keep Kebi out of prison.
That's what a real father does.
Him? He's not fit to stand in your shadow.
Xiuxiu...
About what happened to you—
I failed to help.
That regret still cuts deep.
The land agent is here.
Uncle, why'd you come back alone?
Where are the buyers and Mrs. Fei?
I came ahead.
Mrs. Fei said she'd follow shortly.
My in-laws!
Father,
what are you doing here?
I came here to help.
Help with what? Let's not get involved.
Go home!
Stay aside.
What do you even know!
Stay out of my way.
My in-law!
Cousin brother.
Father.
You...
I heard about the family trouble.
No other intention—
here's 40 silver dollars. 40.
Just take it to settle the trouble.
The child is what matters most.
Feng Er,
Your kindness
Your kindness leaves me
at a complete loss.
Feng Er, please take a seat.
Sit down, please.
Come on here.
Xiuxiu, pour your father-in-law
some tea—quickly!
Father.
Thank you!
We're family—
no need for such formalities!
Feng Er.
I know this money—
for folks like us who work the land—
comes from skipping meals,
patching clothes,
coin by hard-earned coin.
Yes, that's true.
Your willingness to help
touches me deeply,
but I can't in good conscience
take your hard-earned silver.
Let's pick the land properly—
no one ever feared too many fields.
Even between kin,
accounts must stay clear.
Feng Er,
please have a look at the land later.
No—No rush.
Settling the trouble is more important.
Village Chief!
I'm here to help too.
I've come here to offer my help as well.
We can help!
We can help.
Thanks everyone for coming to help.
Let's go and talk outside.
Alright.
We have money here.
I know you all come with money.
I want to thank everyone
on behalf of my uncle.
We do have land available.
Prime plots included—
guaranteed you'll get yours.
Please take a break first, okay?
Okay then, I'll be waiting.
Great.
Just a moment, please.
Then we'll wait here.
I'll be waiting right here.
Dajiao,
I gotta get home for a bite—
I'm starving.
If anything comes up here,
just send someone to call me back here.
All right!
Kejin.
Does Ning Xuexiang know about this?
What did he say?
Will he help?
Father hasn't been home these days.
He went to the provincial capital
to visit Uncle Pan.
I'll grab a bite at home.
Is Father here to buy the land?
Our father—
he knew exactly Second Uncle's soft spot.
Called it helping in need,
but we all know he came for the fields.
Even played the saint while at it.
Now with the good plots almost gone,
he can't keep up the act.
I'm gonna find Susu.
I’ll go with you—
got something to tell you on the way.
Okay.