[This Thriving Land]
[Episode 34]
I want my Silly Tiao back!
Silly Tiao...
I'll go get a doctor.
Good for you, young man.
You can cut more firewood than me now.
Kela,
come here.
Sir, that woman was a dunderhead.
That explains it.
Let's go.
Keep up.
Careful.
Silly Tiao!
Silly Tiao, wake up!
Silly Tiao...
Mother! Mother!
Mother.
Silly Tiao!
Mother!
Silly Tiao, Silly Tiao!
Silly Tiao!
Mother...
Don't worry about me.
Check on Silly Tiao.
Your mother is fine.
But I'm afraid Tiao won't make it.
-Mother, Mother!
-Xiuxiu has left to get a doctor.
Mother, hang in there.
Mother, open your eyes!
Silly Tiao is dead...
Mother!
Those Japanese...
Tietou's mother...
Tietou! Tietou!
You can't go.
If you do see me as your brother,
then don't try to stop me!
Tietou!
Step out of this place,
and you won't come back alive.
Don't you care about your mother anymore?
I must kill those Japanese!
Though Silly Tiao was a dumb cluck,
she gave birth to Kela
and treated me with all her heart.
But those Japanese just killed her.
I swear
to avenge her!
Tietou!
Listen to me.
If you kill those Japanese,
won't their fellows
slaughter the entire village?
But what about Silly Tiao's death?
As long as we're alive,
we'll be able to
avenge her someday.
We definitely will.
My hatred for the Japanese
was no less than Tietou's.
I felt a strong urge to lead him
and the other young men in the village
to join the Eighth Route Army
and Mr. Du
in fighting against the Japanese.
But I knew
that wasn't the right time.
I must stop Tietou
from getting himself killed.
Before long,
we started to hear
good news from the battlefield.
Under the leadership of
the Communist Party,
the soldiers and civilians
in the Anti-Japanese Base Areas
had the Japanese by the throat
and broke their railways,
leaving them in a quandary.
Our guerrillas and militias
kept marching on like ever-growing crops.
The morale was rising and rising.
I knew fairly well
that if needed,
I'd also be ready to fight the Japanese
till my last breath,
with a hoe in one hand
and a gun in the other.
Those Japanese are truly inhuman.
I'm very afraid.
Look at my sister-in-law.
Her mental state is never stable.
I have to keep her from going out.
It must be hard for the two of you
to live through
all these difficult times.
Whether it's day or night,
remember to lock the door.
I know.
Xiuxiu,
I know what you want to ask.
He had a message delivered to me
two months ago.
Since then,
I haven't heard from him again.
Isn't he said to be
hauling artillery for the Kuomintang?
Why is it taking so long?
Dajiao and I
are worried about him too.
Dajiao even made inquiries
through someone.
But there hasn't been a final word.
Humpback Guo has been away for so long.
It's very concerning.
He's a really
tough guy,
like an ant—
if a car ran him over,
he'd just get up, dust himself off
and continue to live and move on.
I'm glad you think it that way.
I refrained myself from asking you,
though I was worried sick.
You've really grown up, Susu.
Xiuxiu,
to be more accurate,
I've grown old.
Some women at my age
have already become grandmothers,
while I'm carrying my first child.
I can't conceal my pregnancy anymore.
I have to wear a large coat
to cover my ugly belly.
Ugly?
Nonsense.
Mothers are never ugly.
Xiuxiu,
I just want to keep my pregnancy secret
from Mrs. Fei.
If she finds it out,
she'll surely be upset for a while.
But I don't think
you can hide it for too long.
If you can't stay
in the Fei Residence anymore,
go to our father's.
If that doesn't work, come to me.
I promise
I'll take good care of you,
so you can wait for Humpback Guo's return
with your mind at ease.
Xiuxiu,
I have a hunch
that he'll come back one day.
I believe he will.
Dajiao and I
will clean up the side room for you.
Taking care of you
will keep my worries at bay.
Don't you think so,
little baby?
Look.
Auntie made you a shirt.
How do you like it?
We'll put it on you after you're born.
Say something.
Thank your aunt now.
Come on, say thank you.
You're welcome.
Haven't forgotten me, have you?
Humpback Guo,
how could I have forgotten you?
Do you know
what I've been through these days?
I thought you had drowned
and become fish food!
I was captured by the Kuomintang
to haul artillery.
I truly thought I'd never make it back.
Bombs exploded right by my ears every day.
Shrapnel tore arms and legs
apart from people.
But every day, as I woke up,
I'd tell myself
that I must not die there.
If I am to die,
I'll have to die where you are.
What's that nonsense?
You're already back. No more death talk.
How did you manage to come back?
The troops were moving again.
I seized a chance
to quickly
roll into a trench
and hide among some dead bodies.
I lay there for a whole day.
I dared not move at all,
in case anyone found me alive.
Then, as night fell,
I sensed I was left alone there,
so I...
I finally made it back...
alive.
Why are you staring?
You're beautiful.
I can't get my eyes off you.
I missed you so much.
I won't let you
leave me again.
I won't go anywhere.
I'll never part with you again.
Even death can't separate us.
It's my baby?
Do you even need to ask?
I'm going to be a father?
I was thinking about going out
to do business
so I could make enough money to marry you.
But I haven't earned a penny yet.
I'll marry you even if you're penniless.
Tomorrow,
I'll ask your father for your hand
in marriage.
I'll go with you.
Humpback Guo
suddenly came back.
It all seems like a dream to me.
How is that?
It should be Humpback Guo's dream instead.
He's making a marriage proposal so soon.
When this room is tidied up,
he can live here with his pregnant wife.
How wonderful.
Mother,
what will be Auntie's baby's surname,
Fei or Guo?
It'll be Ning.
Your brother's joking.
Auntie's baby's surname will be Guo.
This baby has nothing to do
with the Fei family.
Your aunt lives in the Fei Residence
only to take care of Mrs. Fei.
Mother, I don't understand.
Why do I have Father's surname
instead of yours?
What now?
Is your ancestors' surname
not good enough for you?
Whatever your surname is,
Father and Mother
treasure you all the same.
Right, Jiaming?
Mother, then my name will be
Ning Jiaying from now on.
Ning Jiaying?
Ask your father if he agrees.
Don't fret.
Just speak your mind.
Here's tea!
Glad to see you back.
Have some tea.
Thank you.
Stay for dinner, alright?
I'll cook.
Father.
No.
Mr. Ning,
I, Guo Guiyao, am paying you a visit.
Leather shoes.
Father,
Humpback Guo has something to say.
Say it.
I meant to send a matchmaker over
for this marriage proposal,
but then I thought
it would be better if I did it myself.
I brought some snacks
for Young Master Keyu.
Maybe he can try them later.
Humpback Guo, good for you.
You were away for six months.
The moment you're back,
you're asking to marry my daughter.
I...
disagree.
Father,
what's the matter now?
Didn't you tell Yinzi
that you hoped to see Humpback Guo back
and marry me off to him?
I did say that,
but not to his face.
I can't talk like that when he's around.
Come on, sit here.
Take the seat next to me.
I'm doing this for your own good.
No.
If you treat him with hostility,
I'll leave with him right now.
I'll make sure
you never see your grandchild.
Susu...
He's destitute.
You'll live in poverty if you marry him.
You have money.
Why not give him some?
Look at that!
Would a daughter ask her father
for dowry this way?
Besides,
wealthy though I am,
does he know how to farm
if I give him a few mu of land?
Humpback Guo,
do you know how to farm?
I'm acting in your best interests, Susu.
If he can afford proper betrothal gifts,
at least you and your baby
will have a decent life
after you marry him.
Mr. Ning, you're right.
It's true that I don't know how to farm,
but I've figured out a plan.
I promise I'll learn from Feng Dajiao,
my future brother-in-law,
with the will to start from scratch.
I'd rather let myself suffer
than starve Susu and the baby.
Doesn't my daughter deserve
more than a meal?
She was well fed and clothed
when I raised her.
Take Keyu as an example.
What does he eat and drink?
What school does he go to?
My way is the right way to raise a family.
Yes, of course.
You think I'd have respect for you
because you're wearing leather shoes?
You own nothing.
I'd rather keep my daughter
and grandchild around,
so I can provide for them myself.
Mr. Ning,
what are you saying?
How can I let you
provide for my woman and child?
You've really underestimated me.
I've been a merchant for over 20 years.
I've seen everything.
Why do you have to look down on me?
What now?
You want
a fight with me?
Humpback Guo, what are you doing?
Don't try to stop me, Susu.
Since your father has put it that way,
I won't show him any courtesy!
What's your plan?
You...
Get me a brush and paper.
For what?
You want to write in your blood?
I mean for you to write down
a list of
betrothal gifts.
In one year, or three at most,
you'll receive them!
Is it true?
I'm a man of my word.
You have my promise.
I'll start writing then, Humpback Guo.
Keep this in mind—
you're marrying my daughter,
the finest girl for miles around.
Just you wait!
Why did you have to create that tension?
Father, stop it. He can't afford anything.
What's that nonsense, Susu?
Trust me.
It's just about making money, isn't it?
That's what I've spent
half my life working on.
If it weren't for the Japanese,
I would've become
one of the richest men in the village!
Mr. Ning, write it all down.
I'll laugh at you
if you don't make a long enough list!
Shut up, you.
[Farming is the only way
to sustain a family]
Mr. Ning!
Father,
well noted!
Time to cook, Yinzi.
Jiaming, Kela!
All the kids,
take your tools with you.
The Japanese aren't around now.
I'll teach you how to grow sorghum
on the Turtle Hill today.
-Okay?
-Okay.
Where is Keyu?
Is he not here?
He is. I saw him just now.
Keyu!
Where is he?
Uncle said
he had to skip the outing
since he didn't feel well.
Skip?
Where is he now?
He's reading in the room.
Keyu!
Why won't you go to the fields with us?
Do you feel sick or what?
Maybe I can be of help.
Can't you just tell my father
I've worked the fields?
Why do you have to drag me into it?
I'm not cut out for farming,
and I don't like it.
I'm not going with you.
Keyu,
come here.
Give me the book.
No.
You rascal.
Will you go farming or not?
Don't beat him.
Why can't I?
Someone has to correct his mistakes.
You...
Come over.
Nobody is born a natural for farming.
The skills are to be acquired.
When you get home, tell your parents
that I beat you today.
Ask them if what I did was right.
Give me their answer tomorrow.
Do you hear me?
Alright. Time to set off.
Let's go farming.
Go.
Guys, go!
Dajiao!
What's up?
Give this book back to him later.
Tell him
I bought him a few more.
I've learned this trick.
It's a carrot-and-stick approach.
Come back early.
We need to
clean up the side room for Susu.
Got it.
Bye, Mother.
Where are your manners?
One shouldn't raise a hand to an outsider.
Have you forgotten that?
Keyu is my younger brother,
not an outsider.
He should be disciplined by your father.
My father can't bring himself
to lay a hand on Keyu.
It has to be done by me.
But you've never hit Jiaming even once.
How could you hit Keyu?
Mother,
Dajiao is disciplining Jiaming
for both of us.
By contrast,
Keyu has been spoiled
by my father and Yinzi,
so I had to teach him a lesson.
Yinzi wouldn't mind.
My father will figure it out sometime.
I'll prepare lunch!
Look at that.
Did you see?
You must behave.
Sweetheart,
be a good girl.
You have a formidable mother.
She's even tougher than a teacher.
Don't mess with her.
What's with your belly?
Are you pregnant?
Who's the father?
Who?
Sister-in-law,
I'm pregnant with Guo Guiyao's child.
He has asked my father
for my hand in marriage.
I'll marry him soon.
But you are Wendian's wife.
How could you be knocked up
by another man?
"Knocked up"?
That's very rude!
Wendian already passed away.
You know it best.
On the day I married into the Fei family,
Wendian said I was a victim
of this marriage.
He always hoped for me
to have my own life.
Why are you...
acting like you're unaware of all that?
You belong here forever
since you married into the Fei family!
How could you trample on
our family's dignity like this?
The Fei family's reputation...
I've spent my entire life guarding it,
but it's all ruined now...
This is an illegitimate child.
You can't keep it. You can't.
Why can't I keep my baby?
I'm carrying Guo Guiyao's child now.
Why must I obey the stupid rules
of the Fei family like you do?
I came back to keep you company
because I'm worried about you.
Change your attitude,
or I won't stay with you!
Where are you going?
You can't leave.
You belong to the Fei family.
What are you doing?
You belong here.
You can't go anywhere!
What are you doing, Sister-in-law?
Come with me to the ancestral hall,
where you'll kowtow and apologize.
Okay!
Repent of your sins!
Yes, Sister-in-law, I'll do it!
But can you leave me alone for a moment?
Maybe I'll think it through
and choose to stay.
Sister-in-law,
you go there first.
Go ahead.
I'll be with you shortly.
I'll kowtow to the ancestors
for their forgiveness.
How horrifying.
I can't stay here anymore.
I must leave.
What should I do?
[In loving memory of
my husband Fei Wendian]
I disgraced the entire Fei family.
Susu did such a shameless thing
right under my nose.
I've failed...
I've failed all the Fei ancestors.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry!
What is there to do?
The baby...
must disappear.
It must disappear!
It must.
Where are you going?
Sister-in-law,
I'm going home.
After my baby is born,
I'll come back to take care of you.
You've married into the Fei family.
You're our daughter-in-law forever.
I won't let you go. Come back.
I don't belong here.
Come to the ancestral hall with me.
I won't let you go out
and humiliate the family.
Come with me!
Sister-in-law!
Sister-in-law,
I think I'm in labor.
Sister-in-law, get a midwife for me.
Tell my sister to come.
G-Get Humpback Guo here too.
You can't have this baby.
You can't.
Sister-in-law...
Push harder! Push!
It won't work if you don't push hard.
Push, now!
Take a breath.
Breathe.
Take a deep breath.
Sister-in-law!
Push!
I want my sister here!
Humpback Guo too, Sister-in-law!
I-I've informed them.
I've had someone go get them.
Madam Fei,
come help me now.
I need help. Come!
Hold Susu's legs.
Be quick!
Push some more.
I can see the baby's head!
Push again! Harder!
Push!
You're doing great.
It's going well.
Push!
Keep pushing.
What a beautiful little girl.
Though she was born two weeks early,
she seems quite sturdy.
Be careful. Keep yourself warm.
Madam,
congrats.
The young mistress just had a baby girl!
She's not.
Madam,
how will I be paid? By you or...
Thank you!
Is she
really not Wendian's daughter?
Sister-in-law,
you're confused again.
This is Humpback Guo's daughter.
Susu!
Did you...
Did you just give birth?
I thought you hadn't got the news yet.
I went to buy brown sugar.
Can't let the wind in.
It's a girl.
Let me hold her.
But how?
Be careful.
Mind her head.
Let me check her back.
Is it flat?
It is flat!
Her back's flat!
Lower your voice.
My little girl.
This is our daughter.
I have my own child now!
I promised to be with you in labor,
but I ate my word again.
That said, you arrived first.
Look.
Does she look like you or me?
You.
Her big eyes are exactly like yours.
I'm glad that she doesn't take after you.
Mrs. Fei,
I came as soon as I heard!
Susu gave birth, right?
Yes, she did.
Did something go wrong?
In the Fei family,
nothing can go wrong.
Susu!
Xiuxiu!
Xiuxiu.
Sweetheart,
say hi to your aunt.
I just fed her. She's a good eater.
Susu,
I already cleaned up
the side room for you.
Pack your things and leave with me.
Xiuxiu,
I just had a baby.
Won't I catch a chill if I move now?
Why do I have to leave?
There's lightning and thunder outside.
I think it's going to rain.
When I arrived,
I saw your carriage by the door.
Go get it prepared.
We'll leave before it rains.
-Let me hold the baby.
-Okay.
Come on.
Careful.
Auntie's going to hold you.
Alright.
Hurry up.
What's wrong, Xiuxiu?
Why do we have to leave now?
When I reached here,
I saw Mrs. Fei.
I'm concerned.
Just do as I say.
Okay.
I'll pack my things.
The carriage is ready.
Why are you bundled up like a dumpling?
Mind your tongue.
Hop on my back. Careful.
Sister-in-law!
Are you okay in there, Sister-in-law?
I'll go check on her.
Don't go.
It's going to rain.
Leave with me now. Don't catch a chill.
Xiuxiu,
I have to go check on her.
Please don't.
Alright. Don't worry.
Off you go.
Don't let the rain get on the baby.
But...
We'll be right with you!
Make it quick! Take care of Susu!
Sister-in-law!
Slowly.
Go ahead. See if she's fine.
Sister-in-law!
Mrs. Fei.
Are you all right?
Destroyed.
All is destroyed.
The Fei family
is destroyed.
Sister-in-law,
how is the Fei family destroyed?
You're still here, aren't you?
That's right.
I'm not counted in.
Not counted in?
How could you say that?
The Fei family wouldn't have
achieved so much
without your management, right?
Where's the baby?
Taken away,
by her aunt.
We'll be leaving soon as well.
Don't you worry, Mrs. Fei.
We'll come visit you again.
Alright?
Good.
Yes, Sister-in-law.
I'll often come visit you.
No need.
Why?
You don't want to see me anymore?
It won't be easy
for us to meet up again.
I'll go cook for you.
Let this meal
be a proper goodbye.
Don't bother.
We can't dine with you today.
Maybe next time.
We're just relieved to see you're fine.
There's lightning outside.
Susu had better not
get caught in the rain.
We have to go now.
When you're gone,
I'll be gone too.
I'll live with
my brother and nephew hereafter.
Let's dine
for one last time.
Wait for me.
Xiu!
Why did you bring the baby back?
The baby is fine in my arms.
Where are Humpback Guo and Susu?
They'll be here soon!
I'm all good.
The roof of the side room
is leaking!
I'll fix it right away!
Okay.
Go inside!
I don't think we should eat here.
Let's leave.
Your sister must be worried.
I miss our little girl.
Sit down.
It's cold. Wait a second.
Sister-in-law said
after I left,
she'd move in with her brother
and nephew.
They'll take care of her.
Who knows when we will meet up again?
Won't it be too cruel to her
if we don't dine with her?
Fine.
It's pouring rain anyway.
I'm just...
I'm just worried about you.
You jumped into this mess
right after giving birth.
Be friendly and grab a bite.
There's meat.
Mrs. Fei.
I made porridge
with red dates.
It helps Susu recover.
You haven't eaten anything today, right?
Eat with Susu.
How capable of you, Mrs. Fei.
You managed to cook meat
for Susu in this difficult time.
Sister-in-law,
to be frank,
the red date porridge you make
is my favorite.
I'm a bit hungry now.
Eat it then.
Have as much as you can.
I'd like to take this opportunity
to wish you two
a better and better life.
Thank you, Mrs. Fei.
What are we waiting for? Let's eat!
Enjoy.
It's too hot!
Blow onto it.
I like it warm.
Have some meat.
Jiaying,
are your father and brother
still mending the roof?
They went out to get wheat straws.
Mother,
my mind
is still unsettled.
I have to go to the Fei Residence.
Don't go. Let Dajiao do it instead.
Mother,
watch the baby for me.
It's raining. Be careful!
Susu!
I'll take you home.
Susu...
I'll take you home!
Help!
Help! I need help!
Somebody help me!
Help! Please!
[In loving memory of
my husband Fei Wendian]
The millet congee just cooled down.
Have some.
Eat it, good girl.
She's too young
to know how to eat congee. See?
Why not
let me hold her?
I'll take her out.
Perhaps I can find a lactating woman
to feed her.
You stay. I'll do it.
This is a life.
We must fend for her.
Give her to me.
Let go, Xiu.
She has to be fed.
Come on.
Give her to me.
I'll find milk for her.
We'll be right back.
Come on.
Xiu,
your sister is gone.
No matter how many tears you shed,
Susu won't come back to life.
She already passed away.
We should take care of those
who are still around us.
I've told those who buried the bodies
not to disclose any information.
I briefed Yinzi about it too.
Let's keep
this matter secret from Father
for as long as possible.
Xiu,
you haven't said a word
after the incident.
Please say something.
Don't keep your emotions bottled up.
If you want to cry, let it out.
Hit me
if you're mad.
Okay?
Is it lactating?
Give it a squeeze.
How much is it?
Two silver dollars.
Two?
Why not just go rob?
With two more, I can get an ox.
Take it or leave it.
You're lucky to have met me,
with the whole place
under the Japanese' watch.
I'll take it.
Xiu!
Look.
I brought something back.
You got a sheep?
That's great.
Look,
there's food for the baby now.
Mother,
your idea was brilliant.
Let's get some milk
for the baby.
Come here.
Time to get milk for the baby.