[This Thriving Land]
[Episode 7]
Susu.
Last night, did we...
Farewell, my homeland.
Farewell, my Xiuxiu.
Farewell, my forever lost love
and passion.
Susu.
Are you up?
What would you like to eat today?
I haven't decided yet.
Take your time.
Just let the cook know it
and they'll make it for you.
I need to go collect rents
with Steward Liu today
and won't be back until late.
Did Wendian say anything
when he left?
It's okay.
Don't worry about it.
If you need anything,
just tell me.
Let me do your hair.
You can't do it yourself anymore,
can you?
I can't do mine either.
Xiaoqin usually does it for me.
Sister-in-law, my hair looks awful.
I want to have it in braids,
which are simple.
Susu, you can't have braids anymore.
Looks good.
If you can learn more skills
to please your man,
that would be better.
I have to go now.
This hairstyle isn't as pretty
as when Xiuxiu does it.
It looks terrible.
How am I going to explain this to Xiuxiu?
Xiuxiu said
she wanted to come home to see me.
I heard this too from Lianye.
These words from her
are enough to satisfy me.
Mother, I know Xiu wants to see you.
I'll prepare the cart now
and take you to her.
We cannot go.
Why not?
Kejin.
Though your father has many flaws,
he is still your father,
the head of the Ning family.
Your sister is defying him
and if we also make trouble for him,
he'll lose all face in the village.
Then
he won't even be able to
speak confidently to peasant farmers.
Son,
whatever you do in the future,
you must consider
saving your father's face.
It's not just about his pride.
It's about the reputation and honor
of our entire Ning family.
Mother.
Father was so cruel
to my two sisters,
yet you still care about him.
Son,
isn't your mother like a millstone?
I must protect everyone in our family,
protect our bodies and our dignity.
Only then can the Ning family
be worthy of being called
the great family with over 700 mu
of land in this region.
You're right.
I'll do as you say.
Although the villagers have complaints
about my father,
when they speak of you, Mother,
everyone will give you a thumbs up.
Son,
I called you here
because there's an urgent matter
I need you to handle.
Go ahead.
What's up, Fei Wu?
Looking for me?
Dajiao.
My mother wants to see you.
Mother.
Dajiao is here.
Dajiao.
Come in.
Sit down.
Dajiao.
Have a seat.
How
are you feeling now?
I'm
fine.
Dajiao.
You've had a hard time these days.
Not at all.
I know
your father forced you to accept Xiuxiu
to get more dowry.
I'm sorry about that.
That's not true.
He didn't force me.
Dajiao.
I asked you to come today
because I want to talk to you.
After all,
you're now a son-in-law
of the Ning family,
but we haven't really talked before.
We have.
When?
I'm too old to recall it.
That autumn,
right after the sunflower harvest,
Xiuxiu and I,
along with some other children,
were playing in the yard
among the sunflower heads.
You called Xiuxiu home for supper
in the doorway,
and gave me two steamed buns,
thanking me
for always carrying Xiuxiu on my back.
You also said
she would go out to play after eating.
I remember everything.
Those buns you gave me
were very delicious.
Dajiao.
About the dowry,
Xiuxiu said she didn't want it.
I am thinking
that eventually,
I should let you take it back.
If you called me here for this reason,
then I must leave.
I absolutely cannot take it back.
X-X-Xiuxiu will be angry
if she knows this.
Alright,
let's not about it.
Come,
sit down.
Auntie,
let me be honest with you.
My father has his thoughts.
I keep Xiuxiu with me
not because I want anything from her.
Dajiao,
I asked you to come today
because I wanted to tell you a few things.
Please go ahead.
Do you love Xiuxiu?
I knew it.
My Xiuxiu didn't choose blindly.
This room.
is where
Xiuxiu grew up.
That day,
she and the matchmaker
walked out of this very room.
When she left this room,
she truly knew
you must be a good man.
Actually,
as her mother,
I shouldn't bring this up,
but I must say it now.
My daughter has endured many hardships.
I believe you already know about them.
I just want to tell you
that from now on,
you must treat her well.
I...
I will definitely treat her well.
You can rest assured.
Then I, as her mother,
should bow to you in respect.
Please don't.
-I can’t take it.
-Thank you.
Thank you for accepting her.
If one day,
you find her unsuitable
because of her past,
and don't want her anymore,
just send her back to me.
Don't let her remarry.
Just bring her back to me.
If I'm no longer alive by then,
you,
just take her to my burial mound.
Let her cry aloud
at my grave.
It'll be like I'm holding her,
comforting her.
Auntie.
Let's not talk about this anymore.
I swear
I will never,
ever dislike Xiuxiu.
As long as she's willing
to live a hard life with me,
I promise
I'll be good to her forever.
My Xiuxiu
would never mind
living a hard life with you.
My daughter Xiuxiu is capable of
making the best of the worst situation.
I feel relieved to hear
what you've said.
Don't tell her about your visit today.
She's sensitive.
She misses her mother,
and it would break her heart.
We can't hurt her anymore.
Xiuxiu has already had
too much heartbreak in her life.
We won't make her sad.
My poor Xiuxiu.
Mother.
You said you wouldn't cry.
Why are you crying again, Mother?
Mother, stop crying, okay?
No more tears.
Kejin,
please send your brother-in-law home.
Then carry me back to the house.
Alright.
Let's go, Dajiao.
Dajiao.
Bye.
Mother.
Please take care.
Xiu.
I heard you say
you missed your mother this morning.
I am thinking
I could borrow a cart tomorrow
to bring Mother here. What do you think?
Bring Mother here?
Yeah, bring your mother over.
She'll keep you company,
and help ease your mind.
But she's still ill—
she might not be able to travel.
If she stays with us,
she might recover quicker.
Our place
may be a bit rundown,
but who'd care for her
better than you?
And I'll be here too.
Together, we'll do better than anyone.
You're right.
If only she could come…
I miss her so much.
Tomorrow, we'll clean up the house.
I'll prepare the cart to fetch her.
Get some rest.
You too.
Old man,
you're back.
Ugh...
Did I wake you again?
Old man...
come here.
Keep me company for a bit.
I've got something to tell you.
So...
You're not mad at me anymore?
Old Woman...
Y-you—you're finally talking to me again!
Considering we'll
be buried together someday,
I can't keep ignoring you.
Old man,
I've thought it through—
You didn't save Xiuxiu
because you couldn't bear
to lose the land.
That land is your lifeblood.
To you, it matters more than me,
more than our daughter,
more than anything in this world.
This is in your bones and flesh—
it can't be changed.
I don't blame you for that.
I don't blame you either
for letting Susu substitute Xiuxiu.
After all, the Fei family
is better off than others.
What I want to say is—
we're done meddling
in the children's affairs.
From now on,
let them find their own way.
I'll have Mrs. Li
make you porridge right away—
millet porridge with brown sugar,
together with boiled eggs…
Two eggs.
No, three eggs.
Didn't you always say,
after bearing three children,
you never got enough postpartum porridge?
This time, you'll have your fill.
Great.
That's great.
Old man...
This life's been so long,
so weary.
Tell me this—
when I die,
how thick a house will you give me?
Why talk about this?
You're not going to die.
Then make mine four inches thick.
Four inches.
Alright, four inches it is.
Old woman,
you slept peacefully last night—
not a single cough.
Rest a while longer.
I'm off to Kuangzi to collect debts.
My mother, Madam Ning of the Guo Clan,
passed away at dawn today!
Her grieving son, Ning Kejin,
announces her departure with sorrow.
Miss Xiuxiu,
please return at once
to keep vigil by Madam's bier.
What's the meaning of this?
There's only one for Xiuxiu—
nothing for Dajiao!
Is Dajiao even still their son-in-law?
How can you nitpick at a time like this?
Hurry up and get ready
to offer condolences!
Quit dawdling—move it!
And don't forget to hang the lanterns!
Brother,
I've been thinking—
how about hiring just one funeral band
and holding the funeral in three days?
Would that work?
Uncle.
we need to hire two funeral bands—
I won't have Mother leaving this house
until she's lain here seven full days.
Seven days?
How will you manage life with that?
You think a lavish funeral  is great?
You think your mother
would've wanted this?
Brother,
a modest funeral is fine,
but it should still be proper
to let my sister-in-law rest in peace.
Alright, alright.
You decide—
we'll do it your way.
Ren Guanxiu—
One bolt of blue mourning cloth.
Chen Jin—
Chen Bi—One bundle of joss paper.
Zhao Dabao—One bundle of joss paper.
Yan Xueren—One bundle of joss paper.
Mourners, commence lamentation!
Mother...
Take incense and make offering!
Present the libation!
Look.
Your son-in-law has arrived.
Er.
Er!
If Ning Xuexiang accepts
this marriage alliance today,
you'll have your pick of fields to tend
from here on out!
Three more mourners.
He is...
What?
He's...
Take three condolence hats.
Wait...
Dajiao,
they don't treat you as a son-in-law.
I don't care.
See?
See that?
Our Dajiao's got spine!
Er,
you're family-by-marriage—
an honored guest!
You should sit at the head table!
Then as the uncle-in-law,
I too deserve that seat.
Yet here I'm cast aside like leftovers!
Are you really
head to the rotating banquet?
Let's feast!
Feast like it's famine tomorrow—
that tightwad Miser Ning will weep
when his larder's bare!
Eat!
The bereaved return gratitude!
It's your turn, Glutton Fei.
You guys go first.
What are you up to?
Hurry up!
Quit dawdling!
Yinzi, come on here.
Listen here—
go tell the master of the house:
We may have the kids wail at the funeral,
and they'll get steamed buns after.
Go now—quick, go!
That's why I say,
Glutton Fei's idea is sharp.
Let none mock another—
hunger speaks for itself.
Mark my words, we mean well.
Just watch:
the young master and mistress
will wail themselves hoarse
within two hours.
I'm just having children weep for them
fulfills filial duty.
Impressive.
Later, you'll need to
put on the mourning garments—
you hear me?
-Let's go home.
-What are you doing?
Still want those steamed buns or not?
Have you no decency left?
Let's go.
Come back here.
Wait!
Tietou.
Where do you think you're going?
We haven't even eaten at the banquet yet!
You think those kowtows were free?
Come! With me, now!
Mourners, commence lamentation!
Cry now!
Cry and you'll get steamed buns.
Master Ning,
Master Ning.
Please accept my deepest condolences.
Let's skip the formalities today—
what's the matter?
Just now I saw
there aren't enough mourners wailing.
I can bring my wife and son
to help wail the lament.
My boy's got strong lungs,
and so do I.
My wife and I
don't need your donkey-braying mourning.
The debt's due date stands—
when the time comes,
you'd better pay in cash.
If no cash,
pay in lands.
Crying here won't earn you anything—
not food, not drink.
Like your mother did,
go wail at the mourning tent.
Then I'll give your dad
a sack of dried sweet potatoes.
What a stubborn little girl!
So this is who you are, Xiuxiu?
you knew your mother longed for you,
yet you
dared to harden your heart and stay away?
Could you not grant her
one final farewell?
Yinzi.
Yinzi!
What happened to
that silver tongue of yours?
Go on—laugh at my father again!
It was my fault. I didn't mean it!
Yin-Yinzi!
Look, I brought you a steamed bun!
It's so good...
Yin-Yinzi!
Keep following me,
and I'll beat you dead—you hear me?
My tongue's wicked—I'll slap it right!
I'll beat it proper!
Yinzi!
Follow me again, and I'll jump from here!
No, please!
Go away!
Yin—
It's Dajiao. Dajiao is here.
Stop.
Rise.
Now this—this is a proper burial offering!
What a fine child!
Such respect!
The bereaved return gratitude!
Keep it low.
Hey, isn't that Dajiao?
Dajiao's actually come!
Look at Dajiao,
playing the dutiful son-in-law!
This whole setup—
it's the full funeral rites
for a daughter and son-in-law!
Where'd you scrape this together?
How much did it bleed you?
Have you lost all sense?
Scraped together
from two funeral supply shops.
You little brat!
They never took him seriously
to begin with—
now he's doubling down
like he matters!
Er!
Let's go to the banquet!
I'm too furious to swallow a bite—
this rage fills me up!
Mourners, commence lamentation!
Take incense and make offering!
Present the libation!
Prostrate in obeisance!
On behalf of Xiuxiu, I, Dajiao, am
kowtowing to you.
May you
find peace
beyond this world soon!
Mother...
Xiuxiu and her husband are
here to bid you farewell.
Mother...
Mother!
Please open your eyes.
Xiuxiu is here to see you off.
Mother.
What are you looking for?
Red paper.
Why do you need that now?
I promised my mother
I'd cut window flowers every New Year,
and bring them back to her.
I see.
I'll get some for you.
Receive the casket.
Mother!
Rest in peace!
My wife, you're so blessed.
Look—
the whole village has come
to send you off.
Be careful.
Are we sending Xiuxiu's mother?
Yes, right.
There's spirit money inside. Take some
Take it.
Come on.
Just take it.
Take it from here.
Madam,
we've come to see you off.
Auntie. We've come to see you off.
Tietou's mother.
Sister-in-law.
Why aren't you with the relatives?
That doesn't matter.
The old man's fuming inside.
Let's give Xiuxiu's mother
a proper send-off.
Does it matter which way we go?
Old ladies, yong ladies,
and young boys should all stay.
Mother!
[Spirit Tablet of the Late Lady Guo
of the Gu Family]
Mother!
Stop.
Mother...
Mother.
Your unfilial daughter
has come to see you, Mother.
Mother.
Mother... won't you open your eyes for me?
Mother...
Mother!
Mother.
Your Xiuxiu has come to see you...
I didn't even get to see you
one last time.
My Xiuxiu...
It's my uselessness
that made you suffer so.
Even in death, I can't close my eyes
thinking of what you endured.
Mother.
I wasn't... defiled by those bandits.
I escaped unharmed.
I only said those things...
to spite Father.
Mother... can you ever forgive me?
Mother.
Xiuxiu.
Xiuxiu, that's enough now.
Don't cry anymore, Xiuxiu.
Come here, Xiuxiu.
-Xiuxiu.
-Mother.
Mother!
Mother! Don't go, Mother!
Come on here, Xiuxiu.
-Raise the casket.
-Don't go!
Xiuxiu, come here.
Mother is gone.
Susu stayed with the Fei family—
that home once filled with laughter,
now...
holds nothing left
to tie me there.
On Mother's seventh-day memorial,
Susu returned to see Father.
She told him of Dajiao's hardships,
begged him
to help me.
Father said,
if I cross this threshold
and acknowledge him as my father again,
he'll agree.
Hit harder. Mind your hands.
You made it!
You're such a quick learner.
Good girl.
This isn't as good as
what you have at home—
those foreign fire-makers (matches).
I'll make Ning Xuexiang see—
even without the Ning family,
I can thrive on my own.
I'll build a life
bright as blooming flowers,
and outshine him at every turn.
The heavens are truly ingenious—
who first discovered
that striking these together
brings forth fire?
Those foreign matches? Useless.
Just a lazy man's shortcut.
I've smoked my whole life—
always trusted this method.
Alright, alright—
stop fussing with it.
The fire's fine,
just wasteful with wood.
Well then...
how do we save firewood?
Teach me please—I'm ready to learn.
Let me teach you.
Bring that firewood here.
Mother.
Dajiao—
knew you'd be back soon.
Come and eat.
Coming. I'm starving.
Old Man,
dinner's ready.
Let's eat first, Father. Stop calculating.