(This program is intended for mature audiences.
It may feature explicit content, violence, and strong language.)
JOY: Late-night chat on the lawn.
FRAME: You can choose two people,
one for Fall In Love and one for One Night Stand.
RUSAMEEKAE: How is it gonna be?
- CRIS: Who?
- RUSAMEEKAE: Who?
JANEYEH: Oh, that's intense!
TIMETHAI: Oh my god.
CRIS: Oh my god.
TIMETHAI: You've just dropped a bomb
on your own house.
CRIS: Oh, that's so intense!
CRIS: Oh, TOD.
RUSAMEEKAE: They could end up
hating each other.
SUNNY: Go kiss the person
you like the most.
CRIS: Here we go again,
what game is this?
NAMNUNG: SUNNY, I choose you.
SUNNY: Come on.
PEANUT: Come on.
CRIS: This is it.
CRIS: You see!
- CRIS: Hey, girl!
- RUSAMEEKAE: Oh my god.
CRIS: How's that?
CRIS: Oops, X-Land!
JANEYEH: Really asleep.
RUSAMEEKAE: KONG is sleeping
in the middle.
(Snuggling)
CRIS: Oh, TOD, oh.
TIMETHAI: What's under the blanket?
(Legs overlapping)
CRIS: Legs overlapping, huh?
CRIS: Oh, here they come.
TIME: Are you ready?
KONG: Ready.
TIME: Got it.
KONG: Are you excited?
TIME: Excited, right?
TIME: You're gonna meet 9 more people.
CRIS: Are you ready?
KONG: I don't know how it's gonna be.
TOD: Welcome.
KONG: Open another world,
open another world.
CRIS: Can't wait to see the reactions
at home from everyone.
TIME: Is it beautiful?
KONG: Very beautiful.
KONG: Beautiful.
RUSAMEEKAE: Oh, I'm excited.
NAMNUNG: Get up.
(Dashing)
RUSAMEEKAE: Oh, SUNNY. Oh wow.
(Excited)
TIME: Come on.
JUNSU: TIME.
SUNNY: Go ahead.
(Excited)
JANEYEH: The first one always.
RUSAMEEKAE: Oh wow.
RUSAMEEKAE: Curiosity, huh?
SUNNY: Hello.
KONG: Hello, hi.
(Looking)
RUSAMEEKAE: Oh, staring a hole in him.
TIME: The new guy!
(Looking)
JANEYEH: Looking really close.
SUNNY: What's your name?
KONG: KONGPOP.
(KONGPOP)
TIME: KONGPOP. POP, POP.
JUNSU: It's KONGPONG, right?
- CRIS: KONGPONG.
- JANEYEH: KONGPONG.
KONG: KONGPOP.
JUNSU: Hello.
ASSE: Hello.
FRAME: Hello.
CHERRY: Hello.
CRIS: Everyone feels it, right?
Everyone feels it the same way.
KONG: Hello.
FRAME: Hey, I'll go fetch MILL.
KONG: And what's your name?
CANDIDATE: SUNNY.
(Posing together, helping introduce)
- SUNNY: Sunny Day. - NAMNUNG: Sunny Day.
CRIS: Just say it to end it.
CRIS: It's awkward.
(Glancing)
KONG: Ah, SUNNY. Okay.
RUSAMEEKAE: Oh, the more I watch,
the more awkward it gets.
JUNSU: They are all with a smile.
It's better there, right?
(Isn't X-Land better than here?)
(Also curious)
(Biting lip)
- JANEYEH: Why biting your lip, bro?
- TIMETHAI: What? - CRIS: Oh, so cute.
JANEYEH: Not the sexy lip bite.
(Fun)
TOD: It's fun.
(Smiling)
JANEYEH: Oh, hahaha.
JUNSU: Oh, hahaha.
RUSAMEEKAE: Almost had a major nosebleed.
TIME: Answering like this?
TOD: It's kinda fun, isn't it?
CRIS: Well, "it's kinda fun", huh?
CRIS: And how do you think
the rest will feel?
(Hot)
TOD: It's hot.
CRIS: Aww, TOD.
KONG: Last night was so much fun.
(JUNSU sits down next to KONG)
KONG: We went for a swim, ate, drank,
and then we all slept together.
RUSAMEEKAE: Here we go!
NAMNUNG: Probably not.
KONG: Ahaha!
- KONG: Indeed.
- CHERRY: Who slept in the middle?
CRIS: "Who slept in the middle?"
(Looking)
CRIS: CHERRY, you're amazing.
JANEYEH: You're really asking that?
CRIS: CHERRY is amazing.
SUNNY: Do you like it?
JANEYEH: "Do you like it?"
TIMETHAI: Why is he making that face?
NAMNUNG: Nah, the last activity after
showering, what's the final activity?
- RUSAMEEKAE: Ooh!
- JANEYEH: Ooh! - CRIS: Ooh!
TIMETHAI: You know too much.
KONG: Well, there's a game under
each pillow, right? There were post-its
KONG: and each
has a mission to complete. Yeah.
- CRIS: Whoa, she knows.
- JANEYEH: TIME thinks he's been caught.
NAMNUNG: Oh my god.
NAMNUNG: Exactly the same.
ASSE: Hey!
TIME: Exactly the same, really?
NAMNUNG: It's the mission
under the pillow.
TIMETHAI: Hey!
(Looking)
RUSAMEEKAE: Alas.
JANEYEH: So intense.
(Looking again)
RUSAMEEKAE: Aww, really feel for SUNNY.
CRIS: But why did she spill it?
RUSAMEEKAE: That was a slip-up.
CHERRY: Really?
KONG: Has anyone been to X-Land yet?
(Looking up)
RUSAMEEKAE: Oh, NAMNUNG.
CRIS: I've got a headache.
(Looking)
PEANUT: His face says it all.
CRIS: His face just dropped.
JANEYEH: Oh!
CRIS: Uh, uh.
SUNNY: MATHEUS and her.
(Smiling)
CRIS: Ooh, TIME.
RUSAMEEKAE: Ouch!
RUSAMEEKAE: What is KONG?
Is he like gasoline?
JANEYEH: Ouch!
KONG: Really?
KONG: And what did you do?
RUSAMEEKAE: Here we go.
(Smiling)
RUSAMEEKAE: Hit the nail on the head.
KONG: Yeah, you can say it.
KONG: Just go ahead and say it.
CRIS: KONG, stop that.
NAMNUNG: Uh.
TIMETHAI: How do you survive like this?
Just act insane.
RUSAMEEKAE: Hahaha!
CRIS: Just wait for you guys to go
to the X-Land and you'll know.
- TIMETHAI: Hahaha!
- JANEYEH: Hahaha!
RUSAMEEKAE: Welcome everyone
to a brand new
RUSAMEEKAE: love reality show
from Thailand,
ALL: Borderless Love, LOVE(X). Dum, dum.
RUSAMEEKAE: Today, we have a new
LOVE(X)PERT joining us. Welcome, PEANUT.
PEANUT: Hello, hello.
(LOVE(X)PERT SPECIAL
PEANUT PEERANAT VEERANIPITKUL)
PEANUT: I must tell everyone that I've
been following since EP1 to EP4.
CRIS: Oh!
PEANUT: Yes, and I feel that I have
a couple that I've shipped myself.
CRIS: Who?
JANEYEH: Who do you like?
PEANUT: SUNNY and NAMNUNG.
TIMETHAI: Sitting together,
you're on the same wavelength.
(Fan No. 1)
RUSAMEEKAE: They're on the same page.
RUSAMEEKAE: From the last episode,
we saw a new member join us: KONG.
CRIS: And before that,
FRAME came in new.
CRIS: These two coming in
really stirred things up.
RUSAMEEKAE: Hmm.
CRIS: It's chaos, what used to be a love
triangle is now a square, then pentagon.
RUSAMEEKAE: It's confusing for everyone.
CRIS: So confusing.
RUSAMEEKAE: Are you curious about it?
RUSAMEEKAE: Let's go have a look.
PEANUT: Okay. Let's go.
SUNNY: Just came to save the day.
MILL: Hello.
KONG: Hello.
KONG: Hello, hello.
(Talkative)
JUNSU: KONGPONG.
MILL: KONGPONG.
MILL: Hello.
JOY: Hello.
(Correcting)
NAMNUNG: KONGPOP.
JOY: It's KONGPOP.
JOY: KONGPONG? Ah, KONGPOP.
JOY: Hello.
KONG: Oh.
KONG: Did we miscommunicate?
KONG: The names are all mixed up.
(Pleased)
JOY: Can I have a hug, please?
CRIS: JOY is going all out friendly!
RUSAMEEKAE: Dear JOY.
CRIS: Dear JOY.
JUNSU: KONGPOP, KONGPOP.
(Chanting)
JUNSU: KONGPOP.
- KONG: KONG, KONG, KONG from "camera"
- JUNSU: KONG, KONG, POP. KONGPOP.
KONG: Yes.
(That's correct)
CRIS: Cute.
RUSAMEEKAE: Is JUNSU
finding out about KONG?
CANDIDATES: Like.
TIME: Where's MATHEUS?
To think of it, where is he?
PEANUT: He's asking about MATHEUS.
NAMNUNG: Probably went to the hospital.
TOD: Really?
- TIME: What's not coming out?
- TOD: Oh my god.
MILL: It doesn't come out.
MATHEUS always gets hit.
MILL: Got pushed down.
JOY: It's all about MATHEUS.
CRIS: Don't ask MATHEUS for the truth,
I'm begging you, TIME.
CANDIDATES: Huh?
(Now, everyone is invited to the beach.)
JANEYEH: It's starting.
(We are about to start a new round
of the shell coin competition.)
SUNNY: Shell coin competition again!
TIMETHAI: Loves playing games.
TOD: Let's go!
JUNSU: To the beach!
TOD: Go. First time playing the game.
KONG: What game is this?
TOD: Ahaha!
(Squeezing shoulder)
CRIS: Oh.
(Stealing a glance)
JANEYEH: Ouch.
PEANUT: His face says it all.
TOD: Is the sand hot?
(Showing concern)
NAMNUNG: Not hot.
(Sneaking a glance)
PEANUT: He doesn't know TOD treats everyone like this.
(Checking himself)
RUSAMEEKAE: Yeah.
TIME: Is it hot?
(Showing concern)
SUNNY: No, not at all.
SUNNY: I can take it off.
(Looking left)
CRIS: He feels a bit hurt, though.
(Looking right)
RUSAMEEKAE: What are you gonna do, KONG?
JANEYEH: Ouch, stuck in the middle.
(Kicking sand for fun)
(Today's shell coin competition
includes two games.)
(Now entering the first game.)
(Catch and hug the ball by the beach.)
TIME: Catch and hug the ball.
(Catch and hug the ball by the beach)
NAMNUNG: Ah, catching the ball.
MILL: What?
TOD: Catch and hug the ball.
(The rule is that both people must throw
the ball up, and turn around once.)
(Turn around and hug)
(Embrace each other to keep the ball trapped between your bodies.)
(If the ball stays in place,)
(Catch the ball with your body)
(you succeed. The couple with the most catches wins.)
KONG: Throw it up, turn around quickly,
and hug to keep the ball between us.
SUNNY: Oh, okay.
JUNSU: Oh.
TIME: By the sea.
JUNSU: Sea.
JUNSU: Yay.
(Pairing up before the competition)
CANDIDATE: Yay.
CANDIDATE: Okay.
(Before getting into choosing pairs,)
(the newcomer has the right
to choose a partner first.)
(Please choose your partner.)
(Have the right to choose a partner first)
CANDIDATES: KONG.
- CANDIDATES: Wow.
- JANEYEH: So strong.
CANDIDATE: KONG.
NAMNUNG: Come on, KONG, go for it!
JANEYEH: I think KONG may pick
a new person other than TIME and TOD.
RUSAMEEKAE: So, will he pick
a woman or a man?
PEANUT: Might be a new guy.
(Aiming)
KONG: Why're you so still?
CRIS: Is it ASSE?
CRIS: CHERRY may hit you.
KONG: Who should I choose?
JANEYEH: Please don't, dear.
RUSAMEEKAE: JUNSU is nervous. He wants
to pair with FRAME from the start.
KONG: I choose JUNSU.
KONG: JUNSU.
CRIS: You're awesome.
CRIS: That's bad.
(Looking immediately)
CRIS: He turned to ask for permission.
RUSAMEEKAE: KONG, don't get involved.
JANEYEH: He doesn't know anything,
he's not wrong.
(Grabbing the arm)
PEANUT: Oh.
JANEYEH: Hey, hey!
(Can't hold back a smile)
CRIS: KONG.
(Squeezing)
JANEYEH: He's checking. Checking.
- PEANUT: FRAME is awkward now.
- CRIS: Oh.
(Successful pairing)
(Hello, hello)
- JUNSU: Hello! - KONG: Hello!
(Tapping)
CRIS: Checking muscles again.
KONG: I feel JUNSU has a good build.
When he talks or something like that,
KONG: he talks in a cute way, so I chose
him as the first pair for the game.
RUSAMEEKAE: Ah.
CRIS: But I still believe that
JUNSU likes FRAME.
RUSAMEEKAE: JUNSU likes FRAME.
(The remaining 9 people will proceed to
the eye-contact round to find partners.)
(Pairing by eye contact)
RUSAMEEKAE: Huh?
(The rule is that)
(one will turn their back to everyone.)
(Anyone who wants to be their partner)
(walks over and gently taps them
on the shoulder from behind.)
(When they turn around,)
(the first person to make eye contact
with them will become a pair.)
RUSAMEEKAE: Who will end up with whom?
MILL: Anyone wants to go first?
RUSAMEEKAE: SUNNY.
SUNNY: I'm going first.
JANEYEH: There you go.
TIME: I'm going...
(The two going out together)
CANDIDATES: Oh.
JANEYEH: That's an intense look.
JOY: Ladies first.
(Stepping back)
CRIS: Well done, JOY.
(The first)
RUSAMEEKAE: JOY wraps it up.
TOD: You can tell
just by the shadow, right?
RUSAMEEKAE: Who's brave enough
to walk over?
JOY: Go over there.
TIME: Close your eyes.
SUNNY: Close the eyes.
(Waiting)
(Observing)
(Stop)
(Walking out)
JANEYEH: That's intense.
(2 people walking out)
JANEYEH: JOY is fond of SUNNY.
CRIS: NAMNUNG will go soon. Let's see.
TIMETHAI: But it depends on
who she turns to first.
(Walking back)
JOY: She's all yours.
CRIS: Why are you speaking?
(Stepping back together)
TIME: No.
(Going back)
TIME: You go ahead.
CRIS: Why saying that?
(Backing off)
RUSAMEEKAE: What's going on with TIME?
(Looking)
TIMETHAI: He's unclear, right?
(Bailing out)
(If you're ready...)
(3,)
(2,)
(1.)
(Nudging)
PEANUT: Is she turning?
RUSAMEEKAE: Oh my!
CRIS: Very good.
(Eye contact and smile)
CRIS: But JOY is really cute.
(Looking around)
TIMETHAI: Turn to look at the guys.
JANEYEH: Oh, that's adorable.
- RUSAMEEKAE: What a dork!
- JANEYEH: Oh, so intense.
SUNNY: Oh, you tapped on both sides?
I was looking for where it was.
(Observing)
(Pair successfully) - RUSAMEEKAE: JOY has
protected SUNNY since the fruit game. - CRIS: Right.
JOY: At first, I passed this to TIME.
JOY: He walked over with me too.
(Looking at TIME)
RUSAMEEKAE: Wow.
MILL: Oh, really?
JOY: There's a guy team already.
- SUNNY: Does it hurt?
- JUNSU: It hurts.
(Next person, please step forward.)
(The second one)
CRIS: FRAME is tied to whom?
(Anticipating) JANEYEH:
So intense, without JUNSU.
(Looking)
- ASSE: Should I go?
- CHERRY: I will go.
(Walking over)
RUSAMEEKAE: CHERRY.
MILL: I think I'm gonna go.
(Walking over)
RUSAMEEKAE: Wow!
JANEYEH: Oh, wow.
CRIS: That's okay. CHERRY
can be with ASSE, right?
(Pair successfully)
MILL: Join the group.
FRAME: I didn't know she was there.
(Sneaking a glance) - FRAME: I don't know.
- CRIS: That's good. JUNSU is happy.
(Next person, please step forward.)
(Raising hand)
(The third one)
CRIS: If TIME doesn't walk over to tap,
CRIS: I'll cry out.
(Sideways glance)
RUSAMEEKAE: Oh, I'm stressed.
CRIS: Me too.
(Anyone who wants to tap NAMNUNG's
shoulder, please stand behind her.)
RUSAMEEKAE: TOD will walk over, right?
(Walking over)
CRIS: Will TIME walk over too?
TIMETHAI: Such an overthinker!
(Walking over)
(2 people walking out)
TIMETHAI: They're even wearing
swapped colors.
RUSAMEEKAE: Yeah, swap outfits.
CRIS: KONG is confused now.
(Staring)
(Staring back)
(Making eye contact)
TIMETHAI: What's up with them?
(If you're ready...)
(3...)
(Thinking)
CRIS: Oh, I will be crazy!
(2...)
RUSAMEEKAE: I can't breathe right now.
(1.)
(Reaching out)
TIMETHAI: Did he touch her?
(Didn't touch)
TIMETHAI: He didn't.
NAMNUNG: Ouch!
(TOD's hand)
- RUSAMEEKAE: Wow!
- PEANUT: He poked her waist.
CRIS: TOD touched her waist. Good job!
CRIS: Good job, TOD!
(TOD's hand)
NAMNUNG: Ouch!
(Turning to TOD)
(Giving a smack)
CRIS: TOD is smart.
CRIS: A round of applause for TOD.
TIME: Is this allowed?
TIMETHAI: This technique is okay.
CRIS: Take note of that.
(Pair successfully)
TIMETHAI: Oh, wow.
CRIS: But he's not the stressful type.
He's all about the good vibes.
JANEYEH: KONG is confused now.
TIME: I'm playing myself.
(Staring)
- FRAME: CHERRY.
- JUNSU: CHERRY, go.
TIME: Go, CHERRY.
FRAME: CHERRY.
(The fourth one) RUSAMEEKAE: ASSE
and CHERRY are too obvious, aren't they?
JANEYEH: No need to let them pick.
JOY: CHERRY, choose wisely, dear.
FRAME: I'm blushing.
JUNSU: Choose TIME.
RUSAMEEKAE: We want TIME
to go touch her, right?
TIME: Go, go.
CRIS: See? TIME said, "Go, go."
JANEYEH: "Go ahead, bro.
I'm heading to the sea now."
(Walking to her)
PEANUT: CHERRY's waiting with a smile.
(Staring)
(Waiting) CRIS: So sweet.
Just get married after this show ends.
RUSAMEEKAE: Wow!
PEANUT: This is like the scene
where the hero proposes to the heroine.
(Smiling)
CRIS: So cute.
CRIS: So sweet.
(Laughing together)
RUSAMEEKAE: A match made in heaven.
(Satisfied)
CRIS: Oh, I'm over the moon.
CRIS: So cute.
(Pair successfully)
RUSAMEEKAE: Others are jealous.
(No partner) CRIS: Now, TIME is alone.
He might get some special privileges.
NAMNUNG: TIME didn't poke...
- NAMNUNG: Didn't poke me.
- TOD: He did.
(TIME is the last one without a partner.)
(You can choose anyone as your partner.)
(Choose anyone to be your partner)
RUSAMEEKAE: Wow!
RUSAMEEKAE: Who is TIME choosing?
CRIS: Choose SUNNY?
(The person you choose
will get coins for two rounds.)
(The person chosen by TIME will get coins)
JUNSU: Wow!
- FRAME: Wow!
- JUNSU: Wow!
(Who will TIME choose as a partner?)
TIMETHAI: NAMNUNG, go.
JANEYEH: Choose SUNNY.
CRIS: Plot twist.
Turns out he chooses KONG.
JANEYEH: If so,
KONG would be too popular.
TIME: I choose SUNNY.
JANEYEH: If I'd bought a lottery ticket,
I'd be rich now.
TIME: I choose SUNNY.
(Pair successfully)
RUSAMEEKAE: Oh, my God!
CRIS: He's shocked.
(Peeking)
CRIS: Getting stressed?
JANEYEH: NAMNUNG's confused.
NAMNUNG: Are we starting first?
SUNNY: Watch the demonstration first.
(Standing beside SUNNY)
JANEYEH: Oh, my!
NAMNUNG: Ah, they had you stand together
because you're paired up.
(Now, both teams, please bring out the ball
and take positions for the competition.)
(The first pair is about
to start playing)
TIMETHAI: She really
wants to play game.
TIMETHAI: I want to play game!
TIME: You've got this!
(First round: KONG, JUNSU VS SUNNY, JOY)
FRAME: Do your best!
TOD: KONG, you've got this!
KONG: Haha.
JUNSU: Just a moment.
CRIS: Just a moment. Huh?
PEANUT: JUNSU, what are you doing?
JUNSU: It's huge.
JANEYEH: Oh.
TOD: Wow!
FRAME: Wow!
(Staring)
CRIS: What did KONG do to deserve this?
- NAMNUNG: Oppa!
- FRAME: Oppa!
FRAME: Oppa!
CRIS: You're only staring
at his muscles, girls.
JUNSU: Let's go!
JOY: Okay, arms together.
JOY: You can do it.
(Locking eyes and smiling) - JANEYEH: Wow,
look at JOY's gaze. - CRIS: Wow, JOY.
SUNNY: You can do it.
JOY: I trust you.
(Touching lightly) - RUSAMEEKAE: JOY!
- LOVE(X)PERT: Oh, wow, JOY!
JANEYEH: I feel sorry for NAMNUNG.
SUNNY: Oh, right, I've never
teamed up with JOY in any game.
Not sure what she thinks about it,
but I usually blush more with women than with men.
CRIS: Wow! She's shy!
PEANUT: She has a feeling for her.
CRIS: NAMNUNG's got a rival now.
(If you're ready...)
JUNSU: Fast, fast, okay?
(3...)
TIMETHAI: Seems like it's pretty tough.
(2,)
(1.)
TIMETHAI: Hey, three of them...
(JOY fell down)
RUSAMEEKAE: Wow!
(No points)
RUSAMEEKAE: Oops, this is tough.
(Can they catch the ball?)
CRIS: Wow, this game is tough.
(The ball is falling)
(Sliding on his knees)
CRIS: Hey! The pose!
(Holding the ball)
TIMETHAI: It's safe!
CRIS: This pose is very dangerous.
TIMETHAI: Not touching the ball at all.
RUSAMEEKAE: Not touching
the ball at all.
JANEYEH: This is too much.
(Skin-to-skin)
TIMETHAI: Did KONG get
a special privilege or something?
CRIS: Yeah, right. Did KONG get
JUNSU: We got it!
(Scored one point)
LOVE(X)PERT: They did it weirdly.
JANEYEH: So happy.
PEANUT: KONG is having
a sweet dream today.
TIMETHAI: Having a sweet dream
since yesterday.
CRIS: FRAME is confused.
(Next pair, please.)
RUSAMEEKAE: How's this pair? ASSE.
PEANUT: All that's left for this pair
is to buy the ring.
JOY: Go and try again.
- JOY: You can do it.
- SUNNY: Oh, is it us again?
(Second round:
TIME, SUNNY VS CHERRY, ASSE)
TIME: Do you wanna rest first?
(Attentive)
SUNNY: I'm fine. Okay.
RUSAMEEKAE: Oops.
CRIS: When paired with JOY,
it's one thing.
CRIS: Once paired with TIME,
CRIS: it becomes another thing.
CHERRY: You throw.
ASSE: Okay.
TIMETHAI: Oh, look at this pair
and that pair.
ASSE: Just a moment.
CHERRY: Mhm.
TIMETHAI: So different.
The sea is too romantic now.
MILL: The music, cue!
CRIS: MILL said, "The music, cue!"
JUNSU: ASSE!
JOY: Do your best!
JUNSU: Do your best!
JOY: Sorry, sorry.
CRIS: So cute.
TIME: Don't get it, though.
SUNNY: Okay, I won't.
SUNNY: I'll just stay still
and wait to hug you.
TIME: Okay.
PEANUT: "I'll just stay still
and wait to hug you."
JANEYEH: Mother is mothering.
SUNNY: I'll just stay still
and wait to hug you.
TIME: Okay.
PEANUT: Wow, that's so bold!
- TIME: Oh, this is our first game together.
Good luck. - SUNNY: Yeah. Crazy.
TIME: Good luck.
(Reaching out a hand)
TIMETHAI: Hehe.
(Holding hands)
JANEYEH: Reaching out a hand.
(If you're ready...)
(Start.)
CRIS: She loves playing games
and has to win.
(Touching each other) - PEANUT: Oh.
- LOVE(X)PERT: Oh, wow.
(Intimately)
RUSAMEEKAE: It's like shooting
a pre-wedding.
(Hugging)
(Hugging tightly)
CRIS: Oh, so cute!
(Got one point)
RUSAMEEKAE: Whoever breaks
this couple up
RUSAMEEKAE: is really bad.
RUSAMEEKAE: It's sinful.
JANEYEH: You'll be cursed.
JANEYEH: They're just using the game
as an excuse to hug.
(Hugging tightly)
RUSAMEEKAE: Oh, SUNNY enjoys it.
(Hugging)
TOD: What?
CRIS: What are you shy about?
TIME: Oh, my God.
SUNNY: It was fun, but I was a bit shy.
TIMETHAI: Oh, you're being shy, SUNNY?
SUNNY: Is that allowed?
CRIS: Is that allowed?
TIME: I don't know. I couldn't get.
TIME: Is that allowed?
(Caught the ball with hands, No points)
RUSAMEEKAE: No points.
TIME: Okay, can I try again?
PEANUT: Asking for one more try, huh?
- JUNSU: No.
- FRAME: No way.
JUNSU: No hugging allowed.
(Second round results: CHERRY, ASSE:
One point; TIME, SUNNY: Zero points)
TIME: Okay.
CRIS: SUNNY didn't score at all
in two rounds.
(Second round results: CHERRY, ASSE:
One point; TIME, SUNNY: Zero points)
CRIS: You did a good job.
(Third round: FRAME, MILL
VS NAMNUNG, TOD) CRIS: Oh, here it comes.
(If you're ready...)
(Start.)
CRIS: This game is tough.
JUNSU: Go for it!
(The ball is falling)
RUSAMEEKAE: Why am I holding my breath?
I'm holding my breath right now.
(Caught the ball)
CRIS: Oh, they caught it!
RUSAMEEKAE: Oh, they caught it!
SUNNY: They caught it.
(Got one point)
RUSAMEEKAE: Awesome.
CRIS: They're really cute.
CRIS: But they're literally
just friends.
- JUNSU: That's not allowed.
- TIME: Why?
RUSAMEEKAE: Why is that?
TIME: Have to spin.
ASSE: TOD.
CRIS: TOD has to spin.
TOD: One more?
(Didn't spin)
(Spinning gracefully)
JANEYEH: She's spinning so elegantly.
(Throwing the ball coolly)
JANEYEH: Focus on the throw.
(Rushing to catch)
- TIMETHAI: Catch it with chest muscles.
- JANEYEH: With chest muscles, haha.
(So happy)
(But it can't escape JUNSU's eyes)
- JUNSU: That doesn't count. - TIME: Not allowed.
JUNSU: That doesn't count!
(No points)
TOD: Okay, sorry.
(They still don't understand the rules)
TOD: Let's do it again.
TOD: Let's do it again. I know now
I can't throw too high.
CRIS: Throw it just as high, TOD.
(If you're ready...)
RUSAMEEKAE: These two are
definitely great.
(Moving perfectly in sync)
- JUNSU: Oh, wow.
- TIME: Oh, wow.
JANEYEH: Oh, the ball hit her!
(Caught the ball)
TIME: Nice catch.
CRIS: They're screaming
at the same time.
(Got two points)
CRIS: Good job, you two won!
- TIME: This counts.
- JUNSU: This counts.
JUNSU: This counts.
- TIME: That doesn't count.
- JUNSU: That doesn't count. What's that?
TOD: Why?
- NAMNUNG: What?
- TOD: Why?
(Why doesn't that count?)
CRIS: That doesn't count either?
(Here's the answer why that doesn't count)
CRIS: Why again?
(Spinning gracefully one more time)
(Showing the cool spin one more time)
(Caught the ball with hands)
RUSAMEEKAE: Oh, she caught with hands.
- TIME: That's not allowed.
- JUNSU: That's not allowed.
(Can't escape JUNSU's eyes)
TIME: It's not allowed.
(Can't escape eyes of JUNSU and TIME)
JUNSU: That doesn't count.
TOD: Please.
TOD: Please,
can't I just have one shell coin?
TOD: Can't I just have one shell coin?
(TOD is pleading)
(Laughing happily)
CRIS: JUNSU is funny.
TOD: Please.
TOD: Can I?
JANEYEH: What are you doing, TOD?
NAMNUNG: You, listen!
(Me?)
NAMNUNG: Listen!
NAMNUNG: Okay?
JUNSU: No need to say.
NAMNUNG: You guys.
NAMNUNG: How did you handle
the first ball earlier?
JUNSU: Okay,
you can have one shell coin.
- JANEYEH: Oh, she really hit him.
- NAMNUNG: Huh?
- RUSAMEEKAE: Does she have something on her mind?
- NAMNUNG: Stop.
(Gave in)
- TIME: You can have one shell coin. - NAMNUNG: What?
(Round three results: MILL and FRAME, two points
NAMNUNG and TOD, one point)
JANEYEH: That is a long-held feeling
coming out.
RUSAMEEKAE: It's not related to
the game, is it?
JANEYEH: It's totally not related to
the game.
(Round three results: MILL and FRAME, two points,
NAMNUNG and TOD, one point)
(Congratulations to MILL and FRAME)
(for receiving the most balls)
TIMETHAI: But these two are
really amazing.
CANDIDATES: Share some with us.
(Results of the beach ball game:
MILL and FRAME, two points, CHERRY and ASSE, one point)
(NAMNUNG and TOD, one point, KONG and JUNSU, one point,
TIME and SUNNY zero points, JOY and SUNNY zero points)
RUSAMEEKAE: We were all stunned
by that beach ball game.
RUSAMEEKAE: It was so fun.
CRIS: Is there another game?
RUSAMEEKAE: It's even more intense.
Do you know what it's called?
CRIS: What game?
(Rolling Love on the Beach)
RUSAMEEKAE: The Rolling Love on the Beach game.
JANEYEH: Rolling.
RUSAMEEKAE: We've started
to understand the show now.
RUSAMEEKAE: Seems like
they're pairing up again.
CRIS: Oh, they have to pair up again.
RUSAMEEKAE: Let's watch together how intense
the Rolling Love on the Beach game will be.
(Next up is the second game of today,)
(Rolling Love on the Beach.)
(Rolling Love on the Beach)
CRIS: How do they roll?
(In the last round,
MILL and FRAME were the winners.)
(Therefore, they get the privilege
to pick their partners first.)
- RUSAMEEKAE: Wow.
- PEANUT: Oh!
(Others can freely choose
their partners.)
(But there's an important rule.)
(You must not pair with one
from the last round.)
(Can't choose the same person)
JANEYEH: Oh, no.
CRIS: Let's start with the unlucky ones.
CRIS: ASSE and CHERRY.
RUSAMEEKAE: Why?
CRIS: Next is TIME,
who wants to get to know SUNNY better.
PEANUT: They've already paired up.
RUSAMEEKAE: At this moment,
NAMNUNG is like...
JANEYEH: It's my time.
CRIS: It's time.
TIMETHAI: How about KONGPOP
and TOD this time?
- PEANUT: Oops.
- RUSAMEEKAE: Oops.
CRIS: You're really good at this.
RUSAMEEKAE: Let's see
who is paired with whom.
NAMNUNG: TOD.
FRAME: So, we must not pair up?
(Now, let's have our winners,
MILL and FRAME, choose their partners.)
RUSAMEEKAE: JUNSU is already
waiting for FRAME.
FRAME: JUNSU.
RUSAMEEKAE: She chose so quickly,
without a thought.
JANEYEH: Totally awesome.
(Peeking)
MILL: SUNNY.
CRIS: SUNNY!
(Peeking)
JANEYEH: Hey, TIME!
TIMETHAI: But TIME can't choose anyway.
TIMETHAI: Wow.
CRIS: JOY chose TIME.
CRIS: NAMNUNG wasn't quick enough.
CRIS: And now, who is TOD with?
- NAMNUNG: Oh, are they paired already?
- ASSE: Oh.
CRIS: Oh, there are three people left,
how do they do?
PEANUT: Oh, TOD and CHERRY.
CRIS: And who is paired with ASSE?
(No pair)
(ASSE, who has no pair, can freely choose a partner)
RUSAMEEKAE: Hey.
(Who will ASSE choose?)
PEANUT: Don't harm yourself, ASSE.
CRIS: CHERRY is looking at him.
(Praying)
RUSAMEEKAE: JUNSU, maybe?
ASSE: I choose JUNSU.
(Excited)
RUSAMEEKAE: I thought so.
RUSAMEEKAE: Look at CHERRY.
(Following CHERRY)
CRIS: ASSE, you're good.
JUNSU: Guys.
CRIS: JUNSU looks very happy today.
(Rolling Love on the Beach.)
(Two players must hug tightly.)
(Then roll along the path
to grab the flag.)
(Fight for the flag)
(The team who takes the least time)
(will be the winner)
(and will receive the most shell coins.)
(Now, let's have the first team
onto the field.)
- CHERRY: You can go first, it's okay.
- TOD: Alright.
- CHERRY: I'll go first.
- MILL: Okay.
TIMETHAI: They'll compete
against each other first.
(Staring)
JUNSU: ASSE, let's go.
(Going together)
- JUNSU: Let's go. - ASSE: Okay.
(Sneaking a peek)
(Checking)
CRIS: Did he go ask for permission?
JUNSU: Okay.
ASSE: Me?
JUNSU: Me?
ASSE: Okay.
CRIS: Is he lying down?
(Lying down quickly)
RUSAMEEKAE: Oh, I really want to play this game.
JUNSU: Hurry up!
ASSE: Okay, okay.
LOVE(X)PERTS: Go ahead.
ASSE: How do I lie down? Like this?
(Hugging tightly)
CRIS: That's too much.
CRIS: His butt is sticking way out.
I can't stand that.
TIMETHAI: No, they will bump
into each other.
JOY: That's weird, TOD!
(Lifting the waist)
(Checking)
CRIS: ASSE!
CRIS: TOD has naturally
charming vibe.
JOY: TOD!
JOY: That's weird!
RUSAMEEKAE: It upsets JOY.
PEANUT: Looks heartbroken.
(Sad)
TOD: ASSE turns away.
(If you're ready...)
(Three.)
(Two.)
(One.)
(Start)
CANDIDATE: Hey!
(Start early)
- CRIS: Just turn. - TOD: Go.
TIME: He started early.
LOVE(X)PERT: CHERRY, oh dear.
(Try to protect her)
LOVE(X)PERT: He is trying to protect her,
so she doesn't get hurt too much.
(Supporting her with one hand)
CRIS: TOD is quite a gentleman.
(Leading a little)
CRIS: This pair is so close.
I'm confused.
(Faces are close together)
JANEYEH: Oh, he sniffed his ear once.
(Holding tight)
(Caught up in time)
TIME: Be careful!
SUNNY: Heads up!
(Hit a bump at the same time)
(Swing upward)
CRIS: TOD is too strong.
CRIS: TOD just carried CHERRY!
SUNNY: I think
the most impressive person is TOD.
SUNNY: His arms are already huge, right?
He's protecting her, rolling along.
(They're almost at the finish line.)
CANDIDATE: Hurry up!
CRIS: Oh, TOD!
CRIS: ASSE.
CRIS: They arrived almost
at the same time.
(They arrived almost at the same time.)
CRIS: Really good!
TIME: He's really fast!
MILL: Very close.
- SUNNY: But I was so scared.
- MILL: Yes.
(CHERRY praises ASSE)
CHERRY: So good!
PEANUT: Hurry up
and go compliment the team member.
FRAME: Are you okay?
JUNSU: Not okay.
- ASSE: Huh?
- JUNSU: Not okay.
ASSE: I'm okay.
JUNSU: No, you're not.
ASSE: Yes, I am.
JUNSU: Can I cheer for you then?
ASSE: No, you can't.
- ASSE: You can't let go.
- JUNSU: I know.
- ASSE: I choose you.
CRIS: JUNSU is having so much fun today.
(Next pair, please come
to your positions.)
RUSAMEEKAE: Here they come.
MILL: Which side do you want?
SUNNY: How about over there?
MILL: Okay.
JANEYEH: The ladies might be faster.
RUSAMEEKAE: Because they are lighter.
PEANUT: Yeah, a light pair.
TIMETHAI: Here we go again.
MILL: Oh, it's tough.
- SUNNY: Come on, I'll be on top.
- MILL: Okay.
RUSAMEEKAE: SUNNY, you're so good.
FRAME: I have to stay underneath, right?
MILL: Oh!
MILL: Oh, it's tough.
(Move closer)
JANEYEH: Very beautiful.
JANEYEH: NAMNUNG.
CRIS: JOY and TIME are confused.
SUNNY: Hold on a second.
MILL: What position?
(Being close)
- SUNNY: This position? - MILL: Okay.
CRIS: I love it.
PEANUT: MILL looks like
she really loves it.
TIMETHAI: Not just MILL,
everyone loves it.
JANEYEH: Oh my God.
TIMETHAI: TIME and JOY
are totally confused now.
CRIS: They are confused.
(Avoiding eye contact.)
JOY: JUNSU, you go next.
TIME: JUNSU, what are you waiting for?
JOY: What are you waiting for?
- JOY: What are you waiting for?
- TIME: What are you waiting for?
CANDIDATE: What are you waiting for?
(Get in position)
JUNSU: Is this okay?
CRIS: You have to take your shirt off.
It'll get caught.
(Let me be shy for a second)
JUNSU: Just a moment.
(So cute)
CRIS: So cute.
JUNSU: Just a moment, okay.
JUNSU: Let's go.
(Getting close)
JANEYEH: So intense.
(Holding onto the shoulder)
RUSAMEEKAE: This couple, yes! Come on!
PEANUT: Just go for it.
FRAME: Are you fine?
JUNSU: Okay.
FRAME: Go on then, okay.
RUSAMEEKAE: They look a bit stunned.
RUSAMEEKAE: But this is actually
a surprise for KONG,
RUSAMEEKAE: because he just came here.
CRIS: Oh, right,
because KONG didn't know.
RUSAMEEKAE: Who, what, how?
RUSAMEEKAE: One, two, three,
four... all that.
RUSAMEEKAE: So for KONG,
there might be...
CRIS: Start again.
(Start)
JANEYEH: Go, go.
(Starting together)
LOVE(X)PERT: Go again, faster.
RUSAMEEKAE: How do you even
roll like this? JUNSU.
PEANUT: I'm cheering for
the little lovebirds!
(Holding tight)
PEANUT: Hold tight.
JANEYEH: KONG is super stressed.
JUNSU: When I have to roll around with
FRAME in a game,
JUNSU: I just think
JUNSU: I'm having fun and I'm happy.
(I'm satisfied)
RUSAMEEKAE: SUNNY's the one
doing all the work!
CRIS: They're flinging each other around
honestly, amazing.
JANEYEH: SUNNY is so determined.
(Protecting mode)
LOVE(X)PERT: What the heck?
RUSAMEEKAE: JOY is breathing hard.
CRIS: TIME is just standing there
and confused.
(Almost at the finish line)
TIME: JUNSU, hurry up.
CHERRY: No, no, go again.
NAMNUNG: Go again.
CANDIDATE: Faster, faster.
CHERRY: Pull!
CANDIDATE: JUNSU, Go!
TIMETHAI: Let SUNNY win.
CHERRY: Pull!
CRIS: Who won?
RUSAMEEKAE: Who is it?
RUSAMEEKAE: Was it SUNNY?
CANDIDATE: It was JUNSU.
(Raise the flag at 16 seconds)
RUSAMEEKAE: Oh, SUNNY.
(17 seconds)
JUNSU: Does it hurt?
JUNSU: It's okay.
JUNSU: I think I won.
JUNSU: But it's not
the most important thing.
JUNSU: The most important thing
is with FRAME.
JUNSU: We played and we were happy.
TIMETHAI: This pair just overtook
ASSE and CHERRY.
CRIS: KONG has to hug
with NAMNUNG and TIME.
MILL: Ouch.
MILL: It's so red.
FRAME: So good!
RUSAMEEKAE: They're crossing arms now!
RUSAMEEKAE: And he already announced...
CRIS: Mine.
(Even sweeter)
(Please welcome the last pair
to take their positions.)
TIME: Let's take this side.
CRIS: TIME and JOY.
TOD: Fighting!
TIMETHAI: Oh, NAMNUNG
is competing too!
(Glancing)
CRIS: NAMNUNG, keep fighting.
TIME: Good luck.
(Touch)
CRIS: TIME secretly touched, did you see?
CRIS: It's so sad, isn't it?
RUSAMEEKAE: Those two are already tense
with each other.
TIMETHAI: The more you love,
the more you hate.
JANEYEH: True.
KONG: Take this one?
KONG: Won't it get wet?
NAMNUNG: Turn your feet outward.
NAMNUNG: Head goes here.
CRIS: NAMNUNG is leading.
KONG: Right?
(Secretly watching)
CRIS: Turned to look.
TIME: Come on.
(Ouch)
(I feel that pain)
TIMETHAI: I can't watch this.
JANEYEH: Is JOY messing with him?
(Ouch)
LOVE(X)PERT: JOY.
TIME: Emergency, please.
(Looking)
CANDIDATE: JOY.
JUNSU: JOY is having the best time.
TIMETHAI: He's dead
(Ready)
(Go)
JANEYEH: They're struggling so much.
TIMETHAI: But they look
kinda fast though.
RUSAMEEKAE: SUNNY is watching
with admiration.
(Going all out)
JANEYEH: NAMNUNG looks really strong.
LOVE(X)PERT: NAMNUNG is fighting hard.
CANDIDATE: Oh, be careful.
CANDIDATE: Oh, hold on.
FRAME: Faster, NAMNUNG, faster!
MILL: No, no, and JOY is like...
(Overtaking successfully)
CANDIDATE: Whoa.
RUSAMEEKAE: Girl power,
female friends power!
CANDIDATE: Wow.
(Watching)
TOD: Pull, pull!
CRIS: She must fight. Go!
(Raise the flag first)
JANEYEH: So strong.
(15 seconds)
RUSAMEEKAE: Oh, really fast.
RUSAMEEKAE: A real fighter.
(Looking)
(19 seconds)
MILL: Very good!
TIME: You okay?
TIMETHAI: They look like they like each other,
but both have huge egos.
TIME: How did you do it?
NAMNUNG: Does it hurt?
KONG: Doesn't hurt.
RUSAMEEKAE: No one cares, huh.
(CHERRY TOD 12 seconds 60 coins
ASSE JUNSU 13 seconds 50 coins)
(NAMNUNG KONG 15 seconds 40 coins
MILL SUNNY 16 seconds 30 coins)
(JUNSU FRAME 17 seconds 20 coins
TIME JOY 19 seconds 10 coins)
RUSAMEEKAE: The first place goes to
CHERRY and TOD.
RUSAMEEKAE: And last place,
it's TIME and JOY.
TIMETHAI: TIME's game skills really dropped,
early episodes he was brutal.
RUSAMEEKAE: True,
but your partner matters too.
TIMETHAI: JOY and TIME,
her knee hit his crotch once...
TIMETHAI: Ouch.
TIMETHAI: Hey, but SUNNY and MILL
were okay.
TIMETHAI: SUNNY just
wanted to win so bad.
JANEYEH: Total fighter blood.
(Total fighter blood)
JANEYEH: She wants to win every single day.
RUSAMEEKAE: But the one showing symptoms
the most is probably TIME and NAMNUNG.
RUSAMEEKAE: It's not like
they're happy about winning,
RUSAMEEKAE: there's tension there.
PEANUT: Psychological warfare.
TIMETHAI: They like each other,
but both have egos.
JANEYEH: Yes.
RUSAMEEKAE: Yes, but the next
intense moment is coming.
(Night Talk Arena)
RUSAMEEKAE: There's still a Night Talk Arena tonight.
(What is it)
JANEYEH: This...
RUSAMEEKAE: Everyone has to answer a question
they've never told anyone before.
RUSAMEEKAE: And there's
a punishment too.
CRIS: There's punishment too?
RUSAMEEKAE: If you won't answer,
you drink one glass as punishment.
TIMETHAI: If it were me,
I'd fake it like this.
(Pretending to be drunk to avoid problems)
TIMETHAI: Drunk.
PEANUT: Crazy indeed.
RUSAMEEKAE: So brutal.
RUSAMEEKAE: Let's go see how
this game turns out.
CANDIDATE: Hello.
CANDIDATE: Does it hurt?
CANDIDATE: Oh, MATHEUS.
RUSAMEEKAE: MATHEUS is back.
RUSAMEEKAE: Welcome back, MATHEUS.
CANDIDATE: Wow.
CANDIDATE: Very beautiful.
(MATHEUS returns from the hospital)
CANDIDATE: Wow!
CANDIDATE: so beautiful!
JANEYEH: The tea is so delicious.
RUSAMEEKAE: Are there two flavors?
JANEYEH: Yes, there are two flavors.
JANEYEH: Lemon calamansi
and osmanthus-scented tea.
RUSAMEEKAE: Oh, I think...
RUSAMEEKAE: Drink it cold
when it's hot in Samui, it's so good.
JANEYEH: And it's fun
to chat with friends too.
MILL: Ah.
(Mission card)
CANDIDATE: There's also a mission card.
JOY: Night Talk Arena.
JOY: Time-Bomb Questions Night.
JOY: Everyone takes turns drawing slips
(Time-Bomb Questions Night)
JOY: from the random box, one by one.
(Everyone takes turns drawing a question card,)
JOY: If you draw a question,
(then chooses one person to answer or do what it says.)
JOY: you must read it and do it.
(If the other person refuses to answer or do it,
they have to drink one glass as a punishment.)
CANDIDATE: I'm stressed already,
seriously.
JUNSU: Good job.
CANDIDATE: Let's start.
CRIS: Let's start.
SUNNY: Three players will take turns coming
to stand next to you while you keep your eyes closed.
SUNNY: You have to smell them.
SUNNY: their body scent and guess who it is.
(After you close your eyes, three players
will take turns walking up to stand next to you.)
(You're not allowed to open your eyes.
You have to use your sense of smell and guess who it is.)
(Standing up) RUSAMEEKAE: Now it's exciting
to see who's going to stand up.
CRIS: One for TIME.
CRIS: One for MATHEUS.
CRIS: One for JOY.
- NAMNUNG: Face that way!
- TOD: Close your eyes too.
SUNNY: When you get there,
tell me so I can bring my nose in.
(Whispering the plan)
(JOY stands up first)
JANEYEH: JOY.
(NAMNUNG goes along)
CRIS: Oops, here it is.
CRIS: NAMNUNG is going with her too.
CRIS: NAMNUNG, SUNNY, too!
CRIS: MATHEUS goes.
(MATHEUS is the third)
TIMETHAI: You're slow.
RUSAMEEKAE: Oops.
JANEYEH: TIME is slow, see?
TIMETHAI: You can't be
slow in this game.
PEANUT: MATHEUS's eyes are sparkling.
RUSAMEEKAE: Hmm,
he's got his target already.
CANDIDATE: Ready yet?
CANDIDATE:
Okay, the first person goes in.
CANDIDATE: First person goes in...
(Walking forward)
CANDIDATE: Where are you?
RUSAMEEKAE: Oops.
CANDIDATE: Come a little closer.
RUSAMEEKAE: He seems interested in
SUNNY, huh.
PEANUT: Yes.
RUSAMEEKAE: I'm excited already.
CRIS: MATHEUS must be
wearing tons of perfume.
CRIS: TIME is slow.
CANDIDATE: That's enough, close enough.
SUNNY: MATHEUS.
(SUNNY guessed right, It's MATHEUS)
CANDIDATE: One glass for MATHEUS.
MATHEUS: Very good.
SUNNY: Yeah.
CRIS: But MATHEUS was shocked because
- CRIS: Best kiss ever.
- JANEYEH: The best kiss ever!
SUNNY: Okay, who?
(switch spots.)
RUSAMEEKAE: They're in the same room,
you know.
JANEYEH: But NAMNUNG said she's been interested
in SUNNY for a long time, since the very beginning.
PEANUT: Yes.
CANDIDATE: Ready?
(Just a light touch)
RUSAMEEKAE: Oh, just touch lightly.
(Following)
CRIS: Aww, this couple is cute.
CRIS: Even if nobody ships them,
we can ship them ourselves!
JANEYEH: So cute!
JANEYEH: Oh my.
TIME: Is that even possible?
It's too hard.
(She lunged in so suddenly)
RUSAMEEKAE: Will she remember?
CRIS: What's wrong with TIME?
PEANUT: And MATHEUS's face just now...
SUNNY: Ah, NAMNUNG.
CRIS: NAMNUNG, how did she know?
(SUNNY guessed right, it's NAMNUNG)
PEANUT: Wow, she really buried her face in just now.
CHERRY: Well, they're roommates.
TOD: They're together every day.
CRIS: Cute, right? SUNNY.
(Third person JOY) CRIS: JOY probably won't
be easy she's not that close with her.
(Come closer)
JANEYEH: JOY,
she comes in and just offers it,
(Walks straight in)
(Even closer)
RUSAMEEKAE: Sis JOY!
CRIS: Sis JOY has charm though,
kinda that vibe.
(Backing off)
JANEYEH: SUNNY is really aggressive.
PEANUT: SUNNY is here to play and to win.
I'm gonna smell till I get it.
JANEYEH: Don't run away, stay still.
CRIS: MILL said it.
CRIS: She's confused.
JANEYEH: Smelling that much...
CRIS: SUNNY is a bit too much, no?
JANEYEH: I like it.
SUNNY: JOY.
(SUNNY guessed right, it's JOY)
CRIS: How did she know?
SUNNY: I can recognize people by smell.
JOY: SUNNY made my heart race so much.
JOY: Because SUNNY is very cute
and charming.
RUSAMEEKAE: So the fact
she hates letters to SUNNY means...
JANEYEH: Yes.
CRIS: Yeah, since the first episode,
she's liked SUNNY from the start.
TOD: TIME, drink for JOY a bit.
SUNNY: I'll drink for you!
(SUNNY drinks for JOY)
JANEYEH: Perfect.
JANEYEH: This is it.
TIMETHAI: Play it yourself,
drink it yourself.
TIMETHAI: real gangster.
CRIS: Iconic, iconic.
CRIS: Look, the guys are all fainting.
TIMETHAI: Honestly,
the guys can't beat SUNNY.
CRIS: What about TOD?
SUNNY: Don't secretly read it first!
TOD: I don't see anything.
- MILL: The other side
- NAMNUNG: Hey, the other side.
(You're holding it upside down.)
NAMNUNG: Ugh, such an old-person joke.
RUSAMEEKAE: An old-person joke.
NAMNUNG: Just kidding.
JANEYEH: Too late to say just kidding.
TOD: Please choose one person
to answer this question.
(Please choose one person to answer this question:
In your past love experiences,)
(what is the thing you regret doing the most?)
TOD: In your past love experiences,
TOD: what is the thing
you regret doing the most?
TOD: Alright, I can choose now.
PEANUT: KONGPOP.
CRIS: KONGPOP is totally hoping for TOD.
TOD: Okay.
TOD: MILL.
MILL: I knew it.
(TOD chooses MILL to answer the question)
CRIS: Yeah, but I don't really know MILL.
I want to get to know MILL.
PEANUT: Disappointed.
MILL: Oh, disappointed and regret, huh?
MILL: Like, the biggest regret.
JOY: Even mistakes can be lessons,
anything in life.
MILL: Then it's probably...
my ex cheating.
MILL: Oof, what if I say it
and I start crying?
- JOY: It's okay.
- CHERRY: It's alright.
MILL: My ex cheated.
RUSAMEEKAE: TOD feels guilty now.
MILL: Like...
(Voice trembling)
(scratching her arm)
MILL: Three times.
CANDIDATE: Oh my god.
CANDIDATE: Oh.
NAMNUNG: Three?
TOD: You forgave three times.
No more after that?
TOD: Oh my god.
TOD: Has it been a long time?
MILL: Over a year ago.
TOD: And what was the reason
for forgiving him the first time?
MILL: I just thought
it wouldn't happen again.
TOD: But he didn't see it
as an important opportunity.
TOD: He did it again
the second time, right?
(Nods)
TOD: And the last time, what made you
decide not to take it anymore?
MILL: It was many times already,
he probably won't change.
JANEYEH: Oh, she's carrying wounds.
CRIS: If he can cheat so many times,
it's not a mistake. He doesn't love you.
JANEYEH: That's true.
SUNNY: You're very brave.
You've walked away from it.
RUSAMEEKAE: SUNNY,
you're very brave, dear.
TOD: Stay strong, be strong.
TOD: But I ended up
asking a question that
TOD: was painful for her, and it
TOD: made her cry.
TOD: I shouldn't have asked MILL.
I should've asked someone else.
PEANUT: But he feels guilty.
RUSAMEEKAE: If we look at it
from another angle,
RUSAMEEKAE: sometimes
speaking out like this...
JANEYEH: Is also good.
RUSAMEEKAE: It might feel like
RUSAMEEKAE: we accept and dare
to speak out, to acknowledge it.
TOD: I'm very satisfied
with MILL's response.
TOD: Then I'll drink myself.
(Smiles)
RUSAMEEKAE: Okay.
CANDIDATE: One, two, three.
MILL: Why are your hands
shaking like that?
TOD: I hope you find
TOD: someone better.
CRIS: Oh, look, MILLTOD?
CRIS: Are we getting MILLTOD?
RUSAMEEKAE: Oh,
but don't forget KONGPOP.
CRIS: Right, TOD was very charming
when he was with KONGPOP.
JOY: I got it.
- CANDIDATE: JOY?
- JOY: No.
CHERRY: Is it blank paper?
JOY: No, no.
(You can ask any question to anyone or have someone do anything)
TIME: Yay, it's getting more fun.
RUSAMEEKAE: You can ask any question
to anyone or have someone
RUSAMEEKAE: do anything.
JANEYEH: Wow.
TIMETHAI: Blank paper is the scariest.
JANEYEH: Go, JOY, go.
JOY: What should I do?
JOY: What should I make someone do?
(Looks)
TOD: You want more?
TOD: Want more?
(Gives peanuts)
KONG: Thank you.
TOD: It's a bit sweet.
CRIS: He's taking care of him.
JOY: Who should it be?
JOY: I want to know
who KONG wants to kiss.
CRIS: JOY.
JANEYEH: That's brilliant.
CRIS: So brilliant, JOY. So brilliant.
CRIS: So brilliant.
RUSAMEEKAE: Well-done, JOY.
JOY: I want to know
who KONG wants to kiss.
JANEYEH: He's stunned.
JOY: You have two choices,
these two you shared a bed with.
KONG: Really?
TIMETHAI: JOY's on it.
CRIS: Amazing, JOY.
KONG: TOD.
JANEYEH: TOD is shy.
JOY: Come on, kiss him.
CANDIDATE: Come on, kiss him.
CRIS: JOY is so amazing.
(Shy)
NAMNUNG: That's it. TOD, congrats!
JANEYEH: Congratulations, TOD.
JANEYEH: That's great.
SUNNY: Oh, it's so long.
FRAME: Oh, it's so long.
RUSAMEEKAE: And JUNSU has to read it.
SUNNY: You read it, or it'll be slow.
JUNSU: Ok, you translate this.
FRAME: Please choose three people
in the group to answer this question.
(Choose three people to answer who they want to Fall in Love with and have One Night Stand with)
FRAME: Choose two people for Fall in Love
FRAME: and One Night Stand.
CRIS: Here we go.
SUNNY: One Night Stand?
TOD: Wow.
JOY: Oh, I really like this question.
CRIS: JOY, JOY.
FRAME: Okay.
RUSAMEEKAE: Who'll get it?
CHERRY: Over there. Over there.
JUNSU: Me first.
RUSAMEEKAE: Who do you choose?
JUNSU: FRAME.
(FRAME was selected
to answer the question)
PEANUT: That's harsh.
JUNSU: And NAMNUNG, and then...
(FRAME AND NAMNUNG were chosen to answer the question)
CANDIDATE: Oh my god.
RUSAMEEKAE: These two are firecrackers.
JUNSU: A guy.
CRIS: TIME.
JUNSU: TIME.
(FRAME, NAMNUNG, TIME
were chosen to answer the question)
TIMETHAI: Harsh.
JOY: Exciting, wow.
TIME: Fall in Love and One Night Stand.
FRAME: Should I answer first?
TIME: You go first.
FRAME: Fall in Love.
RUSAMEEKAE: Oh my god.
FRAME: You.
JUNSU: I'm happy!
CRIS: Cute.
TOD: Go jump into the water.
MATHEUS: Go swimming.
RUSAMEEKAE: This one Fall in Love, okay?
JOY: And the One Night Stand?
RUSAMEEKAE: One Night Stand.
PEANUT: Next it's getting tense.
(Listening)
FRAME: I don't want One Night Stand.
(FRAME chose
not to answer One Night Stand)
JANEYEH: He's blushing.
MATHEUS: True love forever.
(Help with her drink)
- FRAME: You want half of it?
- JUNSU: Half.
FRAME: You can drink it, right?
JUNSU: I can.
PEANUT: So adorable.
SUNNY: Cute, right? I'm jealous.
(Shakes head)RUSAMEEKAE:
She lost to the voice in her head.
(Looking)
JUNSU: And then TIME.
CRIS: Oops, it's TIME now. It's TIME.
(Closes eyes)
RUSAMEEKAE: Oh my god.
TIMETHAI: Just drink it, bro.
CRIS: Just drink it.
TIMETHAI: Save yourself, bro.
CRIS: Right.
TIMETHAI: Bro in the war zone, man.
TIME: Okay.
TIME: Fall in Love.
CRIS: Oh my god, I'm so excited.
TIME: SUNNY.
CRIS: Did he say SUNNY?
- CANDIDATE: Oh my god.
MATHEUS: Oops.
CRIS: Messy.
RUSAMEEKAE: One Night Stand.
(TIME's One Night Stand is...)
TIMETHAI: I can't watch this.
JANEYEH: Ugh!
(Will it be SUNNY
who he Falls in Love with)
(or NAMNUNG
who he has always been interested)
PEANUT: Does he even dare to answer?
TIME: NAMNUNG.
JANEYEH: Oh, that's harsh.
- CRIS: Please, TIME
- MATHEUS: Bro.
MATHEUS: Oh.
- JANEYEH: Why did you do that?
- MATHEUS: Why?
CRIS: I feel sorry for NAMNUNG.
TIMETHAI: You blew up your own house.
TIME: Go on.
CRIS: Oh my God.
RUSAMEEKAE: This is episode five.
RUSAMEEKAE: I don't know
how they're going to live after this.
TOD: Wow.
CHERRY: There's NAMNUNG.
NAMNUNG hasn't answered yet.
RUSAMEEKAE: Is NAMNUNG
going to retaliate?
(NAMNUNG chooses not to answer)
MATHEUS: Oh my God.
CRIS: Applause for the beauty.
You're strong.
(Reach out to grab)
TIME: I'll help you with it.
TIMETHAI: It's too late,
you already blew up your house.
CRIS: Applause for the beauty.
You're strong.
MATHEUS: It's okay.
JUNSU: No answer.
FRAME: I'll read it now, okay?
(Pick one person to answer this)
FRAME: Pick one person to answer this
(From those sitting here,)
FRAME: From those sitting here,
(who would you like to go to X-Land with the most?)FRAME: who would you like
to go to X-Land with the most?
KONG: Oh.
NAMNUNG: I'm confused.
Can you repeat that?
FRAME: I'll ask TIME.
TIME: Huh?
JANEYEH: Ugh!
PEANUT: I really want to know
what this person is like.
TIME: Huh?
JOY: Don't worry.
JANEYEH: "Don't worry."
- LOVE(X)PERT: JOY.
PEANUT: And SUNNY has high expectations.
TIME: NAMNUNG.
- RUSAMEEKAE: Why!
- PEANUT: Hey!
CRIS: Did he say NAMNUNG?
PEANUT: What's up with TIME?
JANEYEH: What the heck?
JANEYEH: TIME, what's going on?
TIME: NAMNUNG.
LOVE(X)PERT: NAMNUNG is confused.
TIMETHAI: Bro, you killed yourself.
RUSAMEEKAE: She's not happy, indeed.
PEANUT: I need some painkillers.
I can't think straight anymore.
TIMETHAI: He is trying to
use a bottle of water
TIMETHAI: to put out
the fire burning his house.
LOVE(X)PERT: Confusing.
NAMNUNG: Listen, can't you decide?
TIME: Go on.
TIMETHAI: He's feeling guilty now,
but there's nothing he can do.
NAMNUNG: Answering like that
makes me feel
NAMNUNG: kind of bad.
NAMNUNG: Hearing my name might be nice,
NAMNUNG: but it's the wrong time
and the wrong question.
NAMNUNG: The sentence is wrong,
the words are all wrong.
CRIS: It's over.
NAMNUNG: Come.
KONG: Is it empty?
NAMNUNG: Mmm.
(NAMNUNG got a blank sheet)
CRIS: Ugh.
TOD: You don't need to ask,
but let them do anything. Do you want it?
(Ask SUNNY for help) NAMNUNG: Can you help come up
with a question?
PEANUT: Hey.
NAMNUNG: And I'll choose the person.
Just whatever question.
SUNNY: Are you crazy?
JANEYEH: Oh my God.
NAMNUNG: Yes.
CRIS: It's over, TIME
SUNNY: Go kiss the person
you like the most.
CRIS: Perfection.
JANEYEH: That's it.
NAMNUNG: This is crazy.
TOD: Oh.
CHERRY: Ooh.
NAMNUNG: Who should I pick?
RUSAMEEKAE: Is it SUNNY?
TIMETHAI: SUNNY.
RUSAMEEKAE: No.
NAMNUNG: SUNNY.
- CRIS: See?
- RUSAMEEKAE: Ouch.
JANEYEH: Go.
JANEYEH: Go, girls.
TOD: What?
NAMNUNG: I choose you.
JANEYEH: Oh my God.
SUNNY: Come on.
PEANUT: "Come on."
CRIS: This is it.
SUNNY: Come on.
CANDIDATE: Wow.
PEANUT: So they just stand up
and go to find each other?
(Open arms for a hug)
RUSAMEEKAE: Wow.
CRIS: It's awesome.
(Step back)
CRIS: TIME, it's over.
JEANYEH: Oh my God.
RUSAMEEKAE: Isn't it over yet?
CRIS: This is it.
JANEYEH: Go.
CRIS: Give it up.
FRAME: Wow.
TOD: Wow.
TIMETHAI: Go bang your head against
the wall now, get some sense back.
- PEANUT: I'm sorry, I'm satisfied.
- CRIS: TIME.
TIMETHAI: Hello, PAE.
TIMETHAI: That's right. I think
you should watch just this episode.
JANEYEH: This is so satisfying.
TIMETHAI: This episode is good.
RUSAMEEKAE:
How many punches did TIME get?
PEANUT: It's satisfying.
Really hits the spot.
JANEYEH: She did the right thing.
RUSAMEEKAE: He asked the wrong person.
JANEYEH: It's the right person.
RUSAMEEKAE: Even though he could just
RUSAMEEKAE: chose to drink
and not to answer.
CRIS: Why did he have to say it?
CRIS: It's bad in every way.
TIMETHAI: I think he's still young,
and I think
TIMETHAI: he feels like he has to do
something that has an impact,
TIMETHAI: just trying to make waves.
TIMETHAI: But the waves
hit back at himself.
RUSAMEEKAE: Yeah.
CRIS: It's all a mess.
RUSAMEEKAE: It's a mess.
JANEYEH: I think if the girls end up
together, it's good. Let TIME go.
(It's a better ending like this)- JANEYEH: NAMNUNG and SUNNY can be together.
- CRIS: Yes.
PEANUT: Yes.
RUSAMEEKAE: It's possible.
RUSAMEEKAE: But it's okay, keep it
for now as the story isn't over yet.
RUSAMEEKAE: Let's continue watching.
They've finished answering the questions.
RUSAMEEKAE: When they go back
to the villa,
RUSAMEEKAE: let's see how
the atmosphere in the villa is.
CRIS: Ugh.
NAMNUNG:
TOD, wait for me too, wait for me.
- TIME: Wait for me too.
- NAMNUNG: Wait for me.
TIME: What?
(Indifferent)
NAMNUNG: Wait for me.
TIME: Where are you going?
LOVE(X)PERT: Wow!
LOVE(X)PERT: She ignored him.
CANDIDATE: Once I've seen that
(SUNNY and NAMNUNG's room, the two are in the bathroom)
CANDIDATE: MATHEUS is interested in you and me,
CANDIDATE: TIME is interested in
you and me, so it's like...
CANDIDATE: You know?
CRIS: They're having
an open-hearted talk.
(Thinking)
LOVE(X)PERT: Oh my.
CRIS: Think more.
CRIS: You should do that.
RUSAMEEKAE: Is he going to
apologize or...
CRIS: It's too late to apologize.
JANEYEH: Maybe in ten years,
not just two or three days.
JANEYEH: Come back
and talk again after ten years.
PEANUT: But it seems like
he's thinking about it.
TIME: There are many things I have to do
TIME: and to confess.
JANEYEH: What are you doing? Confessing?
(Leave)
TIMETHAI: No, no.
(This afternoon)
CRIS: This afternoon? What?
RUSAMEEKAE: Exclusive One-on-One Date Privilege.
(This afternoon)
TIME: Okay.
(Use 100 shell coins to redeem a date privilege)
(He gave it his all and earned 128 shell coins)
TIME: I have to win.
(He has 128 shell coins)
TIME: How many days have I been waiting?
(Now has 28 shell coins)
TIME: I'm buying a date.
TIME: One-on-one.
TIME: LOVE(X).
TIME: I've been waiting for 5 days now.
CRIS: Plot twist?
CRIS: We still don't know because
in the end, during the day...
(Who will TIME choose to invite?)
(SUNNY and NAMNUNG's room, the two are in the bathroom)
RUSAMEEKAE: And the two are here.
CANDIDATE:TIME is interested in you
and me, so it's like...
JANEYEH: I'm going crazy.
CRIS: Crazy.
What kind of crazy game is this?
CANDIDATE: Who's coming?
Someone's coming.
LOVE(X)PERT: Let's see.
CRIS: Is it over? Is the episode over?
RUSAMEEKAE: Don't, please don't.
JANEYEH: Is it ending like this again?
(Left hanging)
CRIS: Don't tell me after 15 minutes
CRIS: of ranting about TIME,
he actually had a reason?
(Plot twist)
CRIS: That's why he chose NAMNUNG.
CRIS: He said he wanted to go to X-Land with NAMNUNG
because he planned it since earlier today.
- JANEYEH: Very intense.
- CRIS: Wow!
RUSAMEEKAE: It's okay, CRIS.
It's okay, everyone.
RUSAMEEKAE: I believe the viewers
feel the same as us right now.
RUSAMEEKAE: So in the end, who will TIME
choose to invite for a date?
RUSAMEEKAE: We'll find out together
who TIME will choose next week.
RUSAMEEKAE: Tune in every Saturday
at 6 PM Beijing Time, only on WeTV,
ALL: for Borderless Love.
ALL: LOVE(X).
RUSAMEEKAE: That's it for today.
JANEYEH: Ugh! I want to scream.
RUSAMEEKAE: No clapping,
I'm leaving with this mood.
RUSAMEEKAE: No need to clap,
my hair's falling out.
- CRIS: Enough.
- TIMETHAI: I want to have good things.
(Want to meet singles?
Send love to your favorite single person.)
(On the WeTV app
to chat with them on livestream.)
(Preview)
(Today, we will enter the only room swap of LOVE(X).)
LOVE(X)PERT: Oh.
PEANUT: The show is trying
to break up every couple.
TOD: Do what you want to do.
TIME: I want you to be happy
TOD: I also want you to be happy.
PEANUT: Why are you so nice?
(Go to the Room Selection Board.)
PEANUT: Who is MATHEUS changing?
RUSAMEEKAE:
Everyone has the right to change, CRIS.
CRIS: It's a total mess.
(Next, we will enter
the competition between two villas.)
(This round's game is water basketball.)
LOVE(X)PERT: Fighting.
CRIS: NAMNUNG, catch it.
(NAMNUNG deflects)
CRIS: Oops, great job, dear.
JANEYEH: You got your win, SUNNY.
CANDIDATE: NAMNUNG.
CRIS: Oops, NAMNUNG isn't here.
CRIS: Where are you, NAMNUNG?
TIME: If you still have feelings
for me, come tell me later.
RUSAMEEKAE: Ugh.
TIMETHAI: He's not so good at talking,
but he loves with all his heart.
TIME: I just want to thank you.
TIME: You've made me feel this.
TIME: I haven't felt like this
in a very long time.
CRIS: Did you secretly teach him?
JANEYEH: This is how it's done.
(Who will TIME choose?)
TIME: Will you go on a date with me?