Timing and subtitles brought to you by
🌊 The Sea Chronicles Team@Viki.com
Everything is here, Miss Xiang.
Where is Master Gao Ming?
He went to buy horses.
We have a lot of people and luggage.
Not even three horse carriages can fit everything.
I've dismissed the indentured maids and servants.
I also gave them some extra money.
I'm sure you don't mind, Official Zang.
No one in the capital makes more money than you, Proprietor Xiang.
In the future, we have to rely on you.
Xiao Hai! Xiao Hai.
Look who's here.
Official Zhao.
Benefactor.
Zang Hai,
are you going to resign and leave the capital?
I've submitted my resignation to the Cabinet.
I planned to tell you after His Majesty approves it.
Are you free to talk with me now?
A horse carriage...
can go left or right.
Yet,
the reins are in the coachman's hands.
Sometimes, I think...
people are like these horses.
They seem like they have a choice
but in truth,
it's out of their control.
I rescued you back then
and asked you to make your own decision.
You chose revenge.
However, I've been thinking all these years.
Was I right to let a child...
make such a cruel choice?
I owed you a debt of gratitude for saving me.
You also asked my masters to take care of me, raise me,
and let me get my revenge.
I will never blame you.
Yes.
You've grown up over time
and have matured.
Now, your third enemy is dead.
You can begin a new life now.
I want you to make another decision.
Sir, spare me some food.
- Show some mercy.
- Sir.
- Have a heart.
- Spare me some food.
Sir, show some mercy.
Have a heart, sir.
Sir!
Spare me some food.
Spare some food, sir.
Thank you, sir!
Spare me some food.
Be kind, sir.
Thank you, sir.
Thank you.
- Thank you, sir.
Thank you, sir.
- Take it for him.
- Thank you, sir.
We have food now.
Quick. We have food now.
After so many years,
corrupt officials bled Great Yong dry.
The nine rivers flood every year.
Imperial exams are mostly rigged.
There are still people who starve to death under the Emperor's rule.
What decision are you talking about?
Do you still remember when you first entered the Marquis of Pingjin Mansion
and exchanged all the gifts you received
into food for the starving people?
Your father...
used to do the same as well.
He would ask those who starved to work
in exchange for food.
Many of your seniors were orphans of refugees.
They had no one to rely on since young...
and were raised by your father at his mansion.
However, that was all he did.
Do you still remember what I said to you
when you came to my place to probe me back then?
Before you can achieve what you set out to achieve,
assume that you have achieved it.
You mean...
Your father could only save them for a while.
Why not go further and save the people forever?
From tomorrow onward,
I will be the interim Chief Cabinet Secretary.
You have the talent to be a great leader.
If you want to do it,
accept this edict to join the Cabinet
and continue being an official in the imperial court.
If you want to be free from now on, just reject it.
Go and live the life that you want, yet couldn't possess until now.
Let's go.
Antu.
I have a way.
What is it?
Resignation.
Let everyone know that we are leaving the capital
and will not come back again.
If the third enemy truly exists,
he knows who I am
and knows I have knowledge of the Gui Seal and bronze fish.
Do you think he will let me go
and allow me to leave freely?
He will surely keep you by his side where he can see you
and do everything to see
whether you gave the Gui Seal and bronze fish to the Emperor or not.
He will make sure that you won't ruin the next step in his plan.
He may even kill you...
if it's necessary.
That's right.
The person who doesn't want us to leave the most...
might be the real third enemy.
He asked me to stay in the capital and aid him in the Cabinet.
Right now, he is the only one...
who has asked me to stay.
What if he only appreciates you as a talent
and it is all a coincidence?
No matter what, I must give it a try.
Not only will I see him every day after joining the Cabinet,
but I will also have access to many confidential files.
Whether it is him or not,
I will find out the truth.
Help me keep an eye on Master.
If Zhao Bingwen is the third enemy,
are we going to suspect Master Gao Ming as well?
If my benefactor is truly the third enemy,
Master might have been deceived as well.
However, they share a genuine relationship.
Whether it's my benefactor or Master,
I can't show them my true self before the truth comes to light.
Don't worry.
I know what to do.
Why is it always so hard
to write the words Balance and Harmony?
You taught me it must be without excess and deficiency.
Precision is hard to attain.
The same goes for calligraphy as well.
A gentleman is only a person of balance and harmony
if they have the virtues of a gentry.
To interpret it narrowly, it's the virtue of preserving life.
To interpret it broadly, it's to deliver the people from suffering.
That is why you asked Zang Hai to join the Cabinet
and help you govern the empire and help the people.
However...
Zang Hai is still young.
This is not where he excels.
Is this your opinion
or Zang Hai's opinion?
Zang Hai admires and respects you a lot.
This is merely my opinion.
Are you hiding anything from me?
I dare not.
You should do your job well as a master.
Don't let the past incident repeat itself.
Have you found the bronze fish?
Zang Hai is very cautious.
I still can't take action.
It'll be too late if you don't act soon.
I'm doing this for his own good.
Getting him to stay in the capital and join the Cabinet
is the only way to protect him.
I will act as soon as possible.
Grand Secretary Zhao.
Thanks to His Majesty's grace,
I will take over as interim Chief Cabinet Secretary.
I still need everyone's help
regarding the Cabinet's matters.
Please order us as you see fit, Grand Secretary Zhao.
Everyone is sad about what happened to the Shi family.
Grand Secretary Shi did his best to serve the Emperor.
I hope all of you can follow his ambition
and do your duty in the Cabinet
- to share His Majesty's burdens.
- Yes.
His Majesty has approved Zang Hai's appointment to the Cabinet.
In the future, he can participate in important matters of the imperial court.
Zang Hai, you can enter the Cabinet's archive as you wish.
Yes, Official Zhao.
All right.
Get ready for today's meeting.
Zang Hai.
If you need any help, come and ask me anytime.
There's no need to be so formal between us.
Yes.
Official Zhao.
I have something to ask you.
I've gone through the draft opinions in the last few years.
I realized most of them were drafted by Official Zhao.
From what he wrote,
his integrity and loyalty were infallible.
In that case, not only does he not have any flaws,
but the more you investigate,
the more he seems like an official who cares about the empire and the people.
Have we misunderstood him?
I'm not sure if he wants to nurture me
or learn about the whereabouts of my bronze fish.
There must be a larger objective
for him to put up an act for so long.
Before you achieve what you set out to achieve,
assume that you have achieved it.
I must keep investigating.
What comes next is a test of patience.
Darn you, Xiang Antu.
You've been ignoring me recently.
Why did you suddenly think of me today?
I wanted to see you today.
Look. I brewed some premium flower tea for you.
Try it.
I even bought you some fragrance powder.
- Not bad.
- They are for you if you like them.
That's more like it.
How are you doing with Zang Hai recently?
He just joined the Cabinet
and is busy with court matters with your father every day.
I can't even see him.
I knew it.
You only remember mewhen you can't hang out with him.
This painting...
Do you recognize this drawing?
It belongs to my father.
I've seen it since I was young.
Of course, I recognize it.
This is it.
Why do you have this painting?
This painting was in Shi Yiping's residence.
Zang Hai requested it from the Emperor after his death.
Why would Shi Yiping possess my father's painting?
Whatever.
Zang Hai is such a sweet person.
He requested a painting of Dongxia from the Emperor for you
so you won't feel homesick.
That's right. He has no time to accompany me.
He owes me this painting.
All right. Don't stay cooped up at home.
Come and have fun with me outside.
Official Zhao.
I have something I don't understand. Please guide me.
The documents submitted by the Ministry of Works recently
were all rejected by the Cabinet.
It's spring, and many places suffer from floods.
The Ministry of Works knows the damage it will cause
and wants to improve the flood control system
- but for some reason...
- Zang Hai.
In recent years, Great Yong's treasury has been drained.
Even the Ministry of Rites struggled to organize the Spring Exam,
let alone the Ministry of Works.
If we keep allocating money to every ministry's needs,
we're going to create a bigger problem.
This problem must be dealt with at its roots.
Are you talking about getting rid of corruption?
That's right.
The treasury's money has gone to corrupt officials.
It's no use, no matter how much money you allocate.
In the end, it's the problem of the law.
A heavy punishment is needed
to get rid of corruption.
But won't doing this bring the opposite effect?
Zang Hai.
If you can think of that,
it's very good.
This is also what I'm most worried about.
The corruption culture in the imperial court
happens mostly due to officials
who can't feed their families with their meager salaries.
If you don't want them to harm the common people,
killing a few of them won't solve the problem.
I've petitioned the Emperor
to increase the salaries of all fifth-rank officials and above by 30%.
This is the money that the imperial court must spend.
One must have a roof above their head and a full stomach.
Officials must be able to feed their families
so they don't prey on the people.
This is a good method indeed.
However...
shouldn't we start from those working closely with the people?
If the treasury has a lot of money,
I will surely do that.
However, prioritizing the small officials over the powerful officials...
is not something even the Emperor can do.
As the saying goes, "If one intends to take something,
one must first give something away."
You are involved in the imperial court now.
You must remember this in the future.
Yes.
I will remember it.
Tong'er came today and recognized the painting to be Official Zhao's.
She even asked how the painting ended up in our place.
It's his indeed.
This is very suspicious indeed.
I've never lied to Tong'er before.
I didn't tell her the truth today
and I feel a little guilty.
She is my best friend.
I really hope Official Zhao is just your benefactor
and not your enemy.
Tong'er.
Father.
What are you looking for?
Father, did you give Shi Yiping this painting?
Which painting?
The "Landscape of Mount Yuren" painting that was kept here previously.
That painting?
Previously, I went to visit the Shi residence with my colleagues
for a so-called painting and calligraphy appreciation session.
I brought this painting with me without much thought.
To my surprise, he loved it.
He forced me to give it to him, so I did.
I went to hang out with Antu today and saw this painting at her place.
I thought I was mistaken
but when I came back and looked for it, the painting was indeed yours.
This painting should belong to the imperial court
now that the Shi Residence was seized following Shi Yiping's death.
How come she possesses the painting?
She said Zang Hai asked the Emperor for it
to be given to her as a gift because it was a painting of Dongxia.
I see.
Tong'er,
sit with me for a while.
Since your mother passed away,
both of us have been relying on each other,
so I allowed you...
to go to Zhen Tower dressed as a man to tell stories.
But now,
you are no longer a child.
It's time to act your age.
But I enjoy reading and telling stories.
You've been rebellious
since your childhood, because I've always doted on you.
You do things without caring about the consequences.
You will regret it one day.
Father.
Zhen Tower is gone now.
You should cease thinking about telling and reading stories anymore.
From now on, you should stay home and accompany me more.
Master.
I'm going to work.
Go back and rest.
Zhao Geng.
Yes, Master.
Tong'er is a lady now.
When she goes out in the future,
assign a few men to follow her in case anything happens to her.
Yes.
Official Zang, it's late.
Our work is endless.
Continue tomorrow.
I still have work to do for the Ministry of Works
and the Imperial Astronomical Bureau tomorrow.
Grand Secretary Shi used to reprimand me in the past for being lazy and carefree.
If he were to see you now, he would surely appreciate you.
I'll be going back.
What a pity.
I joined the Cabinet too late.
Otherwise, I could learn from Grand Secretary Shi.
Having a superior who keeps giving me reminders
in political affairs is a lucky thing.
You are different from what I imagined.
What do you mean?
Official Zang, you served Zhuang Luyin in the past.
You became an official through recommendation.
However, you caused a mess in the imperial court.
In Grand Secretary Shi's opinion,
you broke the balance he spent his whole life maintaining.
Balance?
But didn't Grand Secretary Shi turn a blind eye to what Cao Jingxian did?
Cao Jingxian and Zhuang Luyin
were two authoritative figures no one would dare offend.
Grand Secretary Shi had been going against them by leading the Cabinet.
Both of them are dead now.
Unfortunately, Grand Secretary Shi passed away as well.
However, rumors in the capital are saying
that Grand Secretary Shi was close to Cao Jingxian.
However, he was killed by Cao Jingxian's surveillance officers.
They say both of them had a falling out and turned against each other.
Impossible. I don't believe it.
Grand Secretary Shi was my superior for many years.
I know him very well.
Official Zang, let me show you something.
This is the name list of Great Yong's officials.
Grand Secretary Shi gave it to me back then.
He started writing this name list when he was the Vice Minister of Personnel.
Everyone said Grand Secretary Shi remembered every official of Great Yong
when he was the Vice Minister of Personnel.
I suppose good memory still has to make way for note-taking.
Before the New Year, Grand Secretary Shi saw that I was busy working
and gave me this name list.
The name list has always been kept at the Cabinet, with no one to retrieve it.
Lu Min?
Lu Min...
I noticed this before.
This should be Cao Jingxian's name before he entered the palace.
All his foster sons have the surname of "Lu".
He just couldn't give up on passing his lineage.
Sir.
I didn't know you were coming.
Sorry for the poor reception.
Sit.
Thank you, sir.
You may leave.
Are you Eunuch Liu?
Yes.
You were the one who taught the new eunuchs the rules in the past.
I want to ask you about someone.
If I know something, I will tell you honestly.
Lu Min.
Lu Min?
Lu Min...
I remember.
Do you really remember?
I do.
He wasn't castrated when he entered the palace.
He had long lost his manhood.
He castrated himself.
There are many rules and forms of etiquette in the palace.
Those who graduated here
can have a chance of becoming a eunuch at the inner palace.
Lu Min was hardworking and liked to study.
It didn't take long for him to learn most of the skills
from veterans like us.
When it was time for him to change his name and enter the palace,
he was more capable than eunuchs
years his senior.
What did he change his name to later?
I don't remember.
I remember he went to work at the Imperial Stables Directorate.
Lu Min was educated, and he could read.
He spoke in a formal and elegant way.
He used to say that he shouldn't become a eunuch.
He said if he participated in the exams,
he would surely become a highly-ranked official.
He told me he used to study in the best academy in the capital,
the Academy of Great Yong.
Sir,
all the original documents and files
since the establishment of the Academy of Great Yong are stored here.
You may leave.
I can search for it myself.
Yes.
Master.
You're back?
We are having Fried Bean Sauce Noodles tonight.
It will take some time.
I'm too tired today and don't have an appetite.
I want to rest for a while.
The Cabinet is a difficult place to be.
Look at you.
You hold three positions at once.
There are too many things you need to do.
I feel exhausted for you already.
All of these responsibilities are too many
and too heavy for me.
Why don't I tell Master
and ask him to relieve you of your burden?
I'll think about it.
Once I think it through, I'll tell him myself.
Xiao Hai.
You're like a stranger to me now.
You won't even chat with me.
Have you forgotten about me now that you have Miss Xiang?
When you put it like that,
I have no choice but to chat with you.
That's more like it.
Peel the garlic.
Master, do you still remember when you asked me
what kind of life I would want to live after getting my revenge?
I couldn't answer you back then.
You also told me the day would come soon.
You were right.
I've made my choice
and I'm still an official with my benefactor.
But I want to know your answer.
Me?
My benefactor asked you to aid me in my revenge.
Now that I've taken my revenge,
haven't you thought about what you want to do?
Are you calling me useless now?
Since you're in the Cabinet now,
you no longer need the things I taught you.
That's not what I mean.
I know that's not what you mean.
I was just teasing you.
Do you really want to know?
Royal silver.
Master, do you still remember the time when you took me
to trick a corrupt official when I was young?
I remember.
Look.
I have gotten the newly minted royal silver now.
Look how much you've achieved.
The royal silver I used back then
was the tuition fee I received from your benefactor.
Yet, I spent all of it in the first lesson.
You are good at pretending to be an official.
Did you learn it from my benefactor?
Why don't you become an official?
That won't do.
I'm just a fraud.
I'll be exposed if I become an official.
I don't think so.
We humans don't need to live for a certain goal.
Living our days with people we care about by our side,
doesn't it sound good?
You are in the capital, and your benefactor is also in the capital.
Where else can I go?
I'll just serve you and become a cook.
If I can't teach you anything else,
I'll feed you instead.
You used to tell me that no matter how capable I was,
I still wouldn't surpass you.
Enough.
You've been busy the whole day.
Go inside your room and sleep.
I'll slowly make these noodles.
You can eat them when you wake up.
I won't need to wake you up.
The smell of the noodles will do just that.
Go on.
All right.
Official Zhao.
My benefactor.
My third enemy.
I used to think my obsession with vengeance
compelled me to keep investigating...
until the truth came out.
Have you thought about what you are going to do?
Should you tell the Emperor directly?
No.
I've hidden the bronze fish as well.
We can't go through the Emperor anymore.
We must deal with it ourselves.
Since I've chosen this path,
I have to see it through until the end.
All right.
Move forward for your past and current self.
Antu, make the preparations.
I want to invite Zhao Bingwen to my residence
and confront him.
Timing and subtitles brought to you by
🌊 The Sea Chronicles Team@Viki.com
"It's Me" - Sun Nan
♫  I conceal the ambition in my eyes  ♫
♫  In my palm, I hold a dangerous desire  ♫
♫  Turbulent waves hide in my sleeves  ♫
♫  Silent like the clap of thunder  ♫
♫  The depth of shrewdness  ♫
♫  Can't escape  ♫
♫  My sharp eyes  ♫
♫  Conspiracies are my amor  ♫
♫  Overt plans are my sword and spear  ♫
♫  With stoic madness  ♫
♫  I cleanse the filth of the world  ♫
♫  The night is not dark  ♫
♫  Because  ♫
♫  My heart is burning bright  ♫
♫  I'm the turning clouds  ♫
♫  I'm the falling rain  ♫
♫  The compass of the human soul is unpredictable  ♫
♫  There will always be people who rise and fall  ♫
♫  I am life and death  ♫
♫  I grant and I deprive  ♫
♫  When faith burns like the scorching sun  ♫
♫  I will sing loudly with you  ♫
♫  I am the sowing season  ♫
♫  I am the autumn harvest  ♫
♫  I am the kingdom  ♫
♫  I am the commoner  ♫
♫  You are also me  ♫