[Legend of Zang Hai]
[Episode 4]
Get ready.
One.
Two.
Three!
My eyes!
My legs!
I can't see!
Nobody move!
I'll think of something!
Sir,
there's no way out for the two of us.
Forget about us.
Just go!
There has to be a way.
Trust me. I'll find a way out!
Sir...
Marquis of Pingjin...
You bastard!
I'll haunt you even after death!
Sir, someone's coming out!
Go!
Report to His Lordship.
Yes, sir!
You!
Get over here!
Zang Hai, a humble commoner,
greets My Lord.
How do you know
how to disarm the traps in the royal tomb?
The tomb's construction
was top secret.
Only the artisans
who built it back then knew the details.
Could it be
you're one of their descendants
and plan to rob the tomb?
My Lord,
I'm confused.
You seek a feng shui master
who can make it out alive from the tomb,
yet you question their credibility.
Do you
not believe in feng shui?
That's enough
of your clever talk!
Speak!
How did you get out?
My Lord,
I only figured out
the Bone-Cutting Wires inside the tomb.
It's a rare mechanism,
so it had to be arranged
in a special pattern.
The tomb passage
is guarded by the Wing-Chariot Beast.
Naturally, it's based
on the Nine-Star Layout.
So the Bone-Cutting Wires
follow the same logic.
You actually know the Nine-Star Layout?
That's a secret technique used only for royal tombs.
We humble craftsmen
only understand a little.
Of course,
we're no match for you officials.
I merely made
a wild guess
in a life-or-death moment.
Thanks to divine mercy, I made it out.
Folk knowledge
can't possibly compare
with official doctrine.
If your jumbled theories
can even brush against
the edges of geomancy,
then consider yourself lucky.
But...
His Lordship has arrived!
So you unlocked the tomb traps?
Yes, My Lord.
Step forward.
Zang Hai, a humble commoner, greets Your Lordship.
Then tell me,
do you have a way
to handle the Empress Dowager's burial?
Yes.
My Lord.
This man's background is unclear.
Letting him handle it
could be risky.
If he made it out of the tomb,
he must have some skill.
Let's hear your solution.
Your Lordship,
as for the Empress Dowager's burial,
it can be resolved
after a heavy rain.
Why after rain, specifically?
Thunder above, water below.
It forms the Hexagram of Release.
It symbolizes easing danger and tension.
When thunder and rain gather energy,
any stalemate
will naturally break.
Will it rain today?
This place is ringed by mountains,
shaped like a screen.
And it's early summer.
Warm southern air is moving in.
Today,
I noticed moist foliage.
Warm air rising, and cool air sinking,
clouds and rain will surge
like thousands of horses.
Is he right?
It is indeed humid today,
but there's no sign of energy convergence.
By our calculations,
rain today
is a fifty-fifty chance.
But before the Shen hour,
it will rain for sure.
We at the Imperial Astronomical Bureau serve the court.
We must speak with caution.
Not like you back-alley mystics,
twisting half-truths
into absolute certainty.
It's not fifty percent.
It's one hundred percent.
The rain
will definitely fall today.
Go outside the tomb
and summon Eunuch Sun!
Yes, sir!
Eunuch Sun has arrived!
The weather was fine.
But when I got to the gate,
it started pouring.
My Lord,
I heard someone
disarmed the royal tomb's traps.
They must have a solution.
We were just talking about that.
You were right.
The rain is here.
So, what's your plan
to solve the burial dilemma?
Your Lordship,
this matter
has already been resolved.
It's just that...
I don't dare say it aloud.
Quit stalling. Speak!
On my way here,
I dozed off.
And in that sleep,
Dowager Noble Consort Li appeared to me in a dream.
She said
the love between the late Emperor and Empress Dowager
moved the heavens.
She wished to fulfill
their wish to be buried together.
You country bumpkin,
why would the Dowager appear to you?
In the tomb earlier,
I faced deadly traps.
If not for her protection,
how else could I
have come out unscathed?
Watch your tongue!
Let him speak!
But a joint burial
is a major feng shui matter,
especially in a royal tomb.
If it defies heaven's will,
at best,
the spirits won't rest.
At worst,
it'll shake the dynasty's foundation.
So we must
light ever-burning lamps
across five sites,
east, west, south, north, and center
of the Great Yong territory.
Then royal descendants must guard the lights
for forty-nine days.
Only then can the realm remain stable.
For 300 years,
whenever an emperor or empress passed,
royals were summoned back to the capital.
But the Dowager says
the princes
must not return this time?
They can't return.
To ensure the Great Yong's future,
the sacred lamps
must be lit
by royal hands alone.
Especially Prince of Linzi,
who guards
the Eastern Azure Dragon position.
Whenever an emperor or empress dies,
that star position becomes unstable.
So Prince of Linzi
must personally hold the line.
So you're saying
the Dowager told you all this in a dream?
How do we know
you're not making it all up?
Every word I said is true.
Dowager Noble Consort Li loved her son deeply,
but she also knew the greater good.
She didn't want to burden His Majesty,
so she chose to move aside
and let the Empress Dowager be buried with the late Emperor.
She'll show a sign before noon tomorrow.
My Lord,
why not wait a little longer?
By tomorrow,
all will be clear.
You want me to wait for you?
Based on what?
Just your worthless life?
This life of mine
is nothing.
But if Your Lordship
has no better option,
why not bet
on me?
Eunuch Sun, what do you think?
If the Dowager truly sent a dream,
then I'll return and wait quietly.
If something really happens tomorrow,
I'll report it truthfully to His Majesty
and let him decide.
Thank you, Eunuch Sun.
Do you know who that eunuch is?
My Lord,
he...
he serves His Majesty directly.
That's right.
All the previous feng shui masters
gave their suggestions,
but Eunuch Sun
was never moved.
But this time,
he actually listened your words.
Do you know why?
Maybe His Majesty
already had something in mind.
You're really clever.
But talk is talk.
What matters is the result.
My Lord,
I have one more request.
May I enter the inner hall?
I'd like
to deliver a message to the Dowager.
You think someone like you
can just stroll into the inner hall?
Take him in.
Lord...
No need to say more.
Let's see
if the Dowager
really shows a sign tomorrow.
Follow me.
Qu Jiao, look into his background.
Yes, sir.
This is the tomb chamber.
The larger coffin belongs to the late Emperor.
The smaller one
is Dowager Noble Consort Li's.
To be here is a rare honor.
Even if you die tomorrow,
your life wouldn't be wasted.
My Lord, may I ask,
why is it so damp
in this hall?
What underground place isn't damp?
You clearly don't get out much.
Seen enough?
Please wait a moment, My Lord.
I'd like to bow to the Dowager
and report something.
Zang Hai, humble commoner,
kneels before the Dowager.
Thank you, Your Grace,
for sparing my life in great peril.
You're bowing the wrong way.
If you disturb her peace,
can you bear the consequences?
I've passed on
your wish.
I didn't fail your trust.
That's enough.
Let's go.
Yes, My Lord.
Once the incense burns out,
noon will have passed.
If the Dowager still shows no sign,
you'll be buried with her.
Please rest assured, My Lord.
Dowager Noble Consort Li will show a sign.
My Lord!
The Dowager's coffin just caved forward!
Congratulations to His Majesty and Your Lordship!
Dowager Noble Consort Li
is kind and virtuous.
This is her way of fulfilling
the late Emperor and Empress Dowager's wish!
Thank you, Dowager, for making it happen!
Thank you, Dowager!
- Thank you, Dowager! - Thank you, Dowager!
You've helped me
settle one of His Majesty's concerns.
What reward do you want?
Helping Your Lordship
is my duty as a humble subject.
I dare not ask for a reward.
Since you don't want a reward,
then let me count
your crimes instead.
You do know
tampering with royal burial rites
is a capital offense?
My Lord,
I wouldn't dare!
How about this...
I'll show both kindness and authority:
kill you first,
then reward you
with a fine coffin and silver for burial.
My Lord!
I came here willingly,
not as a prisoner.
But does Your Lordship know
why I insisted on coming?
To show off how clever you are?
But clever men die young.
The brighter they are,
the shorter they live.
I came hoping Your Lordship
would spare me a meal.
I wish to follow Your Lordship
and serve faithfully!
Plenty want to serve me.
Why should I choose you?
Your eldest son
serves in the Ministry of Works and is swamped.
I'm willing to dedicate my life
to the arts of architecture and geomancy,
to serve Your Lordship and your son
to the bitter end!
My Lord.
Speak.
We've looked into him.
Born in Wenzhou Prefecture.
Orphaned at eight.
Drifted to Qingquan Town in Jiangning.
Apprenticed to a carpenter.
A recent fire
left him homeless.
So he headed north to find work.
Arrived in the capital just a few days ago.
Keep him.
Much obliged, My Lord!
Report to the Marquis's residence without delay.
My Lord,
I have one more request.
The others who came with me
perished in the tomb.
If Your Lordship could offer them
a token of respect,
they would surely
be grateful in the afterlife!
[Marquis of Pingjin's Mansion]
I'm Zang Hai,
the new aide.
Please announce my arrival.
Hold on.
[Marquis of Pingjin's Mansion]
You're Zang Hai?
Yes, that's me.
Here are your robes and badge.
Pack your things.
You'll report to the back gate's Scholar Hall tomorrow.
Understood.
[Marquis of Pingjin's Mansion]
My dear disciple!
With just one move,
you helped His Majesty solve a major dilemma.
It was Dowager Noble Consort Li
who willingly showed a sign and shifted her coffin.
That way,
His Majesty won the court's support
without losing the people's favor.
You had the royals light lamps in five directions,
which gave His Majesty an excuse
to keep the princes mourning in their own fiefdoms,
especially Prince of Linzi.
If he returned to the capital for the funeral,
he might've stirred up trouble.
But you've fundamentally eliminated
the risk of rebellion.
Even now, I can't figure out
how just one heavy rain
made the Dowager's coffin
collapse forward like that.
Tell me the trick.
It's not as complicated
as you think.
When I entered the tomb hall,
I noticed
severe groundwater seepage.
The Dragon Vein Shaft and the coffin
were already corroded.
And the coffin anchoring stones
weren't properly joined.
If just then,
a wedge of lightning-struck wood
was inserted underneath,
it would unbalance the coffin.
Plus, a heavy rain brought
rising ground moisture.
Under that weight,
the Dowager
showing a sign was only natural.
You really did inherit
Xing Dou's teachings.
What I didn't expect
was how deep corruption runs
in the court.
Even a royal tomb gets shortchanged with shoddy work.
Now that it's exposed,
they might finally fix it properly.
Even the Emperor's tomb gets embezzled.
Don't be fooled
by their bows and cheers before the throne.
They're all scheming
for personal gain.
If my father were still alive,
seeing today's
filthy, corrupted Astronomical Bureau,
it would break his heart.
In any case,
you made a brilliant first step.
You really impressed
the Marquis of Pingjin.
What's wrong?
Yesterday, the Marquis
put his hand on my shoulder,
and I couldn't even lift my arm.
Let me massage it for you.
Master, easy!
Come on, bear with it.
Now I finally get
why my benefactor
didn't want me learning martial arts.
For the Marquis
to let me get that close,
he must have absolute confidence
in his skills.
But he chose
to press hard on my shoulder.
It shows
just how cautious and suspicious he is.
He's surrounded by elite guards,
and wears
golden-threaded soft armor.
Even the top fighters in Yong
might not get close to him.
Even if you knew martial arts,
your sword would still be sheathed
before he struck you down.
Relying on brute force
would be the worst plan.
Forget it.
At least I've made it into the Marquis's household.
I'll take my time and think long-term.
Once I'm inside,
I'll study everything carefully
and wait for the right chance.
If you need me, come to the inn.
But stay out of sight.
Master,
when I'm not around,
what do you usually do?
If you weren't my master,
where would you be,
and what would you be doing?
Of course I've got my own life.
If I weren't helping you seek revenge,
I'd be living carefree!
Before I left,
Master Xing Dou told me.
You're the one to ask about my benefactor
and the other three masters.
Want to know?
Then this meal is on you.
I...
Master,
I'm still young and broke.
Well, I'm old
and still empty-handed.
Isn't that even sadder?
Hand it over.
You...
Fine.
Now can you tell me?
Of course I can.
But not just yet.
Hey!
You tricked me again!
Give my money back!
All's fair in war and strategy.
The older,
the craftier!
[Scholar Hall]
You're the new aide?
I'm Zang Hai.
I'm Huijian,
also an aide here.
I got here two years before you.
From now on,
we're colleagues.
Want some?
No, thanks.
I heard about you.
Quite impressive.
You made it out
of the royal tomb alive
and even got into our Scholar Hall.
I'll be relying on you, Huijian,
for guidance from here on.
No need to flatter me.
But I'll say this.
In our Scholar Hall,
being too capable
isn't always a good thing.
I won't be able
to look out for you for long.
You do love to joke.
Come on, follow me.
I'll show you how things work here.
That gate you came through
opens at sunrise, closes at night.
It's for the household staff
to go in and out.
The main gate is for the Marquis
and his family.
Other than that,
it only opens for an hour
on special occasions.
As for us aides,
from 7 a.m. to 1 p.m.,
we write and record history.
From 1 to 7 p.m.,
we discuss state affairs.
During mealtime,
we eat in the east wing.
And by 9 p.m.,
we must finish evening lessons
before going to bed.
That's the basic routine.
Got it?
Got it.
All these rules
were set by the Marquis's senior secretary,
Mr. Yang.
Other times,
you're free to do
as you wish.
But honestly,
after I'm done
with all that each day,
I'm so tired
I just crash.
You'll be the same.
Mr. Yang
really thought this through.
Come on, I'll show you the study hall.
Much appreciated.
Chu,
a promising young man has joined.
That's a good thing.
Why so uneasy?
I saw this Zang Hai
[Clarity arises]
in the royal tomb.
He's smart and cautious.
Yang,
you mustn't
take him lightly.
You worry too much.
As long as he can ease the Marquis's burdens,
I would
be grateful beyond words.
What's there to worry about?
Neither of us could solve
the Empress Dowager's burial problem.
But this Zang Hai,
who popped up out of nowhere,
handled it.
If I were willing to take that risk,
I could've done it too.
But the outcome
is eight parts risk,
and only two parts gain.
Guys like us don't need to take that gamble.
But he's young.
Taking a gamble
[Pawn]
for future glory
is understandable.
In that case,
he does remind me
of a younger version of you, Mr. Yang.
I think this guy's got ambition.
One day,
he might not be content working under you.
If we really have someone
who can surpass us,
then I, Yang Zhen,
should step down and return home in peace.
But from what I heard,
what he's best at
is feng shui and geomancy.
You're not worried for me,
but for yourself, right?
[General]
Check!
Thanks for letting me win.
I'm not satisfied.
Let's play another round.
Qu,
a new aide just joined.
As the Scholar Hall supervisor,
it'd be rude of me
not to welcome him.
Excuse me.
Alright,
this is the study hall,
where the aides
write and compile texts.
Mr. Yang ordered
that the Marquis's achievements
be documented here.
Every so often,
he selects the best works
to present to the Marquis.
In the future,
you'll do the same as us.
We'll submit all our writings
through Mr. Yang?
Even if the Marquis wants
to discuss matters?
What are you thinking?
You expect him to face
dozens of people
all talking at once?
That'd drive anyone crazy.
Mr. Yang
will organize
the proposals,
then lets the aides
speak their minds.
He has someone record everything,
and submits the best ideas.
However...
none of us will ever know
whichever opinion the Marquis adopts
in the end.
Because they all become
Mr. Yang's ideas.
[Zhuang Clan Chronicle]
Nobles founded kingdoms,
and their heirs inherited them.
Thus, the term "clan of legacy."
So this family record of the Marquis
is titled "Zhuang Clan Chronicle."
Greetings, Mr. Yang.
Huijian,
you may go for now.
Yes, sir.
You're the one
who helped the Marquis
solve the Empress Dowager's
burial issue?
I'm Zang Hai.
Greetings, Mr. Yang.
You really are a talented young man.
For the Marquis's mansion
to have someone like you,
I, Yang Zhen, am truly fortunate.
Huijian must've
already explained
the rules here?
Yes.
The rules here
are even stricter than at the Imperial Academy or Court of Attendants.
But once you're used
to them,
you won't make mistakes
or embarrass the Marquis
when you step into court someday.
So, you mean
we aides even have a chance
to enter the court
and serve in office?
Of course.
The Marquis established the Scholar Hall
to scout talent
and future pillars
for the state.
You think you're just here
to waste time?
But do you scholars
even know
how to deal with the Marquis,
a military man?
One misstep, and it's martial punishment.
Forget about promotion,
you might not even survive.
If I don't protect you,
no one else will.
You're truly thoughtful, Mr. Yang.
You know why I had them
write the "Zhuang Clan Chronicle"?
It's so they can understand
the Marquis better,
understand what pleases him,
so they don't
offend him.
Once the time is right,
I'll personally recommend them
for the Marquis's favor.
I see.
Thank you for the guidance.
With your talent for grand design,
you'll surely make your mark
in the Marquis's household.
Mr. Yang!
The Marquis asked
if a new aide
named Zang Hai
has reported in today.
What does the Marquis want?
He said
he wants him to inspect the inner garden's feng shui.
I see.
Zang Hai is here.
Go at once!
Yes, sir.
Oh, right.
I almost forgot
something important.
There was a heavy rain yesterday.
The ancestral hall is leaking.
The Marquis ordered repairs,
but the eaves corbel brackets
are all in old style.
I searched high and low
and couldn't find
a craftsman who knows that method.
If it rains again,
the ancestral tablets
will suffer damage.
I heard you're skilled in geomancy.
Can you handle
old building repairs?
I have some basic knowledge
of geomantic construction.
I might be able to help, Mr. Yang.
That's great.
Judging by today's sky,
it's probably going to pour.
Not sure if there's still enough time.
Forget it.
Meeting the Marquis comes first.
Don't delay the real business.
If the Marquis gets upset,
I'll take the blame.
It won't affect you
in any way.
The ancestral hall
houses the Zhuang family's ancestral tablets.
The Great Yong Dynasty values filial piety,
and so does the Marquis.
If I let the hall fall into disrepair
and damage the ancestral tablets,
I'd be gravely neglecting my duty.
But about the Marquis's request...
Mr. Yang, could you please
explain to him on my behalf?
I'm afraid
I won't be able
to check the garden today.
No worries.
I'll speak well of you
before the Marquis.
Thank you, Mr. Yang.
[Uphold Ancestral Virtue]
[Pass Down Loyalty and Filial Piety]
You didn't get to see the Marquis?
The manor is heavily guarded.
He's a military man after all.
With so many lives on his hands,
he naturally fears for his own.
I studied the sun and clouds closely.
There really was going to be a storm that night.
If I hadn't acted,
the rain would've ruined the ancestral hall.
Then Yang Zhen would've gone
to the Marquis behind my back
and slandered me.
I'd be in deep trouble.
So I backed off,
but I missed a golden opportunity.
These past few days,
the Marquis hasn't
summoned me again.
That's the way it is for men of true talent.
The Marquis forgets people easily.
Day one, he remembers you.
Day two,
maybe a faint impression.
By day three,
you're completely erased.
Yang Zhen knows him too well.
He knows if you don't seize
your first chance,
you'll never break through again.
My benefactor was right.
Yang Zhen may seem kind
on the surface,
but deep down, he's jealous and fake.
He keeps tight control over the Scholar Hall.
Every aide
is under his thumb.
[Zhuang Clan Chronicle]
He feeds them empty promises,
but in truth,
he's made them useless.
What I must do
is take down Yang Zhen
and take his place.
[Hold Truth Within]
How many times do we have to revise this?
When will it be finished?
Everyone,
stop what you're doing.
The Marquis went to the palace today.
The Emperor rewarded him with treasures.
Move everything to the treasury
and record the inventory.
Guo En,
Yuan Shang,
Wang Yuanpei,
Fu Yuwen,
Gu Changsheng, and...
Zang Hai.
One tortoiseshell-carved pipa.
[One Tortoiseshell-carved pipa].
One pair
of Ding kiln white-glazed peony vases.
Two golden-inlaid gemstone belts.
One "Early Spring Landscape" scroll.
One statue of Cundi with jeweled crown and belt.
Two gold armbands from Fuxia.
[Swiftwind Blade]
One Swiftwind Blade.
Two pairs of dragon-carved jade pendants.
Ten Hetian jade belt hooks.
Ten tinkling jade bracelets.
[Imperial Gifts to the Marquis of Pingjin]
Mr. Yang,
all items have been accounted for.
Categorize everything and place them
on the display shelves.
Then double-check the full inventory list.
Understood.
This pair of Hetian jade cups...
why is one missing?
It's not there?
Give me the pen.
"Drawn by the master"...
What does that mean?
Just don't ask.
Pretend you didn't see anything.
[Drawn by the master]
[Virtue Alone Endures]
Mr. Yang,
everything's been logged
and stored properly.
Good.
You're all dismissed.
Yes, sir.
- Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
Zang Hai, stay.
You may go.
Yes, sir.
Zang Hai,
you stay behind
and go over the inventory
one more time.
Yes, Mr. Yang.
I chose you
because I trust you.
Though tedious
and detailed,
this job has
its secrets.
Others are careless
with it,
but you're meticulous.
You've only just arrived,
so you're unfamiliar with how things work here.
So, start with this task,
train yourself, and open your eyes.
Thank you, Mr. Yang.
Much appreciated.
Search this man thoroughly
when he leaves.
If he's carrying anything extra,
arrest him on the spot.
Yes, sir.
Conceal the ambition in my eyes
In my palm, I hold a dangerous desire
Turbulent waves hidden in my sleeves
Silent thunder echoes around
However cunning you are
I can see
Right through you
Schemes are my armor
Overt plans are my weapons
With restrained fury
I purge the world's corruption
The night is not dark
Because
My heart burns bright
I control the shifting clouds
I command the falling rain
The compass of the human soul is unpredictable
There will always be ups and downs
I hold the power of life and death
I grant and I take away
When faith burns like the scorching sun
I will sing aloud with you
I am the sowing season
I am the autumn harvest
I am the world
I am the people
And you are also me