[Legend of Zang Hai]
[Episode 11]
[Zhen Tower]
Excuse me.
Was that...?
That was Mr. Eight.
Mr. Zang, please don't keep Miss Xiang waiting.
Miss, Mr. Zang is here.
Miss Xiang.
Well, that's timely.
I just got back,
and here you are with gifts.
What, are you in need
of Zhen Tower's help already?
Please forgive me.
I'm here to make amends.
I was too arrogant and failed to appreciate
your kindness.
I let you down.
Is it too late to change
my mind now?
Didn't you say you weren't
worthy of my friendship?
Why have you changed your mind?
Did earning the Marquis's favor
make you think
you're above me now?
Favor?
I'd be lucky if the Marquis isn't suspicious of me.
The rumors
these past few days have nearly
ruined me.
So that's why you're here?
What rumors?
I haven't heard a thing.
Miss Xiang,
please have mercy on me.
The rumors from Mr. Eight...
Who said they came from him?
This has nothing to do with Zhen Tower.
Fine...
Let's just say the rumors
didn't start here.
I came today
to ask for your help
in putting an end
to those rumors.
Rumors blow over like the wind.
The wind fades,
but the damage remains.
Rumors stick in people's minds.
Over time,
they forget
where they heard them
and just assume they're true.
You really care that much?
The Marquis said
he'd get to the bottom of this.
Are you threatening me with his name?
I wouldn't dare.
But if you're truly blameless
and unwilling to help,
I'll have to leave it to fate.
You overestimate me.
I doubt I could
convince Mr. Eight.
I believe you can.
Zang Hai,
if you want to chase power and success,
there are plenty
of powerful men in the Capital to rely on.
Why are you
so fixated on serving
the Marquis of Pingjin?
He needed a feng shui master for the burial
of the Empress Dowager,
so he seized me.
I was just a commoner.
To survive, I had no choice.
I was just like a drowning man
clutching a floating branch in the currents
and trying to make it out alive.
It just so happened that the branch turned out to be
a towering tree.
If you ask me,
he didn't choose you.
You chose him.
Sounds like you care quite a bit as well.
In the Capital,
relationships form a tight web.
Grudges
and favors
are like hidden rocks in the river.
You can't see or feel them
until your boat hits one.
Well said.
I'll keep that in mind.
But rest assured.
I'm not your enemy.
Our goals don't clash.
That's not
for you to decide.
Miss Xiang,
just wait and see.
I'll be here in the Capital
for you and everyone else to watch.
I won't be watching.
Whether you turn out good or bad
has nothing to do with me.
[Dried Fruit]
Chili peppers!
- Dried chili peppers! - That stall belongs to a Dongxia merchant.
Dongxia and the Great Yong
trade regularly.
But it's tough doing business here now,
with the Surveillance Office always watching.
He's just
like you said,
under countless watchful eyes.
Oh, well.
You made yourself sound so pitiful.
If I don't give you a break,
I'll be as awful as the Surveillance Office.
Thanks for the gifts.
I'll talk to Mr. Eight for you.
Thank you, Miss Xiang.
I'll take my leave.
Sir,
what would you like?
Have a look around.
Candied hawthorn!
These are handmade,
embroidered
with Dongxia patterns.
Would you like one?
I'll take this one.
Thank you, sir.
Thank you!
So you're letting him off already?
Didn't you want
to sabotage his career and get him
kicked out of the Capital?
I can't figure him out.
He seemed
to have used the rumors to gain
more trust from the Marquis.
He really is something.
Now you're admiring his talent?
He ignored my warning,
so why should I bother?
We'll see how things go.
The real show's still to come.
Fresh cakes!
Hot and sweet!
Master.
You planned to assassinate the Marquis
and didn't even tell me?
Look at you, flying solo already.
Master,
I was wrong.
I was going to ask for your advice,
but someone knocked me out and took me away.
When I came to,
I saw my senior brother, Guanfeng.
He was also working at the Marquis's Mansion.
[Books]
Oh my, so much has happened.
Good thing
the rumors are cleared,
and the Marquis has lowered his guard.
Zhen Tower really is powerful.
They nearly ruined you with just a few rumors.
We can't kill the Marquis now.
I need to keep serving him to find out who the third person is.
Since it was three people plotting together,
chances are
that they're
of similar standing.
Not necessarily.
It's been years.
Officials rise and fall.
We can't rule anyone out by status.
Our target can be
a noble,
a rich merchant,
or even a commoner.
I didn't think of that.
If so, the investigation could take forever.
If only the Marquis would just
tell us himself.
That'd make it easy.
Master,
you're right.
I was joking.
You took that seriously?
Listen,
there is a way to make him talk.
But I can't ask him.
No matter how close we are,
if I bring it up,
he'll get suspicious.
So, I need someone else,
someone who can talk to him
and get him to open up.
Then it has to be someone really close to him.
Jiang Xiang, his principal wife,
is a proud noblewoman.
Even if you're useful to her,
she'll treat you like a dog.
The same goes for Zhuang Zhifu.
Besides, I've drawn too much attention.
Both Yang Zhen and Qu Jiao died because of me.
They won't trust me easily.
So that leaves one person.
Too bad Zhuang Zhixing is such a pushover.
Otherwise, he'd be a good choice.
No. He is the best choice.
But everyone in the Capital knows
the Marquis doesn't like him.
Are you sure?
Yes.
I'll help him earn
the Marquis's favor and trust.
Then he can ask for me.
Why would he help you?
Because people move for one thing: self-interest.
And what do you have to offer?
I'll help him become the Zhuang family's heir.
The heir?
Zhuang Zhifu is the legitimate son.
Zhuang Zhixing is just
a lost cause.
How could he possibly compete?
That's exactly why
he'll be tempted.
I help him rise,
and he helps me learn the Marquis's secret.
Fair deal.
Besides, I heard his birth mother
was once deeply favored by the Marquis.
But over time,
both mother and son got cast aside.
That kind
of fall from grace is hard to live with.
So I believe
he won't turn me down.
[Zhen Tower]
All of you, leave.
[By Imperial Grace and Honor]
- The Great Yong is invincible! - The Great Yong is invincible!
- The Marquis is mighty! - The Marquis is mighty!
Summon
the Princess of Dongxia!
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Kneel.
Hurry.
Bow.
Bow to His Majesty.
The Dongxia girl is ill-mannered.
Please forgive her.
It's fine.
She will learn our ways.
From now on,
she is no longer Dongxia's princess.
I name her
Princess Rouyuan.
"Luxury brings poverty.
As women,
we must not be idle.
A life worth living
is one of diligence.
A year's success
begins in spring.
Tea and wine, well prepared,
bring honor to the home.
As the sun sets behind the hills,
offer guests a place to stay.
Light the lamps,
and prepare the beds.
Be polite and respectful..."
Where did she go?
Look carefully.
Unbelievable!
Madam Ge,
a girl ran into the palace.
Did you see her?
I think...
I think she went that way.
Your Highness,
wait here.
Let's check over there.
Yes.
They're gone.
Why didn't you tell them?
You didn't do anything wrong.
Why should I?
Isn't sneaking in a bad thing?
To me,
sneaking out is worse.
I'm exhausted.
I finally got out on my own.
Do they watch you that closely?
Yeah.
Someone always follows me.
I'm not allowed to talk to others freely.
But you're free today.
If you want, I know lots of ways to sneak out.
Then let's sneak out more often.
[Fragrant Spring Within]
I'll take this one.
Let me pin it for you.
Let me see.
How is it?
Still not quite right.
Then let's try another shop.
So?
Did you finish your assignments today?
The teachers are always
going on about the same stuff,
like Great Yong's etiquette and its glorious history.
I'm so sick of it.
Poor them.
Now,
what story are you telling me today?
All right.
Your Highness,
what would you like to hear?
A tragic romance
or a stirring tale of revenge?
I want to hear
a story from Dongxia.
Sure.
I'll tell you a tale...
a tale of...
a Dongxia songstress
who fell for a scholar from the Great Yong.
Liar. That's not even real.
I've never been to Dongxia.
You should be amazed
I can even make up such a story.
If you want a real story,
take me to Dongxia someday.
What's wrong?
Homesick again?
No.
Have you thought about the future?
I have.
Well,
not too clearly.
But I do know
I hate doing needlework.
And I hate the books
my father makes me read. They're so dull.
What I love
is sitting around
in alleys and teahouses,
listening to gossip,
and turning it into stories.
If I can tell them with shadow puppets,
that would be perfect!
If you perform stories with shadow puppets,
you'll definitely draw big crowds.
By the end of the day,
you'll have more tips than you can count.
I'll follow you with a sack
to collect them!
You little money grubber!
Where's your royal grace?
I hope...
I hope one day,
Dongxia's children
can eat candied hawthorn too,
and that our people
can live as well as those in the Great Yong.
I believe it.
With a princess like you,
Dongxia will see that day.
But I'm stuck here in the Capital.
There's nothing I can do.
What use is a princess
who can't help her people?
In Great Yong, we have a saying:
"Take things as they come."
Since we can't
change the past,
we should do our best with what we have now.
As for your people in Dongxia...
Though you're in Great Yong now,
I believe one day,
you'll find a way to help them.
[Zhen Tower]
That's odd.
This place is usually packed.
Why is it so quiet today?
Because it's not open yet.
Look.
[Zhen Tower]
When did Chen Tower
become Zhen Tower?
Chen Tower was losing money,
so I bought it for cheap.
Even the Emperor approved it.
From now on,
Zhen Tower will be mine to run.
The Emperor?
He agreed to let you run this place?
Don't ask so many questions.
This is my turf now.
Let's go inside.
[Zhen Tower]
Didn't you say
you wanted a stage
to tell your stories to more people?
Now,
you have one.
I'll make sure the entire Capital knows your name.
They'll all come here for your stories.
As for me, like I said, I'll be
behind you collecting the money.
Rest assured.
I'll make sure you make a fortune.
You were right.
"Take things as they come."
Since I can't leave Great Yong,
I might as well make the most
of my time here.
I want to give the lost and homeless a place
to shelter from the wind and rain.
[By Imperial Grace and Honor]
Have you heard?
The Marquis of Pingjin's second son
ran up debts at Zhen Tower again.
How much this time?
This month alone,
900 liang.
What a spendthrift.
I hear
he feasts, drinks, gambles, and visits brothels.
He'll ruin the family sooner or later.
Exactly.
Come on. Cheers.
I don't visit brothels, all right?
The Marquis is a great man.
His eldest son, Zhuang Zhifu,
is already Vice Minister of Works
at such a young age.
How is it
that his second son is so useless?
He's an embarrassment
to his family!
A total disgrace.
Cheers.
You've
got some nerve
talking like that in this place.
Who are you?
What does this have to do with you?
I think Mr. Zhuang Zhixing is just fine.
He actually reminds me of the Marquis in his youth.
He's no less than Mr. Zhuang Zhifu.
Mr. Zhuang Zhifu
is sharp and capable. He has a bright future.
What does Zhuang Zhixing have to compare?
Exactly.
Well,
Zhuang Zhixing carries
the Marquis's blood,
and he's the grandson of General Zhuang Mu.
The family's produced generals for generations.
Mr. Zhixing is just keeping
a low profile for now.
In time, he'll make a name for himself.
Him?
You're
killing me, man!
Cheers.
Mr. Zhuang.
Mr. Zhixing,
what brings you here?
What, I can't be here?
Am I not allowed here?
Go on. Don't let me stop you.
Mr. Zhuang,
we were just leaving.
You enjoy.
Yes, enjoy.
Let's go.
Should I have someone teach them a lesson?
The Capital's
full of people who look down on me.
Don't bother.
You turned me down when I asked you
to join me here.
Why are you here on your own today?
I come from humble roots. Luxury like this is new to me.
After hearing your praise
of these herbal baths,
I couldn't stop thinking about them.
Work's worn me out lately,
so I came to unwind.
I hope I didn't come off too unrefined.
Well, you've picked the right day.
Today's bath has
safflower, red sage, and dong quai.
It's great for circulation.
To thank you for sticking up
for me just now,
this bath's on me.
Thank you, sir.
I'll join you.
It feels great.
As you can see,
everyone in the Capital
looks down on me.
Why do you think so highly of me?
A golden qilin doesn't belong in a pond.
From the moment I saw you,
I knew you weren't ordinary.
You're a strange one.
Shouldn't you be saying that to my brother?
Everyone flatters him,
but I believe your future
will be much brighter than his.
Go on.
You've got grit, a good heart, and an eye for talent.
I'm certain
you'll be the next head
of the Zhuang family.
Then you don't know me well enough.
When I'm bored,
I eat at Zhen Tower.
When I'm restless, I drink at Lingyue Tower.
In a good mood, I take a boat on the lake
and flirt with the girls.
In a bad one,
I gamble.
People
envy my life.
Why would I want to run a household,
worrying day and night?
Are those really your choices,
or has someone
quietly shaped you
into caring about nothing
but food, drink, and a good time?
So this isn't a coincidence.
You came here
for me, didn't you?
True,
the encounter is staged,
but this
is real.
[Treasury List of Marquis of Pingjin's Mansion]
I reviewed the books of the household.
The lady of the house, Jiang Xiang,
[Jia-xia qu] [*Drawn by the master]
quietly paid off nearly 30,000 liang
for your tabs at restaurants,
entertainment venues, and gambling houses.
Do you think she's
a rare, loving mother
or a calculating woman determined
to raise you into a failure
so her son would have
no rival?
See that note?
"Jia-xia qu."
[Jia-xia qu] [*Drawn by the master]
"Jia-xia" usually means family members,
so on the surface, the note says
you took the money.
But "jia" includes the character for pig,
so what it really says
is that a pig
took all the money.
When your family gathered to honor the ancestors,
you were out drinking.
The Marquis was disappointed and angry.
Over time,
he'll lose
all faith in you.
Was it your own choice to stay away,
or did someone make sure you would?
Mr. Zhixing,
how much longer are you going to put up
with all this humiliation?
Lady Jiang's kindness
is easy to accept
but hard to reject.
Don't you want to fight?
Fight for what?
To prove you can surpass your brother.
Do you really think
I can do it?
Of course.
Your brother's mediocre in every way.
He can't ease the Emperor's burdens.
Nor can he win hearts.
Frankly, I think
he's already peaked.
If someone like him inherits
the title of the Marquis of Pingjin,
the Zhuang family
will only decline.
But you're different.
You're bold and free-spirited,
just like the Marquis in his youth.
One day, you'll lead armies and rise to the top.
Mr. Zhixing?
Zang Hai,
no one's ever said
anything like that to me.
That makes me feel
even better than winning at the tables.
We must have a drink together.
All right.
As you wish.
Whatever you say, sir.
Good.
Here.
This is the Tusu wine I've been saving at Zhen Tower.
Have a taste.
Here.
Thank you, sir.
Cheers.
Zang Hai,
you've been looking out for me,
but I doubt
this is all for my sake.
There's something in it for you, right?
Your brother's current success
owes everything
to Jiang Xiang's support.
Even if I joined his camp,
at most I'd be
just another forgettable aide.
He'd never see me as anything more.
But with you, it's different.
You've got nothing to lose.
So why not take a chance?
You see things clearly.
My brother's already in office,
and he's my father's chosen heir.
You wouldn't get far helping him.
So you're betting on me instead.
If it pays off,
you'll win big.
You know how to gamble.
I could never match you, Mr. Zhixing.
Zang Hai,
after talking to you today,
I realize there's actually
someone in the family who cares about me.
Come on.
Here's to you.
You...
I don't hold my liquor well.
Do you think you're too good for my wine?
Of course not.
Here.
This is indeed excellent wine.
I'm good at drinking.
But I'm useless
when it comes to real work.
All I know is how to enjoy myself.
I'm afraid I'll let you down.
You underestimate yourself, sir.
You don't believe me?
Let me tell you something.
When I was a kid,
I was once locked in an underground tunnel
by a bully.
It was just one night, but I nearly died in there.
So no,
I really can't handle hardship.
That just means you're blessed, Mr. Zhixing.
Surviving disaster means there's fortune ahead.
To this day, I still remember that bully.
Back then,
when trying to find his father,
he got whipped by the Princess of Dongxia.
He also seized me
to ask about his father's whereabouts.
Do you know who his father was?
How would I know that?
His name was Kuai Duo.
He was the Imperial Astronomer back then.
But the very next day, his whole family was wiped out.
The kid died too, of course.
He had a deep wound on his back.
They said it looked like a cross
or even a sword,
just like yours.
You're not that bully, are you?
You're too funny, Mr. Zhixing.
The scars on my back?
I got them when I was a kid.
My master whipped me for slacking off.
Is that so?
I guess it's true.
After all, he's long dead.
If he'd lived,
he'd be about your age now.
He'd definitely find a way to get close to my father,
and when the time is right,
he'd kill him.
Mr. Zhixing,
you're
scaring me.
A bully and a massacre?
I don't understand a word of it.
Like I said,
I came to the Marquis's Mansion
just to find a place to settle in.
If anything were to happen to the Marquis,
it wouldn't do me any good.
Wouldn't you agree?
Maybe you're just trying to secure a future.
Or maybe
you realized you couldn't kill my father,
so you changed tactics and came after me.
Am I right...
Zhinu?
Admit it. You're Zhinu.
You didn't die back then,
and now you're back for revenge.
Mr. Zhixing,
you've had too much to drink.
I'll say it again:
You've got the wrong man.
I'm not Zhinu.
My name is Zang Hai.
If you don't believe me,
you're welcome to investigate.
I'm perfectly sober right now.
I'll tell you something.
I've remembered you ever since we first met
in the treasury.
Later, when Yang Zhen and Qu Jiao died because of you,
I started to become suspicious of you.
This Tusu wine contains lovage rhizome and cinnamon.
Drinking it brings back all the scars,
no matter how long they've faded.
Mr. Zhixing,
no one's going to believe your wild guesses.
The scars on your back
are all the proof I need.
We can go right now
and show them to my father.
No matter who you are,
no matter how good you are with words,
I doubt he'll spare you.
If you already figured it out,
why are you just telling me?
Because my father's hands
are already stained with your family's blood.
I don't want him to kill you too.
That night ten years ago,
I couldn't sleep after what you did
to me.
- Father? - So I wanted
to have my father stand up for me.
Father?
But then I got tired,
so I waited outside his room.
He came back very late.
I wanted to call out to him,
but his face was grim.
Father...
I knew
something must have happened that night.
Young Master, where are you going
this early?
To visit the Kuai family.
The Kuai family?
Young Master,
which Kuai family?
Which one do you think?
The Imperial Astronomer's. They live in the suburbs.
Their residence caught fire last night.
Everyone inside died.
But then I remembered the look
on my father's face
and the burn marks
on Yang Zhen's robes that night.
That's when I started to suspect
my father was
behind those deaths.
But I didn't dare think that.
What if it was true?
Zhinu,
I know you've had it rough these years.
I know you hate my father.
But I can't let you take revenge.
He's the only family I have left.
If you try to kill him,
I will kill you first.
Leave the Marquis's Mansion. Leave the Capital.
And never come back.
And if I can't?
You've got one day.
How did he find out?
He's smarter than I thought.
He took notice of me when we first met
in the treasury.
After I took out Yang Zhen and Qu Jiao,
he began to suspect me.
He never saw the scars on my back,
but he remembered how my senior brothers
described them.
The scars had faded,
but today at Zhen Tower,
he made me drink some medicinal wine,
and then the two scars reappeared.
I planned to deny everything,
but he threatened to take me to the Marquis.
With how suspicious the Marquis is,
I'd be dead for sure.
These problems never end. What do we do now?
Zhuang Zhixing didn't turn me in.
He pitied me and gave me one day
to leave the Marquis's Mansion and the Capital.
One day?
You're visiting the ancestral tombs with the Marquis tomorrow.
Zhuang Zhixing will be there too.
While you're there,
he'll definitely be alone at some point.
Let Guanfeng and Shilei
find a chance to kill him.
He's not a bad man. He doesn't deserve to die.
Getting soft, are you?
I'm not.
You hesitate to kill the innocent,
but did the Marquis spare anyone in your family?
Zhuang Zhixing is
just like a powder keg.
Let him live, and you risk your revenge
and your life!
I know!
I'll take care of it.
If he has to die,
I'll kill him myself.
[Late mother Shen's grave]
Mother,
I've come to see you.
The servants did
such a poor job.
They didn't pull the weeds
or refill the soil.
I'll scold them when I get back.
Are you doing well down there?
I'm fine. Don't worry about me.
Father's visiting the tombs tomorrow.
I'll ask him to stop by your grave too.
Lady Jiang treats me well.
She's never harmed me,
but she's always on guard,
trying to raise me into a useless man
so I won't compete with my brother.
But she worries too much.
I've never even thought of it.
And I ran into an old face.
I know he came back
to kill Father and avenge his family.
I told him to leave the Capital
and never come back.
Conceal the ambition in my eyes
In my palm, I hold a dangerous desire
Turbulent waves hidden in my sleeves
Silent thunder echoes around
However cunning you are
I can see
Right through you
Schemes are my armor
Overt plans are my weapons
With restrained fury
I purge the world's corruption
The night is not dark
Because
My heart burns bright
I control the shifting clouds
I command the falling rain
The compass of the human soul is unpredictable
There will always be ups and downs
I hold the power of life and death
I grant and I take away
When faith burns like the scorching sun
I will sing aloud with you
I am the sowing season
I am the autumn harvest
I am the world
I am the people
And you are also me