I heard there was a battle
in the Marquis of Pingjin Mansion last night.
Zhuang Luyin.
Cao Jingxian claimed that you wanted to kill him.
Your Majesty, please judge wisely.
If I wanted to kill Eunuch Cao,
why would I do it in my mansion?
Your Majesty, that's because I was investigating
the corruption allegation of Zhuang Zhifu, the Vice Minister of Works.
Thus, I had to investigate the Marquis Mansion.
To my surprise, the Marquis wanted to silence me.
Everyone present were witnesses.
I hope Your Majesty will be discerning.
Feng Zhang. Lu Gongchang.
- Present.
Both of you were also there last night.
Tell me about it.
Your Majesty, I was indeed there last night.
I only saw Eunuch Cao bringing his guards and giving a birthday gift to Lord Zhuang.
It was a precious blade.
I had matters to attend to. I left early.
What happened after that was...
You, tell me.
Your Majesty, I left with him last night.
However, I heard Eunuch Cao's screaming inside the mansion.
I saw him running out with an injured arm.
He also said that Lord Zhuang wanted to take his life.
Zhuang Luyin, what else do you have to say?
Your Majesty, when my son, Zhifu, was taken away by him,
he was a healthy person.
When he returned, he became a cripple with broken knees.
What was that for?
The surveillance officers interrogated Zhuang Zhifu according to the law
but he was stubborn and refused to explain everything
Hence, I tortured him.
The Vice Minister of Works, Zhuang Zhifu, admitted
to embezzling 30,000 taels of silver from the treasury.
Lord Zhuang, Eunuch Cao was merely carrying out his duty.
Why did you harm him and even tried to kill him?
Because he tried to frame me for treason.
How could I tolerate that?
I've heard about the tricks used by Eunuch Cao to eliminate his enemies.
I was shocked to witness it yesterday.
When facing such a treacherous official
who is corrupt and frames the good,
do you want me to do nothing and await my death?
One of you is the Grand Master for Glorious Happiness
and the other is the Seal-Holding Eunuch from the Directorate of Ceremonial.
Both of you even had a brawl in the capital.
Are you disrespecting me and the laws of Great Yong?
- Please calm down, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, Zhuang Zhifu admitted
that he handed over all the money he embezzled to Zhuang Luyin to raise an army.
I was anxious and afraid that he might harm Your Majesty.
Cao Jingxian broke my son's knees
and tortured a third-rank official.
How can a confession extracted from torture be trusted?
I've no intention of committing treason.
Please investigate thoroughly, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, I think the case hasn't been investigated thoroughly.
It's hard to determine whether a treacherous official has been caught
or a loyal official is being framed.
Your Majesty, please assign someone else to investigate this.
Cao Jingxian, I asked you to lead the Surveillance Office
to keep watch on the officials
and get rid of any treacherous officials for me.
It's not for you to abuse your position
to get rid of your enemies!
I know my mistake.
Zhuang Luyin.
I'm here.
You are a key official of mine.
You should be someone who stops a fight.
When you face a problem, you should come to me.
How dare you use your mansion guards to act out of personal spite?
If everyone in the capital does this,
how can I sleep in peace every night?
- I was wrong.
- Please calm down, Your Majesty.
Both of you are veterans in the imperial court.
I'm sure you know where your priorities lie.
Let me ask you again.
Is Zhuang Zhifu the sole cause of your feud here?
Your Majesty, please investigate thoroughly.
Before this case is investigated thoroughly,
Cao Jingxian will be stripped of his position as head of the Surveillance Office
to serve as a warning.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Zhuang Luyin, tell me how you should be punished.
Your Majesty,
please dismiss Zhuang Zhifu as the Vice Minister of Works
and demote him to a commoner to punish him.
However, taking into consideration that Zhifu is now a cripple,
please spare his life, Your Majesty.
I'll agree to your request and will no longer pursue this matter.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
I failed to educate my son.
That's why he committed such a grave crime.
I am at fault.
I request to retire from the imperial court.
Please approve my request, Your Majesty.
As you wish.
Foster Father, Zhuang Luyin tendered his resignation.
It seems like he has made a painful sacrifice.
He did it to stop His Majesty from doubting him.
He was really bold and nullified our attack.
Has the hostage been found?
We've searched all over the capital.
We also have men keeping a close eye on roads to Dongxia.
However, she vanished without a trace.
What about her own place?
She wasn't found in Zhen Tower or her mansion.
To prevent any suspicions,
the hostage's mansion even asked a servant to pretend to be the hostage.
Mingxiang Antu, what are you up to?
Send a letter to Dongxia.
Tell them the Gui Seal has appeared and the hostage is missing.
It has been many years. It's time for them to contribute.
Understood.
Xiao Hai, Eighth Young Master from Zhen Tower is here.
She means trouble.
What should we do?
Eighth Young Master.
Sorry for visiting suddenly and disturbing you.
You're too polite, Eighth Young Master. Please take a seat inside.
No need.
I came here today to ask you something.
Eighth Young Master, go ahead.
Antu hasn't returned since she left two nights ago.
It has been two days.
I'm worried so I dropped by here.
Do you know where she is?
Miss Xiang is missing?
What's going on?
It was she who appeared that day instead of Miss Xiang.
Lord Zang didn't show up on that day as well.
I was attending a banquet at the Marquis Mansion.
Thus, I couldn't meet Miss Xiang.
I could only send my physician to explain it to her.
I thought Miss Xiang was ill,
but she actually went out that night?
Where did she go?
You don't know where she went?
I really don't.
Two days ago, Eunuch Cao and the Marquis of Pingjin quarreled in the imperial court
and even fought at the Marquis Mansion.
This incident caused a stir.
I didn't have the time to go to Zhen Tower and apologized to Miss Xiang.
And now, you tell me that she's missing.
I'm worried, too.
Eighth Young Master, if you can think of any other possibilities,
I will help you to look for her.
I won't trouble you.
I think Antu is probably throwing a tantrum.
She does that occasionally.
We will search for her ourselves.
We'll be leaving soon.
I hope so.
Eighth Young Master, please inform me if you've found her.
Shi Lei.
I've dressed her wounds.
However, the people I trust are all men.
It's inconvenient for me to take care of her.
I had no choice but to trouble you, Master.
The wound on her body is serious,
but the wound on her heart probably hurts more.
You are really cruel to a lady.
She is my enemy.
Let me ask you.
Are you going to kill her?
I must avenge my family.
Let me go.
Otherwise...
She took Guan Feng's secret concoction of muscle relaxant powder.
She has lost strength in her limbs but it won't harm her body.
Zang Hai, I'm not who you're looking for.
This place is so empty.
How can you let a lady live comfortably here?
I'm going to get a few sets of clothes.
Have a nice chat, both of you.
Your thigh is bleeding again.
I'll ask Master to dress it for you.
Zang Hai.
I'll tell you again.
Your enemy isn't me.
I don't know anything about your parents.
You colluded with Cao Jingxian to steal the Gui Seal that night.
Your desire for the Gui Seal
caused my whole family to be annihilated ten years ago.
I returned to the capital in hopes of killing my enemy one day.
I did meet Cao Jingxian,
but it was because of the Gui Seal.
You keep saying I colluded with him
but don't forget that I helped you to kill his foster son.
If I was working with him, would you still be alive today?
Aren't you keeping me alive just to make a fool out of me?
Yes,
I am extremely foolish.
Before I clarify this,
I've no choice but to keep you here for the time being.
I am a princess of Dongxia.
Aren't you afraid your emperor will punish you for treating me like this?
Forgive me, Your Highness.
How about this? Release me
and I will help you to find your enemy.
How's that?
Since you don't believe in anything I say,
just kill me now, Lord Zang.
What do you want?
I know
you're not the mastermind behind the massacre of my family.
However, it's related to Dongxia.
I will find out the truth.
Sure.
Go and investigate.
Find out the truth before you decide to kill or release me.
But if you accuse me wrongly,
I will never spare you.
No.
Don't kill me.
Mother.
Zhifu is...
Fu'er.
I am here.
Don't be afraid.
- Mother.
- It's all right.
It's all right.
It hurts.
Don't be afraid. It's all right now.
Don't just stand there.
Call for the physician.
Physician!
He Zhi!
You are so slow!
Sorry, Young Madam.
Where's the physician? Where did he go?
Didn't I tell him to stand guard outside?
Second Young Master hasn't recovered yet.
The physician is waiting over there.
Who told you to talk back?
Summon him immediately.
Understood.
He is just an illegitimate child,
but everyone wants to fawn on him.
Mother.
- Fu'er.
- It hurts a lot.
I'm full of hatred.
I know.
Zhuang Zhixing wants to surpass you.
I won't let him do that.
Mother.
The Marquis is mighty!
Great Yong is invincible!
Father, were you looking for me?
The Marquis Mansion lost its power after this mess.
I'm also no longer an official...
and your brother has become a cripple.
Other than the title of the Marquis of Pingjin,
there's nothing much left.
Father, what can I do for this family?
If you want to have a firm foothold in the imperial court,
you must hold real power,
especially in military authority.
If I want to start anew with my current condition, it's a foolish dream.
You are the only hope of the Zhuang family.
I may be just a squad leader,
but there're still opportunities for me to achieve something.
Tomorrow, I'll make a request to the General of Wuyi to go to the border.
There's no need to go to war.
I still have other solutions.
Father, are you saying...
Zhixing,
I want you to participate in the imperial martial arts examination.
If you can become a martial arts scholar,
it's more useful than military achievements.
Martial arts scholar?
Although I've resumed martial arts training but it's still at basic level.
I fear I'm incompetent to compete with the other practitioners.
You are my son.
You just need to do your best.
Yes, Father.
The Marquis left early in the morning?
Yes. He went to Auspicious Month Tower today.
I heard he also invited a few officials from the Ministry of War.
Ministry of War?
They used to be the Marquis' retainers.
The servant that you sent to inquire has verified them.
These officials are invigilators of the imperial martial arts examination.
It seems like the Marquis is determined
to help Zhuang Zhixing become a martial arts scholar.
He no longer cares about me and my son!
My Lady, calm down. Your health is more important.
The Marquis of Pingjin asked you to join the imperial martial arts examination?
Yes. Do you think I can win?
You are cut out to practice martial arts, but you started too late.
You've only stayed in the military camp for a few months.
Although you've improved rapidly,
those who join the imperial martial arts examination
have had at least ten years of training.
It might be difficult for you to get first place.
But I still want to give it a shot.
My father's trust was once deemed unattainable.
But now that I've attained it, I realize it's not stable.
I must have a firm foothold in the imperial court.
The Zhuang family has suffered a great loss now.
If I can become a martial arts scholar,
I can make others see me and the Marquis Mansion in a new light.
It seems you're thinking further ahead than I am these days.
Did the Marquis say anything else?
He only asked me to do my best and didn't say anything else.
There's only half a month until the examination.
I will practice day and night.
The chance might be slim, but I'll seize it.
Since you're determined, you should be well-prepared.
You can't change yourself completely within half a month,
but the strategies and skills during a fight can be improved quickly.
I will tell Shi Lei to train you well.
Thank you, sir.
The first round of the examination is discourse on policies.
I'm done with the questions.
The second round of the examination is sparring.
Han Cheng versus Shi Cang.
Zheng Minglang versus Zeng Wenxuan.
Ye Xingwang versus Kang Hao.
Long Feihu versus Zhuang Zhixing.
Great! Great!
The final winners of the sparring examination
are Zhuang Zhixing and Fang Lei.
These two will compete to become the martial arts scholar
in the final round tomorrow.
The final round is horseback archery.
Whoever first brings back the brocade box hidden in a tree in the forest
will be placed first in the examination.
You followed me?
But let me tell you,
I found this first.
I'm giving this brocade box to you. I don't want it.
You're a coward.
A wise man knows when to cede.
My life is more valuable than being a martial arts scholar.
You are wrong.
Not only do I want your brocade box, but I also want your life.
Trying to become the martial arts scholar
when you're just a mere second young master?
The winner of the final round and examination is Zhuang Zhixing.
Marquis, Lord Zang is here.
Marquis.
Congratulations, Marquis.
Second Young Master has placed first in the examination.
He'll be appointed by His Majesty in the palace two days from now.
I'll host a banquet for important guests tomorrow night.
You should be here, too.
I want to show everyone that I have a successor.
Understood.
You may leave.
Marquis.
Is there anything else?
Now that Second Young Master has placed first in the examination,
he will surely become an official.
In the imperial court, a person's identity is most important.
Are you saying...
Second Young Master is an illegitimate child.
When it comes to promotion or a marriage,
he will still be inferior to others.
I'll support him as my legitimate son and establish him as the heir apparent.
It's reasonable as there's a deep father-and-son bond.
You've thought of everything, Marquis.
Tell Zhuang Shan to raise Shen Wan's status as a concurrent main wife,
and record her name in the family tree.
Find an auspicious day to relocate her grave back to the ancestral graveyard.
Understood.
Madam.
How is it?
Second Young Master is the martial arts scholar.
Fang Lei lost.
The Marquis said he wanted to make him the heir apparent.
Heir apparent?
Mother, I also want to be the heir apparent.
I also want to be the heir apparent.
Heir apparent.
Fu'er,
tell me.
What will happen to us in the future?
- Here.
- Let me raise a toast to you.
- A toast to you.
- Sure.
Congratulations, Marquis.
Congratulations, Second Young Master,
on becoming the martial arts scholar in one attempt.
Lord Huang, that's too much praise.
We still need to wait till tomorrow after His Majesty has appointed him
before he becomes the official martial arts scholar.
I heard His Majesty was very satisfied with the examination.
He even allowed you to watch the ceremony tomorrow.
In my opinion, it won't be long until you are reinstated.
Thank you, Lord Huang, for your nice words.
Please.
Zhixing, quickly offer a toast to everyone.
In the future, you'll need their support in the imperial court.
I am offering a toast to everyone.
If you need my help in the future, just ask.
- Cheers, Second Young Master.
Zhuang Shan!
Marquis.
Zhixing.
I wore this armor when I defeated Dongxia back then.
From now on,
I'm handing it over to you.
The Zhuang family is who we are today,
because of our ability in war.
Every military achievement was exchanged with fresh blood.
It is the same for every head of the family.
From now on, you're the heir apparent of the Marquis Mansion.
Whether it's in the imperial court or the army,
don't let the ancestors of the Zhuang family lose their dignity.
Father, I will not let you down...
and will bring glory to the Zhuang family!
- Congratulations, Heir Apparent.
Everyone, let's drink.
- Thank you, Marquis.
Zhixing, come to my room at the hour of Hai tonight.
(Between 9:00 - 11:00 p.m.)
I have something to tell you.
All right.
Let's drink.
- Sure.
- Cheers.
Cheers.
I should thank you the most for what I've achieved today.
You should thank yourself the most.
Ancestors of the Zhuang family,
I seek your blessing and protection.
Please bless Zhifu for his quick recovery.
Don't let him continue to be clueless and foolish.
Everything that's happening out there today should belong to Zhifu.
Even if I did something wrong in the past,
I should be punished instead.
Zhifu is innocent.
He is the legitimate son of the Zhuang family.
If he can recover soon,
he will regain the Marquis' favor.
Ancestors, please bless and protect my son.
Madam.
Why is this slut's memorial tablet placed here?
Someone!
What's going on with this memorial tablet?
This was instructed by the Marquis.
He instructed her name to be added to the family tree.
He said she...
She's the mother of the heir apparent.
She's what?
He said she's the mother of the heir apparent.
The heir apparent is the legitimate son.
Madam.
"It's me" - Sun Nan
♫  I conceal the ambition in my eyes  ♫
♫  In my palm, I hold a dangerous desire  ♫
♫  Turbulent waves hide in my sleeves  ♫
♫  Silent like the clap of thunder  ♫
♫  The depth of shrewdness  ♫
♫  Can’t escape  ♫
♫  My sharp eyes  ♫
♫  Conspiracies are my armor  ♫
♫  Overt plans are my sword and spear  ♫
♫  With stoic madness  ♫
♫  I cleanse the filth of the world  ♫
♫  The night is not dark  ♫
♫  Because  ♫
♫  My heart is burning bright  ♫
♫  I’m the turning clouds  ♫
♫  I’m the falling rain  ♫
♫  The compass of the human soul is unpredictable  ♫
♫  There will always be people who rise and fall  ♫
♫  I am life and death  ♫
♫  I grant and deprive  ♫
♫  When faith burns like the scorching sun  ♫
♫  I will sing loudly with you  ♫
♫  I am the sowing season  ♫
♫  I am the autumn harvest  ♫
♫  I am the kingdom  ♫
♫  I’m the commoner  ♫
♫  You’re also me  ♫