♫ Let the past stay in the past, let
Your real feelings evolve ♫
♫ The determination between your brows
Cannot be allowed to break down ♫
♫ Precise calculations, invisible armor ♫
♫ Get equipped well, the tanks are setting off immediately ♫
♫ The goals were originally invisible,
How do you realize the dream of reaching the stars ♫
♫ How far and wide is it from the beginning to the end? ♫
♫ Making it through all the difficulties is so thrilling,
Breaking through layers of encirclement ♫
♫ The future is realized step-by-step in the game ♫
♫ Dreams of horses, the world is so complex ♫
♫ A simple heart is the answer ♫
♫ Step-by-step, we set off.
The map points towards the end of the world ♫
♫ Some day, we'll finally arrive ♫
♫ Distant roads ♫
♫ So moving ♫
♫ Every footstep ♫
[GO Into Your Heart]
[Episode 17]
Dad.
Zhiliao, you got me new clothes?
I love this style. Look!
It fits just right. The only problem is that it's a bit short.
- No...no, no. It's not yours. Take it off.
- What are you doing?
No, I love it!
Even if you like it, take it off, Dad.
Why do I have to take it off? I like it. Why should I take it off?
I know you like it, but it will get dirty.
But I haven't had shirts fit this well for years.
I will buy you a new one if you like it, but I need to keep this one clean!
Zhiliao, you are a big girl now. Look at you getting me gifts.
Is it expensive? I can pay you back.
Dad, I don't want to lie to you.
This shirt is not for you.
Huh? Not for me? Who is it for then?
I didn't buy it. It's Sheng Jingchu's shirt.
Did you buy it for Sheng Jingchu?
It is Sheng Jingchu's shirt.
It was raining yesterday.
I got wet so I changed at his place.
I washed it last night and hung it up.
Then... where're your clothes?
At his place.
You... You guys are already...
No, we haven't thought it through.
If you haven't thought it through, why did you leave your clothes at his place
and wear his back?
I am open-minded, but you can't...
What are you talking about, Dad?
Look at you. You got the shirt dirty and now I have to rewash it.
- Wait...
- Gosh!
[Uncle Cheng's Eatery]
Uncle Cheng,
are you cooking something magical?
Sir-fried garlic peel?
- It's over.
- Huh?
Everything's over.
I raised her for 24 years and why did she stop listening to me?
What are you talking about?
She said they are nothing yet and she wore his shirt back.
My heart...
24 years...
You are talking about Cheng Liao, right?
Of course! She wore Sheng Jingchu's shirt back and
left her own clothes there. What was that supposed to mean?
It was raining yesterday.
Her clothes probably got wet.
Isn't it normal to wear dry clothes?
How is it normal?
She doesn't come home when it's raining and borrow clothes at someone else's place?
I'm her father. She can't hide anything from me.
I kept asking her questions this morning.
She couldn't look me in my eyes. She must feel guilty about something.
Uncle Cheng, she's 24 already.
Not a kid anymore. Also,
it's Sheng Jingchu we are talking about.
The GO master!
What's with being a master? And Cheng Liao is my daughter!
You can't be this conservative.
I'm not conservative!
If they are really in a relationship, of course I would agree to it.
But they aren't a couple yet, shouldn't I feel bad?
How should I feel then?
Uncle Cheng, I think you are overthinking this.
Shut up and get back to work! You are annoying me.
Uncle Cheng, it's fine you are peeling the garlic, but could you leave the actual garlic and not the skin?
Stop talking.
If you know other things, you might be even crazier.
What did you say?
Nothing.
I remember it used to be a beach here when we were kids.
We came here and made sandcastles here often.
Zhiliao used to mess with us when we were building.
Every time her castle got hit by the waves, she would sit there and cry.
And then you would go buy her cake.
But I always bought two.
I want to talk to you about the offer.
When should I tell my HR?
I decided not to accept the offer.
Why did you change your mind again?
You know me.
If I leave now,
I would feel like
a deserter, even like a loser.
I hate losing.
You can prove yourself with new shows
when you join Pinecone Video.
But "Conversing with Cheng Yi" will be a failure.
I created a show called "The One Knight."
But I didn't end up making it.
Now, I'm planning a new show called "Reaching Success."
"Reaching Success."
The name is intriguing.
Yes.
Most of the time,
we focus on those who are already successful.
There are others
who are only one step away from success,
yet they pause.
These people might be suffering and don't want to give up,
but they are not negative.
Therefore, I think the stories behind them are worth discovering
and worth telling.
I want to hear about it first.
Also, this is a great idea.
That's why I think this pitch could get a green light.
Just let me have one more try.
I want to draw a period
and leave with content.
I will be waiting in Pinecone for you patiently.
Actually, I've been very anxious.
What's wrong?
I feel like time is passing too slow.
Thinking about going to work, eating, and getting off work with you,
I start to wish time would pass faster,
but I will always respect your decision.
I support you in making "Reaching Success"
and come to me with no regrets.
Here's an early gift for the show.
I'm not a kid. I didn't just graduate.
Why would you give this to me?
But this is different.
This is for a new start between us.
And I want to hold your hand.
Old Xu, did you give me the job offer for this?
Don't misunderstand.
I will always put your career first.
Seeing you every day
is just a little extra gift for me.
Don't take it off. It's just a small gift.
Let's go back.
I still have to polish the pitch.
May I take a look at your pitch?
Of course. Once I'm done polishing it, I'll send it to you.
Let's go.
[Binghai TV Station]
Xiao Cheng, come sit.
Director Gao, have you looked at the new pitch?
What do you think?
You haven't had the time to read it yet?
Truthfully, I didn't read it.
I didn't report it to the station, either.
Why? Was it because of funding?
I've known you for a long time.
I'll tell you directly then.
Funding is part of the problem.
But the station values image more.
It impacts society.
You know your own problems as well.
After your scandalous issue,
the station executives made it clear
that "Cheng Yi's Conversations"
will no longer be broadcast again.
Unless,
the host changes.
Station Chief Gao,
is that really necessary?
"Cheng Yi's Conversations" is
a show more about the people's livelihood and society news.
Its impact on society will be substantial.
The hosts' image, of course, is very important.
I've tried to find some time and convince executives.
But it still wasn't successful.
To say this, my heart doesn't feel any better.
That's why I haven't talked to you lately.
Since we're talking about it today, I'll be straightforward and tell you everything.
Xiao Cheng,
I'm afraid you'll have to prepare yourself
to say goodbye
to "Cheng Yi's Conversations."
Xiao Cheng. Xiao Cheng?
♫ The sky has faded ♫
Hello, Sister Yi
♫ Maybe it's better to leave ♫
♫ In whose eyes are you ♫
♫ A quiet, pure, beautiful, accident ♫
♫ Even the wind slowed down ♫
I'm afraid you have to prepare yourself
to say goodbye to "Cheng Yi's Conversations".
♫ If you keep loneliness outside of life ♫
♫ How can it bloom ♫
♫ Letting go of your hand gently, floating in the sea of ​​people ♫
[Road to Success Show Proposal]
♫ A whole world isn't willing to wake up ♫
♫ All that's left is loneliness lingering in the wind like dust
♫ Helplessly borne about by the wind ♫
♫ Letting go of your hand gently, floating in the sea of ​​people ♫
♫ Waiting for someone to lift the haze of dreams ♫
♫ In whose  ♫
♫  world  ♫
♫ do we start over?  ♫
Why did you drink so much?
He was feeling low and wanted me to drink with him.
In the end, he got himself drunk.
Because of what?
Because he found out Sister Cheng Liao and Sheng Jingchu are dating.
He couldn't accept it.
Let him sleep awhile then.
Can you drink a bit more?
You know my alcohol tolerance.
Sister, what's wrong?
Okay, let's make rules for drinking tonight.
Chatting is okay but you can't ask me any questions.
Not a problem. I'm your cute little invincible garbage can.
You can tell me anything at any time.
Put your hands down.
When you came back from abroad,
did you feel reluctant?
I didn't because the land here is my home.
This was different from when I went abroad as a child.
I thought about all of my friends,
my neighbors, and relatives that I wouldn't be able to see for a long time.
I felt pretty upset.
I even cried on the plane.
To leave a place
is indeed a tough thing.
Whether it's going abroad, transferring schools,
moving houses, or
resigning.
They are all heartbreaking.
Humans are emotional animals.
Staying in a place too long, you can't help but become emotionally attached.
Even if there is a lot of unhappiness,
you can't bear to part.
- Sister, then why don't you decide...
- We agreed, no asking.
Even though I'm afraid to ask, I still have to say what I think.
No matter how much you don't want to part,
if you're no longer happy,
then you must choose to leave.
Twenty-four years...
and you said before...
[She De Spirit]
(TN: She De is produced by a Sichuan liquor company but here She De can be described as 'willingly' to part.)
[Uncle Cheng's Restaurant]
Hi, Mr. Sheng.
Mr. Sheng, you are...
This is my job. How come you are doing it.
Oh, this is a women's style. Is it Journalist Cheng's?
Not bad! You two progressed to this step already.
You're speaking too much.
- What's the situation?
- You're not allowed to ask.
Okay, I won't ask anymore. I have something serious to ask you about.
This Saturday, there is an event promoting GO.
It's for kids who like Go.
It'll be some introductory topics. The event staff asked Jiuzhou Hall.
Guess what the result was.
Everyone, even Master Xie, recommended you to attend.
Here is the event's invitation.
Also, some event materials. Take a look.
They're doing it on purpose.
They know I'm not good at expressing, and
they want me to attend. This event is more appropriate for Xihe.
Then I'll directly decline it for you.
Yes.
I'll grab the door.
Who is it?
Isn't this Teacher Cheng?
- Hello.
It's clean now.
That's enough, you two. Acting like I'm not here.
Here, give it to me. I'll put it back for you.
I won't bother you.
Why are they like my dad?
Really annoying.
What's wrong with Uncle?
Nothing really.
[Invitation: GO Promoting Event Plan]
Are you giving a class to people? Can I go and listen?
You want to go?
To be able to listen to your lecture, it's more than I could wish for.
- Okay, we can go together.
- Hey!
Didn't you just say that you didn't want to attend?
When did I say I didn't want to attend?
Stop right there.
Do you have anything to tell me?
I don't.
Sit down.
Today, if you don't explain it clearly, you're not going anywhere.
Go ahead. What's the problem?
When did you start dating Sheng Jingchu?
- We're not dating.
- You're not dating and you wore his clothes home?
- What's wrong with that?
- What do you mean what's wrong?
You're a girl. Your mom passed away early.
There is no one to teach you these things, and I can't properly explain them.
You have to know how to protect yourself.
At least, establish that you are in a "dating" relationship.
Bring him home so I can meet him. This is a procedure problem, all right?
- You have to give me some respect, okay?
- Dad,
we haven't started dating yet. Give me some time so I can calmly think about it.
It's okay if you haven't started dating yet. Bring him home and we can get to know him together. Okay?
Dad, can you stop pestering? I'm tired. I'm going to sleep.
I find that you don't listen to me anymore.
- I'm telling you! I've seen more people than the roads you've walked or the food you've eaten.
- Hey! Hey! What are you trying to do?
Let me tell you. I'm going to teach her properly today.
Teach her what?
Zhiliao is no longer in high school. She's an adult. Who she wants to date is her freedom.
- Don't you go causing trouble.
- This is a major issue, not some small one.
Hey! Hey! What are you doing? You're going into her room?
I'm her father. Why can't I?
Her mother can't enter. That's her own personal space.
- I don't care about that much.
- Cheng Fengshou.
Let me say this again. You are not allowed to enter her room.
One.
Two.
Come in.
Where is Old Cheng?
Don't worry about him.
Listen, I won't give you too much advice either.
You've grown up. This is your own love life.
Whatever you want to do, it's your own choice.
Anyway, no matter what, I will support you.
Older Sister is still the best.
Is Old Cheng okay?
What could happen to him?
He fought with us for this many years. He should have built up his endurance.
Don't worry. Get some sleep.
Change into your pajamas. Be careful of dark eye circles.
Bye-bye.
- Good night.
Too troublesome. Really troublesome...
You don't know him well enough?
Who have you gotten to know well enough?
Who can you know well enough?
By the time you've gotten to know him, it'll be too late to do anything.
No.
Should I do it myself?
I should do it myself.
Going out? Where are you going dressed like that?
I'm going to attend an event where they teach kids how to play GO.
- Bye-bye.
- Okay.
Let's go.
I know even if it's the precious seat, I should wear my seatbelt.
It's that white one. Driver, hurry.
I can't see it.
Driver, why are we taking this route?
There's traffic ahead. If we take An Ning Road, it will be faster.
[Anning Rd]
What's wrong?
- What's wrong?
- Stop the car! Stop the car!
Driver, stop the car! Driver, stop the car!
What's wrong?
It's okay. Everything's fine.
Everything's okay.
GO God, are you feeling better now?
If not,
I'll tell them and we can do it on a different day.
GO God?
It's okay.
Hello, can we can start now?
Hello.
Why don't I talk with the kids a bit?
When the atmosphere is better, we'll start.
Okay, I understand.
Kids, do you like to play GO?
Yes!
Then do you know, who he is?
Sheng Jingchu.
If you have any questions, you can ask them now.
You want an autograph from him?
Come.
Go away. Get out of the way. I don't want to see you.
I'll explain to you later.
Stop right there.
Apologize right away to the child. Apologize right now!
- Dad, let him through.
- How can he treat a child like that?
- Dad, don't say so much. He's not that kind of person. I believe him. I believe him.
- He should apologize!
You leave first.
Wait, Zhiliao.
Dad, now is not the time. I'll explain it once I come back.
I... I...
Zhiliao!
[Sunac: A Tour Town, A Tour A Life]
Can you tell me
what happened today?
Does it have to do with that intersection?
That day,
I just won the Rubik's Cube tournament trophy.
My parents were taking me home.
[Anning Rd]
- Are you okay?
- I'm fine.
Are you okay, Jingchu?
You still don't have anything to say?
Dad, you've mistook him. There was an unexpected situation today.
I don't care about some unexpected situation!
He shouldn't treat a child from an orphanage like that.
He's not like that normally. You don't know him well enough.
In just one afternoon, I already know him.
I'm telling you now, break up with him. In the future, don't ever see him again.
If you're not going to listen to my explanation, then forget it.
Cheng Liao, how much do you have to suffer before you will regret it?
Dad, if you don't understand someone well enough, don't easily judge them. Stop involving yourself.
You must listen to me on this.
I'm not going to.
I'll say it one more time. I'm not going to listen. You can stay out of this issue.
What is going on?
Go back to your room.
- Stop right there, Cheng Liao!
- Enough, Dad!
- Stop there, Cheng Liao!
Calm down.
She worries me so much!
Stop it, Dad.
What was it? What's with the fuss?
Am I still her father?
Seeing my daughter being taken advantage of and I can't stop her!
Oh, that.
All right. Don't you know Zhiliao?
She looks like a cat, but she has a tiger's temper.
You need to reason with her.
I will talk to her for you, all right?
I'll educate her for you.
She is getting worse as she gets older.
So worrisome.
All right, stop being mad.
I will drink with you when I'm done with her.
You take it easy.
Look who's crying.
He wanted to hit me.
He didn't hit you, did he?
But he shouldn't be mean to me like that.
He doesn't love me anymore.
You always thought he preferred me over you.
But he only praises me with words.
But who did he hide all the snacks for?
You got all of that, didn't you?
Old Cheng cares about you the most.
But he can't talk about Sheng Jingchu like that. He had his reasons, too.
That's right. That old man is so stubborn.
It's okay. I will yell at him later.
Don't cry, don't cry. And you are crying even more.
All right! All right! Did you know how expensive the foundation I gave you was? Just this layer
is at least ¥8.8. And you just cried off ¥2.5. Think about that.
I'll stop crying.
You look so ugly now. Just keep crying.
You make me so angry! Are you my sister or not?
And you're laughing at me?
[Reaching Success]
Uncle Cheng, are you not busy?
Xiao Xu, come sit.
Why are you bringing gifts? That's so extra.
I'm just here to see you. What's wrong?
Don't mention it. I'm having a toothache.
Who made you mad? Tell me.
Who else? It's our Zhiliao, of course.
She doesn't listen to me.
You just can't keep a daughter.
You're... upset about that?
Of course.
I should come another time then.
Why did you come today?
I... I'm afraid I will anger you even more.
There's no need to hide it from me. Just say it.
I... I like Cheng Yi.
What? Really?
- Don't be angry, Uncle Cheng!
- I'm not angry.
I'm happy about it!
Look! I knew you liked Xiao Yi all these years.
But you never said anything and I thought I was wrong about it.
You... you hid yourself so well.
Uncle Cheng, to be honest,
I came back for Xiao Yi this time.
I came to you today to ask for your permission.
You have my permission! You have my full permission!
What permission?
Permission for you two.
Look... You guys grew up together and both of you are outstanding.
I saw Little Xu Chi growing up and I know him well.
That's why, give me your hand.
I'm very happy about you guys!
Cheng Fengshou!
You don't have a toothache anymore?
Come with me.
Go, go!
It still hurts, my dear! But I'm happy.
Old Xu,
you can't take jokes seriously.
I'm not joking. I meant everything I said.
Xiao Yi, why does everyone think that we should be together,
but not you?
Old Xu...
Okay, let's not talk about it.
I've read your pitch. It's great.
I believe this one can draw a perfect period for "Conversing with Cheng Yi."
You can do it.
I will be waiting for you at Pinecone Video.
I have to go.
[Uncle Cheng's Eatery]
Are you working in Uncle Cheng's restaurant?
Do you feel threatened that I'm close to her now?
How do you know you are closer to her than I am?
I'm afraid that it wouldn't work out even if you worked here for the rest of your life.
I've been anxious lately.
I feel like that time passes too slow.
Whenever I think about going to work, eating, and getting off work with you,
I start hoping time can pass faster.
But I will always respect your decisions.
I support your decision in making "Reaching Success"
and come to me with no regrets.
The two of you grew up together and are both outstanding.
I watched Little Xu Chi growing up and I know him well.
I'm happy about you guys!
I've read the pitch. It's great.
I believe this episode can draw the perfect period for "Conversing with Cheng Yi."
You can do it.
I will be waiting for you at Pinecone Video.
I have to go.
Cheng Yi.
When you get this email, two years have gone by.
Have you become a better host?
Did you make the show
that has warmth and depth?
[For Myself In Two Years]
[Reaching Success]
♫ The wind blows,
The moonlight breaks through the sea of clouds ♫
♫ The butterflies are like you, understanding clearly ♫
♫ The sounds as summer nights awaken ♫
♫ Black, white, dissipating colors ♫
♫ Reaching out, but can't touch it ♫
♫ That which was beautiful, but long forgotten ♫
♫ Because you started to dance ♫
♫ Your appearance lit up my world ♫
♫ Warmed my rainy nights, called out and made me see ♫
♫ That life is like a butterfly, breaking out of the cocoon
And flying far because of your talent ♫
♫ Flying out from the barren adversity ♫
♫ I want to respond to all the good you've given me ♫
♫ The clouds float by and hide the sun's brilliance ♫
♫ Waiting for the endless rainy season ♫
♫ All of summer is conversing ♫
♫ Sweet, bitter, it's all unknown ♫
♫ There is color all around you ♫
♫ Even if going against the wind, you won't back down ♫
♫ It was you who gave me new strength ♫
♫ Found the memories of the smells again ♫
♫ Saying a prayer for love ♫
♫ Your appearance lit up my world ♫
♫ Warmed my rainy nights, called out and made me see ♫
♫ That life is like a butterfly, breaking out of the cocoon
And flying far because of your talent ♫
♫ Your existence woke up my past ♫
♫ Embraced my future, taught me to become aware ♫
♫ No one is a lonely island, running aginst the wind with me ♫
♫ Little dreams are flying high ♫
♫ You're my most important treasure ♫