♫ Let the past stay in the past,
let your real feelings evolve ♫
♫ The determination between your brows
cannot be allowed to break down ♫
♫ Precise calculations, invisible armor ♫
♫ Get equipped well, the tanks are setting off immediately ♫
♫ The goals were originally invisible,
how do you realize the dream of reaching the stars ♫
♫ How far and wide is it from the beginning to the end? ♫
♫ Making it through all the difficulties is so thrilling,
breaking through layers of encirclement ♫
♫ The future is realized step-by-step in the game ♫
♫ Dreams of horses, the world is so complex ♫
♫ A simple heart is the answer ♫
♫ Step-by-step, we set off.
The map points towards the end of the world ♫
♫ Some day, we'll finally arrive ♫
♫ Distant roads ♫
♫ So moving ♫
♫ Every footstep ♫
[GO Into Your Heart]
[Episode 35]
[Pinecone Video]
In this China-Korea GO Invitational Competition,
regardless of winning or losing, Sheng Jingchu
will ignite a new round of heated discussions.
Everyone is familiar with Sheng Jingchu already.
So, I won't introduce him much.
The most important segment for today is this.
I, Jiang Yuda, sincerely invite Miss Cheng Yi for dinner today at 7:00 p.m. sharp.
There's something very important, so please accept it.
What kind of trick is this?
This rascal can't be confessing to me just because of the kiss last time?
Miss Cheng, you are an expert in this area.
I'd like to hear your thoughts and suggestions on this.
Miss Cheng?
Cheng Yi.
Sorry, what were we talking about?
Cheng Yi, we were just talking about hoping to get
Sheng Jingchu's interview after the competition.
But this probably depends on you.
I think we should wait and see how the competition turns out first.
If he still performs abnormally this time,
I'm not interested in reporting gossip to get ahead.
But if he performs outstandingly well,
I think an interview would be meaningful and worthwhile.
This is about everything for today.
Everyone can go back to their own work.
Okay, VP Xu.
You don't really look well today.
Have you been working too hard at thinking about the new program?
I'm fine.
Let's do this. You should go back in a while to get some good rest.
I'll give you a ride.
I still have something to do. I'm leaving first.
Looking at this posture, he really wants to confess.
There's nothing to fear. You've seen enough confessions.
Whatever he says, just be poised and refuse him.
Didn't you send a WeChat message to say there's something important?
Why is your face red? Are you sick?
What are you doing? If there isn't anything, I'm leaving.
No!
I really have something very, very important to tell you.
Let's sit down and talk.
What serious matter is it? Can you tell me now?
I'm probably going back on my word.
I can't keep staying by your side.
- You like someone else?
- No.
Absolutely not. You mustn't misunderstand.
In my eyes, in my heart, there is only you.
I can't even see anyone else.
However, the national amateur championship is about to start.
The winner can directly advance to professional first dan.
I've been working hard to prepare in order to win.
Therefore, I won't be available on demand.
Professional first dan?
As Sheng Jingchu's first disciple,
I can't continue to wear the title of amateur 7-dan and never go forward.
If I can win this championship,
I can officially join the professional players
and take a great leap forward in my GO career.
After such a long time living here,
I have finally reached the moment to inspect my achievement.
For Master,
and even more, for you,
I must change my amateur level to a real dan level.
This sounds good. It's a good thing.
Chatting with me is really not that important.
Of course, it's important.
Even though I can't come on demand,
but my heart...
will be with you every minute and every second.
You must wait for me.
Wait.
You'd better look at it when you get back.
Eat first.
Cheers.
♪ I don't care as long as you ♪
♪ are there. It's great... ♪
♫ to be loved  ♫
♫ on Valentine's day. So happy  ♫
Sister Goddess, during this time when we can't see each other often,
just let this little tree stump stay by your side.
Please don't forget me.
I really like you very, very much.
♫ by you ♫
♫ on Valentine's Day  ♫
Let's see how many likes
my Little Fox Private Kitchen has.
There are so many comments.
You're pretty, and your cooking skill is good.
The video explanation is clear.
Simple and easy to understand.
I hope all the viewer friends who have met me through the cooking competition
will like it and succeed in cooking it.
Thanks, everyone!
A woman who causes trouble. A silly girl
with a stupid brain, you affected GO God's game.
Please let go of our baby.
Panda loses and you all get angry.
Who have my clams offended?
No. I've got to vent steam even if I'm not steaming the buns.
I need to speak up for my clams.
You all don't like it that Sheng Jingchu and I are dating.
But the food is innocent.
I'm sharing good food out of kindness.
Those viewers who want to learn cooking from the video
shouldn't be disturbed like this.
I hope everyone will speak reasonably.
Please don't vent your own agitated emotions inappropriately.
Right now, it's a pivotal moment for Panda to adjust himself.
These people online were already unstable.
I can't provoke them even more.
If it's getting worse and Panda sees it,
he would worry.
Hey, Panda, what's the matter?
Why aren't you talking?
Liao Liao, tell me honestly.
Are you in a bad mood?
No.
You have no idea how happy I am in seeing you.
I'll take you to eat something good tomorrow.
I haven't seen you all day and I miss you.
We probably can't see each other every day for a while.
Why?
Because I'm busy with my career now.
This happens to be the crucial time for Little Fox 2.0 to go online.
Are you also studying your new game style?
In martial arts stories,
the leading characters have to enter seclusion to improve their skills.
So you want to enter seclusion
and you also want to send me into seclusion?
It's the crucial time right now for the China-Korea GO Invitational competition.
You should practice GO at home.
Once the competition is over, we will relax well together.
Since Little Fox is so thoughtful for me,
okay then. I will do my best.
Bye-bye.
The Xingya Cup GO Championship successfully concluded yesterday.
Sheng Jingchu, 9-dan, who was originally expected to win
is suspected of being affected by his love life,
continued his downturn from the GO League's Nanjing competition.
He was out in the first round.
On the other hand, player Yao Ke who relied on his steady and stronger strength
battled against strong opposition to lead Jiuzhou Hall to victory
in the GO League competition in Nanjing, once again won the championship at Xingya Cup.
For Yao Ke, this is the first time in 10 years where he is in the same competition with Sheng Jingchu
and has won the championship.
Brother!
Brother, do you know that
the news about your win is being broadcast everywhere.
Look at this one. I even saw it at the supermarket.
Look! This is awesome, Brother.
[Certificate of Honor]
Sheng Jingchu, Sheng Jingchu.
Your name won't appear on my news anymore.
Come in.
Older Sister.
What's the matter?
Cheng Fengshou dispatched me to deliver a cup of juice to you.
Thank you.
Actually, he saw that the news on TV and online
were all about Sheng Jingchu getting out of the game early at the Xingya Cup Championship
and Yao Ke winning the championship,
so he's a little worried and asked me to come to ask you about it.
Older Sis, tell Dad not to worry. Panda is fine.
Actually, it's not just Dad,
I'm a little worried, too.
It's really okay. Don't worry.
I'm not worried about Sheng Jingchu.
I'm worried that if it continues like this, the public opinion will change directions.
The China-Korean Invitation competition is about to start.
I'm worried... I'm worried that some people will target you.
Older Sis, I've been in the media industry before.
I know about public opinion.
Those people who posted and attacked online
simply saw some one-sided news and arbitrarily made conclusions.
And then? They start to enjoy the feeling of
being above other people to decide the world.
When I think about it, I pity them.
So, whatever they say won't affect me at all.
My little girl, you're quite elevated in your mental state now.
If you suffer some mistreatment, don't hide it from me.
Actually, I am a little scared.
Why? Scared of what?
I'm not scared of those online people who talk about me.
I'm scared that Panda will waste his energy because of me.
You don't have to worry about that.
Sheng Jingchu is already an adult.
If he can't even handle this,
how can he be an outstanding GO player?
Therefore, I've decided already.
I'm going to see him as little as possible before his competition.
Won't you miss him?
Of course, I'll miss him.
But this invitational competition is really important to him.
Therefore, I just need to wait until he succeeds in his cultivation.
This is so hard on our Zhiliao.
Drink the juice and go to bed early, okay?
It's so hard for this child.
How is the preparation for the national amateur championship?
After eating, I've hurried back to practice.
Is it really difficult to win the championship?
Yes, there are many expert players, but I can't help it.
I've missed the ranking match in the summer.
I heard that it's only a 10% probability to pass the ranking match, then you will only have 1% probability?
That's about right. But I'm still quite confident.
Even if it's only a one percent chance,
I won't give it up.
If you are tired during the preparation for the competition
or when you are unhappy, you can think of me as your little tree stump, too.
Consider it as my reciprocating your favor.
My mental state is perfectly fine.
Don't worry. It's getting late.
You should rest early, and I'll continue practicing.
Goodnight.
Jiang Yuda, defeat them.
If you don't win, don't come back to see me.
Yes, Sir!
♪ And if the stars go out tonight ♪
♪ I don't care as long as you are there ♪
♪ It's great to be loved on Valentine's ♪
Sister Goddess, during this time when we can't see each other often,
just let this little tree stump stay by your side.
You must not forget me. I truly like you very, very much.
♫ And it's to wonder  ♫
♪ To be loved by you ♪
[Jiuzhou Hall]
Master, I still haven't really found
the most effective method to balance and utilize every stone on the game board.
Jingchu, the road is wide and endless.
It reaches everywhere, up, down, left, and right.
It's actually the same on the game board.
Look at the game board. It has 19 roads horizontally and vertically.
361 intersecting points.
Isn't this a small universe in this square world?
Within it, it contains the cycle of the four seasons,
the intricate balance of mutual support.
Ever since ancient times, the Chinese have regarded
most highly the harmonious coordination between Heaven and Earth, Yin and Yang.
You were saying that you wanted to find the best way.
Actually, it's to find the innate harmony
in this game.
As long as you make the appropriate decision
at the appropriate time and appropriate location,
even if it's the most common game layout,
you can receive a surprising transformation.
Why haven't they released the opposing list for the China-Korea Invitational Competition?
Xiao Lan, you are not in this competition, why are you so nervous?
I'm nervous for you.
This competition is the last one this year and also the most important competition.
Even South Korea's Master Cho Shen Woo has returned to compete.
He's Master's fierce enemy, Oppa Jo Yeon Hoon's Master.
Oppa Yeon Hoon will also compete this time, too.
Did you forget whenever you play against him, what the result always is?
What's wrong?
Xiao Lan, you already have a boyfriend now.
Can you not call someone else "Oppa"?
I'm used to it.
This habit is very bad. You should change it.
I won't.
If you won't, you won't.
Hey.
You didn't hear the key point of what I said!
What if you end up playing against Jo Yeon Hoon again?
It's fine if I do. As long as you don't keep calling him "Oppa,"
I definitely won't lose.
- Is that a promise?
- Yes.
Give me a charge.
It's not fully charged. I want one more here.
Do you want to recharge? 20,000 milliamperes, take your time.
Hurry and eat. The food is getting cold.
It's released. It's released.
Master is playing against South Korea's new star Li Yongzhe.
Senior Brother Jing is playing against Master Cho Shen Woo.
Junior Brother Yao Ke is playing against Eldest Senior Brother.
You...
[Jo Yeon Hoon vs. Cao Xihe]
Sheng Jingchu, long time no see!
Why are you here?
It's the China-Korea GO Invitational, so I have to come.
I know that. What I meant was, why are you here at my front door?
It's because I can't forget it. I can't forget
eating with you, sleeping with you,
and playing GO together. Such beautiful times!
Where should I put this plate?
Let's put it here.
Okay, let's eat.
First of all, thanks to player Sheng Jingchu to give me a chance to repay you.
Don't worry. These materials, decorations,
and the pots... I brought them all from South Korea.
I didn't touch anything in your house.
Even that greenhouse that you cherish the most, I didn't get close to it at all.
Don't worry.
Okay. Let's do as we agreed.
After we eat, you leave immediately.
That's not the key point. The key point is, you must accept my apology.
Drink up this rice wine first.
Cheers!
The second up is to appreciate your taking me in last time.
Oh no, I can't drink anymore.
I can't leave. I can't leave. Jo Yeon Hoon won't leave.
No way.
Mr. Sheng Jingchu! Mr. Sheng Jingchu!
Please let me stay here.
It's such a large place.
No way.
If you insist on making me leave, I'll be forced to wander the streets of China.
I also drank so much wine. What if I get kidnapped by bad people?
Shut up.
What?
You can stay then.
Really? Really?
Really?
Then, I won't be sleeping on this sofa this time.
I'm going into that room!
Your slippers.
You can have them!
Brother, what are you looking at? You're so happy.
The results of the drawing are released.
Xie Chang'an? You're facing him in the first round, Brother?
He is the famous first-round only.
My Eldest Senior Brother.
Sheng Jingchu,
your good days are ending.
My good luck is coming.
Liao Liao.
[Baduk - (GO in Korean)]
Is Jo Yeon Hoon really going to stay here?
He won't leave.
I'm suspicious that he secretly exchanged tips on how to be shameless with Mr. Katou.
Actually, I felt a little guilty about kicking him out last time.
Where is he now?
He heard that you're coming, so he went to the market to shop for groceries.
He said he's making an authentic Korean BBQ for you.
He even knows where the grocery market is now.
It seems that he will be doing much work here.
But... won't he affect you when he's living here?
Aren't you facing Master Cho Shen Woo in the first round?
It's actually not bad.
He can play a game with me every day. After all,
he's Cho Shen Woo's disciple.
Liao Liao, speaking of the competition.
On that day, I hope that you won't go to the competition site.
Why not?
I've resisted for a long time not to disturb your practice. I really want to go to such an important competition.
It's because it's really important,
that's why you cannot show up.
Liao Liao, I will be playing against South Korea's Master Cho Shen Woo.
It's different from other players in this country.
It's fine if I win.
But if I lose and you are at the site,
you would definitely become the target of all the media.
I don't care.
I do.
Think of it as for my sake.
Then you must promise me to take good care of yourself.
In a while, obediently finish drinking this soup.
I promise I'll drink all of it.
Wait.
I bought meat. You're drinking soup tonight?
That's all you wear in the winter? Aren't you cold?
No, but what do I do with all the meat I bought?
Easy. Leave it to me.
I'll make some marinated braised meat. I'll make him one piece a day.
Anyways, the person who fed him before has always been me.
Sheng Jingchu.
Is your girlfriend upset with me because I took her job from her?
If she takes all my stuff, what will I do?
Wait. You took away all my cooking materials, what will I eat tonight?
I'll teach you. Go out the door, walk,
open your mouth toward the northwest.
Today is the last major event in GO this year, China-Korea Go Invitation Tournament.
There are eight players in this tournament.
They are South Korea's 9-dan Cho Shen Woo,
9-dan Jo Yeon Hoon, 5-dan Lee Yong Jae.
Also, China's 9-dan Xie Hanzhou, 9-dan Sheng Jingchu,
9-dan Yao Ke, 8-dan Cao Xihe,
and 3-dan Xie Chang'an.
Among the four rounds today, there are two that attract the most attention.
First, the many years-old grudges between 8-dan Cao Xihe and 9-dan Jo Yeon Hoon.
Hi.
Xiao Lan.
No time no see. You're still so pretty.
Jerk.
I said you're handsome.
She said you're so handsome.
You're also very pretty.
There's something there...
I'm warning you.
Don't touch someone else's girlfriend.
See you next time then.
Are you ignoring me, Jo Yeon Hoon?
If you defeat me, I obviously won't ignore you.
Fighting!
What did he mumble?
If you are good, you can say it again in German, French, Arabic, whatever.
The camera. Watch your image.
May I ask, are you confident in this game?
Based on past matches, whenever Cao Xihe plays against Jo Yeon Hoon,
he always seems to be off his game inexplicably.
I wonder if this is a mutual restriction between players.
You must be steady in a while, and defeat Jo Yeon Hoon in one blow.
So that they won't always say that he is your natural barrier.
Don't worry. It's not a problem.
It's about time. I will go in now.
Wait!
[Red "Zhong"]
(T/N: Literally "Middle")
It's not the Zhong in Mahjong.
It's the "Zhong" in "I like you." Good luck.
Good luck.
Brother! Brother, hurry wake up.
The game is about to start.
Did I fall asleep?
You slept for a little bit earlier. You even snored a little.
Last night, I was studying Cho Shen Woo's GO patterns until really late last night.
It's fine! There's still Senior Brother. He's famous for only playing one round.
You'll definitely be out first later. You can sleep well later when you go back.
Okay.
Ru Mei, I won't bring the phone in later.
Can you hold onto it for me?
This phone...
Chang'an? You will definitely win.
I'll watch you from here. I'll wait for your triumphant return.
- I'll see you later.
- See you later.
Master Nie? Please come in.
- Master Nie?
- Yes.
Master Nie, I haven't seen you in a while.
Why are you here?
I'm here to cheer you on. Aren't you about to play against Cho Shen Woo?
Here to cheer you on and support you. No, no, I don't need a drink.
Old Cho is already this old and he is still competing.
Quickly beat him so that he can rest and retire soon.
Are you worried about me?
I've seen your recent GO games.
They're clear and the overall concept is pretty good.
As long as you play to your standard, you shouldn't have too much of a problem.
Thank you.
Actually, I'm still lacking in a lot of areas.
You don't have to be too modest.
Besides being humble, young people also need to be a little intimidating.
As long as you use both your humbleness and intimidation good enough,
there shouldn't be any problem.
Okay, I'll just say this much. I'll cheer you on.
I'm leaving now.
You don't have to send me out. You'll win for sure.
[China-Korea GO Invitational Tournament]
[Match Room D]
Xie Hanzhou, 9 dan, as a master is competing against the young player, Lee Yong Jae, 5 dan.
Likewise, Yao Ke 9 dan and Jiuzhou's Senior Brother Xie Changan 3 dan are meeting in this competition.
- Please guess your pieces to start.
- Isn't ideal for Xie Changan at 3 dan.
This means these two games aren't going to be very suspenseful.
But another match, that is highly anticipated by the audience against Korean player, Jo Yeon Hoon's master,
Cho Shen Woo 9 dan. and Sheng Jingchu 9 dan is starting.
But due to Sheng Jingchu's abnormal behavior in previous games,
the chances of winning is quite uncertain.
[Match Room A]
Right now, the four matches have already started.
Let's first watch Cao Xihe's and Jo Yeon Hoon's match.
Last time they competed, it was a quick win for Jo Yeon Hoon's white stones.
Today, Cao Xihe once again has the black stones.
He plays the Kobayashi Opening move and white quickly enters the game.
(TN: It is an opening move often used by Kobayashi Kochi.)
The black piece approaches and squeezes. As expected, these two quick players at the positioning stage
are already fighting against each other and neither side is conceding.
Cao Xihe's condition today looks pretty good.  His moves are firm and penetrating.
Right now, the situation for the white pieces is in danger.
Clearly, Jo Yeon Hoon is feeling the pressure. He has slowed down his tempo and has taken a long moment to think about each move.
[Red dragon]
(TN: Chinese in Mahjong also refer to this as red center.)
(Grr.)
In this match, Cao Xihe at 8 dan wins.
I really can't believe it. Cao Xihe 8 dan, this time showed
everyone the art of a beautiful straight line dragon kill.
He directly and efficiently won this game.
- Cao Xihe.
- Yes.
This time, you're finally not showing a disapproving attitude towards me.
I've looked at you for a long time but just only realized
you actually have nothing good to look at.
Let us congratulate Cao Xihe 8 dan for successfully advancing on.
[Match Room A - China-Korea GO Invitational Tournament]
At the same time, Master Xie Hanzhou as expected has beaten Lee Yong Jae.
[Match Room B]
The match between Yao Ke 9 dan and Xie Changan 3 dan is still intensely going on.
At this point, it is hard to say who will come out on top.
Yao Ke looks really confident. Evidently, it seems he has a way to revive his game.
Black piece itself is weak and if it wants to capture white pieces, it'll still be difficult.
Xie Changan is acting unusual in this game. He's playing very aggressively.
He is chasing Yao Ke closely and not letting go.
Good. This black piece is fierce and precisely played.
Obviously, it looks like Yao Ke did not see this move coming.
Xie Changan used a rare kill move to lock in the win.
One careless move and the whole game is lost.
Looks like Yao Ke 9 dan will be eliminated.
- Senior Brother is impressive.
- Senior Brother is really great.
You actually won an official match.
I won.
Senior Brother, you removed the seal today.
Removed the seal?
You could say that.
Chang'an?
Ru Mei.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
Your GO playing is the same as before. Invincibly sweeping away all obstacles ahead.
Let's leave.
Brother, are you all right?
Xiao Pu,
did you see the game? Did you watch it, right?
Do you know who I lost to?
To the one who loses every round of every game, Xie Changan.
Brother. Brother, what are you doing?
At this moment out of the four matches, only the match between Cho Shen Woo 9 dan and Sheng Jingchu 9 dan remains ongoing.
Korean Master Cho Shen Woo's GO style is unexpected and dangerous.
If the opponent gets slightly distracted, they will fall into a trap.
Originally, a highly winnable game becomes a badly lost game.
His style is known as the Blade of the Ghost.
♫ The wind blows,
the moonlight breaks through the sea of clouds ♫
♫ The butterflies are like you, understanding clearly ♫
♫ The sounds as summer nights awaken ♫
♫ Black, white, dissipating colors ♫
♫ Reaching out, but can't touch it ♫
♫ That which was beautiful, but long forgotten ♫
♫ Because you started to dance ♫
♫ Your appearance lit up my world ♫
♫ Warmed my rainy nights, called out and made me see ♫
♫ That life is like a butterfly, breaking out of the cocoon
and flying far because of your talent ♫
♫ Flying out from the barren adversity ♫
♫ I want to respond to all the good you've given me ♫
♫ The clouds float by and hide the sun's brilliance ♫
♫ Waiting for the endless rainy season ♫
♫ All of summer is conversing ♫
♫ Sweet, bitter, it's all unknown ♫
♫ There is color all around you ♫
♫ Even if going against the wind, you won't back down ♫
♫ It was you who gave me new strength ♫
♫ Found the memories of the smells again ♫
♫ Saying a prayer for love ♫
♫ Your appearance lit up my world ♫
♫ Warmed my rainy nights, called out and made me see ♫
♫ That life is like a butterfly, breaking out of the cocoon
and flying far because of your talent ♫
♫ Your existence woke up my past ♫
♫ Embraced my future, taught me to become aware ♫
♫ No one is a lonely island, running aginst the wind with me ♫
♫ Little dreams are flying high ♫
♫ You're my most important treasure ♫