♫ Let the past stay in the past, let your real feelings evolve ♫
♫ The determination between your brows
Cannot be allowed to break down ♫
♫ Precise calculations, invisible armor ♫
♫ Get equipped well, the tanks are setting off immediately ♫
♫ The goals were originally invisible,
How do you realize the dream of reaching the stars ♫
♫ How far and wide is it from the beginning to the end? ♫
♫ Making it through all the difficulties is so thrilling,
Breaking through layers of encirclement ♫
♫ The future is realized step-by-step in the game ♫
♫ Dreams of horses, the world is so complex ♫
♫ A simple heart is the answer ♫
♫ Step-by-step, we set off.
The map points towards the end of the world ♫
♫ Some day, we'll finally arrive ♫
♫ Distant roads ♫
♫ So moving ♫
♫ Every footstep ♫
[GO Into Your Heart]
[Episode 14]
Have more confidence in Sheng Jingchu.
He's our GO God, isn't he?
Even though he lost the first round, that's being polite. He'll reverse it right away.
He'll definitely win the final match.
Have some confidence.
Of course, I'm confident. Who is he?
He's Sheng Jingchu. Can he lose?
No way.
Be confident.
You look like you've got spikes growing on your butt.
(T/N: can't sit still)
[Sihai Jiuzhou Cup Four Countries Invitational GO Tournament]
The starting guess begins.
The match begins.
[Wave]
[Surface - Official - Row...]
Sheng Jingchu!
Do you want to compete against yourself?
Imitation game.
It's not certain that you'll beat me.
You'll have to defeat yourself first.
Jo Yeon Hoon is too cunning.
The two previous games were won by the White player.
He knew about Senior Brother Jing's habit of taking a black stone at the starting guess.
So he took a white stone to make Senior Brother Jing take Black.
See? Now he's playing an imitation game.
So what if he plays an imitation game. You're free on the GO board.
Imitating your opponent's game doesn't violate any game rules.
My Yeon Hoon-oppa can certainly play it.
What's an imitation game?
It's when one side follows the other side symmetrically to place the stones.
Just like how it is on the board now.
So, Jo Yeon Hoon's
white stones are placed by copying Sheng Jingchu's moves?
That's right.
However, usually, only the white will play the imitation game.
Because, if Black does imitation moves,
both sides will have the same-sized territories.
But Black must gain a 3.75 lead,
or it'll always be at a disadvantage.
Once you get to this point, you can be sure
Jo Yeon Hoon's white stones will continue to imitate.
Sheng Jingchu, you told me to go to bed early last night, but what did you go do?
Why don't you pursue and attack? You look so exhausted.
A trap of this level
is too immature, don't you think?
If you don't come up with a new strategy,
you'll fall behind!
The white stones have a clear advantage now.
Senior Brother Jing put a lot of effort into creating a ladder in order to break the imitation strategy.
In the game just now, if Yeon Hoon-oppa hadn't stop imitating in time,
Senior Brother Jing would have been able to use the ladder to capture the white stones.
Just based on the vigilance involved in this game, you can tell how amazing my Yeon Hoon-oppa is.
Little traitor.
At the current moment, Jingchu is clearly taking much more time to think than Yeon Hoon.
After all, he has to come up with a counter-strategy to break the imitation.
Whereas Jo Yeon Hoon only needs to be careful to not be captured.
All he needs to do is imitate Jing Chu's tactics.
The situation isn't looking optimistic.
Forty.
Fifty.
It's all right. Senior Brother lost a lot of black stones this round;
however,
over here the black stones can take over the white stones.
The remaining territory will be open for the black stones.
Since the start of the game, Senior Brother Jingchu and Jo Yeon Hoon
have been fighting hand-to-hand combat. Really intense.
The black stones are struggling.
The white stones are readily prepared and constantly attacking.
Now the black stones are trying to reverse the play,
but the white stones are still better off. Eldest Senior Brother look,
the black corner's position is really bad.
If Jo Yeon Hoon invades the black corner,
Senior Brother Jingchu...
will lose.
That's right. The chance of Jo Yeon Hoon winning is indeed very high.
- However–
- He's Sheng Jingchu!
[Rush]
[Block]
[Tiger]
Sheng Jingchu wins.
Yay, he won! He won! He won!
Yes, he lost! He lost! He lost!
Your old baby has completely lost this time.
You're the old baby!
He won covering three-fourths of the board.
Jingchu suffered a lot in this game.
He fought Jo Yeon Hoon's two dragons.
The game didn't turn until the very end. So difficult.
My Yeon Hoon-oppa lost so badly.
It wasn't easy for Senior Brother Jing to win.
- Why are you crying?
- I'm not crying. I'm happy.
All right, all right. Don't cry.
I'm not crying!
Brilliant, Sheng Jingchu.
I really enjoy playing GO with you.
I haven't had enough yet.
[Four Seas Jiuzhou Cup]
Hey!
Sheng Jingchu!
- What are you doing tonight?
- I have plans.
I know you have plans. I know you must be busy.
But... I learned so much from you this time.
So can you give me a chance
- to thank you?
- No need to be so polite.
Hey, wait!
Forget about the competition.
I'm grateful for you taking me in.
It's settled. I'll come and make some delicious Korean dishes for you.
- You want to cook for me?
- Of course.
It's really delicious.
- Stay right there.
- Wait.
Master, please accept me.
- Your apprentice?
- No.
Master, I watched your game.
To me, you're a god. Please accept me, I beg you.
Tonight, I already have plans with him. He's mine.
I don't care!
Can you get rid of him for me?
Yes, I can.
But are you going to have dinner with me?
Get rid of him first.
You better keep your word.
What are you doing? Hey!
Master! Master! Master! Don't leave!
- Don't leave, Master!
- Hurry up and drive.
Master! Master!
Have dinner with me.
Master! Master! Don't leave!
Master!
My throat hurts!
I can't sing anymore.
Hey, Sheng Jingchu. Dinner's almost ready.
I bought the ingredients and I'm the one cooking.
What are you unhappy about?
I really don't need you to thank me.
No, no, no, no, no. This is a token of my appreciation.
I'm a well-mannered GO player.
You can do whatever.
How can I do whatever?
We're international best friends!
It's ready.
Tada! Okay!
We can eat now!
Let's see.
How is it? Doesn't it look pretty good?
What is this?
This is authentic Korean bibimbap.
It's perfect.
I meant...
this.
I picked it from your greenhouse.
How is it? Really luxurious right?
Wait! Wait!
Why are you doing this?
Hey, wait!
Sheng Jingchu, what are you doing?
Open the door! Sheng Jingchu!
Why did he get so mad?
Wait, why? W-W-Wait.
Why are you doing this?
Isn't there a Chinese saying,
"Borrow flowers and offer them to Buddha"? Did I offer it wrong?
(T/N: Means to win favor using something that's not yours.)
You didn't.
You borrowed the wrong flowers.
Wait! You have so many flowers!
Sheng Jingchu!
You're not keeping your promise!
I'm homeless! Where do I go?
[Director Liu]
Hello? Director Liu, hear me out.
This time I planned to wait
until after the competition to interview Sheng Jingcchu.
- But Sheng Jingchu–
- It's all right.
Cheng Liao, I was just about to praise you.
The tournament and all that isn't important. You don't need to interview Sheng Jingchu.
All of the cameras already got you hugging Sheng Jingchu.
You don't need to find news for me. You are the news!
The situation isn't like that.
- Listen to me explain.
- You don't need to explain.
I saw everything. You did very well.
I'll ask the boss to reward you.
Keep working hard!
You keep stirring the pot. I'm not twice-cooked pork!
(T/N: play on words)
Everyone is your tool for stirring up drama.
[Sheng Jingchu]
"GO God"?
Cheng Liao?
Mr. Sheng.
Mr. Kiyomasa?
Mr. Sheng, please give me some beer.
Mr. Kiyomasa, can I invite you for a drink another day?
This is the most important thing in my life,
so I need to be tipsy before I can tell you.
Beer, please.
Thank you.
Please.
One more.
What's wrong with Mr. Kiyomasa?
Don't mind him. Go see the flowers first.
What's wrong with the flowers?
Take a good look at them.
Plants have emotions, too. If they see a fellow flower get plucked,
they'll be sad and die from depression.
Take a good look.
Who did you hear that from?
I found it online.
You're too cute.
It's fine. The flowers are doing great.
So, you chased out evil-flower-plucking Jo Yeon Hoon?
He's not familiar with this place, where will he go?
Jiuzhou.
The series of traps set by Mr. Zhao in the middle was ingenious.
What's so great about that? He lost anyways.
Senior Jing's calmness in the midst of adversity
is what's worthy to be learned by us, understand?
If you were to play against Yeon Hoon-oppa, you would've lost early on.
- I...
- You guys are talking about me?
Oppa!
I'm sorry. The door was unlocked, so I came in.
Wait.
What are you doing here? May I help you?
- Mr. Jo, welcome. Have some fruit.
- Thank you. You're too polite.
Let's eat and chat. If that's not enough, there's more.
Why are you feeding him? I haven't been fed yet. What are you doing here so late?
Actually, I've been sad about losing to Sheng Jingchu this time.
I've heard a lot about Jiuzhou Hall's fame, so I'm here to learn.
Welcome. Welcome.
You came to learn from us in the middle of the night with a suitcase. What? Are you staying overnight?
I can! I can stay here, of course!
This idea of yours is great, Mr. Cao!
I'm just wondering if it's okay with you all?
It's okay! It's okay! We really welcome you!
Stop messing around here.
Our... Our master isn't here. We can't make the decision.
Our master is not here, but Eldest Senior Brother can make a decision.
- Really?
- Eldest Senior Brother must be...
- Great! We welcome you!
- Thank you so much!
- Yes! Yeon Hoon-oppa, I'll take you to the guest room.
Xiao Lan!
- This way.
- This way, please.
- Come, come.
- Thank you so much, Mr. Cao.
- Senior Brother.
- This way.
You brought a wolf into the herd!
No, our country values etiquette and manners.
You should even more so build friendships with fellow GO players.
Jo Yeon Hoon came this far, we have to welcome him.
Be more generous!
Mr. Jo, would you like to try my health tea?
Jo Yeon Hoon... I'll...
Jo Yeon Hoon...!
Hangover tea.
Mr. Sheng, you need to take care of me.
For what?
My lifelong happiness. You need to take care of me!
Sheng Jingchu, what did you do all night?
I didn't do anything to him.
My girlfriend
is also from Binhai. Her name is Xiao Kong.
I've decided a long time ago that she's irreplaceable in my life.
I planned on dedicating the trophy to her
and then at the award ceremony
propose to my dear Kong.
But he ruined my plan
for the proposal.
Ruined?
That's right!
Ruined!
I didn't have a Plan B.
I couldn't come up with a more romantic way to
propose to my dear Kong.
Mr. Sheng, it's all your fault. My lifelong happiness
is your responsibility. You have to take complete responsibility.
Mr. Katou,
I don't know how either.
I don't care. I don't have other friends in China.
You two have to help me!
I'm not good at being romantic.
Don't push me!
For my lifelong happiness,
I will do anything!
Mr. Katou, please calm down.
Just one second.
I believe Mr. Katou is dead set on you.
How about we think of something for him?
Jo Yeon Hoon was first, and then him.
My plan was completely ruined.
What plan did you have?
Nothing. Let's deal with him first.
[Jiuzhou Hall]
So you agreed to help him propose?
Please help me, everyone.
Or else, I don't know how to face Xiao Kong. Please, I beg you.
That's not necessary. That's not necessary.
Let's think of something.
Yes, let's.
Think.
Why are you looking at me?
I don't have experience with that either.
That's right. None of us have that experience.
To be honest, everyone in this room,
except for Brother Jing and Sister-in-Law,
are single.
We don't have that experience.
How's this?
Jiuzhou has a principle around helping others.
We will definitely help Mr. Katou with his goal.
Thank you. Thank you so much!
Don't mention it. Since we don't have the experience,
I think we should discuss it together.
What do you think? Discussion always solves the problem.
With years of experience of watching dramas,
I think girls like romantic, dreamy proposals.
That's nice, but I think on top of being romantic and dreamy,
you need to add some practical elements. What do you think?
Mr. Katou, I think nostalgia is more of an appropriate style for you.
I think being international is also important.
International won't do. Won't do.
Why not?
You need to go with our traditions, right? This is China.
You need to put some Chinese elements into it.
With your taste, you should give less advice!
What's wrong with my taste? Look at my sweater.
I have... I have... dogs.
Your hair is also problematic. It's like a pot lid.
Your hair is problematic! You look like you are from the 80's and you're talking about me.
You look like Runtu.
(T/N: Runtu is a character in Lu Xun's novel "Hometown".)
I look like Runtu? Do I look like Runtu?
Don't be mad and have them laugh at us.
Let's just discuss the matter and solve the problem. Don't bicker.
- What are they talking about?
- They were just joking.
Don't worry, Mr. Katou. Everything can be solved with some discussion.
Mr. Katou, how about I show you around?
- How's that sound?
- Okay, okay.
- They'll discuss and come up with something.
- All right.
I have a book. In the book...
You all keep discussing.
Do I look like Runtu? Is my hair not cute?
It's cute. It's cute. We were talking about the proposal.
Let's be energetic, okay?
She's here.
♪ The world suddenly became calm ♪
♪ You walked past me ♪
- I didn't expect GO God to sing this well.
♪ Disappearing quietly, your back only a silhouette ♪
- Right? He's the golden voice of the GO world.
He just doesn't sing much, so no one knows about it.
My master said that if someday he doesn't want to play GO anymore,
he can sing on the street and still make a living.
♪ Waiting for that moment when the wind blows, bringing something to place your hope on ♪
♪ Please forgive my weaknesses ♪
♪ For cowering over and over again ♪
♪ Missing it over and over again, I pretend to be lonely and sad ♪
♪ How do get through each moment through the late night?
The city lights confuse me ♪
♪ The coffee in my hands has become cold ♪
♪ I hope you can refill it with warmth ♪
♪ The moment I think about you, I tremble all the time ♪
♪ There's no one like me ♪
♪ Who would go through fire and water for you ♪
♪ Checkmate my sincere heart and break it open ♪
Xiao Kong, I hope you can marry me.
I want to take care of you for the rest of your life.
Marry him! Marry him! Marry him! Marry him!
Oppa, is there a game that you really like to play?
If so, we can play the game together later.
The New Swordsman mobile game? I don't play very well.
But if you play it with me, I think it'll be a lot more fun.
Really? I've been looking for someone to form a team with.
Then let's play it together.
Excuse me.
Here, have a drink.
I quit drinking.
I'll drink it then.
Well...
We came to help Mr. Katou with his proposal today.
But actually, every single person has found something that they wanted to do.
The matter has finally been resolved.
Do you still remember our promise?
What promise?
To take you for a ride.
A ride?
Seriously? Only you would call this "a ride."
The first time I saw you was on this bus.
Come on.
♫ The little sunshine never retreats.
Dispelling all the confusion  ♫
♫ The little sunshine is here every season.
The power in believing  ♫
♫ The little sunshine brightens up the road.
We'll tackle all the problems together  ♫
♫ Let me think a minute. Think about what tomorrow is like.
The future with you everywhere  ♫
♫ Let me make a scene. Hide in your embrace.
Love is like the never changing sun ♫
♫ Half of you, Half of me. As the years quietly trickle on  ♫
♫ Not disappointed, not depressed.
The radiance of the two of us ♫
Listen to some songs.
♫ Your bright smile ♫
♫ My heart beats follow ♫
♫ Why did I suddenly think about the future? ♫
♫ When we intimately say hello ♫
♫ Our eyes meet ♫
♫ Just like that, I suddenly thought of loving you ♫
♫ Believing the whole world is a rainbow ♫
♫ But it's just black and white ♫
♫ Yet, you allowed me to see the dazzling twinkling  ♫
♫ You're like the gentle breeze in my face ♫
♫ Gently moving about in my blue sky ♫
♫ Like the key to my dreams moving back and forth ♫
♫ That romantic universe ♫
♫ Has given me something completely different ♫
♫ The restless desire of love ♫
♫ Sweet movements matching the other person ♫
♫ Can't help but protect happiness ♫
♫ Suddenly the heart is moved ♫
- Cheng Liao.
- Yes?
Got it.
I have something to tell you.
Go ahead.
Every moment with you...
I feel like time flies by.
It's never enough.
I want to be with you every single moment.
I want to be close to you, to understand you more.
I'm a boring person. The person you see right now...
isn't perfect. But thankfully, life is a long journey.
I have enough time to better myself.
Perhaps...
Even in the end, I won't be able to become the person you want.
But I'll try my very best.
Liao Liao.
I...
I've never liked anyone before.
But right now, I'm absolutely sure that...
I like you.
♫ The wind blows,
the moonlight breaks through the sea of clouds ♫
♫ The butterflies are like you, understanding clearly ♫
♫ The sounds as summer nights awaken ♫
♫ Black, white, dissipating colors ♫
♫ Reaching out, but can't touch it ♫
♫ That which was beautiful, but long forgotten ♫
♫ Because you started to dance ♫
♫ Your appearance lit up my world ♫
♫ Warmed my rainy nights, called out and made me see ♫
♫ That life is like a butterfly, breaking out of the cocoon
And flying far because of your talent ♫
♫ Flying out from the barren adversity ♫
♫ I want to respond to all the good you've given me ♫
♫ The clouds float by and hide the sun's brilliance ♫
♫ Waiting for the endless rainy season ♫
♫ All of summer is conversing ♫
♫ Sweet, bitter, it's all unknown ♫
♫ There is color all around you ♫
♫ Even if going against the wind, you won't back down ♫
♫ It was you who gave me new strength ♫
♫ Found the memories of the smells again ♫
♫ Saying a prayer for love ♫
♫ Your appearance lit up my world ♫
♫ Warmed my rainy nights, called out and made me see ♫
♫ That life is like a butterfly, breaking out of the cocoon
And flying far because of your talent ♫
♫ Your existence woke up my past ♫
♫ Embraced my future, taught me to become aware ♫
♫ No one is a lonely island, running against the wind with me ♫
♫ Little dreams are flying high ♫
♫ You're my most important treasure ♫