♫ Let the past stay in the past, let your real feelings evolve ♫
♫ The determination between your brows
Cannot be allowed to break down ♫
♫ Precise calculations, invisible armor ♫
♫ Get equipped well, the tanks are setting off immediately ♫
♫ The goals were originally invisible,
How do you realize the dream of reaching the stars ♫
♫ How far and wide is it from the beginning to the end? ♫
♫ Making it through all the difficulties is so thrilling,
Breaking through layers of encirclement ♫
♫ The future is realized step-by-step in the game ♫
♫ Dreams of horses, the world is so complex ♫
♫ A simple heart is the answer ♫
♫ Step-by-step, we set off.
The map points towards the end of the world ♫
♫ Some day, we'll finally arrive ♫
♫ Distant roads ♫
♫ So moving ♫
♫ Every footstep ♫
[GO Into Your Heart]
[Episode 15]
Every single moment with you,
I feel that time goes by quickly.
There's not enough time.
I want to be with you every second, every moment.
I want to get close to you, get to know you better.
I'm a very boring person. The person you see now is not perfect.
But thankfully, a lifetime is long.
I have enough time to make myself better.
Perhaps,
I may not become the person you want me to be.
However, I will put in my best effort.
Liaoliao,
I... never liked anyone before.
But I know,
I know clearly,
I like you.
I really, really want to be with you.
Liaoliao,
what's your answer?
I didn't know you wanted to tell me this.
I wasn't prepared at all.
I don't know what I should say right now.
I just feel it was really unexpected.
Give me some time, okay?
I'm waiting for...
you.
What should I do? Would he be angry at me?
But I really don't know him well enough.
If I agreed like that, would he think I was careless?
Ugh, my head hurts.
Foxy, think of something for me.
Think of what I should do. What should I do?
I wasn't prepared at all.
I don't know what I should say right now.
But I don't want to lie to you.
Sorry.
Xihe, will you come practice with me?
Hello, the subscriber you dial is powered off.
The phone you are calling is powered off.
[Jiuzhou Hall]
Morning, Junior Brother.
Looks like you're having a good day.
Good thing I shut off my phone early yesterday. I narrowly escaped.
What happened?
Late last night, Senior Jingchu asked me to practice with him.
Based on my past experience, he's probably not in a good mood.
Oh.
Doesn't he always play with an AI opponent?
What nonsense?
As long as he's in a bad mood, he will appear...
- in front of me.
- Why didn't you reply to my message?
I fell asleep.
Let's go play.
Wait, wait. Let's make it clear, just a few rounds.
I have to pick up Xiao Lan in a while.
One round? That I can do. Wait for me.
Continuous play.
Let's not, Senior Brother.
I... I'm not feeling good today. From head to toe, my head hurts.
I can't handle it.
Don't... Don't Senior Brother. I beg you.
Why don't we do this?
Since you came to the hall,
you should play here. I will go get the chessboard.
Junior Brother! Junior Brother!
Junior Brother! Come back here!
Eat some fruit.
Look at this.
Liaoliao,
I never liked anyone before.
But now,
I clearly know
I like you.
Cheng Liao, look. This pace is better now.
Cheng Liao!
What's wrong?
I should be asking you what's wrong.
Don't be forgetting about work now that you're dating.
I don't know if I should actually date.
What do you mean?
- Thanks for the hard work. Keep an eye on it, will you?
- Okay.
Again.
Enough already.
- Again.
- I can't.
I really can't play another round.
If I continue, I'm really going to spew blood.
Junior Brother, you've been watching this whole time. Aren't you going to say a single word?
Don't you want to play a few rounds?
Okay, fine. Keep playing dumb.
Senior Brother, how about you play a few rounds with him?
Okay, fine. You're both are ignoring me. That's great.
Senior Brother, why don't I accompany you on a walk?
Let's go take a walk. Let's go.
Let's go. Let's go for a walk.
After all this time, all that before was a lie.
He only recently confessed to you?
Love is a small thing. Common people
like you makes love so complicated.
If it's really this frustrating, wouldn't being single be good?
But I...
Fell in love with him?
Don't make these heartbreaking expressions. As a senior, I'll teach you a trick.
- Tell me.
- One phrase.
Follow your heart.
The thing about love is that there is no logic to it.
There is no particular reason either. No one can say for sure.
Then why do we start from our hearts?
We do what our heart feels.
If you don't like him, cleanly break up with him.
If you like him, then be together.
I... I don't know for sure.
I have always thought that there was a lot of difference between us. He's a god.
When he told me that he thought of me as a friend, I thought it was my luck.
When he stared into my eyes while he was confessing,
my mind went completely blank.
I didn't want to believe that it was real.
I haven't dated before either.
So I don't know if this is the feeling of liking someone.
But I feel that if I carelessly accepted it,
it wouldn't be responsible for me or Sheng Jingchu.
If you want to understand,
then it's simple. Go see him.
Just sitting here thinking about yourself, even in a whole lifetime, you still won't comprehend it.
You should meet regularly and frequently.
How frequent?
Three times a day.
Three times a day?
That phrase sounds familiar.
Wow, that was a good move.
Who is it?
Practicing GO, Ms. Ding?
Oppa,
why did you suddenly appear?
You made my little heart beat so fast.
Sorry, I scared you.
Continue practicing. I won't bother you.
Wait a minute.
Why don't you practice with me?
I can, but aren't you practicing with the AI?
A famous person said that the "AI game is cold.
Only a game with humans has warmth."
Such a philosophical saying.
Okay, let's play a round.
Right, Ding Lan. Who said those wise words?
Actually, it's not some famous person.
It's just someone who wants to be famous.
They said it so nicely.
How greasy! I really don't know how people in Korean dramas eat it so deliciously.
Senior Brother Xiao Jing, you beat me (in games) all day.
How are you not happy yet? And you're showing me an upset face.
If you continue, I'm leaving.
Cheers.
Shift that over there a bit or the beer is going to get warm.
Does she actually like me?
You mean Little Sister-in-Law?
She's pretty caring about you.
Like...
is different from caring.
She cares about my world,
but still rejected me.
She rejected you?
Oh my gosh.
Even you can be rejected.
Doesn't that mean I don't even stand a chance?
How can you understand a girl's heart?
From my continuous changes in style and different attempts and experiences,
I don't understand their hearts either.
Cheers.
I understand. You can ask me.
Why is it you again?
How did you find this place?
Get down.
Don't worry. Let me tell you.
Let me... I have a lot of dating experiences.
If you're talking about understanding a girl's heart,
I'll say I'm first...
Boy, it's you again. Quickly come down.
- Don't pull on my legs.
- Quickly come down.
- Shut it. Quickly.
- Don't pull on my legs.
My butt!
- Let go of me!
- Security Brothers.
Security Brothers!
Mr. Sheng,
we must send this guy to the police. He's already been here twice.
Master.
No need. I'll take care of him myself.
Are you really okay?
If any happens, call us anytime.
Okay, thank you.
Thank you, Security Brothers.
Master.
I really don't accept students.
Just accept me.
In order to learn GO,
I'm working three jobs at the same time.
My strength is severely weakened.
Look, my hands are still shaking right now.
That's being tired from climbing the wall.
But my heart for learning from you is sincere.
I certainly, won't let you down.
You just said before that you have a lot of dating experience.
Of course! I can't beat you at GO,
but I'm more experienced in love than you are.
Yuda, you haven't eaten yet. Right?
I haven't.
Eat.
She De Wine. Seems like you thought about it.
(TN: She De is produced by a Sichuan liquor company but here She De can be described as 'willingly' as in to say Liquor he willingly brought for his master.)
It's easier to carry smaller bottles.
Small ones are the most enticing. Slightly tipsy is better than being drunken in sorrow.
Master, have a taste.
Just a moment.
Come in.
Sister, are you tired?
If you aren't, I want to chat a bit.
What's wrong? You had an argument with Sheng Jingchu?
We aren't at the point of having an argument yet.
Then, what's wrong?
To you, what does it mean to like someone?
How should I tell you?
First, it starts from taking an interest.
Then, start understanding one another.
If your major values conflict,
no matter how interested you are, being together will be a disaster.
So, the understanding step is also important.
Just like you and Brother Xu Chi?
The problem with me and Old Xu isn't understanding. Rather it's about arousing the heart's interest.
Don't make us an example.
The key is the starting point isn't the same. They are two different situations.
I haven't understood yet.
Do you not like or are you uncertain?
I just don't understand.
Yet, I couldn't get myself to say no.
When I saw his disappointed expression,
I almost rushed to him and agreed.
When I came home yesterday night, I couldn't sleep.
I was just as distracted at work today.
Zhiliao, you don't have to feel guilty.
You did the right thing.
You're a girl.
Having a careful and cautious attitude about love
isn't a bad thing.
When you don't know enough about someone
and you didn't recklessly agree,
that's being responsible towards love, responsible towards yourself.
As well as being responsible towards Sheng Jingchu.
If he knows you're thinking that way, he'll understand you.
But my heart just doesn't feel right.
When I see him like that, I feel even worse.
What should we do? You're feeling bad?
Feeling bad.
Feeling bad is right then.
Feeling bad means you care about him. Your heart aches for him.
If this is liking then what is it?
Don't hesitate. Be bold. Don't be afraid.
What you have to do now is
to get close to him and understand him.
What if? What if he is the right one?
Happiness is at a hand's grasp.
This is the worry of happiness. The burden of sweetness.
That's it. We got nothing more to talk about. You can go now.
- I'm not going. I won't go find him.
- Go find Dad.
Such a child.
Master,
let me tell you, to woo a girl,
the most important point is...
taking the lead.
Even if you live together,
you can't guess what the other is thinking about.
So they say
love must be said out loud.
It must be expressed.
It's not that Brother Jing didn't make himself clear.
It was because my sister-in-law rejected him.
Keep... Keep pursuing her then.
If you want to be good to her, you need to be brave and do things for her.
If you want to express yourself, you need to be loud.
Loud.
But...
But I've already done everything I should.
Why?
Not only did I express myself,
I also had a makeover and expressed it in different styles and tones.
Why did I do that?
I just wanted her to be happy.
What did I do wrong?
You didn't do anything wrong. Let's drink.
There are no secrets.
The secret you believe in
means nothing to the other person.
If you feel bad, it means you care about him. If that's not love, then what is?
All you need to do is to get close to him and to know him.
What if he is the right one?
Happiness is right around the corner.
GO is a lonely practice.
When a player sits in from of the chessboard, all the stress
has to be beard by himself.
♫ The world suddenly became calm ♫
♫ You walked past me ♫
♫ Disappearing quietly, your back only a silhouette ♫
Maybe you will get help from your mates,
but you always play alone.
So whether it's winning or losing,
there aren't many people who can share happiness and sadness with the player.
♫ Please forgive my weaknesses ♫
♫ For cowering over and over again ♫
♫ Missing it over and over again ♫
♫ I pretend to be lonely and sad ♫
♫ How do I get through each moment through the late night? ♫
♫ The city lights confuse me ♫
♫ The coffee in my hands has become cold ♫
♫ I hope you can refill it with warmth ♫
♫ The moment I think about you, I tremble all the time ♫
♫ There's no one like me ♫
♫ Who would go through fire and water for you ♫
♫ Checkmate my sincere heart and break it open ♫
Senior brother!
I'm sorry.
[Numerous voice messages sent]
When did I send so many messages to Cheng Liao?
I don't know. I fell asleep first last night.
We fell asleep at the same time.
My head hurts so bad.
You sent Cheng Liao messages?
What did you send?
Let me see.
[Voice messages]
There are more flowers in the greenhouse.
They are so pretty.
But without you,
nobody tells me
what color they are.
It's so strange.
The photos I took with my phone
are also black and white.
It looks like my phone is broken.
I'll go fix it tomorrow.
I drank so much. I feel sick.
I feel so...
I want to eat the food you cook.
[Voice messages]
I have no recollection of this. And I sent so many.
Based on Yu Da's theory, you did express yourself.
Haven't you guys heard?
When you send drunk messages, other than proving your phone still has power,
it doesn't mean anything.
Xihe.
What's up?
I want to play GO.
Didn't you abuse me on the board all day yesterday?
You wouldn't be happy anyways.
When you're not happy, you drink.
When you get drunk, you message her.
After sending her messages, you are even more unhappy.
And then you come to play chess with me.
It's a never-ending cycle.
What do I do? I'm in such a bad mood.
Sister-in-Law?
Did you guys drink?
No, we didn't.
I made hangover soup for you. Do you two want to drink some, too?
Really? Okay...
Stop it.
We have so many things to do.
We are too busy today. See you another day.
Let's go. I almost forgot.
The soup...
- We'll get going.
- Bye, Cheng Liao.
Don't move. I will bring it to you.
And you still say you didn't drink.
Brother Xihe,
do you think Master will have me as a student?
I don't know if he will accept you.
But you always call him Master, which is intimate.
I want to learn so bad.
If I don't become his student, I won't even have the motivation to work.
Actually, I want someone to keep Brother Jing company.
Xiao Qi is the assistant all right,
but she's not a player.
They can't get along. It's not easy to get to know him.
Brother Xihe, please help me.
I can help you but stay a little away from me first.
Sorry.
You are simply too immature.
What's wrong with me?
You still don't get it?
You want to acknowledge my Senior Brother Jing as master, right? What should you call me?
Older Brother, right?
Junior Uncle!
Respected Junior Uncle,
- please accept a bow from Yuda.
- No need, no need.
You rascal. You look pretty smart,
but you are as dumb as a block of wood. Didn't you see it just now?
You want to acknowledge Senior Brother Jing as master.
It's useless to beg me. You have to conquer my sister-in-law first.
Junior Uncle, you are indeed smart. But how do I conquer her?
If I get too close to my master's wife,
wouldn't Master ruin me?
Do you know about Uncle Cheng's restaurant?
Does it taste good?
It's good. It must have taken you a long time.
No. Didn't you say you wanted to eat what I cook?
Drink slowly. Don't drink too much at a time or your stomach will feel upset.
Does your head hurt?
A little.
Here. Give this to me.
I'll massage you.
You also know how to do this?
Let me tell you. I've been certified with this skill for many years.
When I was younger, my dad drank a lot.
Whenever he drank, his head would hurt especially bad the next day. I would massage him.
Later, my sister started working. There were plenty of unhappy things at work.
I would massage her then.
I've become a professional master at sobering hangovers.
Think it over. Whatever you want to eat, I'll cook it for you in a while.
No need.
What's the matter?
You don't need to work so hard. I can just drink some soup.
I'll take a look at the flowers then.
Uncle Cheng's Restaurant.
Here I come.
[Uncle Cheng's Restaurant]
Young man, are you eating?
- Here.
- Thanks.
This is the menu. Do you want me to suggest anything?
Uncle, may I ask if your store needs any waiters?
Young man, thanks. It's a small business, so I can handle it all.
I see.
Here, take a look. What would you like to eat?
Give me one of each of your specialty dishes.
Can you finish eating all these dishes? Don't waste food.
Whatever I can't finish, I can pack up to take with me. I just want to try more.
Okay. Just wait a moment then.
Young man, you can really eat.
Uncle, the check.
Coming.
You have a good appetite.
Here.
You can really eat.
Uncle,
I don't have... money.
- What does that mean? No money?
- However,
I can stay here and work. You can deduct this meal
from my future wages. What do you think?
Young man! If you don't have money to eat, I could have treated you.
But you planned to eat and run, and waste food!
I will absolutely not allow it!
Actually, I really didn't want to do this.
Uncle, I am really miserable.
I didn't do anything.
You... Why are you crying?
This... Don't cry.
Here, here! Let me wipe.
A man shouldn't easily shed tears. Don't cry. Sit. Sit.
I'm so miserable.
[Uncle Cheng's Restaurant]
Xiao Dada, you can be at ease and work here from now on.
Even though I can't give you much in wages, but there is a bed behind here, so you can live there.
I'll give you food and lodging, ¥3,000 a month. Okay?
Uncle, you are so kind.
A really good person.
Okay. There will be more customers in a while. Wash these bowls first.
- Wear these?
- Yes.
You've washed bowls before, right?
Yes.
Okay. Take it easy then.
- Uncle Cheng, don't worry.
- It's fine. Everything is difficult when you start.
Watch your safety. You must watch your safety first.
- Do it slowly. Be safe.
- Okay.
This... What's going on?
- That...
Child, I know you are being careful.
I pitied you, so you should pity me too.
This is a small business. You can't break these bowls so casually.
[Uncle Cheng's Restaurant]
Follow the list to buy. Nothing can be left out. If anything is missing, I can't cook the dishes.
Don't worry, Uncle. I'll definitely buy all of them.
Helmet.
Also, mention my name when you buy.
They will give you the lowest prices.
Awesome, Uncle.
It's all under my control. Go on.
- Be safe.
- Okay.
Sister Goddess!
♫ The wind blows,
The moonlight breaks through the sea of clouds ♫
♫ The butterflies are like you, understanding clearly ♫
♫ The sounds as summer nights awaken ♫
♫ Black, white, dissipating colors ♫
♫ Reaching out, but can't touch it ♫
♫ That which was beautiful, but long forgotten ♫
♫ Because you started to dance ♫
♫ Your appearance lit up my world ♫
♫ Warmed my rainy nights, called out and made me see ♫
♫ That life is like a butterfly, breaking out of the cocoon
And flying far because of your talent ♫
♫ Flying out from the barren adversity ♫
♫ I want to respond to all the good you've given me ♫
♫ The clouds float by and hide the sun's brilliance ♫
♫ Waiting for the endless rainy season ♫
♫ All of summer is conversing ♫
♫ Sweet, bitter, it's all unknown ♫
♫ There is color all around you ♫
♫ Even if going against the wind, you won't back down ♫
♫ It was you who gave me new strength ♫
♫ Found the memories of the smells again ♫
♫ Saying a prayer for love ♫
♫ Your appearance lit up my world ♫
♫ Warmed my rainy nights, called out and made me see ♫
♫ That life is like a butterfly, breaking out of the cocoon
And flying far because of your talent ♫
♫ Your existence woke up my past ♫
♫ Embraced my future, taught me to become aware ♫
♫ No one is a lonely island, running aginst the wind with me ♫
♫ Little dreams are flying high ♫
♫ You're my most important treasure ♫