♫ Let the past stay in the past, let your real feelings evolve ♫
♫ The determination between your brows
cannot be allowed to break down ♫
♫ Precise calculations, invisible armor ♫
♫ Get equipped well, the tanks are setting off immediately ♫
♫ The goals were originally invisible,
how do you realize the dream of reaching the stars ♫
♫ How far and wide is it from the beginning to the end? ♫
♫ Making it through all the difficulties is so thrilling,
breaking through layers of encirclement ♫
♫ The future is realized step-by-step in the game ♫
♫ Dreams of horses, the world is so complex ♫
♫ A simple heart is the answer ♫
♫ Step-by-step, we set off.
The map points towards the end of the world ♫
♫ Some day, we'll finally arrive ♫
♫ Distant roads ♫
♫ So moving ♫
♫ Every footstep ♫
[GO Into Your Heart]
[Episode 31]
[Sunac: A Tour Town, A Tour A Life]
[Changlai Psychological Counseling flyer]
Sorry, Sister Cheng Liao, I made a mistake. I really made a mistake.
Xiao Qi, don't do this. Hurry and get up.
I said something wrong last night. I was drunk.
You must not blame Mr. Sheng and don't mention it to him, or I'll lose my job.
I still have a litter of kittens at home waiting for me to feed them milk. I beg you.
Don't worry, I won't tell him.
Oh, yes! How about the others at Jiuzhou Hall?
- They won't tell either.
- I really thank all of you. Thank you, Sister Cheng Liao.
Previously, I ordered some special delivery for Mr. Sheng.
I know you like this popular cake.
I ordered all that I could order.
You can take your time eating. I'm going home now.
I'm going to face the wall and reflect on my mistakes.
Bye-bye. Bye-bye.
Brother, I've already registered the new Weibo account that you wanted.
Thanks, Xiao Pu.
Change what I drafted into a fan's tone of voice.
Send it one by one to He Yu.
Pay attention to the pace.
Okay, Brother, don't worry. I get it.
Just let He Yu know that Sheng Jingchu is with Cheng Liao
only for his personal desire to cure his psychological problem.
Then, this game is set up.
Then... what if He Yu doesn't believe it?
It's such an interesting secret. If it were you, would you ignore it?
In this game, I'm betting that He Yu
will care too much and mess it up.
Let me introduce all of you. These three are our organizing party.
This is Mr. Sheng and this is Miss He.
We are the organizers here.
- Hello.
- Please go inside.
Sheng Jingchu, 9 dan. He Yu, 5 dan.
Thank you for accepting my interview,
as China's media representative for the Paris Mixed GO Competition.
You've both coordinated well with each other.
Thank you.
Mr. Sheng, as usual, you treat your words like gold.
(T/N: a person of few words)
Then let's cut to the main topic.
As far as I know, you were put together at the last minute for the competition.
Then facing opponents who have prepared, practiced together, and are well-coordinated,
is there confidence in winning the competition?
Of course, we are. Because I believe that the degree of compatibility between people
doesn't only depend on the time spent together to be accumulated,
but similar levels of intelligence and cognitive levels are the foundation to
quickly understanding each other and building a tacit understanding.
Then let me wish you both overwhelming victories.
Can I bother the two of you for a picture?
Of course.
Three, Two, One.
Good, very good.
[Pair GO Paris Championship]
Sheng Jingchu still reconnected those black stones.
Even if the stones are abandoned, Black is in clear advantage.
Right now White can cut Black into danger.
I can see how Black can stay alive. This difficulty will be turned to He Yu.
Looks like Sheng Jingchu really trusts his partner.
That's the reason why. They are trying to block the opponents there.
This way, the Black stones are alive.
It appears that these two players are really in tune with each other. Such great tacit understanding!
What do you mean in tune with each other? Do you know what you're saying? Don't speak nonsense.
Zhiliao, are you arguing with someone in the middle of the night?
- I'm watching a drama.
- Okay, sleep soon.
♫ The wind turns day and night.
The rain falls like teardrops ♫
♫ Use time and conviction to wake the earth  ♫
♫ It's not a square, more of a circle.
The final result is either black or white  ♫
♫ Our future is caused by the changes made today  ♫
♫ Ordinary life can even make a dramatic turn halfway through. Emptiness is also a type of attainment  ♫
♫ Till the final moment, I still believe ♫
♫ Dreams of horses, the world is changing  ♫
♫ Not afraid of the difficult obstacles  ♫
The spectacular match has completed. As expected, 9-dan Sheng Jingchu and 5-dan He Yu
have won the Paris Mixed GO Competition!
He is trying to avoid her in style.
Awesome!
What do you want to do this time?
Sheng Jingchu, we won.
I know that. So what?
Don't you feel it yet?
We only met a few times before this
and we didn't practice together before the competition. And during the competition, we obviously couldn't talk.
But we could perfectly understand each other's intent in every move.
This is a truly rare tacit understanding.
- We are fated to be together.
- It's impossible that we are fated.
There are many excellent female GO players, but Liao Liao, there is only one.
Regardless of appearance, physique, IQ,
I ask myself, where am I not better than Cheng Liao?
Furthermore, compared to that girl who doesn't know anything about GO,
I can comprehend your spiritual realm better. Why don't you admit it?
Liao Liao is the person that I want to spend the rest of my life with. She is very special.
Even though she doesn't understand GO, she understands me.
That's enough.
Hello? Panda?
I lost.
He Yu?
- Why do you have my phone number?
- During the previous interview,
you gave it to me.
I already forgot.
Your IQ is so slow, even your memory is deficient.
Why are you scolding me?
Are you suffering a huge blow and drinking too much?
Cheng Liao,
I received some messages from a fan.
It's particularly amusing.
Do you want to hear?
You called me. What exactly do you want to say?
That person said,
Sheng Jingchu's color blindness
is a serious psychological problem.
So, since childhood,
he saw and changed many psychologists
in order to find the colors in his sight again.
However,
during the GO Legends of China Competition this year,
he saw a girl in colors.
The psychologist told him
to get closer to this girl.
It's like taking medicine.
Morning, noon, night, at least three times.
Therefore,
he kept this girl closely by his side.
Why are you telling me all this?
That person said,
you are the girl in colors.
Isn't that particularly amusing?
If I lose because of this ridiculous reason,
then there's really nothing else that I can say.
But don't you worry, I will accept my loss for the bet
and totally disappear.
You have an express delivery.
Open it for me to take a look.
[Changlai Psychological Counseling flyer]
[Changlai Psychological Counseling Room]
Sheng Jingchu's color blindness is a serious psychological problem.
So, since childhood,
he saw and changed many psychologists
in order to find the colors in his sight again.
You are that colorful girl.
What I accept is not Pinecone Video but your personal interview.
It can't be anyone else.
We are friends
because you are very precious to me.
Miss Cheng, you called me over here away from my busy work.
Do I only see you looking at the cake without speaking a word?
Encyclopedia Yan, let me ask you something.
If someone can only see the whole world in black and white colors
but only sees you in color,
how would you feel?
Is this some kind of fairytale?
Such a one-and-only, fated destiny, killer set.
I would definitely go crazy!
But the condition is, he must be handsome. If he's not handsome,
let's forget each other then.
If this person can only
see the colors of the world through you,
that's why he would notice you
and then rush to get closer to you,
and tell you that he likes you,
do you think this is love?
Your question is like,
if I am not pretty,
would you still like me?
I have no answer.
It's already at this point, don't tease me.
Okay.
Xiao Cheng, let me be serious then.
Love is something that has tens of thousands of ways to start.
The so-called fate is really just two people
who see each other among all the people for whatever reason.
So, no matter how fantastic it is, it's only the beginning of the story.
But isn't the true feelings and motivation of the story's beginning important?
It's important.
But isn't the journey of the two people getting together even more important?
The heart is something that you can't see or touch.
It cannot be quantified or measured.
So you can only judge it by your own feelings.
Darn.
My head is particularly messed up. I really can't judge it clearly.
When I think about how he's concealed such an important matter from me,
I just can't help but get angry and get sad.
Encyclopedia Yan, if someday,
he can see all the colors in this world,
and he thinks that I'm useless and won't need me anymore, what will I do?
Xiao Cheng, I really do understand you.
People who are in love are always feeling uncertain.
But instead of wondering random thoughts with me right here,
why don't you wait for him to return
and ask him face to face directly?
I will definitely eat the candy you give me.
Eat them slowly. Eat for the rest of your life.
The psychologist told him to get closer to this girl.
It's like taking medicine. Morning, noon, night,
at least three times.
Therefore, he kept this girl closely by his side.
[Panda: New WeChat Message]
Liao Liao, I'm coming back tomorrow.
I especially want to see you, all the time.
Sheng Jingchu,
you can't just be
wanting to look and see me.
[Little fox, how can you abandon me and sleep first?]
Little fox, how can you abandon me and sleep first?
You should sleep well then. Good night.
Liao Liao, I'm on my way to the airport.
I'll be able to see you tonight.
Mr. Sheng, Miss He Yu is going to stay a few more days for personal reasons.
She won't leave with us then.
Please get into the car.
Why are you suddenly wanting to change the furniture?
Master said previously that my home is too boring, like a sample house.
That's right. Your house is huge, stuffy, and empty.
Even the colors are only black, white, and grey.
I didn't care about those things before
because I couldn't see even if there were other colors. But now,
I want to make a change.
I'll take care of it.
Actually, at that time,
the area of colors that you could see was probably already pretty big, right?
Clearly there were lots of time, so many opportunities, to tell me.
[Okay.]
[Sent]
Liao Liao, are you okay?
Why do I feel something strange ever since last night?
I'm about to fly. No matter what happens,
wait for me to come back and we'll solve it together.
[Okay, I'll wait for your return.]
[Liao Liao]
The plane is about to take off, please turn off your phones.
Or adjust the phone to airplane mode. Thank you for your cooperation.
[Pinecone Video]
- Hello.
Sister Goddess, are you home?
No, I'm in the office.
I'm rushing to finish a project plan. What's up?
It's nothing.
It's the weekend, so I just wanted to express my care.
Thank you for caring.
Enough. I'm still busy.
Okay. Bye, Sister Goddess.
Work and rest, take care of your body.
Working overtime on the weekend?
What do I do with this heart-warming surprise?
[Panda Bear]
[Panda Bear: voicemail]
Hello, food delivery.
Do you need anything?
[You don't have to be perfect to be amazing]
Hello, it's your order.
- Thanks.
- So it's you rascal.
You use work as the excuse
to take up Sister Goddess' time for resting.
Old Xu, aren't you treating your employee
in too grand a style?
An entire set of English-style afternoon tea?
After the cooking competition, I wanted to celebrate with you.
But you just wouldn't agree.
Today, we can have a small celebration just between the two of us.
- This is all right, right?
- i Have to admire you.
Also, we should congratulate our Chef Cheng's
successful conclusion of the Success in Sight series.
It also means that "Cheng Yi Conversation"
is totally becoming history.
There will be even more and better programs in the future
that are waiting for you to create another glory.
Why are you here?
- Didn't the security guard stop you?
- No.
It's actually the security guard who used their badge to open the door for me.
Sister Goddess, I especially prepared
a romantic, fancy indoor picnic.
Jiang Yuda, can you not do your nonsense here?
I'm giving a surprise to Sister Cheng Yi. It has nothing to do with you.
It's the office here, not the green grass outside.
- We're still working.
- You call that working?
- We are taking a normal break.
- You are taking a break?
Didn't you say you were working?
Sister Goddess, please.
Can the two of you quit making a scene?
I'm trying to finish work quickly and go home as soon as possible.
Jiang Yuda, did you hear? I'll say it again.
Pack up and leave right away.
Xu Chi, did you hear?
I'll say it again, too.
You should pack up the stuff...
and leave.
I'll pack up for you.
You two...
Oh...
I was just... you touched the cup.
You are too much!
You two, don't fight anymore.
Jiang Yuda, you are too much!
Sorry.
- I'm sorry.
- Old Xu.
Give me one minute. I'll chat with him.
Jiang Yuda, I appreciate your good intentions.
But just like what Xu Chi said, this is an office, it's a workplace.
When you bring in this mess of stuff, you are causing trouble.
But Xu Chi is also deliberately posturing and bringing in stuff.
He and I can drink tea and talk about work at the same time.
What you bring in will only waste time.
I'm spending my weekend working overtime
so that I can finish my project plan quickly.
I really don't have the time and energy to drink, eat, play house with you.
Therefore, if there is nothing else,
please don't disturb me again.
Thanks.
These Spicy Fried Clams
are successfully cooked now.
This is the first dish from my Little Fox Private Kitchen video channel.
I hope all the audience who had met me through the cooking competition
will like it and also successfully make it yourself.
Thank you, everyone.
Okay. Perfect.
It's a wrap.
What's wrong?
It's a success.
Why are you looking like that?
I couldn't cook well. I'm so annoyed.
Sheng Jingchu, it's all your fault.
This expression is very good.
Perfect.
[Panda Bear]
Sorry, the number you dialed is not...
Is this how you make food programs now?
Wow, how many meals will we eat to finish this?
Yan Xiao, I'm sorry.
You came over to help on the weekend, and you only eat this one dish.
It's okay, Uncle. I'm a vegetarian.
It's my first time doing a video, so I'm inexperienced.
I can eat everything.
Zhiliao, I sense that you are in a bad mood.
Are you missing Sheng Jingchu?
I know. You're worried that He Yu is seducing him?
It's not that at all.
Dad, just leave.
It's good. I'll take two platefuls.
Uncle, eat some more!
Sheng Jingchu is probably almost back.
About when will he return?
Probably soon.
[Panda Bear, 14 missed calls]
Hello.
Master, save me.
[Starting October 11th, Qingdao 7th Countrywide... The great nation's roll call without you.]
What's the matter?
Master!
This is what you mean by saving you?
Master, let me tell you.
Get up!
[Beer and GO Big Competition]
Sheng Jingchu! Sheng Jingchu!
Move aside.
Isn't this the famous Sheng Jingchu?
Come play around.
Play a round! Play a round!
Play around! Play a round!
Play a round.
Wait.
Beer GO game.
Not only will you play, but you'll also drink beer.
Your disciple plays pretty well,
but his drinking capacity is too bad. He only played a few rounds, and he's drunk like this.
[What are you doing?]
Master, cheers! Master, cheers!
[Where are you?]
[Are you okay?]
Fine, I won't ask you today.
I will just wait and see when you are going to text me.
[Weekly Tree Hole]
I promised you that I'd be a tree hole just for you.
The kind that's available 24/7.
[Sorry, this item is no longer in stock.]
Master, I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have called you here and got you this drunk.
How about you hit me or yell at me?
I'm so sorry.
Forget it.
What are you thinking? Say something.
I will call my Goddess Sister Yi, too.
Liao Liao...
Sister Yi.
Sister Yi, I...
♪ Do you know how much I love you? ♪
♪ I love you deeply ♪
♪ And my words are truth ♪
♪ The moon is my witness ♪
- Sister Yi!
- Be quiet!
Sheng Jingchu.
Liao Liao,
I missed you so much.
Why did you drink so much?
You are so annoying.
Sis, what should we do?
You take Sheng Jingchu to his place.
I will deal with this one.
♪ I'm willing... ♪
It hurts! Hurts!
- Bye.
- Be safe.
Move over!
♪ All the colors in that garden ♪
♪ All the stars lighting up the city ♪
♪ In May!  ♪
Goddess Sister Yi?
I know you prioritize your career.
But whatever you want to do,
I support you a hundred percent!
A hundred percent!
Let me ask you.
Is it worth it to do all these things for me?
What is it about me that made you like me this much?
Don't you feel it?
The two of us...
have a soul connection.
A soul connection?
Really.
The two of us are both very stubborn.
We'd do anything for our careers.
But at the same time, the two of us
are very lonely.
Thinking about when I first went abroad,
I had to do everything myself.
I believe...
that the loneliness that is carved in our bones
and our stubbornness
led us to run into each other.
You are my soulmate.
As long as it's what you want,
for you,
everything I do for you is worth it.
Sheng Jingchu,
let me ask you.
Do you see...
things in black and white,
but only me in color?
♫ The wind blows,
the moonlight breaks through the sea of clouds ♫
♫ The butterflies are like you, understanding clearly ♫
♫ The sounds as summer nights awaken ♫
♫ Black, white, dissipating colors ♫
♫ Reaching out, but can't touch it ♫
♫ That which was beautiful, but long forgotten ♫
♫ Because you started to dance ♫
♫ Your appearance lit up my world ♫
♫ Warmed my rainy nights, called out and made me see ♫
♫ That life is like a butterfly, breaking out of the cocoon
and flying far because of your talent ♫
♫ Flying out from the barren adversity ♫
♫ I want to respond to all the good you've given me ♫
♫ The clouds float by and hide the sun's brilliance ♫
♫ Waiting for the endless rainy season ♫
♫ All of summer is conversing ♫
♫ Sweet, bitter, it's all unknown ♫
♫ There is color all around you ♫
♫ Even if going against the wind, you won't back down ♫
♫ It was you who gave me new strength ♫
♫ Found the memories of the smells again ♫
♫ Saying a prayer for love ♫
♫ Your appearance lit up my world ♫
♫ Warmed my rainy nights, called out and made me see ♫
♫ That life is like a butterfly, breaking out of the cocoon
and flying far because of your talent ♫
♫ Your existence woke up my past ♫
♫ Embraced my future, taught me to become aware ♫
♫ No one is a lonely island, running aginst the wind with me ♫
♫ Little dreams are flying high ♫
♫ You're my most important treasure ♫