What are you doing here?
I'm going to Seoul.
I won't be back within the next few years.
Why are you suddenly going to Seoul? Tell me.
You said you liked this place before.
I told you... everything will change.
I want to go because I've been admitted to a good university.
Can't you just stay here?
I'll do nothing and just stay by your side, okay?
Are you going to Seoul to avoid me?
Do you hate me that much?
I apologized to you and told you I won't do it again.
It's not your problem.
It's my problem.
Let me hug you one more time.
Don't get hurt.
I can't apply ointment for you anymore.
Bye.
Go Hotae.
Why are you back so late?
I can't believe you just asked me that.
Don't you know why?
So you were looking for me.
I won't be here anymore.
Why?
Why won't you be here?
Why did you leave me?
Didn't you promise to be with me forever?
You lied to me.
Because many things will change.
I've changed too.
Darn it.
How do you know you'll change?
I won't change.
[Drawing Diary]
[In the rain.
September 28, 2013]
Auntie.
Looks like your business isn't doing very well.
Since you're calling me at this hour.
[Kim Donghee]
Didn't I tell you not to get hurt?
You only called me
after I broke my leg.
Hey, Kim Donghee.
Is it that fun in Seoul?
Yes.
Leaving me behind, are you that happy?
You don't need to be so serious.
Does it hurt?
Of course it hurts. My leg is broken.
The doctor said I can't swim anymore. Isn't that funny?
You should smile.
I like to see you smile.
I never smiled that much.
I just realized you don't seem to know yourself very well.
You've always been a gentle guy who likes to smile.
You've been like this since you were little.
You always like to smile, and you're gentle.
Even so, how can I smile now?
I'm not a crazy man.
I haven't smiled for a long time. It's nice to smile like this.
I'm really fine.
You know I'm very tough.
I know.
Go Hotae.
In my eyes, you're fine.
Your leg isn't broken.
[Attention, railway ahead]
Hello.
The commercial area here is good,
but the situation varies significantly with the seasons.
Call me when you decide.
Okay. Thank you.
Go Hotae.
The weather is really nice, right?
Yes.
Hey, Kim Donghee, come here.
One, two, three.