♪Sweat drips onto amber♪
♪The sky is flickering♪
♪Who can break the lock of destiny?♪
♪Fearless in the face of karma♪
♪The good and evil hard to distinguish♪
♪Are left for the world to discuss♪
♪You and I, like shivering shadows♪
♪Trampling on illusions and wastefulness♪
♪Igniting hearts, and flames of the heart♪
♪Persistence, resolute persistence♪
♪Time surges into summer♪
♪The firmament resonates for me♪
♪Igniting hearts, and flames of the heart♪
♪Dedication, determined dedication♪
♪Heaven and earth, life and death,
we'll be together♪
♪That's a promise that will not waver♪
=Battle Through The Heaven=
=Episode 12=
Xiao Yan.
Why'd it have to be him?
Where's he?
It's not the deadline yet.
You're running out of time.
He's already in the Demon Flame Valley.
So what're you waiting for?
He's got the flame,
while I get only one shot at this.
If he becomes wary,
I will have missed my chance.
My patience will be thin.
Take this bottle of elixir
and feed it to him.
His Dou Qi will be suppressed.
By then,
it's your killing time.
If you're interested in his stuff,
I can catch and bring him here.
It would be much easier.
He's my mortal enemy.
But for my serious injury,
I should have sent him to death by myself.
It seems like
you don't want him to die.
Why?
Is he your acquaintance?
If I kill him,
will you keep your promise
that you'd remove our poison?
After coming to this valley,
you have been relying on my antidote
to survive till today.
You're crystally clear
my elixir is the only solution
to your poison.
Killing Xiao Yan
is the last thing I do for you.
When it's finished,
remember to give us the antidote.
Have I ever betrayed my words?
But,
you'd better do your best.
If he's not killed,
Xie Shan and you
will have to spend your remaining life
in this secluded place.
It all depends on you.
A deal is a deal.
A desperate man is capable of everything.
Beg me now,
and I'll kindly inform Xiao Yan
of your last words.
What did you do to him?
I killed him.
You!
Stay still.
Otherwise, I might be too careless
to keep your throat bloodless.
Sounds bad, right?
Aren't you curious about
where Xiao Yan is?
You're targeting him.
If you have made it,
why bother chasing after me?
The only reason you have
is to make him helpless.
By then, you'll succeed
in killing him.
Don't waste my time.
Calm down.
I'm not the only one wanna his life.
Who else?
It doesn't matter.
I'm afraid he's already died of the poison.
Water.
Why am I here?
This is Demon Flame Valley.
You've been unconscious for a day and a night.
I'm an alchemist traveling to this place.
I took you here after finding you.
You saved me.
Dissolve it in the water and drink it.
It helps fight against the poison
of this valley.
If your Dou Qi recovers after dawn,
you'd better leave as soon as possible.
Thanks.
Have we met before?
No, we haven't.
You saved my life.
Please at least let me know
what you look like.
My identity and appearance
have nothing to do with you.
We're two strangers running into each other.
I just don't wanna see people dying
before my eyes.
Will you tell me your name
if I take this?
You will.
It's poisonous.
Why're you here?
Without me,
you were dead now!
She's an accomplice of that scorpion lady!
She should have killed me last night
if she wanted to.
Why wait till now?
You lied to me!
You were not in a faint.
No, I didn't.
I did pass out.
But I remember your aura.
I know you,
even though your face is covered.
You know her?
Little Fairy Doctor,
I didn't expect to meet you again.
In the Magic Beast Mountain Range years ago,
I was badly hurt when taking the beast flame.
I came to the Lush Town
(Lush Town)
(Due to the plague,)
(no one in the town was willing to take me in.)
(I lay down on the ground,)
(with my blood drained out.)
(Then you came.)
(You saved me.)
I'm not the Little Fairy Doctor,
and neither did I go to the Lush Town.
You tried to kill me last night,
but why did you give up
after seeing my Storage Ring?
It's because you remembered me, isn't it?
She's right.
I'm a friend of Xie Shan.
I lured you here to kill you.
Get it?
Let me send you on the way to death!
You can't fool me.
The poisonous gas
is used to save lives.
Saving lives?
She's a Poison Master.
There are few such masters
on the Dou Qi Continent.
Without innate poison bodies,
even the top-notch alchemists
can't develop into Poison Masters.
Why is she able to?
She's got a special body.
Her blood can dissolve various poisons.
It's called Inborn Poison Body, or…
Enough.
She has
a Woeful Poison Body.
Yes.
Woeful Poison Woman, get out.
Out, get out!
Get out!
Hold out.
Your injury has been cured.
Why do you come back?
I heard those people want to hurt you.
I'm worried. Here.
Leave me alone.
You saved my life.
How could I leave you alone?
I have the Woeful Poison Body,
so it's my fate.
You can't save me.
What do you mean by fate?
Every one of us
has a predestined way to live,
and a doomed way of death.
This is fate.
I have the Woeful Poison Body.
I'm fated to be born and die in woe.
I accept how my fate goes.
Who can determine
how one person lives
and how his or her life ends?
Even a bug strived to survive.
Your life is not up to those outside,
but to yourself.
You're practicing
in this Magic Beast Mountain Range.
You must be a Dou Practitioner.
Kind of.
Well,
kill me now and go out.
They won't hurt you.
I've never killed anybody.
As a Dou Practitioner,
you've never killed anybody?
I'm a doctor,
but I have killed others.
Since infant,
I was repelled by all the villagers
because of my Woeful Poison Body.
I was thought to be a demon by all,
except for my mother.
She took me to this Magic Beast Mountain Range
and cared for me every day.
She taught me curing and antidoting skills,
in the hope of
me becoming a doctor one day
and curing patients in Lush Town.
When I was ten,
the Woeful Poison Body activated.
I witnessed
my mother
being poisoned in front of me.
I asked her to leave,
but she refused.
She kept hugging me
until her body
cooled down
and she died.
I'm wondering
why.
Why am I still alive?
It's not your fault.
The Woeful Poison Body is dormant now.
If you can't keep yourself under control,
your mother would have died for nothing.
How I wish I was never born.
To live such an infamous life
is ridiculous as a joke.
You're right.
Why should you hide?
You did nothing wrong.
You should live upright and aboveboard
like them under the sun.
Once Woeful Poison Body attacks
everyone around will be poisoned,
without exception.
If you leave with me,
they will kill you too.
I don't want you to die.
I just want to show them
that I'm the exception.
Woeful Poison Woman
hurts all the people.
She's out. She's out.
Get bows and arrows prepared.
Is there anyone of you not saved by her?
Is there any one of your families
not saved by her?
If there is,
step out
and charge your arrow.
I will take it for her.
Go ahead!
Don't listen to the nonsense
of this outsider!
Woeful Poison Woman must be eradicated!
It's not her fault.
Around the world,
by no means will she be allowed
to stay in a single corner.
She shouldn't even be born.
Loose!
Little Fairy Doctor,
hide behind my back and don't be afraid.
Thank you.
You've done a lot.
I don't need it now.
Little Fairy Doctor.
Don't look at me.
Oh, no.
Woeful Poison Body is breaking out.
Run!
It's too late.
None of you can go anywhere.
Little Fairy Doctor,
keep yourself under control.
No.
Go to hell!
Why are you saving them?
I'm not saving them,
but you.
I hate all the people in this world.
I've done nothing wrong,
but I'm detested and cursed.
I'm just
a bit different from them.
Perhaps they don't see you through,
but I do.
The Little Fairy Doctor I know
is kind and caring.
Should hatred defeat you
and cause you to do this,
you'll be in pain forever.
It's too late.
Too late to stop it.
- If I had met you at an earlier time…
- No.
You can do it.
You can
control the Woeful Poison Body as you wish.
I will leave with you.
Let's leave here forever.
Let's go to a place
where there is no disappointment.
Please trust me, will you?
I have promised
even if everyone betrays you,
I'll be the exception.
Have you ever gone outside the Lush Town?
No.
Let's go down the mountain.
Why?
Leave this place and these people behind.
Try another lifestyle in the outside world.
The outside world?
Aren't you curious about
the outside world other than Lush Town?
Listen,
the Dou Qi Continent is large in territory.
There are endless mountains and rivers.
Some places are freezing cold.
Some are dry without rain for several years.
The sun never goes down there.
Really?
Yeah.
These are just examples I've been to.
There are more places
I've not been to.
The Jia Ma Empire might be tiny like an ant
in the Dou Qi Continent.
It's a pity
that I'm just a low-level alchemist.
And my Dou Qi is at the elementary level.
When I become a Grade III alchemist
several years later,
I'll rid you of the Woeful Poison Body.
Should anyone hurt you,
I'll beat him up for you.
You said you don't remember me.
Then do you remember this?
Where did you go
after leaving the Magic Beast Mountain Range?
Why are you here?
How are you?
None of your business.
- Little Fairy Doctor.
- Just leave.
It will be too late
if the Valley Master comes.
I knew it.
I knew you were forced by someone.
Who is the Valley Master?
Feng City Medicine Emperor.
You're not his match. Leave now.
Han Feng.
Why's he still alive?
What did he do to you?
Han Feng killed my father.
Take me to him.
I must tear him apart.
Don't you understand?
I'm not the Little Fairy Doctor
in the Lush Town anymore.
It's thanks to his elixirs these years that I…
Elixir.
It's the culprit of your poison tattoos.
Trust me. Han Feng is lying.
Stop.
Just go.
Please follow his words.
He's the one sincerely helping you.
He will help your friend as well.
Little Fairy Doctor.
Don't believe in what they say.
Your Woeful Poison Body
and my scorpion poison
can only be removed by the Valley Master.
We're close.
We'll be free when Xiao Yan dies.
Shut up.
I don't like threats.
Little Fairy Doctor,
we don't mean to hurt her.
I just want you to help me find Han Feng.
He's taking advantage of you.
I can take you away
and help you find the antidote.
You believed in me once,
so why don't you trust me again?
Are you willing to help us?
I said
I'm always the exception.
Alright,
prove it to us then.
Let Xie Shan go.
Let her go.
What're you doing this for?
I made an agreement with her that
we would leave Demon Flame Valley
to a place where we are not found
and not despised.
I can take you away.
You can take
the Little Fairy Doctor of Lush Town away,
but not me.
As she said,
let go of Xie Shan.
Xiao Yan,
I would rather
never have met you.
Let her go.
I knew it would happen.
She just didn't want me to see
how the poison affected her.
But I don't understand
why she won't trust me one more time.
It's because
you are different from her.
Han Feng.
That Han Feng again.
Stop staring.
She won't come back
no matter how hard you stare.
Instead of sitting here staring blankly,
it's better to confess honestly.
So I can be prepared in advance
when we encounter some little fairies again
in the future.
It's not her fault.
She's also the victim of Han Feng.
Xiao Yan.
What's wrong? Are you OK?
This poisonous mist has a greater impact
on you than on me.
Even if we find Han Feng now,
we're not in the right condition to fight him.
Don't worry.
I've got this.
You!
It's not the time for joking.
Don't tell me you actually believe that
it can resist the poisonous mist.
I don't trust Han Feng,
but I have faith in Little Fairy Doctor.
Fine.
Go ahead and take it. I won't stop you.
You actually take it?
Xiao Yan, Xiao Yan, Xiao Yan.
Xiao Yan.
Are you OK?
I faked it.
Idiot.
Getting rid of the poisonous mist
is just a matter of time.
How can you trust her like that?
How do you know
it's not another trap set by Han Feng?
I don't know.
Perhaps, it's simply trust.
Even if you're poisoned to death this time,
I will no longer save you.
Bear your words in mind.
Don't… don't…
Stop it.
Get up. Stop your acting. Xiao Yan.
Xiao Yan.
Xiao Yan, don't scare me. Wake up.
Xiao Yan, it's not real, right?
Wake up, Xiao Yan.
Is he really that important to you?
Is he more important than your life?
Stop talking.
You need to have a rest now.
No need to.
How can you save me
if you don't even value your life?
My fate has been determined since birth.
No need to struggle anymore.
I saved you from the mercenaries back then
and brought you to this Demon Flame Valley.
For years,
we've been following the instructions
of the Master
in exchange for the antidote.
I know you have a kind heart.
That's why I took all the tasks
like seizing the Demon Core.
We have never made any mistakes.
Why did everything start to change
when you met Xiao Yan?
Is it because he helped you before?
What about me then?
I saved you not for you
to repay his favor with your life.
If you did it,
how can you repay me?
But for him,
I wouldn't have come
to the Demon Flame Valley alive.
I owe my life to both of you.
Killing my savers
to stay alive
is against my principles as a doctor.
You're not a doctor.
You're the Poison Woman.
You're my younger sister.
Xiao Yan was not born
with a poisonous body.
He won't understand your pain.
Clearly, we are of the same kind.
Sis,
if there's a chance,
I would sacrifice myself for you.
But I can't kill Xiao Yan
as you ask me to.
How come it's active again?
I'm going to ask the Valley Master
for medicine.
Sister.
Xiao Yan.
What's wrong? Why are you still unconscious?
Your Highness, I don't feel well.
What's happening to me?
From what I see, you're dying.
Speak out your last words.
Your Highness,
I must say
your pulse diagnosis is so inaccurate.
Alright, get up if you're not dead.
So inaccurate.
I told you
Little Fairy Doctor won't lie to me.
The elixir is useful.
So what?
You're just lucky.
How many lives do you have
to test all the medicines?
Your Highness,
you should take the medicine as well.
It's time to take action.
The smell here
is exactly the same
as that on Little Fairy Doctor.
Could it be herbs?
I'm afraid not.
Hope it's not what I'm thinking of.
Little Fairy Doctor.
♪The so-called obstacles are covered by hope♪
♪Nourishing love with sincere expectations♪
♪Miracles wait in the light, blooming wantonly♪
♪Now I won't be profaned anymore♪
♪Wu~♪
♪The future I expect will surely come♪
♪Honestly, it should never be replaced♪
♪Repeated comebacks,
shedding the stereotyped mark♪
♪Layers of opportunities,
outlining the definition of passion♪
♪Forever sincere, forever♪
♪Forever passionate, forever♪
♪Time never stops for anyone♪
♪The world always turns, never looking back♪
♪Never looking back♪
♪Don't be too surprised, I'm with arrogance♪
♪Gaining the favor of all things,
facing the world♪
♪Not being arranged by anyone,
the unrestrained exception♪
♪Who understands that I never give up?♪
♪Wu~♪
♪The future I expect will surely come♪
♪Honestly, it should never be replaced♪
♪Repeated comebacks,
shedding the stereotyped mark♪
♪Layers of opportunities,
outlining the definition of passion♪
♪A little courage,
piling up youthful confidence♪
♪Searching repeatedly,
revealing the mystery of the truth♪
♪Forever sincere, forever♪
♪Forever passionate, forever♪
♪Time never stops for anyone♪
♪The world always turns, never looking back♪
♪Never looking back♪