I'm not a kid.
Don't put me before you
because I'm not doing this for you.
(T/N: Literally, he said "because I'm not thinking about you")
If you want to do something for me,
then drink my blood.
This is for me and not you. This is what I want.
♫ Kissed your eyes inside my dream ♫
♫ We both stood inside the rain ♫
♫ Raindrops falling on my heart ♫
♫ I'm still here with you ♫
[Kissable Lips]
[EP 08: Hyung... do you want to kiss right now?]
♫ Every morning, every night filled with you ♫
♫ You're just like a star, so beautiful ♫
If that's what you want...
let's not do what each other wants.
Let's not do what each other wants?
Yes.
Let's be selfish.
Then, Hyung, do you want to kiss right now?
No.
♫ How could I survive without you ♫
♫ Forever is not enough to  ♫
♫ Make all of our memory ♫
♫ I, I'll never let you go ♫
♫ Not letting you be lonely ♫
♫ I need you in my arms ♫
♫ My world, you are my soul ♫
♫ I'm always on your side ♫
♫ You are my life, you are my heart ♫
♫ Nothing's gonna change my love ♫
- I'm awake.
- Are you?
What time is it?
Hold on.
♫ Never leaving your side ♫
♫ Love will never fade ♫
♫ How could I ever forget you ♫
♫ All I need is your love ♫
Is your phone off?
No.
What? It's already 9:00 a.m?
- Get up, Hyung.
- Why?
- We have to go to school.
- What?
[President Ok Mi Ran]
Is your heart at ease?
Yes.
Then, it's all good.
I'm sorry. I came too late, didn't I?
Did something happen?
Why have you been acting like this since earlier?
Be quiet.
I'm never going to lose you.
Tell me. What is it?
I get anxious without you.
Because I'm so happy right now...
and I'm scared.
Hyung.
Live a little longer with me.
Drink my blood.
Please.
Fine.
Then drink it right now.
I'm ready.
It'll be night soon, so let's do it tomorrow morning.
Really? Don't run away.
I won't run away.
I've become afraid, now that death was near.
My final moment with you...
Hyung?
Hyung!
You were here...
Hyung?
♫ And since that day I met you, every day you grow ♫
♫ More and more in my heart ♫
No.
♫ I fall in love with you again and all over again ♫
I guess I was too late. I'm sorry.
Why are you leaving already?
You said you would be by my side.
I didn't want you to see this side of me.
♫  'Cause you are my only one ♫
I liked that you were by my side towards the end of my long boring life.
So much to the point that, even though I lived 500 years,
I want to constantly look back on those moments.
Don't say that.
You said you would be with me.
♫ I'm gonna to lose my mind ♫
Drink it now.
Please.
♫ You and I ♫
I want to be with you even for just a day.
Just one day.
♫ An empty world without you, dear ♫
♫ I can't stand it. All my days ♫
♫ Without you just means nothing at all ♫
♫ Because you're my only one ♫
♫ You're my all  ♫
♫ I wish this time we have could last forever more ♫
♫ Never let you be alone, I promise till the end of time ♫
No...
♫ Don't you fade away with love, you know it ♫
♫ I'm going to lose my mind ♫
No.
♫ I dream of you ♫
You can't leave like this.
I'm not even ready yet.
♫ My heart keeps going straight to you with all its love ♫
♫ Don't be scared, cause I made my mind ♫
♫ just love you the way you are ♫
♫ So here I stand for you. Just take my hand ♫
♫ I wish this time we have could last forever more ♫
♫ Never let you be alone, I promise ♫
♫ Till the end of time ♫
♫ Don't you fade away without me knowing ♫
♫ I'm gonna lose my mind ♫
♫ I dream and dream again, you and I  ♫
Bye, Hyung.
Didn't I tell you not to forget your phone?
I have a lot of friends now. It's not that dangerous.
Listen to the president's words.
The president is even more nosy than you, Hyung.
There are so many spies at school now.
I'll get going.
All right.
❤ Thank you to our channel manager: annaluisaalp ❤
❤ Thank you for the segmenting team: bbf_260
and bjohnsonwong (Chief Segmenter) ❤
❤ Thank you for the editing team: kakashiandme (Chief Editor), cerejacult (General Editor) and 2sharonrose (Translation Editor) ❤
❤ Thank you for all moderators and subtitlers ❤
It's already been a year.
Min Hyun.
♫ Kissed your eyes inside my dream ♫
♫ We both stood inside the rain ♫
♫ Raindrops falling on my heart ♫
♫ I'm still here with you ♫
♫ All I think about is you. Every morning,
every night filled with you ♫
♫ You're just like a star, so beautiful ♫
♫ Here I am ♫
♫ Every time you fall down ♫
♫ Don't you worry, you're not alone ♫
♫ Oh, here I am ♫
You should've at least left a picture behind.
♫ That I will ever love ♫
♫ How could I survive without you ♫
♫ Forever isn't enough to ♫
♫ Make all of our memories ♫
At first, I couldn't come to this place because I was afraid.
Half a year later, and...
this place was already cleaned up.
The only thing you left behind were the memories.
It caused me pain for a while.
Memories...
can't be thrown out if you don't forget.
♫ 'Cause I'm always next to you, yeah ♫
I was tortured the most by that fact.
♫ Just so beautiful to me ♫
♫ Here I am ♫
♫ So every time you're down, down ♫
♫ Don't you fear, you're not alone ♫
♫ How could I survive without you ♫
♫ Forever isn't enough to ♫
♫  Make all of our memories ♫
♫ I, I'll never let you go ♫
♫ Not letting you be lonely ♫
♫ I need you in my arms ♫
♫ My world, you are my soul ♫
♫ I'm always on your side ♫
♫ You are my life, you are my heart ♫
♫ Nothing's gonna change my love for you ♫
And... whenever I look back on those memories, it always comes back to me.
♫ How could I ever forget you ♫
That I still miss him.
♫ Just making our story ♫
I dreamed about growing old with you.
It was a very happy dream.
But when I woke up, I realized
that this was the dream.
♫ Whenever I look at you ♫
♫ I become a little sad. It must be worse than I thought ♫
I wish I had the chance to tell you
that I love you.
♫ It's okay even if it's not ♫
♫  As long as it's all right with you ♫