Zhong Wanruo?
I won't let you hurt Shihua
Zhong Wanruo
You shameless slut!
Liu Zirun died because of you
And you want to my son to die for you, too?
You won't have another chance to seduce him
because I'm gonna kill you
Also...
You always thought it was me
who killed your family, right?
But you know what,
when my men arrived,
your family members were long dead
You idiot!
Wanna take revenge on me all the time
You got the wrong person from the beginning
But it doesn't matter
because you won't have a chance to find
the real murderer!
Wanruo
Marshal
Commander's men are here
It seems they want to investigate Sheng Fang's death
Dig into it
Sheng Fang couldn't have come here by himself
I must know the result within three days
Yes
Give the order
Get my wife the best medicine
Yes
Shaoli
I heard Sheng Fang broke into your place
and injured Zhong Wanruo, right?
Yeah
But I have shot him dead
I've been looking for Sheng Fang
But he never showed up
Why did he break into your place at this time?
Perhaps he was there
to seek revenge since I was the person
who defeated his army
Then how did he get in?
Maybe he sneaked in when the guards weren't
paying attention
Ridiculous!
Your are a Marshal
Yet that old bastard Sheng Fang
sneaked into your place all by himself
This means
your guards are pieces of trash
But don't worry
My security guards are
all good fighters
From today onwards,
they will be responsible for
protecting your family
Nothing will be able to sneak in, not even a fly
He wants to use his soldiers to put me under house arrest!
Thank you, Commander
I'll go back first
All of you
Turn left
Double march!
Marshal
What's going on?
As Sheng Fang died in my place,
Xia Jun began to suspect me completely
Marshal
Now, Commander's guards
have replaced all our men
Wouldn't that mean Xia Jun will know
whatever we do in the future?
Yeah
So we have to put on a show for a while
Got it
Boss
What?
Your father...
What happened to my father?
Last night, your father sneaked into Marshal's Mansion,
and tried to kill Mrs. Mu
He was shot dead on the spot
Now his body is hung on the street
Boss, boss!
Boss
You can't go!
Let go of me
Mu Shaoli
Boss, you can't go!
I'll kill you!
Boss, this is clearly a trap!
He has set up this inescapable trap to catch you
You can't go!
Yeah
Mu Shaoli
I won't let you off!
Doctor
How is my wife now?
The miscarriage worsened her health badly
I'm afraid she can't get pregnant again
What did you say?
Mrs. Mu probably
can't get pregnant again
Marshal
If there's nothing else,
I'll take my leave first
Xia Jun has suspected me for a long time
The situation is getting increasingly dangerous
Wanruo is just a weak woman
If she stays here,
I'm afraid I can't protect her
I have no choice but to come up with this plan
Wanruo
Don't blame me
Why did you drink so much in broad daylight?
The child was gone
What are you still doing here?
Get lost!
Why did you drink so much...
Zhong Wanruo
Are you so reluctant to part with the glorious life here?
Mu Shaoli
I know you felt terrible losing the child
So I can forgive you for your rudeness
But...
Forgive me?
Zhong Wanruo
For the sake of wealth,
don't you even care about your dignity?
What the hell do you want, Mu Shaoli?
Zhong Wanruo
Don't tell me you believe I love you
Look,
in my eyes, you're worse than a dog!
For women like you,
I can have as many of them as I want
Mu Shaoli
Back then, you forced me to...
Mrs. Sheng,
listen,
I'm tired of you now
Get out of my house!
Get lost!
Don't wanna leave?
Fine!
You are just a slut who was divorced many times!
Now, get out of here!
Zhong Wanruo
Make your last contribution then
My soldiers...
in the camp
They want women badly
Piss off
Wanruo
Why didn't you hit me?
Sorry
Wanruo