What on earth do you want?
Tell me,
what's the grudge between you and Zhong Wanruo?
She thought I sent my men
to kill her whole family
But I swear I didn't
I did send some men to her house
But when my men arrived,
her family members were long dead
If what Sheng Fang said is true,
and he had nothing to do with the Zhongs' death,
then who could be the murderer?
Brother
I'm telling the truth
I saw with my own eyes that
Ms. Xin was secretly meeting Zhong Wanruo
It's fine
Don't worry about it
Brother
What's your plan?
I already have an idea
All of this had to be Zhong Wanruo's conspiracy
It has nothing to do with Shaoli
So please don't vent your anger on him
Looks like you still want to marry him
Brother, you know I do
Alright
Since this is your dream,
I'll try my best to help you achieve it!
Really?
But...
Remember our family is your only backup
to secure your position in Marshal's Mansion
I know, brother
How many years have you been with me?
Three years
Sorry to make you suffer
Not at all
You gave me the glory
that every woman wants
Really?
Of course!
This is the consequence of betraying me!
Shaoli
Thank you for your hard work in the army these days
But why didn't you ask me for help
since it was such a serious matter?
Since you let me take charge of it,
certainly, I should use some harsh means
That's true
However,
Zhao is a trusted helper of mine
It can never be wrong to appoint your trusted men
But I don't think Mr. Zhao has any talent
It took him a month to handle the revolt,
and all he did was to kill the leading deserters
He is simply a good-for-nothing and will
hinder you from seizing the Central Region
How are things going between you and Zhong Wanruo?
Since your marriage is just a part of the plan,
don't give your heart to her
Rest assured, Commander
She is just a woman
She can never compare with our goal
of dominating the Central Region
I won't take her seriously
Good
I'm glad to hear that
You know,
Rubing is in deep love with you
And
the two of you are about the same age
Why don't you
take her in as a concubine?
Rubing is such a beautiful
and knowledgeable girl
How could I make her my concubine?
Shaoli
Of course you can
You're a Marshal now
Successful men like us
all have many concubines
You just don't want to upset Zhong Wanruo, right?
How could this be?
She can never compare with Miss Xia
Great
From now on, we're a family
Boss
Make do with it
This bunch of bastards
are having fun in the city, leaving us here
with only buns to eat
Isn't it annoying?
I'd lived a good life in the past 20 years
It's time to share the hardships with the people
That way, I can understand their needs better
Boss
What's your plan exactly?
Are you really going to join hands with Zhong Wanruo?
Zhong Wanruo controlled many businesses in Central Region
If we want to get weapons or supplies,
we have to rely on the Zhongs' Trading Firm
But she is quite hostile to us
Did you get any news
about my father?
Not yet
The whole Zhong family was killed,
and none of the Sheng family survived either
Where should I start with?
But I just found that
Ms. Liu, the old lady we saw the other day,
settled down outside the city with Zhong Wanruo's help
She should know some inside stories
Continue to investigate
I have to get to the bottom of this
I haven't got any news from Ms. Xin for a few days
Could something have happened to her?
Wanruo
You didn't go to the trading firm today?
You didn't go to the military camp either
Thank you
for your last suggestion
You're welcome
And...
Can you reconsider my request?
You still want to see Sheng Fang
He probably is the culprit of my family's death
I must find him
Alright
I promise you
I'll find him and hand him over to you
Really?
Yes
Thank you
Wanruo
Xia Jun
wants to marry Xia Rubing off to me
He wants her to be my concubine
You agreed to it?
I have no reason to refuse
That's right
You have no reason to disagree
Wanruo
Do you know that
what hurt me the most these years
was not the risk of
losing my life in the war,
but the painful memory
and the hatred from the past
I was consumed by the hatred
I was heartbroken
Heartbroken?
No
I won't feel heartbroken
Nor will I feel jealous
I'm sorry, Zirun
To take revenge,
I must have let you down
Zirun
Bless me in the heaven
so that I can avenge you as soon as possible
I promise you
we will see again
when your death is avenged