♪ Our story sounds absurd ♪
♪ It wasn’t perfect when we first met ♪
♪ When I was depressed, you turned up ♪
♪ Maybe we were destined to meet ♪
♪ When you come near, I have a crush ♪
♪ Every lie becomes sweet ♪
♪ Love looks messy, but my love grows ♪
♪ I care for everything about you ♪
♪ If I can say something to tell you I miss you ♪
♪ I’ll firmly say I love you ♪
♪ Love is growing and do you feel it ♪
♪ My world shines more brilliantly
with you around ♪
♪ If I can say something to tell you I miss you ♪
♪ I’ll firmly say I love you ♪
♪ Love is growing and do you feel it ♪
♪ My world shines more brilliantly
with you around ♪
♪ Forever ♪
= Mr. Honesty =
= Episode 10 =
= Li Zhe =
I’m really sorry for today.
You were right.
I actually planned everything in advance.
But I was not doing this
to get information about the project.
I just wanted to chase you.
I’ll apologize now
if I made you unhappy.
It won’t happen again.
Of course,
I hope we can go out on a date again.
Who’s texting you?
Oh.
Just chitchat.
My aunt!
Eat up now.
The porridge is getting cold.
Be careful.
I didn’t see him clearly last time in the company.
He’s got such a nice figure.
But I’ve never seen him go to the gym.
Why is his skin even lighter than mine?
Don’t sit on my clothes.
Oh!
Sorry.
This program is so funny.
Isn’t this a legal program?
Is it really funny?
Mr. Fang,
it’s very late now.
I should go.
Let me drive you home.
There’s no need.
I can take a taxi.
It’s too late. You can stay here.
Ah?
What do you mean?
Get me some more porridge.
Em.
What’s this?
You’ve been sleeping all day long.
But I didn’t.
Are you unhappy
because I disturbed
You and Li Zhe’s date?
Of course not!
I’m actually very happy.
I feel great to work with you
at midnight.
Sorry.
The date to submit the proposal
of the Moon Bay Resort Project is approaching.
I have to speed up.
You’ve been working for a day.
You can sleep now.
I can do it myself.
It’s ok.
I’m not tired.
How can I go to sleep
if you don’t?
Then how about this?
Let’s play a game
to wake you up.
Ok!
Well...
since it’s a game,
there should be some punishments.
The one who loses
should either do a punishment
or
answer another a question.
Lying is not allowed.
Whatever you want.
I won’t lose anyway.
Just don’t cry later.
= Square & Circle Architecture =
What is this?
A bridge.
It’s your turn.
I was wrong again?
Look at your face.
There’s no more room.
Wait.
This is unfair.
Because I’m not good at maths.
Then pick a game you’re good at.
Just tell me
what it is.
Right.
I’m not smart as you,
but what if it’s a game of luck?
Now, take your guess.
Childish!
How come?
Did I do some bad things?
I’m so unlucky.
This is not about luck.
My guess was based on statistics.
Don’t mention statistics.
I’ve been racking my brains.
Do you want to continue?
Come!
I haven’t won even once.
Continue!
This one.
You’re wrong!
Finally it’s my turn to...
I’ll pick “truth”.
How could you?
I finally won,
but you picked “truth”.
You set the rules first, right?
The loser can either answer a question
or let you draw on his face.
I’ll answer a question.
Alright, alright.
So boring.
Then...
do you hate me very much?
Why do you ask this?
Because I always lied to you.
You hate people who tell lies, don’t you?
I hate lies,
but I don’t hate you.
I used to think
a lie is just a lie.
Liars can’t be forgiven.
Now I still believe so.
But after what you told me that day,
I started to think
maybe there’s a reason
when people tell a lie.
Maybe they mean no harm,
or maybe
they just don’t have a choice.
Although
it won’t change
the fact that I hate lies.
But I’m willing to see it in a different way.
So,
you didn’t fire me
even if you knew
I lied to you back then.
You pretended you don’t know
even if you knew it was Sha Sha’s mistake.
Em.
What about you?
Do you hate me?
After all, things
didn’t go well for you
after you met me.
You lost your boyfriend and your job.
And I drove you away
when you came for an interview.
To be honest,
I hated you very much in the beginning.
I thought
you were self-conceited.
You never spoke nicely
and you always pissed people off.
But
after spending some time with you,
I found you’re actually very cute
though you can be weird sometimes.
But most importantly,
you’re a very kind person.
It’s just you don’t know how to express yourself.
So I don’t hate you.
Come.
Let’s continue.
I’m tired.
I’m going to sleep.
How could you?
You quit right after I won.
How boring!
I hate lies,
but I don’t hate you.
Fang Zhiyou,
thank you for not hating me.
This is the greatest thing
I heard today.
Good night.
Where is Xu Yiren?
Why hasn’t she come yet?
She’s on leave.
On leave?
Who approved that?
Me.
Mr. Fang,
I want to remind you of something.
Although Xu Yiren is your assistant,
she’s Administration Department’s employee.
Shouldn’t you notice me
when you let her take a leave?
Ok.
I’ll be careful next time.
Thank you.
Yuwen,
are you free
later?
I need your help.
Ok.
Mr. Zhang,
try the chocolate.
Thanks, Ms. He.
Apart from the coffee,
the chocolate here is also very delicious.
Thank you.
Mr. Fang,
how do you think?
Mr. Zhang,
I’m afraid your company
can’t meet our requirements.
Mr. Fang is saying that
our styles are not
very compatible on this project.
But we can cooperate in the future.
Oh.
In fact...
The coffee tastes good, right?
The chocolate also tastes good.
Have a try.
I was afraid you’d say something inappropriate.
How many modeling companies have we offended?
We shouldn’t burn our bridges.
That’s why I asked you to be here.
I was afraid I may lose control.
We always went to
meet clients together, didn’t we?
Right.
Had it not been for you,
Square & Circle would’ve closed down long ago.
You really mean this?
Of course.
Then I need to prove
I’m worthy of your compliment.
What’s wrong with you today?
Why do you care about how I think of you?
You never knew
what I cared about.
I forgot myself
last time.
I apologize to you.
You mean you wanted to fire Xu Yiren?
Em.
I didn’t take it to heart at all.
Because I know for certain that
no matter what you do,
you’re doing it for the company’s sake.
That’s for sure.
So I say
you and I are the best partners.
No one can replace us.
We’ve evaluated several modeling companies
within the industry.
This one
can’t meet our requirements.
We need to get in touch with the best ones.
Aside from the cost,
there’re just a few top modeling companies.
It’s very likely
they’ve already been fully booked.
Besides, the Moon Bay Resort Project
is small.
I’m afraid they won’t consider it seriously.
I know.
But I want to give it a try.
I see.
Leave it to me.
Thank you.
For what?
It’s just my job,
isn’t it?
Hello?
Mr. Fang! Mr. Fang!
Where are you?
I’m in the driving school.
I’ll talk to you later.
Bye-bye.
Back up!
Steer to the right!
Stop! Stop!
Stop! Stop! Stop!
You should
hit the footbrake
instead of shouting, alright?
Sorry, instructor.
How about
I do it again?
No.
That’s it for today.
You can go home now.
Ah?
Instructor, I...
Practice hard.
A driver can earn more than an assistant.
I’ve taken a screenshot.
I hope you can keep your word.
I never go back on my word.
Don’t you know?
Xu Yiren.
It’s you?
Why are you here?
Don’t give me that look.
I’m really here to change my driving license.
I got my driving license abroad.
I can’t use it in China.
I really didn’t stalk you.
You...
You were very bold
when you talked to me before,
but seems
you’re afraid of me today?
I’m not.
Then is it because you hate me?
You don’t want to see me?
No.
What then?
If I
promise you
I won’t ask you anything about Fang Zhiyou,
can we still be friends?
Still not ok?
I’m almost begging you.
But you...
You’re really not good at acting.
Is it that bad?
Alright.
Seems these tricks
really don’t work on you.
Sometimes,
nothing works better than a sincere heart.
You really talk like Fang Zhiyou.
Actually everything I said just now
is from the bottom of my heart.
It’s true.
I went abroad
after I finished high school.
I didn’t make any friends there.
I also lost contact
with those friends
I used to have in China.
We’ve met for just several times.
But we chatted happily every time.
I admit that part of the reason
why I wanted to chase you
is you’re Fang Zhiyou’s assistant,
but today,
I really mean it
when I say
I want to make friends with you.
It’s true.
Last time in the hospital...
I knew.
It must be a coincidence.
Could this mean
we’re destined to meet?
We always bumped into each other, didn’t we?
So,
Miss Xu Yiren,
can you give me another chance
to let me introduce myself?
I’m Li Zhe.
I’m Xu Yiren.
Yuwen,
sorry to
keep you waiting.
I was in a meeting.
It’s fine.
It’s my bad.
I asked you out abruptly.
Did I affect your work?
You didn’t.
Nothing is more important than you.
Yuwen,
you wanted to see me so urgently.
What can I do for you?
I want to ask you
to do me a favor.
But probably
I’ll put you in a difficult position.
It’s fine
if you find it inconvenient.
I’ll do it for you as long as
it doesn’t harm Liangshan’s interests.
You’re really loyal to my father.
I know
you don’t want to hear this,
but I still want to say it.
Mr. He taught me a lot of things.
He helped me
become who I am today.
So I’ll never betray him.
Not like someone.
Mr. He placed great expectations on him,
but he betrayed Mr. He.
Some things are not as simple as they appear.
It’s hard to say who’s wrong.
But I didn’t come here to argue with you.
Qiming,
are there any
good modeling companies
that you can recommend to me?
You’re doing this for Fang Zhiyou?
Yuwen,
you’re really
making things difficult for me.
I understand.
Don’t worry.
Thank you all the same.
Thank you for making time to see me.
Wait a moment.
Let me think.
There’re several modeling companies
that are cooperating with Liangshan regularly.
I’ll have to exclude them.
But I knew Mr. Qi
from Dasheng Modeling.
I can introduce you to him.
But Dasheng is a prestigious company.
I’m not sure if they will
take your project.
As long as you can put us in touch,
I’ll take care of the rest.
Ok.
I’ll get right on it.
Thank you, Qiming.
From now on,
you’ll take over
Dasheng.
Just let me know
if you have any questions.
Thank you.
You’ll be transferred to the headquarter.
Congratulations.
Mr. Qi,
I heard Square & Circle
is seeking cooperation with Dasheng.
Em.
They asked Chen Qiming from Liangshan
to introduce us.
But I refused him.
Their project is too small.
Besides,
Dasheng can’t take more projects
for this year.
Fang Zhiyou’s my friend,
please take this project
for the sake of me.
I’ll be transferred away very soon.
Since he’s your friend,
why don’t you
cooperate with him directly
after you take over Dasheng?
I actually don’t want to cooperate with him.
I don’t get it.
It’s hard to explain my relationship
with Fang Zhiyou.
Anyway,
I hope you can do me this favor.
I’ll make it worth your while.
Qiming,
it’s me.
I reconsidered that project
you talked about last time.
I’d like to meet them personally
and discuss it.
Ok.
Ok, I’ll await your news.
No problem.
Why did you choose
a resort in such a remote place?
Who will ever come here?
That will depend on
if our design is attractive enough.
Seems you’re very interested
in this project.
You’re even looking for the best modeling company.
That project of Huaxing is very big,
but our Design Department
created the 3D design ourselves.
The size of the project is not important.
What’s important is if it’s meaningful.
The concept of eco-resort is very meaningful.
Besides, I love to create new things.
If we’re just imitating,
no matter how well we do,
we can be no more than a shadow of others.
Only things with our names written on them
are things that really belong to us.
Things with our names written on them?
The only thing I’ve ever
written my name on is test paper.
We’ve got a flat tire.
What should we do?
Let’s walk back.
60 kilometers!
How is that possible?
Hello, Yuwen?
Zhiyou, where are you?
I’m at Moon Bay.
Why are you still there?
Do you still remember
our appointment with Mr. Qi?
Yes, I know.
But there’s a problem with my car.
I can’t go there now.
Can you go alone?
If it’s not feasible,
let’s fix another date.
It’s not easy to get an appointment with him.
Fine. Let’s not change the date.
I’ll go there myself.
Ok.
Thank you, Yuwen.
No problem.
Be careful on the road.
Em.
Xu Yiren.
What are you doing?
I’m searching for the methods
to deal with a flat tire.
Have you found something?
Yeah.
First,
we need to change the tire.
Do you have a spare tire in the car?
We’ll need some tools to do that.
For example, a jack.
A jack is something you use
to lift the car by pressing its handle.
Why did you get in the car?
Didn’t your instructor tell you?
After a car accident happens,
you should first move the car
to a location that doesn’t
obstruct traffic.
Oh, ok.
Eat some bread.
I thought we can go back
before dinner time,
so I just brought some bread.
You can eat yourself.
I’m not hungry.
For real?
Eat yourself, will you?
Oh.
How about...
I give you half of it?
If you don’t eat,
I wouldn’t dare to.
This roadside assistance company
is so unreliable.
They said one hour.
Now four hours have passed,
they still haven’t arrived.
I called the Tourist Service Center.
The person-in-charge said
they were off duty.
So they can only pick us up tomorrow morning.
That’s why I hate liars.
If they had said they can’t make it,
we wouldn’t have waited for such a long time.
Calm down.
Don’t get angry.
Look at this place.
The scenery is very beautiful.
The air is fresh.
And there are mountains and rivers.
We can think of this as a camping trip.
Not bad, right?
You like here?
Yes.
Isn’t it beautiful?
Look there.
Ms. He is really one in a million.
So forthright!
I like to work with forthright persons.
Mr. Qi,
let me drink a toast to you.
We’ve always been looking forward
to working with Dasheng.
Your assistance
in the future would be highly appreciated.
I’d love to do that.
Although Square & Circle is not a big company,
I’ve actually heard about
Fang Zhiyou before.
It’s just
he said
he’d come today.
Now I start to doubt his sincerity.
It’s not like that, Mr. Qi.
Here’s the thing.
Mr. Fang’s car
broke down unexpectedly,
he really couldn’t make it here.
But he said
he’ll apologize
to you personally next time.
There’s no time like the present.
How about this?
You can drink three cups on behalf of him.
How do you think?
Mr. Qi,
Ms. He is a cheap drunk.
Let me drink on her behalf.
Qiming,
you want to be a hero?
Fine.
But you need to drink more.
Waitress.
Get us five cups.
Mr. Fang,
have you got this feeling
that something is staring at us?
We’re out in the mountain.
It’s normal
to encounter wild boars and wolves.
Don’t make a fuss about it.
Really?
But this is a resort.
I don’t think there’ll be beasts.
It’s hard to say.
This place is well-preserved.
Then...
Let’s make a fire.
Animals are afraid of fire, right?
Why are you lying down?
Are you going to sleep?
Look up.
It’s so beautiful.
It’s very hard
to see such a beautiful sky in the city.
So let’s not waste time
talking about wild boars and wolves.
When was the last time
you saw such beautiful stars?
Last year,
in Finland.
There were also auroras.
Well, alright…
What about you?
I...
When I was 12.
12?
Em.
Also out in a mountain like this.
That year,
our teacher took us on a spring outing.
I wandered around
and lost my way.
I couldn’t find the teacher and my classmates.
So I began to cry.
I thought I was going to die there.
And then?
How did you get home?
Then,
I met a boy who’s older than me.
He carried me to a nearby police station.
When I was on his back,
I looked up
and saw stars scattering across the sky.
Just like now.
Are you still in touch with him?
No.
I burst into tears
when we arrived the police station.
I forgot
to ask his name.
When I thought of that,
he had already left.
It’s a pity.
Em.
I’ve tried to find him.
But it’s been so many years.
I haven’t got any clues.
I don’t know how he’s doing now.
That only means that
you’re not destined to meet again.
Probably not.
I always felt that I’ll see him again.
If
I ever
see him again,
I’ll...
What will you do?
♪ Carousels and skyscrapers ♪
♪ Me on the other side ♪
♪ Who sees the weakness ♪
♪ Behind my optimism ♪
♪ Lie in the room ♪
♪ Feels like floating in the black hole ♪
Qiming,
why are you just standing there?
It’s your show time.
Alright.
Wait.
Mr. Qi,
I look forward to a smooth cooperation with you.
Sure.
Be careful. Be careful.
Let me help you.
It’s all right.
I can walk myself.
You can go back.
How can I leave when you’re like this?
Fang Zhiyou is so unreasonable.
How could he
let a lady meet the client alone?
Mr. Qi was not happy about this,
so he made you drink that much.
It’s fine.
No matter what,
he’s agreed to cooperate with us.
Hello,
you need a driver, right?
Yes.
Ok.
Thank you.
Please wait a sec.
Em.
Qiming,
thank you for today.
I’ll treat you a meal another day.
How about
I send you home?
There’s no need.
You should leave.
Mister.
Hi.
Drive safely.
Ok.
Be careful.
Don’t worry, Mister.
No.
I have to give Zhiyou a call
and tell him this good news.
♪ My love for you runs so deep ♪
♪ But you never loved me ♪
♪ How can I heal my wounded heart ♪
Wake up.
Yuwen.
♪ You won’t admit your mistake anyway ♪
♪ I know you won’t compromise ♪
♪ How can I persuade you ♪
♪ Not to leave me ♪
♪ You gave me a promise before ♪
♪ I enjoyed some heart-warming moments ♪
♪ And I never stopped loving you ♪
I knew you’re drunk.
So I followed here.
♪ You lit my hope when you came ♪
♪ You lit my passion ♪
♪ And then you turned around ♪
♪ To seek another relationship ♪
♪ You said we’ll meet again ♪
♪ If you turn back ♪
♪ I’m waiting for you to rewrite the ending ♪
♪ Can you please wait a bit longer ♪
♪ Don’t give up yet ♪
♪ These are all lies ♪
♪ Leave me if you turn back ♪
Xu Yiren?
Em?
Mr. Fang.
Morning.
What a refreshing start!
Does it still hurt?
It doesn’t.
Em.
Did I drool?
I didn’t.
Liar!
You said you’ll never tell a lie.
I’m not lying.
This is
a joke.
This is a joke.
You sound so justified.
Xu Yiren,
now you’re like a little pufferfish.
Mr. Fang,
pufferfish is poisonous.
Don’t mess with me.
Yuwen, you’re amazing.
I always wanted to cooperate with Dasheng.
But our projects were not big enough.
They refused every time.
I didn’t expect
you persuaded them over a meal.
I’m glad you know this.
They sent this contract early in the morning.
I already read it through.
There are a lot of articles.
But they’re reasonable.
Most importantly,
they’ll arrange things to suit our timetable.
I recognize
Dasheng’s ability.
With their assistance,
now I’m more confident
about the Moon Bay Resort Project.
Thank you.
What’s more,
I shouldn’t have
let you go there alone yesterday.
Sorry.
It’s all right.
It was better that way.
So you wouldn’t say anything inappropriate.
What’s wrong?
Are you feeling unwell?
I’m fine.
- Really? - Em.
Ok.
I’ll leave the project to you then.
Sign the contract,
and start the project asap.
Em.
I’m off.
Go back early.
Em.
Sha Sha,
bring me some antacids.
The antacids
are normally here.
How come there aren’t any?
Sha Sha, what are you doing?
Ms. He is having a stomachache.
But she has used up all the antacids.
Alas!
Is it serious?
Her face has turned pale.
No, I have to go out and buy some.
Hey, wait.
I think I have some.
I’ll have a look. Wait a sec.
Really?
Em.
Gosh!
Here you are.
Yiren, I owe you one!
You should hurry.
See you soon.
♪ The most dazzling sun ♪
♪ Outside the window ♪
♪ Who cares ♪
♪ Where it goes after it gets dark ♪
♪ Waiting ♪
♪ Until the moon lights up the sky ♪
♪ The whole noisy world ♪
♪ Should come to a halt ♪
♪ Gazes and cheers ♪
♪ Fall like tides ♪
♪ Back to the room ♪
♪ I think to myself ♪
♪ Loneliness is always quiet ♪
♪ But it feels like being shrouded in a net ♪
♪ The quieter it is around ♪
♪ The noisier I feel ♪
♪ Carousels and skyscrapers ♪
♪ Contrasts in life ♪
♪ Who sees the weakness ♪
♪ Behind my optimism ♪
♪ Something can only be kept in my heart ♪
♪ Raging silently ♪
♪ Me in the mirror ♪
♪ Which one is more like me ♪
♪ Back to the corner from the spotlight ♪
♪ Contrasts in life ♪
♪ Leave much confusion to time ♪
♪ Wait until it falls ♪
♪ Lie in the room ♪
♪ Feels like floating in the black hole ♪
♪ I’m sober when I’m sleepless ♪
♪ Having realistic dream ♪