♪Meeting you, even the clouds
forget to breathe♪
♪For you, the rainbow indulges♪
♪Shortening the distance of the sky,
drawing closer♪
♪You said, to avoid the end of memories♪
♪You need to fold up your thoughts,
in a leaping heart♪
♪But unwilling to stay calm,
I can't help but think of you♪
♪After three reincarnations,
we meet again♪
♪Who is secretly leading us♪
♪Running to you,
the destined stir of heart♪
♪Thanks to the destiny's pity and favor♪
♪You broke into my heart accidentally♪
♪Filling the expectation
of many years' vacancy♪
♪Trying to reach out hands
and bravely love♪
♪Thank you for appearing in my mind♪
♪And chasing away the gloom♪
♪Through blurred sadness,
I can see the clear future♪
♪You're still in my heart♪
=The Deliberations of Love=
=Episode 3=
Wait.
Now, Pei Xun and I have
no connection at all.
Why should I be afraid of him?
(This time I must not marry anyone
who has any ties with the royal family.)
(Surviving is of utmost importance.
Yes, that's right.)
(One month later)
The young man
who was with Miss Liu is Yu Minghe,
the only son of Mr. Yu,
the Assistant Minister of Rites.
He's a famous gentleman in the capital.
A gentleman.
I have to say,
Mr. Yu is knowledgeable
and full of talents.
The only son
of the Assistant Minister of Rites
cannot be stopped
in his future prospects.
Made for each other with Miss Liu.
We don't care about his future.
The key is to marry a stable person.
He is. He is very stable.
So you...
Yes, I want to.
You need to act more reserved.
You can't be racing to marry like this.
Mother, Mr. Yu is reliable.
He's perfect for me.
I will leave everything to you, Mother.
Qing, you've only known
him for a few months.
Then let's set the marriage.
(It must be settled at once.)
(Only then can I be sure
that my fate has really changed.)
So eager to get married?
Let's see then.
We can set the marriage
on a good day first.
Good.
Your father has not returned
from the palace yet.
Could something major have happened?
Something happened!
Oh, there's trouble.
What happened?
Why did you arrive home so late?
Big news in the court today.
(Is Pei Xun...?)
What happened?
Don't keep us in suspense.
His Majesty has appointed
Prince Yi as the crown prince.
The Emperor's edict says,
"The sixth prince, Pei Xun,
exhibits brilliance and unusualness."
"He is exceptionally gifted,
deemed by the heavens."
"Now I obey the initial decree,
follow the rituals,"
"acquiesce to public opinion,
and solemnly inform heaven and earth"
"that I grant him the imperial seal
and ascend him to crown prince."
"He shall shoulder governing duties
and assume the military."
"All departments shall report
to the crown prince for decisions."
That's all.
(Camper Pei succeeded in ascending
to the throne this time!)
It really was a missed opportunity
to join the royal family.
My lord, why would His Majesty
appoint Prince Yi as the crown prince?
My lord, say something.
It seems I'm really not fated
to become a crown princess.
With his character,
after becoming the crown prince,
he must be more arrogant and conceited.
Your Highness, these are sent
by local officials and feudal lords.
The ink is still fresh.
It seems they were taken by surprise
that I took this position. So hasty.
Whose gift is this?
It's from Mr. Zhao,
the Vice Censor-in-chief.
It's time for a replacement
of the Vice Censor-in-chief.
Yes.
This is from Mr. Yu,
the Assistant Minister of Rites.
The Assistant Minister of Rites.
Mr. Yu used to be
a supporter of Prince Chen.
I didn't expect him
to switch sides so quickly.
(The second volume of Shanhai Jing)
He is still waiting outside.
Yu Minghe, the son
of the Assistant Minister of Rites.
Let him in.
Yes.
Greetings, Your Highness.
Mr. Yu, please.
I've long heard that your family
is well-versed in classics.
I've been looking
for this rare book for a long time.
This gift is really to my liking.
I'm very grateful.
It was nothing.
The gift was prepared by my son.
I didn't expect it to have the honor
of being liked by Your Highness.
Very good.
Your son must be
well-educated and learned.
What position does he hold now?
Your Highness, you flatter us.
My son hasn't joined officialdom yet.
What a pity.
This shouldn't happen.
It's crazy that nobody's scooped him up.
My son is naturally indifferent
to fame and fortune.
But at home,
he often mentions Your Highness.
He takes Your Highness
as his role model.
He says that if he's an official,
he must follow you.
He is even not afraid to die
for the country and the people.
Thanks for your respect.
I'll get a chance to meet him.
Thank you for your appreciation.
- You may leave now.
- Yes.
Seeing Your Highness in power, they want
to curry favor with you.
I'll hold a feast in my palace tomorrow.
Send an invitation
to Minister Liu's mansion
personally.
Yes.
(What's going on?)
(I have an ominous feeling.)
♪Time has taken away all
between you and me♪
♪Yet memories surreptitiously remain♪
♪The thrill of encountering you again♪
♪Is but an exchange of glances
in a split second♪
♪The stars that light up the night
scattered around us♪
♪So-called worries become
an excuse to evade♪
♪Not daring to look back again♪
♪Your tenderness is always behind me♪
♪Becoming my reason
to rush towards you unswervingly♪
♪The moonlight has turned white,
and speaks of the future♪
♪Walking together
on the long journey ahead♪
♪Wandering in the crowds♪
♪Holding your hand,
the gaze is softer than the breeze♪
♪Time has taken away all
between you and me♪
♪Yet memories surreptitiously remain♪
♪The thrill of encountering you again♪
♪Is but an exchange of glances
in a split second♪
♪The stars that light up the night
scattered around us♪
♪So-called worries become
an excuse to evade♪
♪Not daring to look back again♪
♪Your tenderness is always behind me♪
♪Becoming my reason
to rush towards you unswervingly♪
♪The moonlight has turned white,
and speaks of the future♪
♪Walking together
on the long journey ahead♪
♪Wandering in the crowds♪
♪Holding your hand,
the gaze is softer than the breeze♪
♪Time has taken away all
between you and me♪
♪Even if it's too late to speak,
my destiny to meet you♪
♪Is but an exchange of glances
in a split second♪
♪The stars that light up the night
scattered around us♪