♪Meeting you, even the clouds
forget to breathe♪
♪For you, the rainbow indulges♪
♪Shortening the distance of the sky,
drawing closer♪
♪You said, to avoid the end of memories♪
♪You need to fold up your thoughts,
in a leaping heart♪
♪But unwilling to stay calm,
I can't help but think of you♪
♪After three reincarnations,
we meet again♪
♪Who is secretly leading us♪
♪Running to you,
the destined stir of heart♪
♪Thanks to the destiny's pity and favor♪
♪You broke into my heart accidentally♪
♪Filling the expectation
of many years' vacancy♪
♪Trying to reach out hands
and bravely love♪
♪Thank you for appearing in my mind♪
♪And chasing away the gloom♪
♪Through blurred sadness,
I can see the clear future♪
♪You're still in my heart♪
=The Deliberations of Love=
=Episode 1=
(The 22nd day of the first lunar month
in Year 12 of Yongde)
The wine served no longer appeal?
(Prince Yi, Pei Xun)
Or getting bored with your concubine?
(Princess Yi, Liu Yueqing)
Why risk your life to be Crown Prince?
When do I have a concubine?
I'm seeking one for you.
But I'm afraid that day won't come.
The moon tonight
is the same as
on the night you married me.
Do you regret it?
(Cut the bull.)
(Does it matter now?)
(We are about to die.)
If there is a next life...
Don't say it.
It's all in the wine.
Farewell to Prince Yi
and Princess Yi!
(If there is an afterlife,
I don't want to meet you again.)
(Camper Pei.)
(Pei Xun once told me
a prince should compete for the crown.)
(In the spirit of being a good prince,)
(he advanced boldly and decisively,)
(and eventually, he got himself doomed.)
(And I got roped into it, too.)
(Rebellion is no small matter.)
(The Emperor was furious
and gave us poisoned wine.)
Your Highness.
(Prince Yi's Mansion.)
(Why am I here?)
Luo, what time is it now?
It's already one in the morning.
What year is it now?
(Maid of Liu's Mansion, Luo)
You must have had a deep sleep.
The 20th day of the first lunar month
in Year 12 of Yongde.
(The 20th day of the first lunar month)
The 20th day.
Where is the Prince?
His Highness is discussing matters
with General Wang in the front hall.
(I went back to the day
before Pei Xun's rebellion.)
Luo, go serve in the front hall.
There are distinguished guests today.
Don't neglect them.
Yes.
(One in the morning.)
There's still time. As long as
I stay away from the death-bringer,
I am able to live well in this life.
My lady, where are you going?
Liu Yueqing, you'd better
behave yourself.
Without my permission today,
you can't step out of the room.
Your Highness,
do you feel uncomfortable?
Luo, I feel like I'm going to die.
I feel cold all over my body right now.
My head is so dizzy,
and I feel like vomiting.
You seem to be pregnant.
That's good news.
His Highness will be very happy.
Yes, Luo. I am pregnant.
Go to see the prince now
and tell him I have
something very important to tell him.
Yes.
Your Highness.
What's the matter?
You are going to be a father soon.
Have you seen the doctor? How far along?
Probably two to three months.
It's too late now.
I'll ask Luo to get a doctor
to have a careful check tomorrow.
If I'm not mistaken,
it's been a month
since you and I last slept together.
I was ordered to leave the capital
for three months before that.
Who's the father?
How dare you.
Tell me, whose child is this?
Please spare me.
Tell me.
(Camper Pei, you fell
a little short in schemes.)
(You want to rebel? Dream on!)
(Now you can't do it.)
(You should thank me after you wake up.)
(I'm doing this to save your life.)
General, it's past the agreed time,
but the prince hasn't appeared...
No more waiting.
Proceed according to the plan.
Yes.
(What can you do now?)
The decree has arrived.
Prince Yi planned to usurp and
is hence granted poisoned wine.
(Oh, no.)
Farewell...
Wait, I know the process.
(I am stupid. Even if I stop Pei Xun,)
(I can't stop his bumbling accomplice.)
(What a bad leader,
causing me to die again.)
(Camper Pei, I hope
I never see you again in my next life.)
(Liu Yueqing.)
♪Time has taken away all
between you and me♪
♪Yet memories surreptitiously remain♪
♪The thrill of encountering you again♪
♪Is but an exchange of glances
in a split second♪
♪The stars that light up the night
scattered around us♪
♪So-called worries become
an excuse to evade♪
♪Not daring to look back again♪
♪Your tenderness is always behind me♪
♪Becoming my reason
to rush towards you unswervingly♪
♪The moonlight has turned white,
and speaks of the future♪
♪Walking together
on the long journey ahead♪
♪Wandering in the crowds♪
♪Holding your hand,
the gaze is softer than the breeze♪
♪Time has taken away all
between you and me♪
♪Yet memories surreptitiously remain♪
♪The thrill of encountering you again♪
♪Is but an exchange of glances
in a split second♪
♪The stars that light up the night
scattered around us♪
♪So-called worries become
an excuse to evade♪
♪Not daring to look back again♪
♪Your tenderness is always behind me♪
♪Becoming my reason
to rush towards you unswervingly♪
♪The moonlight has turned white,
and speaks of the future♪
♪Walking together
on the long journey ahead♪
♪Wandering in the crowds♪
♪Holding your hand,
the gaze is softer than the breeze♪
♪Time has taken away all
between you and me♪
♪Even if it's too late to speak,
my destiny to meet you♪
♪Is but an exchange of glances
in a split second♪
♪The stars that light up the night
scattered around us♪