♪Meeting you, even the clouds
forget to breathe♪
♪For you, the rainbow indulges♪
♪Shortening the distance of the sky,
drawing closer♪
♪You said, to avoid the end of memories♪
♪You need to fold up your thoughts,
in a leaping heart♪
♪But unwilling to stay calm,
I can't help but think of you♪
♪After three reincarnations,
we meet again♪
♪Who is secretly leading us♪
♪Running to you,
the destined stir of heart♪
♪Thanks to the destiny's pity and favor♪
♪You broke into my heart accidentally♪
♪Filling the expectation
of many years' vacancy♪
♪Trying to reach out hands
and bravely love♪
♪Thank you for appearing in my mind♪
♪And chasing away the gloom♪
♪Through blurred sadness,
I can see the clear future♪
♪You're still in my heart♪
=The Deliberations of Love=
=Episode 14=
Miss Liu, this vase
is a precious gift
from the Empress Dowager,
rarely seen in the capital.
I will surely compensate you.
Seriously?
Do you think this is an ordinary item?
Everything has a price.
Name your price, Your Highness.
Han Zhen.
(They're well prepared.)
6,700 taels of silver.
What? It's a rip-off.
Are you going to deny it?
(You devil.)
I don't mind asking Minister Liu
to do the accounts.
No, don't.
The value of these treasures
will be doubled a few years later.
Father, if I get kidnapped,
will you come to rescue me?
Whoever dares to hurt you,
I will fight them to death.
You don't need to.
What if the robbers want a ransom?
Will you use your private money
to save me?
I just fooled you.
Losing my money will kill me.
Don't be silly.
(I'm doomed.)
Have you thought of a solution?
Not yet.
If you can't compensate,
in my opinion,
you can work in the Eastern Palace.
It's deducted from your monthly salary
until it is paid off.
What do you say?
(Well played.)
(It's your trap.)
Your Highness.
I need to discuss it
with my father.
(Help.)
Get her the ink and paper.
Let Miss Liu write a letter
to Minister Liu.
Yes.
Fine.
Thank you.
(To my parents)
(It's a long story, but no worries.)
(An accident happened
in the Eastern Palace.)
(I owe His Highness six thousand.)
(If you have spare money,
please consider redeeming me.)
(If the debt is not paid tomorrow,)
(I'll have to work here
to offset the debt.)
(Fortunately, it's a cozy place.)
(Don't worry about me.)
(I will return once the debt is paid.)
If Qing works in the Eastern Palace,
is it okay?
(Even if my father doesn't help,)
(my mother will save me.)
Your Highness,
I think it's inappropriate.
If I stay, I'm afraid
it will damage your reputation
and attract criticism.
Why? We're unmarried adult people.
But...
(We're fine. Just focus on your work.)
(Do not make His Highness unhappy.)
I can tell
His Highness cares about Qing.
Don't worry.
That's good.
(What a cold father.)
It's getting late.
Miss Liu, please go to your room.
So, you invited me to the Spring Hunting
to be the decoy.
You wanted to save
Shangguan Yan back then, not me
You set me up?
(I was supposed
to keep a distance from that jinx.)
(But I'm trapped now.)
(I'll be tormented before leaving.)
(I can't stand it.)
(Forget it.)
♪Time has taken away all
between you and me♪
♪Yet memories surreptitiously remain♪
♪The thrill of encountering you again♪
♪Is but an exchange of glances
in a split second♪
♪The stars that light up the night
scattered around us♪
♪So-called worries become
an excuse to evade♪
♪Not daring to look back again♪
♪Your tenderness is always behind me♪
♪Becoming my reason
to rush towards you unswervingly♪
♪The moonlight has turned white,
and speaks of the future♪
♪Walking together
on the long journey ahead♪
♪Wandering in the crowds♪
♪Holding your hand,
the gaze is softer than the breeze♪
♪Time has taken away all
between you and me♪
♪Yet memories surreptitiously remain♪
♪The thrill of encountering you again♪
♪Is but an exchange of glances
in a split second♪
♪The stars that light up the night
scattered around us♪
♪So-called worries become
an excuse to evade♪
♪Not daring to look back again♪
♪Your tenderness is always behind me♪
♪Becoming my reason
to rush towards you unswervingly♪
♪The moonlight has turned white,
and speaks of the future♪
♪Walking together
on the long journey ahead♪
♪Wandering in the crowds♪
♪Holding your hand,
the gaze is softer than the breeze♪
♪Time has taken away all
between you and me♪
♪Even if it's too late to speak,
my destiny to meet you♪
♪Is but an exchange of glances
in a split second♪
♪The stars that light up the night
scattered around us♪