♪Meeting you, even the clouds
forget to breathe♪
♪For you, the rainbow indulges♪
♪Shortening the distance of the sky,
drawing closer♪
♪You said, to avoid the end of memories♪
♪You need to fold up your thoughts,
in a leaping heart♪
♪But unwilling to stay calm,
I can't help but think of you♪
♪After three reincarnations,
we meet again♪
♪Who is secretly leading us♪
♪Running to you,
the destined stir of heart♪
♪Thanks to the destiny's pity and favor♪
♪You broke into my heart accidentally♪
♪Filling the expectation
of many years' vacancy♪
♪Trying to reach out hands
and bravely love♪
♪Thank you for appearing in my mind♪
♪And chasing away the gloom♪
♪Through blurred sadness,
I can see the clear future♪
♪You're still in my heart♪
=The Deliberations of Love=
=Episode 19=
You've come up with a great plan.
Now, Pei Xun's been put
under house arrest
by the Emperor
due to the food supply shortages.
The border army is at a disadvantage.
If we launch a surprise attack,
they won't have time to react.
We'll definitely catch
them all in one swoop.
You're flattering me, general.
I'm just doing what I can.
It's due to your brilliant leadership
that we can carry out
the plan unnoticed.
Now the situation is in our favor.
When our great cause is achieved,
I will promote you
and guarantee you wealth and honor.
Thank you for that.
You might be celebrating too early.
The Emperor has banned the crown prince
from leaving his palace,
but it's merely for show.
I came here this time
by His Majesty's order
to thoroughly investigate this matter.
So, we've been working in vain.
What does it matter?
In this world, what can kill people
isn't just weapons,
but also a silver tongue.
Once rumors take root among people,
we just need to fuel the flames a bit.
Even if the Emperor trusts Pei Xun,
he will have to yield
to the public opinion.
You mean...
You two aren't locals.
Why are you here?
Sir,
we are just passing by
after a fruitless relative search.
Looking for relatives?
(Chen Village)
Ahead is the border.
You better go back as soon as possible.
It's not too peaceful around here.
Thank you for the admonition.
It's getting late.
Why not stay here for a night
and continue our journey
early tomorrow morning?
Sounds good.
Sir...
You two don't look like bad guys.
There's an empty room in my house.
You can stay at my place
and leave tomorrow
if you're okay with that.
Thank you.
(Chen Village)
So once the crown prince's misconduct
is confirmed,
everyone will surely be dissatisfied
with his regency.
Then we can make a push,
and it would be considered justifiable.
Kill two birds with one stone move!
Qing.
Pei Xun.
Come here.
(Qing, I miss you so much.)
(Is this what they call
longing in love?)
Pei Xun.
Han Zhen, let's take a look.
Okay.
Sir, what happened?
What else could happen?
The war has been intense recently,
and the border army
has been levying our food
or enlisting those unable
to provide food.
Who can afford that?
A few more times
and we won't be able to survive.
You are outsiders.
Go hide right away.
This is the crown prince's order.
No time can be wasted.
Move faster, all of you!
This is far from enough.
Think you're dismissing a beggar?
It is too little!
Spare me, sir,
I really have nothing left.
I still have an 80-year-old mother
and two children that need to eat.
What is she still living for
at such an old age?
She might as well be buried.
Please understand, folks.
The prince had no choice
but to give this order.
If there is no food,
our soldiers cannot fight
to protect our country.
When the nation is in ruins,
no one can survive.
Nonsense.
Who are you?
Daring to interfere in military affairs,
do you want to die?
The ones seeking death are you.
Taking advantage
of the crown prince's name to do wrong.
How dare you!
Who are you to accuse us
of impersonation?
What proof do you have?
You claim to be
under His Highness' command.
What proof do you have?
I...
His Highness leads
the troops with strict discipline.
He would never pillage the people
or conscript people casually.
You claim to be
under His Highness' command,
yet you behave
no different from bandits.
Are you taking advantage
of His Highness' name
to loot the people around
so as to tarnish
His Highness' reputation?
What are your intentions?
The kind prince
would never levy our vital food.
Impersonating His Highness' soldiers.
They are too bold.
You raving lunatic.
I will take your two heads
and then slaughter
these uncooperative rats.
Miss Liu, you take the villagers and go.
Everyone, go. Go!
Kill them!
Why are you posing as the prince's men
and levying grain everywhere?
What? We are his men.
We are His Highness' soldiers
in charge of grain levies.
Speak the truth, or we will kill you.
I am telling the truth.
All the grain we collect
is sent to the military camps.
Still talking nonsense?
If you're telling the truth,
where is the collected food?
Take us there.
♪Time has taken away all
between you and me♪
♪Yet memories surreptitiously remain♪
♪The thrill of encountering you again♪
♪Is but an exchange of glances
in a split second♪
♪The stars that light up the night
scattered around us♪
♪So-called worries become
an excuse to evade♪
♪Not daring to look back again♪
♪Your tenderness is always behind me♪
♪Becoming my reason
to rush towards you unswervingly♪
♪The moonlight has turned white,
and speaks of the future♪
♪Walking together
on the long journey ahead♪
♪Wandering in the crowds♪
♪Holding your hand,
the gaze is softer than the breeze♪
♪Time has taken away all
between you and me♪
♪Yet memories surreptitiously remain♪
♪The thrill of encountering you again♪
♪Is but an exchange of glances
in a split second♪
♪The stars that light up the night
scattered around us♪
♪So-called worries become
an excuse to evade♪
♪Not daring to look back again♪
♪Your tenderness is always behind me♪
♪Becoming my reason
to rush towards you unswervingly♪
♪The moonlight has turned white,
and speaks of the future♪
♪Walking together
on the long journey ahead♪
♪Wandering in the crowds♪
♪Holding your hand,
the gaze is softer than the breeze♪
♪Time has taken away all
between you and me♪
♪Even if it's too late to speak,
my destiny to meet you♪
♪Is but an exchange of glances
in a split second♪
♪The stars that light up the night
scattered around us♪