Episode 1
Aikachan is a liar.
No one can take it seriously.
Sister, let's go.
I said no more coming, Miss An.
Who is it?
Princess, you have to escape from the Wudang Kachan.
I'm not.
The princess of Wudang Kachan is here.
Who was that?
General Su, you misunderstood.
It was Xiao Mo's illness.
Then why did you have to fight with the princess?
I have a free mother.
I was in the same illness with the woman.
Then I got a few treatment together.
I never did anything wrong.
How could you misunderstand me?
Yes, General Su.
It's obvious that the princess is in love with you.
How could you be so heartless?
No.
I saw it clearly just now.
Young Master, I'm a little bored.
I want to go back and rest.
I'll go back with you.
What else do you want?
Let's go.
It seems that the princess is not ill.
Thank you for your help.
I almost got fooled by Miss.
Miss, you really like General Su?
Yes.
I like the close-up of the heart.
I don't care about the little things.
I want to be with him.
So I want to spend my life with you.
I can?
I advise you.
Don't waste your energy on me.
It's just to admit to the Prime Minister.
I'll spend my life with you.
It's worth it.
What are you talking about?
I don't understand.
You're a scholar and a scholar.
You must have been in the palace for a long time.
Now the marriage is not easy.
It's important for the princess.
It's worth it for the Prime Minister.
It's worth it.
The Su family is the general world.
I'm a small girl.
If I can be a general,
I'll be a good woman.
I'll thank you and my father.
And you're not blind.
You're a rich man.
What's the point?
If I tell you the truth,
you'll change your mind.
Then you'd better not say it.
Stop it.
You're really a good scholar.
An Ning.
Help me.
What's the point?
Turn the wall.
The princess really wants to escape.
I'll explain to you later.
Come on.
Great.
I'm coming.
Come on.
Princess.
What?
You can see it?
How can you let the princess go out alone?
I'm the only woman left in the inn.
So you can only choose me.
Take me back and fight with you.
An Ning.
No.
Why are you everywhere?
Don't be afraid.
Sister.
I'll cure you.
I'll...
Strange.
There's a big king outside the wilderness.
Xiao Feng.
I...
Water.
Are you afraid of water?
I'll take you there.
Come on.
Why are you here?
I'm here to save you.
I'm here to protect you.
I'm not afraid.
But you.
Why are you afraid of water?
I'm not afraid of water.
Okay.
There's no water here.
Miss is afraid of water.
Thank you.
Let's go.
Duan Chang Cao.
I found it.
Look.
It's Duan Chang Cao.
What's wrong?
Miss.
It's Chudu.
Ning, go to my room and get the needle.
The princess is poisoned.
You need to take the needle and seal it.
Take the poison out.
Okay.
The princess is so warm.
Why is she poisoned?
You poisoned her.
You need to save her first.
Otherwise, the poison will not be fully recovered.
General.
Don't blame me.
Coming.
Please leave.
I want the needle.
You want to keep the poison in the room with the princess?
No.
The needle is in the back of the princess.
You need to take off your clothes.
No.
A man and a woman can't be separated?
Yes.
I'm the doctor.
She's my patient.
What's more?
She's blind.
She can't see.
Do you want to see me die?
Okay.
It's important to save people.
Let's go.
Have you come up with 편 maths?
General,
do you have any thoughts?
I was постоян.
How do you feel about the ladies?
An Ning?
If it's a boy,
I'll marry him.
What a pity.
By the way,
I haven't found
a matchmaker
with me.
Xiao Hu Chen?
What about you, Princess?
General Su,
I have a plan.
I often check the story of Luo Ting.
When I see her,
she's really a little girl.
I fell in love with her.
She likes me?
I haven't had a good time with her.
How do you feel?
What's the rush?
There's a man
who's loyal to me.
Princess, you're off.
Go back.
I'm worried about you.
I'll give you some medicine
to cure your fever.
You're still in love with me?
You shouldn't be here.
I heard that
you're a new general.
Now it seems that
you can only choose
the one who wants to live.
You can do it.
I'm not afraid of death.
You'd rather die
than be with me.
I won't die.
You'd better leave the inn.
Why can't I?
Some people have a bad fate.
They're more miserable than death.
Do you understand?
I don't.
My brother was
trying to save you.
Who's your subordinate?
I'm just international.
Eat more and live
for me.
Yes.
Man who's doing well
can survive without Regardless of labor condition.
I'm sure
Let's let the
I'm not afraid of you
You're more than right
the мир
The archeology
Right
By the end of stage
Mom and dad
ая