Phuyai Prik!
- Is Phuyai Prik around?
- Phuyai!
Oh, Phuyai!
- Phuyai Prik!
- Where did Phuyai go?
- Phuyai!
- Phuyai Prik!
Oh, Phuyai!
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
What's going on with you all?
Screaming like someone just died.
Die, die! Definitely die. If we don't hurry now,
someone will definitely die.
And where is Phuyai, P'Nual?
He went to the temple, he'll be back soon.
What's wrong with all of you?
Who, who died, who did what?
Don't ask anything yet, P'Nual.
Hurry and go get Phuyai to go to Phaka's house.
If we delay, Phaka will be in trouble.
Yes, I'll go get the others myself.
- Let's go!
- Go!
Must hurry and find Phuyai.
Phaka!
- Phaka!
Where do you want me to look,
Phim, Duang, Chomm?
I don't see anything at all.
I'm not someone you can mess around with!
You came running, all panicked,
and told me and Chomm...
You said Phaka was about to be killed!
And now what?
We even rushed off to report it to Phuyai,
and now that we're here—there's nothing at all!
I was just walking by earlier
and heard what sounded like a fight going on.
But I didn’t dare go in there alone.
- So I went to get...
- Huh?
- Wait a second!
- Whoa!
- What was that? What sound was that?
- I have to go in and check.
- Be careful, Phuyai!
Be careful, Phuyai.
- Oh!
- Eek!
- Completely startled!
- Hey!
- Hmph! - Yah!
- Eek!
- Phuyai!
- Oh! So scary.
I've got goosebumps all over.
Hey!
Hey! Hey!
What's wrong with you guys?
You're here?
Sorry about that, I was in a bit of a rush,
so this is all I could manage.
Don’t worry about it, Mae Phaka.
I really feel sorry for those three.
Screaming like water buffaloes being slaughtered.
Do they really think we’re going to kill them?
I really feel sorry for Namchok.
From now on, there’s no me, no you guys.
How’s it going to make it?
Namchok.
From now on,
you have to learn to stand on your own.
From now on, you won’t have me around anymore.
I’m sorry I have to go.
Even if I stay,
I probably won't be of any use to anyone anyway.
You have to be able to handle things on your own.
I'm sorry that I have to leave.
I don't want to leave you at all.
When I leave, I'll really miss you, Namchok.
You have to be able to stand on your own.
Don’t be stubborn, alright? Got it?
P’Loy, P’Kaew, I think we should get moving.
I think we should split up quickly
before anyone spots us.
Take this money.
If I go get it myself,
my mom will definitely be suspicious.
Have you thought carefully, Phaka,
about not running away with us?
You two go ahead without me.
Don't drag me along as dead weight.
As for me, I already have a place to go.
Thanks so much for helping us
raise Namchok all this time.
But why don’t you want to stay with Phaad?
I know how P'Phaad feels about me.
If I stay any longer,
I’ll just end up being Phaad’s mistress.
It’s probably better if I just leave like this.
By the way, what about you two?
Going just the two of you like this,
aren’t you thinking of taking any girls along?
You’re one of them! And you’re the other one!
You three,
are you finally going to tell the truth?
Why did the three of you
get beaten almost to death by Loy
and Kaew in Phaka's house like that?
- I’ve already told you everything, bro.
- Huh? Why!
That Phun hired us to trick Loy,
Telling him you were going to sell Phaka
to a brothel.
Then you and Loy would get into a fight.
And then Whan would end up hating you.
So nobody else could steal you from Phun.
Hmph!
And you... What do you have to say?
- And... last night... Phun...
- What about her?!
She wanted to pay us to kill Phaka.
And take her and bury her behind the village.
So that Loy would believe
you trafficked Phaka as well.
Hmph!
Why… You… Say it!
But...
- Why!
- But I didn't see Phaka at all today, brother.
As for us, we only saw Loy and Kaew.
They set an ambush for us at Phaka's house.
But... I think
Loy probably took Phaka and ran away, brother.
Enough!
You three, get the hell out of this house, now!
And don't ever show your face here again!
Go! You can go now.
Argh.... Why!
Why the hell is this happening to me? Damn!
But still,
I must be truly wicked, just like everyone says.
I won't do anything to you.
I just want Phun to realize
she’s no match for you.
I, Phaad, swear to the spirits and tree goddesses,
that I, Phaad, love Mae Phaka sincerely.
If only you’d love me back… even just a little.
If we were back home,
nobody would let us be together.
But here, no one even cares if we’re in love.
I really miss Phaka.
Going alone like that, will she be able to meet
her relatives in Phetchaburi like she intended?
It's said that fate brought us together
To meet each other like this.
I want to keep you close to me.
For us to stand side by side,
our hearts filled with joy.
When you're not here,
know that I'm vulnerable.
But our love might be wrong.
Fate might be too cruel to me.
If we have to face the gaze
of a thousand judging eyes.
Even if others condemn us in their hearts.
I'll remain steadfast, unchanged.
Even if the world crumbles
or fate takes you away.
If love is as strange as people say it is.
If, in the end, we can’t be together.
I'll defy fate,
even if it means our love will fall apart.
I hope one day
my dream of love will come true.
If we have to face the gaze
of a thousand judging eyes.
Even if others condemn us in their hearts
I'll remain steadfast, unchanged.
Even if the world crumbles
or fate takes you away.
If love is as strange as people say it is.
If, in the end, we can’t be together.
I'll defy fate,
even if it means our love will fall apart.
I hope one day
my dream of love will come true.