Listen, P'Kaew and P'Loy,
you're aware that the master
has been regulating the Piphat orchestra.
Any troupe without recognized achievements will
not be permitted by the master to sing or dance.
What about Master Jom's orchestra?
Are you truly going to allow the performance
that Master cherishes
to cease because of your actions?
Why the hell is this our burden?
Since the master does not wish
for traditional Thai performing arts
to impede the nation's advancement.
Then why should we continue this tradition?
How are we to progress as a nation?
If we do not preserve our cultural heritage.
So what would you have us do, Bua?
Then prove it.
Demonstrate that the master's work has value.
Prove to everyone that you both are worthy.
To preserve it.
- Phad!
- Loy!
What are you doing?
Hey! Ming, Mun, Loet!
Man, our village’s got so much stuff.
Don’t you think?
Why, bro?
Check this out.
Even though we're on land,
there are fish flopping around.
Wriggle, wriggle.
Everywhere.
What are you gettin' at, Phad?
Mom told me to sell these fish
so we can pay off your dad’s interest.
That's your own damn business, Loy.
Your mom's owed my dad interest for a long time.
You guys are really shameless.
You and your mama are both so damn bold.
Me and my mom don't have it yet.
Can I have more time?
I'll hurry up and get the money
to pay back your dad.
I'm gonna laugh so loud, all the way to Bangkok.
Someone like me
- Hurry up! Pick it up!
- doesn't give a damn about anyone.
Or your mama ain't gonna eat.
- Hold up!
- Where the hell are you goin'?
Go on, do it again!
Ouch!
I'm really gettin' a kick outta this.
Remember this, you guys. If you’re born broke,
this is all you’ll ever be.
C'mon! What the fuck are you waitin' for?
Y'all, beat his ass again!
Alright! Take this!
- Who's there?
- It's me, Bua.
You okay, P'Loy?
Oh, blood.
- What the hell are you doin', P'Phaad?!
- Huh?
Well, uh, you see...
I was just takin' a stroll,
and I saw these three dudes, they...
- They were beatin' up Loy, so I stepped in.
- Oh! / - Phad!
- I came to stop it.
- Oh yeah? Do you think I'm that stupid?
Can't you see? He's bleedin' all over!
- What the hell are you doin'?!
- Ouch!
This is gettin' outta hand, Bua.
You're my little sister.
Don't you have any respect for a big shot like me?
If people find out, I'll be so embarrassed.
I'm the one who's ashamed.
I'm ashamed to have a brother like you.
The same goes for you assholes.
Ming, Mun, Loet!
You're so good at being his lackeys.
- I'll get you!
- Hold up!
- That's enough, Bua.
- Go home, or I'll send you all home!
- So what?!
- What right do you have?
- Are you talkin' back?! Are you talkin' back?!
- Ouch! Ouch!
- Just let go, hey!
- Are you talkin' back?! Get outta here!
All of you get outta here!
- Let go of me!
- So what?! So what?!
I'll get you for this, Loy.
Guys like you only hide behind women's skirts.
- Oh yeah? Go on!
- Just tryin' to get by.
Go now. If you ain't home when I get there...
- You'll be sorry.
- I'm goin'.
Ugh!
You okay, P'Loy?
You alright?
You okay?
That P'Phaad, you good?
- How's it goin'?
- Duh, it hurts.
It hurts right here.
Sorry.
All done.
Mae Iad, I'm really sorry about this.
Hold on.
You're the one who looked after and helped Loy.
Why the hell are you sayin’ sorry to me, Bua?
You did nothin’ wrong.
No, Mae Iad.
Because the one who hurt P'Loy...
It was my own brother, Phad.
I'm really sorry.
Oh, honey.
It's not your fault, child.
If someone's gotta take the blame, it's me.
Because I'm poor.
Poor people gotta live like this.
Oh, honey.
Oh, Mae Iad.
I'm really sorry.
I'm so sorry, y'all.
I really appreciate you.
For taking care of Loy.
Hey P'Loy! Oh my gosh,
what happened? Does it hurt bad?
- Hello.
- Do I look dead, Whan?
It's just a little cut on my head.
-  Let me have a look.
-  Ouch, that really hurts.
Loy.
Come on, it's just a little scratch,
like something a cat would do.
What kinda cat lives at your place, tiger?
Why don't you try having it happen to you?
Let's see if you'd feel any pain.
Oh, come on...
I've seen you fall off a buffalo countless times
and you never seemed to be hurt.
Just this little thing
and you're acting all dramatic.
Hey man, good thing you're alright.
But my sister, Whan, was yelling her head off,
so startled she was practically dying.
When someone brought me the news
that you got hit on the head by that Phad.
God, it was getting on my nerves.
Oh! And don't you even think
about worrying about your friend?
Well, if you hadn't butted
in wanting to go to the market...
Father probably wouldn't have ordered me
to follow and take care of you.
Oh, Bua dear.
Here's the sweets you like.
I'll give them to you.
Thank you, P'Kaew.
Hmmph. Oh please, in P'Kaew's head,
there's probably only that Bua.
P'Loy is almost dying here,
and your younger sibling is sitting right here.
What is this?
Giving sweets to the one who started it all!
Hey Whan, watch your mouth!
Who's the one who started it? Say it again.
Why didn’t you tie him up in the basement
or slap a muzzle on him?
What is this?
You let him loose to bite people everywhere.
Hold on, Whan, this ain't my fault, alright?
I didn't chain him up.
His feet are his feet, his hands are his hands.
And how would anyone know that he would go
and do such nasty things to someone?
- Oh, well Phad is your brother, isn't he?
- Hey Whan!
Tch! If he's your brother,
then you're definitely wrong.
Then I’m taking the sweets; deal with it!
Wait, P'Kaew bought this for me.
I'm not giving it to you.
Ooh, possessive!
Aren't you happy, P'Kaew?
Hey, if you're so possessive,
then come and take it yourself!
- You brat, Bua!
- Give it back, Whan!
Give it here! It's mine!
- Get over here, Kaew!
- You think I'm scared of you?
What are you gonna do? What are you gonna do?
- What the...!
- Hey, you're playing rough!
- Come on!
- Come on in!
What are you gonna do?
What's your deal?
- Think you're so tough, huh?
- Let go of me! Ouch!
Think you're so tough? Give in! Give in!
- Ouch!
- Hey! Loy!
What's wrong?
Hey! I'm sorry! Does it hurt bad?
- It really hurts my wound!
- Loy!
- I'm sorry.
- Ouch!
I'm sorry. I won't do it again.
- I'm hurt.
- Huh?
Loy, you and your antics!
Kaew, I think we should go home first today.
I'm not feeling too good.
Don't go home yet! Let's play some more!
- I don't think so. The water's really cold today.
- You scaredy-cat!
Ouch, ouch! Loy, help me! I've got a cramp!
- I don't believe you.
- I'm serious! Ouch, help me!
Hey, Kaew! Kaew!
Hey! Don't you die on me, buddy! Hang in there!
Loy, I'm cold! I'm cold!
Warmer now, right?
Loy, you're like this because of me.
I'm sorry.
Hey Phad, you got strong hands and feet.
Why don't you kick her a couple of times?
I love her... I just can't do that to her, Pa.
- P'Phad...
- Phun.
It’s dried grilled sour fish.
I know you like it, P'Phad.
Let him eat it himself,
or are you gonna feed him?
- Really? Then let me!
- Phun!
You're going too far, you Phun!
I got hands, don’t I? I can eat on my own!