No matter which guesses we take, we need to get the spear first.
Now, there is a commotion happening at Observation Mountain,
I'm afraid the demons might also go there.
Dong Hua,
send out my order immediately.
Immortals and Upper Immortals can challenge to take the spear.
Whoever gets the spear and masters it, this spear will belong to him.
But, Your Majesty, if the immortals and demons all go there, I'm worried that there might be trouble.
Don't worry. When the time comes, I'll be there in person.
If there's any trouble, I'll deal with it myself.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Why would the Tai Cang Spear suddenly appear?
Fire Qilin...
Is Bai Jue still alive?
No matter what, you were too impulsive this time.
That was the Demon Emperor, Sen Jian.
Luckily, you're still alive.
I did so to save you.
You had many ways to save me.
If you do such a thing regardless of your life again, I'll abandon you forever.
Understand?
Yes.
Can I talk now?
Father God gave me this life-saving elixir.
Take it.
Feed it to me.
So cruel.
If I choked, you would have regretted it.
Lord of the North Sea, when we were fighting just now, I thought you overstepped your bounds a little.
If you continue doing such ridiculous things, our life is long,
I don't mind letting you be a mute for tens of thousands of years.
Hou Chi.
Since I met you on Observation Mountain,
I felt like I already knew you.
I know you don't believe this.
And you were annoyed that I followed you.
But we went through many difficulties together.
What do you want to say?
I want to say...
this is the first time that I have fallen in love with someone.
I like you.
Lord of the North Sea, I have no feelings for you.
I have many things to do.
I have no time to fall in love.
I know. You're looking for Bo Xuan.
But I will never take back what I've already spoken.
If you are still annoyed about this, I'll stay here.
Who's annoyed about it?
Then why are you looking at me this way?
- Are you trying to deceive me now?
- Yes.
You said so. I'm a dogskin plaster. I should be attached to you.
What if I didn't change my mind?
Then I'll learn from Xiaoli, pretend to be sick and attract your attention.
I'm not as soft-hearted as Sen Yu. Take your medicine on time.
Hou Chi.
Why is he still here?
Didn't you hate people from the Heavenly Palace?
I was careless and fell into their trap.
Upper God Hou Chi, you can treat me like I don't exist
Upper God Hou Chi.
You don't need to do so, Lordess. Please take a seat there.
Thank you for your help this time.
You also arranged for Qing Mu to cultivate here.
I'm very grateful.
Goddess, your words are too much.
I wasn't much help.
Since you're Feng Ran's friend, you can call me Hou Chi.
Then I'll do that.
How is Lord Qing Mu's injury?
He is fine. Don't worry.
It is really rare for Lord Qing Mu to treat you with deep affection.
This kind of marriage should be cherished by Your Royal Highness.
You think too much. We're just friends.
After this incident, my view of this person has changed a lot.
I think he's a gentleman, and he also treats you well.
In this heaven, many men may say they love you,
but how many people can be so protective of each other at the juncture of life and death?
I didn't have any luck with the prince.
I can't meet such a man who would love me that much.
Chang Qin, I heard that the fox has admitted she was pretending to be sick.
Sen Yu asked her to guard the Luocha Region.
Even you learned the news of Xuanjing Palace so quickly.
- I have many friends.
- They often gossip.
Hou Chi.
A'Qin, break up with him if you should or you'll suffer from the torment.
Maybe it's not that person that you can't forget, it's those years you spent with him.
You're so free and unconstrained, you shouldn't waste your life in Xuanjing Palace.
After finishing those things, talk with us in Qingchi Palace.
Let's drink together and get drunk.
We welcome you to Qingchi Palace.
Goodbye.
Besides, I heard another thing. It's about Bo Xuan.
Tell me.
- Who said I was gossiping just now?
- Just say it.
Then tell me first what happened between you and Qing Mu these past few days.
Then you have to tell me what happened between Jing Jian and you recently.
I...
Master, if it were not Wu Huan,
Goddess Yue Mi wouldn't have died in the Swamp of Netherhill.
In recent years, Wu Huan has intended to annex the Demon Clan.
She did so many things behind the scenes.
Mu Guang is the same as her.
Why do we negotiate peace with them?
Since I woke up, because the divine power is thin in the Demon Realm,
I can't be a True God again.
But they have been cultivating in the Heavenly Palace for sixty thousand years.
Their power is no longer what it used to be.
Don't say that.
If you didn't sacrifice the power of the Purple Moon to the Demon Clan, regardless of your own cultivation,
the Demon Clan would have been annexed by the Immortal Clan.
We wouldn't have today's peace.
I heard Bai Jue's Tai Cang Spear appeared on Observation Mountain.
Yes.
Mu Guang asked his son to negotiate peace with us.
He wants to get the Purple Moon Whip.
By gathering four divine weapons, he can open the God Realm again.
But back then, you launched the Array of World Destruction
and have long been regarded as a sinner of the three realms.
Even if the God Realm were to reopen, it would be of no use to you.
I know you're loyal.
But if they get the Tai Cang Spear,
the Immortal Clan will have a higher chance to win.
We can take negotiating peace as a chance to take the spear.
This is the best solution.
Master, you're right. I was short-sighted.
I'll do it now.
Such a huge thing happened on Observation Mountain.
You said Bo Xuan had the power of fire.
Fire Qilin is a beast from ancient times. It also has the power of fire.
Bo Xuan and Fire Qilin. One of them went missing on Observation Mountain, the other appeared on Observation Mountain.
Are they related to each other?
Whether Fire Qilin is Bo Xuan or not, I can investigate on Observation Mountain.
Jing Jian and you can go to the Heavenly Palace to have the Spirit Lock removed.
As for Qing Mu, he can stay in the Demon Realm and cultivate.
No!
If you're looking for Bo Xuan, I'll go as well.
You just fought with Demon Emperor, so you can't travel long distances.
Many things are happening on Observation Mountain. The immortals and demons are all there.
It would be dangerous if you go there alone.
You're seriously injured. Get some rest and take care of yourself.
I just had the elixir you gave me. I feel much better now.
The elixir in Qingchi Palace is different.
Enough, go back and cultivate.
Lordess Feng Ran.
Don't call upon me, I support Hou Chi. I can't help you.
Jing Jian, say something.
He is asking you.
I wasn't supposed to listen. I wasn't supposed to listen.
Why are you looking at me?
I heard Fire Qilin hurt Lord Xian Shan who was Dong Hua's apprentice.
It was fierce.
I'm worried about you if you go there alone.
What about letting Qing Mu accompany you?
It's because the trip is dangerous that I can't bear to take him with me.
You don't know him. He is a person who loves to fight injustice.
In case of conflict with others again, what if he gets hurt and it affects his cultivation later?
I didn't expect you to care about him.
It's not like that.
Jing Jian.
It's a misunderstanding. Misunderstanding.
The Spirit Lock just dragged me,
so I opened the door accidentally.
How about me cutting off your hand?
Then the Spirit Lock won't be annoying.
No thanks, Lordess.
I shall leave now.
It's all your fault. Why did you want to eavesdrop?
I was scolded as well.
Remember, you owe me ten bottles of Ice Wine of the North Sea.
No problem. I'll surely give it to you.
This thing is really good.
Do you have a spare one? Give me one and tie Hou Chi to me.
- I haven't seen you for a few days, why are you so...
- You don't understand.
Hou Chi and I were a couple before.
Where did you hear that?
Story books in the Human Realm?
You don't believe me?
Of course, I don't.
Aren't you the worst at getting close to women?
Do you still remember the sword mound at Observation Mountain?
You can't see it, but I can.
She can also enter that place.
And... this is her bracelet.
It's the same as mine.
The same person made these.
So, you fell in love with her because of this fate?
Sometimes she is clumsy, sometimes she is stubborn,
sometimes she is full of ideas.
She is so cute.
I...
After I got along with Hou Chi,
I have done many strange things.
I never would have thought that you, a piece of wood, would like someone in my whole life.
It's worthwhile.
Your sister said she likes me before.
And she took all chances to meet me.
I didn't understand, and I felt she was annoying.
But now, I can truly feel how she felt before.
My poor sister.
So many immortals like her, but she only likes you.
But about love, I can't force you.
What about Hou Chi? Does she like you?
I won't give up.
I understand. I'll help you.
Lordesses,
can I say something?
Father God went to Observation Mountain.
Lord Feng Ran and I need to unlock the Spirit Lock.
How about the four of us go together? We can take care of each other on the way.
Yes.
What you said makes sense.
I see this Qing Mu character is stubborn.
He won't let you go there alone.
What about just letting him go with you?
Okay. Let's go together.
I've gotten Father God's instruction feather.
He is in Daze Mansion now. Let's go up the mountain.
Feng Ran, go to see the king with Jing Jian first.
Let him unlock the Spirit Lock for you.
I'll wait for you at the back of the mountain.
Hou Chi.
My Father God often says that he once had a good relationship with Upper God Gu Jun.
The Heavenly Palace wants to mend the relationship with Qingchi Palace.
Jing Jian, meet the king with Feng Ran first.
I'll accompany Hou Chi here.
Okay. Let's meet at the back of the mountain later.
Before this divine spear chooses its owner, the king will be at Observation Mountain.
I guess Jing Zhao will come as well.
Till when do you want to stop hiding?
Who said I was hiding?
I'm not afraid of Jing Zhao.
Really? Then let's go.
No.  I won't go with you.
I don't want to be the enemy of all the lordesses in the Immortal Realm.
- Okay. Then on this feast, I'll tell all the three realms.
- Tell them what?
Except the for the goddess in Qingchi Palace,
I don't like anyone else.
How dare you!
I risked my life for you before.
Shouldn't you be looking at blocking the peach blossoms for me in this relationship?
(Peach blossoms = other women)
Stop talking nonsense.  I'll go now.
Okay, don't be mad.
I know. You don't want to meet the immortals of Heavenly Palace.
I have an idea.
What idea?
Jing Zhao won't recognize you.
How's it? Then I can carry you in my sleeve.
Qing Mu, how dare you turn me into a frog?
You...
- How's this?
-  Qing Mu, you've gone too far.
Okay, I won't play any more jokes on you anymore.
Are you satisfied, Upper God Hou Chi?
Good.
Father God.
Father God, Lord Feng Ran and I were locked by the Spirit Lock carelessly.
Please unlock this for us.
Thank you, Emperor.
I haven't been to Qingchi Palace for many years.
Did Gu Jun come back?
Upper God Gu Jun hasn't returned to Qilian Mountain yet.
Since you left Qingchi Palace, where is Hou Chi?
Is she okay?
She is fine.
Thank you for your caring.
Jian'er, you dealt with the thing in the Demon Realm well.
On your way back,
Demon Emperor replied with a letter to Heavenly Palace.
He agreed on negotiating peace.
I've spoken to the three realms.
I'm allowing the Demon Clan to come to Observation Mountain to win the Tai Cang Spear.
I didn't do much.
I am surprised that the Demon Clan has agreed to negotiate peace.
Sen Jian is in charge of the Demon Clan.
How could the hatred before compare to the lives in the three realms?
You're right, Father God.
It's fortunate that the immortals and demons can negotiate peace.
Why won't they let us in?
That's right.
Everyone, calm down.
Although our king said that you can enter Observation Mountain to search for the divine spear,
for your own safety, please have some rest here.
When the divine spear has appeared, we'll let you in.
Feathering Umbrella.
You're Princess Jing Zhao of Heavenly Palace.
It's good that you know me.
You Demon Clan want to win the Tai Cang Spear as well?
I don't think you need to enter the mountain.
Let's have a fight here.
If you lose, it'll be useless to enter the mountain.
Princess, the immortals can't argue...
Enough.
Leave here, or I'll take away your demon elixir.
Wait here.
I'll have a look.
Qing Mu.
Did you also came here for Tai Cang Spear?
I can't just let you. Let's take it according to our ability.
But if I get the divine spear, I'll hold a feast for the three realms.
At that time, you should come to Heavenly Palace and congratulate me.
Princess, why did you hurt these demons?
They spoke insolently.
Demon Emperor will punish them for that.
As the princess in Heavenly Palace, how could you do so?
I...
Thank you for saving us, Lord.
It's no big deal.
Not everyone in the Immortal Realm is so outrageous.
Qing Mu, what do you mean?
Since the Demon Clan has agreed to negotiate peace, Heavenly Palace should be magnanimous.
If the princess in Heavenly Palace is making trouble,
I'm afraid the king will be laughed at by the three realms.
Lord Qing Mu is right.
Really? Why did you just look and not stop her?
People in the Human Realm say that if a lord does a crime, he should be punished as common people.
Even a child knows right from wrong.
But as immortals, you just ignored them. So funny.
Qing Mu, although I was arrogant before, you shouldn't treat me like this.
Because these demons were aggressive today,
I was so angry that I hurt them like this.
Father.
Father, who is this aunt? Why is she so bad-tempered?
- What did you call him?
- Father.
Aunt, why are you so close to my father?
Don't you know my father has my mom and me now?
When did Lord of the North Sea get married? How could we not know?
Don't talk nonsense, kid.
Okay, enough.
This is Princess Jing Zhao of Heavenly Palace.
Qing Mu, is she really your...
I've been living in the mansion of the North Sea. I have never gone out.
Father took me to see the divine soldiers. I didn't imagine it to be so bustling.
You are Princess Jing Zhao of Heavenly Palace.
Nice to meet you, Old Princess Jing Zhao.
Who do you say is old? You naughty kid. How dare you say so!
Am I wrong?
I heard Old Princess Jing Zhao is twenty thousand years old.
But my father is only no more than ten thousand years old.
If it's true, if you got married early,
your son would be the same age as my father.
You are much older than me, Princess.
You...
She is innocent. She knows nothing.
Am I wrong?
You have grown up now.
You should be polite, so others will respect you.
I saw what you did just now.
I didn't do anything.
My father is righteous. He is so handsome.
Relax. I won't be as arrogant as that aunt.
That's good.
Although you're the Lord of the North Sea's daughter, you don't have any divine power.
I guess your mother is just a mortal
who wanted to marry an immortal  by giving birth to his child.
What a good idea.
You're right, Princess.
But you have divine power and are noble.
Why haven't you become a goddess in twenty thousand years?
I heard Upper God Hou Chi in Qingchi Palace
became a goddess before she was born.
You...
Naughty kid, you have offended me so many times.
I'll punish you now.
I'll punish her myself, you don't need to worry.
For your father's sake, if you can kneel down and apologize to me,
I'll forgive you.
Okay. I can kneel down.
You want me to kneel down for nine times,
or do you want me to kneel down for a long time?
Princess, I can kneel down to you.
But I'm afraid you couldn't bear it.
Your mother is just a humble human.
How can I not bear your worship?
Don't regret, Princess.
Who are you? How can you provoke Sky Thunder?
I told you. You couldn't bear my worship.
You...
You're Hou Chi?
You're so imposing, Princess.
This is the first time that I heard someone wanted to bear Upper God's worship in the three realms.
I guess you have forgotten
how it felt when you were punished by Sky Thunder on Observation Mountain.
What's your relationship with Qing Mu? Why are you together?
Princess, this is my personal business.
Qing Mu.
Although Qing Mu is cold to me, he has never acted like this.
You must have done something to him.
If you continue to say nonsense,
I don't mind giving another divine order and entering Heavenly Palace.
You?
I'll let all the immortals see what this Upper God in the three realms really is.
Princess, Hou Chi is an Upper God.
You can't touch her. If you insist on doing this, then don't blame me for being rude.
You want to protect her? Then I won't let her go.
Stop.
Father God.
Are you okay?
From now on, please select talents carefully
and cultivate them for the God Realm.
I'm Mu Guang, from the Golden Dragon Clan on Tianci Mountain.
I, the Goddess of the Stars and the Moon, congratulate you on inheriting the Chief God of Chaos.
I'm the Chief God of Chaos. It's my duty to save the world.
Your Majesty the Heavenly King.
Hou Chi, I didn't imagine that you were grown up now.
Your Majesty, since you're here, you can deal with all the things here.
Qingchi Palace never interferes with the things between the immortals and demons.
I was just helping them a little. I shall leave now.
Let's go.
Demon Emperor and I have agreed to negotiate peace between the immortals and demons.
From now on, anyone who breaks the peace between us,
no matter who he is, I'll punish him.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Who was that man standing next to Hou Chi?
Father God, he is my best friend.
You gave him the title, Lord of the North Sea.
His name is Qing Mu.
It is such good wine. Where did you get it?
Dong Hua asked his apprentice to give it to me.
This lord is such a gentleman.
But we truly need to commemorate today.
"My father is righteous. He is so handsome."
Enough.
I saw Jing Zhao's eyes today. It looked like she wanted to bite me.
Fruits?
When I was traveling in the Human Realm, I learned some little tricks.
Are you trying to make me happy?
You're an Upper God, not a kid.
How can I make you happy with these little tricks?
When I was unhappy as a kid,
Bo Xuan would make me laugh with snacks.
If you want to talk about the past,
I'm here to listen.
If you don't, it's good to just sit here.
Why did you choose to go with me today?
Do you know that the person you left behind was the King of Heaven?
He has the strongest divine power and influence in the three realms.
So what? I just want to go with you.
I can see Jing Zhao values you a lot.
Others want this kind of power and wealth, you really don't care?
We only have three meals and sleep in one bed.
Why should I be so rich?
I accepted the title the king gave me for Jing Jian's sake.
I can't refuse it.
Nonsense.
It's true.
After I received the title, I should have gone to the Heavenly Palace to thank the king.
But I was traveling in the Human Realm, so I didn't go.
You stood the king up?
There are too many etiquettes in Heavenly Palace.
I feel constrained and uncomfortable there.
Why are we talking about me now?
What happened between Jing Zhao and you?
You're not an unreasonable person. The thing had nothing to do with her.
You can live in peace with Jing Jian. Why do you treat her like an enemy?
This is not the first time I have met Jing Zhao on Observation Mountain.
You are Hou Chi? Do you know who I am?
I'm talking to you. Do you hear me?
You're so arrogant, and you dare to yell in front of me.
You must be Jing Zhao in Heavenly Palace.
Hou Chi, you knew I was the princess and you were still insolent?
Qingchi Palace doesn't belong to the three realms.
And my position is the same as your Father God's.
Even if I'm insolent, what can you do?
Call your Father God to hit me?
You're so rude and disrespectful.
You're so weak, no wonder Mother God abandoned you.
You...
That's all you can do? And you treated me so arrogantly?
I can't swim.
Aren't you an Upper God? Just use your divine power.
What? You can't?
Because your divine power is low, Mother God abandoned Qingchi Palace and you.
You are the shame of Qingchi Palace, the shame of Mother God.
And then?
Luckily, Bo Xuan came in time and saved me from the water.
Or I'd be the first Upper God who was drowned in water.
Since then, I have been afraid of water. I can't swim till now.
I'm not talking about this. I mean...
You mean my divine power?
Just as Jing Zhao said, my divine power is low.
It took me forty thousand years to be born.
No matter how hard I cultivate, I can't gather divine power.
Father God goes to find treasures for me, so he rarely comes back.
Feng Ran wasn't here at that time.
Qingchi Palace is quiet and cold. Bo Xuan was the only one to accompany me.
And then Bo Xuan also left.
I never left Qingchi Palace.
It's okay that I lose face.
But I don't want to implicate my Father God.
So, you grew up this way in Qingchi Palace these years.
Sometimes I really envy you. You forgot all your memory.
Your parents are the most powerful gods in the three realms.
You can't be unable to gather divine power.
Is your body sealed by anything?
If there is a seal, how could my Father God not know it?
Okay, stop persuading me.
I won't treat Jing Zhao well no matter what you say.
Since she did such a thing to you, she should bear the consequences.
I didn't know before. I won't interfere in the business between her and you anymore.
I thought you would persuade me.
Jing Zhao was little, just forgive her.
Why should I say that?
You are the most important...
I won't say it.
I don't want to burden you.
Look! Make a wish.
That's just the light when lords are riding the clouds. Why should we make a wish?
If you believe it, your wish will come true.
Haven't you heard of it? Come on.
I hope Hou Chi can become a goddess, and be the most powerful one over the world.
Nonsense.
Come on, make a wish.
I hope Lord Qing Mu's wish can come true.
I made two wishes.
What's your second wish?
I won't tell you.
But I have confidence that it will come to fruition someday.
Don't think too much.
This... The Tai Cang Spear appeared again.
The fire, it must be the Qilin.
Qing Mu, if the Qilin is Bo Xuan, he'll surely protect the Tai Cang Spear.
Those people who want to take over the Tai Cang Spear will fight with him.
My divine power is low, I can't protect him.
No matter what happens, you should protect Bo Xuan.
Relax, I won't let anyone hurt him.
It's really Hong Ri.
Lord Dong Hua, I saw Hou Chi just now.
She really looks like Master Shang Gu.
I was excited and didn't think carefully,
but now I'm calm.
I find this suspicious.
I ask the Old Master to help me distinguish from them both.
Emperor, you don't need to say so.
I know what you are confused about.
When I first met Upper God Hou Chi,
I was familiar with her because they looked alike.
But no matter if it's from their temperament, Power of Chaos,
or Upper God Hou Chi's family background,
maybe she is not Master Shang Gu.
I also think so.
But beside Hou Chi,
there is Lord Qing Mu who has the same look as Master Bai Jue.
I'm afraid this thing is not that simple.
You said, maybe Master Bai Jue came to the Lower Realm.
But if Master Bai Jue is still here, he wouldn't look like Lord Qing Mu.
But if Lord Qing Mu is Master Bai Jue's descendent, he has no parent.
We can't find any evidence.
No matter what the truth is,
I think we have hope to reopening the God Realm.
What about finding a chance to fight with Lord Qing Mu?
Then we can see if he has inherited from True God Bai Jue.
Maybe I can try.
As for Upper God Hou Chi,
Upper God Gu Jun is traveling outside now.
Maybe Heavenly Queen can answer your question.
I'm afraid she knows less about it.
When she left Hou Chi then, Hou Chi wasn't born yet.
I'm afraid we will be able to figure it out when Gu Jun has returned.
- Father God.
The Tai Cang Spear has appeared.
The Demon Clan have all gone to recover it.
Father God, why didn't you go there?
That's a divine weapon from the Immortal Clan.
We can't let the Demon Clan take it.
I've told you many times.
There is no distinction between the immortals and demons in the God Realm.
How could True God Bai Jue's divine weapon be owned by the Immortal Clan?
Father God.
I had a deal with Demon Emperor.
The two of us will not intervene in the matter of the Tai Cang Spear choosing its master.
You can go with Jian'er.
The divine spear has its own spirit.
No matter which clan it chooses as its owner,
as long as two clans can abandon hatred and open the God Realm together,
it's a good thing to the three realms.
Yes, Father.
Jian'er, protect your sister.
Okay, Father God.
People say the one who can get the divine weapon from ancient times can be an Upper God.
Brother, help me. I want to be an Upper God this time.
Zhao'er, the Qilin is protecting the divine spear.
Let's watch first, don't be impulsive.
Lord Xian Shan, did that Qilin appear?
No.
You want to take over the Tai Cang Spear?
I want to see who dares to take it from me.
Hong Ri?
That's not Hong Ri.
But, how? That is his spiritual aura.
It's just Hong Ri's soul fragment.
You commoners, how dare you to come here to True God's cultivating place.  How offensive!
Leave here!
What do you think?
He is not Bo Xuan.
♫ Year after year time goes by ♫
♫ Don't be afraid if our fate comes back ♫
♫ Rains flood and memories last ♫
♫ My longing for you won't change no matter what ♫
♫ I have been waiting for so many years ♫
♫ I never leave despite endless sorrow ♫
♫ Love is like a faraway bright moon ♫
♫ I'll wait through my lifetime ♫
♫ I spend years waiting for returning birds ♫
♫ I never regret it and no one can replace you ♫
♫ I hope we'll uncover the past when we wake up ♫
♫ I'll finally bare my heart to you ♫
♫ Along the way, I watch flowers bloom and wither ♫
♫ Maybe we'll meet and part again in the future ♫
♫ Tears turn into clouds and rain falls in my heart ♫
♫ When the clouds break, our future will be clear ♫
♫ I'll enjoy a free life with you forever ♫