Up and forward. Strive to achieve a state of unity of mind and body.
Stop.
Your Royal Highness, you are a beginner, so don't be anxious.
Use your legs to exert strength, do not focus on your body shape.
It's all about the mind.
Okay.
Stay.
She's slimmer than usual.
Master, Litter Master God has had a big appetite the past few days.
Her waist looks wider.
She's not slim.
Master, we should go to the training ground.
I ate too much today.
I want to stay for a while longer and digest the food.
You said true gods just had soup when they were on a diet.
Master, wait for me.
Bai Jue.
I saw that you usually liked wearing the color of white.
So, I wore a white dress today.
But you're out.
Your Royal Highness.
Why is it you again?
Don't you know other goddesses can't enter Abyss Hall?
Bai Jue did that to you. Why are you here again?
The whole God Realm knows Master Bai Jue treats you differently.
You must be happy about it.
Bai Jue and I are all True Gods who are totally connected.
He should treat me kindly.
Just lie to yourself.
If you weren't a Chief God of the God Realm,
if True God Zhi Yang didn't pick True God Bai Jue to teach you,
given your usual behaviors,
Master Bai Jue wouldn't look up to you.
You're better than us just because of your identity.
You broke my kite. You don't apologize but humiliate me.
It's just a kite. Why are you so angry?
Perhaps I'm right.
As the God of Chaos, you're ignorant and your divine power is low.
What qualifies you to be the Chief God of the Three Realms?
How can you enter Abyss Hall and become his apprentice?
How dare you? If I'm not qualified, then are you?
Of course, I am. You're just superior to me.
You have nothing better than me.
Fine. Since you're so arrogant, let's have a clean fight.
If you win, I'll forgive your insubordination.
- If you fail...
- If I lose, I'll accept my punishment.
Okay.
Your Royal Highness.
Your Royal Highness is noble. I can't hurt you.
Let's battle on these lotus leaves.
Whoever falls down first, fails.
Okay.
Your Royal Highness, it's insulting.
Enough to beat you.
When did Her Royal Highness become so great?
Yeah.
Looks like a fair fight.
Your Royal Highness, you lost.
You cheated.
Lost is lost.
As a Chief God, are you a bad loser?
Emperor Sword.
You said you wouldn't use it when you made the challenge.
Emperor Sword can split the Heaven and the Earth.
If you fight me with it, I'm afraid...
Don't worry. I'll win fair and square.
I won't use the mighty weapon to beat you.
Now you lost and you're mad at me.
This is outrageous.
Her Royal Highness is young.
They didn't say spells couldn't be used before the battle.
Master Bai Jue.
Master.
Master, don't blame me.
I just want to see why I'm not better than Her Royal Highness.
I didn't expect I'd be lucky to win.
But it makes Her Royal Highness angry.
Lucky to win? I think you're joking.
If you didn't cheat, Shang Gu would have won within ten moves.
You're worse than her not just with your moves and diligence,
but also because of your state of mind.
Do you hear it?
Thankfully, he's reasonable.
If you apologize to me, I may be happy and I...
Shut up!
The battle is over.
You shall leave!
Yes.
We're leaving.
You didn't focus on cultivation but messed around in Peach Woods.
She set you up with a spell.
Why are you happy?
Bai Jue.
The best thing you should learn is to govern your emotions.
A few bad words from the God of Snow and the other gods then you pull out the sword.
How will the Gods of the Three Realms trust you?
How will you bring peace to the world?
Xue Ying destroyed our kite.
It's just a kite.
We can make another one.
As a Chief God, you are living in the tranquility of the gods.
Today is like this, what about tomorrow?
For you, the kite is a little thing.
For me, it isn't.
Shang Gu.
Master.
Master, please stay.
Don't be angry with me, Master.
It's all my fault.
I'll do anything to make Her Royal Highness less angry.
If you feel awful about that,
you should go and apologize to Shang Gu.
Rather than acting before me.
Her Royal Highness is still angry.
She won't forgive me easily.
Right. How about I take your millennium divine power as punishment?
- What?
- No?
So, you said something you didn't mean just now?
I can't.
I'm in charge of the seasons of the Lower Realm.
If my divine power is damaged, it may bring up lots of problems.
Besides, I contributed to the war between the gods and devils.
People may judge you if you punish me like that.
You are thinking too much.
However, you deserve the punishment.
You're weak. You didn't work hard but used crooked ways.
I remember I told you no goddesses can enter Abyss Hall.
Including you, of course.
Your Royal Highness, here's the apology gift from the Goddess of Snow.
It's only the millennium divine power. It's worse than my power of chaos.
I don't want it.
You're laughing at me.
You think my power of chaos isn't all that great, right?
I won't go to Abyss Hall tomorrow.
My kite is broken. He didn't comfort me.
It's just a battle, but he made a fuss over it.
He said I changed the way that the three realms viewed me.
I think his brain is upside down.
I'm so angry.
I yelled at Bai Jue just now.
He must be mad at me.
I must not be perfect in his mind.
But it's not my fault, right?
He yelled at me first.
So, I'm still perfect in his mind.
It's so hard to pursue someone.
Yue Mi is right.
I can't get my hopes up, right?
What should I do?
Master, I had the divine gem sent over.
I only said it was from the Goddess of Snow Temple like you asked.
I didn't give myself away.
Put it away. I won't need it anymore.
Master, you won't go to see Her Royal Highness?
No need.
Go and tell her to switch to the Imperial Mind Spell tomorrow.
Yes.
Master, please don't mind my saying this.
When Her Royal Highness returned from Observation Mountain, she worked hard on cultivation.
She's young. There'll be time.
Are you blaming me for being too hard on her?
No, I can't.
There isn't much time for her.
If I don't push her but go easy on her, I'll hurt her.
Go.
Yes.
Ice Cube, Shang Gu hasn't been to your hall for cultivation in a while.
I heard Hong Ri invited her several times, but he couldn't get her.
What? You can't teach her.
Why do you mention this?
Enjoy the good tea. Don't spoil our fun.
Zhi Yang, I just learned a new move. I'm sure you've never seen it.
Shang Gu, you came at the right moment.
Come on.
I heard what happened in Peach Woods.
Bai Jue was partial to you, wasn't he?
Why are you angry with him?
Sit down.
The three of us are intimate, aren't we?
He took the Goddess of Snow's millennium divine power as punishment.
He did that for you.
Really?
- Big mouth.
- Really.
Forget it. No matter what move Xue Ying used, I lost.
Right?
Shang Gu, it's so easy to please you.
You know what they say, don't believe a word a god says.
You can't just...
Shang Gu, I have something to tell you.
We're talking about picking you a sacred beast in Wutong Forest.
When shall we go?
It can't wait.
Shang Gu, let me go with you.
Wutong Forest is a good place.
We can travel all the way and have fun.
You won't go?
I'm occupied.
We can leave a few days late if you're busy.
I'll wait for you.
Well, why must it be him?
Because he's my master.
Bai Jue!
Do you want to ask me why I won't go to the Phoenix Clan with you?
I thought about it.
You were right about the battle between me and Xue Ying.
I was too careless.
And I should admit that I lost.
I'll find a way to win it back.
I don't care about it anymore.
Then why won't you go with me?
Shang Gu, I can't help you solve everything.
This trip is about the Phoenix Clan.
It's a chance for you to control the sacred beast.
And it's the best opportunity for you to grow up.
But I've been cultivating with you.
How could you not go with me to pick a sacred beast?
Master. Your Royal Highness.
Elder Feng Yun wants to see you.
Your Royal Highness.
Master Bai Jue.
Elder Feng Yun, what brings you here?
Didn't you receive my instruction feather?
I came to see you because I received it.
What do you mean?
The Phoenix Clan are guilty of a great sin. Please forgive us.
What happened?
Before Ancestral God passed away,
he picked our empress to be Her Royal Highness's sacred beast.
To carry this duty,
Empress Feng Yan has been working hard on cultivation all these years.
Three days ago, Her Majesty finally reached nirvana.
And your instruction feather arrived.
When she was going to rise from the ashes in Wutong Forest,
someone stole her core spirit.
Feng Yan's core spirit was stolen.
The Phoenix Empress will reach nirvana three times in her life.
Only to rise from the ashes and cut off seven emotions
can she become the greatest beast of all.
Outsiders don't know this secret.
There are a lot of talents in the Phoenix Clan.
And it's the top among all clans.
Who dared break into Wutong Forest and steal the core spirit?
It's Wu Xi. He's the ancestor of the Wutong trees.
He has protected the Phoenix Clan for thousands of years.
He has always been loyal to Phoenix Clan.
If he's loyal, why did he steal Feng Yan's core spirit
when she was going to rise from the ashes?
Your Royal Highness, you don't know.
It's always about love.
A bad destiny.
The monarch of the Phoenix Clan will reach nirvana three times in her life.
Birth, promotion to god, and death.
After she's promoted to god, her body, character, and memories will dissipate with nirvana.
But her cultivation won't disappear in each nirvana.
Therefore, every death makes her become stronger.
I see.
So, each Phoenix monarch is the same one.
Well... yes and no.
Except for cultivation, each Phoenix monarch is different.
This Phoenix monarch and Wu Xi grew up together.
They adored each other since they were young.
I knew they were attracted to each other.
But Ancestral God made a decree that
Her Royal Highness's beast would be picked from Phoenix Clan.
The Phoenix monarch is the greatest in the Phoenix Clan.
So, only the Phoenix empress can be Your Royal Highness's beast.
However, after Empress Feng Yan fought the devils,
her divine power was greatly reduced.
Now she's only as good as an upper god.
So, Her Majesty decided to go on the second nirvana.
But Wu Xi stopped her from nirvana this way.
It's no different than death
if Feng Yan went on the second nirvana.
Ice Cube Bai, am I right?
All things in the three realms have their own survival laws.
It's not about good or evil.
Since Feng Yan went on nirvana,
I guess she made the choice.
But Wu Xi stole the core spirit to stop her.
According to the divine laws, he must be killed.
Bai Jue.
Rules are rules. Wu Xi went against heavenly rules.
If we ignore Ancestral God's will for him, then what are the rules for?
Elder Feng Yun, don't worry.
The loss of the core spirit is serious.
I'll get it back in person.
Didn't you ask me to go through it by myself?
Why do you take it on?
Wu Xi may still be in the Immortal Realm.
But he holds his breath, so it's hard to find him.
I think there's a way.
How do I look?
Give me the Immortal Tracking Bell.
Why? It's a treasure I asked from Yue Mi.
It can track an immortal's breath.
So what? You don't know Wu Xi and Feng Yan.
Way ahead of you. I asked Elder Feng Yun for their portraits before we came down here.
You've learned something.
- It smells good.
- Yeah?
- Yeah. Taste it later.
- I'm hungry.
Why not we eat before we go?
True gods can fast.
I can't. I'm a growing girl.
Maybe I can get taller.
You are what you eat. Wonton.
I have to eat what I need.
We have something serious to do.
I mean, I'll come back to eat it after we're done.
There you go.
They're nearby. Go.
Your Majesty, please forgive my disrespect.
I've been with you for many years. I love you so much.
The thought that you'd forget our past after you reached nirvana
put me through hell.
I had to bring you out before your core spirit was disconnected.
I...
Wu Xi, I made it clear to you
before I rose from the ashes.
I owe you too much in this life.
I don't deserve you in the afterlife.
Why did you make such a big mistake?
No.
It's not you but Little Master God, Shang Gu owes me.
If she didn't choose a beast, our love wouldn't end.
But the Wu Xi that I loved is not like you.
How could you get the Phoenix Clan into trouble by saving me?
You aren't done with me in this life.
I don't want the next life.
I... I regret it.
What?
Do you regret that I took you out without asking you
or regret being with me?
I regret nirvana.
I saw your tears
when you stole my core spirit out of the Phoenix Clan.
I thought I'd let go of this life,
but I can't let you go.
I decided, whether it's wandering around the world
or being chased and killed in this life,
I want to be with you.
I won't let you down.
I'll do everything for you without regret.
Now that I have brought you out of the Phoenix Clan,
we must have aroused the God Realm and the Phoenix Clan into investigating us.
There are too many eyes here.
We can only stay here for a while.
This is not permanent.
You put my core spirit on a phoenix flower.
I could be a flower fairy.
Maybe it can hide my identity.
But it's not fair to you.
Just wait for me here. I'll go to find a paradise.
And we'll enjoy a free life. No one can find us.
- Immortal Tracking Bell.
- What?
Elder Feng Yun must have told the God Realm about us.
The  Immortal Tracking Bell is absorbing our breaths. They're coming.
I don't want to leave you.
Don't worry. They must think your core spirit is on me.
I'm going out to distract them.
Wu Xi, don't go.
I'm afraid you'll be in danger.
Here's the phoenix leaf connected with me.
Now your spiritual power is low. You can't have a confrontation with anyone yet.
You must hide yourself.
After this crisis, it'll lead you to find me.
You must wait for me here.
Wu Xi must be happy.
He's drinking and having fun here.
This place is very lively.
I'll bring Yue Mi here next time.
Are you here for having fun or doing business?
I told you I have my own way.
I am very experienced in arresting and being arrested.
I've come down to the Lower Realm without permission before many times.
I don't know how many times I was caught by Zhi Yang.
You can't rush something like this.
What's in this suet? It smells good.
Your Highness, this is not suet.
This is the signature Peach Wine of Dong Feng Restaurant.
It smells good and tastes sweet.
It's smooth. It comes with an aftertaste.
There's such a good thing in the Immortal Realm?
Is this real or fake?
You will know if you order a bowl.
Taste it.
Wu Xi.
Wait for me here.
Wu Xi knew I was under the protection of Bai Jue.
But he dared attack me.
It's a diversion.
Maybe Feng Yan's core spirit is still in this restaurant.
Who is it?
Your Highness, I passed by here.
I got a little lost.
May you show me the way?
I'm new here.
Why not ask the waiter?
Your Highness, you're pretty and kind.
I've been trying to find my way and have gotten thirsty.
Can you take me in for a while?
I have something important to do. I can't take you in.
I think the fairy is more beautiful than a delicate flower.
I took a fancy to you, so I couldn't help but say something.
Your Highness, are you from Flower Clan?
Yes.
You should be careful if you want to go far.
It's been pretty rough in the outskirts lately.
What happened?
Recently, there's a deflowering beast occupying the Nanhai outskirts.
He preys on beautiful fairies like you.
Really?
You're of the Flower Clan. How could you not know it?
I... I heard about it.
Not just that. Something confidential and big happened has happened in the Phoenix Clan lately.
I was born loving to travel and gossip.
From a Chief God picking a beast to an elder turtle taking concubines,
I know everything about the three realms.
Forget it. This is about the Chief God's face.
We're juniors. Don't bother worrying about it.
Since you're going far, I'm leaving.
See you.
Your Highness.
You just said
Master Bai Jue was investigating the core spirit theft in Nanhai City.
Did he find something?
You're a flower fairy.
Why do you care so much about the Phoenix Clan?
I love gossip like you.
The Phoenix empress' core spirit isn't on you.
What? Do you really want to turn against the God Realm?
If you True Gods hadn't forced me, I wouldn't have done so.
Ridiculous!
If word leaks out about the core spirit theft,
it will cause immortals and monsters to covet it,
leaders of all races will want to absorb it to enhance their spiritual power.
I'm afraid there'd be a mess in Nanhai City.
You and Shang Gu must solve it soon and come back to the God Realm.
Now, the God Realm is almost sure
that Wu Xi put the Phoenix monarch's core spirit on a flower.
It was confidential. How did the God Realm know?
The fish has taken the bite.
Why is Ice Cube Bai taking so long?
Peach Wine is delicious and intoxicating.
I drank a little too much.
You see, the Phoenix monarch's core spirit is divine.
How could a flower take it?
When she resides on a flower,
her spiritual power will be too low to protect herself.
I think all realms will fight for it.
Little Master God thought it was Wu Xi's own decision.
She didn't expect the Phoenix monarch would be involved in it.
How should they end it?
If the Chief God knew her trip to the Phoenix Clan to pick a beast
would make Wu Xi and Feng Yan suffer this,
she wouldn't go there.
Now it's turned into such a big thing.
Why do you think Feng Yan chose to walk this path
and have so many people involved in it?
Seven emotions and memories aren't allowed in nirvana.
Miss, without seven emotions and memories,
is Feng Yan still Feng Yan?
The Phoenix monarch carries the Phoenix Clan's blood.
She was born to undertake God's will.
So, she was born to experience nirvana and leave her beloved.
Don't you think she's pitiful?
Even if she's the Phoenix monarch,
she's no better than girls in the Immortal Realm.
They're allowed to love people.
There are so many miserable people in the world.
No one can disobey Ancestral God's will.
I wonder if the superior gods know
that there are also many people in the Phoenix Clan who are of humble origins
but are able to take on the mission of a sacred animal.
Feng Yan has neither the ability to assist the Chief God
nor the vision to help the three realms.
She just wants to be an ordinary girl
and spend the rest of her life with her beloved.
Any questions?
Shang Gu. Chief God.
- If...
- No ifs.
When Your Royal Highness loves someone,
you'll know the meaning of "love makes people suffer."
I'm sober now.
Please show me the way, Your Royal Highness.
Forget it.
I didn't want to break you two up.
Now I see you are so determined.
What do you mean, Your Royal Highness?
Go before I change my mind.
Your Royal Highness.
Go.
I'm afraid you can't leave when True God Bai Jue comes back.
Thank you, Your Royal Highness.
- Wu Xi.
- Feng Yan.
What took you so long?
I was anxious. Did you have any problems?
That's good. I wanted to meet you in the restaurant.
But I feared I'd blow your cover if someone followed me.
Her Royal Highness recognized me.
Don't worry. She's a reasonable person.
She let me go.
Wu Xi, we got her wrong before.
It's completely Shang Gu's fault.
You can forgive her, but I can't.
Outrageous!
My head hurts.
You still try to kill me
When will your good tastes be changed?
Ice Cube Bai, I'm dizzy.
Look!  Didn't you say that you would treat me a little more tenderly?
Don't always be aggressive with me. Right?
I envy the relationship between Wu Xi and Feng Yan.
They gave it all up for their love.
They even defied God's will and risked their lives.
Wu Xi made a big mistake for his own selfish desire.
He acted without considering the consequences.
Stop your drunk talk.
I'm not drunk.
Do you think I look drunk?
Did you hear me?
I envy Wu Xi and Feng Yan.
I don't want to catch them.
Who was drinking with you?
Feng Yan. Who else could it be?
Where are you going?
Zhi Yang sent me a message. The three realms know about the loss of the Phoenix monarch's core spirit.
As the Chief God, you're still drinking and making mistakes.
It doesn't matter.
Why are you still gving me a whole lecture again?
Look. Bai Jue,
if I violate the rules of Heaven for love someday,
will you punish me according to the rules?
Rules and disciplines are superior to a relationship.
Relationships have nothing to do with rules.
♫ Time is like you, disturbing my feelings and thoughts ♫
Look at you.
Except for being good-looking, what's the big deal with you?
You're drunk. Let me sober you up.
♫ I can never forget ♫
Shang Gu.
♫ ...the memories of you ♫
♫ I cherish the time to be with you ♫
We are at Pilgrim Hall. No one will come and save you.
What do you want to do?
Do what I've always wanted to do.
♫ When I meet you ♫
♫ I hope we can be together forever ♫
♫ When we meet again ♫
♫ I'll travel with you without hesitation ♫
♫ Feel each other ♫
Who else have you gotten drunk with?
God of Flowers, God of Night, and God of Rain.
Tian Qi, Yue Mi, and Zhi Yang.
All right.
Don't drink with them again. Do you hear?
♫ Such good times and beautiful scenery ♫
♫ May you stay by my side ♫
Why?
You're a female and I'm a male.
You can't touch wherever the clothes cover.
There's no clothes on your face.
It's more exhausting than beating a fierce beast.
Just stay here and rest.
Wu Xi and Feng Yan are in danger now.
I'll be right back.
I've set the barrier. Strangers can't walk in.
Its owner is an immortal crane.
He flew up to the God Realm not long ago.
I don't think he'll be coming back.
It's a paradise.
Let's stay here for the moment.
After the crisis, we can come up with a better plan.
The environment here is indeed a bit embarrassing.
I didn't think about it properly.
Yan'er, I'm sorry.
No matter how dangerous it is, I'm not afraid.
This is nothing.
Wu Xi, now we've made a big mistake.
There's no turning back.
From now on, we have to hide.
But my spiritual power is low,
I'm afraid I'll slow you down.
Yan, you know I'm not good at talking.
And I can't say sweet words to you.
But I swear to God,
I'll make you happy even if I have to risk my life.
Let's...
Let's get married, okay?
Since we're going to marry, we should clean it up.
Don't just stand there stupidly, come and clean it up.
Right.
I'll do all the housework.
Oh no. Someone broke into the barrier.
Is it True God Bai Jue?
Go.
Wu Xi, go if you don't want to die.
We want the Phoenix monarch's core spirit.
No way!
Why did I fall asleep?
I kissed him?
No.
Absolutely not.
♫ Year after year time goes by ♫
♫ Don't be afraid if our fate comes back ♫
♫ Rains flood and memories last ♫
♫ My longing for you won't change no matter what ♫
♫ I have been waiting for so many years ♫
♫ I never leave despite endless sorrow ♫
♫ Love is like a faraway bright moon ♫
♫ I'll wait through my lifetime ♫
♫ I spend years waiting for returning birds ♫
♫ I never regret it and no one can replace you ♫
♫ I hope we'll uncover the past when we wake up ♫
♫ I'll finally bare my heart to you ♫
♫ Along the way, I watch flowers bloom and wither ♫
♫ Maybe we'll meet and part again in the future ♫
♫ Tears turn into clouds and rain falls in my heart ♫
♫ When the clouds break, our future will be clear ♫
♫ I'll enjoy a free life with you forever ♫