The Qiong Qi appeared in the Lower Realm?
Yes. I saw it with my own eyes.
Now Nanhai City is in a mess now.
If True God Shang Gu and Bai Jue were not there,
I'm afraid something wrong might have happened.
- Bai Jue went to the Immortal Realm with Shang Gu?
- Tian Qi.
True God Shang Gu asked me to go back to the God Realm and tell you.
Please investigate the thing about the Qiong Qi.
You shall leave now.
Okay.
Don't pull a long face.
Although the Qiong Qi are fierce beasts from ancient times,
Shang Gu and Bai Jue are there.
There should be nothing wrong.
I'm afraid this thing is not that simple.
Don't forget, when the Qiong Qi attacked the God Realm last time,
we thought it was because of the devils.
But now the Qiong Qi appeared in the Lower Realm.
There must be something wrong in the Demon Realm.
Okay.
I'll go and check it.
I own the Demon Realm.
If anyone dares to create problems for me,
I'll let him feel regret.
I'll give you some divine power.
No need. It's just some old wounds.
I'll be fine after some rest.
Save your divine power to be in charge of the Chief God's instruction feather.
Something wrong is in Immortal Realm. We need to go back to the God Realm.
You still think I'm useless as I was a thousand years ago?
The war we had today was so fierce.
I really enjoyed it.
We're more tacit than we were on Observation Mountain.
Now your divine power is high.
You look like the Chief God of the three realms now.
The clan of Qiong Qi live in the desert of the Demon Realm sealed by Ancestral God.
I felt strange when the devils led them to the God Realm.
But they broke the barrier and came here today.
I guess Zhi Yang and Tian Qi have gone to the Demon Realm to investigate.
Don't worry. Let's go back to the God Realm first.
Shang Gu, you'll be in charge of Chief God's instruction feather tomorrow.
At that time, the gods in the God Realm and powerful people in the Lower Realm will come.
The inheriting ceremony will be complicated.
Relax. I've recited the sets of etiquette a few days ago.
There will be nothing wrong.
Okay.
Well, Chief God's instruction feather involves the Power of Laws and the Power of Chaos.
Be careful when taking it.
The Power of Chaos in my body has combined with the Power of Laws.
Chief God's instruction feather won't hurt me.
That's good.
True God Bai Jue. Don't worry.
I'll be the Chief God smoothly and inherit the God Realm.
I know, I was just reminding you.
If the goddesses who like you were here,
if they saw True God Bai Jue become a wordy old lady,
would they like someone else?
I don't care what they think.
I'll get some rest, goodbye.
Wait.
When you are in charge of the instruction feather, can you go to Peach Woods with me?
There is something on my mind.
I've been hiding it for a long time.
I want to tell you there.
It's a deal.
I'll definitely go.
Master, you really...
Enough. I've made up my mind.
This is the only solution.
But we can tell Master Zhi Yang and Bai Jue.
Zhi Yang and Bai Jue,
their destiny is to protect the world, Shang Gu, and millions of creatures.
Who do you think they will support?
What? You just made use of me.
Now you are turning against me?
Don't panic. You are becoming a devil now.
So,
we are the same to some extent.
Nonsense.
I'm the Goddess of Snow.
How could I be the same as you?
Whether you're a devil or not, you have plenty of time to think.
But don't forget the thing you promised me.
At the inheritance ceremony tomorrow, you'll be the spy for the devils.
We've helped you go back to the God Realm.
I think such a little request is not too much.
Wu Huan.
Elder.
It's been a long time.
How are you, Elder?
I'm fine.
Please come in.
Okay.
Wu Huan.
Wu Huan has some power now.
She is different from what she was a thousand years ago.
She is arrogant with little power now.
When the Phoenix monarch is reborn, she can't stay in Pilgrim Hall anymore.
You're right.
Wu Huan, change clothes for me.
Wu Huan.
Why are you here?
It's not early now.
I couldn't find you, so I came here.
Wu Huan said you didn't want to get up and let me wake you up.
Your Royal Highness.
It's not early now. You should wake up
and welcome the gods from the Lower Realm at the Realm Gate.
I'm the Chief God.
Why should I welcome them? You can go.
Go there for me.
Even if you don't welcome them at the Realm Gate,
you should wake up now.
All gods in Pilgrim Hall will go to prepare the ceremony at Universe Pavilion.
At that time, no one will help you change clothes.
I've learned about it in the Netherworld.
Just go to work.
I want to nap for a while.
Then, remember to wake up later.
You can nap for fifteen minutes at most.
Don't be late.
You overslept?
Impossible. I'm going to be the Chief God.
How could I oversleep on the inheritance day?
I just napped for a while.
Okay.
You're so busy. You should nap for a while.
Why were you looking for me?
It's Zhitian brocade.
I found some and made clothes for you.
You can wear it after you became the Chief God.
Only this can match the Chief God of Chaos.
It takes ten thousand years for the goddess on Buzhou Mountain to weave a bolt of cloth.
Where did you find it?
I heard there are no clothes made of Zhitian brocade in the God Realm.
In early times, I knew you would be Chief God someday, so I prepared it for you.
In early times?
Many years ago, I saw the notebook of a young girl.
Her sacred meridian was blocked,
but she wanted to cultivate.
She didn't have the divine power to protect the world,
but she remembered all the sufferings in the world.
Before she owned the Power of Chaos,
she wanted to protect the world.
Going through many difficulties, she hid everything in her heart.
But I saw her diligence and effort.
What she sacrificed to get these,
I knew better than anyone else.
From that day, I believed,
that she could be the Chief God of Chaos who would protect the world.
I've been waiting for this day for a thousand years.
Change clothes. I'll go to Universe Pavilion with you.
God Zi Han.
Why do you come to the Secret Pavilion today?
Does Master Tian Qi need any treasure to make a weapon?
You are smart. You're right.
Master got an obsidian recently.
He wants to make a sword, so he asked me to fetch some Tiansheng Grass.
God Zi Han, you didn't give us True God Zhi Yang's permission card.
You're right.
I came here in a hurry just now, so I left it in Everlasting Hall.
Well, I can give it to you later.
No, you can't go in. If you want to go in,
you need to give us the permission card from True God Zhi Yang.
There are too many treasures and evil things here.
We can't afford the responsibility.
Okay. I'll go back and take it here.
Okay, God Zi Han.
Who is it?
God Zi Han.
I, Goddess of Seasons, on behalf of the Gods of Wind, Rain, Thunder, and Lightning,
congratulate you on being the Chief God of Chaos.
I, Goddess of the Stars and Moon, congratulate you on inheriting the Chief God of Chaos.
Congratulation on inheriting the Chief God of Chaos.
May the Chief God live with the heavens and the three realms.
Please stand up.
Thank you, Chief God.
Thank you for teaching me for ten thousand years, brothers.
I shall never forget it.
The time has come, take out the Chaos Stone.
Please open the Chaos Stone,
and take Chief God's instruction feather.
- Tian Qi.
Tian Qi, what are you doing?
Tian Qi.
I've been planning this for thousands years, and you ruined it.
Tian Qi, you can't play jokes here.
Give the instruction feather back to me.
Don't come closer.
What if I don't?
Tian Qi, don't play jokes today.
Why is Chief God's instruction feather hers?
Why am I not qualified to be in charge of the God Realm?
Tian Qi, the instruction feather is the seal of the God Realm.
Only the Chief God of Chaos can take it.
It's a crime if you grab the feather.
So what?
You also said that the instruction feather is the seal of the God Realm.
Now the instruction feather is mine.
After some time, I'll be the most powerful God in the God Realm.
And I'll be Chief God in the God Realm.
Tian Qi.
You can stay here. I'll chase him back.
True God, God Zi Han broke into Secret Pavilion and killed the guard.
He is heading to the Realm Gate now.
Listen to my order, knock the Chaos Bell.
- We can't let the instruction feather leave the God Realm.
- Yes, Master.
Bai Jue, lead the soldiers and catch Zi Han.
You went too far today. Have you played enough?
Go away. I don't want to fight with you.
Neither do I.
But every god saw it, I have to explain to them.
Explain?
Do you know what I'll become if they catch me?
You know how they treated Xuan Yi seventy thousand years ago.
But you're not Xuan Yi.
In their eyes, a god that is not loyal to the God Realm
is the second Xuan Yi.
Shang Gu, if you still regard me as your friend, let me go.
I promise you I just want to borrow the Chief God's instruction feather.
When the matter has ended, I'll return it to you.
Tian Qi, what trouble did you meet?
Can't you tell us?
My problem is too huge.
If the people in the Lower Realm meet problems, they can ask for help from the gods.
But what if a True God meets a problem?
Let me think.
I don't have time, Shang Gu.
Do you really want to see me be punished and be doomed eternally?
Zi Han, what happened in Secret Pavilion?
Did you really kill the guard?
What? The guard died?
I didn't!
That's good. If you didn't kill the guard, come back with me
and tell us the matter that happened in Secret Pavilion.
No. I can't go back.
Zi Han, Tian Qi has betrayed the God Realm.
If you make any more trouble, it's harming him.
True God Bai Jue, my master gave me an important mission.
I can't go back.
I'm sorry.
Why do you have the Purple Jade Whip?
Zi Han, how can you incite the Demon Clan to revolt? Are you crazy?
What is Tian Qi's plan?
If you really want to help him, go back with me.
True God Bai Jue, I have no choice.
You'll understand later.
You silly. I let you monitor the God Realm
and let Shang Gu be Chief God smoothly.
But you let Tian Qi ruin my plan.
Calm down, Demon King. I didn't notice it.
What should we do now?
If Shang Gu dies, it will be troublesome to handle the three of them.
But if Tian Qi betrayed the God Realm,
we can take this chance to let them fight with each other. This is a good solution.
Okay, Demon King.
Tian Qi.
You broke the rules in the God Realm.
You will be killed by the gods.
Master Tian Qi grabbed the instruction feather and ran away. He is very arrogant.
Please give the order to punish Tian Qi, Master.
Master Zhi Yang, how could Tian Qi betray the God Realm?
You know him well. He didn't want to settle the affairs you gave him.
How could he want to be the Chief God?
Shang Gu and Bai Jue have gone to catch him.
I believe they can't escape the God Realm.
The tribunal of the three halls has not yet come out with a result,
and the truth about the matter of the Secret Pavilion has not yet been found out.
We can't declare Tian Qi guilty.
Master Zhi Yang, are you trying to cover up Master Tian Qi?
Goddess of Snow, don't say nonsense.
Master Zhi Yang, I'm just worried about the God Realm.
If Tian Qi didn't ask Zi Han to betray the God Realm,
how could he kill a guard?
That's right, Master Zhi Yang.
We still have the witness of Zi Han's murdering case.
If you don't make a decision now,
I'm afraid the disaster that happened seventy thousand years ago will happen again.
Master Tian Qi fought for the God Realm many times. He made many contributions.
If he didn't meet a huge problem, he wouldn't do so.
Even if you don't trust him,
I trust him. Even if you don't support him, I support him.
Enough!
Don't talk nonsense in Chaos Hall.
God of Wind, you mean, I should kill Tian Qi?
I didn't mean that.
I know what you're worried about.
I don't believe Tian Qi will be like Xuan Yi.
Before he received punishment from Heaven,
he is still the owner of Everlasting Hall, a True God in the God Realm.
I'll investigate the truth with two True Gods,
and give you a satisfactory explanation.
Yes, Master.
Tell a True God that Tian Qi has escaped the God Realm.
Bai Jue, why are you so seriously injured?
In order to resist Purple Jade Whip at Realm Gate,
I used my core power, so my core spirit's old wound aches again.
It seems I can't use my core power within a short time.
Tian Qi escaped the God Realm.
You let him go?
Yes.
Have you thought that other gods won't respect you anymore by doing so?
Even if he returns Chief God's instruction feather,
you might not be able to take charge of the God Realm.
But I can't let you and Zhi Yang scrape his divine bone
and lock him in the Netherworld.
Zhi Yang and I won't do so.
Even if he won't die, he will be punished.
Bai Jue, ten thousand years ago, I was born in Universe Pavilion.
The first one I saw was Tian Qi.
Yue Mi and he accompanied me and saw me grow up.
He is my dearest brother and the one I trust most in the three realms.
Shang Gu, we don't know what Tian Qi wants to do now.
We can save him if he stays in the God Realm.
I only know, if he wants to be the Chief God, in ten thousand years,
he had many chances to kill me and betray the God Realm.
He wouldn't have chosen today.
Yes, I know.
Tian Qi is disobedient.
Even if we let him be Chief God, he wouldn't agree.
Today...
Master.
there must be something wrong.
Your Royal Highness, what happened to Master?
His core spirit is seriously injured.
It needs to be cured by medicine made of the pith of Ancestral Wutong in Phoenix Clan and the chaos core power.
I'll go to Phoenix Clan later.
Stay in the Abyss Hall. No one shall come in before I come back.
Okay, Your Royal Highness.
Hong Ri, tell me what happened to your master in these thousand years.
As long as she is safe, it's just ten thousand years' lifetime core,
even if it's a hundred thousand years' core, I don't care.
You got so seriously injured in the Netherworld in order to protect me.
You have been accompanying me.
You got injured because of me.
But during these years, I've been hesitating and thinking too much.
You love me,
but why didn't you tell me earlier?
When you wake up,
let's not miss each other. Okay?
♫ Time loaned me the eternal galaxy ♫
♫ But where's the old friend ♫
♫ Leaving a shadow and haunting dreams ♫
♫ How many years have been reincarnated
after thousands of tribulations? ♫
♫ Looks like you're before me
and there are mountains and oceans between us ♫
Shameless devil!
I brought you to the inheritance ceremony.
What else do you want to do?
A beauty like the Goddess of Snow,
how could you be so unromantic?
You are also a devil like me.
You're so noisy.
Do you want all the gods in the God Realm to know you're a devil now?
Nonsense! It's because of you.
You did something to me in the Netherworld,
so I became a devil now.
What a pity.
Even if you returned to the God Realm,
True God Bai Jue doesn't like you.
Even if your life is luxurious, so what?
As long as you cooperate with me,
Demon King will help you get what you want.
Wu Huan.
I didn't know you were here, Goddess of Snow.
What do you want, Goddess of Snow?
You're loyal to her.
No wonder you came from the Lower Realm.
So silly.
I heard she asked you to cultivate in Kun Lun when she came back.
Does she know how tiring it is to manage True God's Hall?
You need to balance the elegance of Chief God and a relationship with the other gods.
This is harder than cultivation.
Did you come to Pilgrim Hall to care about me?
Wu Huan, I want to say I understand you.
She is superior.
She has many important matters to deal with.
She just said thank you, and let you work in Pilgrim Hall.
Does she know how tiring it is to manage Pilgrim Hall?
Does she care about you and know what you did for her?
I have no time now, goodbye.
According to the schedule, I want to say I understand you.
At that time, will Shang Gu still let you serve her?
Without the protection from Pilgrim Hall,
you'll live harder than a thousand years ago.
Her Royal Highness won't treat me like this.
Don't try to make mischief between us.
We're both pitiful gods, so I'm just reminding you.
Do you know Shang Gu went to the Phoenix Clan?
Whether it's true or not, you can go back and ask.
You don't need to worry about my business, Goddess of Snow.
Shang Gu.
Yue Mi.
Shang Gu, did you really let Tian Qi go?
I did it myself. But I have something important to deal with.
I'll explain to everyone when I come back.
Where are you going at this crucial moment?
What?
Why would he fall into a coma because of an injury to his core spirit?
I met many difficulties in the Netherworld. He saved me with his core spirit.
I didn't expect this Bai Jue to be more affectionate than you were back then.
But the situation in the God Realm is tense now.
We can't let others know Bai Jue is injured,
or every god in the God Realm will feel insecure.
He has been hiding his injury because of this.
Four True Gods are being doubted now, so there can't be any problem.
Luckily, the pith of Ancestral Wutong in the Phoenix Clan can cure his injury.
I'll fetch it now.
Before this, I hope you can stay in Pilgrim Hall and help Wu Huan manage here.
I'm afraid she might be bullied.
No problem. I'll stay here for you.
I won't let the other gods embarrass Wu Huan.
Now we don't know what has happened in the Demon Realm.
Be careful when you go to the Phoenix Clan.
There is one more thing I need to remind you.
Feng Yan is going to be reborn.
You can take her back when you go to the Phoenix Clan.
The Phoenix monarch's core spirit is fake.
Even after a thousand years, she won't be reborn.
What? Anything wrong?
I know you care about Wu Huan.
But the God Realm is in a mess now.
With her identity, she can't make Xue Ying and other gods satisfied.
It's no good for her to let her manage Pilgrim Hall.
And I think her personality is too surly and flamboyant.
She needs more cultivation.
And the Phoenix Clan is the head of all beast clans.
With the Phoenix monarch assisting you,
the authority of the Pilgrim Hall will be stable.
I understand, Yue Mi.
Let's talk about it after I come back.
Okay.
Phoenix Clan.
Phoenix Monarch.
Yue Mi.
I've told you, we shouldn't let Her Royal Highness catch Tian Qi.
We don't know the relationship between them.
No wonder. She let the traitor escape the God Realm so easily.
I heard there is a barrier around the Demon Realm.
And the Demon Clan has betrayed us.
Where do you think this is? How dare you say so here!
Yue Mi, although you're the Chief Goddess of the Stars and Moon, this is Chaos Hall.
It's not your turn to order us.
Where is Her Royal Highness?
Tian Qi escaped under Her Royal Highness.
Why doesn't Her Royal Highness explain it to us?
Master.
Like you said, I asked Shang Gu to catch Tian Qi.
So you mean I also let Tian Qi escape?
I didn't mean that.
Shang Gu went to the Lower Realm to find Tian Qi.
She is not in Pilgrim Hall.
If you dare to talk nonsense here, I'll definitely punish you.
I think this is not suitable, Master.
The case about Tian Qi is serious.
If we don't catch him now, he'll make trouble to us.
Enough!
When is it your turn to be in charge of the God Realm?
I didn't mean that.
I said so for the God Realm.
The Chief God is young. Her relationship with Tian Qi is good.
We understand that she doesn't want to punish Everlasting Hall.
Master Bai Jue and you
all experienced the rebellion of the Demon King seventy thousand years ago.
Do you want this huge catastrophe to happen in the God Realm again?
At that time, what would the God Realm and the world be?
Goddess of Snow is right.
Please consider the interest of the world, Master.
Goddess of Snow, how do you think I should punish Tian Qi?
According to the rules, remove him from being a god,
receive punishment from Heaven, scrape his divine bone,
imprison him in the Netherworld, and never let him come out.
Don't worry.
The disaster that happened seventy thousand years ago won't happen again.
If what Tian Qi did harmed the God Realm,
I'll atone this with my life.
Master Zhi Yang is just.
Since Master said so,
we'll wait until Her Royal Highness comes back and then decide this.
I finally came from the Phoenix Clan to the God Realm.
No one can let me go back.
No one.
Wu Huan, the outside is in a mess now.
Why didn't you explain for Master?
Her Royal Highness let Master Tian Qi go.
I'm afraid the other gods would embarrass me and I didn't know how to react.
Then they might suspect us.
Even if they embarrass us, Master will defend us.
What are you afraid of?
I...
Her Royal Highness is a Chief God.
Even if she made a mistake, no one dares to judge her.
But we are different.
We are just servants in the God Realm.
If the gods try to blame us, there is nothing we can do.
Master treats us well and trusts us.
If there is anything wrong, she will surely protect us.
You should trust her.
Of course, I trust Her Royal Highness.
But just now, I was in a panic and didn't know what to do.
I shouldn't have blamed you, but we have our backs against the wall now.
We need to guard the Pilgrim Hall for Master.
Your Royal Highness, this is the pith of Wutong Forest.
Thank you, Elder.
This pith is very hard.
You need to refine it with fig wine and Chaos fire,
then it can be effective.
Elder, is Feng Yan's core spirit in the crown of the tree?
Yes.
According to the schedule,
the Phoenix monarch will be reborn after a few months.
Although you are kind and don't mind our nature as beasts,
after the Phoenix monarch is reborn, she should go to the God Realm and be your sacred beast.
Elder, I want Wu Huan to follow me forever.
Well...
Your Royal Highness, Wu Huan is just a five-colored phoenix.
Her divine power is limited.
I'm afraid she won't be powerful in the future.
I knew her talent was not high.
But since I chose her, I'm willing to wait for her.
As the Chief God in the God Realm,
if I abandon her and choose the Phoenix monarch because of her low divine power,
in the future, if there is a beast stronger than the Phoenix monarch, what should I choose?
You're right, Your Royal Highness.
Okay. I hope she can cultivate hard
and not lose face for the Phoenix Clan.
Thank you, Elder.
When Feng Yan is reborn, she...
Just let her grow up happily and lightheartedly.
♫ Year after year time goes by ♫
♫ Don't be afraid if our fate comes back ♫
♫ Rains flood and memories last ♫
♫ My longing for you won't change no matter what ♫
♫ I have been waiting for so many years ♫
♫ I never leave despite endless sorrow ♫
♫ Love is like a faraway bright moon ♫
♫ I'll wait through my lifetime ♫
♫ I spend years waiting for returning birds ♫
♫ I never regret it and no one can replace you ♫
♫ I hope we'll uncover the past when we wake up ♫
♫ I'll finally bare my heart to you ♫
♫ Along the way, I watch flowers bloom and wither ♫
♫ Maybe we'll meet and part again in the future ♫
♫ Tears turn into clouds and rain falls in my heart ♫
♫ When the clouds break, our future will be clear ♫
♫ I'll enjoy a free life with you forever ♫