I will go to Shenyin Mountain for 100 years,
which is neither long nor short.
The one I worry about most is you.
Don't worry.
I'll help you guard Qingchi Palace.
But no one knows your heart, won't you be lonely?
How could I be lonely?
I can read stories and roll the dice.
I'm pretty good at entertaining myself.
Then, who should you tell your affections to at this moment?
You can tell?
We've been together for ten thousand years,
so we would know each other best.
Is he Jing Jian?
Did I guess wrong?
What do you think of Jing Jian?
Is he the "one"?
Do you think he will treat me like the way Qing Mu treats you?
You finally admit it!
Just go and ask him directly, instead of fidgeting here.
You are not as graceful as usual now.
If he were anyone else,
I'd definitely take him to Qingchi Palace and ask clearly.
But he is Jing Jian,
Jing Yang's younger brother
and the Heavenly Queen's son.
I don't think Jing Jian is the same as his family.
He is principled and rightful.
For you, he has defended Qingchi Palace many times.
I think in his heart, you are the most important person to him.
I love Feng Ran with willingness,
not forced by her.
Do you remember what I said at the bottom of Huajing Pond?
"If he treats me with sincerity,
I'd pay him back in kind."
Oh no!  Upper God asked me to help him buy something.
I nearly forgot about it.
Hou Chi, thank you.
I must go now.
Has she really understood my words?
Why are you here?
Qing Mu asked me to come.
I've received the medicines you sent. Thanks.
What Jing Yang said about you was also heard by you as well.
If that has upset you, I apologize for him to you.
Is there nothing else?
No.
Be a man!
If you love, then say you do.  If you don't, then say you don't.
Can't you just speak it out?
Recently, I have broken through my cultivation so I want to find a high-level talisman.
Come and take a look!
Why do you bring me to Observation Mountain Fair?
Of course, to go shopping at the market.
Shopping?
These undignified goods are for humble immortals,
you can take anything you like from the Purple Pine Hall.
You know nothing. Shopping here is more interesting.
Whatever, you spoiled my fun today.
You'll have to pay for anything I want here.
Okay.
I'll buy everything you like for you.
- Two spiritual beads of low quality are enough.
- Too expensive.
Lordess, what can I do for you?
Gentleman. How much are these red candles?
Lordess, you have a good eye.
Although this pair of candles aren't good looking,
they were used in the wedding of the Qingqiu Fox Fairy
and the Immortal Golden Dragon of the East Sea.
A symbol of happiness.
A spiritual bead of high quality for a pair.
You made up a nice story.
The heavenly power on them has evaporated,
there is only a thousand years left for them to burn.
A spiritual bead of low quality is not even worthy.
I can't believe that you are an expert in it.
Fine, you can buy them with a spiritual bead of low quality.
Look. There will be a wedding at our house.
I'll buy your red candles,
and give me this, this, this one, and this.
Let me take them by a spiritual bead of low quality, okay?
Lady, this is too much.
I won't make such kind of deal. Never.
Wait. Two spiritual beads of low quality.
I can't, really. I mean it.
Say something helpful.
Upper God Gu Jun asked me to go out for business.
If I can't complete it well, he will blame me when I get back.
Sir, you've said that these candles
were used at the wedding of the Qingqiu Fox Fairy and Immortal Dragon of the East Sea.
I happen to work in the Heavenly Palace,
and know that the marriage between immortal
and demon is strictly forbidden.
As an immortal, you keep these kinds of prohibited items secretly.
Heavenly official, don't be mad.
I won't do it anymore. Okay?
I bought so much with a spiritual bead of low quality.
Today, we got a great bargain.
Now that Lordess Feng Ran is satisfied,
can I be forgiven?
Do you want to comfort me with so little?
If I can't empty your wallet,
I'll write my name of Feng Ran upside-dow.
All right.
Hou Chi.
What brings you here?
Didn't my father say that we can't meet before the wedding?
Don't worry. I've bribed Jia Ye.
I want to give you these.
What are these?
Shenyin Mountain is a treacherous place since ancient times without even a plant.
But there are many fierce beasts.
Although you've improved your spiritual power, you have to spend a hundred years alone.
It will be hard to keep yourself safe,
so I refined these elixirs for you just in case you get hurt.
Are these all refined by you?
And also these spells.
I made them with the Tai Cang Spear's power.
At a critical moment, these will keep you safe.
It's so nice of you to think things through so carefully.
However, why do you only think that I'll get hurt?
What if I get lonely and bored over there?
I've already prepared for that, look.
What animal is it? Quite cute!
Lord Dong Hua deceived me!
He said it's a one-in-a-century divine dog,
but has no spiritual aura at all.
It is just cute.
It can relieve your boredom. Do you like it?
I like it very much.
This is the best gift I've ever gotten.
What is this?
You are the wife of the Lord of the North Sea.
Among the Heavenly Realm, I'll find anything you like.
Xiao Huang, if he betrays me in the future,
you must help me bite him hard.
Hou Chi, I prepared another gift for you.
You will surely like it.
Dibei City?
Upper God Hou Chi, please go with your husband.
A pot of tea, please.
Okay.
Did she learn from you?
Shuo'er has no spiritual vein
but I think it's enough for her to protect herself with martial arts.
It should have taken a lot of effort to teach a child of the Human Realm.
When did you teach her?
My wife, have you started monitoring your husband before getting married?
Sister!
Finally, you have come to see Shuo'er.
I thought Qing Mu cheated me again.
Impossible. When did I cheat you?
Qing Mu is stricter than my father.
He even threatened that if I didn't practice hard, I couldn't have a meal.
Bai Shuo.
But martial arts is something that Shuo'er has to learn on her own.
My mom told me that I can't rely on Sister for everything.
My dad is gone,
our Bai family will depend on me in the future.
Shuo'er has grown up.
Later on, both Dibei City and your mom will rely on you.
By the way, it's rare for you to come.
I'll ask my mom to cook for you.
Also, my favorite osmanthus cake.
You must like it, too.
Upper God Hou Chi,
let me guess. Do you want to thank me for Shuo'er?
You've absorbed the evil aura and sealed it in the Underground Palace.
You hadn't recovered your spiritual power when you came to teach her.
I feel deeply touched.
Don't just say you're touched, you should show gratitude like this.
Sweet. Sweeter than the osmanthus cake.
Why did you say you'd bring me to an excellent place, and then bring me to the Demon Realm?
Look.
You grew up in the Heavenly Palace,
and couldn't have seen such beautiful sunset.
Let me broaden your horizon.
Sunset with a nice wine. So beautiful.
I heard that the cloudy sky after the rain in the Swamp of Netherhill is a must-see in the three realms.
Looking at it today, it really lives up to its reputation.
I've been wandering around in the Demon Realm since I was a child.
I often came here alone to watch the sunset.
The old guy always searched for me on the mountain.
If he failed, he'd call me by the Red Feather.
I keep saying that I will get revenge for him.
But to this day, the debt has not been repaid with blood.
If Jing Yang wasn't your brother,
I'd have taken action earlier on.
I didn't mean it.
Feng Ran, only by being nice to you can I make up for the mistakes my family made to you.
Just because of guilt?
Of course not.
Thousands of years have passed,
the sunset hasn't changed,
but the people who see it have changed.
There is something urgent, I have to go.
Take care of yourself.
Drink slowly, no one will rob it from you.
Feng Ran, I'm sorry for my rudeness just now.
Do you know why I brought you here?
The sunset is beautiful, but it's also short.
Just like a god's life is long,
it's but a drop in the vast ocean.
So we should cherish the present.
What do you think?
Feng Ran.
Go back and rest.
I'll see you at the wedding reception tomorrow.
Okay.
Jing Jian, I have something to say to you.
I don't like talking in a roundabout way.
I want to tell you that I have feelings for you...
and I know you have feelings for me, too.
Or else, you wouldn't have talked to your brother like that.
- Feng Ran—
- I... I know.
If you want to be with me,
there are too many difficulties to overcome.
But nothing in this world is easy.
So I order you to go back tonight and figure it out.
If you are willing to stay with me, no matter what difficulties are in Heaven and Earth,
I will face life and death with you.
If we can't be a couple, being friends is fine as well.
But you must reply to me at the ceremony tomorrow.
I don't want to guess anymore to feel unnecessary worries.
Do you understand?
♫ If our love turns into ashes in the end ♫ ​
So be it.  I'm going back first.
See you, Prince Jing Jian.
♫ I'm willing to search for thousands of days and nights ♫
Feng Ran, you're right.
Tomorrow, I will give you an answer.
♫ Exchange a lifetime for a second of encounter ♫
♫ It's not a pity to be able to accomplish it ♫
- You...
- I...
You said that you had prepared the wedding well yesterday.
If I change my mind now, would it be okay?
Of course not.
The marriage is serious, can't be changed randomly.
What are you thinking?
It's not like what you're thinking.
I won't marry anyone but you.
I was scared. I thought you didn't want to marry me.
You said that you'd marry nobody but me.
Can you say it again?
I mean, as we went to the Human Realm today,
I suddenly want to hold a wedding like a normal couple,
saluting Heaven, Earth, the moon, and the sun.
Those who attend it are all our family and friends with best wishes
instead of many guests.
I wonder if my whim will fail the wedding you prepared in advance?
No. How easy it is.
A once in a lifetime promise.
As long as you want it, everything is within reach.
Let's be a normal couple.
We have so many years to grow old together,
and we can have many babies.
I'll teach them to kill demons and devils while you...
you can teach them music, chess, writing, and drawing.
How about this?
Qing Mu, I don't know anything about those things.
I can teach you first.
Heavenly Queen, the air in here is too oppressive,
making walking extremely difficult.
Can you bear it?
I have to even if I can't.
The evil aura in the Netherworld was once very strong.
Although it becomes thin now,
if I can unseal the evil aura here
by Refining Sky Bow and improve my cultivation,
maybe I can reach the top level of Upper God,
reaching enough strength to rival a True God.
Although the Refining Sky Bow is good,
it is a devil weapon, the risk can't be estimated.
I'm afraid that...
You're afraid that I'd become a devil?
I know it's dangerous, too.
I tried so hard
but failed to inflict heavy losses on Qingchi Palace when Hou Chi grabbed the three treasures.
What's more, Mu Guang felt disappointed in me.
If I don't take another try, it'll be hard for me
to enjoy the title of Heavenly Queen.
Your Highness, you're over-worrying. How could it be so?
The conflict between me and the True Gods
is not only this one.
I'll definitely be careful when I cultivate.
For Yang'er, Jian'er, and Zhao'er's sake,
I won't allow myself to lose control and become a devil.
Heavenly Queen.
Stop persuading me.
Go back.
Help me remind Yang'er
of eradicating the scourge as soon as possible.
And... help me to guard Fuyao Hall well.
Yes, Your Highness.
Father God.
If you want to plead for your mom, too, just go back.
As the king, I've made up my mind.
I came to visit after hearing that you were unwell.
I won't talk much about my mother god's issue.
It's all up to your decision.
Father,
taste the nutritious food Zhao'er made for you.
You've gone through so many things
and you've grown up.
In the past, I was naive
so you kept worrying about me.
From now on, I will cultivate my mind
instead of being arrogant and willful.
Father God, please take good care of yourself.
The peace of the three realms relies on you.
Lord Dong Hua is here.
Your Majesty. Princess.
Dong Hua, I called you here to ask you to check
the Underground Palace in the imperial mausoleum of the Human Realm.
Does Your Majesty want to know
about the leak of the evil aura in the Human Realm?
The evil aura is raging in the Human Realm.
Although it was caused by Hou Chi grabbing the Soul Tower,
Bi Xi has guarded the tower for 60,000 years.
With his spiritual power, even if he lost the tower,
he should have held it back for a few days.
This matter has been bothering me.
Please go and investigate
about whether I should be concerned or not.
Yes, I'll go to the Human Realm to investigate now.
If a clue is found,
- I'll report to Your Majesty immediately.
- Thank you for the trouble.
I'll take my leave.
Master.
They'll get married in the Human Realm.
You wouldn't want to see this.
During the 60,000 years,
I followed every command of yours,
but only this time, I'll do what I want.
If you want to blame me in the future, then just blame me.
Don't take it out on Qing Mu or Hou Chi.
During the 60,000 years,
unconsciously, I've taken Hou Chi
as my daughter for real.
I just want her to be happy.
Even though the happiness for her can't last forever,
it would be a kind of precious firework.
For this life, Hou Chi has been wronged many times.
After all,
it's us that owes her.
Master, it seems that you've recovered.
How has Hou Chi been these days?
Her Royal Highness has been pretty good recently.
Pretty good?
She turned the realms upside-down for Bo Xuan.
She abandoned her identity of god and has to stay
in the Shenyin Mountain for a hundred years.
How could this result make her live well?
Master.
Her Royal Highness is really happy.
But her happiness might not be good news for you.
Congratulations!
Be careful.
They're coming!
Congratulations! Congratulations!
Be careful. Pay attention.
Congratulations!
- Wish you happiness!
- Congratulations!
Well, Auntie Zhang. Let's skip it.
Lady, brides dress like this when they get married.
You can't violate the auspicious rules of happiness.
If so, let's make it simple.
Hou Chi, this marriage is a major event in life that only comes once in a lifetime.
How can we keep it simple?
I've prepared everything for you.
Not one piece is missing.
About this, you have to listen to the experienced ones.
Right.
You know what?
The higher the bride's hairstyle is, the better and more prosperous the future will be.
Look. Do you want the style with
the nine-tiered crown of a eight-treasure lotus
or the phoenix hairpin with four symbols?
I'm regretting.
I should have stayed in Qingchi Palace to receive the blessing from the three realms.
Knock on wood! It's your wedding day.
How can you say such unlucky words?
You can't regret today.
Eat some candied fruit later, for good luck.
They're coming.
Congratulations.
Qing Mu, my waist is sore because of waiting for you.
What does that mean?
It's said that in Dibei City, the bride's family should block the door before marriage.
So I came to enjoy this custom.
Which side are you on?
Is it necessary to ask?
I'm certainly the bride's family.
Then no need to bother.
Hurry up and have a drink at the banquet.
It's not a bother, not a bother at all.
We are good friends.
I must make your wedding lively and dramatic.
Qing Mu, are you afraid?
Of course not!
Tell me. What is the custom of blocking the door?
How can I get in?
According to the rules in the Human Realm,
the first round is to send lucky money.
How hard is that?
How is it?
Pick it up.
Quickly.
It barely counts.
Do you think he's qualified to pass?
Yes!
- Sure!
This round was too easy for you.
But the second won't be that easy.
Please.
Let's go.
Congratulations!
What does it mean this time?
Today is a happy day.
It would be too indecent if it was compared to the immortal method.
So let's play a game.
If you win, I will agree with you to marry Hou Chi.
Among four of these, one of them is Hou Chi.
But you can't touch them.
If you select the right one, you can pass this round.
If you guess wrong,
not only will the wedding be canceled,
but your bridal chamber night will be postponed for another hundred years.
Give me some hints.
Buddy, I really can't help you. Rely on yourself.
Look carefully.
- Wife.
- Husband.
Not her.
Too impulsive. Look carefully.
She is too disgusting, it wouldn't be Hou Chi.
I was tender and gentle.
How can you say I was disgusting?
Turn back now.
When I think of what you said just now, I feel even more sick.
When did Hou Chi's waist become so thick?
Bastard Qing Mu.
Who do you think has a thick waist?
Be careful I don't extract out your rotten mouth!
How dare you lie to me?
Touching is not allowed, but lying was not mentioned.
Full of cunning tricks.
All of you, on this happy day,
what are you joking about?
Please forgive us. We dare not any more.
Qing Mu, you cheated!
How can you cheat?
I also think you cheated.
You said that Hou Chi was one of the four of you.
Where is my wife?
Fine, fine.
The moment of the wedding is priceless.
He must be quite eager.
The bride is waiting in the back.
Let's invite the bride to come.
Who is he?
Jing Yuan?
How dare you marry Hou Chi before getting my permission?
- Hou Chi's father has agreed to this—
-  Shut up.
Jing Yuan.
I am marrying Hou Chi after seeing three matchmakers, sound betrothal gifts, and Heaven and Earth as our witnesses,
according to the rituals of the god's and mortals.
What concern is that of yours?
Mr. Immortal, why do you wear a wedding gown, too?
Do you also want to get married today?
Little girl, you're really smart.
Right,
I came to snatch the bride today.
I think this gentleman looks handsome, too.
Right.
Everybody, my master is enormously wealthy
so he must marry a nice lady like Hou Chi with enough sincerity.
Come!  Help yourselves, my friends.
Today, let's see who will be the bridegroom.
That's right.
Pretty nice.
Jing Yuan!
Qing Mu, don't get impulsive on your wedding day.
This marriage was not only decided by the parents,
but was also agreed by Hou Chi herself.
I'm afraid that it will be hard to change.
Hou Chi decided personally?
She's always muddleheaded,
and not able to recognize people accurately.
She must have been deceived by someone.
What do you mean?
What are you doing?
It's the best time to start. Why don't you welcome the bride?
Why are two bridegrooms here?
It's the business between them, just leave it to Hou Chi.
Jing Yuan.
I'm here.
Thank you, Master Jing Yuan, for your protection.
Your grace has been branded on Hou Chi's mind.
Today is my wedding.
Master Jing Yuan, please step aside and drink more.
Hou Chi, let me ask you.
Have you made up your mind to marry this guy?
Yes.
If I insist on grabbing you from the wedding?
Master Jing Yuan, you clearly know that I'm not her.
I am who I am.
You treat me well because of Shang Gu but not Hou Chi.
In the future, don't take me for her anymore.
Okay?
Brother.
Zhao'er.
Why are you here?
I looked for you everywhere.
Father God doubts the evil aura's invasion.
You can't make anymore mistakes.
Go to the Xuan Tian Hall with me to confess your fault to Father God.
- He will forgive you.
- No.
This is related to Mother God, we can never let Father God know about it.
I'll kill Bi Xi. Only when no one in this world knows the truth
will Mother God return as soon as possible.
My master said that he'd feel sad by witnessing this.
He won't come to be greeted.
Her Highness has been unable to always follow her heart since she was a child.
Today's ceremony is up to you to decide.
Father God, Hou Chi, and Qing Mu are paying respects to you.
The first bow.
Secondly, bow to Heaven and Earth.
The couple may bow to each other.
♫ Time is like you, disturbing my feelings and thoughts ♫
♫ I hold your warm hands tightly ♫
♫ The meteor is shining in the sky ♫
♫ I can never forget the memories of you ♫
♫ I cherish the time to be with you ♫
♫ It's still vivid for me ♫
♫ When I meet you, I hope we can be together forever ♫
Let's go.
♫ When we meet again ♫
♫ I'll travel with you without hesitation ♫
♫ The feels ♫
Wife.
♫ That distance. The small talk ♫
You haven't finished the ceremony.
Mr. Bridegroom, look how eager you are.
Can't you be a little bit reserved?
What is there to be reserved about?
I wanted to call her like this long before.
From today, Hou Chi is my pure and innocent wife.
- Zhao'er.
- You can't fool around today.
Don't accuse me wrongly, I didn't know they'd get married today.
Hou Chi. Qing Mu.
I have to leave to deal with some family business.
Jing Jian, is there anything wrong?
Do you need our help?
Speaking of which, it still has something to do with Hou Chi.
Zhao'er, you are talking too much.
Thank you all for celebrating our marriage.
The banquet is ready. Please move to the side hall for merriment.
Sister Immortal.
Mrs. Bai. Shuo'er. Please help us serve the guests.
Don't worry, My Lady.
Bi Xi identified Hou Chi at the Heavenly Palace by the orders of my Mother God.
My brother was worried that my father would know, so he's going to kill him.
This is what's going on.
Bi Xi is in danger, so let's go to the imperial mausoleum quickly.
No. Your wedding ceremony hasn't been completed.
It's the Heavenly Palace that delays your wedding.
Qing Mu. Hou Chi. Thanks for your kind will.
I got you into trouble
and don't let me feel more guilty.
This trouble was caused by me, how can I escape responsibility?
Hou Chi is my wife, her business is also mine.
Let's go. A life is at stake, any delay may cause changes.
You came at the wrong time.
I just want to save our brother.
You'd better stay there to face your death,
no need to struggle desperately.
I can't believe my momentary slip
of making a deal with devils
should lead to such a consequence, I deserve this.
However, Your Highness, if I die,
the evil aura seal in the Underground Palace will definitely disappear with the passage of time.
If the evil auras reappear, the Human Realm will never be peaceful.
I can't consider that much.
If you don't die, my Mother God will be in danger.
I have no other choice.
Bi Xi, sorry.
Stop!
- Zhao'er!
- Jing Yang, stop it.
Jing Jian, how could you fight against me?
Brother, don't make any more mistakes.
Go to the Heavenly Palace with me to apologize to Father God.
Zhao'er, you don't want our elder brother to make more mistakes,
but why do you stop me again?
Jing Jian, I thought the same as you
but if Father God punishes our brother, Mother God will be punished, too.
If it is known by the three realms
that the underground evil auras were released by him under Mother God's instruction,
she will...
Jing Yang released the underground evil auras, killed immortal peers,
which has endangered the three realms!  How could it be tolerated?
Even if this matter involves Mother God, I'll never show favoritism.
Three realms.  Three realms.
You and Father God only care about the three realms! Not our family!
Mother has been asked to live in the Netherworld.
Hasn't she suffered enough?
If Father God knows about this, not only will Elder Brother's life be at stake,
Mother God will never come back.
Jing Jian, you can't tell this to Father God,
and you also should ask Qing Mu and Hou Chi not to say it.
Or else, our family will be gone.
Zhao'er, I have taken our family into consideration
and act with personal feelings.
How can you force others to cover up for our family?
Gods, don't waste your divine power.
I'm dying.
It's all my fault.
If I hadn't insisted on taking Soul Tower away,
things wouldn't have been like today.
You don't need to blame yourself,
everything has its fate.
For 60,000 years, the God Realm has been sealed,
True Gods are nowhere to be found.
Wars and disasters are endless in the Human Realm.
I didn't want to see the Human Realm suffer,
so I colluded with the Heavenly Queen,
with stupidity but it was to no avail.
I'm a dead man.
I deserve my death.
But if I die,
no one will suppress evil auras.
There will be chaos in the Human Realm.
True God Bai Jue entrusted me but I let him down.
Lord, trust me,
I'll clean the evil auras and protect the Human Realm in the coming 100 years.
♫ Year after year time goes by ♫
♫ Don't be afraid if our fate comes back ♫
♫ Rains flood and memories last ♫
♫ My longing for you won't change no matter what ♫
♫ I have been waiting for so many years ♫
♫ I never leave despite endless sorrow♫
♫ Love is like a faraway bright moon ♫
♫ I'll wait through my lifetime ♫
♫ I spend years waiting for returning birds ♫
♫ I never regret it and no one can replace you ♫
♫ I hope we'll uncover the past when we wake up ♫
♫ I'll finally bare my heart to you ♫
♫ Along the way, I watch flowers bloom and wither ♫
♫ Maybe we'll meet and part again in the future ♫
♫ Tears turn into clouds and rain falls in my heart ♫
♫ When the clouds break, our future will be clear ♫
♫ I'll enjoy a free life with you forever ♫