[Episode 30]
In order to have the upper hand,
I've decided to attack them first.
And this time, I'll lead the troops myself.
You can't do that, Your Majesty.
It's a long journey to Wei.
The battlefield is dangerous and unpredictable.
You are the master of this country.
You can't just go into war.
Sir Yang is right. Please reconsider your decision.
Please reconsider your decision!
I've already made up my mind. No need to advise me against it.
For the war this time,
I'll bring along a right-hand man with me.
Father, I recommend Wuyou.
Wuyou has studied hard since young and is an expert in the art of war.
If you bring Wuyou along, you'll gain a speedy success.
I'm willing to go into war to be of service as well.
Please allow me to do so.
No, Father. Although Wuyou is good in the art of war,
he lacks experience in an actual war. Rrather than bringing him along,
it's better to bring along a general who has fought countless battles.
Please reconsider.
If so, in your opinion,
who will be the best choice?
Father, I recommend...
Father, I've been away from military affairs for too long.
I don't know about the conditions of our generals.
How about you ask General Fu for his opinion?
Your Majesty, I think that...
Prince Chen is very right.
Prince Li is an expert in the art of war.
And he had led the war at the southern border.
And he knows the situations of every war like the back of his hand.
He's a fast learner.
I feel inadequate compared to him.
So I think,
it's best to bring along Prince Li for the war this time.
Even General Fu has recommended Prince Li.
All right.
Wuyou, you'll come along with me for the war against Wei.
I'm not willing.
I already said that...
we need to pacify the people first before we attack others.
Now, there are pirates running wild along the coast.
Western Qi and Chen are eyeing us covetously.
We suffer from natural continuous calamities and we are out of money.
The Southwest region is in a state of famine.
We have both domestic and foreign troubles.
It's better for us if we wait until we are strong again...
and our people are well-rested and are in unity.
Only then can we send out our troops...
to bring peace to our country.
Nonsense.
Northern Lin has enjoyed propitious weather and good harvest constantly.
The people are living peacefully and we are in unity.
We don't have calamities.
And we don't have domestic unrest or a famine problem.
What nonsense it is.
Guards!
Prince Li has disobeyed my order. The war is almost upon us.
He has exaggerated things to cause alarm to the people.
Throw him out.
You sit in your precious palace all year long and you have...
no regards for the people's sufferings.
You just know how to praise yourself and try to cheat the people.
My teacher was right back then.
People like you will never be a brilliant emperor.
Insolent fool! How dare you say that I'm not a brilliant emperor?
Unfilial son.
You are indeed the best student of Qin Yong.
You never listen to me.
He has been gone for so many years.
But you still remember each and every word he has uttered.
Why are you standing there for? Throw him out!
No need!
I've never wanted to be here in the first place.
From now on, don't think that I'll ever come back again!
You!
Get lost! Go back to your southern border!
Don't come back every again!
- Father, Wuyou is just...
- Shut up!
I'll throw you out if you say another word.
Please calm down.
Since Wuyou is not willing to go into war with you,
I would like to recommend the General of Defense to go with you.
General Fu is very experienced on the battlefield and has never lost in one.
He can help you achieve victory.
We'll go with Prince Fanyang's advice then.
General Fu, get yourself prepared immediately.
You'll come along with me for the war in three days' time.
When I'm at war,
all public affairs will be handled by the crown prince
with Prince Chen as an assistant.
The court is dismissed.
Thank you, Father.
Farewell, Your Majesty!
I heard that you are tagging along with him for the war against Wei.
He had moved 300,000 soldiers from all over the place to join the war...
except for my Armour Troops.
He ordered me to go into war with him on my own.
Of course, I know... the real reason behind his actions.
Looks like we have to move our plan forward.
We've waited for so many years. Finally, we have our chance.
When do you plan to make a move?
The entire plan is in my head. I know what to do.
As for you, you just need to act according to my orders.
Hen Xiang told me that you want to change your plan for a woman.
Is it true?
We have been planning for many years to get this far.
Victory is in sight.
We have to go with the plan.
I address you as Uncle Lin...
because you are my mother's most loyal servant.
You've saved me before.
And you've taken great pains to teach and train me.
The bone-piercing pain that I suffered every year...
is a burning reminder of my mother's hatred.
They are burned into my mind.
But I want to remind you.
You are just an assistant to help me complete this revenge.
As for the how,
it's entirely up to me.
Looks like you have deep hatred against me.
I wasn't trying to make the decision for you.
I'm just reminding you that...
our master has been waiting for too long in the dark.
Don't worry.
For those who've hurt my mother,
I'll make them pay a terrible price for it.
Good.
This is the young master that I know.
Only by doing so, can you repay our master who had suffered in order to protect you.
If we want to take revenge,
we have to get rid of Zongzheng Wuyou.
Rong Le is his biggest weakness.
Only by using her, can we make sure that nothing will go wrong.
I don't need to use Rong Le to get rid of Zongzheng Wuyou.
Is that so?
From the surface, you are at an advantage.
But Zongzheng Wuyou's strength lurks in the shadows.
If you want to fight him in the open,
you'll ruin the plan that we've spent so many years on.
You have always been the illegitimate son who lives in darkness.
Why do you want to fight him in the open?
Do you think that Rong Le will like you by doing so?
Stop dreaming.
As long as Zongzheng Wuyou lives,
you won't stand a chance.
Go.
Go and feel the bone-piercing pain that your mother had once suffered from.
Remember that suffering...
and you'll remember your identity.
At the same time, it'll clear your mind.
Guards!
Young Master.
Master, Young Master has done nothing wrong.
Why do you want to punish him again?
Hen Xiang,
you've healed so quickly in such a short time?
Don't think that I know nothing just because you kept it a secret.
In order to save Rong Le,
Young Master had hurt one of his own seriously.
And he tried to change the plan.
I know everything.
How did you know...
when I've never told you about it?
Since you are already hurt,
I won't punish you today.
But remember.
I'm the one who saved you from the gate of hell.
I taught you martial arts...
and trained you into a remarkable assassin.
You like Young Master.
I don't mind it if you want to keep his secrets for him.
But if it'll affect the plan of our revenge,
I will not forgive you easily.
I wouldn't dare to do so.
In order to initiate this plan sooner,
I have a task for you.
Disguise yourself as Rong Le...
No.
No. I can't do that.
I can't do that.
Only by doing so, will you be able to avenge your family.
Maybe after that, you'll have a chance to marry the person you like.
Two birds in one stone.
I can't do that.
You already know about my plan.
If you are not going to do it,
then I can't let you live.
Guards.
- Take her out!
- Let go of me.
You can't kill me now.
I need to help Young Master control the crown prince.
If I die now, it'll affect his plan for revenge.
He won't forgive you for that.
He's just a useless crown prince.
It's not that hard... to control him.
Let me tell you truthfully, Hen Xiang.
I've already planned this... for quite some time.
If you don't want to do it, there will be others to do it.
Rather than letting others do it,
it's better for you to do it instead.
Brother, although Fu Chou will be joining you in the war,
his Armour Troops are still here in Zhongshan.
And there is a sudden influx of refugees to the city.
I think that something is not right with it.
Would you reconsider delaying the war?
We have the Royal Army here.
I'll leave behind a secret decree.
If something is amiss with the Armour Troops,
the Royal Army will be under Wuyu's command.
Besides, the generals of the Armour Troops...
are under the close surveillance of Wuyou.
There won't be any problems.
As for the refugees,
something is not right with it indeed.
Wuyou will take care of it.
Wuyou?
He was already banished from this city by you, right?
The date for war is already set.
We'll agitate our soldiers if we delay it again.
We can't change our plan for the war against Wei.
What about the crown prince?
When Fu Chou is gone, the crown prince can't do much alone.
He's under Wuyu's surveillance.
And Wuyou won't be too far away from Zhongshan...
to give them a loophole to exploit.
Wuyou!
Wuyou.
This is not for me.
Are you really going to go back to the southern border at a time like this?
Today, Father said those words in a fit of rage.
Don't take it to heart.
Besides, are you really not going to join father in the war?
If you go with him and come back with victory,
you'll be welcomed by the officials and cheered by the people.
And everyone will forget about Fu Chou's contributions.
When that time comes, naturally, you'll hold the military power.
Why did you refuse to do this kind of beneficial thing?
I...
Did I say something wrong again?
You might be right if you told me about this one year ago.
That time, Fu Chou was still at the frontier pass...
and didn't have real power in the court yet.
But now, Fu Chou has expanded his clique...
and he has ganged up with the crown prince.
Besides, he's cooperating with Rong Qi, the emperor of Western Qi in secret.
All the generals in the Armour Troops are his trusted aides.
If I join the war together with Father now...
with only the crown prince and Fu Chou in command of the capital,
what do you think would happen?
Are you saying that they'd revolt?
Crown Prince is not that brave.
He is not.
But Fu Chou is.
Wuyou, since you already knew, why did you fight with Father then?
I get it now. Both of you did it on purpose.
No. What happened today...
is just a show that you'd planned together with Father. Right?
I'm just afraid that Fu Chou won't be so easily fooled like the others.
It's impossible that he'd go against the order to stay out from the war.
Father has left you in the capital to spy on the crown prince anyway.
Make sure to keep a close eye on him.
About that, I was still puzzled about why Father trusted me so much...
to let me help the crown prince with the public affairs.
So, he wants me to keep watch on the crown prince.
Now, there are more and more refugees in the city.
Find a way to lure them out to the city.
Open up more food relief centers and give out food all day long.
Keep a close eye on the response of the refugees.
If you see someone suspicious, find a reason to lock them up for interrogation.
But don't use force.
I understand.
Wuyou, don't you have anything else for me to help out with?
For example, Man Yao?
Don't make things difficult for her.
I wouldn't dare to do so. She is the one you like.
When I'm not here, look out for her.
If there's anything, report to me at once.
All right. I get it.
This way please, Generals.
The Royal Army?
This way, please.
Princess Rong Le, take this medicine.
Although it's just a supplement, at least it can replenish your energy.
Thank you.
Princess, actually, His Majesty...
Don't mention him.
If he so much thinks of me as his sister,
he wouldn't try to control me with poison.
He even lied to me saying that it was the aftereffect of my escape.
The cure that he gave me can only suppress the effect of the poison temporarily.
It can't neutralize the poison at all.
If I beg him now, I'd be his string puppet for sure to do his bidding forever.
I don't want that.
Maybe... you wouldn't be controlled forever.
After we get the medicine, Xiao Ke can study it.
If she can find the original prescription for the poison,
she might be able to find a cure.
- He's right.
- Princess, I realized that many people were led into...
the general's study by Chang Jian for a secret discussion.
Among them are the generals from the army.
And they were wearing the plates of the Royal Army.
Royal Army?
The Royal Army answers to His Majesty. Why are they here with Fu Chou?
I don't know.
Recently, that place has been heavily guarded.
It's hard for me to spy on them.
The war against Wei is going to start soon.
What is the reason for Fu Chou to meet these generals in secret?
I have to get into his study.
Xiao Sha, go back to Western Qi to get the medicine.
Tell my brother that I'm at the death's door.
If he still wants me to work for him, give me the cure immediately.
Roger that.
- Be careful.
- All right.
Why are you here?
I'm here to get some food from the kitchen.
General's Manor is so strange. Why are there so many people guarding the kitchen?
This is General's Fu study. Nobody can come near it. Leave now.
This is the study? It's not the kitchen?
Then, do you know where the kitchen is?
I'm starving.
It's that way. Leave at once.
That way?
Leave now.
What happened to you? Wake up!
The candle in the manor is changed every day.
From the stub, they must have been here for the whole night.
Fu Chou knows how to play zither only.
When did he learn how to play the flute?
[Zhongshan City]
Distribution map for armed forces.
- General Fu.
Princess Rong Le.
[Granary]
[Armory]
[Prince Li's army]
General Fu!
- What is it?
- Lady Rong Le has fainted.
What?
[Tranquil Garden]
Rong Le.
- What happened?
- General Fu.
I don't know why but she fainted suddenly...
and she hasn't woken up since.
Princess Rong Le fainted because her worries made her ill.
General Fu, we need to get her medicine at once.
Or else, if she continues to sleep,
her body might be damaged and she might never wake again.
What kind of medicine do you need?
This kind of herb grows only in the deep mountains.
It's very rare, valuable and only I can recognize it.
Let me out. I'll get the herb for Princess Rong Le now.
Wait.
If you go out, who will take care of my wife?
How about this?
Write down the name of the herb. I'll send someone to get it.
I already said. It's a rare herb and only I can recognize it.
General Fu, let Xiao Ke go.
Just write it down for me.
There are so many physicians in the city.
Even if they don't know,
we still have the royal physicians from the palace.
Take good care of Lady Rong Le.
Don't always think about escaping from here.
Outside is not a safer place compared to here.
Remember. All lands belong to His Majesty.
And all soldiers are our men.
Even if you manage to go out from this door, you might not...
be able to survive the outside world.
Maybe this is... the safest place for you to be in.
Ling Yue, get me a piece of white handkerchief now.
Your Highness, General of Defense wants to meet you.
Why is he here?
I'm not going to meet him.
He said that he has a very important gift for you.
What can he give me?
Bring him in.
Yes, Your Highness.
Greetings, Crown Prince.
Aren't you going to join my father in the war?
Do you still have time for me?
From the way you are talking,
looks like you are still mad at me...
for the incident at the court yesterday.
I wouldn't dare to be mad at you.
It's fine that Wuyu recommend him.
But how can you recommend him as well?
What do you mean by that?
If Wuyou is victorious, he'll hold the military power.
What good will it do to you?
Luckily, my father is wise and banished Wuyou to the southern border.
Or else, there would be no place for me in this court anymore.
What are you laughing at?
Do you think that His Majesty will bring Prince Li along...
to fight in the war just because I recommended him?
Do you really think that Prince Li has disobeyed the order...
and by making His Majesty mad, they'll turn against each other from now on...
and your position as crown prince will be secured?
If you really think so, then you are too naive.
It's such a miracle that you are able to sit in this position...
as crown prince for so long.
What do you mean by that?
That day, in the court, the fight that His Majesty and Prince Li had...
was just a show they made in order to fool you.
Do you really believe it?
Just now, you asked me why was I laughing.
I'm laughing because you are already under the guillotine...
and you are in imminent danger.
But you are still drinking your celebratory wine here.
Do you really think that it's a good thing...
for me to go out for war while Prince Li is here?
Don't you know that... it'll be our death warrant?
What did you say?
Father left Wuyou behind to finish me off?
Impossible. Don't try to scare me.
If you don't believe me,
then don't blame me when your head is on the ground one day.
Please wait!
General Fu...
Their fight was too sudden that day.
Father didn't even punish Wuyou when he rejected...
the marriage in public back then.
This time, why are they in such a fit...
just because of some disagreements?
But what is the purpose of this show between my father and Wuyou?
If Father wants to kill me, he doesn't need to put in so much trouble.
He even entrusted me with the country.
That's the most vital step in their plan.
You are chosen as crown prince...
because Lady Yun is in debt with your mother.
But this kind of loving-kindness will burn out eventually.
Prince Li used to be very tolerant of you.
Now, he treats you worse than he treats a stranger.
Same goes for His Majesty.
Ever since you failed in the war against Wei,
His Majesty has been wanting to strip you of your position.
I think you know this better than anyone.
Otherwise, you wouldn't have hired the Creed of Vengeance...
to assassinate Prince Li at all cost.
Continue.
He needs a reason to strip you of your position.
He can't do it without any reason.
All these years, you've done your duty well.
And you haven't done any major mistakes.
Even if you did, His Majesty has no solid proof about it.
If he wants to strip you of your position,
he has to find a concrete reason to do so.
What kind of reason?
His Majesty knows that we have ganged up with each other in secret.
That's why he put on this show...
to make sure that I have no choice but to join him in war.
His real purpose is to separate us and attack us one by one.
I have to join His Majesty for the war without my Armor Troops.
He falsely banished Prince Li...
so that he can go back to the southern border to send his troops here.
He asked you to take care of the nation with Prince Chen's help.
If you put it nicely, it's to help.
But he's actually here to spy on you.
If something is amiss, you'll be labeled as a rebel.
And by then, Prince Li will send his army into the city.
You won't even have the chance to explain.
- I...
- And you'll die in vain and unjustly.
Then I'll do nothing so that they won't have a reason to kill me.
It'll still be the same whether you do it or not.
All of them have spent so much effort to set this trap.
They won't let you get away easily.
If I'm not wrong,
someone must be working for His Majesty in the Armor Troops.
They'll make trouble in your name.
When that time comes, you'll be dead.
And I won't fare any better than you.
Father is so ruthless.
General Fu.
You have to save me, General!
No. We are in the same boat.
Saving me means saving yourself, General.
What should we do?
No need to panic.
I'm here today to do exactly that.
This...
What do you mean by this?
Now, nobody else can save us.
We are the only ones who can save ourselves.
We are our own salvation.
Are you saying that... we should rebel for real?
Please think carefully, Crown Prince.
This is the only way... for both of us to survive this.
No.
You said it yourself. Father planned this out so meticulously.
We won't succeed.
We won't if it's just you alone.
But I already told you,
I'm doing this to save myself too.
How confident you are?
If it fails, it'll be a done deal for us.
We are done for anyway.
Since we will be dead anyway...
and we'll be labeled as rebels,
why not we take a risk to save our lives?
If we want to get the things we desire,
we have to pay for it.
What is your desire?
When you wear this dragon robe...
and sit on that almighty dragon chair,
you'll know what to do.
I just hope that when the time comes, you'll be kind to me.
All right.
Since you've proposed this,
I'm sure that you've already a plan in mind.
I believe in you.
As long as you can help me become the emperor,
I promise you, aside from the throne, I can give you...
whatever you desire.
I'll take my leave then.
Your Majesty.
This is such a handsome robe.
It's way better than any other robes that you have.
I can't wait to see your dashing appearance...
in this robe while you stand in front of the Xuande Hall...
to receive your support and love from the officials and the people.
Xiang.
I've waited so long for this day.
I've had enough of this crown prince title which is all name and no power.
Xiang,
how long have you known General Fu?
What kind of a person is he?
I haven't known him long.
He is...
a gentle... and modest gentleman.
Why did you ask me this suddenly?
Could it be that you are suspicious... about General Fu?
Suspicious?
How could I suspect General Fu?
General Fu is my most trusted ally now.
I'm counting on him... to make me into an emperor.
That's right.
It's good that you understand.
You are in a difficult situation now.
And you have no one to rely on.
As long as you have General Fu's help,
you'll get what you wish for.
When that time comes,
no one in this world will dare raise their voices against you anymore.
And no one... will dare disobey you again.
Xiang, you are right.
But what if I fail?
Xiang, will you leave me if I fail?
You are destined to be an emperor. You were born for it.
It is your destiny.
- You will not lose.
- I mean what if?
There will be no what-ifs.
I believe in you...
and I believe in General Fu.
All right.
All right!
Xiang, if you say I won't lose, then I won't lose.
For you, I'll take this risk.
After I sit on the throne and sentenced Zongzheng Wuyou to death,
I'll confer you the title as Imperial Consort.
When that time comes,
you'll rule over the imperial harem.
Besides you, I want nobody else.
You have to keep your word then.
Don't worry. I won't go back on my words.
[Dezheng Door]
Arrival of His Majesty!
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Rise.
March forward!
Victory!
[Dezheng Door]
This is bad! Help!
Lady Rong Le has fallen ill again!
- What happened?
- Lady Rong Le is sick again.
She is already unconscious. I need to get her the medicine.
Last time, General Fu had brought her the medicine, right?
That was last time. Her illness is more serious now.
The one we used last time can't cure her now.
I'll go to the apothecary house to get it then.
This is not a normal medicine.
I need the Dragon Flower.
This flower is the rarest among the rare.
You can't find it in a normal apothecary house. Let me out.
Tell me what the flower looks like. I'll get it for you.
You can find the flower only on the moss that grows on the dragon stone.
Its color is different for every season of the year.
It's entirely up to your luck to be able to find it.
And you have to be careful when you pluck it.
You can't pluck the newly bloomed and you can't pluck the newly wilted.
You can only take the petals, not the nectar.
If there's any nectar on it,
it'll become poison and the person who takes it will die for sure.
- Do you have the skill to pluck this kind of flower?
- No.
Let me out now. I'll go to the eastern suburb to get the medicine for her now.
But General Fu has ordered us that no one can leave the manor.
You give us no choice.
Let me tell you.
If something happens to the princess,
you'll be responsible for it when the general gets back.
This way, please.
Both of you stay here. The rest, follow me.
Princess, they are gone.
I hope that she will be successful this time.
♫ The snow falls on my palm ♫
♫ I just want to gaze at you one more time ♫
♫ I wait for the warmth of your gaze to melt it ♫
♫ We are fated to get hurt from the moment we met each other ♫
♫ I miss you but I can only gaze at you in silence ♫
♫ You are keeping me out with your care
Although we are together, I feel lost ♫
♫ I can wait for you until my hair turns white ♫
♫ I can endure all the loneliness just for you ♫
♫ I will be your hearth in the coldest of places ♫
♫ For you, I am willing to suffer ♫
♫ I want to ward off the coldness for you ♫
♫ As long as I can be with you, I'm willing to give you all of me ♫
♫ In a blink of an eye, my hair has turned silver ♫
♫ I'm fated to live in loneliness without any regrets ♫
♫ The winter may be cold,
but I will watch from afar and keep you warm ♫
♫ I'm willing to wipe away your blood and wounds for you ♫
♫ I'm willing to live in darkness for you ♫
♫ As long as I can be with you, I don't mind... hiding in the dark ♫