[Episode 29]
Even if you kill me today, I won't let you go.
But if I die, there'll be no one in this world...
who will treat you sincerely.
I lost my family since I was young.
Our master took me in...
and I went through the cruelest training together with you.
There were so many days and nights...
where we relied on each other.
We've spent the toughest time together.
I thought that I was different from others.
You once told me that I was your most trusted person.
Because of that, all these years,
no matter what you asked me to do,
I did all of them willingly. Because I believe that...
I was very important to you.
But recently, you've been disappointing me with the tasks that you are given.
That's because I'm afraid.
I'm afraid to see you falling deeper and deeper for Rong Le.
I'm afraid that she'll one day harm you.
I don't wish to see you suffer from the bone-piercing hurt again.
I don't wish to see you suffer from any harm.
I don't want you to be tortured by hate.
Even for our master,
I won't give him any excuses for him to hurt you.
The pain that you've suffered in the past...
should be repaid by all the best things in the world.
But now, I want to have even more.
Do you mean Rong Le?
She is not worth it.
She was once betrayed by her family.
And she was used by the people she trusted.
But she is still so kind and generous.
She is different from me and you.
That's because she's not hurt enough.
If everything is taken away from her...
and she can only survive by fighting in blood and sweat,
I don't believe that she can still keep her hands clean.
So, I won't turn her into another you.
We have the same enemy.
All these years, we have had the same goal.
So, everything that you did today...
was not only for me.
It's for yourself as well.
Because you want this revenge, too.
Hen Xiang,
I don't want to kill the person that you want,
and I won't let you kill her either.
I'll disappoint you sooner or later.
Will you betray me?
The feelings and loyalty that you've mentioned...
are just something very shallow.
You are no longer my match.
I've never wanted to become your match.
I just wanted to try my best...
to help you with everything within my power.
You constantly remind me about revenge.
But she... has always given me light.
Where am I?
Why am I here?
Why are you laughing?
I'm just laughing at my own foolishness.
I've always wanted to protect you.
I never thought that you would be malicious towards me.
Chen Yu,
what do you want from me?
I won't hurt you.
My goal is just "The Book of Mountains and Rivers."
So, you are here for the book as well.
Looks like you are not the real descendant of Qin.
You are indeed very smart. A hint is all you need.
I'm not Chen Yu.
And I'm not a descendant of Qin.
My only purpose in Northern Lin...
is to get my hand on this almighty, remarkable book.
And here I am, seeing you as my friend...
and trying my best to protect you.
It looks like you don't need it at all.
You used your hand in exchange for my life.
You gave me the zither music score...
and gave me refuge in Moon Embrace Teahouse.
The sincerity that you had shown me is something so rare.
Actually, I've already considered you as my close friend.
But this book is with Prince Li now.
It's too hard to get it from him.
I don't have any other choices.
This is the only way.
The only way.
Who are you working for?
You are neither a person from Northern Lin...
nor a person from Western Qi.
Stop asking me. I won't tell you.
You have no choice because you are under someone's thumb.
Tell me. Maybe I can be of help.
Look at yourself. How can you help me?
You are stuck in this situation today because of that book, too. Right?
Although our identities are different, our fate is very similar.
Both of us are here for "The Book of Mountains and Rivers."
But I'm doing it on my own free will...
while you were forced to do it. And you were betrayed by others.
All pawns will be sacrificed sooner or later.
You are no exception.
Maybe you are right.
Now, no matter if it is to be...
controlled by others in the name of a mission...
or to live our lives freely,
we have no say in it.
At least I'll fight for my right to choose.
I won't be a string puppet forever.
I'll remember... what you have said today.
I've already informed Prince Li.
As long as he is willing to give me the book,
I'll release you at once.
You've calculated wrongly. He won't come.
The onlooker sees most of the game.
You are too blind to it because you are a part of it...
but I see it very clearly.
Although Fu Chou is very gentle and attentive to you, he bears a deep grudge.
He might not derail his plan for you.
Prince Li on the other hand... is very cold towards you,
but he's a sentimental and righteous man.
He won't even hesitate to sacrifice himself for you.
Let alone "The Book of Mountains and Rivers."
What if he doesn't come?
He will.
Ever since he came back to Zhongshan, he has saved you repeatedly.
He still loves you. Even the blind can see it.
And you still love him, too.
But you are not willing to admit it.
That's right.
All of you can see it very clearly.
That's why all of you have a reason to use me.
And you said that you have no other choices.
Fine.
You have your own standing.
I understand.
I was once like you.
But, Chen Yu,
no matter what your reasoning is, you've used me.
And it's a fact that you've betrayed me.
We can't be friends anymore.
The nation's affairs are not a child's play.
Where did Wuyou go?
Father, I...
Do you want to be sent to the royal tomb?
Please calm down.
A report from the southern region came.
It's an emergency about an outbreak of rebellion in Qingzhou.
Wuyou had gone back to take care of it.
This is bad. Come back quickly, Wuyou.
I can't cover up for you much longer.
What did you say?
- I...
- Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, Prince Fanyang has requested to meet you.
- Let him in.
- Yes, Your Majesty.
You may leave first.
Yes, Father.
Uncle.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Be at ease.
Xuanming, you'll be in charge of the war against Wei.
Yes, Your Majesty.
But Wuyou is respected for his brilliance in leading an army.
He's way better in the art of war than me.
Wuyou is indeed bold and talented.
But he has always opposed to the war against Wei.
He won't agree to go into war with me.
I plan to bring along Fu Chou with me.
And I'll leave the crown prince behind to take care of the country.
You want to bring General Fu away and leave behind the crown prince.
Are you trying to separate the two?
Although Fu Chou looks very gentle, respectful, and cautious,
he is a cunning person.
He's like a tiger or wolf.
He used the banquet as an excuse...
to give a girl to the crown prince.
He must have wanted to use the crown prince's status to his benefit.
So, it's better to keep him by my side.
If he so much as blinks wrongly,
I can punish him at once.
You are indeed thorough and far-sighted.
You have my admiration.
Prince Li, long time no see.
How are you?
The thing that you want is here.
Release her.
Why are you here?
There is no need to care about me.
Instead of using my life as leverage to harm another innocent,
I'd rather you just kill me.
I told you before. I can see clearly the feelings you have for each other.
Prince Li, do you know that...
Man Yao wasn't married to General Fu willingly?
She did it because the Emperor of Qi threatened her...
with the lives of everyone.
You are the only one she has ever loved.
Stop the nonsense!
Is it nonsense?
You clearly haven't forgotten about him.
You'll be depressed whenever you think of him.
She says all of these because she wants you to give the book to her quickly.
That's right. I'm here for "The Book of Mountains and Rivers,"
but what I said is true.
While you were away from Zhongshan, she often went to the teahouse alone...
to spend most of her time there.
She'd sit at the place where both of you first played chess together.
And she'd look at the plants in the garden...
while reminiscing the time you had together.
Sometimes, she'd be brought to tears.
Man Yao, is she telling the truth?
Chen Yu, you were indeed my best friend.
I'll kill her if you take one more step forward!
She saved your life before. Is this how you'll repay her?
Who sent you?
What's your purpose here besides "The Book of Mountains and Rivers?"
- Cut the nonsense.
- Stop it!
If you want to save her life, hand me the book.
Or else, I'll jump off from here together with her.
I'll be dead anyway if I fail my mission. I'd rather die with her.
- At least I'll have a companion.
- All right!
- I'll give it to you.
- No!
I'm the one who found the book. You have no right to give it to her.
You want to die, right? If you're not afraid, why should I be?
Man Yao!
Do you know how much effort I put into getting this book?
Because of this book, I had used you.
And because of this book, you had tricked me.
But you can't let this book...
fall to the wrong hands just because of me.
Are you done yet?
You don't believe what I said just now, right? I'll prove it to you now.
Miss,
although you no longer treat me as your friend, I still want to give you a word of advice.
Flee to a faraway place with him.
Because in this world, nobody else will treat you better than he does.
Farewell.
Can you come up by yourself?
Was she telling the truth just now?
This is not the time for you to think about it! Your life is at risk here!
- Don't let go of your hand!
- Is it true?
Yes! I think of you every day and I can't forget about you! Satisfied?
♫ I don't want distance but I stayed away from you ♫
♫ I want to do it but I can't ♫
♫ I just want to watch you in this cold world ♫
Everybody sees very clearly the feelings we have for each other.
But we ourselves are too afraid to be sure of it.
Man Yao, I've always been confident and arrogant.
But when it comes to you,
I'm afraid that it's just an unrequited love.
I'm sorry.
I've made you suffer.
Aren't I the one who had got you into trouble?
Their target is me.
You were dragged into it...
because I've fallen in love with you.
It's my fault for putting you in constant danger.
Man Yao, remember this.
It's my choice to like you.
And it's my decision to hand over the book.
You did nothing wrong.
Chen Yu is right.
You should flee to a faraway place with me.
Leave Fu Chou.
I can only protect you well when you are by my side.
I'll make sure that no one will harm you and use you ever again.
I can give you an unrestrained life.
I can give you the freedom you crave.
Unrestrained life.
Freedom.
The southern border has spring all year round.
It's brimming with flowers.
You'll like it there.
But I...
Do you know...
how happy I was when I saw this chess piece?
You've kept it by your side all this while.
It's proof that you've never forgotten about me.
Finally, we are together again.
Man Yao,
as long as you are willing to come with me,
nothing in this world will be a problem for me.
Are you willing to come with me?
I'm willing.
But...
But I made a promise to Fu Chou.
We have a one-year marriage contract.
I don't want to break my promise. I owe him an explanation.
Don't worry.
I'll wait at the hunting ground for you at 8:00 tomorrow morning.
If you are not there,
I'll settle this personally with Fu Chou.
Are you all right, Rong Le?
You are hurt.
It looks like you know what happened to me.
This is not my doing.
I know.
When I heard that you were gone, I had searched for you everywhere.
I wanted to save you, but I never thought that...
someone would beat me to it.
You should know that...
no matter how many people there are to stop me,
I won't leave you alone to fend for yourself.
I believe you.
But now, there's no point for you to tell me that anymore.
I know.
Chen Yu is the perpetrator.
I will send someone to kill her.
This is between me and Chen Yu. Don't stick your hands into it.
You are Chen Yu's savior. Not only did she not repay your kindness,
she had tricked and hurt you. People like her...
are not worthy for you to plead on her behalf.
Chen Yu had indeed hurt and tricked me.
But now, she's not the only one who had tricked and used me.
If you want her dead just because she did this,
it would be more dangerous for you.
In your heart,
I'm the same as Chen Yu?
No, it's not the same.
At least, you've treated Chen Yu sincerely...
while you've treated me coldly and you're always on your guard.
Forget it. Since you are back, get some rest.
Fu Chou, I don't want you and I to turn out like me and Chen Yu.
How about we stop it here?
Such a cruel thing for you to say.
You want to leave me for him, right?
During our wedding night, I already saw your handwritten divorce paper.
You hid it in the wedding suit so, that one day,
I could choose the answer that you want from the two choices you gave me.
You've never cared about the two choices that I gave you.
Because in your heart,
you already have the answer, right?
You had given me your true love before.
And I'm thankful for it.
But so much had happened. There's no turning back for us anymore.
How can you act as if nothing had happened?
I don't care if you think that I'm insensible,
that I behave capriciously, or even think that...
I'm a villain who goes back on my word.
From now on,
I won't allow you to leave me again.
When I searched for you everywhere like a lunatic, I swore to myself.
Our fate is still not over as long as our promise is still valid.
From now on, I won't let you leave me.
Chang Jian.
General Fu.
Zhongshan has been quite chaotic recently.
Take good care of Lady Rong Le.
If she takes a step outside of this manor...
or if she has another wound on her,
I'll have your head.
Yes, General Fu.
- Lady Rong Le.
- Fu Chou!
I've already sent someone to bring Ling Yue and Xiao Ke here.
If you dare leave this manor without permission,
I can't guarantee their safety.
Princess Rong Le.
Xiao Sha, have you found a way to get out?
Just now, General Fu has given his order to tighten security.
I've checked. Only Tranquil Garden and the front yard are heavily guarded.
Not so much for the rest of the place.
Maybe at night, when they change their shift,
we might be able to find an opening.
All right.
At first, I wanted to end this on good terms.
He's the one who has forced me to do this.
No matter what, we have to get to the hunting ground at 8:00 tomorrow.
Yes, Miss.
Prince Li.
Where is Man Yao? Did something happen to her?
As soon as she went back to the manor yesterday, she was grounded.
She has asked me to tell you that we'll have to plan this out first.
[General's Manor]
Who dares barge into the General's Manor?
Prince Li.
General Fu.
[A Calm Foundation, A Quiet Residence]
I thought that you'd rein yourself in after...
your introspection at the southern border.
I never thought that you'd still act with such arrogance.
This is the third time you've barged into my manor.
Looks like you don't have any respect for this General of Defense.
Cut the nonsense. Give me Man Yao.
I don't have a Miss Man Yao here.
Rong Le is the Elder Princess of Western Qi.
She is the legal wife of the General of Defense.
If you want to see her, I'll have to say sorry.
She is not feeling well today.
She's not fit for a visitor.
Princess! Princess!
Princess.
Prince Li is here.
Didn't I tell you to pass on my message to him?
I've failed my duty. Prince Li is confronting General Fu in the front yard now.
Don't think of using the imperial order to threaten me.
You know I have no care for it.
Fu Chou, you talked about imperial order and status repeatedly.
Is there anything else between both of you besides that?
What a foolish question it is.
We have the mutual affection of husband and wife,
the time we spent together for half a year...
and more than 200 nights of sleeping together between us.
Not to mention that these are false,
but even if they are true, so what?
Do you think I'm like the others...
who will give up just because of that?
Fu Chou, you are a somebody.
It doesn't matter that you lie to me with those.
But isn't it ridiculous that you're trying to kid yourself?
You've had her once and then you lost her.
You did all of those by yourself.
Now, she's been married to me for months.
And you want to take her back now?
Who is being more ridiculous?
Looks like you are set on keeping her to yourself.
Don't blame me for being rude then.
I've always been courteous towards you.
But you've become even rude to me.
You barged into my manor several times and treated me as a nobody.
I can tolerate it, but...
I'm already at my limit.
This is the real Fu Chou.
Today, let us fight like real men.
I'm curious to see how capable you are as well.
- Princess Rong Le.
What's wrong, Princess?
Did the poison in her body attack her again?
Tell me.
You've been without a cure for too long.
Without the cure to suppress it,
the poison has eaten through your organs and has gone into your blood.
If it attacks again, you'll faint if it's mild.
And you'll die... if it's serious.
How much time...
do I have?
Maximum half a year and minimum three months.
Aren't there any other ways to neutralize the poison?
This is a complex poison.
Without a prescription, it's hard for me to create the cure.
But I'll try my best to find a way to neutralize the poison.
Worst comes to worst...
♫ There was once happiness as grand
as three thousand rivers and mountains ♫
♫ Although we haven't known each other for long,
I already miss you so ♫
♫ Do you dare to...? ♫
I'm set on standing against fate.
But why do I have...
no control over my life?
- I'll get the cure form His Majesty.
- Xiao Sha!
Princess.
I don't want to beg him.
And don't tell anybody...
about this either.
♫ After all of those hardships, we are no longer young ♫
♫ I'm doomed to live in loneliness forever ♫
♫ It's bad but I can't help it ♫
♫ Are you suffering just like me? Are you in turmoil as well? ♫
♫ After all the boom and bust, I have lost all hope ♫
- Princess.
- Princess Rong Le.
Princess.
Man Yao, why?
Do you know how dangerous it is?
You can't hurt him.
He is my husband.
He set you up for marriage, he used you,
put you in constant danger and now, he imprisoned you and took away your freedom.
Do you still see him as your husband?
This is between me and him.
It's best if you stay out of it.
You barged into my manor today with an army...
and you almost hurt my wife.
I don't think it'll do you any good if His Majesty knows about it.
Since I dare come here, I won't be afraid of that.
Man Yao.
Did something happen?
It's nothing.
Are you still going to leave with me?
No.
Fu Chou, what did you do to her?
He didn't do anything to me.
I'm the one who is not willing to leave this manor.
Although he had made some mistakes, he is sincere towards me.
I'm not willing to betray him.
Do you think I'll believe you?
Man Yao, I know clearly...
what kind of a person you are and what kind of a life you want.
It's fine if you are not willing... to leave with me.
But I want to hear the truth.
I don't want to ruin my reputation...
and I'm not willing to give up my identity as the princess.
Because I think that...
you are not worth it.
Prince Li, please leave.
I don't want to see you again.
I'm not worth it.
Man Yao, if you really mean it...
Of course, I mean it.
I'm at fault for today's incident.
It's my fault for not making things clear between us before this.
I've troubled you to come here for nothing.
If His Majesty wants to blame someone,
I'll take full responsibility for it.
No need.
I've always borne the consequences of my own actions.
No need to trouble yourself, Lady Rong Le.
That's right. I'm the wife of General Fu.
Please keep it firmly in mind.
From now on, if someone else threatens my life,
please remember to mind your own business.
My husband will save me.
Mind my own business.
I'll make sure to keep it in mind.
Why did you say that?
Are you telling the truth or are you lying?
I lied.
Everything that you did... is indeed for the good of Zongzheng Wuyou.
You are worried that I'll gather up the officials and generals...
to exert pressure on His Majesty together with the crown prince.
Of course, you can take full responsibility for it.
And for His Majesty, he'll be glad to punish you alone...
given that I'm not hurt.
You know clearly that his attack won't kill me.
He'll only hurt me.
Of course, you don't care about whether I'll be hurt or not.
The only thing that you care about is,
if I'm hurt, others will say that Zongzheng Wuyou has no regard for the law,
that he barged into the manor fully armed to take you by force.
And I almost lost my life while protecting my wife.
If this spreads amongst the soldiers,
someone would be indignant with unfair treatment.
And by that time,
His Majesty wouldn't be able to protect him...
in case there was a mutiny amongst the troops.
Although you've thought ahead for him,
have you ever thought that what if he didn't manage to stop his attack?
It's very possible that you'd die by his hand.
He won't do it.
You are right about everything but one.
It's very possible that he knows about your sinister intentions.
If he wants to kill you, he won't bring along normal guards but The Hidden Ones instead.
You didn't give your best and neither did he.
Or else, how could he stop his attack so quickly?
He came to find me today...
just to make sure that... I was fine.
If that's the case, why didn't you leave with him?
It's possible that... he'll be able to give you the happiness and freedom...
that you crave.
Freedom.
What freedom?
My life is in others' hands.
My craving is just wishful thinking.
I'm just a heavy burden.
What did you say?
Fu Chou, don't put your hopes in me.
I can't give you... what you want.
[A Propitious Sky is Favorable for the Land]
You are back, Wuyou.
Where did you go, Wuyou?
What happened, Wuyou?
What's wrong with Wuyou?
What happened? Why is he so angry?
It's Man Yao again, right?
- Let me confront her.
- It's better if you don't.
- Why not?
- You still don't get it after so long?
She is the one Prince Li loves. No matter what she does,
nobody can touch her without Prince Li's permission.
What should we do then?
Are we going to sit here and watch while he dwells in depression?
Your Highness, Eunuch Chen is here.
Your Highness, His Majesty has summoned Prince Li to the palace.
All right.
Wuyou! Eunuch Chen is here.
Father must have had something for you. Today, I...
Leng Yan, ask Agent Wu to investigate these people in secret.
- Yes, Your Highness.
- Let's go.
Wuyou!
These are the names of the generals in the army.
Looks like Wuyou has found a way to take down with Fu Chou.
Wei has always been a festering wound for me.
All these years, we've been in a constant war with them.
Many have sacrificed themselves for us.
A few years ago, we had the chance to defeat them once and for all.
But we were defeated because of the crown prince's mistake.
Once this war starts,
it'll take a huge toll on both of the countries' armed forces.
For the past years, both countries had been making preparations for this war.
We trained up soldiers and gathered food.
A few days ago, our scout from the frontier pass had reported that Wei...
is gathering up their troops and is readying themselves for war.
So, this war between us is inevitable.
In order to have the upper hand,
I've decided to attack them first.
And this time, I'll lead the troops myself.
♫ The snow falls on my palm ♫
♫ I just want to gaze at you one more time ♫
♫ I wait for the warmth of your gaze to melt it ♫
♫ We are fated to get hurt from the moment we met each other ♫
♫ I miss you but I can only gaze at you in silence ♫
♫ You are keeping me out with your care
Although we are together, I feel lost ♫
♫ I can wait for you until my hair turns white ♫
♫ I can endure all the loneliness just for you ♫
♫ I will be your hearth in the coldest of places ♫
♫ For you, I am willing to suffer ♫
♫ I want to ward off the coldness for you ♫
♫ As long as I can be with you, I'm willing to give you all of me ♫
♫ In a blink of an eye, my hair has turned silver ♫
♫ I'm fated to live in loneliness without any regrets ♫
♫ The winter may be cold,
but I will watch from afar and keep you warm ♫
♫ I'm willing to wipe away your blood and wounds for you ♫
♫ I'm willing to live in darkness for you ♫
♫ As long as I can be with you, I don't mind... hiding in the dark ♫