[Princess Silver]
[Episode 9]
I really want to know what's so good about this.
Is it good because you are protecting each other,
is it because you got rid of a dissident,
or is it because you can treat human lives as nothing?
That's not true, Your Highness.
If you are worried about the matters regarding Prince Chen...
Today is my birthday.
How about I use my luck today to ask the crown prince...
to beg for Prince Chen's pardon from His Majesty?
No need.
Anybody who did wrong has to be punished.
No matter it's him or anybody else.
You mentioned luck.
Today, it's your birthday.
But I would like to take something from you.
What is it that you wish to take from me?
- Father!
- Please think again, Your Highness.
- You can't do that, Your Highness.
- Your Highness!
I want to take your head. How about that?
Wuyou, you threaten an officer's life in public.
Are you trying to revolt?
Let's see who the one trying to revolt is here.
Sir Yu, looks like you haven't taken a look...
at the content of the ten art of war books that I had given you.
How is it, General Fu? Do you understand now?
Do you think we can still settle this in peace?
I can't be sure of the authenticity of this name list.
It doesn't if you are not sure.
I believe that Sir Yu is very clear about it.
The ten scrolls on the floor contain the names of all those who are involved in this rank-selling case.
Sir Yu might be able to kill Li Zhiyuan.
But you won't be able to kill those thousands of witnesses whose names were recorded by him, right?
Sir Yu, is Prince Li telling the truth?
Crown Prince, this is slander.
Prince Li, you can't prove us guilty with your words alone.
What are you trying to do?
Father, we can't just let go of the foundation that...
our family has built for generations today.
His Highness dares to accuse us in public...
and point his sword at you. So, there is no need to be courteous to him.
Yu Wenjie, you are just struggling for nothing.
I know that you are very courageous.
Even if you don't care about your own safety...
or the safety of Prince Chen who is in jail,
you only care about the safety of that mistress from the teahouse. Right?
Please think carefully.
If you can let go of me today, we can start anew.
And we will let go of your woman.
Sir Yu, nobody dares to threaten me.
And nobody can threaten me.
Prince Li, you really don't care for that woman's life?
Guards, bring that woman over.
You dare touch her?
Wenjie.
Prince Li, you are the one who forces my hand.
This matter involves the many lives and honor of the Yu family for three generations.
I won't let you leave this place easily.
Guards! Close the door!
Don't you dare!
[The Crane Cries at the Nine Springs]
A decree from His Majesty.
As decreed from His Majesty,
it's unforgivable that the father-son duo of Yu...
is involved in rank-selling and has duped His Majesty.
They will be stripped of their ranks, their properties confiscated...
and will be sent to Supreme Court for trial.
The manor of Yu will be taken back and Prince Li will be in charge of it. Signed, His Majesty.
So, you came prepared.
Scoundrel, it's time to admit to your crime.
Yu Shihai, you are always smart as a rule, but this time a fool.
Do you think that... you'll be able to threaten me?
You sell ranks for your own profits and kill the innocent. Such grave crimes.
Today, I won't let go of anyone within the three generations of your family.
Guards! Arrest all of them!
Roger that!
Your Highness, let me send you back to the palace.
Farewell.
Let's go.
- Your Highness.
- Leng Yan.
Find someone to clean up this place...
and seal the door.
Nobody can enter this manor without my permission.
Yes, Your Highness.
You are really good, Wuyou.
You managed to solve this case in seven days' time.
I would like to thank you on behalf of those who had died unjustly.
Go back to your manor and pack your clothes. Stay at my place tonight.
What? Stay at your place? Why?
Someone is coming in tomorrow. I have some work for you.
Wuyou! I just got out of jail.
I still have wounds all over my body.
Let me rest for two more days.
You've been resting in jail for seven days with good food and good sleep.
You still want to rest?
So, the treatment that I got in jail...
I knew that you treated me best.
I'm in jail. Of course, you'll send someone to take care of me, right?
All right. I'll go and pack now and move over to your place.
[Life]
Father, there's always a way out.
It's still not over for us, right?
- Crown prince—
- Shut up.
Beware of eavesdroppers.
If you had known it would come to this, you wouldn't have acted thus.
Who asked you to act on your own?
Now, we have totally offended Prince Li.
Zongzheng Wuyou is evil. He is treacherous and ruthless.
Usually, he looks like he paid no attention to public affairs.
He must have done a lot of evil things behind our back.
And that low-life Li Zhiyuan.
How dare he haunt us even in death.
Everything is in the past now.
I've decided to offer all of my properties...
for His Majesty to prepare for war against Wei...
in order to beg for our lives.
Father, our house is already confiscated.
If you donate all of that, what are we going to do when we get out?
Our lives are already on the line now.
How can you still care about that money?
Now, we need to raise our guard against the crown prince.
Crown Prince? He's on our side.
- He won't leave us to die.
- Idiot.
Now, for the crown prince,
we are a liability just like Li Zhiyuan.
Then we are totally done for.
Not necessarily.
I have already prepared for this.
All these years, I have a detailed record of all the money
that was sent to the crown prince palace.
And I have another copy just in case anything happens.
As long as the crown prince visits us,
I'll have a way to make him keep us alive.
What did the crown prince say?
His Highness said that no matter how they interrogate you, admit to nothing.
Sit back and observe. When the time comes,
His Highness will send someone to save you.
How dare he, Yu Shihai. I had trusted him.
How dare he betray me and do something so hurtful to the nation.
He deserves to die.
And you. First, you lost in the war against Wei.
Now, you sell ranks to earn money? What did you do?
Father, I'm innocent.
Although I'm quite close with Sir Yu,
I have never been to the Ministry of Personnel.
And I have never seen this name list before.
Your Majesty, Prince Li has entrusted me with all the evidence
that are related to this case.
The account book has shown that it's indeed the work of the Ministry of Personnel.
But when Sir Zhao was still alive,
the letter that he passed on to Prince Chen...
accused His Highness directly.
Father, that letter was used by Prince Chen to slander me.
Please render me a fair judgment, Father.
Your Highness, why are you so anxious to defend yourself?
When we get the statement from the father and son of the Yu family,
everything will be clear then.
Minister Sun, you are still ill.
And yet you have to deal with the aftermath of Yu Shihai.
If everybody in the court were like you,
I wouldn't have so much on my plate.
Your Majesty, I'm no longer young.
I don't have any sons.
So, it's only right for me to serve the country until the very end.
If I had a son,
I would have gone back to my hometown...
to enjoy the rest of my life.
Your Majesty, Yu Shihai and his son have committed suicide in jail.
What?
I already ordered the guards to keep a close eye on them.
How did they still manage to commit suicide?
Prince Fan Yang. Investigate this case together with the Supreme Court.
Don't let any of their affiliates get away.
Yu Shihai and his son are proven guilty of selling ranks and titles.
They have committed grave crimes by breaking the imperial rules.
Cut off their heads and display them as a deterrent for the public.
The three generations of Yu, including their relatives and servants...
will be sent to the border as soldiers.
Brilliant decision, Father.
We need to be swift to get rid of traitors like them.
The crown prince has befriended the traitors and has bad conduct.
He is to be confined to the Eastern Palace until further orders.
Yes, Father. Thank you for your forgiveness.
Prince Fan Yang, go to Prince Li's manor to pass on my decree.
Reward him for contributing to this case.
His three states in the southern fringe will be tax-free for five years.
From now on, all the matters regarding those states...
no need to be reported to the court. Just report to Prince Li's manor.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Your Highness! Your Highness.
We have already taken care of the father-son duo as you asked.
Did you find it?
We found this account book in another courtyard of the Yu family.
It contains all of the records written by Yu Shihai himself.
I have no choice but to sacrifice him to protect myself.
I'm sure that he'll understand.
Creed of Vengeance leaves no trace. You can be rest-assured.
We won't leave a trail.
Don't worry. You have done me a great favor.
I will reward you handsomely.
The Creed of Vengeance doesn't need any rewards.
We just hope that you can support us when you become the emperor.
Creed of Vengeance will be at your service.
But now, you have lost a right-hand man.
Do you have any other more useful supports...
to help you defeat Prince Li and secure the throne?
[Lush Greenery and Good Harvest]
[Pavilion of Enjoyment]
Wuyou, I can't do it anymore.
I can't.
Yu Shihai has made this manor into such a luxurious place...
with so many contraptions.
He deserves to die indeed.
Such excellent workmanship.
Wuyou, where did you find this expert?
He's acting so out of the world and so crazily every day. Is he dependable?
Master Xin, you have already searched for two days. Any clues?
It must be here somewhere. Qin Yong is very smart.
He must have hidden it in an open place.
The entrance to the secret room must be located at the most unexpected place.
Old Man Xin, I had already searched this place inside out for two days with you.
We even checked every crack in the wall.
Besides Yu Shihai's secret weapon and illegal punishment room, we found nothing.
We didn't even find a trace of that secret room that you talked of.
Master Xin, how long will it take?
I can't be sure.
Wuyou, no need to trouble yourself so much.
We can just tear the whole place down, right?
Nonsense.
For a secret room that is built by Qin Yong,
if you could find it by tearing the house down, it wouldn't be a secret room.
Let me tell you. If you tear down the house, the secret room will be destroyed.
And you'll get nothing.
How dare you talk like that to me. I can punish you for this disrespect.
Wuyu.
Wuyou, let this old man find the house alone.
We didn't rest for two days already.
Look at him. He's still very energetic.
I'm already exhausted. I can't do it anymore, Wuyou.
Let me clean it up myself. I wouldn't dare trouble you.
I'm the one who knocked into you. It's my fault.
I wouldn't dare to blame you.
Are you blaming me for the matters regarding Lian Xin?
I wouldn't dare blame you.
What if you suspect me again?
I investigated Lian Xin because I noticed that she brought ill will towards the princess.
You didn't betray the princess. Why would I investigate you?
Your hand is bleeding. Let me take a look.
Let me take a look.
Why are you crying?
If someone sees you like this, they'll think that I had bullied you.
Stop crying.
Is a cut to the hand so painful?
Yes, it is!
All right. I'll cut myself too so that I can feel what you feel.
What are you doing? Don't you know that finger cuts are extremely painful?
Idiot.
When I came here during the party last time,
I had the geography here memorized.
But this place is heavily guarded. We have to be careful.
- Aren't you an expert in contraptions?
- Enough.
It has been so many days and we can't even find the secret room.
- Let alone the book.
- Stop being so noisy.
It won't be so easy to find the secret room designed by Qin Yong.
I never thought that they'd be searching for the book too.
But looks like they are not very successful in it.
Qin Yong is indeed the wisest man on earth.
The contraptions that he designed are indeed extraordinary.
It means that we still have a chance.
Who is it?
Your Highness, what happened?
- Give chase now!
- Yes, Your Highness!
Your Highness, if you want to give chase in that direction,
you can just forget it.
Because the contraptions will get them.
No need to be so anxious.
Really?
Princess, find a chance to escape.
I'll take care of them.
Don't be so nervous.
Follow me.
Princess, how did you know this place so well?
Right, left, left, right, right.
Follow my steps. Don't take a wrong step.
- Long Yue.
- I'm fine, Princess.
Let's leave this place first.
[Moon Embrace Teahouse]
- Mistress.
- Take a seat now.
Let me take a look.
I'm fine.
Thank you, Princess.
You're welcome.
If it wasn't for you who had protected me from harm last night,
I would have been the one with injuries today.
We had gone through so many dangers together.
We can be considered as sworn friends already.
It's my duty to protect you, Princess.
This Yu family's fort is indeed full of contraptions.
And it's heavily guarded.
But after yesterday's incident,
it'll be hard for us to sneak inside again.
I had been to the manor twice.
I keep on feeling a sense of familiarity with that place.
Yesterday, I woke up suddenly.
The structures of those doors and walls...
are designed based on the Eight Trigrams.
The grass, woods, flowers, and stones are the variables.
Princess, I have always felt puzzled about one thing.
With Prince Li's affection towards you,
you can totally request him...
to let you tour the whole manor with him.
Why do you have to sneak in like that?
You know that... I have lost my memories.
I treat everyone in this world as strangers.
Those who treat me well,
I'll consider them as my friends and family.
Those who treat me badly,
I'll consider them as my enemies.
But after that, I realized that...
the hearts and feelings of the people in this world are not black and white.
I came here for my brother and for Western Qi.
I think I did the right thing.
But I'll often dream and wake myself up.
I feel that one day, they'll forget about me.
And they'll leave me here alone.
I sent Lian Xin away.
I feel that I had given her the best option.
But sometimes, I will feel angry.
Why did she betray me?
I need to find the book.
So, I have to get close.
But I vaguely feel that...
if I can't treat him with honesty,
then I shouldn't get too close to him.
So, this is the reason you avoid Prince Li so often.
Long Yue, if you truly like a person,
are you supposed to ask for nothing in return...
and you'll be satisfied as long as everything goes well for him?
In this world, everybody treats feelings differently.
Some, give their all.
And some, use it for their own advantages.
You have to ask yourself...
whether or not you wish for something in return.
Thank you.
I feel much better now.
Mistress, a customer has insisted to meet you.
Is that him?
Go on.
You are so beautiful.
I have fallen in love with you.
I have many lands and many servants.
Why don't you come back with me?
Why are you laughing?
If you go back with me,
you'll be able to enjoy untold wealth and glory.
It's better than depending on others for a living...
and live in humiliation, right?
I thank you for your offer.
But too bad that...
I have a broad outlook on life.
It's better for you to come back after a few years when you have grown up.
Don't look down on me.
People like you only care about fame and gain, right?
The things that you offered, I can easily get them myself.
I rather have a man who is young and handsome.
I have fallen in love with you too, Princess Zhao Yun.
You...
You have seen through me?
It doesn't matter.
Wench. Let me tell you.
I'm here to test you.
Stay away from Brother Wuyou.
He is already engaged.
Princess of Western Qi is noble, elegant, beautiful, and wise.
She is way better than you.
I'm trying hard to avoid Prince Li.
But he's the one who always kept me by his side.
If you could spend more time with your Brother Wuyou,
then he wouldn't have time to look for me.
You...
You are such a bully!
Have you found out who the people that sneaked in that day are?
That day, I was too far away.
So, I didn't have a clear look.
But from their shapes, I think they were both female.
Your Highness.
They might be the female assassins from Creed of Vengeance.
Creed of Vengeance?
I have found out that those who tried to assassinate you in the teahouse came from the Creed of Vengeance.
Creed of Vengeance is a gang that has become popular in recent years.
Their business focuses on stealing secrets and assassinations.
But it's very pricey to hire them.
The assassination of Sir Zhao and the other officers...
together with the death of Yu Shihai and his son...
are their doings.
How dare they do that.
A gang dares to meddle with the public affairs of the nation?
Only the Eastern Palace is able to pay such a high price...
and commit such grave crimes.
I already sent someone to pursue and capture them.
I never thought that they'll still dare to send someone forward.
I don't blame you.
No matter if it's Sir Zhao or Li Zhi Yuan,
they are always there right on the dot.
They leave of trace and they are as silent as the wind.
Looks like they have already infiltrated themselves into the court.
That's why they can be so precise.
Wuyou, let me investigate this together with Leng Yan.
We can't let them escape this time.
The crown prince is getting more and more rampant.
If he really becomes the emperor one day,
there will be no peace in this world.
Wuyou, you asked us to search for "The Book of Mountains and Rivers."
It means that you still remember Lady Yun and Minister Qin's behest.
How about we use this chance...
- to pull down the crown prince?
- Wuyu.
I have my own plans.
This is not something that should be spoken aloud.
Yes, Wuyou.
Master Xin, did you find anything?
I found this just now when I searched the manor.
This is weird.
Why would they have a Western Qi tool in this manor?
- Western Qi?
That's right.
Although this climbing hook is not something rare,
the way it was tied is very special.
You know that the weather is very rough in Western Qi, right?
It's very windy and sandy over there.
So, in order to prevent the rope from tearing,
they will use a complicated way to tie their hook.
And every once in a while, they'll retie it again...
to make sure that it's sturdy.
So, the people who sneaked into the manor that day...
are people from Western Qi.
Your Highness, there is a lady outside asking for you.
She said that she is the mistress of Moon Embrace Teahouse.
Have a drink, Your Highness.
This is indeed a good tea.
You love tea.
So when I got this new tea, I thought of you immediately.
That's why I brought it to you.
People who love tea will know what's best to be eaten with the tea.
This box of red dates has a subtle sweetness to them.
It's best to be eaten with the tea.
Have a taste.
Thank you, Your Highness.
How is it?
The fragrance of dates with the fragrance of tea. Sweet with a bite.
They are an excellent match.
If you like it,
I'll ask them to give one to you, only you.
Looks like you really like this place.
Maybe it's the grass or the trees.
I have a sense of familiarity with this place.
This manor is occupied by Yu Shihai and his son for so long.
It's such a waste.
No wonder Leng Yan said that you were caught by Yu Wenjie...
the last time because you were wandering around.
I'm sorry that I had troubled you.
I planned to bring you here for a tour...
after everything was settled at first.
I never thought that you'd lose your patience come by yourself.
You don't welcome me?
If you like it, I can show you around.
But... it's better if you don't wander alone.
There are many contraptions here.
If you trigger them accidentally, you might get hurt.
With you here, I can't possibly wander around myself.
Please show the way.
Before this, I heard that this fort was very deep...
and the buildings were very complicated.
Today, it looks like... if this place was without those contraptions,
it would be a gorgeous and breathtaking place.
When I gave you Man Yin Chamber, it didn't seem like you enjoyed it.
But you are so interested in this manor.
The threshold of your manor is very high.
Everything in the manor belongs to you.
Others can't touch it without permission.
You gave me a chamber without any reasons.
How could I accept it?
No matter how high the threshold is, it's not set for you.
As long as you are willing, I can give the whole manor to you.
How about that?
If other people were to hear this, they'd misunderstand.
You are a noble.
It's already bad enough that you're associated with me.
We have known each other for so long.
Have I ever cared about your name, background, status, or rank?
At first, I thought that you didn't care for all of these as well.
Nobody can truly be oblivious about them.
No matter what you think,
it'll still be impossible for us.
Then, why did you come to me?
Is it really because of the scenery in this manor?
Or do you have other intentions?
What are you doing?
Don't you think that this is a very familiar scene?
I don't understand what you mean.
If you don't like me here,
then I just won't come again.
Nothing is definite in this world.
A status or a standing... is a matter of personal choice.
The things that are important to you today...
might become a thorn in your heart in another day.
The things that you deemed impossible...
might become possible in the near future.
When my teacher, Qin Yong, built this place in the beginning,
he never thought that his people-based transformation would fail.
When Yu Shihai transformed this manor with glee,
he never thought that the Yu family would one day be destroyed.
Man Yao, things are always changing.
A little fire can burn this manor into nothingness.
People are forgetful.
No matter how glorious a family is for generations,
people can forget about it completely.
Those that need to be forgotten will be forgotten.
So,
if there's something in front of me that I want,
I'll do my best to grasp it in my hands.
Nothing can stop me.
♫ The snow falls on my palm ♫
♫ I just want to gaze at you one more time ♫
♫ I wait for the warmth of your gaze to melt it ♫
Your Highness, it's raining.
♫ I miss you but I can only gaze at you in silence ♫
♫ You are keeping me out with your care ♫
♫ Although we are together, I feel lost ♫
Looks like the sky wants to keep you here.
Even God is helping me.
This place used to be a library built by my teacher.
It was my favorite place.
When I was young, I could stay here for the whole afternoon.
Now that I can stand here again with you today,
it's like the peaceful time from back then...
has come back to me again.
What is it?
Nothing.
♫ In a blink of an eye, my hair has turned silver ♫
♫ I'm fated to live in loneliness without any regrets ♫
That's right. Hug her.
Wuyou is indeed very capable.
♫ I'm willing to wipe away your blood and wounds for you ♫
♫ I'm willing to live in darkness for you ♫
♫ As long as I can be with you ♫
♫ I don't mind... ♫
Your Highness. I should go back.
♫ ...hiding in the dark ♫
Why did she leave? How can you let her leave at a time like this?
Just now, you shouldn't have let her leave.
With my swaggering experiences,
both of you care for each other.
I think you might be able to capture her heart and her kiss very soon.
I can achieve my goal without having to do that.
Wuyou, you have really fallen in love with her, right?
- Look how shy you are.
- Shut up.
If you don't like to hear it, then I won't speak of it.
Stop looking. She has already left.
Yali.
Your mind has been wandering as of late.
I'm very worried about you.
Yali!
Father.
What is it, Father?
You have been stuck in this manor for too long.
You even refused to go out with Prince Li.
I'm sorry that I had made you worry.
But you are not well.
I wish to accompany you to the house.
I didn't mean to blame you.
If you want to be filial to me, go to Chengxi for me tomorrow.
What is it that you need that is so urgent?
♫ I've been secretly missing you for several seasons already ♫
♫ Who was the first to talk about love? ♫
♫ I'm still trying to be nice to myself ♫
♫ Just allow me to get you back to this date ♫
♫ The western wind dyes the flowering season
in thick gray color ♫
♫ And I am still standing here waiting for the rain to come ♫
♫ No matter how good or bad the season turns out ♫
♫ I will still try with my utmost to make a home for us ♫
♫ In just one day, I've tasted the entire human world's warmth ♫
♫ Yet, you are always the one I'm longing for ♫
♫ Even with thousands of feelings, we'll have no regrets ♫
♫ Look at this love, because of you I have a sweet aftertaste ♫
♫ In just one day, I've tasted the entire human world's warmth ♫
♫ Yet, you are always the one I'm longing for ♫
♫ Even with thousands of feelings, we'll have no regrets ♫
♫ Look at this love, because of you I have a sweet aftertaste ♫
♫ Nothing will... go away ♫