[Episode 28]
Miss Yali, if you may.
Your Highness, I'll go and take a look.
Go on.
Father.
Focus when you are playing the lute.
Come, let me show you how.
Man Yao, you never cease to amaze me.
I am still an amateur.
My lack of control broke the cord and caused that awful sound.
I apologize for that.
You may be an amateur,
but the song you played has a vigorous spirit.
Each of you have your own prowess.
Indeed.
The melody of your song was more elegant than what Yali played.
But you still have a lot of training to do.
There were still some mistakes.
Your Majesty, you enjoyed both the tea and the music.
It's about time. We should go now.
Goodbye, Your Majesty and Empress.
General Fu, send the empress back to the palace.
There are some matters... I must discuss with Lady Rong Le in private.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Empress, if you may.
- Move on.
- Yes.
Goodbye, Empress.
Your Majesty, I finally realized...
there are always people with more talents than we do.
I wish to learn from Lady Rong Le.
I will be in Prince Li's manor in a few days.
I was thinking about playing some new songs for him.
Sure, I understand what you are trying to do.
General Fu, let Yali stay for a couple of days.
Let Lady Rong Le share some of her techniques with Yali.
Your wish is my command, Empress.
Your Majesty, you wish to talk to me?
Calm down, I come in peace.
When I met you at Lady Yun's tomb,
I knew that you were not one that would cross the line.
Now that we meet again,
I can tell you are special.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
That melody of yours... carries an intense and strong message,
so strong that it felt like the charging of an army.
It reminds me of the time I spent on the battlefield.
It is reminiscent of my past.
I know. You care for the peace of the world.
Even if your homeland gave up on you,
you never stop defending the pride of its people.
I had always held prejudice against you.
But I finally understand why Wuyou is so madly in love with you.
Your Majesty, you told me to never overstep the line.
Why are you telling me these now?
That is because I remember what happened in the past.
I feel like I should not let Wuyou repeat the same mistake as mine.
I don't want him to live in regret like me.
So, I am asking for your thoughts on his behalf.
I don't know.
Reconsider what I said.
It took me so long to realize.
If you want to live without regret,
you must cherish what you have.
The small gathering with you was very pleasant.
Your Majesty came to visit us in person,
I am greatly honored and grateful.
You are one of the most important officers.
You contributed to the peace of the land.
I granted you this marriage...
as it was supposed to be a reward.
But I never expected it would turn out to be a joke.
You are mocked by many.
I know it must have been hard on you.
Not at all, Your Majesty.
For my emperor and the nation,
this is what I should do.
You are very devoted.
But I cannot be a heartless emperor...
and let you suffer from humiliation.
The marriage alliance with Western Qi is as good as an empty hush.
This is why I have decided to terminate this marriage.
No, Your Majesty.
There is no interest for us to gain from the marriage alliance.
There is no need for it to continue.
Do you have another opinion about this decision?
My marriage with Rong Le was for the sake of our nations.
But after spending months together,
I have grown very fond of Rong Le.
I don't want to leave her.
I hope Your Majesty can withdraw that decision.
What about you?
Why? Do you also grow fond of General Fu?
You don't want to leave him?
Ever since we are married,
General Fu has never mistreated me.
I know I have brought him shame.
I don't deserve to be his wife.
I am willing to accept Your Majesty's decision.
I will accept this dissolution.
Since you understand the gravity of this matter, then so be it.
General Fu, submit your letter of dissolution as soon as possible.
Princess' house is so noisy.
Those people charged right into her house
wearing those weird clothes.
They walked in like they are the bosses around.
That was so rude.
Come again!
Lady, you didn't pay for that!
Pay for what?
You took my food and pretend nothing happened?
It's just some candied berries.
Had you spoken nicely I might have even give it to you.
Now that you stole from me, and you lied!
I am taking you to the officers.
What?
Stop! Everyone, gather around!
Everyone, gather around! Look!
- What is going on?
- Gather around!
Gather around.
This lady over here took the food from my stall.
She refuses to pay and denies knowing anything!
Gather around!
This girl took the food from me and didn't pay!
How should I deal with her now?
She lied about it!
Everyone, be my witness. I am taking her to the officers.
Sir, excuse me. This is my sister.
She has some mental problems.
She sneaked out while we weren't looking.
Would you be so generous and let her go this time?
There you go.
Judging by your outfit, you seem to be from a rich family.
If she is ill, why didn't you take her to a doctor?
And now she took my stuff and caused me trouble.
Fine, I will let it slide this time.
Back to your work!
- You can go now.
- It's okay.
Everything is fine here.
- Get up.
- Don't touch me.
It's you again! How dare you touch me!
Don't use your poison on me.
I just saved your neck.
Then do me a favor.
You are in the capital.
You are not in the mountain anymore.
If you want something or get anything done,
you need money to pay for them.
- Do you get it?
- Are you going to help me?
Okay, what is it?
A bunch of people just came to the princess' house.
They walked right in without a word.
The Moon Embrace Teahouse may be noisy,
but at least no one is trespassing.
Are you seriously asking me to bring Man Yao out of the manor?
You really are a nutcase.
It's the General of Defense's manor.
It's heavily guarded. Who would dare to trespass?
I am telling the truth.
Are you helping me or not?
If you won't, not only will I make you feel the itch,
I will make you feel the pain for days!
Fine, you won.
I am going with you.
Come.
Ling Yue.
- Did you find her?
- No.
- Let's go inside and look.
- Let's go.
Sir Xiao, you know the rules here.
No one can enter or leave the manor.
- But I am...
- Brother!
- Ke'er?
- Ke'er.
Come over here.
Where did you go?
I went to get us help.
Prince Chen, I know you enjoy the company of women,
but please stay away from my sister.
This is none of my business.
You and your sister sure love to wrong the good guys.
I found her on the street.
She insisted that I come with her.
She mentioned there arepeople making noises here.
Please, Your Highness, His Majesty is visiting the manor.
He is still inside.
I was just passing by.
Take it as I was never here.
- Is that clear?
- Yes.
- Ke'er.
- Where are you going?
Brother? Brother?
Brother, I get what you are doing.
In order to protect Man Yao, you went to great efforts.
You sent your men to watch over her house.
Both you and I know that... Fu Chou is planning something ill.
Man Yao will most likely be caught up in it.
But I was so surprised today.
I never thought our father would go in person...
just to make Fu Chou end the marriage.
He is doing it for your own good.
If Man Yao is freed, you can be with her again.
This is great.
But to win her back, it will take true love.
Any means by force... will only push her away from me.
However, leaving General Fu... is still what's best for her.
Yes, we also severed the connection between Fu Chou and Qi.
It's two birds with one stone.
Father made a very wise move!
I am afraid Fu Chou won't give up so easily.
Perhaps behind all of his patience,
a greater plot is brewing.
Your Highness.
Your Highness, it's from the Hidden Ones.
There are disturbances in the south.
Agent Wu wishes to remind you...
the main routes in the south are blocked by natural and human causes.
Delivery of messages will be obstructed.
If anything does happen,
we might not receive the news at once.
I knew it.
Someone might use the campaign as an opening for an uprising.
My father set his mind on taking down Wei,
but there are others that wait to strike from the dark.
Leng Yan, inform the Hidden Ones.
There is a change of plans.
Defense of the south is our priority.
Yes.
- General Fu, I am...
- Get out!
You can talk to me,
but please show some respect.
You are jealous because of Yali and Zongzheng Wuyou.
While the Emperor and Empress were here,
you tried to show off your skill to Zongzheng Wuyou's fiancée.
When you did that,
had you thought about respecting me?
You took it wrongly.
- Your shoulder was...
- I misunderstood?
Haven't you noticed?
You have been overstepping the line since he returned to the capital.
You were in the water with him at Linglong Palace. I let it pass.
On Zhao Yun's wedding day,
you two spent the night at the inn, I let that pass too.
You were secretly meeting him in the tomb, I look past that too!
Do you know what the tomb means to me?
It's humiliation.
The greatest shaming of all!
If you know everything, you should realize that...
all of those are mere coincidence.
- The Linglong Palace...
- It's coincidence?
Once? Maybe.
Twice? Maybe.
But it happened again and again.
How is that coincidence?
Rong Le, when it comes to Zongzheng Wuyou,
you will always forget that I am your husband.
So this is how you see me?
Every time I came back here, I could feel someone watching me.
You were spying on me, eavesdropping, and tailing me.
You are living under fear and suspicion.
You don't even have the slightest trust for me.
What more do you expect from me?
I want to be there for you all the time.
Every time I come home, the first thing I want...
is to see your face and hear your voice.
But what do I get in the end?
Zongzheng Wuyou refused to marry you.
His Majesty searched for a replacement.
Now that Zongzheng Wuyou is deeply in love with you,
he wants me to end this marriage.
What is this all about?
Do you take me as a fool?
The emperor wants to terminate this marriage,
and you said you don't deserve me.
Such a noble excuse!
All of you only ever care about Zongzheng Wuyou!
You only care about Zongzheng Wuyou!
What am I? What I am to you?
Why is everyone giving up on me because of him?
- Why?
- Let go of me!
Today, I will let you know you are my wife!
Let go of me! Let go of me!
Let go of me!
Your broke our agreement.
I have nothing more to say to you.
From now on, we will never see each other again.
If you really want to leave,
I won't stop you.
But I hope... for the sake of my reputation...
and the alliance between Western Qi and Northern Lin,
for the next three months, please don't meet Zongzheng Wuyou again.
If you won't agree with this,
I would rather have the two of us die in here.
Fine.
You have my word.
After three months, it's all over for the two of us.
♫ I can't help but to ask after you ♫ -
♫ Our hearts are a lifetime apart ♫
♫ No one comes, also no one asks ♫
♫ How do we keep living this life? ♫
♫ Finally, I've learned how to trust ♫ -
♫ But I've underestimated love and hate ♫ -
♫ We've thrown away fate that we'd received by chance ♫ -
♫ I have to admit to my mistakes ♫
♫ I regret the one mistake that I made so much ♫
♫ All hope is lost, how do I start over? ♫
♫ I asked for too much, I hesitated for too long ♫
♫ Blame the mistake that happened too soon ♫
General Fu, why are you doing this?
That was embarrassing.
I shall send you home right away.
No, I am not leaving!
Don't you understand my love for you?
♫ I must preserve the memories that are wonderful ♫
♫ I walk in a desert, but my heart is being flooded ♫
♫ My heart is beating senselessly ♫
Miss Sun, what exactly do you want?
All the officers in the Imperial Court know that Prince Li is your fiancé.
No!
You know what I mean.
Prince Li is just using me as an excuse.
It's just like the marriage you had with Rong Le.
I always suspected you were not having any joy in this marriage.
But today, I finally know the two of us are the same.
We are all shackled by love.
I really do love you.
You are the only one I will love.
If you can't escape from this fake marriage,
I am willing to spend my life with you.
I don't care if I am banished from my family.
I don't care... if I can only become a lowly servant of yours.
I will be there for you.
♫ I won't let our love be a regret ♫
♫ Living without sorrow, dying without any hate ♫
♫ This is the leniency that you've shown to me ♫
♫ We are not holding hands, but you are holding my heart ♫
♫ Although this might not be forever ♫
♫ I've locked you in my heart and I've locked you in my dreams ♫
Princess, the curfew of the city is in effect.
If General Fu did something awful to you,
there is no need to leave in such a hurry.
Xiao Sha, ready the carriage.
Ling Yue, pack up all the things.
I don't want to stay here for another moment.
- Yes.
Your Highness.
Are we really leaving?
General Fu is actually very nice to you.
Look. After the two of you came back from Lady Yun's tomb,
you refused to wear this wedding gown for the wedlock ceremony.
But he didn't say anything about it.
He even hired the best tailor in the city to mend it.
After some repairing, it looks like new.
All General wanted was to see you wear this dress...
and become his real wife.
But you never even batted an eye for this dress.
It's been kept inside the closet.
It looks a little old now.
All his effort just went down the drain.
[Letter of Dissolution]
Rong Le.
It takes three lifetimes of fate to become husband and wife.
We may be married,
but the two of us are not part of fate's plan.
I couldn't swallow it.
I forced you to be my wife.
It was our wedding day.
I still hold a wee bit of hope that in one year...
I can turn things around for us and be a real couple.
If while you are reading this letter...
and still have not the slightest bit of love for me or even hate me,
I am willing to set you free.
Let this be the end of us.
Let us part in peace.
Princess, are we taking this with us?
Take everything.
Don't leave anything behind.
Yes.
Have some tea.
General Fu wrote you this letter?
Have you thought about what you will do next?
Right now, I am just as lost as I was before.
When I am leaving, I am so determined and bold.
I just want to leave this place for good.
I won't let them hurt or use me again.
I want to leave this cage.
But when I step out of it,
as soon as I walk out from the shadow,
I have no idea...
what danger lies ahead of us.
You mean...
not only will you leave the manor,
you are also leaving Zhongshan?
I must sever all ties with Fu Chou.
He is frustrated, so am I.
Three months from now, all the burden will be released.
I will leave Zhongshan.
But if you leave just like that,
aren't you going to find out who you are?
I remember you saying that...
the secret of your past might be hidden inside Fort Yu.
I remember now.
While I was playing the lute,
some flashes of memories came to me.
Perhaps Ke'er's treatment...
is making those memories much clearer for me.
Why don't we go to Fort Yu before you leave this place?
It might bring back even more memories of the past.
Miss Man Yao, do you know the person on this drawing?
It feels familiar to me, but I am not sure.
I hope this is the truth.
With that, I can know for sure...
that I once had a mother and a happy family.
But I also wish it's not the truth.
I don't have to face the truth of my family being killed...
and the pain of losing everything again.
Please, don't see it that way.
Sir Qin may be dead,
but he lives on inside the people's hearts.
After I got here,
it reminds me a lot of my childhood.
What do you remember?
You have been here before?
Maybe.
Everything here seems so familiar to me.
When my father wrote...
"The Book of Mountains and Rivers" with Sir Qin,
this is where they were.
The woman on the drawing would be Lady Qin.
I remember she gave me some candies before.
What else can you recall?
Have you seen the two daughters of Sir Qin?
I wish we had more time.
We can spend more time here to recall the past.
Miss Man Yao, now that you are here,
it means you have found the book.
Why don't we look around?
Maybe we can find more clues.
The book is not with me.
Where are you keeping it?
You only told Long Yue about its location?
You must be curious...
about the fallout I had with Prince Li.
That's because I handed over the book to him.
But I later found out he was using me to get the book.
You mean... the book is now with Prince Li?
Yes.
I am sorry.
I cannot let you go.
Your Highness, there is a letter for you.
Your Majesty, the Court started over an hour ago.
We can't just wait and do nothing.
Father, you knew my brother had some objections to the campaign.
Why must we wait for him to discuss it?
Besides, you know very well about his temper.
Even if you drag him here,
he wouldn't give any constructive ideas.
Just shut it.
I don't care how many objections he has for the campaign.
There are rules to follow in the Imperial Court.
He can't just be absent without any reason.
I sent Captain Xiang to search for him.
Let's see what he has to say.
Captain Xiang arrives!
Your Majesty.
What took you so long? Where is Prince Li?
Your Majesty, when I arrived at the manor,
the guard said Prince Li left in the night and hasn't come back since.
I led my men to the places and shops His Highness frequented.
But he is nowhere to be found.
Curse him!
He hides himself right when I need him!
Does he think the campaign can't go on without him?
Father, Wuyou was never been interested in the politics of the Imperial Court.
All the national affairs he worked on... are mere covers.
His old habits have started to kick in.
Father, just let him be.
I have some suggestions for the campaign.
I shall gladly discuss them with the fellow officers...
and be at your services.
Forget it.
I am getting tired of this.
Let's get this over with and dismiss.
As for your plans, write them down and submit your proposal.
- I'll read it when I am free.
- Yes!
Dismissed!
Long live Your Majesty.
Rong Le?
Where is she?
I don't know.
After the quarrel you had that day, she left in the night.
She hasn't come back since.
We never intervene with your matters with Lady Rong Le.
I wouldn't dare to stop her without your permission.
We could only let her leave.
Why didn't you inform me she was leaving?
- I apologize for that.
- Look for her now!
Yes, I will look for her right away.
I didn't have the courage to talk to you.
I couldn't face you.
But I never thought...
it was just my wishful thinking.
You were in such a hurry to leave me.
Can't you wait for another moment?
You broke our agreement.
I have nothing more to say to you.
From now on,
we will never see each other again.
Your Majesty, when I arrived at the manor,
the guard said Prince Li left in the night and hasn't come back since.
I brought this down upon myself.
I can't even have a fake marriage.
Rong Le, I should have sworn...
to never deceive you again on our wedding day.
That dissolution letter took me fourteen times just to complete it.
But I never thought you would be so cruel.
As soon as you are freed, you eloped with him.
Hen Xiang?
What are you doing here?
Are you searching for Rong Le?
Is this all your doing?
Tell me where she is now!
So, in your eyes,
every harm done to her is my doing?
But not this time.
It's Chen Yu, the person she trusts the most.
Chen Yu?
As for Chen Yu's true identity,
not even our master knows about her.
I don't know why she would take Rong Le with her.
But we found out that she informed Zongzheng Wuyou.
We can know her target is not Rong Le.
We have Zongzheng Wuyou to rescue Rong Le.
You don't need to worry.
Are you sure Zongzheng Wuyou will be there?
If he doesn't go, Rong Le will be in grave danger.
He definitely will.
We tried it so many times, isn't that right?
I can't trust him.
Stand aside.
Zongzheng Wuyou is not the one you can't trust.
You are afraid after he saves Rong Le,
they will fall in love again.
Stand aside!
Young Master, our plan is in motion.
This is a crucial time for us.
There are other matters you must see to.
You can't give up the greater good for the sake of a woman.
I know what the greater good is.
I don't need you to lecture me.
Stand aside now...
or I won't show any mercy.
You can't go!
Even if you kill me,
I still won't let you go to her.
But if I am dead,
no one in this world will ever truly care for you.
♫ The snow falls on my palm ♫
♫ I just want to gaze at you one more time ♫
♫ I wait for the warmth of your gaze to melt it ♫
♫ We are fated to get hurt from the moment we met each other ♫
♫ I miss you but I can only gaze at you in silence ♫
♫ You are keeping me out with your care,
Although we are together, I feel lost ♫
♫ I can wait for you until my hair turns white ♫
♫ I can endure all the loneliness just for you ♫
♫ I will be your hearth in the coldest of places ♫
♫ For you, I am willing to suffer ♫
♫ I want to ward off the coldness for you ♫
♫ As long as I can be with you, I'm willing to give you all of me ♫
♫ In a blink of an eye, my hair has turned silver ♫
♫ I'm fated to live in loneliness without any regrets ♫
♫ The winter may be cold,
but I will watch from afar and keep you warm ♫
♫ I'm willing to wipe away your blood and wounds for you ♫
♫ I'm willing to live in darkness for you ♫
♫ As long as I can be with you, I don't mind... hiding in the dark ♫