[Episode 6]
In order to save me, you had a fallout with the crown prince.
People might take it wrongly if words got out.
What they think is none of your concern.
But for me, you are...
a rare well-matched partner in chess.
I really enjoy playing chess with you.
I don't wish to be affected by common views.
Did you really save me... for the sake of chess only?
♫ You who came to a strange land to build our lands together ♫
♫ I think of you when night has fallen... ♫
♫ and when the fog has parted ♫
Your Highness, we have reached the Moon Embrace Teahouse.
♫ My yearning for you has turned you... ♫
Thank you, Your Highness. Farewell.
♫ You are my happiness, my worries and... ♫
♫ my abyss ♫
♫ I can't touch you for you are like... ♫
♫ the reflection in water ♫
♫ I don't want distance... ♫
- Leng Yan.
- Yes, Your Highness.
- Let's go back.
♫ I just want to watch you... ♫
♫ in this cold world ♫
I didn't manage to protect you. I have failed the emperor.
And I have failed you, too.
You did well in arranging the matters in the manor.
Ling Yue and Lian Xin have become smarter, too.
I should have gone back immediately.
But Long Yue has destroyed all the contraptions.
And I can't just use the front door.
Mistress.
Thank you for sacrificing yourself to save me.
It's my fault for not being meticulous enough... until I had caused you such disgrace.
If you need anything else from now on,
I'll put my life to it.
We are here in Northern Lin.
We should take care of each other and complete this mission.
I won't let you sacrifice yourself.
Thank you, Mistress.
How's Chen Yu?
She is still unconscious from being severely wounded.
Prince Chen has already sent someone over to treat her.
She can come when she's feeling better.
I'll leave this Moon Embrace Teahouse to you.
We can no longer use this place as our rendezvous point.
We need to find a new place immediately.
Yes. Don't worry, Mistress.
I already made the arrangement last night. We can get in touch...
with the kite and Western Qi soon.
But we can no longer use the original secret path.
Meanwhile, I hope that you can stay put...
while I look for another route for you.
For now, it's better if you go back to the manor at once... in case something else happens.
Arrival of Her Majesty!
Greetings, Mother.
It has already been two months.
Why isn't there any progress at all?
Don't be anxious, Mother.
- Recently, the kite...
- You can't be overcautious.
You need to give them a kick.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, drink the medicine.
You'll feel better after you take it.
Go out.
I am in good health.
No need to worry about me.
As for the rare book hunt,
put your safety before everything else.
There is no rush.
I feel relieved that you are doing well...
in Northern Lin.
Xiao Sha.
What do you need, Princess?
For the Eastern Suburb Inn and the man that saved me...
that I had asked you to investigate, have you found anything about them?
I already checked the inn.
It often has a lot of customers and it looks normal enough.
As for that man, I had asked the innkeeper. He did remember the man.
But that man left after staying for just a day.
And he didn't leave behind his name.
It might be because I was wounded that day.
That's why he had to find the nearest inn the treat my wounds.
I don't think it's necessary for you to repay his kindness.
In this world, this kind of meeting is a fate.
But there is something that I have been wanting to report to you after some considerations.
I think I know what it is.
Answer me first.
Did you touch the lock on this box?
That box contains the secret letters between you and the emperor.
And I have never touched it.
Usually, only you, me, Ling Yue, and Lian Xin...
can come into this room.
And you are the only one who knew what's inside.
But I believe you.
Are you going to report that there are spies in our midst?
How did you know?
By the way, where is the assassin that was knocked unconscious?
That day, after I changed and came out from the room,
I saw that the hiding spot for the assassin was not very secure.
I was afraid that he'd cause trouble if he woke.
That's why I and Lian Xin tied up his hands and legs...
and threw him into the firewood storeroom.
After that, we rushed to your side...
and we don't know what happened next.
That's right.
After Yu Wenjie barged into my manor,
I started to feel that something was not right.
How can two girls that grew up in a palace...
know how to deal with an assassin so cleanly and neatly?
And somebody had touched this lock.
I had laid down a trap when I designed this box.
That's right. Recently, I had found some problems as well.
- Princess Rong Le.
- Princess Zhao Yun!
Princess Rong Le.
I had read Princess Zhao Yun's pulse.
Her blood flow is blocked. I think someone pressed on her pressure point.
She didn't faint because of the drugging mist.
No one else can know about this. Keep a close eye out for these few days.
Yes, Princess.
Lately, the weather is very nice.
Everything is coming to life.
I'm old already.
I have to come out and take a walk more.
Luckily, I have you to accompany me.
It's my fortune to be able to accompany you.
Moreover, you are still young.
There are many troublesome things in this palace. Here, we grow old fast.
But under the spring sunlight, you look so lively.
It must be because something good has happened.
I heard from your father that... Wuyou has already promised...
to go flower viewing with you in the suburb in a few days' time.
Prince Chen is tagging along, too.
Both of them are very busy. So, we haven't set the date.
Actually, I'm already very happy that I can accompany you... to come out for a walk.
Look at you.
I heard that Princess Rong Le has recovered.
How about you pay her a visit in my stead and invite her along for your excursion?
We can use this chance... to matchmake her and Wuyu.
Prince Chen and Prince Li are very close.
If Princess Rong Le is willing to marry Prince Chen,
His Majesty will be glad to see that too.
All right.
You have good taste.
This hairpin is from the Western region. It's expertly carved in copper.
The carved flowers symbolize good fortune.
They said that Moon Embrace Teahouse has a mysterious Rare Item Chest chamber.
And it contains treasures from all over the world. I'll take this.
Welcome to the Rare Item Chest chamber, Miss.
We have high quality silks and satins here,
high-quality rouge in rose color...
and jade-wares that are expertly carved.
I'm not sure if you are willing to sell the things that I want.
What do you want?
I want the string of a soft-winged kite.
Soft wing can stand against the wind to rise up to the sky.
We have this in our collection as well.
Your Highness.
Unfortunately, our mistress has gone to the tea plantation to check on the source.
She will only be back after a few days.
Recently, I had come here three times.
But every time, I just happened to miss her.
Our mistress is very devoted to this teahouse.
I'm truly sorry, Your Highness.
How about I ask Miss Chen Yu to come and play a song for you?
No need. I'll just come again next time.
[Rare Item Chest]
Wuyou.
Our teacher is set on marrying her daughter, Yali to you.
Even the empress has supported that.
But you are still engaged to Western Qi's princess. What should we do?
What they want has nothing to do with me.
But Wuyou, you are in love with Miss Man Yao from Moon Embrace Teahouse, right?
Look at you. You should just admit to it.
You went to the teahouse again these few days, right?
But she's avoiding you. Actually, that's weird.
For a money-grubber business woman like her,
you are a money tree for her.
She's not a money-grubber.
Please tell me more.
The art of steeping is about patience and the state of mind.
If you are not a resolute person who is indifferent to worldly matters,
you can't capture the quintessence of the art of steeping.
I think the way to enjoy tea is not about the tea itself...
but the state of mind one has when one drinks tea.
How about you relax your mind and taste the tea in earnest?
A person like her cannot be a money-grubber.
She is not a person like that.
Why did she act like that then?
She is keeping you at arm's length.
Could it be that she's baiting you to attract your attention?
How can you make a hasty conclusion?
Look at you. You clearly like her.
Arrival of His Majesty!
Wuyu, recently, I haven't seen you much at the court.
You hang out at Prince Li Manor every day.
You learned nothing but bad habits from your brother.
That's not true.
Enough. Leave us.
I have something to discuss with your brother.
Yes, Father.
Wuyou.
I haven't seen you in a long time.
Ever since I last saw you at Yun's Tomb,
I have been thinking a lot.
If you really don't want to marry the Western Qi's princess,
I won't force you.
The empress told me that...
you had known Yali, the granddaughter of the Central Secretary since young.
This will be a good marriage, too.
I don't see how this is a good marriage arrangement.
Do you really like the granddaughter of the Sun family...
or just the power of the Sun family that takes root in three states of the southern region?
Wuyou, you should understand the troubles I took...
to give you those three states in the southern region.
Why do you have to fight with me every step of the way?
Somebody told me that you reject the idea of marriage alliance...
because lately, you had been spending your time with a businesswoman.
And you wrecked the prison of the Ministry of Justice because of her.
My choice has nothing to do with her.
As for why I refuse to marry the Western Qi's princess,
I think you know it better than anyone.
You hung the map in your reading room.
I can see that you are very clear about the situation of Northern Lin.
The crown prince's failure has affected the Northern Li.
We have lost hundreds and thousands of our soldiers.
In order to avenge them... and to get rid of this thorn in our side,
I have decided to band with Western Qi to battle Wei.
Do you really think that we lost that war because of the crown prince's mistake alone?
The people have to pay war tax every year and they are suffering.
Northern Lin is not in top condition anymore.
Even if I marry the Western Qi's princess or the daughter from a noble family,
it would do the country no good.
I had never lost in a battle before.
If I personally lead the army this time, we can defeat Wei for sure.
When the time comes, we can conquer the world.
We are not racing against the time to conquer the world.
If we begin another war now, you'll ruin our country.
For now, it's best to recuperate and wait until the country is strong again.
Shut up!
Until now,
you are still holding on to the fallacy of that traitor, Qin Yong.
His People-Based Transformation theory. What nonsense!
He killed your mother!
My teacher is not a traitor.
Since you don't dare to mention his name in front of others,
how dare you speak of my mother?
I know clearly who killed my mother.
And don't ever forget.
The reason Northern Lin can become so strong in such a short time...
is because of my teacher's People-Based Transformation theory.
Looks like you still haven't given up on it.
I don't take part in managing the country anymore.
Do I have to let you dictate my thinking and my beliefs, too?
Fine.
Since you are like this,
I'll make a half-year deal with you too.
Within half a year,
if you can find the long lost rare book of the Qin family, "The Book of Mountains and Rivers,"
I'll allow you to restart your People-Based Transformation.
And I'll allow you to marry freely.
"The Book of Mountains and Rivers?"
Yes. You didn't forget about that book, right?
If you can't find it, you have to marry the princess of Western Qi.
And you have to help me take down Wei as well.
The book has been lost for so long.
It is not an easy thing to procure in the first place.
Moreover, even if I managed to find "The Book of Mountains and Rivers,"
you won't give an explanation to the world about my mother and teacher, right?
You!
[Princess Manor]
Other noblemen and women in the capital city treated me with venom.
Why are you willing to befriend me?
I feel very guilty for passing on my illness to you the last time.
That was just a false alarm. I'm so healthy that I recovered after a nap.
I remember that when I was bullied by others,
you were the only one who stepped out to help me.
Look at this. Is this flower pretty?
- You are prettier than the flower.
- Really?
Looks like both of you are having a good time.
Greetings, Princess Rong Le and Princess Zhao Yun.
I heard that Princess Manor is decorated with Western Qi's design.
Now that I see it today, it's really the work of craftsmanship.
You flattered me, Miss Sun. Take a seat.
Miss Sun, have you been to Western Qi?
I'm a home type of girl. Unlike you who traveled the world,
besides Zhongshan, I only ever traveled to the southern area every year during the Qingming festival.
Zhongshan is very beautiful. You should go out and walk around.
All right.
By the way, Prince Li and Prince Chen have invited me to go on an excursion in the suburb.
Are you willing to come along as well?
That's great.
Princess Rong Le, you are already engaged with Brother Wuyou.
You should get to know each other more and bond with each other.
Although Brother Wuyou looks fierce most of the time,
he's actually a righteous, bold, talented, intelligent, and sophisticated man.
He's the real hero.
I think that Prince Chen is younger, more energetic, and interesting.
He is an intriguing person.
In comparison, Prince Li is cold and hard to predict.
How did you become so close with him?
I stayed in the palace for a while when I was young.
He wasn't like this in the past.
He treated others kindly.
He still treats me kindly now.
A few days ago, he had helped me by teaching that elder son a lesson.
Princess Rong Le, don't be fooled by Wuyu.
That man is a sweet talker and he's insensible.
He has many fans in every corner of this city.
Princess Rong Le.
Moon Embrace Teahouse has sent this new tea for you to taste it.
Their shopkeeper said that today, they have an important guest.
They have tea tasting, chess playing, flower viewing, and sword dance.
They had reserved a seat for you.
If you ever have the time, the invitation will is open.
I just asked Xiao Sha to go and buy me some tea leaves.
I never thought that their shopkeeper would be so generous.
Award the person who sent the tea.
Express my thanks to the shopkeeper for the invitation
I'll go there when I have fully recovered.
Yes, Princess.
You know the shopkeeper of Moon Embrace Teahouse?
I heard that she's really good.
And she has collected many treasures from all over the world.
For example, she has this high-quality dress and rare night-luminescent pearl...
from the Western region in her Rare Item Chest chamber.
Princess Rong Le, can you bring me along?
Princess, what is wrong?
You have just recovered.
The doctor said that you have to rest more.
We have disturbed you from resting.
Princess Rong Le, rest well.
We'll invite you again to go out with us another day.
I'll take my leave then.
Princess Rong Le, I'll visit you again on another day as well.
All right.
Tea tasting, chess playing, flower viewing, and sword dance.
The teahouse is all about peace and tranquility.
They don't allow any weapons.
Usually, Long Yue will find some excuse for me.
Since she sent someone over today, it must be because there's no other way.
- Ling Yue. Help me change.
- Yes, Princess.
[Moon Embrace Teahouse]
You are here, Miss Man Yao.
I'm wondering if you could make me some tea today.
I know clearly whether you are here to drink tea or to find troubles.
How can you be so sure that I'm not here to drink tea?
If you are here to drink tea,
why would you hide wine inside the bamboo tube?
I purposely used this old bamboo tube for soup to hide this wine.
I thought that it would be able to hide its smell.
I never thought that you'd find out about it. You are really good.
Wuyou can't drink wine. But I can't drink tea.
I can not eat for a day but I can't live without wine.
You are the mistress here. How about you drink some with me today?
What are you thinking about? Wuyou is not here.
Since you have already invited me, of course, I can't reject your kindness.
But I'm the same as Prince Li. I can't drink wine.
We have a full house today.
If I drink too much and embarrassed myself,
not only would I humiliate myself which is nothing,
but I'd affect your reputation which is the real problem if someone sees me.
After all, everybody knows that...
Moon Embrace Teahouse sells only tea and no wine.
I never thought that besides being meticulous, you are good with words as well.
Since you already said that, I'd feel guilty to force you.
Fine. I'll act nobly today...
and enjoy this good wine by myself.
Take a seat.
Sit down.
Somebody, please bring me my tools to warm up the wine.
- Miss Long Yue.
- Miss Chen Yu, yow's the mistress?
She is still with Prince Chen.
They have been in there for so long. I'm worried that she'll be in danger.
Prince Chen is very unpredictable. I don't know what his plan is.
Please spare my life.
No matter what, you have to make tea for me today.
All right, Your Highness.
Go and check on them again at once.
All right.
Miss Man Yao.
Before this, I heard from Long Yue that you just came to Zhongshan not long ago.
Before this, where were you?
Are you interrogating me?
No, I'm just asking for fun.
My father is a businessman.
I had followed him everywhere since young.
We don't stay in one place.
Traveling around the world has always been on my wish list.
Where have you traveled before?
I have been to many places.
I don't know where to start.
Just tell me about some of the places you've gone to. Just think of it as broadening my horizon.
Are you drunk?
I heard that you are an expert in traveling and having fun.
How can there be places that you don't know of?
Where were we just now?
You want to know that which places are beautiful to me.
Yes. I really want to know. Tell me.
I already told you just now. Are you drunk?
You didn't tell me just now.
I want you to tell me about some places but you haven't said anything.
Let me think about it.
Miss Man Yao, before you come to Zhongshan,
where were you?
Before I come to Zhongshan,
I am...
Where were you?
What's wrong with me?
I am...
in a tearoom.
It sounds so nice.
Where is the tearoom?
The fire for your wine has gone out.
Let me light it up for you again.
Miss Man Yao, are you all right?
Wuyou, you are here.
Wuyou, this is the Shilixiang wine that I stole from your manor.
I thought that it can lower one's guard.
We were doing fine just now.
Wuyou, I never thought that it would...
That it would...
It will indeed lower one's guard.
Are you all right, Miss Chen Yu?
Your Highness, I feel dizzy.
It'll be all right.
♫ I miss you but I can only gaze at you in silence ♫
♫ You are keeping me out with your care.
Although we are together... ♫
♫ I can wait for you until my hair turns white ♫
♫ I can endure all the loneliness just for you ♫
♫ For you, I am willing to suffer ♫
♫ I want to ward off the coldness for you ♫
♫ As long as I can be with you, I'm willing to give you all of me ♫
You are awake.
This is a specially brewed hangover soup.
Do you want me to feed you personally?
♫ The winter may be cold,
but I will watch from afar and keep you warm ♫
Slowly. It's a little bit bitter.
♫ I'm willing to wipe off the blood and wounds for you ♫
Thank you for your help. I won't disturb you then.
♫ As long as I can be with you, I don't mind... hiding in the dark ♫
Look. You can't even stand straight. How are you going to go back?
Don't worry. After you sober up,
I'll ask someone to send you back to Moon Embrace Teahouse.
I'm really grateful to you for saving me.
But I can't trouble you further.
Why do you have to keep me here?
Why did I go into the prison to save you that day?
Because you know that I'm innocent.
You are wise and just.
You can't just be impervious to injustice, right?
Do you have to lie all the time?
I know that you bear goodwill, but I really need to go back.
I have to take care of the teahouse.
How much can your teahouse earn in a day? I'll pay you.
What is it?
Man Yao, this is a good chance for you to name a price.
Aren't you glad?
Since you have invited me so warmly to stay here,
I'll accept your invitation.
100 tael a day. I thank you first, Your Highness.
All right.
The water is reflecting the light and dusk is upon us.
This beautiful scenery is fleeting.
But you are not willing to enjoy this scenery with me in peace.
You are just thinking about rejecting me.
It's not that I'm not willing, but I...
am different from you.
Unlike you who can do things as you please...
Again with your teahouse.
Man Yao, you are not like others.
But you keep on pretending to be a sordid merchant.
Are you looking down on me?
Do you think that I'm not worthy for you to treat me sincerely?
You have exaggerated.
You are a royal, you are charming and elegant.
Unlike me who is just a commoner. I'm not very knowledgeable.
- That's why you'll think that...
- Forget it.
I don't like to force people.
If you really want to go back, go ahead.
Helmsman, please turn back and let me off at the nearest wharf.
Helmsman.
Helmsman. Helmsman.
He is old. His hearing is not that well.
I have a way if you want to go back.
Calm down and enjoy the scenery with me.
And I'll ask someone to send you back to Moon Embrace Teahouse.
Why do you have to make things difficult for me?
Prince Chen had invited me to join him with wine.
What are you going to do to keep me here?
Sister Ling Yue, how about we go back?
Go back?
Lian Xin, think carefully.
This is a rare chance that the princess is not in tonight.
Are you sure about that?
Fine. Let's go.
Here. Carry them here.
Yes, Sir.
Cover them well.
Line them up nicely.
- We still have some bodies there.
- All right.
Scoop him up.
- Check over there.
- Yes, Sir.
Be careful.
Greetings, Your Highness.
What happened here?
Your Highness, it's a shipwreck.
Quick! There are bodies over there.
Yes, Sir.
Move it over here.
Deputy Minister Ma from the Ministry of Personnel.
Give them a proper burial. Make sure to get all of them out of the water.
Get me two horses as well.
I rushed here after I received the report.
I just simply brought that horse with me.
You can take that horse if you don't mind.
He is just a child.
Is this an accident?
There won't be so many accidents.
Let's leave now. We can still make it back to the city before the gate is closed.
Do you know this man?
If this is an accident, will someone uphold justice for them?
Justice?
There is no justice in this chaotic world.
Aren't you a self-claimed merchant that cares only about money?
Why are you so set on this?
Everybody has compassion.
Even you won't feel nothing when you see such tragedy, right?
Then what do you think I should do?
I wouldn't dare to ask you to do anything.
I just feel that...
what have they done wrong...
until they have to suffer like this?
I'm too much of a busybody.
In the end, I'm just another person in this world.
We can do nothing about it in this chaotic world.
Maybe one day, I'll become one of the innocent sacrifices as well.
Let's go.
With me here, who dares to sacrifice you?
♫ I've been secretly missing you for several seasons already ♫
♫ Who was the first to talk about love? ♫
♫ I'm still trying to be nice to myself ♫
♫ Just allow me to get you back to this date ♫
♫ The western wind dyes the flowering season
in thick gray color ♫
♫ And I am still standing here waiting for the rain to come ♫
♫ No matter how good or bad the season turns out ♫
♫ I will still try with my utmost to make a home for us ♫
♫ In just one day, I've tasted the entire human world's warmth ♫
♫ Yet, you are always the one I'm longing for ♫
♫ Even with thousands of feelings, we'll have no regrets ♫
♫ Look at this love, because of you I have a sweet aftertaste ♫
♫ In just one day, I've tasted the entire human world's warmth ♫
♫ Yet, you are always the one I'm longing for ♫
♫ Even with thousands of feelings, we'll have no regrets ♫
♫ Look at this love, because of you I have a sweet aftertaste ♫
♫ Nothing will... go away ♫