[Episode 33]
You are still going to launch a mutiny?
What's done is done.
Yet, I am still asking this foolish question.
How silly can I be?
I don't even know if your resolve is real...
or simply a lie.
Truth or lie,
you never cared.
All you will ever do when you start to suspect me...
is to tell Zongzheng Wuyou about everything.
Or you would risk your own life and report to the main camp.
Do you really think... everything I do is wrong?
Have you ever thought about... why I made those decisions?
I know it all.
You are the son of Empress Fu Yuan.
A man disguised as you and had conversations with His Majesty.
I know that too.
Did you hear that the so-called emperor that is my father...
has never seen me as his son?
Whether you believe it or not, he is still your father.
This is a fact that can never be changed.
Fu Chou, stop your plan.
Do not let your hands be stained with the blood of your kin.
Kin?
What about your brother Rong Qi?
Do you see him as your kin?
He used you...
and that brought you great pain.
The so-called emperor that is my father...
hunted me down for five whole years.
The warmth of a family was turned into a cold blade that slaughters.
You want me to stop?
Do you even know how desperate I was back then?
I simply feel like...
there is no need to have the innocent killed.
You asked me if I see my brother as a family.
Yes.
He used me for his bidding and hurt the people I love.
But I cannot use others' lives to have my revenge.
It would make me the same villain as he.
The soldiers should be the nation's strongest defense.
But your revenge will make the river flow with blood.
How can you be at peace with that?
And in the end,
you will be killing your own father and brothers.
Even if you won,
what can you possibly get from that empty and cold throne?
Whatever I get in the end...
is still better than having nothing at all.
He is not my brother.
The emperor is not my father!
I had nothing to begin with.
What could possibly be worse for me?
Your Majesty. Wuyou.
Wuyou, come down here. You can't be so rude.
- Mother.
- Wuyou, come.
Look at yourself, you are sweating so hard.
- Your Majesty.
- Father.
Wuyou is such a nice kid. Isn't that right?
Wuyou, go on and play with your mother.
Okay.
You should have some rest.
Who is it?
Xiao Sha?
Father!
[Emperor Sejong Gwangmu of the Zongzheng Clan]
I have failed you!
I have failed you! Father!
If I were at your side,
you wouldn't have been killed by those scoundrels, Father!
[Emperor Sejong Gwangmu of the Zongzheng Clan]
Crown Prince.
May you mourn in peace.
Crown Prince, please mourn in peace.
Here.
His Majesty has passed away.
This is the loss of our nation.
But the campaign must go on as planned.
Now, we must deal with traitors and enemies.
I suggest... we leave the coffin at the side hall and keep it a secret.
Relocate a few troops to create a distraction at the border.
After the rebels are dealt with,
we will hold a state funeral for His Majesty.
Sure.
We'll proceed with your plan.
Father!
Leng Yan, with our marching speed,
when will we arrive in Zhongshan?
Your Highness, there are three days of journey ahead.
Take him down!
I was ordered by Princess Rong Le to send this to Prince Li.
It seems like the whole of Zhongshan is now under Fu Chou's control.
Even the Royal Army is doing his bidding.
With Fu Chou's mind,
he won't let someone else take command.
If my guess is right,
Fu Chou never followed my father on the campaign.
He has been hiding in the capital...
deploying his soldiers.
The campaign was led by His Majesty.
How did he pull this off?
When Zhao Yun was attacked at the inn,
he ordered someone to disguise as Man Yao.
He is using the same trick again.
He had an imposter go on the march in his place.
His Majesty would never expect Fu Chou...
to use such a lowly and cunning means.
Your Highness, if General Fu is so treacherous,
and this man is his personal bodyguard,
we cannot trust him even with the Inked-Jade Fan.
- This might be his plan all along.
- You...
If you don't trust me,
give me back the tactical map.
Man Yao would give up her own life...
before this plan...
and the Inked-Jade Fan were taken by someone else.
I believe in her.
So, I trust you.
Send out the order.
We will travel day and night to Zhongshan.
Leng Yan, you will lead a troop of elites...
and go to our main force.
Make sure His Majesty is safe.
- Also...
- I understand.
Your Highness can count on me.
Can you still walk?
I am fine.
I hope all will go well for Lady Rong Le.
Man Yao, have you met with my father?
As of now, are you safe?
- Your Highness.
- At ease.
Thank you, Prince Li.
If Man Yao is willing to give you the fan,
it means she places her trust in you.
Lady Rong Le saved my life.
My life... is hers to command.
Fu Chou knows you betrayed him.
That's why he hunted you down.
He only knows I betrayed the Creed.
But he doesn't know about the letter I sent you.
The Creed is tracking Lady Rong Le.
It was an accident that they found me.
So, Fu Chou knew it all along...
that Man Yao found out about his plan.
If Man Yao is still at the main camp,
and if she didn't get to inform my father...
and was found by Fu Chou's men,
it will not...
Your Highness! Your Highness!
Did something happen at the main camp?
Your Highness.
I investigated and ask around the camp.
His Majesty was assassinated in the main camp.
His Majesty passed away.
My condolences, Your Highness.
Our condolences, Your Highness.
Who was the killer?
After Fu Chou transported the body back to the capital,
he framed Your Highness in front of the officers,
claiming that you were planning to seize the throne,
which is why you went to the camp and killed His Majesty.
Fu Chou.
The Imperial Court is under his control.
Crown Prince has ordered us not to say a word about His Majesty.
Once you enter the city, they have an order to kill you on sight.
Prince Chen is under house arrest, too.
Your Highness, you must turn the tide at the capital
and take down the villains.
Take down the villains!
Your Highness, I found this...
at the location where the main camp was.
It looks like His Majesty's handwriting.
Yun, I am advancing with the army.
I can feel that ambition is beyond my reach.
I can't fall asleep.
Sometimes, I wish to forget all of it and join you.
But Wuyou is still young.
I wish to hold on for him for a couple of years.
As you know, once a man sits on the throne,
he will lose all that was once dear to him.
When the time comes, choices will be a luxury.
Yun, while I was on the march with the army,
I kept thinking about the time when Wuyou was a kid.
Back then, he wanted to learn how to ride a horse.
But I was so afraid he would fall from it.
So, I let him ride on my back.
Back in the days, I let him ride on me.
But I am too old now.
I even have to pass the duty onto his shoulder.
Father.
You promised me you would bring peace to the world for me.
Why are you leaving me behind?
Father,
have you met my mother?
I know she never blamed you.
Honestly, I understand how hard it was for you.
But I never got the chance to tell you myself.
Father,
I will shoulder the duty for this nation in your place.
I won't let Fu Chou get away with his treachery.
I will bring justice to you.
You shall not die in vain.
[Dear Wuyou]
Wuyou,
Zhongshan will be in a mess soon.
In order to keep the innocents safe,
you must return here at once.
But I fear for your return.
I don't want you to get hurt...
and I wish to keep you away from the fighting.
What else can I do for you now?
Princess Rong Le, Ke'er gave you two pieces of advice before she left.
You must not catch a cold or burden yourself with thoughts.
And now you are facing the breeze and bothered by worries.
You are doing everything that goes against her advice.
You are just as disobedient as Ke'er when she was younger.
You never talked much before.
When did you learn to nag like Ling Yue?
Princess, the medicine is ready.
Have it while it's warm.
- You may go now.
- Yes.
I have some important tasks for you.
Yes, Princess.
After you leave to get the medicine for me,
do not come back again.
Your Highness, I fear that General Fu might try to harm you.
I should stay here and keep you safe.
The whole manor is being watched.
Even the Tranquil Garden is being monitored.
Once Fu Chou makes a move, you are no match for him.
You might even lose your life.
- But under no circumstances...
- This is important.
There are more pressing matters than protecting me.
If Wuyou received the news,
he will be on his way back.
As soon as he enters the city,
you must give him this letter yourself.
Fear not, I will keep watch at the city gate.
There is another task. I want you to stay alive.
Look after Ling Yue for me.
For the rest of your life, never leave her again.
Princess Rong Le, both Ling Yue and I will follow you to our last breath.
While she is with me, she is constantly in fear.
She never had any easy time for herself.
She thought while she was here with me that this would be her home.
But now, this is nothing but a prison.
I am glad she escaped. I hope she never sets foot into this house again.
Soon, I will die. I might be dead at any moment.
It's my fault for not finding His Majesty and getting you the antidote.
But I believe in the next three months, Ke'er will find a cure for you.
I keep feeling dizzy as of late.
I know the poison is invading my body.
As of now, having three months seems like a luxury.
Do not make it hard for Ke'er. This is my destiny.
That was a lie.
You want to leave this place. That's why you lied to me. Isn't it?
- You should go.
- You can either tell me the truth...
or none of you will leave this house.
It's true.
I was poisoned. I am dying.
You are in my house! Who would dare to poison you?
If my guess is right, the emperor you mentioned was her brother.
Only he would dare to hurt Rong Le.
You take the medicine from him every month.
You must have the antidote.
Tell me. Where is the antidote? You must have the antidote.
Fu Chou, stop.
You can fool Rong Le, but not me. You are the spy planted by the Emperor of Qi.
He won't let Rong Le die so easily. He is in another land, so you must have the antidote.
You can either hand it over or I will slice you into pieces!
Rong Le!
Don't kill him!
Princess, don't beg him because of me.
Hand over the antidote and I will spare your life.
I don't have it even if you were to kill me.
Xiao Sha was working for my brother because he had no other choice.
He lost my brother's trust. He doesn't have the antidote.
He wouldn't have fought back unless you struck him first.
Please, let him go.
General Fu!
Seize this man!
Let him go.
Lay down your weapons.
Leave now. I can take care of myself.
- But...
- Leave!
General, you are hurt. The wound needs to be treated.
I am fine.
You are dismissed.
General.
Yes.
Dismissed.
I assure you. Whatever reason your brother has to poison you,
I will get to him and get you the antidote.
There would have been a chance if we had gotten it earlier,
- but it's too late now.
- I don't believe it.
If I can't get the cure from the E=emperor, I will go to Prince Li.
I'll bring Ke'er back here to brew a cure for you.
If that doesn't work either, I will send out all the soldiers I have...
to search for a healer.
Ke'er only told the truth about my condition to me alone.
The poison is invading my organs.
The best option I have is to extend my life with other medicines.
Completely removing the poison is impossible.
Finding a cure is pointless for me.
Which is why I didn't tell you.
I don't want you to waste time on false hope.
I...
I will never let you die.
You told me...
you will never forgive me for using you and lying to you.
You hate me for locking you up in here. So live on.
So live on. Stay well and live this life.
You can have revenge on me.
I can spend my whole life for you.
The time I have left is getting short by the second.
I don't have time for grudges.
We became husband and wife.
Whether it was for a year or just months, our fate intertwined in the past lifetime.
But ever since the incident at Lake Qingliang,
all I have for you is hate.
But now that my life is running out,
I have one last piece of advice for you.
- Will you...
- I will.
Whatever you ask of me today,
I will agree.
Do you mean it?
Will you give up on your hate for me and put an end to your revenge?
Yes.
As long as you agree to my term,
I will give up all I have for you.
What is it?
Leave this place with me.
Let me have your love.
Let me take care of you for the rest of your life.
I hope you will give me the answer after you thought it through.
Days of summer, nights of winter.
Years from now, I will become a breeze and follow you to the next life.
Ash to ash.
Together, we will leave this world.
Rong Le.
You agreed?
I can agree to anything.
I regret it.
I really do regret it.
If we can turn back time...
If we can turn back time, when I first saw you,
I would have left all grudges behind and left with you.
We can live in hiding. Perhaps we can live in the woods.
We can be a normal couple.
A bridge over that little brook. A land of serenity.
Every morning,
when I see the sunlight shine on your face,
I can't bear to wake you up.
I will stare at you quietly.
And then, you wake up.
I don't have to do anything. I will just watch you.
In a time of peace and free from worries, I am willing to spend my life with you.
Perhaps we would be fighting over trivial matters such as our meals.
Rong Le, will you believe me?
If I weren't a general, I would be a great farmer.
If you weren't a princess, aside from making dumplings,
what other food can you make?
But speaking of which,
I love the dumplings you make.
At every sunset,
we will be holding hands.
Under the glow of starlight, we have each other.
Time may pass, but we never left each other.
Seasons after seasons, year after year.
After all those years, I will have a face full of wrinkles...
and you will have long grey hair.
We would tell our tales to the children.
Those little brats will think of our life as something plain and boring.
But the simple life and peace we have...
came with a great cost.
In my heart, this life is more precious than anything.
As I spent my youth,
we would grow old together.
When we become old,
I will no longer be able to see your face...
and you can't listen to how I say "I love you."
But I think the best form of love
is to be together till the end of time.
Rong Le.
You have nothing to fear.
I can't be with you in this life.
But I have decided...
to accompany you to the afterlife.
Time is running out for both of us.
But I assure you,
in our next life, I will find you.
By that time, you will have lost all the memories of this lifetime.
The two of us can start over again.
I will wait for you.
Even if you can't find me,
I'll be right there waiting for you.
♫ How do we keep living this life? ♫
♫ Finally, I've learned how to trust ♫
♫ But I've underestimated love and hate ♫
♫ We've thrown away fate that we'd received by chance ♫
♫ I have to admit to my mistakes ♫
♫ I regret the one mistake that I made so much ♫
♫ All hope is lost, how do I start over? ♫
♫ I asked for too much, I hesitated for too long ♫
♫ Blame the mistake that happened too soon ♫
♫ You are behind me ♫
♫ Mocking the promise that I made for you ♫
♫ I must give all I have ♫
♫ To accept the lies of affection ♫
♫ It never ends, love will fade ♫
♫ The blossoms fall, and I wait in silence ♫
♫ I cling to the past despite the pains ♫
♫ I won't let our love be a regret ♫
♫ Living without sorrow, dying without any hate ♫
♫ This is the leniency that you've shown to me ♫
♫ We are not holding hands, but you are holding my heart ♫
♫ Although this might not be forever ♫
♫ I've locked you in my heart and I've locked you in my dreams ♫
♫ Blaming myself for falling in love with you ♫
General Fu.
Speak.
- General, Lady Rong Le is...
- I know about Lady Rong Le.
There is no need for a report.
- Very well, I shall let her...
- It's all right.
Dismissed.
Yes.
Rong Le, will you really leave with me?
I do hold a place in your heart.
Chou.
What did you call me?
Please.
General.
I have made my decision. I will...
I am sorry for interrupting.
Rong Le!
- My answer is...
- I hope you can just hear me out.
What you saw in there is not the truth.
I was drunk last night. I thought she was you.
No explanation needed.
You did nothing wrong.
It was me that failed as a wife.
- I really mistook her for you!
- I don't want to lie to you.
Which is why I am telling you my decision.
I can surrender my life,
I can follow you to anywhere you go.
But my heart... belongs to Wuyou.
You are lying.
You misunderstood me because of this.
- That is why you turned me down.
- I didn't misunderstand you.
It was you that misunderstood.
My answer is the same all along.
I was such a fool.
I should have known.
You would never care about me.
You never care about what I do, unless...
my action will bring Zongzheng Wuyou harm.
You only agreed with me,
reconsidered my offer, and came to this yard...
all because of him!
I so naively thought
everything you did was for me.
Do you even remember...
the only time when you have addressed me as your husband?
That day, Zongzheng Wuyou took you by force.
To keep your illness a secret from him,
you used me to turn him down.
You rushed in front of me.
With me as your husband, you shielded me.
After all that you did, I know well enough that...
your only motive is to keep him from having...
the slightest pain in his heart.
Tell me.
How could I not hate him?
If you must hate,
then hate this fate we have.
We can be husband and wife,
but we can never be lovers.
This is not about anyone.
Even without Wuyou,
the outcome will still be the same.
Then I must fight for my fate!
The person who will be with you to the end...
and die by your side...
is none other than me.
For this lifetime, this is where my fate with you ends.
♫ The snow falls on my palm ♫
♫ I just want to gaze at you one more time ♫
♫ I wait for the warmth of your gaze to melt it ♫
♫ We are fated to get hurt from the moment we met each other ♫
♫ I miss you but I can only gaze at you in silence ♫
♫ You are keeping me out with your care
Although we are together, I feel lost ♫
♫ I can wait for you until my hair turns white ♫
♫ I can endure all the loneliness just for you ♫
♫ I will be your hearth in the coldest of places ♫
♫ For you, I am willing to suffer ♫
♫ I want to ward off the coldness for you ♫
♫ As long as I can be with you, I'm willing to give you all of me ♫
♫ In a blink of an eye, my hair has turned silver ♫
♫ I'm fated to live in loneliness without any regrets ♫
♫ The winter may be cold,
but I will watch from afar and keep you warm ♫
♫ I'm willing to wipe away your blood and wounds for you ♫
♫ I'm willing to live in darkness for you ♫
♫ As long as I can be with you, I don't mind... hiding in the dark ♫