[Episode 31]
Why do you keep following me? You are going wherever I go.
Can't you make your own decision? This is not fun at all.
Aren't you just going to gather the herbs?
Your Highness, there is movement at General Fu's manor.
- What is it?
- Miss Xiao just came out. The guards are following her.
That fool.
Let's go.
Miss Xiao, you are going to the eastern outskirts.
How did we end up in the western part of the city?
I didn't mention the eastern outskirts. I said western outskirts.
Did you hear that? Did you get it?
Listen closely. I am going to the western outskirts for herbs.
It's the bamboo forest on the western outskirts.
Let's go and gather some herbs!
Hey, pay for that!
What is taking him so long?
Where is she?
Search for her! Don't let her get away!
Yes!
- Split up and search!
- Yes!
You actually came here.
Of course.
With my wits, I can easily tell you were in trouble.
So, I came to your rescue.
You silly girl, what have you got yourself into?
Why are the guards after you?
How would I know what they want with me?
They started following me after I came out from the manor. I couldn't shake them off.
The same goes for the garden entrance. Soldiers are blocking it.
I have been locked up for three days. I must come out before boredom kills me.
What about Man Yao?
She can't get out. She sent me to get help.
I saw you at the market and I thought you could help.
Nicely done. You actually know I can help you.
But judging from the circumstances, there is no other way.
We must charge right in there.
While Fu Chou is gone, I can get reinforcements and save Man Yao.
Okay, I will inform the princess right away.
Where are you going? Why would you want to go back into that hellhole?
Come with me.
What is taking Xiao Ke so long?
Maybe she has been compromised.
What do we do now?
Xiao Ke was our last hope to get help.
I can't just wait here. I need to escape.
This is still a safe place. You can stay here for now.
Your Highness, you are going by yourself?
Yes.
Wait here. I will find a way to get you out of here.
Be careful.
[General's Mansion]
Prince Chen, what is the meaning of this?
Someone broke into my house.
I have been tracking the thief. I found out the thief is in General Fu's manor.
Stand aside, I am going in for investigation.
I am afraid you are mistaken.
Your house is heavily guarded, why would anyone break in?
What thief would be bold enough to hide in here?
I saw it with my own eyes. I am certain of it.
I must search this manor.
Don't you dare get into my way!
Search!
- Search!
- Yes!
Someone is in here.
Come out!
- Come!
- Let go of me!
Your Highness, we found a girl.
Ling Yue?
- Let go of her.
- Prince Chen.
- Where is Man Yao?
- She couldn't wait for help,
so she got out on her own.
She escaped?
If she is in a hurry to leave, it must be about something important.
Could it be about my brother?
[To Recieve One Hundred Blessing at the Door]
No one is living in this shack.
Why is someone sending food here?
[Purple Clouds Give Auspicious Light]
("Purple Cloud" is an auspicious portent in astrology)
Young Master, have some food.
Fu Chou?
Isn't he on the march with His Majesty?
Why is he still here?
How was his resolve after I left?
Did he waver?
Not at all.
He longed for that position.
Now that the opportunity presented itself, he will surely hold onto it.
Young Master.
He is much more avaricious than we expected.
If he gets what he wants eventually,
not only will he kill Zongzheng Wuyou,
your life will be at risk too.
He wants to kill me? I doubt...
he is capable of that.
Keep an eye on that crown prince.
This is the moment when all of our patience is tested.
Tell him to be patient.
I don't want him to ruin my plan.
I understand. You need not worry.
What's the matter? How is your wound?
It's been years. I'll be fine.
I believe this will be the last time.
Soon, Zongzheng Wuyou will experience the pain I suffered.
It's been over two decades,
over seven thousand nights.
Not a second goes by without me waiting for this day to come.
- He and his father owe me this.
- Xiang Ying?
Lady Rong Le, come with me.
I am sorry but you must hide in here for now.
Ling Yue is still at the manor. Can you get her out of there?
General Fu will soon realize that you are gone.
The manor will be heavily secured. I doubt I can even get inside.
But don't worry. Ling Yue is your friend, General Fu won't hurt her.
You have my thanks.
Please, do not say that. Like I said, your wish is my command.
I will not regret my decision.
After the attack at Lake Qingliang,
General Fu punished me.
He left me at the shack.
No one came to my help.
Xiang Ying?
Xiang Ying? Xiang Ying?
You were following Fu Chou's order for the attack.
But I never thought he would hurt you so badly.
This is too much for a punishment.
It's his order.
He wants me to keep you safe at all costs.
I failed my duty and failed to protect you.
I deserve this punishment.
I have no complaints about it.
But you saved me despite what I did in the past.
I am eternally grateful.
From now on, I shall follow you.
I will give it my all to serve you.
Xiang Ying, did you know Fu Chou was still here?
I didn't know.
He secretly came back and hid in the shack.
What is he planning?
He no longer trusts me.
I have no access to this important information.
Do you know anything about his background?
I swear I will serve you to repay your kindness.
I can do whatever it takes to fulfill your order.
But he was once the master I swore to serve.
The general's past... is not something I can betray for you.
Very well, I shall not pry.
Get up.
I have an important favor to ask of you.
This is the tactical layout plan I found in Fu Chou's study.
The troops deployed inside and outside the capital are marked.
I overheard Fu Chou's conversation with Hen Xiang.
They have an agreement with the crown prince for a mutiny.
What is your next plan?
I need to stop this.
- You want to expose his plan?
- No.
I must stop this tragedy from happening.
No matter how carefully planned a mutiny is,
there are sure to be casualties.
Bring this and rush to Prince Li. Tell him what happened.
What about you?
I am going to the main camp and will talk to His Majesty.
Okay.
I will do as you ordered.
Please, watch your back.
Rong Le must have gone to the south for Wuyou.
Bring her back to me.
If you fail, only death awaits you.
Yes.
Why isn't His Highness here yet?
The court started hours ago.
Yet the crown prince is still absent.
What exactly happened?
Right, what happened?
Crown Prince arrives!
Long live the Crown Prince.
At ease.
Thank you, Your Highness.
I stayed up all night to read through your scrolls.
My father's duty is not an easy task.
As his son, I couldn't do much to help him.
That is indeed my fault.
You made it sound so noble.
You were clearly drunk last night.
I bet you couldn't wake up this morning.
- You...
- Isn't that right?
Ever since His Majesty left with the army,
the Eastern Palace has been filled with joy and ecstasy.
Do you really think no one would find out?
You...
Your Highness, I have a plan to suggest.
- Speak.
- Your Highness.
His Majesty leads the march.
But the army needs more provisions.
The Eastern region was struck by disaster.
The yield is much less than previous years.
All the people have now are the seeds for planting crops.
It's almost impossible to get extra provisions.
What's wrong with seeds?
The warriors are fighting at the borders, they can't get starved.
Besides, my father is leading the army himself.
We will take everything, including the seeds.
Yes, Your Highness.
We cannot let His Majesty and the warriors get starved.
But this concerns the harvest of the following year.
If Your Highness ignores the consequences...
and force the people to hand over the seeds,
I am afraid without the seeds to plant the crops,
we might cause an uprising.
If there is an uprising, just suppress it.
We have thousands of soldiers.
A few farmers can't harm us.
Absurd! How could you make such a decision?
We may have thousands of soldiers,
but the people are the foundation of our nation.
Not only are you going to take their food,
you even threaten to kill them.
You are nothing more than a tyrant!
You are the merciful one.
Then you should get the provisions.
- But...
- Send out my words.
Prince Chen will be in charge of getting the provisions.
He has ten days.
If he fails, punishment by martial laws.
- You...
- Dismiss!
But this is...
General Fu arrives!
At your service, Your Majesty.
I just came back from the patrol.
I was informed Your Majesty wanted me to join the meal.
I was surprised and worried at the same time.
Sir Fu, you mean having a meal with me is too formal for you?
No, Your Majesty.
I am grateful for Your Majesty's kind offer.
We are in a camp, not the palace. Formality is not needed.
Have a seat.
Much appreciated, Your Majesty.
Our priority for this battle is the pre-emptive strike.
We need to be one step ahead.
Our army marches before the enemy does.
We need to hasten the march afterward.
General Fu, do you have any plan for this battle?
I think Your Majesty's plan is well thought.
I went on countless battles when I was young.
I claimed many victories.
I still carry the ambition.
But age got the better of me.
It can't be helped if I feel the lack of strength in myself.
General Fu, you are young and strong. You are a great warrior.
With so many years of experience in leading the troops,
you should be giving me advice on strategies.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, we have reports to make.
- Let them in.
- Yes.
We left in a hurry and didn't carry enough provisions.
We have only left for days.
But the provisions are what make the army whole.
Precautions are needed.
General Fu, write a letter for me to the capital.
Urge the crown prince to get ready.
Yes, Your Majesty.
- Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, we have reports...
General Fu, you may leave now.
Yes.
Generals.
- Your Majesty!
Your Majesty.
Have a seat.
What's wrong, Your Majesty?
Are you all right, Your Majesty?
His Majesty is not feeling well.
- Get the royal physician now!
- No!
It's been a long time since I led the troops.
We left the palace in a hurry.
I am simply not used to the environment. I am fine.
If you summon the royal physician now,
it will draw attention.
The morale of the army will waver.
But Your Majesty's health comes before everything.
Your Majesty was feeling unwell in the palace.
The main camp of the army is even more crude.
The march could be tiring. I am worried for you.
Your Majesty, maybe we should turn back.
Imbecile!
- Your Majesty.
- The army is marching.
We cannot turn back during a march.
If someone had said the same thing,
I would have punished him for disrupting the morale.
I apologize, Your Majesty.
I apologize for the mistake.
Please forgive me.
At ease.
What do you have to report, Generals?
Your Majesty.
Who is it?
Insolent woman. This is an army base, you cannot enter.
Leave now!
I am the wife of General Fu Chou.
I have an urgent report for His Majesty.
Inform him now!
If you delay this important information,
you will pay with your life!
These two strongholds are crucial.
We need to take down these strongholds.
With them out of the way, the Wei army will be pushed to a corner.
Your Majesty, a woman claims to be General Fu's wife. She wishes to see you.
Rong Le?
Why is she here?
Eunuch Chen.
- Your Majesty.
- See if it really is her.
If she is here, bring her to me.
Don't let Fu Chou see you.
Yes, Your Majesty. Consider it done.
Generals, you may go now.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
At ease.
Much appreciated.
Eunuch Chen, keep watch outside.
Yes.
Did something happen back in the capital?
I came here... to advise you to withdraw the army.
When the people know peace and everything is calm, we can still take down Wei.
Who sent you to tell me these?
- Your Majesty.
- The outcome of this campaign...
will decide the fate of Northern Lin.
I planned this for so long, I can't possibly withdraw now.
If you came after the main force, to try what Wuyou did...
and persuade me to cancel the campaign, then don't waste your time.
- Go home.
- That is not what I came for.
There are some situations in the capital.
The crown prince is conspiring with others...
to launch a mutiny while you are away.
Isn't this weird? Princess Rong Le came all the way here.
But she didn't go to Fu Chou.
- She is meeting His Majesty instead.
- This is odd.
Did something happen in the capital?
I bet this has something to do with Prince Li.
If Fu Chou and Prince Li stand against each other,
which side will the princess choose?
Who cares? Our duty is to serve the emperor and win this war.
Don't worry about the other matters.
You are right.
The crown prince is working with someone? Impossible.
I had everything ready before I left for the march.
The Armor Troops stay in Zhongshan.
Fu Chou is right by my side.
The Armor Troops won't make any sudden movements.
The command of the Royal Army is with Wuyu.
Wuyou will secretly deploy the army from the south to the capital as a precaution.
If the crown prince tries anything foolish, he would be digging his own grave.
General Fu is here?
This isn't right.
I saw him in the manor before I came here.
Fu Chou is in his manor?
Impossible. I just summoned him moments ago.
General Fu.
General Fu, why are you here?
His Majesty is planning the strategies inside.
No one should bother him.
If there is anything, please come again tomorrow.
Your Majesty, I have an urgent report to make.
General Fu, His Majesty didn't say anything.
Perhaps you should come again tomorrow.
The military affairs cannot be delayed.
Pardon my intrusion.
General Fu! You cannot go in there!
General Fu!
Get out!
Yes, Your Majesty.
At your service, Your Majesty.
What is so urgent?
What is so urgent that you ignore my order...
and charge into my camp?
Weather Prophet Qin forecasts that...
there will be a downpour tomorrow.
It will go on for two days.
Our camp is located in a lowland.
I think we should be ready to leave tonight.
Before the downpour arrives,
we must find another spot for our main camp.
That is our best option.
We shall proceed as you planned.
Please grant me the Tiger Emblem.
I shall deploy the troops tonight.
Very well.
Order General Li, General Wei, and the other officers...
to my camp to discuss it.
I will see to this matter myself.
General Fu,
you are bold enough to disobey my order.
What do you plan to do with the Tiger Emblem?
You gave me the order when we were having the meal.
You want me to assist you.
The march is tiring. Your Majesty is getting old.
Relocating the main camp should be left to me instead.
Your Majesty.
Please grant me the Tiger Emblem.
You really are a devoted officer.
You remember every word I told you.
Do you still remember when you returned victorious...
after you pacified the skirmish in the south?
We had a tour around the Royal Garden together.
I told you that you remind me of my younger self.
Of course, I remember.
Your Majesty values my talent.
I will remember that till the day I die.
Liar!
We never went to the Royal Garden together!
You are not Fu Chou! Who are you?
Guards!
- Yes.
- Search for the girl.
Yes!
Rong Le came without permission.
What did she tell you?
What made you suspect my identity?
You are right.
I never went to the Royal Garden with you.
But I do remember that you once told me...
you looked a lot like me when you were younger.
Do you remember that?
You...
General, she is not here.
Where is Rong Le?
Where did she go?
She... She is gone.
She is gone.
General Fu, everything is in place.
All the entrances are sealed off.
What exactly are you planning?
Guards!
Stop wasting your time.
All the officers in this camp...
are working for me now.
General Fu, a letter from your manor.
Send out my order.
Split up and search for Rong Le.
Remember.
Capture her alive.
- Yes!
- You...
You...
What did you do to me?
Why do I feel so weak?
I can't even muster any strength.
Your Majesty, calm down.
Fear not.
This is just a special brew from the royal physician.
He used two different herbs to mix into your meals.
It will render you immobile for now.
You will live.
How dare you!
Who are you?
Even if you really are Fu Chou,
I have rewarded you and granted you ranks.
I made you the first rank general.
I gave you the right to command.
I gave you the reward you are due.
Why did you conspire with Western Qi and try to kill me?
That is a good question.
Your Majesty, don't you remember?
You once sent your men after a child.
You are Fu Yuan's son?
Impossible.
That child is dead.
Captain Xiang said the child fell into the river.
Please understand that...
this is known as "rebirth from the ashes."
If you hadn't thought he was dead,
how would he survive?
He would have died.
So you joined the army and climbed up the ranks...
just to get revenge on me?
Fu Chou?
A name of vengeance.
I never expect it to have such meaning.
You are not my son!
I raised you in the Cold Palace for years.
That was more than merciful for you.
Blame Fu Yuan if you must!
Fu Yuan set you up because you betrayed her first!
You are not Fu Chou.
No one would address his mother by name.
Who are you?
You... are as disgusting as you were before.
You are the eunuch that served Fu Yuan, you are Lin Shen!
So, you still remember me.
If you remember who I am,
you should be aware of...
how cruel you were to me and Fu Yuan!
Do you remember?
Now that you know who I really am,
I cannot allow the others... to find out.
Open your mouth. Open your mouth.
Where is the Tiger Emblem?
You...
You always thought... you had control over everything.
But you never realized...
the whole army is now under my command.
Guards!
- General.
- Keep watch here.
No one enters or leaves.
Yes.
Your Majesty?
Your Majesty, how do you feel?
Are you all right? Your Majesty?
Your Majesty?
Your Majesty? Are you all right?
- Your Majesty?
I am bringing you out of here.
Wu...you...
Wuyou?
You want me to go to Wuyou...
and tell him what happened here?
Lady Yun...
Lady Yun's tomb?
The jade...
There is someone suspicious. Search over there.
- Yes.
- Your Majesty.
I am taking you with me.
Your Highness, this is His Majesty's order.
You should leave now.
The camp is under their control.
Leave before it's too late.
You can't escape if you take him with you.
I can stay and look after His Majesty.
Prince, go before you run out of time.
But you will be in grave danger.
My life doesn't matter.
I hope Your Highness won't let His Majesty's trust...
and Prince Li's love for you go to waste.
- Your Highness.
- No, I can't.
I must bring you out of here.
Go, Princess. Just go.
You are out of time.
Princess, just go!
Stop right there!
Stop!
Report!
Lieutenant, Prince Fanyang has returned.
What? Inform General Fu right now!
- I will stall him.
- Yes!
Prince Fanyang returns, who dares block his way?
Order from the general. No one shall enter the camp.
His Majesty is in the camp.
Which general gave the order?
Stand aside and make way!
His Majesty appointed me as the vanguard...
and must be deployed to the border against our enemy.
But there have been some situations.
I must report to His Majesty now!
But someone told me the camp is sealed off.
Not even I am allowed to enter.
Is it true?
Your Highness misunderstood.
It was His Majesty that gave us the order.
We didn't mean to stop you.
Princess Rong Le, General Fu's wife...
came into the camp without permission and obstructed our operation.
His Majesty is furious and wishes to punish her.
But she got away.
We can't find her.
We are ordered to search for her.
- Princess Rong Le?
- Assassin!
Stop right there!
Arrest him!
Stop!
Your Majesty!
Your Majesty, what happened to you?
Brother, what is going on?
What happened here? Who was the assassin?
Brother? Guards!
Who was it?
- Your Majesty?
- Summon the physician!
Yes.
Your Majesty?
What is going on?
What happened?
Who was the assassin?
♫ The snow falls on my palm ♫
♫ I just want to gaze at you one more time ♫
♫ I wait for the warmth of your gaze to melt it ♫
♫ We are fated to get hurt from the moment we met each other ♫
♫ I miss you but I can only gaze at you in silence ♫
♫ You are keeping me out with your care
Although we are together, I feel lost ♫
♫ I can wait for you until my hair turns white ♫
♫ I can endure all the loneliness just for you ♫
♫ I will be your hearth in the coldest of places ♫
♫ For you, I am willing to suffer ♫
♫ I want to ward off the coldness for you ♫
♫ As long as I can be with you, I'm willing to give you all of me ♫
♫ In a blink of an eye, my hair has turned silver ♫
♫ I'm fated to live in loneliness without any regrets ♫
♫ The winter may be cold,
but I will watch from afar and keep you warm ♫
♫ I'm willing to wipe away your blood and wounds for you ♫
♫ I'm willing to live in darkness for you ♫
♫ As long as I can be with you, I don't mind... hiding in the dark ♫