[Episode 56]
Greetings, Mother.
So, you do remember me as your mother.
Take His Majesty and Princess back to the palace.
Man Yao!
[The Book of Mountains and Rivers]
Your Highness.
We found this villager outside the house.
Who are you?
What happened here just now?
Why is there so much blood by the bed?
She just gave birth to a boy.
The boy?
How are they now?
Both the mother and the son are fine.
Calm down. Tell us what happened here.
A group of soldiers came into our village.
They took the child from me.
They even knocked me out.
I think they said something about...
going back to the palace.
My son?
My son? My son?
Do you know what you did?
Not at all.
No?
For so many years...
you never thought about having revenge.
You went against me at every corner.
If I hadn't found you earlier,
are you really going to leave this place for good?
Mother, calm down.
Deep down in your heart,
you never cared about my life.
You know better than anyone...
that my destiny was already decided by you...
before I was even born.
That is all thanks to those who hurt you!
Because of them,
you suffered years of pains from the illness.
Because of them, you are unable...
to realize your vision of unifying the land.
You spent the last two decades...
to stage a tragedy for everyone.
But in the end,
is the hatred finally relieved?
You have to live in the trauma of your past.
Only by reading scripture...
can you have a moment of serenity for your mind.
What you have done...
and what you made me do...
are basically pointless.
I must have my revenge.
But that is not what I want!
I just want her to live.
I don't want to defy you.
My only wish for this life...
is for Rong Le to find her happiness.
I wish she can live on healthy and well.
Please, stop getting into my way.
Stop hurting Rong Le.
Mother,
I want you to hand over Rong Le's son as soon as possible.
Otherwise...
Even you...
have learned to make demands of me?
For years, you bowed down to me as you had no choice.
You never dared to defy my will...
simply because you wanted that little girl to live.
What gave you the courage to defy me now?
I have had enough of this!
I may be known as the ruler of this land,
but you control me like a puppet.
I couldn't have my own life.
I couldn't have love.
You were in love with your enemy's daughter!
Back then, Qin Yong... loathed me with vile words!
If he hadn't alienated my relationship with Zongzheng Yunhe...
all for the sake of that cursed Lady Yun,
I wouldn't have been sent to the Cold Harem.
I wouldn't have been violated by that cursed...
And I wouldn't have been born.
I know.
I am the living proof of your humiliation.
But that was over twenty years ago.
You killed Qin Yong.
Lady Yun is dead because of you.
Zongzheng Yunhe lives in hell because of you.
Are these not enough for your revenge?
If Zongzheng Wuyou must pay for the sins of his parents,
what about the lives that were lost because of your plan for revenge?
How many times do I have to die just to pay for your sins?
In your heart,
was I ever truly a son to you?
Do you remember...
how much I have... gone through and how much effort I put in...
just to make you the emperor?
You seized the throne for me,
but did you do it for me...
or was it for your own deceptions?
I am sure you know it better than anyone.
I think after over twenty years,
all that I have done for you...
are already enough.
I brought you into this world...
I would rather not be born into this world!
Qi!
I am a dead man walking.
My only wish for this life...
is to spend... some quiet time with Rong Le that is not bothered by anyone.
But even this little wish of mine...
is too much for me to ask of you.
In that case,
why would I even care now?
Don't be ridiculous.
You are not dying!
I will figure out a way to let you live.
My days were numbered long ago.
You should know that by now.
Why do you keeping lying to yourself?
Fine.
Stay here and rest well.
Starting tomorrow,
all the matters of the Imperial Court...
will be taken care of for you.
You are dismissed.
Yes.
You are still weak.
Why are you standing here in the cold breeze?
I need to talk to you. Follow me to the house.
It was you.
You took my son from me.
You locked me up in here.
Your son is safe.
Don't worry.
Do you have your own reason for this?
Don't be paranoid.
The most pressing matter now is your health.
Why?
Why must you lie to me again?
When we were in the hut, I trusted you.
I even defended your actions.
Perhaps all the lies you fed me and how you used me...
were because you had your own reasons.
That is why I believed you...
and left my son and myself in your care.
But you...
I can assure you that for now,
your son won't be harmed. He is safe.
I won't lie to you.
Man'er, I will cure you of this poison!
Stop calling me that!
Drop the act, I won't believe another word from you.
You had me locked up because you wanted to cure me.
But when the child was born, you took him from me right away.
You were clearly trying to use the child as a hostage...
to control me and threaten Wuyou.
You said you informed him.
But he never came.
Rong Le!
This is my last request for you, please believe me.
Return my son to me...
or you can stop showing up with your false kindness.
Your Majesty!
Her Majesty asked for your return.
If Your Majesty refuses to go back,
she'll hold the princess responsible.
[Solitary Cold Door]
The Emperor of Northern Lin killed your family.
It was me that saved you... and brought you to Western Qi.
I trained you in this Cold Harem.
If you want to avenge your family,
do as I say and train harder.
Do not leave this place.
Do not expose your identity to anyone else.
So that reminiscence does not linger,
so that sorrow never lasts.
♫ The fragrance of loneliness, the past is dense, pouring down in my heart ♫
♫ The rain is emptying out, a willing tumultuous surge, pouring out into old dreams ♫
♫ Select a pot and ask the autumn wind,
what are the use of vows? ♫
From now on, you will be the Elder Princess of Western Qi.
You will be married to Northern Lin.
I will help you get your revenge.
Was it my goal to seek revenge...
so I willingly impersonated the princess?
Who was it that poisoned me?
What about Rong Qi?
How is he connected to all of these things?
[Solitary Cold Door]
- Who are you?
This is the Cold Harem, you can't just come in here.
You need to leave.
You got the wrong note.
I got it wrong?
This is where you press it.
Then, press on this chord.
- Like this?
- Almost there.
This is nice.
Come on, I have a gift for you.
What is it? You are being so mysterious.
This is osmanthus jelly.
This is greengage cake.
And this is maidenhair cake.
I made them for you myself.
You made these all by yourself?
This is delicious.
As your reward,
I have a gift for you as well.
What is it?
This is for you.
What do you think?
Brother Qi, aren't you a prince?
As a prince, shouldn't you learn to rule the nation and help the people?
You only spend your time cheering me up.
Here is something you don't know.
I am not the kind of prince you would expect.
For me, this huge palace...
is just the same as what the Cold Harem is to you.
It's like a giant cage.
Don't worry, I am here for you.
I will always be with you.
I may be a mere servant,
but I can also be your friend.
Man'er.
For the rest of my life,
you will be the only family I have.
I will be here for you and be nice to you.
From now on, your life is mine as well.
I will do my best to protect you.
Do you like it?
Have a guess.
So that reminiscence does not linger, so that sorrow never lasts.
Let me see if your handwriting has improved.
Your handwriting is getting better.
This looks great.
"So that reminiscence does not linger, so that sorrow never lasts."
It's getting dark, I must go back now.
You are leaving so soon?
I was hoping you could stay and listen to the song I play.
Next time, perhaps.
I sneaked out by climbing over the wall.
If my master finds out, I will get punished again.
Very well.
In that case, I hope you still remember...
we will watch the maidenhair together at the hut...
three days from now.
I am leaving.
Man'er.
"So that reminiscence does not linger, so that sorrow never lasts."
[Cold Harem]
Rong Le, I am taking you out of this Cold Harem.
Man'er?
Why are you here?
I am your sister Rong Le.
- Greetings, Brother.
- You...
What did you just call me?
Brother.
I apologize for keeping this a secret from you.
No.
This can't be real. This can't be real.
Why did you lie to me?
When we were in the hut,
we vowed to marry each other,
we made a life vow.
Brother,
the servant Man'er never existed.
How is a promise with her even possible?
The only person kept in here... has always been me.
I am your sister, Rong Le.
Man'er, this can't be happening.
You have your reason to do this, don't you?
Tell me the truth.
Brother Qi,
I...
The Empress Dowager arrives!
Qi, bring your sister out of here.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
I hope my brother will pardon my rudeness just now.
Absurd.
This is absurd!
You are the ruler of this land,
how could you commit such unspeakable sin?
How long did you plan to lie to me?
She is not Rong Le.
She is Qin Yong's daughter, Qin Man!
I heard your conversation with Lin Shen.
You plotted against Qin Yong and had his whole family executed.
I won't allow you to hurt Man'er again!
I am going to marry her.
No one can stop me from this.
You have grown tough,
how dare you eavesdrop on us!
Man'er!
You ordered him to bring me here.
You trained me.
You want me to impersonate Princess Rong Le...
and be married to Northern Lin.
But you are the murderer that killed my family!
And you,
you clearly knew who I was.
You knew your mother killed my family.
But you said nothing.
Since you know everything,
then I have no more reason to let you stay.
Mother.
What do you want?
Man'er, run!
Run!
Qin Man'er!
If you step outside this hall,
I will kill him right here.
Run! Run!
How could you...
Because of you, he would even betray me.
A treacherous son like him...
will serve no purpose for me.
This is the "Destined Poison."
Either you die, or he will.
The choice is yours.
Run!
Leave me be!
Man'er, no!
♫ First is sadness. Second is happiness ♫
♫ Love and obsession intertwine ♫
♫ Third is passion. Fourth is desire ♫
♫ All beauty has been exhausted ♫
♫ I know that we can't go back anymore.
I know that I have to leave you ♫
♫ Ignorance is bliss ♫
♫ The sound of the bamboo flute from my memory
reminds me of the love we had ♫
♫ When had it changed until you no longer loved me anymore? ♫
♫ I'm the one who made you leave me ♫
Man'er.
You need to leave.
Never come back again.
♫ When the cloud and the rain hear about your life ♫
♫ Even they will stop and wait for you ♫
♫ I can see you turning your back towards me ♫
♫ I weep for the good times we had that were broken ♫
♫ I have so many memories of you but it'll never be enough ♫
♫ The pain is unbearable ♫
♫ Maybe this wasn't meant to happen ♫
Brother Qi.
Brother.
The murderer of my family!
Who was talking to me just now?
What is this place?
Why am I here?
Yes.
Someone just told me to leave.
♫ I'm the one who made you leave me ♫
♫ It's the ultimate goal that I'm trying to achieve ♫
♫ When the cloud and the rain hear about your life ♫
♫ Even they will stop and wait for you ♫
♫ I can see you turning your back towards me ♫
♫ I weep for the good times we had that were broken ♫
♫ I have so many memories of you but it'll never be enough ♫
♫ The pain is unbearable ♫
♫ I tried to capture you but I've broken your wings ♫
♫ This is the destiny that I have no power to stop ♫
[Solitary Cold Door]
Your Majesty!
Your Majesty, slowly.
Your Majesty.
The Empress Dowager arrives!
All hail the Empress Dowager.
Qi'er.
It pains me to see you suffer from this sickness.
As long as you will just listen to me like you used to,
complete this last mission for me,
I will give you the cure.
From then on, you won't have to suffer the pain of relapse every month...
and be controlled by others.
Qi'er,
you have done so much for that girl.
But your affections mean nothing to her.
She doesn't even remember you now.
She sees you as an enemy.
Why must you keep lying to yourself and be humiliated?
Besides, that girl is already doomed to die soon.
She doesn't deserve you.
Mother,
if you try to hurt Rong Le again,
I will even give up my life...
in order to stop you.
Your Majesty?
Your Majesty? Open your eyes!
- Your Majesty?
- Qi'er?
Your Majesty?
Your Majesty? Open your eyes!
Your Majesty? Help!
Help! Bring the doctor here!
Send in the doctor!
Your Majesty?
From what I know about Rong Qi, he would have taken precautions.
If we invade Western Qi now,
he will surely have us surrounded.
When the battle starts and turns into a long fight, Rong Le will be in greater danger.
Jiangdu can withstand seige.
If we charge in there recklessly,
there will be heavy casualties and innocents will die.
Man Yao is still the Princess of Western Qi.
There is nothing wrong for a brother to take her home.
If we openly call for war,
the reason may be unacceptable.
There is only one way to save Rong Le.
Divide the troops.
A stealthy infiltration.
Brother, I scouted the area ahead.
The northern gate is their weakest point.
They never had a strong army, to begin with.
With our strength, a focus attack on this area...
will force Rong Qi to hand over Rong Le.
This is the best viable option.
We will only need a hundred elite soldiers.
They will disguise as common folks and merchants,
entering from different gates at different times.
Agent Wu and the men from the Hidden Ones are there to aid us.
We will split up.
When the time is right, rendezvous in the city.
Very well.
Eunuch Xun!
- Fine.
- Eunuch Xun! Help!
- Eunuch Xun!
- I must talk to Empress Dowager.
We will speak once I am back.
Eunuch Xun!
The food was meant to be sent to Princess Rong Le in the Cold Harem.
But I heard the palace is haunted by a ghost who hung herself.
I am scared! Please, Eunuch Xun!
Send a guard as my escort!
Nonsense!
Even someone as delicate as the princess can live in that place.
You are a mere servant.
What do you have to be afraid?
- Eunuch Xun!
- Send the food there now!
Eunuch Xun!
Come out.
- Why are you here?
- I will take you to her.
Sure.
[Solitary Cold Door]
Sister!
Xiang! Why are you here?
Sister, it's my fault for not protecting you.
You hands are so cold.
You can't stay here.
Where is your child?
Rong Qi took him.
I don't know where my child is...
or if he is starving and feeling cold.
Don't worry.
Rong Qi took your son because he wants to use him as leverage against Prince Li.
Unless he get what he wants,
your child will still be safe.
Your Highness,
I will escort you out of here.
We need to go now. We might be compromised soon.
We need to leave this place.
Sister, exchange your clothes with me.
Disguise as a servant and leave with Xiang Ying.
What about you?
I...
I can always disguise as someone else and escape.
I am not the one they are after.
It's easier for me to get away.
Sister, I finally found you.
I finally reunited with you.
We lost our parents.
You are the only family I have left.
I can't lose you too.
Nothing else matters now. You need to go.
Hen Xiang...
You must stay alive.
- For your daughter.
- He is right.
You still have a daughter.
- My daughter is...
- She is gone.
What? What did you say?
My daughter is gone?
What happened? How did she go missing?
I just returned from Qingzhou.
The foster family that took her in said...
that your daughter was missing.
Xiang, leave me here.
Just as you said, my son will be safe.
You and Xiang Ying should leave and search for your child.
No.
I can't leave you here by yourself.
The three of you, come out!
Lin Shen?
Don't you think this scene...
seems quite familiar?
♫ I don't think that we will be talking anymore after this ♫
♫ We have been through so much ♫
♫ Why didn't I realize it sooner? ♫
♫ My heart was bleeding when I saw you leaving me ♫
♫ There was once happiness as grand
as three thousand rivers and mountains ♫
♫ Although we haven't known each other for long,
I already miss you so ♫
♫ Do you dare to face the possible truth? ♫
♫ I cried when you left, and I keep on reminiscing
about the happy times we had ♫
♫ The regrets that I have will last me a lifetime ♫
♫ After all of those hardships, we are no longer young ♫
♫ I'm doomed to live in loneliness forever,
It's bad but I can't help it ♫
♫ Are you suffering just like me? Are you in turmoil as well? ♫
♫ After all the boom and bust, I have lost all hope ♫
♫ Let's drink to forget our worries, and bottoms up...
for you who have turned grey ♫