I'm not sure if I'm going to be able to do this, but I'm going to try.
I'm going to try to get the best out of this.
Tuna.
Eat some of this.
Snake! Snake! Snake!
This wild boar's neck is imitating people's voices.
We were fooled by it before.
This... this is...
Isn't that a trap?
What trap?
A parrot can learn to speak.
This wild boar's neck is imitating people's voices using the snake's vibration.
This is a trick to lure the prey.
This place is indeed not safe.
Everyone, bring your equipment and set out immediately!
What should we do?
Little... Little Third Master.
Why didn't you tell us to do it instead of the others?
Did we get fooled by the snake?
You're overthinking.
Little Third Master! Little Third Master!
Can you do it? Can you?
The ground and the bridge are all in a state of apathy.
I will definitely cover it with my eyes.
This is a little slippery.
You should be careful when you walk with the fat man.
Yes, Little Third Master.
Be careful at the back.
Let's go.
The light.
We're now at the ground.
We should be able to get out of the well soon.
No wonder it's soft. What is this? A big, soft bed?
This is a snake retreat.
Snake retreat? How could there be such a big snake?
Anything is possible here.
This thing should be the snake I guessed before.
So this snake really exists.
I saw a snake's talisman in the temple before.
I originally thought it was just a legendary snake.
Now I think it should be this one.
Today, I...
will open my eyes.
Such a big snake should be a monster.
I wonder if it's still in the well.
Then if we are targeted by it,
will we die?
It's not sure if we will die.
But you and Little Third Master,
after you go,
because after all, you two are both targeted by snakes.
Don't be so nervous.
This snake retreat is not so fresh.
It looks old.
It's quite clean here.
It should be that other snakes are afraid and dare not come close.
Yes, this is good for us.
Today, we have been waiting for a day.
Let's rest here.
What? Here? In the snake retreat?
Yes, it's the safest here.
Third Master, I still want to go to the cave before to rest.
I'm scared.
Everyone, be alert.
Okay.
I will tell Black Eye to take you to the cave.
You go with him.
I will go with you.
Go to the temple and find Little Third Master.
Leave here.
Be more natural when you leave.
Don't let them suspect you.
I'm not leaving.
You must leave.
This has nothing to do with you.
This has nothing to do with me.
I have a video tape that shows everyone coming here.
I'm still in Ani's video tape.
I saw someone who looks exactly like me.
In the Hermes nursing home,
there is a diary of Aunt Wen Jin.
I have been to all the places in the diary.
Do you think this has nothing to do with me?
Where is Wen Jin's diary?
Give it to me.
Answer my question first.
Okay, you ask.
In the diary, you mentioned three tapes.
One for me, one for Ani.
And the other one is in your hands.
Yes.
Then I will give you the code.
It's the one you and Ani
set up outside the Demon's Castle.
Okay.
19 years ago,
Wen Jin handed the three tapes to your grandmother?
Yes.
Then in these 10 years,
has your grandmother seen her?
I don't know.
No.
Then when did you start to send out the video tapes?
It's like this.
Three months ago,
Wen Jin contacted my grandmother.
She asked my grandmother to send out the tapes.
Did you see her?
Did she see you?
No.
Then how do you know
that it was Wen Jin who sent the messages?
I didn't see Wen Jin before.
I don't know who sent them.
I don't know if he sent them.
There is a code.
Uncle Bai,
Qiao Man can answer Qiao Man's call.
You can tell that she is Wen Jin's aunt
by a code?
Of course not.
I told Zhuo Ma and Chen Wen Jin
to meet up.
I exposed her on the spot.
But,
Wen Jin must have arranged all this.
Only she would come to me.
Wen Jin used this method
to lure everyone in step by step.
Later,
my grandmother said that Wen Jin was waiting for me in front of her.
She gave me another way
to enter the rain forest faster.
I realized that
this could be the last chance to see Wen Jin.
So you believe that Wen Jin's aunt is still alive?
If Wen Jin really is not here,
Lu Xiang Dai would have sent her away.
She must be alive.
But why did Lu Xiang Dai
send us three people?
You, me, and Ning.
Is there any connection between us?
It's you, me, and Xiao Ge.
I know that Ning
must be interested in this.
I also need her material and human resources
to open the way for us.
So I asked Xiao Ge to take Lu Xiang Dai
and find Ning to be the transparent light.
You were the one who got Ning in here?
I just provided the information.
It was her who decided to do it.
Ning is dead.
Have you ever heard of
no protection against rock climbing?
What do you mean?
There is no protection.
There are many rock climbing
that are very dangerous.
The whole process is very dangerous
and there is no way out.
But there are still people who keep challenging.
Some people say that
no protection against rock climbing
is more dangerous than living.
What we do is very similar to them.
Death can be predicted.
I just don't know if it's today
or tomorrow.
I think Ning
understands this.
Since you have made your choice,
don't think about other possibilities.
It's meaningless.
Just like you are willing to sacrifice
for Xiao Ge.
I can also sacrifice
for my choice.
You and Xiao Ge
were both in the archaeological team.
What about me?
Why did you choose me?
I can only ask you.
Do you know her?
Her?
The one who stole the cover.
The source of the tape
means that the person who kept the tape
couldn't contact me.
Or I was dead.
Or she had found me
and I had left this city.
It's also a concept
that Aunt Wen Jian mentioned in the diary.
She also gave us another way.
She wanted you and Ning to separate.
She was also worried about her.
Let me see.
Uncle,
you can see it.
You have to get some hard material.
I can show you the tape.
The point of the tape is not the content.
This is not hard material.
I'm different.
What to see?
See, of course.
Where are we?
Are we out?
Is there salt?
Be careful.
Where are we going?
There's no sound.
Those things are coming again.
Uncle Li.
The sound of the horn.
I heard the same sound
in front of the bronze door.
Uncle,
is the video taken in Yun Ding Tian Palace?
Did they also enter the bronze door?
What's going on?
I don't know.
You don't know?
You always say you don't know.
How could I know?
Wu Xie,
I told you everything I know.
You really don't know anything else.
Where's Wen Jian's diary?
You should show me.
I can see it.
But not now.
I left it in the camp.
I'll show it to you when I go out.
You're lying.
Uncle, I did it for your own good.
OK.
You and I have learned a lot.
I'm sorry.
Go out and solve it.
Kill!
I thought you were a big shot.
You're such a little kid.
You scared you like this.
Master Hua, Master Hei,
I'm a worker.
I don't want to die.
I'm really scared.
Please help me go.
I want to go home.
We really want to let you go.
But you can't, Tuoba.
You're like this.
Once you go out and meet a wild chicken,
you'll die.
Kill!
I bet he can't live a kilometer.
Twenty thousand five hundred meters.
That's right.
After all,
it's a wild chicken's neck.
Where is it staring?
You're angry.
Let's go out for a kilometer.
Let's go out and win.
I'm not going.
I'll burn your teeth tomorrow.
I can't see.
I don't want to die.
You're really not going?
I'm really not going.
You're so annoying.
Stop playing.
I'm still being burned by Fatty.
I'm going.
It seems like we're going down again.
This should be the tail of the snake.
We're finally at the end.
I'm going out first.
You guys follow me.
There's no way.
It's probably because of the earthquake
that the lava collapsed.
Burn the soil.
Empty.
Let's use water glue.
Don't.
Water is precious.
I'll go.
Take the rope.
I'll go down with the dark eye.
What are you doing?
You're not going to dig the way?
Just stay up there and wait.
Fine. You won't let me go down, right?
Then don't go down.
Fan Yan, your nephew doesn't trust you.
He's afraid you'll run away.
You can't be the first one to go down.
If you want to go down, you have to follow us.
Fine.
But the three of us have to be on the same side.
Don't be afraid.
There are dead people inside.
These mud puddles are all dead people?
In ancient times, when building the Daxing Palace,
there were many casualties.
These craftsmen died here.
The mud on the body was buried.
In history, there are such places
near the Daxing Palace.
Come here.
Look here.
This is Brother's mark.
I saw it when I was in the Cloud Sky Palace.
Are you sure?
Yes.
But Brother...
He's not the only one who saw it.
But isn't Brother taking care of Pan Zi?
Why is he here?
This mark has been here for a long time.
It's not from the present.
It's been here for years?
Brother came here?
He didn't tell you?
Maybe it's something he did before he lost his memory.
But he might have told you.
He hid it from me.
This mute is mysterious.
Brother has his reasons for everything he does.
It's also related to his past.
Fortunately, there's a mark that shows we're on the right track.
I think...
this path should be below that path.
The earthquake has loosened the sand and soil layers.
We're going over a path.
Tell the people above to come down.
Slowly.
Fatty, you're finally awake.
Tian Tian.
Water.
You know you have to drink water?
Here, slowly.
Fatty, how are you? Can you still walk?
Third Master.
Why is he here?
What happened?
I'm looking at you now.
Why do you look a little bit like a ghost?
You were bitten by a snake.
Then you were dragged into the snake den by a snake.
We were rushed to the ground by the water.
Fortunately, Third Uncle and the others were nearby and saved us.
Friends are still blessed.
How dare you say that?
You're so smart.
I almost died while I was running after you.
Do you know that?
Just wait.
If you don't lose weight when you go back, I won't save you next time.
What do you know?
I'm Chu Bei Liang.
Thank you, Third Master.
Be careful.
This... this is a dead end.
It should be blocked by the branches and branches here.
Go.
Clean up all these mess.
Yes.
Everyone, be careful.
Don't destroy the cultural relics and get into the trap.
Shoot!
Everyone, be careful!
Wu Xie, take Tao Zi and run!
Third Uncle!
Come on.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I just ran into the water and got into trouble.
I didn't mean to offend you.
I'm sorry.
Come out.
Xiao Ge?
Come with me.
Are you Chen Wen Jin?
Yes.
Wu Xie, wipe your face.
Don't worry. I won't run away.
Are you feeling better?
Hey, hey.
Si San,
you should rest.
I'll go find him.
You can rest for 100 days.
I'll find Wu Xie for you.
So we were right.
It's really you.
But Aunt Wen Jian,
why do you look
not old at all?
And you look exactly like the photo.
Shouldn't you be the same age as my third uncle?
Youth is not a good thing
for me.
I didn't expect you to be this old.
I even washed your urine
20 years ago.
Time flies.
Aunt Wen Jian,
to be honest,
you suddenly appeared.
I really don't know
how to react.
Who said we haven't seen each other for a long time?
Are you the daughter-in-law
of my third uncle?
The person who was with us
before that...
Aunt Wen Jian!
Is it you?
So you've been following us.
Wait.
How did you and Xiao Ge
get together?
We were in the same group.
No.
I just separated from my third uncle.
They met another hunter.
How about we go find them first?
It's too dangerous to go out now.
The gap here is too wide.
It's easy to miss
when you find him and he finds you.
Let's take a break here
and go out later.
But...
Don't worry.
As long as we follow these paths,
we can reach the lake.
That's the end of all waterways.
Wu San Xin and our destination are the same.
As long as he doesn't have an accident,
we can meet him.
The same destination.
So you stole our stuff
and let us follow you
at the temple
just to lead us to the lake.
That's right.
I know you have a lot of questions.
You can ask me now.
All right.
Why did you pretend to be
the daughter-in-law of the main horse?
For the sake of the god.
You're hiding it from me too.
I've hinted at you.
Nonsense.
When did you hint at me?
I...
I was just pretending.
What did you mean by that?
My grandma said
that Sister Cheng Wen asked me to give you a message.
Damn it.
What kind of face is that?
Who would understand you?
Zhang Qi Ling can't be blamed for this.
There are people in the team that are her.
And we don't know who they are.
If we get caught,
we'll be in trouble.
All right.
Can you tell me about
the tape?
This is a plan.
It's too long to tell.
If that's the case,
I'll ask in order.
Why aren't you old?
Look at this first.
This is the scene from 19 years ago
when you went to West Desert with the team.
But I only know a few people
who are involved in this
in the photos.
It's all right.
Just tell me you know them.
This is Xiao Ge.
Yes.
This is you.
This is my third uncle.
Why do you think
this is your third uncle?
This is my third uncle.
I've seen my third uncle
when he was young.
He looks the same as this.
In this world,
not only photos are similar.
People with blood relations
may also be similar.
What...
What do you mean?
You mean
he's not my third uncle?
He's not.
He's Xie Lian Huan.
No.
How is that possible?
I've seen Xie Lian Huan before.
How could this person be Xie Lian Huan?
Your third uncle was with us.
But he wasn't in this photo.
This is the photo.
He wasn't in this photo.
Because he was the photographer of this photo.
Your so-called third uncle
is not Wu San Xing.
This is also the reason
why he would never tell you the truth.
Because from the beginning,
everything was wrong.
He was in the West Mountain Sea
and had already switched with Xie Lian Huan.
No.
You must be lying.
Aunt Wen Ji.
You are lying to me, right?
Tell me.
You must be lying to me, right?
Wu Xie.
You've lived with him for so many years.
I know you wouldn't believe this.
So I thought I wouldn't tell you this.
But you are too obsessed with this mystery.
Even if I don't tell you now,
I don't think he can hide it for too long.
Things have become like this.
There are too many leaks.
He kept lying to you.
There is no way to get through this.
It's too late for you to choose not to believe it now.
The blood on the bottom of the West Mountain Sea
is clearly written.
Wu San Xing caused me to die.
The path is Xie Lian Huan.
You have misunderstood those blood lines.
The blood is clearly written.
How did you misunderstand it?
Write it down as you see it.
I will not let you go.
Write down as you see it.
I turned the blood into ink.
That's right.
Normally, everything on the tablet is written down as ink.
All the
lines are written from the left from the right.
If you turn this sentence over,
everything will be completely opposite.
How is that possible?
How is this possible?
How could this be?
We were then dazed by you.
When we woke up,
we encountered some things that I still can't understand.
Wuling.
We were missing a few people.
Zhang Qilin is gone.
And the time on the watch
is already more than a week after we were unconscious.
And we found that the team has been being watched.
Who?
Him.
Him?
I can't describe it.
He's been watching us.
This is what we found when we were researching the whole thing.
It could be said to be a kind of power.
Power?
After we were born,
in the nursing home,
we did everything from start to finish.
We found that
there were some key points missing in many things.
That is to say, if this thing were to happen,
it would be more than enough for the people we have now.
It's like there's a person who's invisible
filling this void.
But until now,
this person has never appeared.
He only exists on the logic.
So we called him.
This is a power other than the Qiu Dekang, Xie Lianhuan,
and us.
This power has never appeared.
So many years have passed.
None of us have changed.
It must be when we were in a coma.
Someone touched our bodies
and when did they disappear?
So you were born?
Do you remember
the thing we met in the underground of the Gormu?
Is that really a fire spirit?
After 1990,
it seems that it has stopped watching us.
We continued our investigation.
But after Tamdua came back,
the fire spirit started to change.
Smell it.
This smell is so familiar.
It's the same smell as the fire spirit.
This smell means that after a while,
I will also start to change.
My body will avoid the death step.
I will become a monster
from a living person.
I wanted to continue to be a person
who is invisible
and who is invisible.
But I was too afraid to do so.
But a few months ago,
I smelled the smell of my own body.
The fire spirit is our most important thing.
I am its last life.
I have no time.
Tianzhen.
Fatty, this way.
I finally found you.
You are hurt.
Hurry up.
Tianzhen.
Don't worry.
I am the third son of the Wu family.
I can't die.
Wenqi.
You...
Wu Xie knows
that I am the third son of the Wu family.
Don't hide it.
I know.
Your third uncle was at the front
to kill the snake.
But he got hurt.
Is the wound still there?
Why is there still blood?
Where is the medicine box?
Wu Xie, calm down.
The medicine box is lost.
We used all the medicine we could find.
Wu Xie.
I am sorry.
Let go.
Wenqi.
Don't worry.
I am not dead.
Wenqi.
I know.
Lian Huan.
It's not your fault.
You are back.
What did you call him?
Xiaohua.
We haven't found the way to the West King's tomb.
My third uncle,
your uncle,
Aunt Wenjing,
and our ancestors,
they all wanted to find it.
Isn't it?
Yes.
But I need to deal with the family business first.
Sorry.
He is dangerous.
Look, Mark.
You are bad, Tuoma.
You are like this.
Sorry.
I am really...
Sorry, director. I forgot the lines.
Take a breath.
Let me win.
There is nothing here.
Let's go.
I am sorry.
Sorry.
He is coming.
I will make it.
I have such a case.
All big cities in history
have such cases.
I have such a case.
Here it is.
Let's take this one.
Yes.
Come on.
significant
I'm here!
I'm sorry, I'm late.
You're the daughter-in-law of Dingzhu Zongba?
Oh, yes.
The next one.
What the hell.
Who can understand you?
Let me answer it.
Okay.
Let's go.
Sorry, I'm late.
I'm sorry.
I'm late.
I'm sorry, I'm late.
Okay, okay.
I forgot the procedure.
I can't remember it.
Are you relieved?