Yeah!
The legend we once knew
Since it's a big talk
I'm not good for last minute things
My son will give you
a lesson today
Your daughters
Enter your room!
True handsome!
Save me!
Dongshan
I'm sorry.
I called you two to save me.
You two are so annoying.
I'm about to fart.
Shut up.
Lie down.
You said you were going to lie down.
How can I lie down?
Sit down first.
You...
Come on, pull your legs out.
Slow down.
Don't move too much.
We're under the toilet.
If I shake my legs,
will there be any kind of danger?
Shut up.
I don't care anymore.
Give me your hand.
You bastard.
The entrance is closed.
Look! There's a door!
The door should be east.
I don't know if we can get out.
Let's go.
Why is there something so bad under the fire?
Uncle Xiu Ru said this is a scrap shop.
I think it's for training.
This old lady is really something.
Just a scrap training ground.
She almost buried me in the soil.
This is your
This is an entrance.
I think there's an exit.
How about we go in and have a look?
How dare you put me in?
You can't go in.
Come.
I'm going to kill you.
Let's go.
God gave me a pair of black eyes.
Let me find light.
This is the first floor.
I think there will be a second floor.
But why is there no place to go upstairs?
The shape of this room is a square.
I think the house is a replica of the building.
Either a tower or a building.
The face of the face.
This is a replica of the mechanism and the setting of the place.
It looks like it's really a training ground.
We have to be careful.
If these faces are washed into the lung,
It's enough for us to lose weight.
What is this?
A heater?
Don't talk nonsense.
Your heater is not closed.
If it's not closed, it's smoke.
The countdown.
This Huo family won't be able to stimulate him to go to the training ground again, right?
What if he kills someone?
The alarm is ringing.
Let's leave the city.
Look at that window.
The window is exactly the same as the picture.
Could it be that the person who imitated here is a foreign object?
If that's the case, it's too much of a coincidence.
This old lady Huo has long been thinking about your picture.
She's been thinking about you.
This is probably the same place as the sample of the mine you have.
It looks like a training ground.
And it's related to the sample.
There's probably a trap here.
Please.
Boss Huo, can you hear me?
Let's discuss it.
Turn off this prop.
Let's sit down and have a drink.
Let's talk slowly, okay?
Don't you just want the sample?
If you don't show up, I'm dead.
I'm really dead.
Enough, enough.
Stop messing around.
It looks like this old lady Huo doesn't know that we were brought here by her granddaughter.
If she knew, she would have brought someone to kill us.
There's not much time left.
Hurry up and think of a way to get out.
Little brother, is there a problem?
Have you been here before?
Look,
there are four identical pillars.
But this Qilin
is always facing that pillar.
There must be something fishy.
What is this?
Qilin's head,
dragon's body.
What is this?
Green copper, gold, and gold Qilin's head.
Look.
Your pattern on the sample
is the same as the one on the nail, right?
It's really the same.
There are also numbers.
From one to seven.
Could it be
the corresponding floor?
It's possible.
The patterns on it
correspond to this nail.
And the floor above
corresponds to
the pattern on the sample.
Then we will find the corresponding nail
according to this pattern.
Press it.
Is the door open?
What?
Could it be that
there is a time limit?
No.
Don't be angry.
So this is where the sample came from.
Did Hu Laotian push it too hard?
Is this nail Qilin really the one?
Wu Xie, you can press it.
Don't rush.
I have to see which one is it.
All of them.
Go.
I heard it.
Welcome to the second floor of the hotel.
I didn't expect this sample
could be used to pass the test.
No wonder this old lady Huo wanted it.
But now it seems
this old lady Huo
will know we are here.
Think about it.
If we go to this old shop,
and Fatty falls from above,
it's not a coincidence.
It's been arranged.
What do you think this old lady wants?
She wants to trap us here
and put it in your hands.
It's a pity that with this sample,
this old lady Huo
won't be able to trap us.
I think we should go.
Let's go.
Let's see what's in this sample.
This sample is designed to be a set.
During the reign of the Leisong people,
Fan Zhongyan set up a set in Suzhou
to trap the people.
Later, it became
a place to hide the coffin.
It was used to stop the people from dying
in the city.
According to the theory of Fengshui,
Yizhuang is the place of the big brother.
The more people die,
the more unlucky Yizhuang is.
This old lady Huo is really not a coward.
Why is there no staircase in this building?
Ancient people believed it.
So Yizhuang
usually doesn't design stairs
and exit-like things.
He was afraid of destroying Fengshui.
But there will always be some hidden passageways
for the people who are buried
and the craftsmen to enter and exit.
This sample is marked on the thunder.
I guess it's a way to open these passages.
Just now,
you and Xiao Ge were smart enough
to make this sample.
Otherwise,
I don't know how much
I have to eat to lose weight.
The pattern on the sample is large and small.
It's small and big.
It's small and small.
From the perspective of the clay sculpture of the Qilin,
the shape of the roll is thunder.
It corresponds to the nail on the pillar.
I should have learned to draw
and learned some tricks.
I would have used it to escape from this secret room.
I always feel that this old lady
is cheating on us.
Let's see.
How about we try a trick?
Scold her a little bit and blow her out.
Do you think that old lady
is a person like you?
That's right.
This Qilin is in this direction.
This way.
There is a slide here.
It was a moving maze.
But this is still a chessboard.
There are eight doors here.
Pick one.
In that room just now,
the Qilin team is the pillar that opens the door.
Let's go in the direction of the Qilin.
The Qilin team is the door.
The Qimen Dunjia Li,
Northeast,
is the door.
The door is the door.
The Qimen Dunjia Li,
Northeast,
is the door.
Actually, when we were in the Western Mughal Empire,
we used this trick.
I didn't expect that after a few thousand years,
it would still be the same.
Then let's see
if there is anything new.
Let's go.
Let's go around.
What do you think these iron bars are for?
I don't think it's easy to pass.
I don't know.
I don't know if this old lady
is going to be able to get out of here.
I don't know.
I don't know what this old lady
is going to say.
No.
We were supposed to go through the door.
Why can't we get out?
Let's go further.
Luckily, Xiao Ge reacted quickly.
Otherwise, we would have been caught.
How can we get people into the dead end?
Let's go.
You go first, Tianzhen.
Hurry up.
Xiao Ge.
No, no.
We can't go like this.
This place is really a moving maze.
We walked through the door.
What's wrong?
This is a dead end.
A dead end.
There used to be a place that looked like this.
That's right.
It's a place where dead people are stopped.
Where do dead people go through the door?
It should be the dead door to the southwest direction.
That makes sense.
Southwest.
Let's go and try.
Let's go.
Tianzhen.
Wait.
We've been in this maze for so long.
Where is the direction?
Restore the Qilin
What's going on?
Xiao Ge.
You mean the sculpture is spinning?
Fine.
We've been in this maze for so long.
I don't know how many degrees the sculpture has turned.
The Qilin has changed.
They're really stubborn.
They won't let us go back.
You're right.
But it's also wrong.
If this is the original building,
there's probably no turning back.
It's just that this is a model building of the Huo family.
So there must be something we can use.
What we have to do now is to find a reference point
to clearly defend it.
If this is in the wild,
there are many ways.
In this place,
what can we use as a reference point?
Stop.
The Qilin
It's the mechanism of that room just now.
The southwest.
The room just now
is facing northeast.
The exit of this room
is also on the wall of the northeast.
Yes.
So this direction is southwest.
Southwest.
South.
Southeast.
Thank goodness the Huo family didn't put their efforts on the soundproofing.
Otherwise, we would be in real trouble.
No matter how the iron armor moves,
how the waist is rotated,
how the outside changes, it will be chaotic.
The directions of the southwest and southwest will not change.
It won't interfere with us.
This old woman is playing tricks again.
The
This powder will be sprayed for three minutes.
We must go out within three minutes.
It can help us find the direction.
Let's go.
This should be the pillar pointing to the dead door.
Living is dead.
Dead is living.
I think this
Tianzhen, let's open the door and go.
What is this?
Why would the people of the Huo family put their information here?
Isn't this your third uncle?
Who is the little girl next to him?
She looks pretty elegant.
She is not a little girl.
She is a little flower.
Little flower?
I didn't see that coming.
But to be honest,
the flower is quite elegant now.
And this person is not my third uncle.
1983.
This team has not been to Xisha yet.
She is Xie Lianhuan.
What does the Huo family mean by taking Xie's photo?
Put the information here.
Otherwise it is not important.
It is not worth taking away.
Otherwise it is too important.
I put it here on purpose.
This time it is really the third uncle.
It was Xie's family just now.
Now it is Wu's family.
It seems that other families will not leave it.
The old lady Huo has not been idle these years.
She collected a lot of information about the old door.
This is when I was a child.
This is the third...
No.
1989.
It is Xie Lianhuan.
Xie Lianhuan is celebrating my birthday.
Where did you get this old lady Huo's photo?
I will tell you.
This person looks exactly like me.
Chen, you...
You have also got the opposite sex memory disorder, right?
It is the same as Xiao Ge.
Loss of memory and not old.
How is that possible?
I was only 12 years old in 1989.
And these two photos are only two days apart.
Could it be that you have also been replaced?
Is it you?
How can a person with a mask be called a gang?
And think about it.
This person is much older than me.
If I want to replace someone, I will replace him.
It makes sense.
No matter what you say,
you are the only person in my heart.
The rest are all fake.
No.
This is an old fake.
Let's see if there are any other clues.
Brother Wu Xie.
Where is he?
Oh no.
It's a phone.
These are old photos of the nine gates.
It's a life-threatening photo.
Only this one is different.
It seems that this photo was deliberately shown to me.
This old lady is not kind.
Do you still want to continue?
Continue.
We can't waste her thoughts.
She put so much effort into arranging us here.
Just to get the sample.
But what is she calculating?
Where did she get these photos?
I have to find out.
My grandma asked you to take me home?
Yes, Miss.
It seems that it was grandma who arranged to bring them here.
Where are my friends?
I don't know.
Where is my grandma?
This...
I don't know.
The head of the family just asked me to take you home.
I can't even ask my grandma.
Can't I ask you guys?
Miss.
What are you doing?
The head of the family just asked me to take you home.
It should be this pillar.
Yes.
Be careful.
I wonder what this old lady has prepared for us.
Here.
No problem.
It's fake.
And this is a treasure that the Huo family can't get.
The organs of the two rooms before were made exactly the same.
There are no organs in this room.
It's not normal.
Human face turtle?
It's said that in the
Tudong of the harem of the Shennong clan,
there are human faces.
One of them is a human face turtle.
Taiping Yulan mentioned it before.
What does it mean to put it here?
If the human face turtle is real in the building of the Huo family,
it's too hard to believe.
This thing is very rare in the market.
Not many people know it.
What kind of wealth can make such a big human face turtle?
It's not normal for the model to design a table by hand.
In this room, there is nothing valuable except the human face turtle.
Let's take a look at the next room.
Grandma, I don't even know.
There is a training ground under the old shop in our house.
You led them there,
just to get the key in his hand.
Is it necessary for everyone to do this?
Can't we sit down and talk?
You said it yourself.
That's just a training ground.
It's a secret room escape.
What kind of danger can there be?
They will definitely come out.
Our training ground is for exploration and inspection.
Is it necessary for them to go in?
They are my friends anyway.
I can't let them get in trouble.
If you don't let them go, I'll go by myself.
If you dare to go, I'll break your legs.
You usually make a mess.
But now I'm doing something big.
I won't let you go.
I didn't make a mess.
You don't tell me anything and you use me.
If you don't let them go,
I'll sit here and I won't go.
Get up.
Is this your seat?
I'm so used to you.
Go back to your room.
Three.
This group.
I said this is the pattern on the thunder.
It's quite detailed.
Look.
This pattern is a positive circle.
It represents the positive side.
This one here is only half.
The corresponding one should be the side one.
This one is the opposite.
Something's wrong.
This should be the oval one.
That's right.
It's oval.
It's a bit angular.
Right.
Wrong.
So that's how it is.
What do you mean by that?
Hurry up and press it.
No, I think I...
What's going on between you two?
You're so secretive.
Secretary какаяrection?
What's so secret you need?
Why are you trying to get me to say this?
White
And the key to Wu Xie's hand is still unclear.
It's okay.
He's walking down the stairs,
and he handed it to me.
It's nothing.
Yes.
The first two floors have been restored to the ground
according to Wu Xie's actions.
I just smelled something dangerous.
It seems that Xiao Ge has also smelled it.
Something dangerous?
Why didn't I smell it?
You two are playing dumb here.
What?
I'm not playing dumb.
I'm just playing dumb.
You two are playing dumb here.
If it's dangerous here, then get out of here.
It's not that dangerous to say it's dangerous.
It's a legal society now.
Besides, this old lady is also my senior.
She won't act rashly.
Since you're all here,
you can't go back empty-handed.
Although this room is not mysterious,
the statue of the Human Face Turtle
actually revealed a lot of information.
I'm sorry, Professor Wu.
The big logic you're talking about
has already been exposed to my IQ.
The statue of the Human Face Turtle was mentioned in the Peace Preview.
Come here.
I'll give you a lesson, and you'll understand.
Professor Wu, if we're going to have a lesson,
can we go out and give it to me?
Can we just leave it here?
Is there a pen?
Can you write something?
Yes.
You...
You can do this.
I...
I can't.
Professor Wu, stop being so arrogant.
You have something called a bag on you.
Right.
This one?
You have to write it down to see it.
Look at it carefully.
Okay.
You really think you're a professor.
Come on.
Hurry up.
Come on, get ready.
Where's Mei?
Come on, let's go.
Either sit down, or move.
I'm sorry, I forgot.
Either move, or move.
Come on, come on.
Come on, get up.
But...
You can do it.
Come on, get up.
If Lei draws this,
it'll be too ugly.
In the Qimen Dunjia,
the northeast is the door of life.
One more time.
This time, the Qilin team is...
This one?
Turn.
The door has a slide.
Where's the door of life?
It should be the door of death.
Where's the door of death?
It should be the door of death in Xinnan.
Xinnan.
Director Feng, one.
Wait a minute.
The exit is on the north-east wall.
Yes.
Come on.
Thanks to this old lady,
she didn't work on the sound.
Come on, take it.
I'm sorry.
Come on.
This guy...
I'm a man.
Don't say that.
Impossible.
I was 12 years old in 1989.
And these two photos are only two days apart.
Look.
Where are they?
Are you a man?
Grandma, I don't know.
Our old man hid a training center.
Stop.
The next man is...
The one who is in the front is the representative of heaven.
He can summon the power of the evil.
The one in front is the representative of earth.
He can summon the power of the earth.
The question is...
What's the word?
The teacher.
If we're going to class,
can we go out and go up in a daze?
Can we not stay here?
Can we write something on paper?
You're not good at this.