=Spring Rewritten=
(Adapted From "A Phoenix Perched on Wutong Tree")
=Episode 25=
I haven't cleaned up this place
in a while. Have a seat.
Chi.
Father, Mother, Qiuling,
Luo Yu, and Su Ruan.
They all failed to escape the fate.
Does that mean
that no matter
how many times I'm reborn,
I can't change the outcome?
That it might even end worse?
At least this time,
we survived.
But those dearest to us died
for the greater good.
How could we live only for ourselves
and scrape by?
Have you ever heard of this saying?
People only truly live
for a few moments.
And those transient moments
are eternal.
I experienced eternity
in our encounter.
Actually, I've always felt inferior.
I've been ashamed of my background.
And I'm afraid to face the past.
You've done well enough.
Many who've walked through the mud
find it hard to believe in sunlight.
Having suffered so much,
they want others
to suffer just as they did.
But you're different.
You've been through the rain,
yet you still hold umbrellas for others.
Well,
even if you can't face the past,
it doesn't stop you from moving forward.
You and Qiuling showed me sunlight.
That's why I believe in it.
Happy birthday.
I didn't get you a cake this time.
I'll make it up to you after this.
Thank you, Chi.
Eat up.
I've thought it through.
I'm getting you out of South City.
Are you really going to do that?
I lost my family and friends.
The fewer people
who experience that, the better.
And I want Zhou Chi to live.
Sure.
We'll leave tomorrow.
Chi.
If I had never met you,
would you...
As long as I'm here,
there's no "what if."
(Chi.)
(Perhaps it was my obsession)
(that led to
an even more unbearable result.)
(This time,)
(I want to protect you.)
(I'm putting an end to all this.)
I didn't go to you.
But you came to me instead.
Let her up.
Speak.
What do you want with me?
I came to kill you.
Very well, my wife.
Let's make it a fair game.
It's just the two of us here.
Tell me.
How do you want to kill me?
Come with me.
Zhou Chi is here.
I knew you wouldn't give up so easily.
Thus,
I laid the trap in advance.
You think Zhou Chi
can walk out of Yisen Manor alive?
Let him go.
All of this started because of me.
Let him go. Kill me instead.
For the sake of your brotherhood.
You want to save Zhou Chi that badly?
Even if it costs your life?
Fine.
Tell me
that you love me.
You led me on, Zhao Chunman.
Say you love me!
Is that a difficult thing to do?
With the gun pointed on your head,
why don't you say it?
Shoot me to death.
You think I dare not do so?
I never doubted that, Gu Shizhen.
But let Zhou Chi go.
Kill me.
Go ahead and kill me!
Shoot me.
♪The hats, long scarves, and old coats♪
♪In the window♪
♪A letter
left lying on the wooden table♪
Zhao Chunman.
I want to ask you this one last time.
Have you ever fancied me,
even just for a bit?
No.
♪Intentionally asking
for separation and reunion♪
♪But beneath it all
is nothing but reluctance♪
♪Hidden secrets
in the game of hesitation♪
Things have come to this point.
I've lost my brother,
and I've never been loved.
♪Who knew it was already known♪
♪She's so crazy
she deserves to be stuck in the mud♪
Chi.
Are you alright?
Yes.
I'm okay.
Chunman.
I want to go home.
Sure, let's go home.
Chi.
Chi...
Chi. What's the matter, Chi?
♪When the hour hand passes this moment♪
♪Sunlight replays♪
Chunman...
I might need
to say goodbye here.
No way. Let's go home.
I'll take you to hospital.
Hang in there, Chi.
Chi.
♪Who escaped with whom♪
♪The vortex
that confuses time and space♪
Chunman...
Are you okay?
No...
I can't see now.
Chi.
I'm right here, Chi.
♪I'm looking for your dream♪
♪In every time and space♪
Promise me one thing, okay?
Mm.
You must
live well
in this lifetime.
No, I don't want that.
Live a good life.
I don't want it.
No.
Hang in there.
We're going home.
We can head home soon.
Okay?
We're going home soon.
You promised to always stay with me.
Do you remember that?
Chi.
Let's go home.
Let's go home, Chi.
I will. I'll always...
I'll always stay by your side
and protect you.
Deal?
♪Do you still remember me?♪
I love you.
I love you too.
♪The feelings grow even stronger♪
♪I'm looking for your dream♪
♪In every time and space♪
Chi!
♪With the spring wind♪
Don't go!
Chi...
Chi!
=Spring Rewritten=
(Episode 25, End)
♪When the hour hand passes this moment♪
♪Sunlight replays♪
♪When flowers
fall on the roadside again♪
♪It's yesterday's color♪
♪Who promised whom♪
♪Who escaped with whom♪
♪The vortex
that confuses time and space♪
♪Looking back at you and me♪
♪I'm looking for your dream♪
♪In every time and space♪
♪Yet I never catch up♪
♪With the spring wind♪