=Spring Rewritten=
(Adapted From "A Phoenix Perched on Wutong Tree")
=Episode 14=
Sorry,
I can't let this happen again.
(If you don't go to
the Yuchun Theater this time,)
(everything might change)
(and I might be able to protect you.)
I'll be back soon.
(Yuchun Theater)
Move those stools over here.
Come on.
Good. Set them down here.
Chi.
Has Mr. Zhao arrived yet?
Not yet.
(Zhou Chi, did you knock me out)
(just so you could work for Yi Gang?)
(In the previous life,)
(Luo Yu and Gu Shizhen)
(were in the dressing room.)
(This time, no one came for the list.)
(Dressing Room...)
(The list is here.)
Why are you here?
What are you doing?
Nothing.
Gu Shizhen, let go of me.
What's your mission today?
What do you mean?
Is the list here in Yuchun Theater?
I know you're with
the Rose Organization.
I also know
what your mission is.
But even after I killed Luo Yu,
I can't bring myself to kill you.
Why?
Because I love you.
Why can't you be with me?
If it were before,
I'd hold you at gunpoint
and threaten you to be my woman,
but now,
I'm asking you to be my woman.
You say I don't know how to love.
I can learn.
Isn't that enough?
You'll never learn.
Then teach me.
If you're willing to teach me,
I can do it.
Gu Shizhen,
loving someone is a skill.
You don't have it.
You do.
You can try to love me.
You'll never truly love anyone.
Back then, when I loved a woman,
all I wanted was her body.
But I don't want your body.
I want your heart.
You want Zhou Yisen dead, don't you?
I can do it.
Zhou Chi can't.
He's too soft-hearted. He can't do it.
Will you love me
if I kill Zhou Yisen?
Let go.
Zhen.
Foster Father's here.
(Why did she still come?)
Right.
Good.
Watch the performance with me.
I don't want to see Zhou Yisen.
Foster Father,
it's all set.
Hmm.
Chunman,
go home now.
Why can't I come here, if you can?
Didn't you say
you weren't helping Yi Gang?
You didn't take my words seriously.
Why should I listen to you?
I'll explain later.
Chi.
Come here.
Don't make a scene here.
There's an ambush.
I'm just going to the restroom.
You want to tag along?
(No!)
(Everything's back to square one.)
Chi, come here.
Coming.
The performance is good.
Mr. Zhao.
(Someone shot Zhou Yisen.)
Shooter's on the second floor.
Go. Hurry.
Don't let them get away.
Close the gates.
Block every exit.
Quick. This way.
Hurry.
Search every room.
Come on. Over here.
Come over here.
Follow me.
(If we keep going,)
(will we run into Zhen?)
(In the previous life,)
(he came up from this staircase.)
(Zhou Chi... Why did he stop?)
(Gu Shizhen's about to show up.)
(If we can get out safely,)
(everything should finally end.)
Once we leave here,
we'll be out of the woods.
Leave and don't look back.
(This scene overlaps with last time.)
Chi!
Zhou Chi,
why did you have to come?
Why?
Because
I can't
watch you die again.
(Die)
(again?)
This time,
everything should be over.
Zhou Chi.
Zhou Chi!
(I'm in a hospital.)
(I didn't die.)
(Does that mean the ending has changed?)
Don't move.
You need a jab later.
You're awake.
Didn't expect you'd shoot me
over a woman.
If I really did,
you wouldn't be alive to question me.
So I should thank you instead?
Chi,
I've never thought
we would end up like this
because of a woman.
She wasn't the one
who tried to kill Zhou Yisen.
I know.
That's why I killed Wen.
I promised I'd take Zhou Yisen out
for her
and protect her.
Gu Shizhen,
you're such a hypocrite as always.
What are you doing? Let go of me.
Gu Shizhen, let go.
Can't you see you're hurting her?
Chi, are you okay?
Is it serious?
Why are you so shy?
Let me see your wound.
Man, wait outside.
I'll take care of him.
Why are you drawing the curtain,
Su Ruan?
Let me check your wound.
I have something to say to Chunman.
Your priority now is
healing up.
Got it?
Are you jealous?
They've known each other
since childhood, just like us.
Zhou Chi spends way more time with her
than you have.
Naturally,
they're closer.
Feelings aren't measured by time.
Zhao Chunman.
I saved your life.
And this is how you treat me?
I can give you back my life.
Gu Shizhen,
if you love someone,
you don't use threats or favors
to control them.
Man, Chi's resting now.
Thank you so much
for taking care of him these days.
As for his stuff,
I've collected it from your house.
(Why is Su Ruan)
(acting so strange?)
(Zhao Residence)
(She really took all his things.)
(But this)
(doesn't feel like
something Zhou Chi would do.)
Eat up. What are you waiting for?
Okay.
Zhou Chi,
why did you have to come?
Because
I can't
watch you die again.
(Watch me die again?)
(Could it be that Zhou Chi)
(remembers something just like I do?)
=Spring Rewritten=
(Episode 14, End)
♪When the hour hand passes this moment♪
♪Sunlight replays♪
♪When flowers
fall on the roadside again♪
♪It's yesterday's color♪
♪Who promised whom♪
♪Who escaped with whom♪
♪The vortex
that confuses time and space♪
♪Looking back at you and me♪
♪I'm looking for your dream♪
♪In every time and space♪
♪Yet I never catch up♪
♪With the spring wind♪