=Spring Rewritten=
(Adapted From "A Phoenix Perched on Wutong Tree")
=Episode 11=
Bummer.
Stay here and don't move.
If you don't behave,
I'll bring your mother over
to keep you company.
(Zhao Residence)
Where's Ms. Zhao?
I haven't seen her
since I woke up this morning.
Maybe she went out.
Fine, I'll come back later then.
Sure.
Someone's lying over there.
Looks like someone from Yi Gang.
Let's go check.
Excuse me.
Coming through.
Fulu?
Fulu.
Who's that?
Thank you for bringing Fulu back.
Fulu said
if he ever
died out there
and someone brought him home,
it could only be you.
He told me to give you these diaries.
(Wednesday, rainy)
(We've been watching a boy
named Zhou Chi.)
He's got his eyes on the girl
who was betrothed to Zhen.
Zhen, he wants your girl.
Let's beat him up.
Don't.
I'll make him my sidekick.
So we pretended to bully him,
then Zhen swooped in and saved him.
What are you doing?
- Money!
- Let's go.
Are you all right?
(Tuesday, sunny)
(Zhen's been wanting to get us
into Yi Gang.)
(Today, he finally came up
with a plan.)
The two of you
find some desperate guy in the casino,
get him to assassinate
Yi Gang's boss, Zhou Yisen,
at Richard Hotel this Friday.
This is all the money
Chi and I earned from shining shoes.
Whether we make it or not
depends on this shot.
We will make it.
That guy seems to be
Yi Gang's boss, Zhou Yisen.
They're gangsters, right?
So what?
As long as we can feed ourselves.
And they treat their members well
and are loyal.
Mr. Zhou.
Run, Mr. Zhou!
Chi.
(So everything was a setup
from the get-go.)
(Gu Shizhen,
this is who you really are.)
You!
Are you in?
Zhou...
This is my last warning.
My patience is wearing thin.
Stay put and don't move,
or you'll never
see your mother again.
Wait here till I get back.
By the way,
some good news for you.
King of Hearts took Luo Yu's body away.
But don't expect him
to come for you.
He won't make it here.
You're in?
Why didn't you open the door?
Let's talk.
Fulu's dead.
Who dares lay a hand on my people?
Where's Fulu right now?
I found his body by the moat.
I had him buried at home.
Thank you, Chi.
Whose turf is that?
The Big Knife Gang's.
But Fulu didn't die there.
There are wood splinters and blood
under his nails,
so he didn't drown.
Are you suggesting...
(It was you, right?)
Foster Father.
If that's the case, nothing we can do.
We have to be even more careful
from now on.
Fulu'd been with us for over ten years.
Why aren't you sad at all?
We live on a razor's edge.
Staying alive depends on skill.
In the future,
watch
what you say and do.
I need to head out for something.
Do you need my help?
No.
(Is he going after)
(Zhao Chunman?)
You were so eager to meet me.
When are you setting up my meeting
with the boss?
He's returning to South City soon.
I'll make the arrangements.
You seem down.
How do you cheer up
a stubborn woman?
If they're regular women,
clothes, jewelry, flowers, and dessert.
But I'm not sure about
the type you're talking about.
She's not like others.
Regular women just take my gifts
and cling to me.
She gives gifts back
and keeps pushing me away.
What's on her mind, really?
I remember you saying
women aren't worth the trouble.
You've changed.
Did she change you?
I don't know how to love her.
What does loving someone really mean?
Chunman's still not back yet?
No. What's going on with her?
Flowers for sale!
Sir, buy some flowers
for your girlfriend.
Give me a bouquet.
Here you go.
How much? Take it yourself.
One, two.
That's enough. Thank you, sir.
Flowers for sale!
Come here.
This is for you.
Thank you, sir.
Flowers for sale!
(Where are you, Zhao Chunman?)
(Is it because of Gu Shizhen?)
♪Why can we never catch up with time?♪
♪Flip the book to the last page♪
(Why do I keep feeling)
(like I see her today?)
(Maybe I should think
where else I can look for her.)
♪How do I
choose an answer that isn't bad?♪
♪You left me a piece
to teach me to savor repeatedly♪
♪I've watched hundreds of movies♪
♪Still haven't grown up♪
♪Before I could step into the dream♪
♪I was told that the sky in my memories
is about to dawn♪
♪Only fragments of light
are left to trace your shape♪
♪The stars fall on your shoulders♪
♪Paving the way for my fleeting years♪
♪Can you stay for me?♪
♪Will you stay for me?♪
♪The buds of my youth♪
♪Grew into fruitless flowers♪
♪Can you not give up?♪
♪Work hard with me♪
♪The stars fall on your shoulders♪
♪Paving the way for my fleeting years♪
♪Can you stay for me?♪
♪Will you stay for me?♪
♪The buds of my youth♪
♪Grew into fruitless flowers♪
♪Can you not give up?♪
♪Work hard with me♪
Greetings, Zhen.
Hmm.
Are you trying to take my woman from me?
Yes, I am.
You think you deserve Zhao Chunman?
I don't,
but do you?
Pick one. Her or me?
Zhou Chi, if you leave this place today,
don't ever come back.
I never look back.
Zhou Chi!
Anyone who stands in my way today dies.
Out of my way!
Let him go.
=Spring Rewritten=
(Episode 11, End)
♪When the hour hand passes this moment♪
♪Sunlight replays♪
♪When flowers
fall on the roadside again♪
♪It's yesterday's color♪
♪Who promised whom♪
♪Who escaped with whom♪
♪The vortex
that confuses time and space♪
♪Looking back at you and me♪
♪I'm looking for your dream♪
♪In every time and space♪
♪Yet I never catch up♪
♪With the spring wind♪