=My Dear Guardian=
=Episode 23=
Where were you?
Dong'an.
Liang Mu Ze found the tapping device.
Okay.
"Okay?"
We need to retreat right away.
If we go back empty-handed,
do you have a good explanation
for Old Master?
-Old Master.
The money Gui accepted for the goods,
I've received it.
-Did the transaction go smoothly?
-Yes.
Any progress with Xia Guang Yuan?
His assistant, Tang Lin,
has accepted the 100,000 I offered.
She also agreed to provide us
with more research data.
Good.
Make full use of this opportunity.
On a side note,
in a few days,
I'm going to release more goods.
For this batch,
you'll still be in charge
of the transaction...
from start to end.
Old Master.
Any problems?
Old Master, didn't you say that
once you get the formula for the sedative,
you'll be able to come back
with Xia Guang Yuan in tow?
There have been some changes.
The Chinese market had previously been
under the control of Sang Kun and Gui.
Now, we finally found a way in.
I want you guys to expand
on the network there,
find new business channels.
Particularly the youth in China.
Knowing what they like
and their preferences...
is key to securing future markets.
This is T4's real opportunity.
Understood, Old Master.
And you, Zhuo Ran?
Understood.
But as for my mother's transplant...
Zhuo Ran.
Old Master has never intended
to treat your mother.
He's only using her to control you.
Old Master isn't going to save my mother.
Is he?
When will we ever be able
to obtain all the data?
The police
would've probably found us by then.
Not probably,
but definitely.
Ever since the medical forum,
they've already been keeping an eye on us.
So what now?
What do you think?
I think
we should just take the man away.
If we can't have Xia Guang Yuan,
at least we can get the daughter.
You're right.
Doing things step by step like this
is too slow.
Some things...
need to be wrapped up.
I'll leave Xia Chu to you.
I'll sort out the production.
In two days,
we'll meet at the same place.
Commander Dong,
based on the comprehensive clues
we've gathered,
the prime suspect
should be Xia Chu's first boyfriend,
Zhuo Ran.
That man
has had numerous altercations with Mu Ze.
It looks like
he still hasn't gotten over Xia Chu.
So you think he has a clear motive?
That's right.
I've sent men
to conduct surveillance on him.
If this case is indeed related to him,
he should've known
that the tapping device was discovered.
We're expecting him to take action.
(Long Yi)
I've arrived at her neighbourhood.
We'll act in one hour.
What's happening, Lei?
You may go in, mister.
Call the captain.
Okay.
I got the picture now.
What do you want our unit to do?
The two people living at Mu Ze's house
are the witness of the case, Xia Chu,
and Mu Ze's cousin, Liang Shao Xue.
I propose that before things
are sorted out,
they be moved to somewhere more secure.
No problem.
The Special Forces Brigade
can provide shelter and security.
Mu Ze.
Any other concerns?
-Let me take this call.
-Okay.
Where?
Okay.
Got it. I'll be right there.
Zhuo Ran turned himself in.
Yes.
I installed the tapping device.
Why did you do it?
Because I wish to get Xia Chu back.
I wanted to know
what she's doing at home...
every moment of the day.
I want to know everything about her.
To make up for the eight years
that I wasn't with her.
Do you know who that house belongs to?
I didn't know at first.
The day I installed the device,
I almost ran into him.
Meaning to say,
through the tapping device,
you learned that Xia Chu wanted
to give Liang Mu Ze tranquillisers.
So you purposely switched it.
Right?
Yes, it was overheard on the device.
But I wasn't the one who heard it.
It was Long Yi.
He's my assistant.
He was the one who switched the pills.
(No Access)
Why would he do that?
Because Old Master told him to.
"Old Master?"
He's the founder of T4.
The terrorist attack...
that happened
at the medical headquarters in Isaia,
was that T4's doing?
Back then,
he smuggled into Willick from China.
Under the code name T4,
he set up his own army of mercenaries.
On the surface, he operated
under the pretence of trade investment,
but in actual fact,
the things he did were illegal.
What is his real name?
I don't know.
From the first time I met him,
I've been calling him Old Master.
As for his history in China,
I do not know either.
How did you two meet?
In my final year of high school,
a distant relative...
had arranged for my mother
to be treated in Willick.
We ended up at an illegal factory.
There,
we endured a very dark time.
We finally managed to escape.
But we ended up almost starving
to death on the streets.
It was Old Master that saved us.
He gave us a place to feel safe.
He even paid for my education.
So in the beginning,
I was very grateful towards him.
You could say that I relied on him.
Until...
Until what?
Until I graduated university,
he started to let me take over
some accounts of the company.
That's when I realised...
the ugly truth
behind his so-called company.
I didn't want to help him.
I tried to make him stop.
But why would he listen to me?
If you are against his ways,
why would you still work for him?
He has my mother.
I have no choice.
He's been trying to groom me
as his right-hand man.
I've done all I could...
to not get involved in matters
outside of the finances.
But knowing that my mother's safety
is at risk,
I'm not sure how much more I can take.
So you came to Ningjiang...
because Old Master told you to?
Yes.
He wants me
to find Sang Kun's younger brother, Gui.
Then he sent his underling, Long Yi,
to become my assistant
in order to monitor me.
So have you found Gui?
We have.
But I only found out later
that Long Yi had killed Gui...
behind my back.
And on the day itself,
he almost went head-to-head
with you people.
He downloaded a program online...
and printed a 3D gun.
And then,
he sneaked Gui out of the hospital,
shot him...
and set up the crime scene.
What about you?
What was your role...
in all of this?
I'm a victim.
I'm bearing the risks of being found out
and losing my mother...
by coming here to tell you guys this.
You have to ensure my safety.
I no longer want to live like a dog.
This isn't the kind of life I want.
I've had enough.
Even in my dreams, I tried to escape
from the shackles he put on me,
but I couldn't.
Everything I do gets reported
to Old Master.
My mother's life may be in danger.
And Xia Chu.
What about Xia Chu?
He knows...
how much Xia Chu means to me.
Just like how he's using my mother
to control me,
he wants to do the same with Xia Chu.
Use her to force me...
to establish drug-trafficking channels
in China,
to be his accomplice in crime.
I can only try my best to buy time.
But with me...
By myself,
there's no way for me to stop him.
For the sake of the two
most important women in my life,
I'm begging you.
I'm willing to cooperate with the police
to bring Old Master to justice.
Officer Rao.
I know you must be dubious...
about what I just said.
It's fine.
You can verify it later.
But right now,
you need to send men
to Liang Mu Ze's house.
Because Old Master has given the order,
for Long Yi to take care of Xia Chu.
Is there no electricity?
I don't know. I was watching a drama,
and the Internet suddenly stopped.
Hello.
Hi, Ms Xia.
Please come
to the building management office.
What's the matter?
There's a problem
with your house's electricity meter.
We need to check with you
before we can fix the problem.
What's the problem?
What's up?
Something is wrong
with the electricity meter.
No wonder the hair dryer
suddenly stopped working.
I'm going to the management office.
Stay here and be good.
All right.
"Miss Xia?"
Liang Mu Ze!
No matter how fast the lift is,
within three storeys,
a human running
can easily catch up to it.
So if there's an emergency,
and you have to take the lift,
make sure it goes
more than three storeys.
If needed, press a few more floors
to confuse the pursuer.
Anything you find around you
can be used as a makeshift weapon.
If you can't get away,
try your best to go somewhere
with people...
and call for help.
Fire! Fire!
Evacuate!
-Fire!
-Forget about the things!
-Are you okay?
-Someone's after me.
I didn't see his face.
He addressed me as Ms Xia on the phone.
But I never registered
with the building management.
So I'm pretty sure he came for me.
I was reaching the basement.
I turned and ran just like you taught me.
I pressed several floors in the lift.
I got off halfway...
because I thought someone
might be waiting there.
You did good.
It's okay now.
I'm here.
When the incident occurred,
it happened to be the change of shifts.
There was no one
in the night shift office.
Rao Zhi.
Anything?
Li Lei and the rest
are at the basement car park.
The management staff and I
have checked the floors of the building.
We didn't find anyone suspicious.
The culprit probably sneaked out
in the minutes following the alarm.
We'd like to check the CCTVs.
Sure, come with me.
All right, guys. Follow me.
Okay, pay attention.
Thank you, everyone.
Please wait here for a bit.
Go with him.
Okay.
We're sorting it out. Please remain calm.
Xue.
Do you have time?
I'd like to talk to you.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Please wait here.
Yes, I'm at home.
Okay, got it.
Okay.
Xue is with her dad.
That's good.
Did the police catch the culprit?
Who is he?
Why did he come after me?
Don't ask.
Is that confidential?
Yes.
All right.
Xia Chu.
I have to return to the unit
before lights-out.
Your break is over?
Come along with me.
I don't mean anything else.
It's much safer at the unit.
It will be the same as last time.
You'll stay at the guest lodging.
I'll be at the barracks.
Commander Dong has spoken to the chief.
-You're welcome any time.
-Thank you, guys.
I understand.
You're doing this for my own good.
Including your timely appearance today.
I'm very grateful.
Get to the point.
But I can't go.
At least not now.
The ER is short-handed.
If I leave without notice,
it will only cause more stress
to my colleagues.
Besides,
the patients I'm currently looking after
in the ER...
haven't been released to normal care.
I have to follow up
when I get back to work.
As for my personal safety,
don't you worry.
I'll protect myself well.
I'll carry pepper spray with me.
I won't take dark alleys,
won't go to secluded places,
won't simply open the door.
I won't give any chances
for the bad guys to get close.
Is that...
okay with you?
All right.
I have to go to the hospital.
I'll take you.
Okay.
Sun Xiao Mo,
you and Li Lei will split up.
You'll continue to locate Long Yi.
Ask Li Lei to send two men
to the hospital.
Before we find Long Yi,
he's in charge of Dr Xia's safety.
All right? Notify me if there's anything.
Get down here.
Leaning out like that is dangerous!
What if you fell?
I'm already 21. I've come across
countless dangerous situations.
Since when have you come to my rescue?
Speak. What's the matter?
What do you mean?
Didn't you tell Mu Ze
that you'd only speak in front of me?
You escorted me to the police station
so early in the day...
and disappeared with my bag.
I waited an hour here for you,
and this is what it's about?
You could very well be a witness.
I have someone I like.
I'm not asking about that.
But I want to talk about it.
Two nights ago,
you went to Yunshan Tunnel, right?
Why should I tell you?
What time did you go?
Did you see anyone there?
Take a guess.
-Guess!
-Xue.
This is very important.
I don't care a lick.
Mind your tone.
I'm not one of your suspects.
I don't have to be interrogated.
You want to talk to me? Sure.
Resign from this stupid job,
and come to the US with me.
We'll have a meal with Mum.
While eating,
I'll be glad to chat with you.
But here, I'm not saying one word.
Xue.
Xue!
Who is the guy you like?
Liu Ran.
How do you feel?
Miss Xia Chu.
The doctor said my numbers
have returned to normal.
Am I going to be discharged soon?
That will depend on your overall recovery.
Dr Zhang will decide when you do.
What's on your mind?
If...
If my dad could see how I overcame this,
he would be proud, wouldn't he?
From now on,
I will do as you say.
I will live...
for his sake as well.
You can cry.
Cry all you want.
You'll feel better after.
Dr Xia.
I want to make a police report.
Are you...
sure?
This is the hospital's
first successful case...
of saving a patient poisoned
by paraquat...
with supplementary therapy using ECMO.
How long was ECMO installed
on the patient?
Including the waiting time
for the organ, seven days.
I see. Seven days.
Okay.
Try to utilise ECMO outside
of the operating room...
and into the emergency care
of severe cases.
It will be beneficial...
to the establishment of the hospital's
emergency response system.
Xia Chu.
Mr Zhang.
Sir.
Let me introduce to you Xia Chu.
A top student
from the Military Medical University.
She obtained her Physician's License
two years after graduating.
She's completed the regulatory training...
and was previously stationed
at Cardiac Surgery Department.
Her performance has been outstanding.
Right, Dr Chen?
Now at the ER,
she played a part in rescuing Liu Ran.
I know her.
For the past two weeks,
I've been conducting
experiential research...
on the various departments
at the hospital.
I bumped into her one time.
That day, she was totally drenched.
She was pulling a cooler box
containing an organ for transplant,
running towards the operating room.
Do you remember?
So that was you.
That's right.
This young lady looks gentle and meek,
but when carrying out her duty,
she's full of vigour.
You know how things are at this hospital.
Over here, women are treated like men,
men are treated like livestock.
You joke.
She's always the one going the distance.
Sir, you're exaggerating.
I am just carrying out my duty, is all.
Yes, good.
Let's go and check on the patients.
Okay. See you.
See you.
During lunch break,
come see me in my office.
You're still here.
Yeah.
If the 4S shop calls, go and get the car.
You're asking me to drive?
You need practice.
It's a necessary life skill.
Next time, you can run faster.
Okay.
I'm off then.
Liang Mu Ze.
From a professional standpoint,
I am considered half your comrade.
I know the meaning
of the military uniform to you.
In one's life,
how much they earn,
what kind of house they own,
what car they drive,
those are all done for others.
There's only one thing...
What kind of person you wish to become
is done for yourself.
Staying true to oneself is hard.
Perhaps it's a life-long lesson
we continue to master.
I am still a newbie.
So I'm sorry.
I can't give you better advice.
But I'd like you to know...
that your decisions are always right,
Captain Liang.
I believe...
Liang Mu Ze, this is the hospital.
You asked me before...
if anyone's habit is found in my life.
You said no.
Not at that time.
But now, I'm telling you
I'm learning to eat durian.
I'm learning to omit the salt
when cooking soup.
I've gotten used to your taste buds.
I remember what you said about the heart
being on top of the stomach.
I no longer want to be even with you,
Dr Xia.
If you insist on getting even,
the next time we meet,
you can ask for it then.
Are you confessing your feelings
right now?
Will you say yes?
I have work to do.
I need to get back to it.
(Ultrasonography room)
(CT room)
If the incident made you realise
my importance...
You're important.
But not because of the incident.
This is what I've been wanting
to tell you.
I like you too, Liang Mu Ze.
Although you're proud and snarky,
always wanting to win,
your intelligence and honesty
make me feel safe.
But most importantly,
you've got a good-looking face.
Thanks.
Especially when you smile.
It's like the desserts you make.
It's rare,
but every time it's filled with warmth.
Living under the same roof
with such a guy,
after some time,
pink bubbles naturally emerged
in my heart.
I feel like I'm the female lead
in an idol drama.
I've even fantasised many times...
about the moment when the two of us
took things off the screen.
You did?
Yes.
Especially yesterday.
You kissed me for the first time.
It was the climax of all my fantasies.
If you had professed your love to me then,
I would've agreed without thinking.
But now...
I know you're getting transferred.
To be honest,
I hate goodbyes.
I don't like being left behind.
Because when the distance is too large,
you'll lose sight of it forever.
You may think my worries are ambivalent,
but they are my honest thoughts
at this moment.
I need time, Liang Mu Ze.
I need to think this through,
whether or not I have the courage
to be in such a relationship.
Can I?
Take your time.
I'll wait.
♫Exchanging everything
We'll become each other's destiny♫
♫I'll make your heart my kingdom♫
♫You and I will make our dream
Come true with our lives♫
No way.
Listen.
I've seen too many long-distance marriages
that most often ended up broken.
A long-distance relationship
not only puts a strain on time and money,
more importantly,
it tests one's character and dedication.
We are already stretched thin at work.
So why choose Hard Mode
in our relationships?
A companion.
It's not a companion
if they can't keep you company.
Spiritual companionship counts, right?
Spiritual?
Do you raise the next generation
with your spirit?
This scene needs voice-over.
Note it down.
Okay.
Don't be silly, girl.
If marriage is the grave of love,
then becoming a widow
is the abyss of hell.
Either he stays or you resign.
Otherwise, be prepared to eat
and shop alone,
celebrate festivals alone,
go for prenatal check-ups
and give birth alone,
handle both parents alone,
and endure a pitiful life
with no one to share your ups and downs.
I don't think it's as bad
as having to use the word "pitiful."
Of course it is.
Think about it.
Your "love rival" is our beloved nation.
Is your land bigger?
Do you have more people?
How can you compare?
Right.
What you said is true.
It's an undeniable fact.
But when he brought it up,
I couldn't turn him down.
Not only did you not turn him down,
you went ahead and divulged
your innermost thoughts, didn't you?
I'm dumb, aren't I?
Dumb and naive.
Would you have done that?
Me?
I'm even more dumb.
Because of Zhuo Ran?
Aren't things going well with you two?
Go and transfer yesterday's B-rolls
into here.
Okay.
Two days ago,
we were supposed to go and watch a movie.
But he said he was busy.
Where did he go?
Supposedly for work.
Anyway, the date was cancelled.
I haven't heard from him since.
Work?
What is it?
Nothing.
Yeah, it's nothing.
In a relationship,
it's either mutually showing love,
or mutually giving or getting hurt.
We're adults, not some young kids.
I'm fine with any outcome.
Anyway,
it's not like I have no suitors.
It doesn't have to be him, right?
If it really came down to...
If I really had to let go,
promise me you'd drink with me then.
Drink until we puke.
Drink until we pass out cold.
All right?
Mi Gu.
The fact that I'm living
at Liang Mu Ze's house,
did you ever mention it to Zhuo Ran?
No, I didn't.
Why do you ask?
Xia Chu.
You're living with that kind of man.
Aren't you afraid?
How did you know?
Mi Gu.
She told me.
Hello?
It's nothing. I'll leave you be.
Bye-bye.
Miss Gu, the producer wanted me
to remind you of the requests.
(Liu Song)
At the hallway today,
Mr Zhang specifically introduced her
to the visiting head of the inspection.
That's right.
Director Chen didn't look too amused.
Mr Zhang did a splendid job
during the operation,
so Director Chen couldn't say anything.
Seems like Xia Chu was the most beautiful.
She even charmed Mr Zhang's soul away.
She deserves it.
Doesn't she?
Sorry, guys.
Mr Zhang asked me to come.
I overheard your discussion just now.
Sounded like I was the main star.
It was probably not the first time,
nor will it be the last.
Firstly, I'm thankful that you all approve
of my looks.
I know, I am quite the looker.
There's no doubt about that.
Secondly,
Mr Zhang introduced me to the head...
not because I am pretty.
It's because I was involved with
Liu Ran's treatment from start to end.
I was the one who convinced her uncle
to install the ECMO.
I was also the one
who delivered the lung for transplant...
from the airport to the operating room.
While you guys are busy chit-chatting,
I was in the EICU,
staying by the patient's side
through nights on end,
up until today when the ECMO was removed.
My effort should be remembered.
Lastly,
I'd like to share my favourite motto
with you all as an encouragement.
Being professional and reliable...
is the most cost-effective form
of socialising.
Let's work hard together.
All right. I should head back to the ER.
By the way,
please inform Dr Zhang when he's here
that I dropped by.
Next, let's welcome the President
of Ningjiang's Hospital Association...
who was also our former dean,
Mr Zhang Li Fu, to brief us on his work.
Let's welcome him.
I'm glad to be here.
During the inspection,
I've seen a lot, and heard a lot.
But the thing that impressed me
the most is...
that resident doctor named Xia Chu.
Take a look.
This is a photo I took by chance
of her back.
In this photo,
I can see the most invaluable character
a young doctor should have.
Simple.
Pure.
You could say that she's bordering
on naivety.
But I believe...
that it's the same naivety
that has allowed her...
to bravely speak her mind.
To fight for the patient
with good reason.
She refused to become a vassal
for the more senior doctors.
Amidst the challenging
medical ethics environment,
she abided
by a doctor's code of conduct.
Such a cute heart.
All better.
We often talk about good hospitals...
and good doctors.
What does "good" entail?
Aside from having
the best medical technology,
most advanced equipment...
and a huge number of case samples,
-I think a good hospital...
-Get ready 200 joules...
is not solely defined by
the responsibility and care for patients,
but more so the way
we treat the young doctors.
The bigger the hospital,
the more it should provide space
for young doctors to grow...
and opportunities to improve.
Please remember this.
An industry without young blood
is one without prospects.
That is the reason why I decided...
to share this photo with everyone today.
So, being straightforward...
and not having to compromise
feels pretty good.
♫I had a quick glance at your eyes♫
♫It could be the destiny
But it is not practical♫
♫Your expression popped up on my mind♫
Still reminiscing about my confession?
♫I learn to face the music
Instead of evading it♫
You're thinking too much.
Drive safe. No need to reply.
♫If I can't predict the future
I'll leave it up to fate♫
♫I can't remember
When I fell in love with you♫
♫I am afraid
That I might lose you one day♫
♫Every minute, every second
How do I resist?♫
♫I can't help but look forward
To your return♫
♫Replaying the moment I fell in love♫
Is Xia Chu okay?
Have you had lunch?
Where's the coffee?
Just make do with that.
She being fine doesn't mean you're fine.
Worry about yourself instead.
Regarding the tapping device,
I'm willing to bear the responsibility.
And the rest?
The rest?
-The rest of what?
-Why did Long Yi target Xia Chu?
That's Old Master's order.
-Why did Old Master give that order?
-I don't know.
What exactly is your relationship
with Old Master?
I've told you everything.
In spite of the threats
from the evildoers,
I've come clean about my mistake.
I turned myself in,
and am cooperating with you.
I'm not hoping for any recognition.
I just want to be reunited with my mother.
If you don't believe me,
go ahead and verify it.
But you better do it quickly.
Time is ticking.
Of course we'll verify it
as soon as possible.
Since you are so willing
to cooperate with us...
and have provided us with important clues,
we will ensure your personal safety.
So, I hope you don't mind...
spending the night
at the detention centre.
Certainly, Officer Rao.
What are you doing here?
I came to visit the parrot.
Get in.
You get off.
Roger that.
Everyone, ready to deploy parachutes.
Stand up. Clip on the snap hook.
I don't understand.
Why is his job more important to him
than family?
Catching criminals is more important
than his daughter's happiness.
He's trying to destroy my confidence
towards men, love and marriage.
He hasn't had a wink of sleep
in three days, Xue.
Why is that my problem?
I don't care.
He asked for it himself.
He's forgotten that he's a husband
first and foremost,
and a father next,
and a police officer last.
Tell me then.
What about the way you express your
feelings so heatedly and aggressively?
I did not.
Xue.
He is your birth father.
Right?
Just because he doesn't show his emotions
as openly as you,
doesn't mean you're not important.
I'm not important.
He's just cold-blooded.
Are you all right?
Tian Yong!
Are you okay?
-Yeah.
-You should be ashamed.
You're an experienced paratrooper
but still got caught in a tree?
It's not his fault.
He was trying to help the new recruit
open the parachute.
That's why he drifted off course.
Are you okay?
Reporting, sir!
I can still jump!
You're still going to jump?
Look at the state you're in!
I'm fine.
Help him. Quick!
Get him to the infirmary.