[Boys Be Brave!]
Who cares about the type?
I should've told him I liked him.
[Study for certification]
[Gi Seop]
I was too late again
and I'm all alone now.
I'm going back to how I used to be.
To my lonely self before I liked Jeong Gi Seop.
[Episode 6
Realizing your feelings and confessing]
All good now.
Bye.
Okay. Bye.
You pretended?
You seem fine.
Go now.
Okay.
Look who is here.
Hi.
About time, isn't it?
I'm not feeling well.
Seriously, what's up with this?
Where have you been
and what have you been doing these days?
You've got a lot alarms recently
and you didn't come home or go to the doctor.
I was at Jin Woo's.
At Balgeum's?
No.
Not Balgeum? Then which friend?
You don't know him.
What's wrong with you?
Gi Seop, tell me what's wrong. Come on.
I'm just not feeling well.
Were you not feeling well
at that friend's place the whole time?
Stay still.
Ouch!
My heart just started beating faster.
I'll get some medicine.
I must've been.
I must've been unwell the whole time.
You seemed okay for a while.
I should've paid more attention.
Stop by at the school first.
You know what you need to do there, right?
Why do I have to go to the school?
Stop goofing around.
We have less than 15 days left
before going to the US.
Go get the documents
that I told you about from the school.
I'll pick you up from school.
Let's go see a doctor.
The US?
Listen to you.
Gosh. The US?
Seriously, did something happen?
[Today's to-do list]
[Recruitment Briefing Session for International
and Exchange Students to the US]
[2024 Study Abroad Guide]
The person in charge is on the phone,
so you have to wait a little.
Please have a seat and wait.
[Immigrating to the US]
Hey, do you remember this day?
You and Kim Jin Woo are in it. Wow, hilarious.
I've got something to say to you.
Let me tell you now.
I wonder why I wasn't brave enough
to ask you out.
Go for it.
I like you. Would you like to go out with me?
Accept. Accept.
[He's looking at someone so romantically.
But who is he looking at?]
I've seen
this gaze a lot somewhere.
It's the way you look at someone
you like!
I like him.
Okay, Mr. Jeong Gi Seop. Mr. Jeong Gi Seop.
He… He
likes him, right?
Do you? Do you like him?
I'm not capable of liking anyone,
but maybe I like him.
Yes, if you like him that much,
you should tell him.
I'm going now.
Are you Mr. Jeong Gi Seop
who wants to discuss studying abroad?
- Let's get started right away.
- I'm sorry.
Please excuse me.
I'm the type that never says "no,"
but I have to confess my feelings to someone.
I need to go. I'm sorry.
But we can
get started right away.
You won't be loved by anyone.
So in the end, you won't be loved by anyone.
I don't care if no one loves me in the end.
The important thing is
the fact that I like Kim Jin Woo.
Kim Jin Woo.
The subscriber you are calling
is not available…
What's going on?
Who are you?
What about you?
I'm Jeong Gi Seop.
What?
What's your problem?
I don't know who you are,
but you can't just come into Jin Woo's place.
Jin Woo?
Oh! You're
Jin Woo's friend, right?
Yes.
I see.
Seriously, who are you?
I own this place, you punk.
Got that?
I see. Okay. Hello.
Yes, hello. Nice to meet you.
Did something happen to Jin Woo?
Sorry?
His father kept calling me
saying he couldn't reach him. Gosh.
It doesn't look like
he came home last night, either.
Do you know where he is?
He never does that.
Tell me about it. Gosh.
Hello?
Yes. Go ahead.
Okay, one moment please. Answer it.
- Who is it?
- Jin Woo's father.
- His father?
- Talk to him.
He wants to talk to you.
Hello? My name is Jeong Gi Seop… Pardon?
Sorry?
Why aren't you coming?
What is he talking about?
Hello?
Yes, hello?
Hey, I'm at the theater. Where are you?
Really? I'm on the fourth floor
at the entrance of Cinema Six. Do you see me?
What?
But the entrance to Cinema Six
is on the second floor.
No way. Hold on.
I'm sorry. I'll be right there.
They have Seogyeong
and Seogyeong Jungang locations.
I mistakenly came to Seogyeong Jungang instead.
I'll send you the reservation,
so start watching first. I'll be right there.
No, I'll just wait for you here.
It's okay. Just start watching it first.
Should we cancel this one
and reserve the next one?
No, don't. I said just go in first.
No, it's okay to just cancel it
and reserve the next one.
What are you doing out here?
I told you that I would wait for you.
What about the movie?
I couldn't cancel it,
so I just reserved the next one.
Did you sprint here?
Let's take our time.
Aren't you thirsty?
Should we get a soda and popcorn too?
Okay.
Which popcorn flavor do you like?
I'll buy. Let's go.
[Jeong Gi Seop, I'm on my way to Hoengseong now.
I have something to tell you when I meet you.]
[Jeong Gi Seop missed call]
Hello?
Sorry?
Jeong Gi Seop is on his way to our house,
you mean, to Hoengseong?
The subscriber you are calling
is not available…
It's still powered off.
I'm sorry about earlier.
I don't know why I got the location mixed up.
Gosh, why did I do that?
It's nice to take a walk like this.
We're almost at the restaurant.
It's right around the corner.
Okay. Let's take a walk again after we eat.
Aren't you going to be cold?
You're by my side.
Wow, the ambiance is great.
Do you think so? I'm glad.
Hello. May I take your order, please?
Well, what would you like to eat?
This one.
One is enough?
Yes.
Let's also order these two.
Okay.
We'll order these three. Anything to drink?
Can we also have these two?
Okay. We'll bring them right away.
You did that last time too.
You ordered a lot again.
Eat them up.
If we get sleepy after eating again,
should we just stay here?
That's a bit…
I need to use the restroom.
Okay.
[Coupon 80,000 won]
Weren't you using the restroom?
I stepped out for a second.
It's my gift to you.
Thanks so much for everything today.
A gift?
I got another one when I was buying mine.
You can't really check your messages
when you're doing your part-time work.
I want to check your messages right away too.
I asked a nearby place to hold it for me,
so that I can surprise you.
Your food is ready.
Balgeum, it looks delicious. Let's enjoy it.
Enjoy your food.
Are you okay? Is something going on?
I never asked you for this.
Come on. I just wanted you to have it--
I don't need things like this.
You barely ate anything.
My stomach feels a little funny.
- Shall we go now?
- Okay.
Please charge this card.
That would be 83,000 won.
Pardon?
Isn't it 79,000 won?
You ordered three dishes and two drinks.
So the total is 83,000 won.
No way.
Can I see your menu again? I'm sure--
One moment.
Please use this one.
But I'm sure I saw it correctly.
Thank you for the food.
I really enjoyed it, Balgeum.
Choi Balgeum.
We finished eating too quickly.
Where should we go next?
Do you want to go get a drink?
We never had a drink together.
I looked up a bar nearby
and it had a good ambiance.
You don't feel like going to a bar?
Then should we just go home?
We can just get some drinks
from a convenience store and drink at home--
Shouldn't you go home?
What?
You didn't quit piano, right?
When are you going back?
You should go back to your house, not mine.
Should I quit piano
and just stay here with you?
- I like the way things are now--
- No.
I don't like the way things are now. Go back.
Sorry. I'll get going first.
Choi Balgeum.
Let's just end this.
What's the matter with you today?
It's not just today.
I knew it wouldn't work from the beginning.
I shouldn't have started it.
Is it because I didn't go ahead
and watch the movie first?
Or because I can't eat much?
If not, because of the gift?
Just tell me and I'll change.
I'll do as you say.
It's not like that.
Then what is it?
How would I know if you don't tell me?
I can't just let you go again like this
without even knowing why.
It's because I feel ashamed.
I feel ashamed that I'm broke
and that my family has become poor.
I'm struggling to earn
a meager income to be with you
and to spend a day together.
But I'm even ashamed to be happy for a second
when I received an expensive gift.
It was the same back then.
I was ashamed that my family had become poor.
That was the reason.
Ji In Ho.
I still like you.
I lied when I said I didn't like you.
I still like you so much,
but I really hate myself.
I really hate myself for being like this.
Choi Balgeum.
I hate myself even more when I'm with you.
Even this moment.
So…
So, please. Let's just end it here.
[Hoengseong]
[Jeong Gi Seop]
The subscriber you are calling
is not available…
[Jeong Gi Seop]
Hello?
Where are you now?
How did you get in touch with my father
and how did you know to come here?
Left.
What?
I'm right by you.