[English subtitles are available]
Timeless Love Season 2
[All my pride collapses when you’re in front of me. “Lowliness”]
Episode 20
[Profile of Jiang Dian]
You came here.
That’s a big step you took.
Dr. Xie,
do you have any drugs which can help me control myself?
According to your condition,
drugs can only be of little help.
The key is
believing that you deserve to be loved.
When you grow up, if there’s
no return for your love for a long time,
you’ll feel sad,
angry, hopeless and start to deny yourself.
The self-denial
will be buried in your mind.
One day when you
love someone for real again,
in order not to be sad,
you tend to
deny yourself first.
So when you suffer a setback,
you never give up easily.
However, after you fall in love,
because you’re afraid of losing her,
you’ll tend to work hard,
get worried
and doubt about yourself constantly.
When you can’t control yourself,
look at the one who you love
and do not think about anything.
Just look into her eyes.
You’ll find yourself.
But I can’t accept that
there’s another guy in her eyes,
even if they’re already done.
I understand what you said, but I
can’t control myself. I...
Sorry.
Jiang Dian,
do you think the starry sky is beautiful?
Do you think the brightest star
will still be shinning as before
when other stars are all gone?
Stubbornness can make you
become perfectly strict with love.
To any kind of possession,
no matter it’s a good one or a bad one,
you just can’t accept it.
Think about the sky.
The brightest star
can definitely make others appear to be dark.
If you don’t believe me,
just look into her eyes.
Sorry, I got a phone call.
Hello.
OK. I’ll be right there.
Dr. Xie,
please help me...
Help me hide
my medical records.
Don’t worry.
Your medical records
are strictly confidential here.
No one will
know you’ve been here.
Thank you.
Taking your medications on time
can stabilize your medical condition.
Thanks.
I gotta go.
He could have told his girlfriend,
but he chose to keep it secret.
Why?
[New Song Release Party]
Today I’m very happy.
Thank you for attending
my release party.
Thanks.
Look here.
Please look here. Thank you.
Look at the camera. Thank you.
Thanks.
Smile.
Thank you so much for coming here today.
I will...
Cheng Feng is here! Cheng Feng is here!
Look at the camera. Thank you.
- OK. Thank you. - Thanks.
Thank you all,
but my boyfriend is not a star.
Please do not take pictures of him. Thank you.
I’ve prepared some food and drinks for you.
By the way, Zhou Yao has
prepared some gifts for you.
Follow me, please.
There are gifts.
Let’s go.
Hi, Chengcheng.
I took my boyfriend here.
Do you mind?
Of course not.
No matter if you mind or not,
do not call my girlfriend by
her nickname in public.
It’s not appropriate.
What my boyfriend means
is also what I mean.
Please take a seat.
Good job, Dian.
Everyone is shocked.
Some people
may think
it’s the engagement party of Cheng and you.
Great.
You’re here to shock everyone.
Baoling,
I already said the same words.
Dian,
let’s get a drink there.
What you wear is fancy.
You’re here to steal the show.
No.
I just want to announce that Dian is my boyfriend
to make him feel secure.
I know you’re in love,
but you don’t have to
provoke others this way.
Then try to provoke me.
Are you gonna keep hiding from him?
He doesn’t like me.
That’s it.
It’s OK.
I know you’re always assertive,
but please don’t get hurt.
It’s Zhou Yao’s celebratory party,
but it was held by the company.
By convention
the company may also
advertise some other stars.
Why do those journalists all focus on Zhou Yao?
Lian Ruoshen is going to release a new song too.
I thought
scheduling Lian Ruoshen’s song
and finishing it as soon as possible
could bring him some opportunities.
However, I forwarded my plan several times.
Our boss hasn’t replied to me yet.
Now I’m wondering
if it’s because Lian Ruoshen
contradicted him last time.
So he plans to ignore us.
He’s capable of that after all.
So what’s your plan?
What’s my plan?
I have to do something.
There are new stars every day.
If someone is slightly behind,
he’ll be completely forgotten.
I have to
convince our boss to make Lian Ruoshen famous,
or
I quit and do it on my own.
Think about it carefully.
It’s not easy to work alone.
Don’t worry. I got it.
If it’s not necessary,
I won’t quit.
Chengcheng,
wait a moment.
I have to talk to DK.
Why are you asking me?
Handle it by yourself.
Sir.
You can go.
OK.
Come in.
Sir,
you made every effort to found
the Royal Entertainment.
Today there are a lot of people.
They came here for you.
Stop flattering me. Get straight to the point.
Sir,
you’re always good at finding talents.
People selected by you all became famous.
So I’m gonna ask you a question today.
What do you think of Lian Ruoshen?
He’s gifted,
but
it’s not enough.
I can’t give the best resources to him.
I understand that.
He just began to be a star.
In terms of his popularity and advertising,
he’s not that good.
I’m not greedy.
I don’t hope
you can give him the best resources now.
But...
His new single is going to be released.
The release
will be a great opportunity for him.
You said he’s gifted.
Well, if he’s gifted,
his single will be the top 3
of the domestic single charts.
There are several key variety shows.
I hope our senior staff members
can offer some help.
About the specific plan,
I already told it to you before.
Now I just need your approval.
Since you talk to me,
I can help you.
It’s obvious that
you care about him.
Otherwise, you wouldn’t
help him again and again.
I just cherish talents.
Think about his ability.
He won’t let you down.
His attitude
doesn’t matter.
What matters is your attitude.
Baoling,
you’re a senior staff member.
Do I have to make it clear?
[Gangzhou Hotel]
Later
I’ll wait for you upstairs.
Sir,
what do you mean?
Baoling,
you’re not young anymore.
You have to create a superstar
to help you stay in the entertainment industry.
As to me,
I can make anyone famous.
Why should I make someone who
always contradicts me famous?
To put it simply,
I care about you.
To come or not,
it’s up to you.
Bastard, I won’t forgive you.
Let’s toast the success of Zhou Yao’s new song.
Cheers!
Next, let’s invite the host,
Zhou Yao,
to say something to us.
Cheng Feng,
thank you for
helping me this time.
I want to invite you to
come with me.
My boyfriend hates
me being close to other guys.
There are a lot of people today.
I don’t want anyone to think that
I’m using you to hype myself up.
So let’s stop here.
Why are you so arrogant?
Think about where you are
and who you are.
Mind your tongue.
You guys asked her to come here.
Ask? You’re kidding.
Who are you?
You’re ignorant.
Don’t ever think that you can do
whatever you want.
It’s your honor to be invited.
So you’re kicking down the ladder?
You should stop talking.
You’re just a gigolo.
To those who don’t respect others,
there is no need to be polite.
Sorry, guys.
Sorry for disturbing you. Have fun!
Stop!
You raised hell in my place.
Now you just wanna leave?
Do you wanna fight me?
I’m not afraid of you!
OK.
Hit me.
You’re fired!
As the CEO of Royal Entertainment,
you insulted your business partner
and planned to beat him up privately.
If I publish the video,
what will happen? You know it.
Dai Baoling, you’re insane!
Delete the video now,
or I’ll let you pay for what you did!
Baoling, don’t worry.
I’m here.
Baoling, calm down.
It’s personal.
Essentially,
I have you involved in it.
Sir,
you shouldn’t
say something like that again.
Recently,
you connived with Pang Ting to
take resources for Lian Ruoshen away
and gave them to Zhou Yao secretly.
I didn’t complain.
However, you refused to
publicize Lian Ruoshen’s new single.
You know what’s the reason.
Don’t blame me.
You should blame yourself.
It’s meaningless for me to
keep working for this company.
What do you mean?
I mean
from now on,
I quit!
I’m fed up with you,
I quit, too!
You…
Dude.
Idiot.
Go with me.
Let’s toast to our victory.
Cheers!
- Cheers! - Cheers!
Great!
I’ve been through a lot these years.
I finally quit.
I regret that we left early.
I should kick him.
Eat some vegetables.
I agree with you.
I’m starving.
I was drinking before.
I didn’t eat anything.
Didn’t you order the staple food?
Yes, we did. Here it is
Don’t throw it into the hot pot directly.
Look.
I’ll show you
my improvisation.
I can stretch the noodles while singing.
♫ When I have wings ♫
♫ I can fly to a bigger world ♫
♫ I change in the last second ♫
♫ Breaking the cocoon into a butterfly ♫
You regret it, right?
No, I don’t.
I’m happy.
No matter how hard it will be,
I will never regret my decision today.
Before, I
often felt depressed.
Suddenly my life
felt lacking in direction.
Now it’s different.
As long as he agrees,
I’ll get him out of there
at any price.
Whatever decision you are going to make,
I’m always behind you.
If you need help in the future,
I’ll try my best to help you.
Drink some hot water.
Your stomach will feel better.
Dian,
somehow,
I feel unhappy now.
What’s wrong?
I’m
a little worried.
I’m worried that I’ll fail.
What should I do?
You don’t have to be worried.
Ask yourself.
Do you think I’m gonna succeed?
It depends on your attitude.
Do you really like singing?
Or do you just want to be famous?
Is there a difference?
Of course, there is.
If you do like singing,
you won’t care about the fame.
If you just want to be famous,
in the future,
your life will be full of worry.
How can you focus on music?
Believe in yourself.
Are you sleeping?
No.
Do you want to see the stars?
Yes.
What are you doing?
Look at the stars.
Where are they?
There.
Are they your favorite stars?
No.
No?
My favorite is
the one who looks at stars with me.
Baoling,
why are you here?
What did we do?
We did nothing.
I thought you might feel cold,
so I tucked you in.
Where is Dian?
Stop looking for him.
You move frequently while at sleep.
Will he sleep with you?
We should go.
The loving couple
has been separated by us.
Well, I’d
like to tell you something bad first.
After leaving Royal Entertainment,
you’ll be less stressful.
But you’ll lose all the resources
which Royal Entertainment has.
In the future, we
have to fight for everything.
It’ll be hard.
Ruoshen,
can you handle that?
The reason why I
stayed in Royal Entertainment for a period of time
is not that I wanted resources and money.
I stayed because of you.
When my dream got denied,
you believed in me,
praised me
and helped me with my debut.
As to me,
you’re the savior
and the confidant of my life.
You left Royal Entertainment.
Whatever resources it has,
I don’t care.
You trust me so much.
What if I fail to make you famous?
Baoling,
no matter what happens in the end,
I will always be there for you.
You stay,
I stay.
Dude,
why are you so emotional tonight?
Baoling.
OK.
Thinking of what you said,
I’ll keep you accompanied till the end.
I told you
you can’t get in without a reservation.
Please go back.
Ruoshen,
let’s drink a toast to Ms. Gao.
OK.
Ms. Gao.
Hey,
come here.
Drink with me.
Ms. Gao,
he can’t drink too much.
If you do want to drink,
I can drink with you.
Come here.
Ms. Gao.
It’s your honor to have my support.
You’re no longer a member of Royal Entertainment.
Stupid boy.
Ms. Gao!
Sir,
we’ve talked about
the contract before.
Could you please sign it now?
Sir.
Mr. Chen,
why did Lian Ruoshen’s
first song become a real hit?
Royal Entertainment did help him,
but it’s more about himself.
He’s cheerful, decent,
optimistic and upright.
All of these characteristics
are rare in the entertainment industry.
I believe
as long as you give him a chance,
he can be more popular than before.
Baoling,
why are you so naive now?
Do you really think
without Royal Entertainment,
Lian Ruoshen’s song
can still be popular?
As old friends of Royal Entertainment,
we offered all of our resources
and tried our best to support him.
Without us…
Mr. Chen,
what you said
is not appropriate.
Before, you told me that
you liked Lian Ruoshen’s song the best.
Because of DK,
you denied all the effort we made.
Mr. Chen,
you can’t be so mean.
Dai Baoling,
who do you think you are?
How dare you talk to me this way?
After leaving Royal Entertainment,
you’re nothing.
Fortune knocks once at every man’s door.
Wait and see.
Dai Baoling,
why are you so arrogant?
The reason why you succeed
is that
you have an affair with DK.
Mr. Chen.
You!
Please mind your words.
You’re a general manager.
You shouldn’t talk like a jerk.
By the way,
you might forget that
I’m good at Muay Thai.
So
don’t piss me off.
Dai Baoling,
don’t be so cocky.
You'll loose your momentum soon.
I was so stupid before.
Why did I work for Royal Entertainment?
It’s a disgusting company.
The CEO threatened to shut me out by media
and told me to kowtow to him.
He’s insane!
I’d rather give up my business
than go back and beg him for help.
I’m an excellent celebrity manager.
I’m quite famous in the industry.
I’ve never felt so humiliated.
Well, Chengcheng,
you asked me to come here over the phone.
What happened?
Glory Media
is looking for an endorser
for their game.
I’m the choreographer of their artists.
I recommended Lian Ruoshen to them.
After an assessment,
they think Lian Ruoshen is suitable.
They want to invite you to
participate in their event tomorrow.
By the way,
they’ll announce that
Lian Ruoshen is their endorser.
Really?
Well, it’s a little bit weird.
A big company looks for an endorser.
I’m the celebrity manager.
They didn’t talk to me
and made a decision directly.
I also think it’s kind of weird,
Since there’s an opportunity,
I told you about it first.
To take it or not,
it’s up to you.
Actually, I don’t have to be worried.
We should take it.
It wouldn’t do us any harm.
Maybe…
As a big company
and an employer,
it's normal to be a bit condescending.
Or maybe
their procedure
is different.
Anyway, Chengcheng,
thank you so much.
In the world, there are genuine emotions,
true love
and true warmth everywhere.
I love you so much, Chengcheng.
Stop flattering me.
You’re right.
I have to call Lian Ruoshen
and ask him where he is.
I want to tell the good news
to him in person.
How’s your preparation for the concert?
It’s not bad.
Everything is on the right track.
What about the new dance teacher?
How’s your cooperation with her?
I’m still adjusting.
It’ll take me some time to be familiar with a new partner.
Looks like
you still prefer
your ex-girlfriend Cheng Feng.
Although I don’t like her,
I can tolerate her
as long as she can
create business value for me.
Your first dance
and your current popular dance
were both choreographed by her.
After she left,
your other dances
haven't been that popular.
About the reason,
we both know.
I don’t have to explain, right?
If you can convince her
to be your permanent choreographer,
your future career will be promising.
Sir, I wish I could.
But…
I already broke up with Chengcheng.
Besides,
she has a new boyfriend now.
How can she be my
permanent choreographer?
Nothing is impossible.
She’s active in the industry recently.
She must be
busy helping Dai Baoling and Lian Ruosheng.
However, you should know
if I decide to blacklist them,
I will never let anyone help them.
When I put pressure,
you come to help them.
Maybe she’ll be grateful to you.
I don’t know much about her,
but I can tell that
she’s a sensitive and caring woman.
If Baoling is in trouble,
she will definitely help her.
Understand?
Yes.
Get out!
We’ve been together for many years.
You never
cooked for me.
It tastes like what I think,
but it still can be improved.
If you don’t get out,
I’ll call the police.
Recently I heard that
in order to help Dai Baoling and Lian Ruoshen,
you contacted some people in the show business.
It’s none of your business.
I can help you
as long as you come back to me
and be my exclusive choreographer.
Here is the contract.
[Choreographer Employment Contract]
Sign it.
I’ll convince DK to
forgive them.
Stay away!
You don’t have to worry about us.
Why?
Is it because
I borrowed a dance from you?
Are you gonna hate me all your life?
Chengcheng,
look at you.
Your life is miserable.
You’re too good for Jiang Dian.
He’s neither rich
nor famous.
He can’t give you anything.
But I’m different.
Now I’m rich and famous.
I can give you everything you want.
I left you before
because I didn’t want you to
suffer with me.
I thought one day
when I can
create the life you want,
I’ll come back to you.
I did it.
Chengcheng,
please come back.
Come back to me.
OK?
You plagiarized my dance.
Zhou Yao,
you can’t be more shameless.
Didn’t you know what’s the meaning
of that dance to me?
You knew it,
but you still did that.
Do you really love me?
Zhou Yao, wake up.
You only love yourself.
[Choreographer Employment Contract]
Zhou Yao,
I felt disgusted with myself for being together
with you before.
How many dirty jobs
did you do?
Cheng Feng,
you know I won’t hurt you,
so you feel secure, right?
You hurt me so many times.
One day
you’ll come to me.
I’m home.
Why did you clean up all the dishes?
I didn’t have dinner.
They got cold.
I want to cook something new for you.
Did anyone drop by here?
No.
Go upstairs.
[Choreographer Employment Contract]
Dian. What’s wrong, Dian?
Cheng.
I’m sick.
Will you leave me?
Will you hate me?
Dian,
I won’t hate you.
I won’t leave you.
Will you always be there for me?
Yes.
Dian,
this time,
let me cure you.
Don’t worry.
I won’t sign the contract.
Well,
Dian,
can we go to sleep now?
Tomorrow morning
I’ll get you to the hospital.
Let’s go.
Good morning.
I have to go to school
and hand over my work first.
Then I’ll wait for you at hospital.
Go back to sleep.
I’m gonna get up.
OK.
Hi.
Hi,
could you please help us find
the seats of Dai Baoling and
Lian Ruoshen?
OK. Wait a minute.
Sorry,
your names are not on the list.
Maybe it’s the wrong place.
It’s impossible.
I’m the endorser of your new game.
Sorry, your name is not on the list.
[Action Competitive Games]
Thank you.
[Gathering domestic professional game development team]
You’re welcome.
Cheng,
we arrived,
but they said we’re in the wrong place.
Will you…
Stop calling her.
Let’s go.
Since you’re here,
why not stay for a while?
Well,
you don’t have seats here.
Sorry, I forgot it.
Anyway, I can ask the waiter
to bring you two chairs.
You can sit in hallway.
It’s weird that
I got the endorsement easily this time.
You’re playing tricks.
Recently no one stops you,
so you become out of control?
Did you forget what I said?
Sorry,
our boss did it.
Bastard.
Hi, Baoling.
It’s been a long time.
How are you?
Have you been through a lot?
You look tired.
Do you need…
Thank you for asking.
I’m good.
But I feel sorry that
you failed to make life miserable for me.
I’m just a nobody.
Do you have to direct at me?
I worked for Royal Entertainment
several years,
but you kicked down the ladder.
How ruthless you are!
How dare you bully her!
Let me go.
I can avenge for you.
Sorry, my hand shook.
Wait and see.
What happened today,
I’ll remember for you.
Baoling, I’m sorry.
I didn’t expect that.
It’s not your fault.
You didn’t mean it.
Please get out.
Please.
Stop.
We can go by ourselves.
Don’t look down upon us.
Let’s go.
This time
it’s my fault.
I didn’t talk to them in advance,
which makes you feel disappointed.
But I promise you
things like that
will never happen again.
Baoling,
I’m fine.
Don’t worry.
I know you want to help me.
In the future,
we’ll get better and better.
I believe you.
The car is here.
You should go.
Cheng,
please take care of Baoling.
Go.
Would you like to
drink with me?
Let’s go to my place.
Chengcheng,
I’m worried actually.
I thought
after years of work,
I already became an expert.
Even if I leave Royal Entertainment,
I can still bring him a good future
on my own.
But now, I feel like
I can’t do it.
Compared to the resource,
my ability is nothing.
If I fail,
I will still be fine.
But if I ruin
a boy’s hope,
how can I compensate him?
I can’t sleep over night.
I’ve been thinking
what I should do
to not let him down.
I’ve really tried so hard.
Why are the results
always unpleasant?
Stop drinking.
What’s wrong, Baoling?
Do you have the medication?
I’ll get you to the hospital.
I hate going to the hospital.
I always feel like I can get in
but cannot get out.
Do you think I’m a coward?
I want to be alive.
If I’m not,
how can I make his dream come true?
What about your dream?
My dream
is to make his dream come true.
[Choreographer Employment Contract]
[Party B: Cheng Feng]
Chengcheng,
I’ve been waiting for you at hospital for a long time.
Why didn’t you…
Why didn’t you go there?