2 Days and 2 thousands
I few thank you
Thanks
데τι
나와보네
constante
여기 만 hab in
태어
Don't go.
What is it?
Don't you have something to say?
That's...
You haven't talked about this before.
I missed you so much that I missed you so much.
Did you come back safely?
Yes, I came back safely.
After you left, I was busy with the opportunity.
And then I realized how much you liked me.
In the end, I think you made the right choice.
If you go back to that time, I think you can send me better.
Well, that's already over.
Okay, I understand your feelings.
It's all over anyway.
Let's just forget about each other and look at each other comfortably.
What?
I'll do that from now on.
Then I'll go.
Han Yeop.
I've been waiting for you.
Let's put that hand down.
I heard you had something to say because you came to the museum like that.
In fact, I was looking forward to seeing you again.
But I guess it wasn't.
I guess it was really over.
We broke up really well.
I think it's really over.
Then I don't like it.
What do you think about me after that man is over?
The first love I told you was actually you.
I don't know why I really did this after we met again.
If I just met you, I would have been in a daze.
I think so.
If you went there and ruined it, you would have said it all.
What are you doing?
I thought you'd be really comfortable.
I'm here.
Hey, I didn't come.
You brought that heat wave and something to get on it.
You don't drink.
You said you wanted to comfort me.
I didn't mean that.
Now I understand your heart.
I'm sorry.
I wanted to start over.
I think I can send you back better if I go back to that time.
What.
That's already over.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing here?
It's my house, so give it to me.
Then, brother.
Hey, aren't you the one who brought me here?
Hey, my friend, come here with me.
Hey, leave me alone.
I'll take you with me, too.
Hey, Dong-ah, don't take me.
I'll change it for you.
Dong-ah.
Yeah.
You know me, right?
I want to be handsome.
Dong-ah.
When I first saw you, you were standing in front of the table.
I don't know if it's a table or a table.
Hey, I don't have any cheap things, but honestly, I thought it was a good thing.
Really.
I'm not sure if it's a good thing or a bad thing.
Correct.
Good.
Let's go home.
Dong-ah.
Wake up, wake up.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
I'm so heavy.
When did you two get close?
You're drinking and going crazy together.
How did you get here?
Hye-joon.
Do you guys play?
Of course.
The timing is amazing.
As soon as I got to know my ex-boyfriend, I confessed my first love.
Then did you drink like that because it was over with you?
Huh?
Um, no, I went to take Dong-ah to my brother-in-law's house yesterday.
It doesn't matter what he drank at the end of the day.
I'm not looking at my ex-boyfriend.
You can do well with your first love now.
It's like a dream to be with your first love.
You're both my first love.
I envy you.
First love.
Huh?
Hey, what are you doing? Hurry up and get it. Hurry up.
Hello?
No, Hong Jae-hye.
Why are you drinking so much?
Thank you.
Do you know how hard I was yesterday?
I don't know how long it's been.
I really thought about throwing it away a few times in the middle.
Okay, you can use something delicious.
When?
When the foreign letter is over.
Okay, I remember.
Oh, right.
I should have done it when I only put in the insert, right?
Yeah, I should go to the studio and do it now.
What?
Where did you go?
The president's son.
What?
Is there an insert in it?
Yes.
Oh, look for it well.
Why is there so much shit?
Are you sure you put it in this room?
You can put it down here.
Oh, shit.
Oh, here you are.
Oh, yes, my friends.
Oh, hello.
See you again.
Hello.
Oh, my God.
We're screwed.
What do you mean?
I lost it in the warehouse.
Oh, I'm done with the ad.
Oh, my God.
It's okay.
I left it in the taxi.
The driver can't contact me.
Oh, if I can't find it, the concept is completely ruined.
Oh, my God.
I'm screwed.
I should go.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know there was such a place.
Do you come here often?
What do you think?
Oh, no.
No, I'm thinking about something else.
I'm really sorry, but I think I have to go.
I'm sorry for what happened in a hurry.
Please, please.
Oh, my God.
Hey.
No.
Go with me.
I left my bag in the taxi.
I checked it with this machine and it said it was a ghost driver, but I couldn't get a call.
Oh, that bag.
I went to the police station to dance.
I couldn't contact you because I was out of my phone when I was dancing.
Where's the driver's bag?
Where did he say?
Oh, where's the game?
I think I'm here.
Wait a minute.
Hello?
Jae-yeol, it's because of our E-onpik ad.
Yes.
You know that tomorrow is the last day of the O.
Tomorrow is the last day?
Why?
Isn't there anything wrong?
No, it's not that there's nothing wrong.
Me too.
Yes, yes.
Then until tomorrow?
Yes, I can.
Then I'll be in your care, Jae-yeol.
Yes.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Let's go over there and ask.
Excuse me.
Are you okay?
Oh, my, my, my.
Oh, I'm sorry.
What should I do?
I don't want to clean the water.
It's okay.
Oh, I'm so tired.
No, come in.
Come in.
Come on in.
It's cold, isn't it?
No, you're more tired than me.
You're on your side.
Are you okay?
Look.
No, I'm okay.
I was just surprised.
Yes.
Teacher, wear this and come here.
I'll dry it for you.
Teacher, you look better than me.
Yes.
Oh, my.
I just saw it.
I think I'm in Seoul.
What's going on here?
Oh, right.
Do you know who's the boss?
Oh, the taxi driver?
The old lady's son?
Yes.
Do you know?
Where do you live?
This is the third house here.
I'm sure he's not home today.
Why?
I went out with my grandma this morning.
I told her I was going to the beach.
Where?
I don't know.
Oh, my.
You're hungry.
I'm hungry.
Do you want some ramen?
Then, two bowls.
Wow, the ramen here was a good place.
Awesome.
I got it from the old lady.
Give me your hand.
Yes.
It's okay.
Give me.
You can't get caught by the water.
Yes.
Thank you.
What are you going to do now?
I couldn't find the foreign card.
There's nothing we can do.
I'll go to the airport tomorrow and see the rain.
But why did you come today?
That's because I have work to do.
I was worried.
Oh, it didn't mean anything.
It's just that I'm not the one you don't know.
We should help each other out.
Don't you think so?
It's okay to be somewhere else.
What?
You know, Pan.
I've been weird since I was a kid.
I didn't go to school and even the summer school.
So what I wanted to say was...
I missed you so much.
It's not.
Oh, my.
It was the green text you wrote.
Come out.
I almost fell asleep.
Don't laugh.
Thank you.
But are the students going to Seoul now?
Yes.
Then let's go together.
It's free.
Come on.
I'm here.
Thank you.
Pan.
Thank you for today.
Take care.
Goodbye.
Okay.
I missed you so much.
Pan.
I'm sorry I went out of the blue yesterday.
No.
Did you do well?
Yes.
That's a relief.
The guy you talked about last time...
That ex-boyfriend.
You still like him, right?
Yes.
I thought he was my first love.
But I think my first love is now.
You did too much.
What?
Do you have to take your first love and title?
I don't know anything else, but that's a little sad.
I'm really sad right now.
But did anything happen to Pan yesterday?
No, it's just a guy.
I'm out of my place.
I'm not looking for a real ex-boyfriend.
Did you see everything I said?
When did I do that?
When?
Yes.
It's going up.
Oh, no.
It's going up again.
How far are you going?
No way.
We're dating again.
I didn't mean that.
What?
Then we're not dating again.
Who's been telling you to date these days?
It's obvious when you look at the mood.
No, they're not the first time they've met.
We're going to break up and meet again.
You have to be clear.
If you said you wanted to see him, you would have been reaction.
You didn't hear anything?
Hey, does that make sense?
I missed you so much.
No.
Hey, students, it was the green text you read earlier.
Come out quickly.
Oh, my God.
They're not the first time they've met after taking a dump.
We're going to meet again after breaking up.
You have to be clear.
You're not home yet?
It's almost time.
Oh, I'm going to move out.
Then can you put this on the way out?
Yes.
Thank you.
Why aren't you dating?
It's the yellow moon you interviewed earlier.
I don't think I was honest in the interview.
I'm still waiting for my girlfriend who left a year ago.
I was lacking at that time, so I lost that friend, but I know now.
I really like you.
I think I've seen you for a while.
You are the forward star.
I'm looking for your traces in the light of my heart.
I'm searching for your skyline.
I'm looking for you.
I'm looking for your skyline.
Bani, it's me.
Where are you now?
I'm in front of the library.
Library?
I'll be right there.
Wait there.
I'm sorry.
I've been waiting for the day you came back.
I'm doing well with my clothes.
I'll make it harder.
I didn't say it right, but I still like you.
I've never liked you for a moment.
I like you more, Bani.
I missed you so much, too.
No, I missed you more.
I'm sorry.
It's been a long time since I've been going to class holding hands like this.
So don't think about coming here all day long.
I was so surprised when Bo-bae and Dong-ah saw me.
I'm going to be surprised and surprised.
You have to handle that.
It would be so fun if you and Bo-bae had a double date.
I really wanted to do a double date.
Hello, Bani.
Why are you two like this?
Ask your friend.
Why are you telling me?
Did you two fight?
What?
That hand?
Let's date again.
Really?
It's a total cut.
Don't do that.
Why are you so good at it?
What's the reason?
You're my woman.
I can't go anywhere without my permission.
I can't even take a step.
We were not in a relationship from the beginning.
Who decided that?
What's the problem with me liking you?
You know, I can't do it without you.
Kiss?
What?
You didn't tell me you had a kiss scene.
No, never.
What's wrong with you?
I mean, I've been learning how to date a girlfriend for a few years.
Congratulations can't be done.
Do you do the opposite because of the kiss scene?
Kiss scene?
No matter how much you act, it's nonsense to talk to your boyfriend about the kiss scene in advance.
I have to understand you.
Why are you so considerate?
Haoh is a princess.
A princess?
You said you were a princess to me.
Do you think I'm sensitive?
I'm sensitive to my work, too.
Stop it.
What are you guys doing?
What are you doing?
Are you okay?
You're so careful.
I told you not to carry anything with such a weak wrist.
Are you going to do that again?
No.
Hand.
Oh, my.
Why are you fighting when you're going to be so angry?
What do you mean?
You're cute.
You two are.
It's not cute, it's amazing.
Why? I'm cute.
If we fight like that, let's get angry right away.
I don't want to.
I'm not going to fight.
Okay.
I'll go in, too.
Just.
What a waste of time.
Father.
No, they're not even kids.
They're adults, but they can do this much.
I don't think so.
Oh, my.
I'm so happy to see you.
I'm so sorry.
Hey, Yeon-ah.
I'm so happy to see you again.
Me, too.
Father.
Mother, too.
I'll get in the car.
Thank you.
Oh, my.
That's what you did, right?
It's the first day without us.
I'm not in touch with you yet.
Yes.
What's this?
Oh, my.
Hey, didn't Bani order this in advance?
Oh, my daughter must be so pretty.
I didn't ask Bani later, so I thought you'd be hot.
It's late, but thank you.
No, it's not.
You're surprised, right?
I haven't forgotten the taste of the car, so I practiced a little bit, but drink it.
Yes.
How is it?
It's similar to the original.
It's more delicious.
Really?
But what's the taste?
You don't have to know yet.
Oh, my.
Okay.
Son, let's clean up and live.
Mom, can I have some time tomorrow?
Thank you.
Enjoy your meal.
What's wrong?
Why are you suddenly asking me to eat all of a sudden?
I made an advertisement contract this time.
What's this?
So you're shooting one side for your mom?
Yes.
Oh, my son.
When did your son grow up so well and bought you a meal with money?
You're alive.
Eat my food.
I'll eat it deliciously.
By the way, you're going to meet Bani again, right?
How did you know?
Your face is completely red.
Take it.
No, no, no.
I'll take it later.
You can take it.
You're a boyfriend.
Well, eat your meal at 3 o'clock next time.
I just didn't want you to meet two people.
I always felt like I was a legend to you.
I think that was a bit of a shame.
Is that possible?
Mom just...
I was just loyal to my feelings every moment.
I didn't know it would hurt you.
I'm sorry.
No, it was my mom.
I know now.
I'm being honest about how much I like you.
I'm sorry.
You said you're doing great these days.
The students are already here.
I'm jealous.
I should've gone to the CD store because I got a good job.
But Bani went to the preschool, so you're going to prepare for it, right?
No, I'm going to get a job.
I knew it when I went there.
I don't know where to start, but I'll think about it slowly.
You're here?
Yes.
Let's finish this and go out.
Slowly.
Why?
Do you look cool when you work?
Yes.
I'm cool and I'm jealous.
You're jealous?
It's embarrassing to hear that from a talented student who went to the preschool.
But you're sure you want to do it.
I don't know yet what I want to do.
You can find it now.
You're going to find it for sure.
I know.
What do you believe in?
That's it.
Because you're my girlfriend.
Enjoy your meal.
Thank you.
Are you ready to go to the US?
Do you want to go to the US in two months?
Oppa, I'll go alone this time.
You're going alone?
Why?
You've been taking care of me a lot.
I also went to school and I got to know that I was dating my friends.
I'm sure you have friends like this at school, but you've always been by my side when I needed you.
I'm sure you've given up on a lot of things.
No, I don't have that.
I have a lot of friends there and I have my parents, so it's okay.
I can do it well without you.
Looking at it today, I've been in an accident for 10 years already.
Thank you for playing with me for 10 years.
Did you get in well?
Yeah, I got there a little while ago.
I should have brought you home.
No, you're busy.
But you're going on a date with me on the weekend?
Of course. I'll definitely finish it before the weekend. Don't worry.
Okay, I'll work on it and call you before I go to bed.
Okay.
Wow, you drew so well.
I was in the set for a while, but I almost got in trouble.
Thank you.
No, it's a relief that it helped.
But did you call me a assistant?
Yes.
Next time, if you have any thoughts, please contact me.
Yes, thank you.
It's been a while since we've had a date, so I like it so much.
That's right. This is a date for a long time.
I wrote everything I wanted to do with you.
Is that a lot?
Yes.
The first one is this.
Coupling?
Yeah, I wanted to do this hook.
Why?
Isn't it sudden?
Let's do the ring next time.
Okay?
Yeah.
Let's go.
Ugh, I'm not even cleaning up.
Why?
Did I call you?
I guess I'm right.
I'm here.
Who's there?
No, don't come over here.
Don't come over here.
It's not that.
Mom.
Dad?
Mom?
What's wrong with you while you're parking?
I'm really sorry.
You must have been so surprised.
No, no.
I'm sorry.
There were a lot of misunderstandings and apologies at the beginning.
No, no, no.
We came so suddenly because we were so embarrassed.
I came to bring some side dishes, but I didn't have any at home.
I told you the password.
Oh, I see.
Oh, my.
You're taking care of all that stuff.
I guess it's all because of your parents that Bani grew up as a warm and warm child.
Oh, what a nice word.
He's so nice and polite.
He raised his son very well.
No, I didn't raise him well.
He grew up well because he was young.
Was our daughter eight years old?
He's smaller than his friends, so I was worried.
But he saw me and said,
I'll grow up quickly and protect my mom.
I'm doing this to not worry about anything.
Oh, that's so nice.
I'm so relieved.
Oh, my.
I'm the host.
No, I'm not the host.
What?
Why are you crying?
I thought about it when we were growing up.
Our Bani.
I told her that if she was a father, she would take all the people who were bullied.
Oh, my.
This is how he is.
He's so famous.
Oh, my.
I'm so happy.
What are you doing?
I'm talking to Yeoreu.
I'm watching a movie with Dong-ah.
Kkotnim.
Oh.
At first, the boys said they liked it because they were all funny and funny.
After the meeting, they all got out of the group and left.
I'm the only one left.
What's my problem?
Why do you have a problem?
Kkotnim is so bright and nice to you.
If it's a problem, it's probably the problem that no one knows you.
There must be someone who will know you well.
Have a good time.
Why can't you eat?
I'm done with the star.
Have a good time.
I'll see you soon.
Have a good day.
Bye.
Oh, my dad can't stop me.
My mom.
Banyang.
I'm sorry.
I was very upset.
Just look at me once.
Okay.
No, I think I'm still upset.
No, I'm not.
I think I'm right.
Yeah, right.
I was a little upset.
Are you done?
Really.
Hand.
No.
Give it to me.
What?
I wanted to give you a present when I get my first contract.
Then, because of this...
Yeah.
It's so pretty.
Then, I'll put it on.
I don't think there's a perfect relationship in the world,
but I think I can do it as much as a relationship without regrets.
Yeah, Banyang.
What?
Hey, you woke up so early.
I was going to give you a present.
You're already up.
I'm going to meet you earlier than I thought.
Okay, see you later.
Call me when you're done.
I'll take you there.
Okay, see you later.
Okay.
Oh, yes, art director.
Are you going to the cafe?
Oh, yes, I'm going to go now.
Okay, see you later.
Okay, see you at the cafe.
Before you love someone,
you have to love yourself first.
Bona.
Congratulations on your debut.
Thank you.
If you can show me your talent without hiding your lacking self.
There will be a big event today on the top floor of the Chaon Foundation.
It's going to be noisy, so please tell me the heat and heat fairy to use as much as possible.
Yes, sir.
Don't worry about it.
But Chaon Foundation is different from the third generation.
You're going to be an intern like this.
I'm also an intern.
Oh, my.
You're so good at this.
You're so good at physical strength.
Oh, my.
That's why I'm saying this.
Can you come out with us for a meeting?
Once.
Meeting?
Sir, there's nothing difficult.
If you just sit still, we'll take care of you from the beginning to the end.
No.
You're precious to me.
Thank you.
Have a sweet bite.
If you know my feelings and be honest with me.
Bani.
I'll show you the light of love that you'll recognize.
Wow, it's a little bit of a flower bloom in the middle.
That's right.
It was a wish to make a relationship with the person you love.
Then I made a wish.
No, I did this.
I came to you.
That's how we love each other without regrets.
Thank you.