YEONHWADANG
Wow, that sunset...
It's amazing.
Did you buy that
with the money you won from me?
This one I got with my own money.
Would you like some?
Is that the only gambling you do?
There was one time
when I bet my entire life on something.
Did you win?
I'm planning to.
Do you live near here? I've seen you
at the Go club a few times.
Do you live nearby?
Not far. Do you work around here?
Aren't you hungry? Or do you not like food
from convenience stores?
It's not that. I'm just watching my carbs.
I haven't found out
a single thing about you.
Are you usually so full of questions?
Normally,
I keep quiet, believe it or not.
Why do you like to play Go?
Because I like that
you have to fight to the death in silence.
I also like that, for you to win,
you need to destroy the territories
that your opponent carefully built.
Why don't we play together
from time to time?
Now I know what you like to eat
and how you like to play.
JAEPYEONG CONSTRUCTION
CEO HA DO-YEONG
I'm Ha Do-yeong.
Next time, bring more money when we play.
You won't eat this, right?
Is that your breakfast?
You come here every morning.
Do you ever cook for yourself?
Have you eaten yet?
Do you work at Semyeong Elementary?
I noticed the sticker on your car.
You have a nice job.
Can I ask you about something as well?
You're the owner
of Semyeong Real Estate, right?
I think I saw you there
when I first visited to look for a place.
Yeah, that was me.
While living here,
I realized that my place
is a lot cheaper
than the other apartments around here.
Why is that?
Isn't it good that it's cheap?
Why do you ask?
Teachers aren't paid very well.
Back then, you couldn't have known
that I was a teacher.
I'm sorry for asking
about something like this,
but...
is that apartment haunted?
Huh?
Until now, I thought
you had no sense of humor.
That's rich.
Make sure you take your trash with you
when you head back down.
These are the receipts for parking, gas,
and other expenses this month.
Sorry, it seems like
revenge is pretty expensive.
MONTHLY PARKING FEE
GAS MONEY
OTHER EXPENSES
I spent my twenties tutoring
so that I could spend money on this.
I've got plenty saved up, so don't worry.
Following them around, I've found
that Hye-jeong is the easiest to read.
She's always on her phone.
I've been thinking
about stealing her phone.
I think I'm pretty talented...
I THINK I'M PRETTY TALENTED
Will it be possible?
Just leave it to me.
By the way,
did you meet Park Yeon-jin yet?
Everything went smoothly, right?
Shall we meet up?
Were you scared? Intimidated?
You should have crushed her spirits
like a piece of scrap paper!
I did something.
That's good. I'm glad.
I'm proud of you.
I was so worried about you.
You know Park Yeon-jin's mom?
The photo came out a little blurry.
She visited the shaman this month too.
Every other week as always.
With the same man again.
I thought that they might be dating,
but they leave in separate cars.
They arrive separately too.
There must be a reason
if there's a pattern.
Let me know if you find out anything.
And did you
happen to tail this person?
Tail him?
Don't follow this man.
I didn't tell you this
because it might scare you,
but that guy's a cop.
Before, when I first met him,
he was the chief.
He's a senior superintendent general
at Bukbu now.
He's fallen behind his classmates,
who are now chief superintendents.
How did you know that?
Didn't you see the receipts
from the seolleongtang diners?
I picked four seolleongtang diners
in front of the agency and waited there.
When you threatened me
the first time we met,
I had no idea how scary you really are.
Me?
Don't put yourself in danger.
Yeah, I won't.
Oh, can you look here for a second?
Think of it as work.
Wait, I...
What? Is something wrong? Are you okay?
I'm so sorry.
I'm great at taking pictures
of flowers and birds now,
but my hands start sweating
when I try to take pictures of people.
It's okay.
Take another.
I'll try it one more time.
Oh my!
It's your first Gucci, Ye-sol!
Do you like what Grandma got you? Hmm?
"Babies can't tell the difference."
"She won't even be wearing that
for a month."
Right?
Sorry?
You're living like that
because that's how you think.
A different start takes you
to a different destination, you know.
-Go get a new nanny.
-Sure.
Your paycheck and other fees
will be deposited into your account.
Thanks for your work.
Keep these clothes safe, and make sure
she carries them on her milestone days.
It will remind her to try her hardest
like she did when she was born.
Just as I did for Do-yeong.
Yes, of course.
Oh my!
Ye-sol, honey,
say "Grandma" for me.
Say "Grandma."
I'll make sure Ye-sol never has to
try her hardest for anything.
How have you been, Mr. Principal?
If you're free, can I meet with you?
Yeah, right now.
The homeroom teacher, Ms. Moon?
Director Kim recommended her.
The school was in a bit of a tight spot,
since Mr. Yang quit so suddenly.
Hold on.
Are you telling me that Dong-eun
knows the director personally?
How?
I can't say for sure.
Well, does that mean
she didn't have the qualifications?
That's not the case.
We've done our own research,
and she has a great résumé.
It's odd though. It's rare
for a teacher from a public school
to transfer to a private school.
I see.
Could I possibly take
a peek at her résumé, then?
Well.
We have to be careful
with private information nowadays.
Of course. I know. I can't ask that.
So maybe you could just happen
to be holding her résumé,
and I could just steal a glance.
How does that sound?
Hey! You're doing it wrong!
You can't color it like that!
Ms. Moon, you need to use pink
to color cherry blossoms, right?
I can do what I want with my flowers.
My cherry blossoms
are transparent, you know.
There's no such thing.
Ms. Moon, Ye-sol's wrong, isn't she?
Seung-a's tulips look pretty
because they're full of color,
and Ye-sol's cherry blossoms look pretty
because they're empty.
I think they both look awesome.
Now, let's try to finish our drawings.
How much?
Stop with your bullshit,
and just ask me for money.
I'll give you as much as you want.
I'll compensate you for all
of the mental and physical damages.
You've made a fortune just now.
Do I need to write something?
"I'll never appear in front of you again
until the day I die."
I need that handwritten and signed by you.
Just like how your mom signed
your withdrawal letter.
I don't get why the likes of you
would take it out on the wrong person.
It was the parents who did the most harm.
Don't try to save face.
Tell me how much you want.
Wait.
You're not doing this to get
a sincere apology or something, right?
You'll be turning 40 soon.
Isn't that too much of a fairy tale?
It's all in the past!
So I can't do anything about it now.
Don't you agree?
Of course not.
Don't apologize.
I didn't bet my teenage years, twenties,
and thirties on this just for an apology.
You need to get punished.
Criminal punishment if God's on your side,
and divine punishment if God's on my side.
God?
Oh, so are we in scripture now
instead of a fairy tale?
What God?
Goddamn it!
You're holding my daughter hostage.
And what?
You think God will be on your side?
Holding her hostage?
Me?
What did I do?
Did I choke Ye-sol?
Did I hit her in the chest?
Did I slap her?
Or did I burn her
with something scorching hot?
What did I do to Ye-sol?
I actually tried to encourage someone
who lives in a world
where she can't understand
how the rainbow has seven colors...
HA YE-SOL
...or notice that a fruit is ripening.
Because colors don't matter
in my classroom.
But they might be
a slight disadvantage for you, that's all.
How...
How did you find out?
I'm not going to do anything with Ye-sol.
I have a lot of other things I can do.
For example, parent-teacher meetings.
As you might know,
the mother isn't the only person
who comes to those meetings, right?
So never test me again
on how far I'm willing to go
or how far I could push you.
I want you to wilt away slowly,
over a long period of time.
Let's slowly wilt
and die together, Yeon-jin.
I'm so excited right now.
What an interesting scene.
I wonder what that's about.
Hi, Bixby.
Call "Son of a Bitch."
Calling "Son of a Bitch."
SON OF A BITCH
The person you are trying to reach
is unavailable.
Please leave a message after the beep.
Has that motherfucker actually lost it?
Mr. Jeon, a package just came for you.
-Here?
-Yes, sir.
Here, on this street?
What is this, The Avengers?
HA YE-SOL
What is this?
It seems the secretary's office
is incompetent.
No outsiders should be allowed here.
Did you make a lot of money?
I like it when you're wearing
your work clothes
more than when you're wearing your suit.
It's sexier somehow.
You just put Zegna and Versace
out of business.
Do-yeong, should we just send
Ye-sol abroad for school?
What are you talking about?
Ye-sol is only eight years old.
There are professional guardians now.
Many kids are sent abroad early.
What's brought this on?
Do you want to go abroad?
It's not like that.
Then, it's even weirder.
You won't even let the nanny take her
to school without a driver,
and now you want to send her abroad?
Do-yeong, you've been golfing a lot
with Director Kim lately, right?
Can you help me meet with him just once?
Well, Ye-sol got a new homeroom teacher,
and she's crazy.
How is she crazy?
Crazy enough to get the director involved?
Give me some details.
I need more information than that.
Never mind. Don't worry about it.
I'm a bit emotional right now
because I'm feeling tired.
I'll go straight to work from Mom's place.
I'll call you.
Her finances, boyfriends,
and family members.
Friends, coworkers,
even her distant relatives.
Find out everything about her.
Good one!
Your mother broke 90 yesterday.
RÉSUMÉ
Moon Dong-eun. Who is she?
JAE-JUN
That's what I'm asking you to find out.
What I used to know about her
is meaningless at this point.
Effervescent vitamin tablets?
Yes.
You know how bubbles start coming up
when you drop a tablet in water?
I feel a lot calmer
when I'm listening to that sound.
And why do you think
that sound helps you feel calm?
It kind of sounds like a breeze
blowing through ginkgo trees.
It also sounds like raindrops
falling on a Go board.
When I keep listening to it,
I start to feel so lonely.
You know, something like that.
So your body's getting healthier,
but your heart is lonely.
You could try
changing up your environment.
Like moving somewhere new
or going on a trip.
I'll consider it.
I have patients to see as well.
You must be a good doctor.
You're always late for our appointments.
You get paid by the hour.
It's good for you that I'm late.
We'll have to run a CT scan to be sure,
but if it feels this hard,
there's a good chance it's an osteoma.
But it doesn't hurt.
Do I really need to get surgery?
You may not have any symptoms now,
but it could start hurting in the future.
I see.
If I do get surgery,
how long will I be in the hospital?
I'm a schoolteacher,
so I'd like to do it during break.
The examinations and the surgery
will take about a week.
-So, you're a teacher?
-Yes.
At which school? What is it like?
I've seen vlogs
where teachers can't eat well
because they have to eat with the kids.
What about the kids?
Do they listen to you?
Are you a parent?
No. I'm not interested in kids
but in what it's like to be a teacher.
What?
SHANGHAI
Did you lose weight?
Yes, a little bit.
I told you to make sure
that your weight matches mine.
The fit's going to change!
-Do you want a bad performance review?
-I'm sorry.
Just return that one. Next.
Okay, Hye-jeong.
Get your weight back up
before your next flight.
If your weight changes again...
What the fuck is this?
What's wrong with my phone?
Did it get switched
with a passenger's phone?
How the hell would I know?
Call Incheon Airport quickly!
Ask if they have a lost phone.
Okay.
Aw, you've got to be kidding me!
Really?
Well, it was a piece of cake.
What else do you need? Tell me anything.
Great work. I'll see you next time.
Oh my, wait just a minute!
You act so cold every time I see you.
Eat before you go.
I thought we'd be meeting outside again.
I liked what we did last time.
It was like a picnic.
This is, you know,
something meaningful.
"The bird fights its way out of the egg."
"The egg is the world."
From Raemian.
Sun-a was reading it.
That bird can't fight its way out.
You've boiled it.
Also, Raemian is an apartment complex.
The book is called Demian.
I didn't boil it. I baked it.
Can't a girl get emotional
just because she's trying to get revenge?
Ouch! I had a bruise there!
I bet it'll bruise again.
"Beloved,
never avenge yourselves,
but leave it to the wrath of God,
for it is written, 'Vengeance is mine,
I will repay, says the Lord.'"
-Amen.
Let us pray together
while reminding ourselves
of His words from Romans 12:19.
Let us pray.
Loving Father,
I thank thee with all my heart.
You always embrace us with love
even though we are lacking.
Let us thank you again for your grace.
Lord, you always told us
to love our enemies.
But how many times have we tried
to love and care for our enemies?
We failed to live by your word
and treated them with hatred and grudges.
We pray that
you'll forgive us for doing so.
What's a shabby person like you doing
in a precious place like this?
Sa-ra, I'm honestly curious,
so let me ask you.
Do you actually believe in God?
Do you really?
What you just said is blasphemy.
Repent if you don't want to suffer
God's punishment.
-Really?
-Yeah.
Yeah, I just prayed
and reached an agreement with God.
He's fine with it.
You crazy bitch. You're crossing the line.
You don't give a fuck
because we're all grown up?
Watch your mouth, Sa-ra.
We are in the house of God.
One second.
Oh no.
Your God is super pissed off now.
He says you're going to Hell.
Hey!
Have you lost your mind? Are you high?
You're the one who's been taking drugs.
Lots of them.
Often too.
What's this fucking bitch talking about?
I'll give you 15 days.
Fill it with cash and wait for my call.
I want it in dollars.
Hey!
This is called blackmail,
you fucking bitch!
Do you know how many high-ranking cops
come to this church?
You've never been threatened before,
have you?
Hey, let go of me!
Shit!
I haven't even started to threaten you.
Sa-ra.
Turn left at Gyodae Park intersection.
GYODAE PARK
YEO-JEONG
Did you save my number?
I'm making it easier for you
in case you didn't.
Also, my name is Joo Yeo-jeong.
There's going to be a heat wave today.
How are you doing?
It's snowing heavily today.
Walk carefully like a baby
so you don't fall.
Take care.
Did you see the sky today? It's so clear.
I hope you're staying healthy.
CIALIS
TO: SEOUL JOO GENERAL HOSPITAL
JOO YEO-JEONG
FROM: KANG YEONG-CHEON
Yeo-jeong, you got a text.
DONG! EUN! SENT A MESSAGE
Whoa, I think my phone's broken!
There's no way she texted back
after seven, eight years!
We did run into each other once, yeah.
But still, she replied?
Maybe I looked cool that day.
Oh, I see. That's right. I did.
Is Dong-eun married or not?
Hey, don't read that!
Why? What did she say?
Is it a wedding invitation?
Is she getting married? To whom?
She's getting a divorce, right?
Or is it a remarriage?
Is it?
She wants to know what Cialis is.
What medicine is this?
DONG! EUN!
-Let's talk in person. Where are you?
-Are you mad?
-The professor is coming soon.
-Oh, not right now.
Where will you be after seven o'clock?
Sorry if you were busy.
I got busy after your text.
I had to change my on-call schedule.
Have you been playing Go?
I win some money from time to time.
Are you still living in Seoul?
Or Semyeong?
How did you know that?
You said before that
you weren't working in Semyeong "yet."
So you're there now.
I'm working at Semyeong Elementary.
Are you close with that person?
-The one who uses that medicine.
-Not yet.
Oh, so that one's a "not yet" too.
I'm only going to say this once,
so listen closely.
Cialis is a drug that contains Tadalafil.
It has a very long-lasting effect.
And?
That'd be a nice thing.
Viagra is a similar product.
I know that.
Is it used for a purpose
other than the one we know?
What are the two purposes
that you're talking about?
Well, it could be used
in a different situation.
The word is, some people take it
to cure altitude sickness.
But from a doctor's point of view,
it's an erectile dysfunction medicine.
Does that man live in Semyeong?
Those are two different stories.
Meet a guy who doesn't need pills.
As a doctor, I'm a bit worried.
As a man, it gives me a lot of thoughts.
You've got it wrong.
You've become ruder
since the last time I saw you.
Who are you to tell me I'm wrong?
But you already knew
that the pill was just an excuse.
I did.
You can easily look up what Cialis is for.
But
I didn't know why you needed an excuse.
So I got a bit excited.
And although I don't know who he is,
"Does he have any other illnesses?"
"I hope every part of his body
is sick in some way."
That's what I thought.
I wanted to apologize.
Apologize?
I don't know
what you went through at the time,
but back then,
I was rude.
I'm sorry if I hurt you.
But hey,
why does your apology sound
like a farewell to me?
It is, isn't it?
You're telling me to stop texting you now.
But why?
You don't even text back anyway.
Am I that unattractive?
Yes, I don't like you.
You're not my type.
No way.
I don't know what you've got going on.
I really don't know why you're doing this.
But just do it.
Do everything you want to do.
But you should date me too.
I'd make you happy.
You know those moments?
Those moments
when you're allowed to like someone?
If those moments mean that you're alive,
then how many days do you think
I have really lived, Yeon-jin?
Why are you laughing?
I guess I felt happy just now.
But, Yeo-jeong...
I'm not looking for a prince.
What I need is not a prince,
but a headsman
who will join me in the sword dance.
What?
She doesn't pass out in eight seconds.
It was a lie.
-Hit her in the chest.
-What?
You have to hit her hard enough.
If she doesn't pass out,
that means your fist is weak.
Hey. Do you know who set the top score
on the punching machine at Jongro-gu?
It was me.
Tell me if it hurts, Dong-eun.
I'll pray for you.
Look here.
Dong-eun. Stand up straight.
If I miss, I might hit you in the tits.
You called me out to a tteokbokki place
to talk about something serious,
yet you haven't ordered.
Excuse me. Tteokbokki,
fries, and sundae, please.
Sure.
You eat sundae, right?
-You're not covering your tattoo now.
-My tattoo?
Oh, on my neck.
Nobody gives me crap about it now.
You remember we had Spanish class
in school, right?
You see, I really hated Spanish.
But I started liking it again
thanks to your tattoo.
Wow, you're dumber than you look.
Hey, this isn't Spanish. It's Latin.
"Memento mori."
"Remember that you must die."
But you used to cover only a part of it
with a pain relief patch
which gave it another meaning in Spanish.
What meaning?
I do eat sundae.
-Did you go to the hospital?
-Yeah.
Hey, it looks like
you found something big.
So-hee's body was actually there.
Wow, damn it. I don't even know
how much money I should ask for.
So, who was it?
The amount depends on
who we're talking about.
-What if I told you?
-Just tell me who it was.
The rest is easy.
I'll bark at them day and night.
They won't be able to eat or sleep.
I'll turn them into a raggedy mess...
and deliver them right to you.
I know I'm not the one.
Was it one of the four?
Sa-ra? Did she do it while she was high?
Yeon-jin?
The scariest one of the four.
Hye-jeong.
It must be her if So-hee spread the rumor
about the gym teacher and Hye-jeong.
Jae-jun? If So-hee brought up his eyes,
then it's that bastard.
We're in the same boat now.
Which one of them killed So-hee?
Dong-eun asked you for money? How much?
I don't know. She threw me a bag
and told me to fill it.
Fuck! The bag is so freaking big!
-Why won't you pick up my call?
-When did you call me?
-Not you.
-So you, then.
Hey, did she really not come to you guys?
It's not money she's after.
I offered her money first,
but she ignored me.
Why is it so hard to reach Myeong-o?
Did you fire him?
That asshole wouldn't know if I had.
He's ignoring my calls.
Her too.
Do you guys remember clearly
what happened in high school?
How's Ye-sol?
Who is she with now?
What exactly did we do to Dong-eun?
Was it bad?
She really didn't throw a bag at you guys?
Damn it, she must have watched
a lot of movies.
Fill it with dollars? Fuck me.
Ye-sol must be in elementary school now.
Where? Semyeong Elementary?
If she wants us to suffer the same,
what would she do to us?
Jeez, I didn't even get her a school bag.
Which class is she in?
Can you tell me your destination
and if it'll be a round trip?
Wow, I've always wanted to try this.
I didn't imagine that this day would come.
Vladivostok. One way,
I've been thinking about you all day.
Want to meet up?
Fuck off.
You want to see me alone? Why?
I'm curious. Why would you want to see me?
Who? Son Myeong-o?
You fucker, where the hell are you?
How about Yeon-jin?
Did you set up a date with her?
"Me..."
I...
"...mori."
...am dead.