The left side should be a bit lower.
Mr. Jeong, a little bit to the left.
Maybe pull it to the right...
JOO YEO-JEONG PLASTIC SURGERY
My hand might touch you.
Don't get startled.
I was at the car repair shop,
and a button on my sleeve fell off.
I crawled on the floor
like a crazy woman.
Ugly, right?
My scars.
They're injuries.
If you ever collapse again,
call me so you don't make it worse.
I've also hit rock bottom before,
so I understand
the weight of your anger.
Hold on. I'll put on a new button for you.
Here.
Just trust me.
My sewing is better
than most tailor shops'.
Who was the person
that you wanted to beat
by learning Go from me?
This device is switched off.
Please leave a message.
You were here?
I thought you didn't come home at all.
I'm going to work now!
What is this?
A sudden trip down memory lane?
I'd never have imagined
you digging this out by yourself!
High school friends, right?
That's before Hye-jeong got
her nose and boobs done!
I should've gotten a boob job too.
Should I get one?
Is Son Myeong-o not in this picture?
I wonder where he is.
By the way, how do you know Myeong-o?
Do you see them often?
Jeon Jae-jun or Son Myeong-o.
Sometimes.
I do my fittings at Jae-jun's shop.
But I haven't been able to reach
Myeong-o lately...
Ugh, this is so embarrassing!
He tends to do some weird stuff sometimes.
Did he threaten you or something too?
What did he say?
This doesn't seem normal.
When I mentioned Son Myeong-o,
you and your friend both asked
if he threatened me.
Drive safe.
RECENT DESTINATIONS
PLATINUM CC
He met with Jae-jun?
It's Ha Do-yeong,
the CEO of Jaepyeong Construction.
He's Yeon-jin's husband.
The perpetrator's husband?
When my revenge ends someday,
I don't want Yeon-jin
to have anybody left by her side.
Not her friends, parents,
daughter, or husband.
Nobody.
She must have no love left.
Did you win the Go match?
I won,
thanks to a good teacher.
The passcode to the front door is 3724.
It might take months or years,
but let's play a match again.
I'll make one move, and you'll come back
one day and make your move.
Then I'll know that you were here.
It's okay if you don't call me
or pick up my calls.
But keep in touch that way.
That's all I need.
Then I'll do whatever you say
like it's a royal command.
Anything at all.
I'll show you a wild sword dance.
YEONHWADANG
-Write your name here.
-Okay.
-They say this shaman is good.
-Really?
Excuse me.
Do a lot of young women usually come here?
This shaman must be good.
I don't know. This is my first time here.
But according to my friends
who've been here before,
this shaman provides
a fundamental solution.
"Fundamental"?
Next.
Kang Hyeon-a?
Yes! Kang Hyeon-a!
Right here. That's me.
It's an oil stain. Will it come out?
Sure it will.
You want a new button here, right?
I'll just...
leave it as is.
A plant has been sent to congratulate
Dr. Joo's private practice,
and these are letters
that were addressed to the hospital.
Okay.
That brat.
Maybe he sent me his credit card bills.
CHEONGSONG PRISON
KANG YEONG-CHEON
PATIENT MURDERS A HOSPITAL DIRECTOR
SERIAL KILLER KANG ARRESTED ON SITE
TO DR. JOO
HELLO, THIS IS KANG YEONG-CHEON
YOUR FATHER WAS GOOD
THE SMELL OF BLOOD WHEN I PIERCED HIS NECK
THE VESSELS BURST, HIS EYES TURNED RED
Son of a bitch...
That son of a bitch!
One hundred and eighty-two centimeters
and 75 kilograms...
Let's at least stick
to the rules, Dong-eun.
Why did you pick
such a holy place to rob me?
Well, I like this place.
I feel like your Father who art in heaven
will be a witness for us.
I don't have to count, do I?
God, you used to be fucking nothing.
Now that you've got some schooling,
you've become a fucking bitch!
I'll get going, then.
This fucking bitch has somewhere to be.
Hey! You can't go to heaven anymore.
But I can.
I've repented for all that I did to you,
and I've been saved.
You've got good connections.
Okay.
You should go to heaven when you die
because your life here will be hell.
What do you mean by that?
Are you not done with me yet?
Let go of me,
or I'll call your father from his office
and appoint him as our witness instead.
Hey, you little...
Answer me. Hey.
Hey!
Damn it!
Are we having our session here?
You'll take an assessment test today.
It's very simple, so don't be scared.
Come out when you're done. I'll wait.
What kind of assessment test is it?
I'm going to have you study abroad
in the United States.
Study abroad?
Something unexpected came up,
so I can't tutor you anymore.
That's why I want to find
a better teacher for you.
Wow.
Isn't that too big of a lie?
How will you send me to study
in the United States?
Are you rich?
Yeah. I just came into some money.
Come in.
TAIL - DO YOU HAVE THE MONEY?
You were awesome today, Ye-sol.
Just like Sonny.
But the kid with the pink socks
doesn't seem to understand "fair play."
Someone can get hurt.
Number two, Kim Ji-uk?
Yeah. He always tackles people.
Really?
Oh, right!
Dad, we have an open house
at school next Friday.
It's just for dads.
But it's okay if you can't come.
A busy dad is a good thing.
No way.
Of course I will be there,
no matter how busy I am.
Oh, Ye-sol.
Can I ask about your homeroom teacher?
Mom doesn't seem to like her very much.
What about you? Do you like her?
But why? She's a friend.
A friend?
Whose friend?
My teacher is Mom's friend.
They went to the same high school.
Why wouldn't she?
Ha Do-yeong?
Why are you asking
about Yeon-jin's husband?
Just wondering what he's like.
I realized I don't know a thing.
He's nice, but he's a son of a bitch.
You always see assholes like him
in first class.
They think of flight attendants as maids
who can speak a bit of English.
Fuck. Do you have any idea
how many people I beat to get the job?
This is a new one from Vera Wang.
It's a mermaid cut,
so perfect for brides
who have a beautiful figure like you.
What do you think? Is it pretty?
Totally my type.
So,
what exactly is a nice son of a bitch?
How is that different from me?
You're an obvious son of a bitch.
But, Ha Do-yeong, how should I say this?
You have to look closely
to tell he's a son of a bitch.
He's not trying to be one either.
He's just used to ordering
people around all his life.
Oh, that explains
the damn look he gave me.
Did you meet Yeon-jin's husband? Why?
Does he know about you and Yeon-jin?
Hye-jeong.
Yeah?
Even if he knew,
you still wouldn't have a chance.
You should know that by now.
However, the dress does look great on you.
You really should get married.
You'll never meet another man at your age
who lets you wear a Vera Wang.
Oh, make sure to ask your guy
which hotel he had his last wedding at.
They might give a discount
to a regular customer.
He's not the groom?
Would you like to try on another dress?
You said this is the most expensive one.
Just get it altered.
The chest is so freaking tight!
Son of a bitch.
It's bigger than Yeon-jin's.
It's bigger, so what's the problem?
Snow White even lived with seven men.
Why?
Because they dig gold from the mines!
DOES ANYBODY KNOW
WHERE THAT BASTARD MYEONG-O LIVES?
-The person you're trying to reach...
-Damn it!
Where are you? You're not at home.
Did you meet with Do-yeong?
Your golf club address
was in his car GPS...
JAE-JUN SENT A NEW MESSAGE
Can you look for my watch if you go there?
He lives at 34-9 Eulseo-ro, Jongno-gu.
Don't know the code.
INCOMING CALL
JAE-JUN
Why haven't you picked up? Where are you?
Weren't you ignoring my calls first?
I was busy. Did you see the texts?
Let's meet. Where are you?
Let's talk later. I'm out of town
for a family gathering.
Ye-sol!
Ye-sol.
Sorry.
I'm just happy to see you.
I know how to cross the road too.
Never mind. Where's Mom?
Oh, I'm by myself today.
I came to see you.
What do you like?
Gaming consoles? Dolls?
I like stocks.
Samsung Electronics or Kakao.
I'm just kidding.
Mom told me to say that
if anybody asked me that question.
Wow, an eight-year-old understood
a joke like that?
Wow, you're frea...
Very smart.
You're such a genius, Ye-sol.
I wonder who you take after.
Who the fuck does that in a school zone?
I'll cut those damn hands off.
Can't you see there's a child here?
I've made up my mind.
Just now.
I'll protect you from now on.
I love you, Ye-sol.
Ugh, it smells!
What the hell is this?
Did he run away or give up halfway?
What an idiot.
He actually stole Jae-jun's stuff?
Holy shit!
Bitch, you should be at church!
You see, you can pray anywhere, anytime.
I was wondering who would come.
Turns out it's Sister Hye-jeong.
You crazy bitch!
Why do you even want to know that?
The perpetrator always returns
to the scene of the crime.
Don't you know?
Shut it. Was Myeong-o not here?
-Did you make this mess?
-Yeah.
"Knock, and it shall be opened."
So I knocked, and it really did.
Look. My prayers are answered.
Shoo, you'll make me smell.
Damn it, I really need to see him.
If he comes to my wedding
with some weird pictures,
I'll be totally fucked!
Why would he try so hard
to screw you over?
Because he couldn't have me.
Do you know what he said over the phone?
No clue.
I think he went on a trip.
A trip?
"Vladivostok"?
Why are you going to Russia?
Oh, did you actually decide
to become a dog?
A sled dog?
What?
So, he was serious about Russia?
Why didn't he go, then?
Oh fuck! Is it really because of me?
-He didn't go?
-Well, you're holding his passport.
Why the hell do you scream all the time?
I can see that the lights are on!
Come on. Open the door!
Didn't you say you were in a hurry?
People are asking to see your room.
Why don't you pick up your phone?
What is it? What's the big deal?
-We went to Myeong-o's place!
-He might be dead!
One at a time. What was that?
Myeong-o's gone missing.
We went to his house.
The landlord can't reach him either.
He was going to move out.
He packed up and bought a plane ticket.
-It's just weird.
-Then, report it to the cops.
Why did you call me instead?
Report? What do you mean?
You can't call the cops
just because something is weird.
Yeah. Sa-ra's right about that.
I'm getting married soon.
I can't go to a police station.
Well, why did you call me here, then?
I need to head out
with the production truck!
I mean,
didn't Myeong-o call any of you guys
before we lost contact with him?
Well, I called him quite often.
He's Jae-jun's driver.
When do you mean?
Around October 19th or 20th.
Why do you want to know?
I got a super weird call from him!
So I was wondering if he called you too.
What was so weird about it?
I got a call too.
You did, right? What did he say to you?
I don't know. He said something stupid
about sending a gift, so I just hung up.
I wasn't in my right mind either.
So, you got a gift?
Fuck, he asked me out!
The asshole told me that he loves me
and asked me to visit him in Russia!
Does he think I'm crazy or something?
Oh, I'm getting pissed off
just thinking about it!
I mean, how could he dare to like me?
Does he really think he's on my level?
You must've wronged him big time
for him to have done that!
-You got punished!
-That's so freaking funny!
I'm leaving.
I'll be on the news truck,
so don't try to call.
No wonder.
So that's how you knew the passcode
to his house, "696969"!
What about you, then?
How did you know the passcode?
I've been there a couple times.
I just don't remember how I got there.
I'm rooting for you two.
Fuck, it's not like that!
Saturday, three in the afternoon.
Locker number C7.
Passcode, 4885.
STORAGE AND DELIVERY
RÉSUMÉ
AN JEONG-MI
Ms. An Jeong-mi?
Yes. Nice to meet you.
I've heard a lot about you.
Looking forward to working with you.
You too.
I'm looking forward to it.
How are you feeling?
Very good.
I'm sleeping well,
and I've started working out.
I heard you opened a practice
in Semyeong. Congratulations.
Thank you.
I regret not listening to you sooner
when you told me to change my environment.
That's good. How are you eating?
There are great restaurants in Semyeong.
Does it still comfort you
when you listen to the bubbling sound
of effervescent vitamin tablets?
I'm here to say goodbye.
I won't be coming again.
It's a two-hour round trip,
and we meet only once a month.
Is it too difficult for you?
It's not because of the distance.
It's just that
you weren't able to fix me at all.
So, what kind of shit
are you in this time?
Watch your mouth, asshole.
It's not shit this time.
There's something
really small and precious.
-I want to take it from someone.
-Something small and precious?
A jewel?
Hey, are you stealing things now?
I'm the one who got robbed
for fuck's sake.
Buddy.
Listen closely.
Okay, I'll get straight to the point.
No. It's impossible.
-You can't get the kid.
-Why can't I?
Why not? I'm her father.
You're her biological father,
not her father.
A child who is born during a marriage
is legally considered to be the couple's.
Therefore, her father is Ha Do-yeong.
Fuck, that's nonsense.
I ran the DNA test and everything.
It was a 99% match. Isn't that science?
Why did you waste your time on it?
Even if it were 990% instead of just 99%,
as long as the legal father
doesn't abandon the child,
you're in second place forever.
Son of a bitch. Shouldn't you still
try to file a lawsuit or whatever?
I'm saying you can't even file a lawsuit
because you're a third party.
Who are you calling a third party?
I'm the father, damn it!
Shit.
What kind of a fucked-up law is that?
You can only file a lawsuit
if the legal parents
were obviously unable
to have a child at the time,
like one of them was locked up
in prison or on a business trip.
Is that a possibility?
No. They are freaking lovebirds.
Then, is the father abusing the child?
If so, why would I have called you, idiot?
I would've gone to the cops.
Well, then.
The best-case scenario for you right now
is not a lawsuit.
It's the mother's divorce.
Because child custody
is a whole other matter.
Divorce?
I went to the shaman's shop,
but I haven't found anything promising.
I'll go there a couple more times
and then tell you.
And...
You're not pulling out more eggs, are you?
Oh, not at all! I'm working here!
What's that over there?
You know, about the rental car guys.
We've actually got something this time!
STORAGE AND DELIVERY
I followed them from the storage lockers,
and they drove down
Bukbu Expressway for a while.
Then they went into a motel in Namyangju.
And just when I was wondering
if I should just go back,
guess who showed up.
Yes!
It's the cop who visits the shaman
with Yeon-jin's mother.
They're all on the same side!
Amazing, right?
You know, I don't even get scared anymore.
So, I've been thinking.
If I'm ever born again,
I want to become a spy.
Then I'm going to put on red lipstick
and wear a cool leather jacket.
You can put on red lipstick
in this lifetime too.
I don't think that Son Myeong-o
has simply gone missing.
No way, me wearing red lipstick?
He's not gone missing?
Wait, do you think
that Son Myeong-o has actually...
died?
I think these men are Yeon-jin's thugs
who take care of things
outside the law.
The cop is not the one
helping Yeon-jin out,
but Yeon-jin is the one
helping out the cop.
Wait, then by "outside the law," you mean...
Yeah.
That's why Myeong-o disappeared.
Myeong-o acted by himself
because he couldn't trust me.
He even got a plane ticket,
which means he definitely met
with Yeon-jin.
And then he disappeared.
What now?
What did you want from Myeong-o, ma'am?
We're in the same boat now.
Which one of them killed So-hee?
Park Yeon-jin.
Nice one!
But...
I'm sure Yeon-jin also knows
that So-hee is at Joo Hospital.
Do you have any proof?
Can you prove that Yeon-jin did it?
So-hee was holding this in her hand
when she fell that day.
PARK YEON-JIN
Why do you have this?
Were you there that day?
Now you were there too.
Because we're in the same boat.
Wow.
Fucking hell!
This is insane!
I think I'll ask for a billion won!
Call me when you set up a date
with Yeon-jin.
I'll give you this tag on that day.
No matter how much money you get,
that money is all yours.
I want something else.
Something else? What is it?
Park Yeon-jin's confession.
If Myeong-o managed to get the money,
that would have been her confession.
Myeong-o said
that he would record everything for me.
Oh, but
you said that the incident
was ruled as a suicide.
Do you think
that her confession could change things?
That's why I wanted
to make her a social pariah.
My chances are slim in a legal fight.
I wanted to let the world know
about what she did with her confession.
I wanted her to feel like
she was burning for the rest of her life,
with pus oozing from her wounds.
So she wouldn't be able to laugh, eat
or live another day in peace.
Does this mean
you can't get her confession anymore?
It's not like we can go look
for Son Myeong-o's corpse.
What should we do?
We need to find him first.
How?
Just relax.
What will the test results tell me?
It's a 12-panel STD test,
so it will catch most things.
Since you added an HPV test,
you'll see results
for resident flora and STIs too.
Nothing else will show up, right?
Here are the papers that you asked for.
Family Relations,
College Graduation Certificate,
and my ob-gyn examination results.
You could have just texted them.
Who carries around paper copies nowadays?
I'll take a look at these.
-Which bank do you use?
-Excuse me?
I won't be able to stand it
if you have a bunch of debts.
Just tell me which bank,
and I'll take care of the rest...
Ms. Moon?
Ms. Moon!
Oh my, it's so great to see you!
How long has it been?
You've gotten even prettier!
Choi Hye-jeong?
Do you two know each other?
That's my son's girlfriend.
Oh, we went to the same high school.
Oh, I guess I can't act
quite as friendly to you anymore.
What are you talking about?
What she does has nothing
to do with you, Ms. Moon.
You're hurting my feelings!
We're going to eat dinner at the temple.
If you have time, you should join us.
Sorry, I have plans today.
So, you're getting married?
Congratulations.
I'll make sure to come earlier next time.
Sure. Go ahead!
I wish she was marrying Tae-uk.
I'm stuck with this brat.
By the way, why didn't you even say hello?
Ms. Moon looked happy to see you!
Well, it was so sudden,
and we weren't very close.
Just one moment, please.
Dong-eun!
We didn't get to talk back there, did we?
My God, what a coincidence!
It's good to see you.
Can I have a word with you right now?
Shall we?
What on earth have you been up to?
And why won't you take my calls?
Do you know
how many times I've called you?
Seventeen times.
Speaking of, Yeon-jin,
do you have anything to tell me?
What do you mean?
Why the hell did you meet Do-yeong?
You really don't have anything to tell me?
Don't change the subject!
Who arranged the meeting? You or Do-yeong?
I didn't ask to see him first.
Your precious Do-yeong came to me
and asked where the fuck Myeong-o is.
And I'm asking you a question too!
Do you really have nothing to say?
Like what?
Dong-eun being Ye-sol's new teacher?
Okay, that too.
But I'm talking about something else.
Something else, what?
Tell me exactly what you want to know...
Are you crazy?
You're the one who's crazy.
How dare you raise my daughter
as Ha Do-yeong's?
Choose your words wisely.
Did you find out
after you gave birth to her,
or did you know it
before you gave birth to her?
I'm just curious, that's all.
I want to know if you kept your marriage,
knowing that you had my kid.
And why you left me again
if you knew the truth.
I want to know...
if you've ever loved me.
If you break a vessel in my eye,
I can't go on TV tomorrow!
-Ji-won.
-Yun-seo.
Hey, Han-sol!
Hi, Han-sol's friend!
Seo-u!
I've been seeing a lot of you lately.
At this rate,
we're going to be best friends.
What are you doing here?
I actually have a secret love child.
Just kidding.
A friend from school is here.
Not one of the parents.
Nice to meet you all.
I'm Moon Dong-eun,
the homeroom teacher for Class 1-2.
I'm friends with her.
Class 1-2 teacher, Moon Dong-eun.
I've heard...
that you all went
to Yeon-jin's high school.
Yeon-jin told you that?
Well, those two weren't friends.
I'm guessing she was
friends with you, then?
You could say we were close friends
who knew everything about each other.
I know her well.
I know what her bare skin is like
underneath her clothes.
Oh, I'd like to ask you something.
Have you ever...
had something precious taken from you?
We will now begin our class open house.