Hello.
The lights over there.
Surprised?
You didn't expect me to come.
Mr. Lu,
is this your...
I'm Mr. Lu's
neighbor.
Just neighbors. Nothing more.
Why are you here?
I'm here
because I need your help.
What is it?
Since we're roommates,
could you do me a favor?
What favor?
Listen,
you know,
our job
can be quite annoying.
Our boss
wants to start livestreaming
and sent me here to learn from you,
to pick up some skills.
You're here to steal my techniques, aren't you?
That's a harsh way to put it, don't you think?
I'm just here to learn from an expert.
How can you call that stealing?
You can't just show up at my set whenever you want.
Then I'll have to tell Grandma.
I'll tell her
you survive on coffee during the day,
and melatonin to sleep at night.
Working like this,
your health will eventually collapse.
5 minutes.
Just 5 minutes.
After 5 minutes, you leave.
And no photos.
Salute!
Stay on track.
Come on, change positions.
Miss, please step aside.
Me?
Yes, move quickly!
You're in the shot.
Sorry, sorry.
Be careful!
Yi Feng, watch out!
Yi Feng!
Lu Chen!
Open your eyes! Don't fall asleep!
Please don't!
Little girl.
No! No!
You are a little girl.
I'm not a little girl. Let me go!
Little girl! Little girl! That's what you are.
Let me go!
You are! Only little girls wear colorful clothes.
Let him go! Little girl! That's what you are!
Go away! Stop bullying! Go away!
Yi Feng!
Yi Feng, we're at the hospital.
Hang in there. Don't fall asleep.
Yi Feng, stay awake.
There's really nothing wrong at all.
We've examined everything that needed to be checked.
No bleeding, no fluid buildup, no external injuries.
No dizziness or nausea.
No sensory impairment or memory issues.
No cognitive dysfunction either.
The scans only show minor indigestion.
No medication needed.
Just get some rest.
Keep her steady!
The hallucination the patient mentioned is back, isn't it?
Since it's a hallucination, it's only temporary.
It should disappear soon.
Don't move.
Yi Feng, stop it.
I'm sorry.
This is extremely strange.
It doesn't look like a physical issue to me.
I suggest that you
transfer to another department.
Doctor, what should we do next?
Go see the psychology department,
which is psychiatry.
Given her current condition,
there seems to be some mental issues.
Psychiatry.
Schizophrenia.
She's probably under a lot of stress at work lately.
It's caused by overwork.
Mental strain.
She should get better with plenty of rest.
The family needs to be aware.
Try to keep her in good spirits.
Don't let her experience any more stress.
It's not real, it's not real.
It's all hallucinations, it's all hallucinations.
What do these numbers really mean?
Why are they different for everyone?
Why am I number 1
and he's 10?
Let's go home.
No, I haven't finished my task yet.
Let's go home. Grandma is still worried about you.
I won't allow you to go to the film set anymore.
You need to rest.
The doctors say you have schizophrenia.
Just let me go one more time.
Even if I have schizophrenia,
you're the one who pushed me to this point.
My dear granddaughter,
you've scared me to death.
Why am I so unlucky?
You again?
You're bullying my granddaughter again!
Get out!
Get out! It's me, Grandma! Let's go.
Grandma, this is our home. It's okay.
She's the one staying here temporarily.
I was just joking. He didn't bully me.
Go back to your room and rest.
Go rest in your room.
If you bully my granddaughter, I won't let you off.
Her condition is acting up again.
Yeah.
Grandma doesn't remember me, her own grandson, again.
Yi Feng, your lucky turtle.
My little turtle.
You have no idea
what I've been through today.
Use your superpower
to give me strength when I'm at my lowest.
Don't be sad.
They're all bullying me
calling me a little girl.
Don't be afraid. I've chased them all away for you.
Thank you, heroine.
You're welcome.
Blow on it.
Why?
My turtle is a lucky turtle.
It was abandoned by its peers right after birth.
But it still survived bravely.
If you blow on it,
you'll receive its lucky energy.
Hello?
So you finally answer your phone.
Do you know how many messages I sent you?
Where the hell have you been?
I
told you to go to the NS set.
Did you go?
Don't tell me you didn't get in.
I did get in.
Then where's the footage?
Send it to me!
I
didn't get the shot.
I hit my head.
Can't you come up with a better excuse?
You can't even handle such a simple task.
Is the company paying you for nothing?
I just got back from the hospital.
I'll go to the celebration venue right away to explain.
Don't you dare come.
You want to embarrass yourself?
Let the clients see how bad our employees look.
Not only do you look sloppy,
you can't even do your job properly.
Forget about becoming permanent.
Your probation period is extended.
You won't even listen to my explanation.
You won't let me attend the celebration.
Why can't I become a permanent employee?
Don't you want to attend that celebration?
What's it to you?
Are you just giving up like this?
Come with me somewhere.
Teacher Shen Ke, help me figure this out.
No problem.
Usually in comics, the female protagonist
takes off her glasses
and becomes a great beauty.
It seems
she isn't one.
So what's going on?
Mr. Lu is going to a lot of trouble.
I spent two months overseeing the design and process,
dealing with clients,
and independently completed a cosmetic repackaging project.
My boss controlled me
and stole all my achievements.
Today is the celebration party for this project.
My boss thinks I look too sloppy
and excluded me.
This kind of makeover revenge scene
gets my blood pumping just thinking about it!
The workplace is the battlefield of modern people.
Appearance can also be used as a weapon.
Let's start with the eyebrows.
If you want to look pretty, cooperate a little.
Right now I'm a six.
Whether you want to fight her or expose her,
it's all up to you from now on.
This loser.
I put all my energy into the Flower project.
Doing research, writing proposals, revising designs, monitoring processes.
I worked through more than 60 days and nights,
from 9am-9pm, 6 days a week to working around the clock,
to the point that
even my period stopped coming.
Thank you Flower for recognizing my efforts.
I'll work even harder.
Thank you.