You scared me to death!
I thought you were paparazzi.
What are you doing?
So I'm trending online?
All those reporters outside
want me to talk about
the messy story with my ex-boyfriend.
Why aren't you at work?
I quit.
Quit? Why?
I don't think I'm suitable for that job anymore.
You worked so hard just to quit?
Because Lu Chen is innocent.
He shouldn't be dragged into this because of me.
Do you have feelings for Lu Chen?
What are you talking about?
Your actions have already given you away.
Don't move. I'll go.
Uncle and Auntie,
Chacha,
Yifeng, look who's here.
Xiaofeng, my dear daughter.
Did you miss Mom?
Xiaofeng.
Why are you all here?
Chacha called us saying you were feeling down.
We were worried about you.
So we came to see you.
Yes.
You should have called ahead.
I could have booked a hotel for you.
No need.
I happen to be going out for a shoot these days.
Uncle and Auntie, you can stay in my room.
Make yourselves at home.
What are you shooting?
Why haven't I heard about this?
You should stay home for now.
It was a last-minute job.
It's also a good chance for me to clear my head.
Just spend some time with your parents.
Thank you, Xiaofeng.
It's nothing, Uncle.
My precious.
Here, take this.
Dad, why did you come over suddenly?
I was planning to visit home soon.
Your mother wanted to celebrate my birthday.
So we decided to come see you.
Consider it a vacation.
You could at least come help.
Always fiddling with that junk of yours.
I'm almost done with this.
Really.
Mom, if he enjoys it, just let him do it.
And you.
Look at yourself.
What are you wearing?
It looks terrible.
So ugly and you're still wearing makeup.
You look prettier without makeup.
Dad, is it ugly?
Don't mind her, she's just trying to get attention.
I like this tone.
It's from an Italian painter.
Morandi's style.
Very sophisticated.
You have good taste.
I support you.
Xiaofeng,
mom bought you a new one.
Look how beautiful this is.
Come try it on.
Dad, come here.
Make her happy.
Show it to your dad.
Isn't this beautiful?
Don't you think so?
I need a red one.
I should go buy one.
Who are you looking for?
Hello.
Does Yi Feng live here?
I'm his father.
Hello, sir.
I'm sorry,
I came in a hurry
and didn't bring any gifts for you.
Hello.
Who are you?
My name is Lu Chen.
You can call me Xiao Lu or Xiao Chen.
Lu Chen.
Xiao Chen.
Look how fast time flies.
Xiao Chen is all grown up now.
How is your grandmother doing now?
Auntie, my grandmother is doing quite well.
I signed her up for a health retreat group.
They have professional doctors there.
So she can travel and recover at the same time.
That's good, that's great.
While she's still in good health,
it's nice for her to travel around and see things.
Yes.
What bad timing.
We actually wanted to visit your grandmother.
Indeed.
I miss her so much.
Actually, Uncle and Auntie,
you both could stay at my place.
I have plenty of rooms.
Sounds good.
No, no.
We appreciate your offer, Xiao Chen.
Isn't Chacha away from home?
We'll just stay here instead of moving around.
We mainly want to spend time with Xiao Feng.
We'll be heading back in a couple of days.
Xiao Chen.
Has anyone ever asked you to model before?
Model?
Have you noticed your face is perfect for painting?
The lines of your face are clear and strong.
You could definitely model for me.
Dad, he's our guest.
He's not here to be your model.
Xiao Chen, have dinner with us tonight.
I'll show you my cooking skills.
And after dinner, you can model for me.
I'm so sorry.
My dad really loves painting.
He gets excited when he sees someone with good features for painting.
Just ignore him, it's fine.
No problem, Uncle.
I'd be happy to model for you.
Great, it's a deal.
No taking it back now.
I'll go make dinner.
Alright!
Xiao Chen, dinner's ready!
Eat up!
Come on, start eating!
Try uncle's cooking!
Sure thing!
You eat too!
Okay.
I will.
Look at dad failing to cook
Try this one.
and ordering takeout instead.
Hmph, that man
is so unreliable.
Just eat your food.
Fine.
Eat.
All his life he's just loved drinking and painting.
At his age, he still doesn't act like an adult.
That's just my fate.
It's so late, it's inappropriate.
Can you control them?
Make them finish early.
Control him? He doesn't listen to me.
Let them drink.
Fine.
They can drink themselves to death.
Please do something about it.
I heard you're Xiaofeng's boss.
I was his former supervisor.
Yes,
he's my boss now.
An elite!
Not really. Bottoms up!
Wow!
Easy now, be careful.
Okay.
He drank so much.
Help him lie down.
Lie down quickly.
I'd love to be your model. Lie down.
Good! I like hearing that.
Why did he drink so much? Really!
Come on, cover him with the blanket.
Wake up,
sober up.
Look at this kid, so tall,
but a few drinks and he's like this.
Seriously, you kept pouring him drinks.
This young man is really handsome.
Handsome? Really?
Yes, very handsome.
Not as handsome as when he was younger.
If this isn't handsome, what is?
Look at him, so fair-skinned,
looking like a delicate young actor.
A real man
should have a crew cut and square face,
standing tall like a true hero.
You must be talking about me then.
Don't be so vain.
You've had too much to drink too.
Go to bed now.
Let him sleep here tonight.
Keep an eye on him.
You all go to bed.
Okay, let's go.
Let's go.
Yi Feng.
I'm sorry,
wrong room.
Don't go.
I'm sleeping in the living room today.
Why did you resign?
Why did you leave?
This job is no longer suitable for me.
But I don't want you to go.
I can't bear it.
We're all adults.
Don't say such childish things.
I don't want to lose you.
I can't bear
to see you leave.
Please come back.
Morning.
Lu Chen.
Auntie,
breakfast is ready.
I'm not hungry, I'll skip it.
My goodness, you still reek of alcohol.
Let me tell you,
an empty stomach will damage your health.
I have some business at the company.
I need to go there first.
By the way,
did you drive here?
Well, you can't drive now.
Xiaofeng, call him a taxi.
No need,
what a coincidence.
This morning I went to buy breakfast
and picked up a second-hand bicycle.
What did you buy that for?
I was thinking about going out to sketch today.
It's convenient to have it.
See? It's already coming in handy.
Is this appropriate, Uncle?
Why wouldn't it be?
Today is my birthday.
Come over for birthday noodles tonight.
Remember, we'll do some painting after dinner.
Let's go.
Yes, yes, yes.
I'll go first, uncle.
Ah, okay, okay.
Goodbye, uncle and auntie.
Be careful.
Bye-bye.
Let's eat, let's eat.
Where are you going?
Isn't this the car?
How are you sure it's this car?
Isn't this the only car here?
Car keys.
Oh, I don't want to ride anymore.
I'll just take a taxi home.
Mr. Lu, are you trying to tell me you don't know how to ride?
I just forgot.
It's been a long time since I rode one.
You didn't say anything earlier.
So what do we do now?
That's it, start pedaling.
Look ahead.
Slowly move forward.
Very good.
Look forward, don't look back.
Hey, where are you?
Don't look back.
I'm right behind you.
I've been here all along.
Look ahead and stay strong.
Don't overthink.
Everything will get better.
I'll wait for you to come back.
Hey, we're filming here.
But Teacher Zhaoxu should get a chance.
Where are you?
I found a place to isolate myself for a while.
You're not at home?
Yi Feng's parents came to visit.
I'm keeping her company for a couple of days.
I just cleared out the space to make them feel at home.
What a good friend you are, I'm jealous.
Well, her parents are only staying for two days.
I'll be back tomorrow.
Has Mr. Lu gone to see Yi Feng?
I don't know about Lu Chen.
By the way, Yi Feng resigned from NS.
This Lu Chen has hurt Xiao Fengfeng terribly.
Not necessarily.
I think none of us can really understand what's going on between them.
I also think there's something between them.
Even you noticed it.
That's surprising.
Of course.
Hey, what are you trying to say?