Let me take you to bed.
Let's go.
What's that?
It's a room key card. Are you stupid?
I used to stay here when I worked late.
This isn't a room key card.
It's a discount card.
You're still drunk.
What are you talking about?
Fine, suit yourself.
I'll go by myself.
This small hotel isn't safe.
I'll take you to a better one.
I just need to sleep. Let's hurry up.
Good.
Smart move.
I'm thirsty.
Where can I buy water?
So long.
No,
look at this trouble again.
A bit later, okay?
Alright,
I'll hang up now.
Hello.
Beautiful lady.
Are you alone?
Do you know what time it is?
Are you by yourself?
Don't touch me.
Miss, miss.
I don't mean anything by it.
Don't be afraid. I'm just concerned about you.
Why don't you get a hotel room to rest?
Watch out! Creep!
Don't fall.
Let me go, that's enough!
We're almost there.
Let's go.
Let me go!
What are you doing? What do you want?
Let go! Let go!
I'll call the police!
Go ahead.
Call them!
Get away! Let's see who dares to touch him.
Try to move one more time.
I was just worried.
It's okay, it's okay.
Why are you so silly?
Why did you stand in front of me?
What if you got hurt?
I was afraid you'd hurt him
and get taken away by the police.
There's only one room left.
What? Only one room left?
It's a standard room, right?
I'm not afraid.
Only bad people are afraid.
Right?
Oh magical God of Beauty,
the gap between him and me is too vast.
If you can help me,
please reduce his score to zero.
What are you doing?
I'm sleepwalking right now.
I'm in a dream.
I fell asleep.
Good night.
Was she trying to kiss me just now?
Why did I suddenly wake up?
If we weren't colleagues...
Oh my God.
We've become colleagues.
How am I going to face him?
This is too much for me.
He must have forgotten.
She probably still remembers.
Chacha.
Yifeng, you're here.
I was just about to look for you.
How does this outfit look?
Please give me your opinion.
I've been waiting for you.
It's impossible not to look at the scores.
Sister Cha.
This one looks good, right?
Yifeng.
What do you think?
The overall look is very harmonious.
The bag really enhances it.
No other comments?
This bag...
This bag won't work.
This bag is covered in rhinestones.
The dress is made of silk.
The rhinestones could easily scratch the silk.
Do you have any alternatives?
Try this one.
Look, it perfectly balances Chacha's style.
Makes her look softer.
That makes sense. If this issue happened during the show,
it would be devastating for the brand.
Where did you learn that?
At the dry cleaner's.
Great.
Let's go with this outfit.
Yifeng.
You did well today.
I can give you a little reward.
What is it?
How about I treat you to a nice dinner?
I can't make it.
Do you have plans?
Chaoxu asked me to have dinner.
Go ahead without me.
Lu Chen doesn't allow me to use my superpowers at work.
I don't know what to do anymore.
Today he asked me to choose accessories and bags for Chacha.
Surprisingly, I managed without using my powers.
Lu Chen is a bit strange.
But as a boss,
he has his own temperament.
It's okay. You just need to get more familiar with him.
How could I possibly get used to him?
With that weird temper of his.
Look at this bracelet. Isn't it beautiful?
It's gorgeous.
The embroidery is so intricate.
This pattern
is actually just several gold threads.
They're woven together, one thread after another.
What you need to do now
is just like these gold threads.
Find the pattern
and sort it out.
Step by step, stitch by stitch,
and the beautiful pattern will emerge.
Do you like it?
If you do, it's yours.
Really?
Yes, really.
Thank you.
This is the best restaurant I've been to since returning to China.
I wonder if Mr. Zhou will like it.
Thank you for your thoughtfulness, Mr. Lu.
I really like this craftsmanship.
It suits you well.
Professor Chaoxu.
Mr. Zhou.
Long time no see.
What a coincidence.
Are you dining with your girlfriend?
What a coincidence!
Mr. Lu.
Mr. Zhou, this is my reserved table.
Let's sit down.
Bring us a bottle of your Patius wine.
I'm sorry, Mr. Lu,
the wine you ordered is sold out.
I apologize.
Seems I won't have the pleasure today.
The wine Mr. Lu mentioned has me quite intrigued.
Professor Chaoxu, would you mind sharing a glass with me?
Of course.
Mr. Lu and Mr. Zhou.
I wonder if Yi Feng and I being here
would be interrupting you two.
It's fine.
Mr. Zhou and I are just having a friendly drink today.
Let's all relax and chat casually.
Actually,
I've known Professor Zhao Xu
since two years ago.
Back then, our factory
was still manufacturing for small brands.
Thanks to Professor Zhao Xu's help,
he introduced us to many partnerships
which led to what our small factory has become today.
Of course, I'd like to thank Mr. Lu for honoring us with his presence today.
We're still hoping to collaborate with NS.
Mr. Zhou is a renowned cosmetics manufacturer.
All the major first-tier cosmetic brands in China
are manufactured by Mr. Zhou.
Mr. Zhou's production lines are now very well-established.
So,
he now has the idea of creating his own brand.
And coincidentally,
we at NS also have the idea of collaborating on a cosmetics line.
The fact that we can sit down and talk today
is all based on Mr. Zhou's outstanding work capabilities.
So I believe if we can reach an agreement,
we'll be very compatible partners.
Looking forward to it.
Here.
Have some of this. Thank you.
Miss Yi Feng, what's your skin type?
She has dry skin,
but with some sensitivity as well.
So I'd say it's combination skin.
Looks like you two have a good relationship.
You know your girlfriend so well.
Miss Yi Feng,
I'm with you every day
and I had no idea
when you became Zhao Xu's girlfriend.
Oh, right,
do you remember
when Shen Ke did your makeup last time,
she said you had oily skin?
She spent forever covering your acne with concealer.
So what is your skin type, really?
I actually don't use cosmetics normally.
The lighting in Shen Ke's makeup room is way too bright.
Anyone would look like they have oily skin there.
But every morning when she wakes up,
I see her face is all shiny with oil.
I understand.
Please give me your address,
and I'll send you a complete set of our cosmetics.
No problem. Just use whichever works for you.
Thank you both for your hospitality today.
You're welcome, Mr. Zhou.
So that's settled.
I'll go first.
I won't see you out then.
Goodbye.
Bye.
Insisting on sharing our table.
What's their intention?