♪When I glance back♪
♪It feels like the first sight♪
♪Even if you're only in my dreams♪
♪I willingly hold on tight♪
♪Like it's the first♪
♪As if a thousand years have passed♪
♪Can we pen our love across the years♪
♪Cherish every moment that appears♪
=The Princess=
=Episode 34=
=Love Goes Sour, Time Is Wasted=
Uncle, it's you.
You always bring good eating.
Where is Sister?
They are still in bed.
I will be cooker.
Good for you, Xiaozhentou.
It's Sister's favorite cake.
Can you give her this for me?
OK.
- Be careful.
- Uncle, bye.
Xiaozhentou.
What's the matter?
Yanting,
I understand your concern.
The Li family showed no love for Muran.
He and his mother later
came to live with our family.
He was clingy.
If you don't like it,
I'll put it in the kitchen.
It's fine.
He's Xiaozhentou's father.
He can see his son.
Yanting, in fact, Xiaozhentou is...
Sister! Bad news, Sister!
Qiu family's treasure
has been taken away by Xiao's men.
No way.
Very few people know about it.
I-I saw it with my own eyes, Sister.
What now?
Sister, the treasure map
your father gave you?
Where is it?
It is gone.
It's...
Sister, you always have the key on you.
Who else can get it?
Sister,
could it be him?
Yanting is still in Ningcheng.
I must go and ask him.
Sister.
Sister, be careful.
Bro, it was fun.
Right.
Watch it.
B-Bro,
she's the daughter of the Qiu family.
- Look.
- The Qiu family's daughter
is so sad.
Do you think she knows
it was an act that night?
What?
Well,
that phony dude that night
tried to win your love.
He paid us to kidnap you,
then he came to your rescue.
I remember this key.
You always have it on you.
Right.
You know this key, right?
Why do you have tears in eyes?
When we first met,
did you pay those men
♪A strange tale♪
to kidnap me?
♪A blend of truth and lies♪
Answer me.
♪Hide behind the mask just to get by♪
Yes.
♪Without asking for a return date♪
♪Love is fleeting♪
♪But hate is unwavering♪
♪An endless supply♪
♪The cheapest wholehearted love♪
You approached me
because of the Qiu family's treasure.
♪The bustling street echo
with clatter of carts♪
Initially yes, but then I...
♪The sun and moon, heaven and earth,
play an endless game♪
Boss,
♪Who waives and who wanders♪
what's the matter?
She has found out
that I approached her
for the Qiu family's treasure.
But you did fall in love with her,
and you didn't steal the treasure map.
The mission failed,
and you got brutally beaten by the Warlord.
It took you half a month to get well.
So what?
A mistaken is a mistake.
I can't justify myself.
Tell her the truth.
Otherwise, the misunderstanding
will last forever.
What's the point of that?
No matter how many excuses I use,
it's irretrievable.
If I had returned earlier,
her family wouldn't have been massacred.
♪Playing my part
through absurd years of strife♪
Her seven years of misery,
at the end of the day,
is my fault.
All on me.
♪Rushed out of the play,
but got trapped again♪
Dad,
I'm sorry.
I let the enemy in.
I got you all killed.
(My Beloved Father Qiu Nianyuan)
(Longxi Hall)
Sister,
I will help you get rid of Gu Yanting.
Muran,
my influence
is built on his Northern Division.
He cannot be dead yet.
But he doesn't deserve you.
You will receive the Du family's aid.
Muran,
be at Aunt's side.
Stay out of it.
Sister,
you can finally see
Gu Yanting's true colors.
You will understand
that in this world,
I'm the only one who truly loves you.
You shouldn't have come.
You were away for two days.
Gu Liang
told me you didn't eat well.
I won't eat anything you cook anymore.
Take them away.
You may hate me,
but you shouldn't be hard on yourself.
Will you justify yourself?
I'm sorry.
Why didn't you dodge?
Don't you forget
that you taught me this.
Do you enjoy
toying me?
♪Fleeting thoughts drift♪
♪Like scattered leaves♪
♪So many words my heart believes
hidden in heart's wraps♪
If it makes you happy,
you can just kill me.
Sometimes, I don't know
what is the real you?
I love you.
It's real.
♪Scattered♪
♪In the tales of our past♪
♪When I glance back♪
Do you think I'd still
listen to these words?
♪Even if you're only in my dreams♪
Don't come again.
I don't want to hurt you.
♪Like it's the first♪
♪As if a thousand years have passed♪
♪Can we pen our love across the years♪
♪When I glance back♪
♪It feels like the first sight♪
♪Even if you're only in my dreams♪
♪I willingly hold on tight♪
People say,
"love is as new as first sight."
♪Like it's the first♪
The funny thing is,
our first sight was a plot.
♪Cherish every moment that appears♪
Can we have him?
Don't know.
(Northern Division soldiers?)
Gu Yanting, we were ordered to kill you!
- Run!
- Go!
Hurry.
Ma'am.
Ma'am, bad news.
Boss got assassinated.
What?
Is he...
Is Gu Yanting dead?
He's still alive.
But heavily injured.
Do you know who did it?
Judging from the clips,
it was Northern Division soldiers.
You're back.
You escaped death.
Very lucky.
If you want me dead,
you can do it personally.
Don't you worry.
I will kill you myself.
But you still have worth,
so for now,
I let you live.
Gu Liang,
stop following me anymore.
You watch him closely.
Starting today,
Gu Yanting
are not allowed to leave this room.
♪Who penned an extra line♪
♪Altered the words' design♪
♪The metaphors are vague♪
♪Just a phrase or two to find♪
♪Love and hate too fierce,
hearts racing in the chase♪
♪Time is a sonnet♪
♪Destiny's playful and coy♪
♪How can I choose it♪
♪Yet it lingers, impossible to destroy♪
♪Context shifts♪
♪Quietly hinting at themes♪
♪On a page, a flawed phrase gleams♪
♪Names erased, lost in the seams♪
♪The reason why remains unseen♪
♪Time is a sonnet♪
♪Destiny's playful and coy♪
♪How can I choose it♪
♪Yet it lingers, impossible to destroy♪
♪Context shifts♪
♪Quietly hinting at themes♪
♪On a page, a flawed phrase gleams♪
♪Names erased, lost in the seams♪
♪The reason why remains unseen♪
(The right of communication
through information network of the production)
(is exclusively owned
by Shenzhen Tencent Computer System Co., Ltd.)