♪When I glance back♪
♪It feels like the first sight♪
♪Even if you're only in my dreams♪
♪I willingly hold on tight♪
♪Like it's the first♪
♪As if a thousand years have passed♪
♪Can we pen our love across the years♪
♪Cherish every moment that appears♪
=The Princess=
=Episode 38=
=It Snows Again, But He Is Gone=
(Sunshine Western Restaurant)
(It's snowing.)
(In our childhood,
Muran and I loved the snowing days.)
(We could have snowball fights)
(and make snowmen.)
(Now that we are adults,)
(we are always troubled.)
(We don't have such fun anymore.)
Qiu Ruoran,
if it wasn't for you,
Wanrou wouldn't die.
I will make you pay with your life.
- Yue!
- Sister!
Muran!
S-Sister, I'm sorry.
I made many mistakes.
I harmed you and Gu Yanting.
Can you please forgive me?
I will never blame you.
Stop talking.
Sister,
do you still like me
the way you did when we were little?
I do.
Good.
I...
I'm so cold.
The scarf you gave me,
I can't find it.
It's okay.
I'll buy you another one.
OK.
It's snowing.
Muran.
I'm going to see Mum.
I am not a good son.
Nor am I a good brother.
Sister.
Sister, it's snowing.
Muran.
Muran!
Run.
So cold.
♪A strange tale♪
Cold?
Here.
Does it warm you up?
It does.
Tie you up as well.
Sure.
Let's go.
Be careful.
Run!
Here we go!
♪The sun and moon,heaven and earth,
play an endless game♪
♪Grudges and disputes have become an obsession♪
♪Playing my part
through absurd years of strife♪
♪I waited, but dawn never breaks♪
♪Rushed out of the play, but got trapped again♪
Wanrou...
Muran...
You will never see them again.
They are going to Heaven,
while you are going to
Hell.
Muran is dead.
Muran.
I failed to protect you, Muran.
I'm sorry.
I'll take him to another room
in case he annoys you.
Only with Xiaozhentou around
can I have the peace of mind.
You haven't had anything today.
Would you like some porridge?
Let me feed you.
Here.
Muran's funeral is ready.
Will you see him one last time?
Muran couldn't withstand cold.
He told me he couldn't find his scarf,
I'd like to buy him a new one.
I'll go with you.
Yue,
the three of us
are a family.
Just don't face danger on our own
without telling us.
Mum, will Uncle like the scarf I choose?
He will.
What are you looking at?
Nothing.
Mum,
when will we visit Uncle?
Now.
Dad,
will we buy some desserts for Uncle?
He always buys desserts for me,
so I'd like to buy some for him.
Sure.
(Alice Bakery)
(Bugao Alley)
Boss,
Old Warlord is losing in Ningcheng.
It's urgent.
We have received message that Old Warlord
plans to take his troops to Jiangcheng.
Father is coming
to Jiangcheng with his men?
Then war is upon Jiangcheng.
He must be stopped.
I need to go out of the city.
You wait me at home.
Dad,
war is dangerous.
I don't want you to go.
Is it that urgent?
Xiao Li still lurks around.
When my foster father is here,
they will meet,
and my soldiers
won't be able to cope
with their joint forces.
Things will only get more difficult.
So I must stop him
before he gets in town.
It is urgent.
For the sake of Jiangcheng,
I have to go.
Xiaozhentou,
do you know
who your real dad is?
I don't know.
But I love Daddy here.
Who you are looking at
is your biological father.
Really?
Dad.
I'm your real son.
I have finally found my father.
Dad.
Dad!
- My son.
- Dad!
No tears.
Dad!
My son.
- I want no regrets.
- Dad!
I hope
you come back home safe and sound.
Wait for me to come home.
We'll take a family picture.
Boss, time to go.
♪Lost in the years, one after another♪
Yue,
I have a file on my desk.
After Muran's funeral,
when you feel better,
you can check it.
♪In the end, it fades like smoke in a dance♪
♪Scattered♪
♪In the tales of our past♪
♪When I glance back♪
♪It feels like the first sight♪
I must go.
Yanting,
♪I willingly hold on tight♪
I know I can't keep you.
♪As if a thousand years have passed♪
So you must be careful.
I promise you
that I will be back.
♪When I glance back♪
♪It feels like the first sight♪
♪Even if you're only in my dreams♪
♪I willingly hold on tight♪
♪Like it's the first♪
♪As if a thousand years have passed♪
♪Can we pen our love across the years♪
♪Cherish every moment that appears♪
♪Who penned an extra line♪
♪Altered the words' design♪
♪The metaphors are vague♪
♪Just a phrase or two to find♪
♪Love and hate too fierce,
hearts racing in the chase♪
♪Time is a sonnet♪
♪Destiny's playful and coy♪
♪How can I choose it♪
♪Yet it lingers, impossible to destroy♪
♪Context shifts♪
♪Quietly hinting at themes♪
♪On a page, a flawed phrase gleams♪
♪Names erased, lost in the seams♪
♪The reason why remains unseen♪
♪Time is a sonnet♪
♪Destiny's playful and coy♪
♪How can I choose it♪
♪Yet it lingers, impossible to destroy♪
♪Context shifts♪
♪Quietly hinting at themes♪
♪On a page, a flawed phrase gleams♪
♪Names erased, lost in the seams♪
♪The reason why remains unseen♪
(The right of communication
through information network of the production)
(is exclusively owned
by Shenzhen Tencent Computer System Co., Ltd.)