♪When I glance back♪
♪It feels like the first sight♪
♪Even if you're only in my dreams♪
♪I willingly hold on tight♪
♪Like it's the first♪
♪As if a thousand years have passed♪
♪Can we pen our love across the years♪
♪Cherish every moment that appears♪
=The Princess=
=Episode 30=
=But Only You=
(House of Qiu)
It's been years
since you came home last time.
Are you worried
that you can't face them
because they are yet to be avenged?
You staying alive
is the greatest solace for them.
(Longxi Hall)
(My Beloved Father Qiu Nianyuan)
Dad,
believe me,
I will avenge the Qiu and the Li families,
and realize your dream
of saving our nation.
(Longxi Hall)
(Mr. Qiu,)
(I know, for who I am)
(I shouldn't even be here,)
(but I guarantee)
(that as long as I can,)
(I will take good care of Yue)
(and help her achieve her goals)
(until I am no longer needed.)
Where are Du's men?
They have been driven out.
When did you do it?
Why didn't you tell me?
The Armory is now yours.
Both Xiao Li and Du Hanqing
will hold you in respect,
including my foster father.
In Jiangcheng,
no one will dare to threaten you.
Mine?
I'm only managing it
for you for the time being.
Now that you have returned
and are in good shape,
the Northern Division should
be handed over back to you.
You are more suitable for it.
Why me?
Because all the other people
have their own interest,
nobody is like you
or your father
who worked whole-heartedly
for the interest of Jiangcheng civilians.
What about you?
Me?
I have mine as well.
What is that?
My interest is
you.
Also, the Armory
was originally the Qiu family's asset.
You are the rightful owner.
Dad, tea for you.
Dad,
why must we
establish a machinery factory
to do business with foreigners?
Because in the modern age,
the Westerners
own the advanced technologies.
If we wish to develop,
we must first learn.
Like what Mr. Wei Yuan said.
"Learn from foreigners to beat them."
Ruoran,
I hope you return soon
and help me run the factory.
Unfortunately,
Dad didn't achieve his goal,
instead, our family was ruined.
And this place
has become the target
of all those warlords.
I actually agree with Mr. Qiu.
However, in this day,
a peaceful and stable life
has become wishing thinking.
Yanting,
we may pick up your previous plan
and provide arms for everyone.
When the war is over,
we'll convert it
into a machinery factory
to provide resources for everyone.
This way,
our life will get better and better.
OK.
Oh my.
A rare visitor.
Welcome.
Mr. Du,
how things have changed.
It isn't easy to meet you.
You are out of Xiao Mansion.
Which, too, is quite a change.
What would you like to talk to me?
A good deal.
(Title Deed)
Title dead for the Armory.
Too bad,
you warlords
keep competing over the Armory,
so even if I have this deed,
what would be the point?
With this deed,
you'll be the legal owner of the Armory.
What?
Do you plan to buy me off with this?
Mr. Du,
I remember
you were the largest shareholder
of the Armory initially,
but Gu Yanting took it from you
and gave it to a woman.
Word on Jiangcheng street
says you, as the biggest arms dealer,
couldn't even keep your own thing.
How can you tolerate it?
How would you like me to help you,
so I can have the deed?
Help me rebuild my Jiangcheng Army.
Mum, why are dressing like this?
Are you feeling unwell?
It's you. Where's your dad?
Dad said
he knew I miss you,
so he let you have me tonight.
He's avoiding me on purpose.
Mum, do you prefer Dad
over me?
No way.
I love Xiaozhentou.
Tonight, you sleep with Mum.
I'm sorry.
I thought your injuries
had gotten better,
but they are even worse.
Boss,
you wanted the Armory back,
I could have done it for you.
Why must you personally do it?
You weren't healed,
and now you're in a worse state.
I must get back
what belongs to Yue myself.
But...
No but.
Don't tell Yue I'm injured.
♪Broken apart in the heat of love♪
I'm okay. The wounds dehisced.
I'll be fine soon.
♪Tasting the sting of hidden lies♪
♪Only to realize♪
This is the deepest cut
and it's the closest to your heart.
It's a fatal wound.
You are agile and alert,
the person who did it
must be someone you know
or even very close to.
Don't make wild guesses.
♪Pulling at my every smile♪
Could it be your ex-wife?
♪Unaware of love's uncertain mile♪
I swore that I wouldn't get jealous,
but you once loved her very much.
No matter what,
she shouldn't be so cold.
She hurt you so badly,
why do you still defend her?
♪As the heavy rain pours down♪
♪I alone bear the win and loss♪
♪In every life, my wish remains♪
♪To be your redemption, no matter the cost♪
♪If not for that fateful mistake♪
There has been no one else.
But only you.
♪How could parting become
our last path to salvation♪
♪Once the snow fell softly♪
♪We promised to walk until the end♪
Then you must be good.
You mustn't be injured again.
Sure.
♪Who penned an extra line♪
♪Altered the words' design♪
♪The metaphors are vague♪
♪Just a phrase or two to find♪
♪Love and hate too fierce,
hearts racing in the chase♪
♪Time is a sonnet♪
♪Destiny's playful and coy♪
♪How can I choose it♪
♪Yet it lingers, impossible to destroy♪
♪Context shifts♪
♪Quietly hinting at themes♪
♪On a page, a flawed phrase gleams♪
♪Names erased, lost in the seams♪
♪The reason why remains unseen♪
♪Time is a sonnet♪
♪Destiny's playful and coy♪
♪How can I choose it♪
♪Yet it lingers, impossible to destroy♪
♪Context shifts♪
♪Quietly hinting at themes♪
♪On a page, a flawed phrase gleams♪
♪Names erased, lost in the seams♪
♪The reason why remains unseen♪
(The right of communication
through information network of the production)
(is exclusively owned
by Shenzhen Tencent Computer System Co., Ltd.)