♪When I glance back♪
♪It feels like the first sight♪
♪Even if you're only in my dreams♪
♪I willingly hold on tight♪
♪Like it's the first♪
♪As if a thousand years have passed♪
♪Can we pen our love across the years♪
♪Cherish every moment that appears♪
=The Princess=
=Episode 25=
=Now, I Am the Northern Division Commander=
(Xiao Mansion)
Mr. Du,
welcome.
What brings you here?
Captain Gu,
let's have a word in private.
We can talk
in front of my bros.
Now, Gu Yanting and Xiao Li
are missing at the same time.
Jiangcheng is
in the Northern Division's control.
A new Division Commander is needed.
Captain Gu, what do you think?
Who do you suggest,
Mr. Du?
It's men's business.
Stay out of it, woman.
Muran,
get out of my way.
This is Boss's gun.
Yes, it is.
Yanting gave it to me.
The gun represents the man.
The gun is the witness.
From today on,
before Yanting returns,
I am the Northern Division Commander.
Anyone who proposes
cooperation
are welcome.
Gu Liang,
now that Mr. Du is here with his offer,
why don't you take the gold bars?
Yes, Madam.
Jiangcheng needs to be rebuilt.
The money comes just in time.
To express the gratitude
for Mr. Du's generosity,
a pennant will be made
and delivered to your mansion.
Miss Jiang,
I underestimated you.
Call me Mrs. Gu, please.
If you want collaboration,
you're welcome to come.
Gu Liang,
see them off.
Please.
Sister.
- I...
- Muran.
Come with me.
Sister.
Just come with me.
Wise up, you!
Muran,
don't act against
your father because of me.
Go now.
Sister, what about you?
I'll go to Gu's house.
Take care of yourself and your mum.
Just go.
Let's go.
(Xiao Mansion)
(Bugao Alley)
Yanting,
I don't care about what people say.
I will wait for you to come back.
You'll be okay.
Won't you?
Madam, bad news.
What's the matter?
When I was in your aunt's house,
Xiaozhentou had already been
taken away by Du's men.
They also asked
to you got to Du Mansion.
Sorry, we have rules.
This way, please.
Ruruo,
you are Wanrou's niece
and Muran's loved one,
there's no need
for hostility between us.
We can talk.
About what?
I have heard
you are mustering Jiangcheng Army
which served under Xiao Li.
Mr. Du,
you are a businessman.
I'm afraid
this is not the right topic for us.
Keep Gu Yanting's
Northern Division separated,
name your price,
I want the rest of Jiangcheng Army.
And why is that?
Mr. Du,
I am curious
about your purpose
behind your action.
A businessman
always pursues profit.
As far as I know,
both you and Gu Yanting
care much about the boy.
Soldiers!
Put down your guns!
Do it. Do it.
Put down your guns.
You'd better give the boy
back to me safe and sound.
A woman and a boy,
with no one to rely on,
aren't you tired?
Just choose an easy way.
Shut up.
Where is he?
Go. Go.
Listen to me.
Just listen.
Muran is in deep love with you.
You may even
become my daughter-in-law.
Just shut up!
Sir, bad news.
Young Master has taken the boy away.
(Bugao Alley)
Xiaozhentou
Mum!
Xiaozhentou.
Sister.
Are you injured?
Xiaozhentou,
go upstairs with Gu Liang.
Come on.
Let's go.
Sister,
our child died young,
but from now on,
I will take care of you and Xiaozhentou.
Thank you for getting him out.
But I'm doing fine.
I can take care of myself.
Muran,
let's talk.
I admit that Du Hanqing
shouldn't take Xiaozhentou away.
I apologize to you on his behalf.
You are right.
But what Du Hanqing did has got
nothing to do with you.
This isn't what I want to talk about.
My enmity with Du Hanqing
puts you in a difficult situation,
which isn't what I intended,
but it is what it is.
There's no way back.
So,
how about we...
You wish to break off with me.
Since I learned about the past,
I have noticed
we are walking away from each other.
It's late.
Go home.
Du Muran, what are you doing?
Sister, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean by that.
I just don't want you to leave me.
I've got used to you.
I've got used to
the life with you since we were little.
I can't accept what you said to me.
I feel terrible. I'm sorry.
Sister.
Muran.
You have changed.
I...
Sister,
are you sure
it isn't you who have changed?
(Bugao Alley)
♪A strange tale♪
♪A blend of truth and lies♪
♪Hide behind the mask just to get by♪
♪Endless sighs day and night♪
♪Without asking for a return date♪
♪Love is fleeting♪
♪But hate is unwavering♪
♪An endless supply♪
♪The cheapest wholehearted love♪
♪One's love fails the other's♪
♪The world hold boundless joy ever since♪
Muran,
aren't you cold?
I'm okay.
I'm not cold, Sister.
Auntie punished you again?
♪The sun and moon, heaven and earth,
play an endless game♪
♪The hardest thing to grasp is
the human heart♪
How do you feel now?
♪You stubbornly choose your way alone♪
♪Painting peace in a world overthrown♪
You silly.
Auntie isn't serious.
Come. Let's get inside.
♪Grudges and disputes
have become an obsession♪
♪Playing my part
through absurd years of strife♪
♪I waited, but dawn never breaks♪
♪Rushed out of the play,
but got trapped again♪
♪Who penned an extra line♪
♪Altered the words' design♪
♪The metaphors are vague♪
♪Just a phrase or two to find♪
♪Love and hate too fierce,
hearts racing in the chase♪
♪Time is a sonnet♪
♪Destiny's playful and coy♪
♪How can I choose it♪
♪Yet it lingers, impossible to destroy♪
♪Context shifts♪
♪Quietly hinting at themes♪
♪On a page, a flawed phrase gleams♪
♪Names erased, lost in the seams♪
♪The reason why remains unseen♪
♪Time is a sonnet♪
♪Destiny's playful and coy♪
♪How can I choose it♪
♪Yet it lingers, impossible to destroy♪
♪Context shifts♪
♪Quietly hinting at themes♪
♪On a page, a flawed phrase gleams♪
♪Names erased, lost in the seams♪
♪The reason why remains unseen♪
(The right of communication
through information network of the production)
(is exclusively owned
by Shenzhen Tencent Computer System Co., Ltd.)