If I don't have feelings for Dugu Ruonan,
I won't like her.
You know, liking someone
is like
having allergies,
You can't hide it.
You care about her,
care about her, be nervous about her,
Be soft on her,
Ji Mo Think about it carefully,
You really don't have feelings for her?
Those snobs,
when you're popular,
Count them back one by one.
Sis,
forget it. You're tired too.
Why don't you go home and rest first.
I'm going home. Where are you going?
You can't go back to the hotel.
If you are recognized,
there will be paparazzi.
Right,
I don't know where to go.
Just stay at my house.
Let me see where Chen Fei'er is.
I can go find her.
Okay,
Hello? Are you home?
How are you doing
in the hospital?
Are you all right?
Is there anything else wrong?
I'm fine. Don't be nervous.
Didn't I tell you
on the phone,
I feel much better now.
Why did you come all the way here?
I heard from Xiaoxiao,
you're allergic because of Ji Mo.
He put you in the hospital?
I told him to leave first.
I'm leaving.
Why don't you let him stay with you?
What's the use of keeping someone
but not keeping my heart?
Silly girl.
Find a way to keep him first.
Then win your heart.
Take him down first.
Who am I?
Chen Fei'er,
I did it for a man
who doesn't like me at all.
I'm going to
grovel to him.
It's boring.
So I decided to give up.
I gave up.
Didn't you say
you liked him a few days ago?
But the person he likes is you.
It's impossible.
I knew it a long time ago.
The way
he looks at you is different.
Trust my judgment on men,
that's right,
Don't be ridiculous.
It's impossible for me to be with him.
Why?
Because of me? Yes.
It's impossible for me to like
the man my bestie once liked,
Dugu Ruonan,
what time is it now,
Can you not be
so old-fashioned? Don't be so old-fashioned.
I like him. That's my business.
What does it have to do with you?
Besides,
I'm not in a relationship with him.
You're not
a third party involved,
Just a man.
Is it comparable to
our best friend's relationship
for so many years?
Am I right?
Don't hang in there.
I can tell you're upset.
I … I do. Yes, I do feel
bad.
But losing to you
will make me feel
a little less sad,
If it were someone else,
I wouldn't be convinced.
Let me tell you,
in my heart,
you're not the only one who cares about me,
Besides me,
what about the best woman in the world?
You and Ji Mo?
Actually, they are quite suitable for each other.
Two happy enemies.
Since I abdicated,
you have to make up for it successfully.
If Ji Mo dares to bully you,
you must tell me,
As it happens, I'll avenge my old
and new enmity together.
Miss,
mind your own business.
Take good care of yourself.
Don't make random matches for me.
I really have
a lot of things to do recently.
Sida still has a lot of things
to deal with,
I didn't even dream about it.
Some or not,
You're right.
Work matters.
I really think,
Ji Mo is a really
good man.
Hold on to it.
Again
Think about it.
Sis,
How are you? Are you okay?
It's okay.
I chatted with her for a while.
I came out after seeing her sleeping.
Let's go.
Where are you going?
You're so busy with Chen Fei'er
that you forget your business.
Welcome.
Welcome home.
Why did you change your attitude again?
Don't smile like that. It's scary.
What are you talking about?
I just want to
express my feelings for you
as a roommate
before you move out,
I have no feelings for you.
A sloppy,
overbearing and snobbish woman like you,
How could I have feelings for you?
And I can't move out.
It's okay. I want something from you.
I can bear it.
Why are you here?
Hello,
Sida has been under a lot of pressure lately,
I want to enlighten him more.
After all, I'm a senior.
So I decided,
until the problem is solved,
He lives with us.
He wants to live here.
There are only two rooms.
Where does he sleep?
I'll sleep
with you. You've both slept together.
Once born and twice cooked.
Let's take a step back.
You don't have to move out.
How about letting him move in?
Dugu Ruonan,
are you mistaken?
For the sake of your
homelessness,
That's why I asked you to move in.
It's fine now.
I led the wolf into the house.
You occupied the nest of magpies,
without even saying a word.
So I brought him in.
Do you think this is a dormitory?
Sis, why don't I go home first?
Don't interrupt when adults are talking.
No.
What if it's dangerous?
Mr. Ji,
I'm really pitiful today.
Being bullied everywhere, I … I'm so
tired.
I'm begging you. Please, brother.
I'm begging you.
Please,
look at him,
With such a young child,
where can he go?
It's dangerous.
Please, brother! Please!
Please, brother,
it's okay to live here,
But sleep on the sofa.
What's wrong with me today?
I can't believe she's acting.
You care about her.
Nervous
and soft-hearted towards her,
No way.
I have to move out today.
It's useless for you to cry.
I won't be soft-hearted if it doesn't work.
That's good.
He sleeps in my room,
Sis,
It's not good. I'll sleep with you.
Who's sleeping with you?
What are you thinking?
Can you sleep in my room
and I sleep on the sofa?
You sleep on the sofa
alone. Forget it.
Sleep with me.
Mr. Ji, Mr. Ji is so nice.
Mr. Ji,
thank you, Mr. Ji.
You're so nice.
-Thank you. -That's great.
So fierce.
Forget it. Never mind.
Success
We did it.
Brother,
Are you going to the toilet?
the toilet is over there.
Brother,
Are you sleepwalking?
Dugu Ruonan,
sleepwalkers are like this.
Brother,
this is Ruonan's room,
Our room is over there.
I like Dugu Ruonan,
why do you
like Ruonan?
It's not impossible.
I don't like Dugu Ruonan.
That's right,
Do I like her or not?
It doesn't matter anymore.
Let's go back to sleep.
Thank you.
For what?
Thank you for accepting Sida.
I know what to do,
It might cause you trouble.
But he still had the cheek
to bring him here.
Because for me,
this is the safest place.
How are you going
to solve Sida's problem?
On the contrary, it was this incident
that made me realize,
The most important thing to do right now,
is not to knock anyone down,
It's about strengthening yourself.
I'm relieved
that you're so aggressive.
When you think about it,
actually,
You've helped me a lot,
you,
Although it seems unreliable,
it's actually quite reliable.
Sis,
I've changed it.
Sida, let's go.
Sis,
Where are we going today?
Do you want to see a reporter?
Back to the company,
I'm going to hire some teachers for you
to give you some professional training.
Like singing, dancing,
saying lines or something,
About the fight,
Sida?
I know you're upset.
I also thought that
I could just post the recording online,
But to do so,
it's just a short-lived act,
You're an artist
trained by the company now.
If the company
wants to suppress you,
It won't do you any good.
Man,
you have to succeed.
You have to learn to be patient.
We have to face the reality,
because we are not strong enough.
Instead of wasting your energy
dealing with your opponent.
It's better
to make yourself better.
Remember,
man's greatest rival.
Always yourself.
Not someone else.
Sis,
Actually, I don't care
if I'm wronged, do I?
I'm just afraid that
I might get you into trouble.
I'm afraid you've been wronged.
You've done too much for me.
You hired a teacher and got demoted.
Yeah,
I'm a great kid,
Remember,
I'm not the kind of person
who gives for nothing.
When you become popular in the future,
make a lot of money for me,
And let me be
my managing director again.
I will try my best.
How about I do it myself?
Don't move.
It hurts.
As long as it hurts.
Are you stupid?
Scratching your car and pushing you?
You didn't even fight back.
How can I fight back?
If I fight back,
the other party will definitely add fuel to it,
He said Sida's agent hit someone,
how can he do that?
Sis,
Sis, are you okay?
Why did you ask him to come to me?
If you let him laugh at me, I … Are you still a
man?
You're not responsible at all.
You didn't say anything when you saw her being bullied.
No,
A woman was beaten for you.
Don't you feel embarrassed?
Don't blame him.
I told him to stay out of it.
Also,
when will it be your turn
to teach my artistes a lesson.
Okay,
It's not his fault,
it's my fault,
It's my fault to meddle.
Don't take his words to heart.
Ignore him. I'm fine.
It hurts, right? It doesn't hurt.
It's just a small injury.
It'll be fine tomorrow.
Brother,
Am I useless?
When that senior
pushed Ruonan,
I wanted to stop him.
But he's a senior member of the company.
I'm afraid I'll offend him.
He'll get back at us in the future.
I blame myself. I regret it.
I regret why I was
so cowardly back then,
You're right.
I'm not a man.
You can't even protect
the woman you like.
Sida?
Women need
men to protect them.
Just because she doesn't cry pain
doesn't mean she doesn't.
If you don't help her
relieve the pain in time,
It will cause secondary damage to her.
Don't wait until one day,
she leaves you.
If you regret it again.
I know what to do.
What are you going to do?
I have to face it alone.
You're right.
I'm a man.
You shouldn't just hide behind women.
There are many ways to solve the problem,
so we should treat it rationally.
Don't be impulsive.
Do you hear me?
Don't worry, brother.
I won't cause Ruonan
any more trouble.
Why did he get up so early?
Although yesterday,
you were rude to me,
But considering that
you care about me and do what's best for me,
Then I forgive you.
From now on,
just don't cause me any trouble.
Brother and sister,
I've prepared breakfast for you.
Thank you. You're so sensible.
Aren't you going to eat?
I'll take a walk downstairs later.
I'll be back in a minute. It's good
that this happens,
I'm going to relax.
Adjust your mood,
but if you put on your mask,
In times of emergency,
don't be recognized by others.
Take good care of yourself.
I've caused you
a lot of trouble recently.
I'm sorry.
Why did you say that again?
This is my job.
It's what I should do.
There's nothing to be sorry about.
Come back early.
Yes.
Why don't you eat?
Sida's expression is wrong.
He's been covering it up.
Suppress your emotions,
you'll be sad
if something like this happens.
Just relax.
Don't think too much.
I'm still worried.
I'll go check it out.
You eat first.
No problem.
Sida?
Brother,
Where are you going?
Let me walk around.
Don't lie, kid.
Brother, I'm in a mess right now.
Leave me
alone.
I just hope,
before you do anything,
You have to think about it carefully.
Don't do things you regret
on impulse.
Don't worry, brother.
I know what to do.
Also,
yesterday was just
a bit heavy-tongued,
It's too much to say.
If you're impatient,
I don't mean to dislike you.
I just hope,
when something like this
happens to you in the future,
I'll do better.
Don't let it happen again.
It won't happen again.
I promise you,
it won't happen again
in the future.
I'm going for a walk.
This kid is really worrying.
I hope he can recover.
I'm here.
Who is it?
What do you
want to do?
What do you want?
I'm telling you,
you're trespassing.
I can call the police.
What do you want me to do?
So that you can spare Ruonan and me.
So you're here to make peace.
What's wrong? Are you scared now?
I'm here to admit my mistake.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have done it last time.
Pretending,
Sure,
If you kneel down,
I'll forgive you.
You really knelt down.
I'm telling you,
don't do this to me.
If a man has gold under his knee,
get up if he's a man.
I was wrong, brother.
Get up! Zihao,
get up!
If you don't kneel enough,
I'll kowtow to you,
Please forgive me.
I was really wrong.
Zihao, please come forward to clarify,
and forgive Ruonan and me.
Dugu Ruonan, you're really capable
Si Da, listen to me,
She's brainwashing you now.
I told you to be obedient to her,
but after a few years,
When you have your own ideas,
and you don't want to be exploited
by her anymore,
She'll kick you away.
Then she'll find someone else
to replace you.
Just like now. No.
No, it's not like that.
I asked for it myself.
Ruonan didn't ask me to come.
Please forgive us.
I just need to clarify anything.
Okay,
I can clarify it.
Get up first, okay?
Come on, get up.
Really?
I can go.
Are you really willing to clarify?
Sida,
I'm not here for you.
I can clarify it for you.
But it's impossible for Dugu Ruonan.
I will never forgive her.
Why?
She's no longer your agent.
It has nothing to do with you.
Why are you still pestering her?
What can I do
to make you forgive Ruonan,
What do you want me to do?
Tell me.
Tell me,
what do you want me to do?
You're right.
I have nothing
to do with her anymore.
Why should I give her a hard time?
Does that mean as long as
I don't target Dugu Ruonan anymore,
You can do whatever I ask you to do.
Yes.
Okay,
You said it.
Kid,
why are you the only one at home?
Where's Sida?
I was just about to ask you.
Isn't he with you?
He couldn't find anyone,
and he didn't answer the phone. What's wrong?
In the morning, I felt like,
he's not looking right,
He even specifically told him
if anything bad would happen to him?
Calm down.
Let's analyze it calmly,
Sit down
Sida must have subconsciously
thought it was him.
That caused you to be besieged by fans.
So he must have been
looking for a solution.
I can't solve it.
How to deal with that kid?
Or to put it another way,
among the people he comes into contact with,
No one can
help him solve the problem.
Song Zihao,
Zihao is very hostile
to Sida.
If he goes to see him,
he'll die.
The priority now
is to find Sida.
I remember now.
I was secretly
on Sida's phone,
Have you installed
positioning software? Are you a pervert?
It's a top priority.
What are you doing
in the night club?
Each of you, make a toast to my junior brother.
You must
make my junior brother drink well today.
Sure. Handsome guy,
come on. I don't drink.
I don't drink.
Have a drink. Have a drink.
I won't drink it.
Brother, I don't drink.
Sida?
You don't have to
drink it. From today on,
It has nothing to do with you.
Let's go.
Handsome guy, you're a good drinker.
You're amazing.
Don't pretend to be reserved
just now. Yes. Drink more.
Drink a little more and keep drinking
Okay,
Handsome, let's have a drink together.
Let's drink together.
You're a good drinker.
Zihao,
I've finished four drinks.
That's a lot.
That's too much.
After drinking this pot of wine,
I'll clarify it to the reporters tomorrow.
For Dugu Ruonan,
are you worth it?
After I finish this wine,
don't forget what you promised me.
Drink it.
This is your choice.
Don't blame me,
handsome boy. I can't do this.
Get up, handsome boy.
Come on.
Up ahead.
Sida?
Sida
He was drunk a lot.
What do you think? Pale face,
hypothermia,
It could be alcohol poisoning.
Send him to the hospital.
Come on,
be careful. Be careful,
okay? Let's go.
Luckily, you came in time.
If you were a little late,
The patient's life will be in danger.
Now that the patient's signs are stable,
just take a break.
If anything happens,
you can call me anytime.
Okay. Thank you, nurse.
Are you okay?
It's okay.
I just heard what the nurse said,
I think it's scary.
If you hadn't found out that
he was poisoned by alcohol,
He might be dead.
Don't worry. He's fine now.
Stay with me all day.
You're tired too.
Go back and rest.
I can stay with him.
I'll stay with you for a while.
Multiple people,
multiple partners.
Thank you.
Why is he
so silly?
Hello, boss. What is it?
Dugu Ruonan, what are you doing?
What do you mean?
Look at what Sida has done.
How do you discipline
your own artistes.
Read it online.
It's already on the hot searches.
I'm calling to tell you,
this kind of misdeeds
won't be taken by the artist company.
Hello.
Brother,
You're awake.
Why am I in the hospital?
You were drunk yesterday,
and Ruonan and I
sent you here.
What happened yesterday?
Yesterday,
no need to ask.
What he did yesterday
has been on the hot searches.
Sister.
No,
that's not true, sister.
What did you do yesterday?
Why are you
with Song Zihao.
I want to solve this problem.
So I went to him.
He asked me to drink the wine,
so I could clarify it.
He said he would clarify it to the media.
I didn't expect you
to believe Song Zihao's words,
What is he capable of?
To manipulate the media.
What should we do, sister?
How many times have I told you?
Don't be impulsive.
Don't get emotional.
Learn to be patient.
What is it?
You have to be the first to tell me.
But now you're hiding it from me.
Go find Song Zihao.
Now that you're in such a big trouble,
how can I help you deal with it?
He wants to protect you too.
He won't cause me any trouble.
It's good enough.
I'm also responsible for this.
I could have stopped Sida.
Blame me if you want to blame me.
Can blaming you
solve the problem now?
What's the use of worrying?
If something goes wrong,
you have to find a solution.
All right, stop arguing about this.
It's my own responsibility.
I'll do things by myself and be responsible by myself.
I quit the entertainment industry.
Sida?
You can't leave the hospital now.
Stop right there!
You quit the entertainment industry
so easily.
Do you think it's that easy?
What about the sufferings you've suffered?
Have you forgotten your dream of being an actress?
Forget it.
It doesn't matter anyway.
It doesn't matter.
Then what's important?
It doesn't matter if you say it's not important.
I'm your agent.
You respected me for quitting
without telling me,
Recite the artist's rule.
I don't need any rules anymore.
I don't need an agent.
Too tired in the entertainment industry?
I don't want to stay any longer.
After he calms down,
I'll talk to him.
No need to talk.
I don't need an artist
who gives up so easily.
Look, that's Sida
who was on the hot searches before, right?
You know him too?
Do you want another identity?
What identity?
My artist.
You have to believe in yourself.
Even if you don't believe in yourself,
you have to believe in me.
I can
make you
a top star,
From now on, no one will dare
to call you rubbish again,
Carry me first.
It's my turn to carry you
later. No need. Let me carry you
when you're drunk. No.
Why do you
have to be loyal when you come out to mix?
I'll carry you later.
I'll carry you.
I'll carry you on the podium.
Good actor,
We have a lot of feelings.
You have to love and feel pain.
I've been hurt before.
Only in this way can you
understand happiness, sadness and happiness,
So that you can bring your true feelings
into the play,
Use real emotions
to interpret other people's lives.
From now on, you just need to
listen to me,
What should I ask you to do?
What are you going to do?
I won't let you do anything.
Don't even think about it.
You can't lie to me or hide from me.
If you don't contact me,
your phone must be turned on 24 hours a day
and you must reply
to
text messages within two minutes.
You told me to go east, but I won't go west.
Sister, it's not that I don't want to recite it.
It's not that I don't want to carry it. I don't want to
Me,
I don't want to wait for you to abandon me.
It's not that I don't recite it.