What about
Do you want to help me?
Can I not help you?
But I'm really
A little sad.
You're so proactive.
Ask me out.
I thought you missed me.
I didn't expect that
Let me help you take the newbies.
Dugu Ruuo, let me ask you something.
Is work important?
Our relationship is more important.
You are important.
I want to make money.
Or you'll be old.
How can I raise you?
Okay, I want to hear this.
Seriously,
Help him more.
Teach him to walk on stage.
What kind of audition is there?
Just give him a lift.
I know.
What you asked me to do,
I will definitely help.
Correct!
Last time,
The one I told you about.
The new endorsement deal.
Guess who I met.
who
The handsome guy downstairs
The one downstairs
What a coincidence.
Is it a coincidence?
I didn't expect that
He is the president of Wing Fashion.
He is
It shows a very bad smell.
Promise me you won't go near him.
Stay away from him.
decline
Well
What does that mean?
Beauty, let's meet.
I don't have time.
Who are you?
I'm her husband.
husband
Aren't you a woman?
What's wrong with women?
You're free to be in a relationship now.
To disturb us.
Do you know?
Get lost
My husband is so handsome.
Kiss me.
roll
There's more drama.
My best friend.
So handsome. Thank you.
One more cup.
You feel safe.
Look, look.
You're so graceful.
Her legs are so long.
You're new here.
They say that serious men
The most charming.
To see you.
I finally believe that.
Don't you have the habit of knocking?
Knock it.
You didn't hear me.
What's the matter
Can't I come to you if I'm fine?
Yes
I have something to do today.
Please help me.
This new product show
I want to bring a male model on stage.
If I remember correctly,
This brand show is for women's wear.
We don't need male models.
But your subsidiary brand
Don't you have menswear?
Besides, every time,
Are all female models.
Walking here and there.
It's so boring.
Women's wear is for women.
Which woman?
I don't like to see handsome men.
Don't you think so?
It's a good suggestion.
but
This brand show
Has been rehearsed many times.
If a new model is installed,
To re-rehearse the design.
Will delay the project.
Don't worry.
You only need one.
When I came on stage,
He will stand next to me.
I'll be in charge of his rehearsal.
It seems that you're not interested
You're very thoughtful.
Are you jealous?
I'm never jealous.
That's because
You haven't met
Who can make you jealous.
For example,
If you don't agree,
I'll take it as
I'm jealous of him.
I promise you,
Really?
Thank you
This is your reward.
Bye
what
Ask Star to leave.
Wing fashion show.
That's right.
You asked me to help you.
Looking for a chance?
Then I'm
A ready-made opportunity.
And you know Zimmer.
Two people working together,
You're so talkative.
No way
I told you.
I don't agree with Ji Mo.
It's not good to touch them together.
It's you who can't pull your face.
Ask for help.
I've already said that
I would never...
To cooperate with Wing Fashion.
I'm going to beg him.
Isn't it very embarrassing?
I think this face
You have to fight.
Think about it.
For a year,
It'll be over soon.
If that handsome young man
We should hurry up.
Is that right?
Listen to me.
Hey, handsome guy.
Yes, he is so cute.
You're shy.
Let's go.
Why are you hiding?
It's all girls. I'm nervous.
This is the workplace.
These women are your colleagues.
You're here to finish the work.
What's there to be nervous about?
Show me your expertise.
I'm telling you,
Today,
I have one enemy.
Don't drop the ball.
Personal enemy
Well
Who is the enemy?
Don't ask so many questions.
Phil!
Mr. Ji, what you said
The male model?
We'll be there soon.
You know his manager?
I know him too.
If it's a male,
What a coincidence.
Hello, President Ji.
You look great, President Ji.
come
This is Star.
Tell me, Mr. Ji.
Hello, President Ji. I'm Si Da.
Such a good girl.
Hello
Phil!
Take Star with you.
To visit the company.
What a beautiful company.
I have something to tell you privately.
To talk to President Ji.
Alright. Take your time.
Let's go, handsome.
All right, everyone has left.
Stop pretending.
sorry
President Ji.
I was wrong last time.
But you're not the kind of person
Who seems to have a personal vendetta.
Our relationship
Don't affect the cooperation.
Star is my artist.
He's completely innocent.
I hope you can give him
A chance.
You really...
I'm willing to compromise for five rice.
But I'm telling you the truth.
This brand show
Is very important.
I can't use your artist.
why
You said that.
What's his strength and talent?
Nothing.
I want professional models.
It's not an embroidered pillow.
You didn't use him.
How do I know he's unprofessional?
As far as I know,
The theme of your company
Wild and primitive.
Is there any place in the world
Men and women
More primitive and wild?
The shape of Star is exactly the same.
All he needs is a chance.
It seems you came prepared.
Of course
I'm very familiar with it.
Each of your themes
I'm really sincere.
To cooperate with you.
Please give me a chance.
good
For the sake of your sincerity,
I'll give you a chance.
Thank you, President Ji.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Good cooperation.
Come in.
on
Just one.
Where are the clothes?
The theme of this issue is
The original wild
Have you ever seen a primitive wearing clothes?
Is there any doubt?
I'll wear it later.
In front of so many people,
The interview naked.
You're so conservative.
If a man says you are simple,
I believe it today.
As a model,
You can't let it go.
How can Ruonan lead you?
No wonder she has a headache.
I'm telling you,
Today,
I have one enemy.
Don't drop the ball.
I'll change.
that
Take off your clothes.
Then someone
I'll measure your figure.
Well
The clothes on show today are pretty.
Are you wearing it?
I haven't tried it yet.
Let me have a look.
Who are you going to be?
I don't know.
Help me.
That's it.
Your skin is so nice.
Thank you
Hold it for me.
I'll try over there.
Yeah.
I want to be professional.
I want to work hard.
I can't embarrass you.
Hello, President Ji.
hard
Sida
brother
Brother, I'm here.
It's almost time. Come out.
Brother, can you come in?
Brother
I just want to show it to you.
Are you satisfied?
Brother, brother.
What's wrong with you?
Who taught you that?
Nothing.
Sister, save my sister.
Why did you hit my artist?
He seduced me.
No, no.
It's a misunderstanding.
It was Phyl who asked me to take off my clothes.
Waiting for an interview.
I dare not show it to others.
I want to show him first.
I didn't expect that
So he hit me.
You're so sneaky.
Don't ask others to misunderstand.
You don't want to be seen.
How to be a model?
And you.
He's a new guy.
You have no judgment?
He said it was a misunderstanding.
He will explain it clearly.
Sida
You can be a good model, right?
I
can
Yes, he can.
I'll wait and see.
Don't be nervous.
I'll take you with me later.
Relax
Is this what you call a good model?
At the beginning,
Sida
Oh, my god. Am I so charming?
What's wrong with Star?
What's up
What's wrong? Let me see.
Are you all right?
Don't touch him.
lying flat
Look at the ceiling.
Take a deep breath
sister
Well
It's okay.
She's recovered.
Come here, Si Da.
How is it?
sister
It's all right.
Is it OK?
His eyes were wandering just now.
Breathing is irregular.
Pressure on the throat.
This is a heterosexual relationship.
The symptoms of the disorder.
It's a kind of self-obsession.
As long as the patient is close to the opposite sex,
I'll be nervous all over.
It will cause syncope.
Yes
Yes, I think he told me
What heterosexual disorder does he have?
You knew he had the symptoms.
And asked him to be a woman.
Work in a clothing company.
Why are you the manager?
At this stage,
Not suitable for modeling.
You should find him
Psychiatrist
Aren't you a psychiatrist?
My idea is that
He can.
While working.
And treat the illness.
But I didn't know about his illness.
Are you kidding me
I'm busy.
I don't have time to fool around with you.
I'll take him.
To see a psychiatrist.
And I'll come back tomorrow.
No way
Dugu is like a man.
In any case
I won't let him
To be the model of this rookie.
Are you all right?
Where are his clothes? Are you all right?
sister
Back off.
to be dead
Don't cry.
Hold back the tears.
There's nothing to cry about.
Hello, President Ji.
good
Who let you in?
Why are you here?
You forgot?
The whole world knows that
Our relationship
How could you not let me in?
Good morning, Mr. Ji.
Good morning.
I just want to ask you one thing.
What are you doing here?
I just want to
The fact that Star can walk in the show,
To have a friendly negotiation with you.
But you didn't give me a chance.
I have to use
My own way.
Are you threatening me?
To force me to give in.
I'm telling you, there's no door.
You want to waste time?
Then you'll have to
It depends on how long you're using energy.
So bad-tempered.
Okay, President Ji.
Thank you
What's wrong, President Ji?
What happened?
You scared me.
If you're a male sister,
Get her out of here.
Hurry up.
Isn't it appropriate?
If the male sister
I've done so much for you.
Get out of here.
What has she done for me?
President Ji.
Stop avoiding it, okay?
If you're here for me,
Has gone to the company.
You're here to help.
Your stories have been touched.
The cleaner.
What story?
A ghost story.
For Zimmer,
I've been patient again and again.
No matter how he treats me,
Why are you so cold?
How could you trample on my dignity?
But I will always
I will always use it.
With my warm face,
To stick his cold ass.
I also know that
Without dignity.
But you know what?
Love has no dignity.
If we all know about it,
It's not easy for you.
Everyone is young.
Is it wrong to love someone?
that's right
When you were young,
I've never loved a few scumbags.
yes
But he's not really bad.
Sometimes,
Will treat me well.
Didn't I say that
I want to come here
What are you complaining about?
I just I know
I'm just too wronged.
I know. We all know.
Thank you.
But I hope
Don't tell him.
About my affection,
No, I won't.
because
I think this love
Just stay in my heart.
I don't want to
To trouble him, okay?
Don't worry, Miss Ruuo.
Don't worry.
Ah
Come on, guys.
Come on
We support you.
Thank you, aunt.
Dugu is like a man.
Are you done?
You're finally willing to talk to me.
Stop acting. No one is here.
I know you want Star on stage.
But he's really not the type.
You can only
You're doing harm to others.
Star is already training.
He just got cold feet yesterday.
I promise, next time,
He will never make a mistake.
No
Do you have any self-esteem?
Like you,
In the broker industry.
Are you always like this?
There's no bottom line.
Do you know what an agent is?
The agent is
The other side of the artist.
How beautiful the artist is.
How humble an agent is.
So what if you have no self-esteem?
If I want self-respect,
My artist.
You can't stand out.
I really admire you.
President Ji.
Do you know why I
Are you so eager for quick success?
Because in this industry,
The competition is fierce.
The chance is gone.
But now,
To give Sida a chance.
Only you.
I really appreciate your persistence.
But I have my principles.
Are you still here?
You love to stay here, right?
Okay, stay here. I'm leaving.
President Ji.
Long time no see
An'an.
Why are you here?
Last time you saved me on the rooftop,
I've been looking for a chance.
Thank you so much.
You're welcome.
I've been thinking about
What you said to me on the rooftop,
I think you're very manly.
Makes me feel safe.
President Ji, I think you misunderstood.
I'm like this to everyone.
Actually, these days,
I was always scared.
I'm afraid of being alone.
I hope that
Someone can protect me.
You're suffering from trauma.
You need to find a psychologist.
I'm busy.
It's okay. You're busy.
When you're not busy,
We can make an appointment.
Are you free tomorrow?
There's no time. The day after tomorrow,
I'm busy every day.
I'll get back to work.
There were wolves and tigers.
To save the situation.
Someone is bothering me.
Help me get rid of her.
President Ji is asking me for help.
After the event,
Give Star an interview.
Deal
What should we do now?
I'll handle it.
She was on the rooftop last time.
The woman who wanted to jump off the building
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
I didn't have time to tell you.
you
Aren't you on the rooftop?
The lady who saved me?
Why are you together?
Because of
And saved lives.
And come together.
I think this is fate.
impossible
Don't you already have a husband?
I'm divorced.
Because I'm planning to marry him.
Right?
Yes
impossible
President Ji, why do you like it?
Such an old woman.
Why are you talking like this?
We are all women.
Why are you attacking the age?
Won't you be old?
Yes?
Am I wrong?
I'm younger than you now.
You're old and I'm younger than you.
You're too old to be shameless.
Old woman. Old lady.
Old lady.
So what if you're old?
The salt I ate
More than you have ever eaten.
About experience, ability and wisdom.
You are not my opponent.
Besides being young,
Without any advantage.
The nutrition is on your legs.
You don't have much brain.
An excellent woman like you
It's like
In the CBD.
Although he's older,
But the location is good and the price is high.
A lot of people can't get it.
And people like you
You're a brainless young girl.
It's like a new building in the suburbs.
The price is low.
Even if I post ads all over the street,
No one wants it.
Do you think it's comparable?
you
He's my man.
You can be jealous or jealous.
This is the charm of old women.
President Ji.
What do you really like about her?
She filled my life with excitement.
stimulate
baby
I'm old.
A little hypoxic after the fight.
Really?
Baby, you worked hard.
Baby, let's go home.
You're so thoughtful.
Okay, baby. Go.
You're working so hard, baby.
Baby, you want to cook?
Give it to me, baby.
Baby, I'll go back.
I have to cook for you.
Baby, you're so thoughtful.
Hurry home.
Let's not talk about it, okay?
Baby, let's go.
You two are both idiots.
What are you laughing at?
I'm laughing at your mouth.
It's like a machine gun.
Obtrusive
No matter what,
You're right.
I'm just a talker.
What about
You pissed her off.
Whatever you say,
just
Thank you.
No need.
You just need to cash it.
What you said is fine.
Of course.
What I said,
Everything counts.
But you should pay attention to
She's unstable.
I'm afraid that I will make
And aggressive behavior.
When you meet her,
Don't irritate her. Stimulate her.
Contact me in time.
I'm telling you,
Don't cheat anymore.
She's a little girl.
Are you responsible for the problem?
I told you,
I have nothing to do with her.
So she got lost here.
I saved her before.
And her ex,
Before.
So it caused her
You see me as a safe haven.
So she had
Dependency and craving
But the craving is pathological.
The blind stress.
It has nothing to do with real feelings.
therefore
I kept my distance from her.
Is actually helping her.
For her sake.
Why are you so nervous?
So much about psychology.
I don't understand.
All men are the same.
If you get it, you won't treasure it.
You are so prejudiced against men.
Before,
What kind of stimulation?
Don't think you've studied for years.
psychology
You know me very well.
Stop it.
Do you think it's handsome?
shoulder
head
Look at me.
I don't believe it.
I can't cure you.
see
Look at me.
Sister, I can't.
sister
Alright.
Relax.
Now you imagine me as
You're the most familiar with it.
The closest person.
And imagine her.
Standing in front of you,
Are you feeling better?
It's better.
You lack of love experience.
If you have
The woman you like,
All your problems are gone.
If you love someone,
What does it feel like?
yes
The feeling of heart beat.
When you see her,
Your heart will beat fast.
And your joy will double.
but
And the pain will double.
in short
If you want to know,
Whether you like someone or not,
Just ask your own heart.
That's it.
Well
Correct!
That
That's all for today.
I'm going on a date.
I'll stay and practice on my own.
Just follow
The way I taught you.
Come on.
Bye
And march forward.
You are so prejudiced against men.
Before,
What kind of stimulation?
Who is it?
Why are you here?
Where's Zimmer?
How do you know where my home is?
You followed me?
Cut the crap.
Where is Zimmer?
He doesn't live here.
How could it be?
I saw
You got into the elevator together.
Zimmer
He doesn't live here, okay?
Stop it.
You...
Is it here?
Give it to me.
What are you doing? Let go of me.
Let go of me.
This is my home.
Don't play tricks on me.
Ask Zimmer to come out.
Come back.
Calm down.
You're sick now.
You should go to the doctor.
Not looking for a man.
You've been
Once.
You can't do that to a man.
To find a sense of security.
Do you know how to love yourself?
Zimmer won't accept me.
But I didn't expect that
He will like it.
You are such a scoundrel.
I'm telling you,
You don't have to deal with my affairs.
Is he over there?
Come back.
Let go of me.
What a fart!
Move. I'll wait.
Hold on.
What's the smell?
Do you smell something?
What about my room?
How to do it?
Don't go.
feed
119?
My house is on fire.
Thank you
Nothing
The surname is Ji.
I'm not finished with you.
What happened
What happened to your family?
How dare you ask?
An An,
You did this to my family.
I burned everything.
It's An'an's house.
You're such a loser.
Hapless
bane of others' existence
It's bad luck to meet you.
Get out of here.
I warned you.
Don't irritate her.
The first person to contact me
You're telling me this now.
Is it useful?
Did you see that?
Have you seen my house?
I was careless.
Are you all right?
I'll take you to the hospital for a check-up.
Find a place to stay.
I'll handle the rest.
I was careless.
sister
Why are you here alone?
Who made you angry?
Sister, why are you...
She came out wearing this.
All I have now
This dress.
Why are you naked?
Because my house was burned down.
Was burned.
Are you all right?
You wouldn't have come.
I just came back from the police station.
I'm bored.
But don't drink.
Zi Hao was drinking.
Well
Have a coke.
Waiter/Waitress
Give him a Coke. Thank you.
OK
Why don't you drink Coke?
Drinking is bad for your health.
Your Coke.
Thank you. Give me another one.
good
I asked Phyl to come here.
Stay with me.
But she went on a date.
It's good for her to go on a date.
I'm here for you.
Please.
It's better for Si Da.
And obedient.
come
Why don't you have a Coke?
Nothing
Why aren't you sick today?
Maybe it's my sister.
So I feel kind.
be familiar with
You won't be sick.
Right?
I told you it was good.
Zimmer said it can be cured.
What psychologist?
Is a quack doctor.
Then carry me now.
Hold on. I'll carry you.
No, you're drunk.
Let me carry you.
may not
why
You should be loyal to each other.
Hold on. I'll carry you.
Alright.
It's your turn to carry me.
Alright
I'll carry you.
I'll carry you to the podium.
all right?
But I'm afraid
I'll be a drag.
Imp
Since the first day I signed you,
I knew it.
You will definitely hold me back.
it doesn't matter
What I want to do,
I can definitely do it.
sister
Before I met you,
No one has ever done that.
Encourage me and support me.
And gave me a chance.
Sometimes I wonder
What do you see in me?
Put me down.
Put me down, can you?
How much is it?
He can drink very well.
Forget it.
It's too wet there.
Come on. Sit here.
OK?
sorry
The number you dialed
Can't be connected for the moment.
I remember.
When I first saw you,
You have stars in your eyes.
Stars
Well
What star?
The first time you told me,
When you like acting,
Your eyes are glowing.
At that time,
I said to myself,
Even if you're a deadwood,
I'll also try my best
To carve a flower.
sister
You're so kind.
Then I'm a rotten tree.
I will follow you.
Yes
That's my home.
This is the place.
This is my home.
My home is here.
We're almost there.
Alright, alright.
Put me down.
I'm fine.
Go home.
I'll send you in.
No need
Male artist
You can't just enter.
A woman's home.
What if it's really troublesome?
Please.
I'm sorry.
Everyone is in trouble.
It's red hot.
Hurry up.
Or your own home?
comfortable
Are you all right
Where are you now?
I was worried about you.
What sound?
I misheard you.
Wake up.
Who told you to sleep on my bed?
How did you get in?
I want to sleep.
Wake up.
This is my home.
I don't have a home.
Why are you throwing up?
Don't vomit here.
Here, I'll help you up and go to the toilet.
to feel relieved
I have great taste.
I won't vomit.