I hate your face.
It seems that people all over the world
It's impossible to leave you.
Do you know why?
Are all the people avoiding you?
That's because
You're too arrogant.
You don't care.
The feelings of others.
In your eyes, only work
Only gains and losses,
So you are doomed to be unloved.
That's why Lin Huan left you.
Go back to the crew.
We can talk tomorrow.
Is that necessary?
Zihao
Songzihao
You ungrateful woman.
I'm kind enough to help you.
Leave me there.
And came out.
The situation I just had
I can only push you out.
What do you want me to do?
If it weren't for you,
I can be so embarrassed.
Sir
Your car key.
The car has been parked for you.
What are you doing?
Get off the car
The car?
What are you doing?
Don't you want to rent my house?
I'll let you borrow the car.
He's been unstable recently.
Zihao, don't do anything stupid.
She was injured in the car accident and suffered a lot of bleeding.
Heart rate is unstable.
25 breaths per minute.
Arterial pressure is 60, 40.
The brain could be severely hit.
Has been in shock.
To the operating room.
Immediately.
good
The patient is temporarily out of danger.
She needs to be sent to the ICU.
Continue to observe.
Due to the head injury,
He's still in a coma.
We need further observation.
When will he wake up?
It's hard to say.
He may wake up at any moment.
But it's possible that
And passed out like this.
Depends on his next step.
Hello, President Ji.
good
Good morning, Mr. Ji.
Hello, President Ji.
Dugu is like a man.
Don't go.
Isn't it great to have a boyfriend?
Really?
You came here to torture the dog?
Dugu is like a man.
Don't go.
Bullying me, not having a boyfriend.
Right?
No, no.
You must give me an explanation.
I suggest you don't wear it in the future.
This style and material
Doesn't fit your body shape.
What? Who are you mocking?
Nothing.
Who are you mocking?
Really?
Allen, inform the design department.
The meeting will be held in ten minutes.
President Ji.
For the new season.
We still need to figure out
It might take some time.
Don't think about it.
I've thought it through for you.
I want to make a plus-size dress.
A plus-size dress.
that's right
It's for a lady with a big body.
Tailor-made high-end clothing.
Why are you wearing a tight dress?
Can only be designed for thin people.
Everyone enjoys beauty.
And comfortable beauty.
People tend to be thin.
And appreciate being thin.
Even the clothes
Are designed
Only thin people look good in it.
This kind of aesthetic is sick.
Is twisted.
Wing Fashion wants to be innovative.
To guide you.
To expand the consumption base.
First of all,
The advanced aesthetic concept.
What's our attitude?
Our attitude is
To satisfy everyone.
The psychology of female consumers
I want to make a plus-size dress.
Not only the big dress,
The models for the next season.
I also want to use fat models.
but
Fatty is not fashionable.
Don't laugh at fat people.
Maybe one day,
Would you cry for the fat man?
All right, meeting dismissed.
Male sister.
What should we do next?
To block the news.
As long as possible.
The media knows about it.
Inform the public relations department.
Ask them to make a schedule.
Before the media knows about it.
And make a response.
good
I'm going to handle it.
The follow-up situation.
Stay here.
Let me know if you need anything.
If you're a male,
Coffee, please.
I'm sorry.
About Zihao's car accident and hospitalization,
Was exposed.
I didn't ask the hospital
To block the news?
How could it get out?
Not only the hospital,
The picture of the bar last night.
Was also posted on Weibo.
Now the Internet is exploding.
So many reporters.
Give us a call.
gosh!
Call the relevant department meeting.
Male sister.
You haven't slept all night.
How about I help you with the meeting?
Take a rest.
It's okay. Get used to it.
Since the worst scenario
He's already here.
Let's face it.
It's so cool.
Is this Mr. Ji?
President Ji.
You know that?
What do you know?
Didn't you read the entertainment headlines today?
Song Zihao was in a car accident.
Really?
You don't know
Should I know?
Of course.
Before his car accident,
I was fighting with you.
I fought with him.
That's right.
Look, there are you on the Internet.
Where are the photos of the fight?
The landlord and Song Zihao
There was a conflict.
You stood up for the landlady.
I fought with him at the bar.
President Ji.
feed
Hello
I'm Dugu Ruuo Man.
I'm looking for you.
I asked Tong Tong for your phone number.
I want to thank you.
Last night
It happened so suddenly.
How dare you mention last night?
I'm now
The whole company.
I'm kind enough to help you.
And got into a lot of trouble.
sorry
I know.
The photos and rumors on the Internet
Brought you trouble.
You have a bad reputation.
Don't drag me down.
I don't want to be with you.
With you.
Why did I get a bad reputation?
Even if I have a bad reputation,
I'm in your way.
Anyway, when I met you,
Nothing good.
I don't want to be with your circle.
In any way.
You think I want it to happen?
This kind of thing?
I just want to say thank you.
Could you please speak better?
Don't thank me.
If it wasn't for the house,
I won't be with you at all.
Together.
I found that knowing you,
It's been eight lifetimes.
you
Hang up.
bastard
The police have issued a notice.
Even if I didn't name him,
There are so many people at the scene.
Song Zihao and President Ji were fighting.
It's embarrassing.
In a bar fight.
And had a traffic accident.
What will the company do to him?
Male sister, female sister.
Male sister.
This is our public relations department.
And the publicity department
A response plan.
Please have a look.
You can't do this.
To cancel it.
Since the police have issued a notice,
How to explain it?
You are trying to cover it up.
Zimmer
You don't want to
Is it related?
I won't.
I'm coming.
Hello, Miss Dugu.
I'm a reporter for the Orange Dispatch.
Please tell Song Zihao
How is the injury now?
It will affect his body.
What follow-up?
Song Zihao is stable.
I just need to rest and rest.
I believe that after a period of time,
He will be in a better state.
To face everyone.
Sorry
I didn't take care of Zihao.
I'm in love with the president of Wing Fashion.
But he's an outsider.
So I don't want
There's too much public opinion.
To affect him.
President Ji.
This is the new design.
Here, give it to me.
The tone is too dark.
Lack of novelty
I want a visual conflict.
This conflict
More intense.
The more impact it has, the better it is.
Do you know
Why are you pointing at me?
President Ji.
I know you.
It must be strong.
It has to be powerful.
President Ji.
I didn't expect you
The taste is strong.
What is it?
Isn't this a design?
I know you.
This woman is not bad.
Men don't love you.
You don't have to think about the world.
What are we doing?
We are artistic.
People who engage in art,
What's wrong with the taste?
is or isn't
Get rid of the characters.
I'm an artist.
You and I don't know much about art.
Don't worry about that.
What are you doing anyway?
I support you.
No
You don't have a fever. You took the wrong medicine.
President Ji.
Stop hiding it from me.
You and the landlady
Sister-in-law
About you and your sister-in-law,
The whole company knows about it.
Your love story.
Has been on the news.
What did you say
Your love story.
It's on the news.
How can you pretend?
Wait a second.
Let me show you something.
I don't believe it.
I'm in love with the president of Wing Fashion.
But he's an outsider.
So I don't want
There's too much public opinion.
To affect him.
No,
I really didn't.
President Ji.
Why are you pretending?
Look, sister-in-law,
How brave you are.
In front of the media,
To announce your relationship.
You disappointed me.
Brother Lun.
What should I do now, Brother Lun?
What? What to do?
Accept her.
What a nice girl.
By the way, there's one more thing.
It's all spreading on the Internet.
Songzihao
Because after you two beat me up,
A car accident because of losing control.
I caused the car accident.
play
Go on.
to step aside
Sorry
play
Go on.
I'm not finished with you.
Who is it?
I
Why are you silent?
Guilty, right?
I'm telling you,
I'll count to three.
If you don't open the door,
Don't come to me for help.
Wait a second.
Let me change my clothes.
Stop making excuses for me.
I'll count to three.
One or two
three
What's going on?
You really need to change your clothes.
You can change first.
If there's anything, tell me.
To protect their artists,
You sold me, didn't you?
Are you saying that
I told you about the scandal.
I'm also a victim.
I'm a good woman.
It's not impossible.
fart
Has seriously affected
My work and life.
Do you know
It's going to be so messy.
I didn't expect that.
Now?
Not a word or two.
Can be solved.
Anyway, it's already taken.
Why don't you go to the capital city
Last time,
you
I'm telling you,
Don't be too utilitarian.
Be careful.
Do you think I want to
To hang your boyfriend title.
Is the disgrace of my life.
I don't want to talk nonsense to you.
Get changed and explain to me.
No.
If you want to go, go yourself.
This kind of thing,
I can't make it.
Where are you going?
You rascal.
metamorphosis
Sex wolf
You run fast.
Open the door and solve it first.
If you don't solve it today,
I'm not leaving.
Then you stay here.
Just stay here.
My legs are soft.
Why are you here so early?
I told you I'm not leaving.
and
I can't let you
And sneak away.
Am I such a low-end person?
This is my home.
I went to work openly.
Before you go to work,
To clarify with me.
I told you.
I'm not going.
Save it.
No soft ones, hard ones.
is or isn't
Why?
No, no.
No way
Why did I call you?
what are you doing?
Put me down.
Let me go.
Are you all right?
Is it not hard enough?
My chest hurts.
I can't breathe.
to do sth more quickly
The hospital?
No
Call an ambulance.
Remember to call an ambulance.
Go through the back door.
There's a reporter at the front door.
such
I'll take you to my home.
Let's wait for the ambulance, okay?
can
Alright.
Who passed out.
And worried about reporters.
I was almost fooled by her again.
To play tricks with me.
I want to see
How long can you last?
That's right.
When the ambulance comes,
I'll find a way to escape.
Everything goes according to
My plan will proceed.
I'm a genius.
The doctor is here.
What's wrong? Who is sick?
She's not sick.
You're not sick.
Why did you call me here?
She has been giving me trouble.
Besides,
And loves acting.
Since she wants to act,
Let's play with her.
You are so happy now.
Come on, let's have a look.
Who is sick?
It's so serious.
doctor
This patient
Is very ill.
It's very difficult to cure.
I tried many ways.
She can't wake up.
This time,
To increase the dose.
How many shots?
Don't worry.
This is the ultimate enhancement.
Make sure she wakes up.
He won't really
Call a doctor.
A few more shots.
it doesn't matter
If she doesn't wake up,
This bottle is all hers.
Zimmer
This dose should be enough.
That's enough. Fill it up.
And fill it up.
That's right.
Where am I
My head.
Where am I?
Why am I here?
What happened?
My head hurts.
I seem to have fainted.
OMG
I'm fine now.
Then I'm leaving.
What disease can recover so quickly?
Could it be that
What's wrong with you?
Well
I think her spirit
There might be a problem.
That's right.
I am.
Hypoglycemia
I often lose weight with low blood sugar.
As a woman,
I was hungry and then I fainted.
On TV,
That's how it's done.
It's easy.
All my patients say they are not sick.
to feel relieved
But I'll give you a shot.
You will feel better.
No, no.
Give me a shot. No, no.
Really?
Don't.
Don't shoot. I'm really not sick.
You'll feel better after a shot.
Listen to me.
Give me a shot.
No, don't touch me.
Don't hit me.
Did you pass out?
The performance is too exaggerated.
This girl
Probably learned acting.
Stanislavsky
Brechts
I'm familiar with it.
Is a good prospect.
Wake
Go on.
All right, young master.
If you don't wake up,
I've given you an injection.
Miss
I'll give you an injection.
You will wake up after a shot.
It's real.
If you don't wake up,
The needle will hit you.
Something is wrong.
She really passed out.
How could it be?
This is saline.
And he didn't even fight.
Come and have a look.
You're really dizzy.
To the hospital.
Hurry up.
Doctor, what's her condition?
Why did you pass out suddenly?
Don't worry.
Nothing serious.
Maybe.
Lack of rest for a long time.
Then I was too stressed.
Which caused her heart rhythm to be irregular.
Decreased immunity.
When I was frightened,
She passed out temporarily.
And rest here for two days.
You'll be fine.
What about
What did the doctor say?
For a few days.
You'll be fine after a rest.
Thank you.
And made a special trip.
Why are you being so courteous to me?
Back then,
If you don't help,
I can't even hold my diploma.
But then again,
You're the only one
Such a famous student.
You can change your career.
Our professor still sends emails.
Ask me about you.
You suddenly changed your job.
Is it because of Su Xiao?
Let's not mention the past.
I'm fine now.
You're doing well.
Is it because of this room?
This woman
What does it have to do with her?
I think it's very important.
For so many years,
I haven't seen you.
Who are you so obsessed with?
You called me all the way here.
Acting with you.
I think she can
To affect your mood.
Is really capable.
Affect my mood.
And angry.
Angry emotions.
It's good.
Really
After you and Su Xiao,
I think you're numb.
No one
There's nothing else.
Can affect your mood.
We both studied psychology.
You know very well that
If a person
Without emotion,
What a terrible thing.
Right?
If she can piss you off,
I really have to thank her.
Don't compare her to Su Xiao.
Alright.
You don't want to hear it. I won't say it.
Okay?
I have something to do in the hospital.
I'm leaving now.
See you later!
Mr. Zhang really said that.
That's right.
He said he would cancel the contract with us.
He said that
I won't contact Ruo anymore.
Let's change.
It seems that this time,
You really made her anxious.
This is the place
Something happened at the junction of bones and eyes.
If the man can't get through,
In that case, we have to replace him.
To contact the advertisers.
I'll leave it to you.
Boss
I have no problem working.
But this matter
If she knows about it,
I'll be scolded by her.
How dare she scold you?
She's the boss, I'm the boss
I didn't mean that.
Okay, that's it.
Her job
You'll be in charge for now.
His own artist.
Such a serious thing happened.
And absent without reason.
I really love her for nothing.
What is she doing?
You're awake.
Why am I in the hospital?
I remember.
Is your crazy doctor.
To give me an injection.
I was too nervous to pass out.
He's my senior brother.
And a psychiatrist.
What happened today?
Fortunately, we're here.
Otherwise, he might die at home.
You just died at home.
I'm not kidding you.
A professional woman like you,
Life is stressful.
Working under pressure.
In the body.
The hidden danger of many diseases.
Don't make money by then.
I'm telling you.
I'm fine now.
That's great.
You can go now. Thank you.
That's impossible.
I have to wait for your discharge.
To clear my name?
Don't worry.
You're a patient.
A gentleman like me,
I won't force you.
I'll take care of you.
You haven't...
Completely devoid of humanity.
Yours is there.
Eat more fruit.
Supplement your vitamins.
when the moment comes
You wouldn't be in front of reporters.
She fainted.
For a long time.
You have ulterior motives.
To deal with
And unscrupulous woman.
You must use the way of others.
And treat him.
What are you doing?
Can't you leave the hospital?
You've come to the hospital.
I have to meet someone.
I know you care about him.
That's why I brought you here.
To the hospital where he is.
I can't tell.
You're a bad person.
But I still care about
Your artist
I took him for three years.
I watched him go from nobody
Step by step,
And climb to where we are today.
Watch him little by little.
It's shining.
Actually, our agent
Is the artist's designer.
Dreammaker
In my eyes,
Song Zihao is my work.
Like my own child.
Actually, I'm contradictory now.
I regret it.
When he's sober,
Be nice to him.
I was thinking
If I were tougher on him,
Wouldn't he have developed
Today,
You are arrogant and self-willed.
If I had no choice,
As his manager.
He may still be the one
Nobody
At least it can be healthy.
You don't have to lie here.
I'm going to rest.
Go back first.
I'm exhausted.
President Ji, you're finally here.
There's an entertainment reporter inside.
I've been waiting for you for a long time.
You can't drive them away.
What have you been doing these days?
Why didn't you come to work?
Taking care of patients in the hospital.
Who's sick?
Hello, President Ji.
We're entertainment reporters.
You want to take Song Zi's car accident
To interview you.
OK?
All the details about this matter.
According to the police report,
I hope the client can recover as soon as possible.
I hope that
Don't give her too much pressure.
President Ji.
That was so cool.
perfect
No, President Ji, I think
You're not interested in this relationship.
It's not the same.
I haven't seen you before.
Other girls are like this.
Even in this world,
There's no woman left.
And I won't fall in love with Dugu Ruuo.
Go to work
What do advertisers say?
I made an appointment yesterday.
You didn't come all of a sudden.
They're very angry.
He said he wanted to cancel the contract.
When we signed the contract,
All kinds of requests.
Now something has happened,
You're looking for barbs.
So snobbish.
But that's right.
People are like this.
Everyone is the icing on the cake.
Who would give timely help?
At this moment,
No one will jump out.
To speak for me.
The artist, Song Zihao.
Speeding incidents
Has aroused wide public concern.
Hello, President Ji.
If you want, Song Zihao.
The car accident
Can I do an interview with you?
to wait a moment
All the details about this matter.
According to the police report,
I hope the client can recover as soon as possible.
I hope that
Don't give her too much pressure.
Male sister.
You two have made a deal.
Why didn't you tell me?
You scared me.
I didn't agree with him.
I didn't tell you.
Why is he so cooperative?
Why is he?
Why else?
But it's because
My personal charm
Yes, he must be infatuated with you.
although
His love for me
Is doomed to be unrewarded.
But he helped me, right?
He's busy
I still want to thank him.
When it's important,
Is quite manly.
Strangled me.
I can't breathe.
It's all your fault.
Before getting on the plane,
What do you want me to eat?
Don't you know that starch and meat
Will it produce fat?
You just had a little bite.
And then threw up on the plane.
I'm a model.
I can't have it on me.
A bit of fatty meat.
I can only wear the smallest size.
Are you imitating me?
No.
Do you think I'll be fat
Will the audience still like me?
Do you think the photographers
Will you still film me?
I was wrong.
I won't be there again.
How about eating in front of you?
I'm already hungry.
You don't even have the strength.
I have to
You're smiling.
I really...
Alright.
I know you're tired.
Master, take Phil home.
No, I'm not going home.
I'm going to a place.
Because I want to meet
Special people.
So hungry.
I heard that
In front of the reporters,
Put on a good show.
You're good at acting.
Thanks.
Seems a little too cold.
today
I'm here to thank you.
Thank you.
In front of reporters,
To expose me.
Thank you
Thank you.
It's too unimposing.
No, no.
Less cold.
More of my own.
style
You know,
In our industry,
Recurrent
Dealing with reporters.
But thank you for today.
Thank you for helping me.
A good prospect.
I turned around for you.
Doing acting exercises.
I'm here to see you.
If it's because
About the reporter today,
You're welcome.
Who said I wanted to thank you?
Then why are you here?
Peeping at me.
I'm here to ask you.
Why today?
Suddenly changed his mind.
Is it because of me?
Don't be narcissistic.
I'm just too lazy to talk to those reporters.
Just talking.
Next time you come to my house,
Remember to change your shoes.
Don't dirty my floor.
What are you talking about?
And this is my home.
To rent to you temporarily.
Turn around for you.
I will turn around.
Is there any surprise?
Who are you?
I should ask you that.
I'm Ruo's boyfriend's friend.
I'm here to see Ruonan.
Is she there?
Wait
Are you her?
Your boyfriend?
Don't get me wrong.
She rented this house to me.
I'm looking at you.
Why are you so familiar?
From where?
You look familiar. It's normal.
After all, many people know me.
But we
You must have never seen it before.
If you're a man,
I rented the house to you.
Where is she?
It's 4 & 1 upstairs.
understand
Thanks, handsome.
You have to be an actor again.
Pleasantly surprised
How could it be you?
Come in.
I wanted to give you a surprise.
I didn't expect that
Who knew you moved?
The handsome guy downstairs
He said you live upstairs.
But I'm curious.
Why did you move?
It's a long story. Change your shoes.
Come in, I'm telling you.
Did you miss me?
It's great to have you back.
Then I will have a partner.
Tell me the truth.
Have you got a boyfriend?
Love is the most important thing
Is not a necessity.
Is likely to become
consumables
Why should I bother?
You have to
Learn from me, you know?
To have more relationships.
Haven't you heard of it?
Love is the best for women.
Skincare products.
I've gone through
When I was young.
When you're with someone,
It's hard to find the strengths of each other.
Instead, you should think about
Each other's shortcomings.
I'm thinking that when it's over,
How could I?
Without being hurt.
Stop talking about me. Let's talk about you.
How many new boyfriends?
Let me have a drink first.
I'll talk to you later.
Go ahead.
Alright.
Slow down.
Go straight ahead.
What? It's so mysterious.
We're almost there.
Okay, one more step forward.
one
to be ready
I let go.
What about
Where is this?
This is our home.
Didn't you say that
Get married if you have a house?
You have a house now.
Marry me
Stop it.
I just came back.
After two years,
But I can't wait.
What do you mean?
Don't you see that?
I'm proposing to you.
I'm a girl.
I don't need to be reserved.
You're a boy.
What principles do you insist on?
Zimmer, marry me.
Marry me. Let's get married.
Xiao, why don't you understand?
What do I mean?
Don't listen to me.
Zimmer
We're here.
Let's put one here.
It's a big sofa.
Then what?
If we have a fight,
I will punish you for sleeping on the couch.
Then this way.
here
Let's put a desk.
And put an easel.
Then you read the psychology book.
What time is it?
I can draw the design.
This way.
Look. Look this way.
Suxiao
Xiao
Where are you, Xiao?
Suxiao
Su Xiao, where are you?
sorry