Why is your business card here?
Why is Xiao Longzhou's card here?
What?
Come back here!
Stop right there!
Go away!
You can really run, huh?
Who exactly are you?
Where is Jin Xuehua?
Speak!
Jin Xuehua is in danger.
She doesn't have much time left.
What exactly is going on?
Talk!
I took a job.
Someone wanted to kidnap Jin Xuehua.
I didn't dare do it myself.
So I found Lao Wei.
Lao Wei.
You got the wrong guy.
I know you can settle things for people.
Who told you that?
Don't ask so many questions.
Big job.
You taking it or not?
That chapter is closed.
I don't do that stuff anymore.
You've been on the streets.
You can't wash your hands clean.
Besides...
After you finish this gig,
you'll have the money for your daughter's hospital bills.
400,000.
70-30 split.
You get seven, I get three.
Take it.
I can't do murder or arson.
Oh, come on.
Brother, help me out here, will you?
It's a society ruled by law.
Who goes around killing and burning these days?
Just snatching a person.
Don't worry.
I just need you to take her to a specific place.
That's all.
Just that is worth 400,000?
It's not 400,000.
Thirty percent of that is mine.
And hey...
If you're gonna do this job,
then don't ask too many questions.
I waited at the agreed spot for Lao Wei to deliver her.
But nobody showed up.
And he wouldn't answer the phone.
I put a tracker on Lao Wei's car.
And found their location.
It's made of plastic.
Where is the real one?
Xiao Longzhou.
Surprise, Xuehua.
Lao Wei! Lao Wei!
Is this how you do business?
You kidnapped the person,
you brought her back,
but you won't hand her over to me?
Is there such a rule on the streets?
You...
I'm the one who kidnapped you, Jin Xuehua.
Are you some kind of good person?
Do you have a conscience?
You deceived Lao Wei.
You said performing a ritual could wake his daughter.
What is this?
This is feudal superstition.
Lao Wei couldn't bring you to me, could he?
So I'm doing it myself.
Come here.
Come with me.
Jin Xuehua!
Take Yuanyuan and go, quick!
Xuehua!
Yuanyuan!
Jin Xuehua!
Jin Xuehua
After Lao Wei knocked me down
I couldn't find Jin Xuehua anywhere
The client was pushing hard
And I didn't have a clue myself
I figured if Jin Xuehua ran, she must have gone home
You know the rest
Know my ass
Who is the client?
Why kidnap Jin Xuehua?
I don't know
A guy named Brother Feng found me
What are the details?
What exactly is going on?
I haven't got a clue
Jin Xuehua ran away
Why didn't she contact me right away?
I find that strange too
This whole thing
I tailed you thinking Jin Xuehua would contact you
I thought following you was the fastest way to find her
But
Jin Xuehua isn't in danger, is she?
Is anyone there?
Anyone home?
Can I help you?
What's wrong?
Can we borrow your phone?
My phone is dead
My house isn't far
You can call from my place
You look...
What happened to you?
She's fine, she's fine
Come, come, come
After you, after you
What's the matter?
Have some water
Thanks
No problem