WELCOME
TUTOR KIM HYE-NA
It's okay. I'll get the door.
Please tidy up.
Hye-na.
Come on, Ye-bin. She's your tutor now.
Hello, Tutor Hye-na.
Thank you for hiring me.
I should thank you.
Please take good care of Ye-bin.
By the way,
can I really get into the intensive class?
Of course.
You're super smart, you know.
This is so great.
See? I told you that you just have
to trust her and do as she says.
Come on in.
I'll carry this for you.
It's okay, Ye-bin. I got this. It's heavy.
Ye-bin.
-Yes?
-I have to talk to Hye-na about something.
What?
All right.
Your goal is to get Ye-seo
into SNU's med school.
So?
Hye-na knows
that she is Dr. Kang's daughter.
If Ye-seo or her mom finds out,
she'll fail to get into med school,
-and it'll ruin her family--
-There's no need to worry about that.
Ye-seo will get accepted.
I'll make sure of it.
But Ms. Kim,
Hye-na is a daring
and unpredictable child.
If you let someone like her
live with Ye-seo,
it'll be like installing a ticking bomb
beneath Ye-seo's desk.
We'll have to see if she'll turn out
to be a ticking bomb or a firecracker.
Ye-bin comes home
from her academy at 10 p.m.
You can teach her for two hours then.
School break starts soon,
so you can teach her
according to her new academy schedule.
I made a lesson plan for Ye-bin.
In order to get her
into the intensive class in three months,
it'll be better to cover a chapter a day
instead of teaching her
for a set amount of time each day.
You pick her up from school
and from the academy, right?
Would it be okay if I went with you?
You want to come with me?
I don't mind riding the bus.
But commuting to and from school
takes me about an hour in total.
So I thought I could teach her
some mathematical formulae
and briefly cover the concepts
during that time.
Sure, that's a good idea.
Anyway, I'm counting on you
to get Ye-bin into the intensive class.
Yes, I'll try my best.
Then shall I show you your room?
Ye-seo's a little sensitive these days.
You know why, right?
Don't worry.
I'll make sure I don't bother her.
Okay, thanks.
I'm not sure
if your room will be to your liking.
I used to live in a place
that didn't get any sunlight.
Really?
This may be the basement,
but you'll get plenty of sunlight.
My gosh, I love it.
Is this my room?
I'm glad you like it.
Let's eat dinner
once my husband and Ye-seo come home.
Could you tell her about the other things?
Yes, ma'am.
Thank you.
I'll see you later then.
Listen carefully, kid.
You can use the bathroom
that's across from this room.
You can only leave the house
on the weekends.
The same applies during school break.
And you can never go upstairs
apart from when you go up to teach Ye-bin.
So you're telling me not to be seen
by anyone in this family.
I'm telling you to be careful.
You should be grateful.
Today's your first day here,
so you'll be eating with the family.
But you'll have to eat with me
starting from tomorrow. Okay?
Please
send my meals to my room.
I'll eat by myself.
-What?
-I'll clean my own room
and do my own laundry.
So don't come into my room from now on.
You're unbelievable.
Mom.
I've finally made it into this house.
This is only the beginning.
If you hadn't revealed your past,
we wouldn't have had to take in
some stranger.
Things have turned out this way now.
There's no point in talking about--
Do you think I don't know that?
I'm only saying this
because Ye-seo's grades went down.
She'll end up helping out our kids,
just like Coach Kim said.
So don't be too cold toward her.
Cut the nonsense.
Do you think I'll make it obvious
that I don't want her here?
My goodness, how gorgeous.
Gosh, my little baby.
-Mom!
-My goodness, gracious!
Gosh.
You punk.
Didn't I tell you to not talk to me
when I'm taking care of my babies?
How many times do I have to tell you?
If I don't get accepted to into the
more advanced class, it's all your fault.
What?
My goodness.
That little punk. What did you
just say? Come over here.
What did you say?
What?
If I fail my assessment test again,
it's all your fault.
Are you being serious?
Why is that my fault?
Hye-na moved into Ye-bin's place. Darn it.
I told her first
that I wanted her to tutor me.
She moved into her house?
As a live-in tutor?
If Ye-bin moves up into a better class
and I fail, it'll be so humiliating.
That's why I told you
to get private tutoring lessons.
You even said no to a student from SNU.
But you want a high school kid?
I told you already
that Hye-na's a great teacher!
Why don't you believe me?
Why do you do things your way
when I'm the student?
You're going to scold me if I fail again.
-My goodness.
-It's so unfair.
Where are you going?
You should be studying! My gosh.
Why are you being so harsh
on my precious son?
I'm not being harsh on him.
He's just laying the groundwork
because he thinks
he's going to fail the test again.
Gosh, that punk. He's so smart.
But it is strange.
Why would she hire
a high school student as a live-in tutor?
WELCOME
TUTOR KIM HYE-NA
You even baked a cake for Hye-na?
You agreed to her moving in.
Do you think I liked the idea?
I only agreed because of Coach Kim.
Whatever the case, just be on good terms
with her while she's here.
She's right. You could actually
become really good friends
if you befriend your rival.
You should get along with her.
Hye-na's here, Mom.
Okay. Come here, Hye-na.
You must be Hye-na.
Hello.
Hi. Take a seat.
Let's all sit down.
Nice.
Welcome.
I'll trust you with Ye-bin.
Okay, I'll do my best.
She's a great teacher, Dad.
She explains things much better
and is more fun than academy teachers.
My gosh, really?
Seeing Ye-bin this excited
makes me look forward to the results.
You think you can get Ye-bin
into the intensive class?
Isn't that too ambitious?
What if I get in?
Stop it.
Don't worry, Ye-seo.
Ye-bin will get into that class.
My gosh, you're way too confident
about yourself.
How are you going to do
what the top teachers
in Daechi-dong failed to do?
Ye-bin's smart,
so she'll catch up
once she learns all the concepts.
I tested Ye-bin yesterday at the academy
in order to come up with a study plan.
Oh, really?
Once I taught her the principles,
she managed to solve the hard questions
quite easily.
I think Ye-bin lost interest in studying
because she wasn't fully aware
of the basic concepts but had to catch up
with studying ahead of her grade.
Do you think the academy wouldn't
have taught her the basic concepts?
Don't you know how good that academy is?
Even you go there.
Regardless of how good an academy may be,
they have a limit to teaching students
based on their individual levels.
They can teach know-how
about how to solve questions
in order to improve our grades
in a short period of time.
But they can't get students
interested in mathematics.
Ultimately,
an academy's purpose is to earn a profit.
Hye-na, you're very smart.
Gosh.
-Wow.
-Ye-seo.
How's your new Korean teacher?
Just so-so.
A bit better, I guess.
He'd better be better.
You got full marks on everything
but got three wrong in Korean.
That means the teaching method
was the problem.
Exactly.
She'd have gotten full marks
if the new teacher had come sooner.
She can get full marks next time.
My daughter can do anything.
Right, Ye-seo?
You bet.
I'll go to SNU med school's
alumni meeting with you when I'm older.
Yes, of course.
Let's walk in together arm-in-arm.
Eat up.
What an idea.
That's great.
I was so worried about her.
I know I suggested
that we let Hye-na move in with us,
but I was a bit worried.
You too?
We thought
you'd insist that we let Hye-na stay.
Come on, Dad.
I'm a grown man.
A grown man living with a female friend
is a very touchy issue.
You're so good at reading your mom's mind.
I'm pretty good at reading your mind too.
Hurry up and do the dishes, honey.
Your mom's slaps really hurt.
-Hello?
-Ms. Lee?
This is Cha Min-hyeok.
Hello, Professor Cha.
I called to check because you seemed
to have forgotten your promise
to give us an answer within three days.
It's been over ten days already.
I'm sorry, but...
I never said I'd give you an answer
within three days.
What a pity.
Do you still not understand
how serious this issue is?
Professor Cha, it's Hwang Chi-yeong.
I wasn't able to attend the meeting,
but I heard what happened.
Then you must understand
that I called because the residents
kept calling me about it.
I'd like you to make up your mind,
and soon.
I thought you'd approach the issue
more rationally than anyone.
I find it very regrettable that you defend
only one party.
You may consider this
the tyranny of the majority,
but when the interests
are so deeply opposed,
isn't it the rule of democracy
to follow what the majority wants?
Of course, it is.
But if the majority vote is abused
in the name of democracy,
isn't it the case
that the few become victims?
I can't just watch my wife
become a victim.
I believe you can understand that.
Goodbye, then.
He's just like his wife.
Is she insisting
on writing the book or what?
You were really cool, Dad.
Seo-jin's the ringleader.
Why take the lead
when she's not doing anything?
Didn't you hear the residents' calls?
I got three just today.
That's why she put you in charge.
You're never satisfied
until you handle things on your own,
and she is using that to her advantage.
What do you take me for?
Do you think I'll let myself be used?
Gosh, I'm jealous.
If that friend of yours could help,
nothing in the world would be impossible.
If your hospital director is promoted,
that would be good
for your career as well.
It'd be killing two birds with one stone.
Yes, it would.
If only that were possible.
I can have my cake and eat it too,
or clean a stream and catch the fish.
You can sweep a yard and find a penny,
or find your love and get lucky.
I'm using Kang Jun-sang.
He looked down on me
because his family is powerful,
but this time he came to me
groveling for a favor.
He's just a butcher with a scalpel
and yet he pretends
to be a scholar who knows literature.
But deep inside him,
he has great ambitions.
Dr. Kang?
I thought
he was far from being ambitious.
You're a terrible judge of character.
If he doesn't have ambition,
why would he be trying
to get Director Choi
what he wants
when he should be gnashing his teeth?
What are you saying?
What does the director want?
Wait and see.
Jun-sang will become the planning manager,
the second most powerful man
of Junam University Hospital.
That's it?
Is that why you told me
to appease his wife,
whether she's Han Seo-jin
or Kwak Mi-hyang?
Of course.
Why else would I help Kang Jun-sang?
I'm doing this to better our future.
Our future.
THE FAMILY WHO LIVED IN YOUR HOUSE BEFORE.
DO YOU KNOW WHY THEY MOVED?
No. Why did they move?
The mom...
killed herself.
So everyone left.
Her husband and Yeong-jae.
Now that I gave her
SNU's med school acceptance letter,
I've fulfilled my duties as a son.
I, Park Yeong-jae,
am not your son anymore.
"I got in for you, now leave me alone"?
Should I let that punk be?
He wants to take revenge on us.
Must we leave this jerk alone?
If he disappears on us,
we'll never find him again.
I can't give up on Yeong-jae.
I can't give up on my son!
COACH KIM JU-YEONG
I'm sorry. You must be busy.
It's fine.
I was wondering
how you were doing with your book.
That's actually
what I wanted to see you about.
I had no intention
of writing a story literally
based on Yeong-jae's family.
But I think I should still ask
his father for permission.
I was wondering
if you had Mr. Park's number.
I can help you locate him,
but even if you do get to meet him,
do you think he will
give you his permission?
Locate Yeong-jae's father.
What for?
Yes, ma'am.
Lee Su-im meeting Park Su-chang?
Why didn't I think of that?
If they just meet...
Of course.
If you become the planning manager,
wouldn't our department
become the most powerful one
in Junam University Hospital?
-Right?
-Yes, of course.
You bet.
Powerful? As if.
Not when there's
the Spine and Joint Center.
Their profits are terrible these days.
Everything that Hwang Chi-yeong
gets into doesn't make money.
It's terrible.
This could be...
the perfect opportunity to ride on
the thousand-year-old tortoise's back.
Don't you think?
By the way,
did you know that, Dr. Woo?
What?
You know the party representative
Kim Hyeok-jae.
Both he and Professor Cha
graduated from Namseok High.
Then...
That's how they know each other?
Apparently,
they grew up like brothers
in the same neighborhood.
Then...
how about I ask Mr. Im
to arrange something
so that you, Professor Cha,
and the Tortoise can
play golf together?
KIM HYEOK-JAE
What's going on?
Dr. Kang has a connection
with the representative of the party.
Oh, boy.
It's been a while
since I last saw Dr. Kang.
Shall I meet him for some tea?
Yes. I'll give him a call, sir.
MR. IM
I told you to take about ten days off
and get some rest.
Why are you already back at work?
Since you did such a perfect job
with the surgery,
I can handle this much work.
Right,
this place felt so empty
without you, Dr. Woo.
Pardon? Oh, I see.
Just a moment, please.
Dr. Kang.
Yes, Kang Jun-sang speaking.
Director Choi would like to see me?
Now?
Well, I'm with a guest at the moment.
Yes, let him know I'll stop by
in about 30 to 40 minutes.
Okay.
That's not enough.
You should keep the Tortoise on his toes
by making him wait longer, Dr. Kang.
As if.
I could've gone by myself.
You didn't have to come with me.
You two have never met before.
It'll be easier to get his permission
if I come along.
Thank you so much.
How can I repay you?
You can repay me by writing a great book.
I told you not to,
but you keep doing it all day long.
You'll hurt your shoulders
if you keep this up, Dr. Park.
Are you the person who called?
Yes, sir.
Mr. Park.
It's me, Kim Ju-yeong.
I've been thinking about...
what you said to me.
I, too, hope no one else experiences
what Yeong-jae went through.
That's why I brought someone
who's been wanting to meet you,
even knowing that it could come across
as discourteous.
Get lost at once.
I'll make sure my book
doesn't harm you or Yeong-jae in any way.
You.
Don't you get it?
I told you to make sure
that such a tragedy doesn't happen again.
Because you ruined my son's life...
and killed my wife.
Yes,
I ruined his life and killed her.
Blame me all you want.
Will you blame others
and stay resentful forever?
You said you wanted to be
a decent father to Yeong-jae now.
Will chopping wood all day long...
help you be a decent father to him?
Oh, boy.
He chops wood nonstop all day long
because waiting for his son
makes him anxious.
Sir.
He's waiting for his son?
What do you mean by that?
MY SON
You know the mountain cabin
we used to go together often
when you were little, right?
I'll wait for you there.
I heard you're waiting
for Yeong-jae.
Telling me what you've been
bottling up inside
might help you
feel a little less anxious.
I met a student...
during my teacher training 20 years ago.
She also had a problem
with her parents due to her grades.
Back then,
I just stood by and watched like a coward.
But I don't want to repeat
the same mistake, so I came to see you.
Do you know...
what thought crossed my mind first
when I heard about my friend's son
who took his own life a while back?
"What did his parents do
for him to take his own life?"
I blamed the parents first.
If people find out about
what happened to my wife,
they will
blame us, her family, first.
Yeong-jae must be...
beating himself up over his mom's death,
and...
I'm sure the guilt is suffocating him.
I can't let people point their fingers
at him on top of that.
I must...
protect my son.
I didn't think that far.
But Dr. Park...
we should make sure
this tragedy doesn't repeat--
Do you think...
people will change
after learning about my family's tragedy?
Do you think they'll sympathize deeply
with my son's pain
and change as a result?
Dr. Park.
Every year, young students die
because of their grades
or the stress of getting into college,
but the world isn't changing at all.
Until when do we need to watch those kids
suffer from such wrongful and sad deaths?
So are you saying you believe
that you can change the world
by writing a book?
It won't change right away,
but someone must step up.
-If we keep trying--
-Get rid of that false hope.
I was like everyone else.
Even when I heard that
my friend's son committed suicide,
I only blamed his parents.
And I said that the kid was
too weakhearted to be a man.
This is something
no one will ever understand
unless they experience it themselves.
I understand your sincerity,
but it'll all be useless.
It'll only end up ruining...
Yeong-jae's and my life.
-Hello.
-Welcome.
Have you been well?
Yes, it's been a while
since you last came.
She's going to quit writing
about Yeong-jae?
How did you manage
to convince that stubborn woman?
You shouldn't worry about that anymore.
How's Hye-na?
Ye-bin is
starting to enjoy studying.
More importantly, she hasn't caused
any problems with Ye-seo.
She's a smart kid,
so she's behaving a lot better
than I expected. But...
Never mind. It's nothing.
Winter break is coming up.
How is Ye-seo's schedule going to change?
You know she needs to study harder
during the break, right?
You just need to create
a comfortable environment
and make sure Ye-seo doesn't get stressed.
Yes, of course. I know that's my job.
She keeps making mistakes in Korean.
Shouldn't you come up with a solution?
She could actually use this chance
to her advantage.
She'll be able to come up with a story
about how she managed to increase
her grades even during a crisis.
That can only happen
if she actually manages to overcome it.
I'd like to hear how you're going
to help her overcome it.
I'll help her overcome her weakness
by making her divide each sentence
and practice analyzing
the meaning behind it.
Her new Korean teacher
used to make questions
for the CSATs. You know that, right?
There's no point
in shutting the stable door
after the horse has bolted.
You need to prepare her
for the worst-case scenario
so that she doesn't make
the same mistake again.
She might have to take a different
approach without a good school record.
As I've always told you,
there's not a single error in my plan
to get Ye-seo accepted
to SNU's med school.
Of course,
that will be based on the fact
that she doesn't get stressed at home.
Yes, of course. That's a given.
Of course,
that will be based on the fact
that she doesn't get stressed at home.
It seems like she knows something.
Did Ye-seo tell her?
No, Ye-seo's too proud to tell anyone.
MR. JO
Yes, Mr. Jo.
Ye-seo won't eat dinner?
I said, no.
I don't want to eat.
I have indigestion anyway.
You didn't eat lunch,
and you want to skip dinner too?
Have some.
You need to eat in order to study.
You can't study on an empty stomach.
Hurry up and eat.
I need to feel at ease in order to study.
What's wrong?
Did something happen?
Don't you get it?
I hate Hye-na,
but I have to see her face all day.
And my own mom lied...
How do you expect me to eat?
Okay, fine.
By the way,
did you tell anyone about me?
Why would I
when it's nothing to be proud of?
Gi-jun and Seo-jun knew already
even though I never told them.
So?
Are you always going to get angry,
refuse to eat,
and act out every time
something like this happens?
-It'll only be your loss.
-Do you think I don't know that?
I don't want to think about it,
but I can't help it.
I should be studying
every second of the day.
I'm so angry that it's driving me nuts.
I'm asking you like this.
Please try to concentrate.
If you fail to get into
to SNU's med school--
Why wouldn't I get in?
I have Coach Kim.
If I exchange this with this,
this will become 288
minus 72 pi.
The answer is...
ANSWER: NUMBER 5
Number five.
You got it right. Good job, Ye-bin.
How was it? Do you understand it now?
Yes, I understand it completely
now that I tried explaining it.
That means you didn't
get this question wrong.
Let's make it a star.
A star? Really?
I'm so happy!
My gosh!
-It's a doctor's gown!
-Yes.
-Awesome! It even has my name on it.
-Dad.
Dad.
Hey, Dad.
Hey.
Just a second. What's up?
I got into the basics class.
I got into a higher class, Dad.
-Really?
-Yes.
You're incredible, Ye-bin.
You finally got in.
Yes, I'm confident about getting
into the intensive class as well.
I should give you a reward.
What would you like? Do you want anything?
I don't need anything.
You should reward Hye-na instead.
-Shall I?
-Yes.
Hye-na, come here.
Tell me if you want anything.
I'll buy it for you.
No, it's okay. I only did my job.
Then how about I give you a bonus?
No, thank you for the offer.
But I'm already getting paid to teach.
That's more than enough.
Your mom raised you very well.
Thank you.
90% OF THE WORK TO GET A KID
INTO COLLEGE IS DONE BY THE MOM
I think
Hye-na's a really decent girl.
She teaches Ye-bin really well.
And she's humble and polite.
My gosh.
She's doing better than I expected.
But she's too mature for a kid,
and that makes me feel uneasy.
It's hard to be like that at her age.
Plus, she's not causing
any trouble with Ye-seo.
That's because she knows
no good will come from that.
She's a poor kid
who doesn't have any parents.
My goodness,
you're unbelievable.
You tend to see the worst in people.
My gosh.
Raise your arms.
Look. Look at this.
You drive me crazy.
How do you always get 60?
When will you get better?
How will you get
into a specialized high school?
How will you get accepted
to medical school?
My gosh.
What about Ye-bin?
Did she pass the test?
-Yes.
-She passed? She really passed?
You little...
That's why I said
I wanted to learn from Hye-na.
When did you ever hear me ask
for a private tutor?
Wait.
Her grades improved because of Hye-na?
She's a really awesome tutor.
Ye-bin said studying is fun.
-She did?
-Yes.
You stupid idiot.
Seo-jin wouldn't let a high school student
stay for no reason.
You.
Do you still want to learn from Hye-na?
Yes. With Ye-bin.
Okay. I'll sort it out tomorrow.
Don't grin.
I haven't called her once
since we found out she's Kwak Mi-hyang.
It's best I pretend we met by chance
at the kids' academy.
No.
Why should I tiptoe around Kwak Mi-hyang?
Where's Seo-jin?
Upstairs. I'll get her for you.
-Hello.
-Why are you here?
I haven't been around lately.
I got really sick
after sorting out my dish collection.
Bring us some tea.
Darn you.
Dr. Kang worked wonders
on my husband's back.
We might have another child at this rate.
What do you want?
I heard that Ye-bin went up
to the basics class.
I'm so jealous. You must be pleased.
So what?
Since winter break has started,
can Hye-na tutor Su-han as well?
With Ye-bin.
Those two always studied together.
It's true what they say about never
knowing who people really are.
I really can't trust anyone!
Shouldn't you know better?
They need to be on similar levels.
How can people in different classes
study together?
Are we done?
I'm a bit busy.
This is unbelievable.
You're acting just like a Kwak Mi-hyang.
What did you just say?
Su-han and Ye-bin.
They've done everything together
since they were three.
Did you tell me you'd get a live-in tutor?
You never mentioned it.
Like how you hid you're Kwak Mi-hyang.
Did you know that you have a habit
of stabbing people in the back?
-Say that again.
-What are you doing?
Hey, Kwak Mi-hyang!
Let go!
Let go. Why are you being so unrefined?
"Unrefined"? I'm being unrefined?
Shall I show you the real Kwak Mi-hyang?
I dare you to say that again.
I'll rip your jaw open.
She'll rip
my jaw open?
I'm telling the truth.
I asked her so nicely.
She suddenly grabbed my hair
so that my eyes went like this.
I could even see behind me.
She's a mad psycho.
She is Kwak Mi-hyang, isn't she?
You're right.
I told you to forget about Kwak Mi-hyang.
What's more important is
that she's my boss's wife.
You coward.
Your wife got her hair pulled out,
but you're defending her?
Then shall I quit my job
and move us out of here?
I'll quit if you want me to.
I'll quit and go
to that Kwak Mi-hyang woman
who touched your lovely hair
and pull out all of hers.
I'd rather kill myself.
Right?
Just wait and see.
I'll get Su-han
into the intensive class first.
I'll find a tutor a thousand times
better than Hye-na
and rip Kwak Mi-hyang's jaw open.
-Honey.
-My poor Jin Jin.
I've never heard such curses
since high school.
That's harsh.
How's your hair?
I think I'm going bald here.
I think so too.
Mom, let's decorate the Christmas tree.
The tree?
Are you kidding me?
You idiot. Do you know
what I went through for you?
I'll kill you today.
-Hang it up there.
-Okay.
-That's it.
-It's up.
-Do you think it's done?
-Yes.
It's beautiful.
Your dad must be in a good mood.
He's decorating the tree.
Of course I'm happy.
My daughter Se-ri's coming home.
Not just anyone gets into Harvard.
That's right. She got in
because she's our sister.
That's right.
When she arrives,
let's throw a lavish party for her.
What for, when we had a huge one
when she got into Harvard?
I'll just prepare
a simple Christmas party at home.
My goodness.
Se-ri.
-It's her?
-Se-ri?
Have you eaten?
-Isn't it breakfast--
-Give me that.
Se-ri, it's Dad.
Me too.
I'm dying to see you too, my baby.
My gosh, someone please save me.
Okay, 5:30 p.m. tomorrow?
Of course, I'll be there.
My amazing daughter's coming home.
Se-ri, get me a Harvard jacket!
Me too!
And a cap.
-A jacket.
-A cap.
Me too.
Her plane landed 30 minutes ago.
Why isn't she here yet?
She must be waiting for her luggage.
Why can't she hurry?
It's not her.
Dad!
Hey, Se-ri.
Se-ri!
-Have you been well?
-Yes.
My goodness.
Mom.
-Let's go home.
-Okay.
Se-ri, what kind of friends
do you have at Harvard?
To be honest, everyone there thinks
they'll become world leaders.
Their dreams and ambitions
are on another level.
My closest friends
are Neesha from New Delhi
and Fujiwara from Tokyo.
They both want to be prime ministers.
Se-ri, is it true that Harvard libraries
are open for 24 hours?
I once studied for three days and nights
at Widener Library.
-Three days and nights?
You just have to.
We have exams and papers every day.
Oh, my roommate Julie once
went a week without sleeping.
She took 15-minute naps
and used six alarm clocks.
-Wow.
-Can you do that?
My university is famous worldwide
for a reason.
All the professors and students
are outstanding,
but it's mainly because
of our 24-hour libraries.
I see.
Then,
what do you want to do
after you graduate, Se-ri?
I want to work in the US government.
At the White House, if possible.
In the States, competition among
different ethnic communities is prevalent.
So I want to be the voice
for Korean Americans
who are still considered
to be a minority there.
My, you're so impressive.
Seung-hye, you must be so proud of her.
I envy you so much.
Se-ri, how about you give us
our gifts now?
Twins, follow me with my suitcase.
Seo-jun, bring her suitcase. Let's go!
-Su-han.
-Hurry.
Be good to Seo-jun and Gi-jun.
Go on.
-U-ju, go on.
-Don't fight.
Hurry up.
I must say
you have such incredible foresight.
Sending Se-ri abroad at a young age
was a very wise decision.
The education system here
is all about college admission.
I figured it wouldn't be right
for a prodigy like Se-ri,
who's a free, creative spirit.
Let's be honest.
Even International
Mathematical Olympiad winners
mostly end up going to medical school.
An environment like this
can't produce talented people
who can make a difference in the world.
I wanted Su-han to go to medical school,
but I should change the way I think.
It's foolish to be fixated
on medical school.
Yes, there's no need to be fixated
As for Ye-seo, she really wants
to go to med school,
so I have no choice.
But in Su-han's case...
Yes, Harvard is great.
Shouldn't he pass
the level-up test first though?
What? My goodness.
Would you like more dessert?
-Sure, that'd be great.
-Shall we?
Yes.
-That little...
-Hey.
-Don't.
-Let go. I got this.
-Let's go smoke some cigars.
-Sure.
I quit smoking though.
All right. Dr. Kang, let's go.
Can I have some maple syrup?
Ms. Kwak Mi-hyang.
Jin-hui, I told you not to cross the line.
"The line"?
Who are you to keep telling me
not to cross the line?
Is this the 38th parallel?
Who's the one that grabbed my hair
and crossed the line first?
Jin-hui, please.
Do you want me to pull your hair again?
Or shall I pull it all out this time?
Why don't you just go ahead
and rip my jaw open?
Jin-hui, don't get cheeky with me.
Whether I'm Kwak Mi-hyang or Han Seo-jin,
you're still beneath me.
Do you think I'm a total loser?
Why must I be Kwak Mi-hyang's minion?
I asked for maple syrup!
I'm so sorry.
Seung-hye, give her some wet wipes.
You crazy psycho.
Oh, my goodness.
Gosh!
Gosh, I can't even open my eyes.
-Everyone, come here.
-Move!
Quick! Come here.
Is everyone in the frame?
-Just take it, will you?
-What? No, no. Okay.
All right, one, two.
-Okay, I'll send this photo to everyone.
-Okay.
You even got one for me. Thank you, Se-ri.
Gi-jun kept telling me to get one
for you and U-ju as well.
Hey, Ye-bin!
Don't you have to study?
Hey, why should I study
on a day like today?
-You can study if you want to.
-You little...
Ye-bin, you can have fun
for 30 more minutes.
We should finish off the rest, you know.
I'll go and get ready for our session.
I'll walk you there.
It's okay. I'll just go alone.
Yes, it's just a few steps away.
Don't go overboard.
Your parents aren't even home.
-We should have fun today, right?
-Totally.
Thanks to Se-ri,
I can take it easy all day long.
It's the first time this year.
Hey, we should take another photo
since Se-ri is here.
-Good idea. Gather, everyone.
-Okay.
-Can I stand here?
-This isn't a good spot.
Can't we go over there?
-I think this spot is better.
-Just take it.
-Everyone's here, right?
-Yes.
-Hye-na, come on in.
-Hurry, Hye-na.
Ye-bin!
Have a seat.
-You must be hungry.
-Yours isn't mixed yet.
-Yes.
-Okay.
-It looks good.
-It's so good.
Hye-na, you should try this too.
-I want one too.
-How is it?
-Is it good?
-Hye-na.
Give me one too.
Hye-na, let's take a selfie together.
-Hurry.
-Hye-na, come join us.
All right, a selfie.
-One, two, three.
-What's this?
-Oh, my.
-Will this be like a treasure hunt?
-Yes.
-Try it on.
-It's my turn now.
-Okay.
-I'll open it.
What could it be?
-My gosh!
-What is it?
-It's a doctor's gown!
-Yes.
Awesome! It even has my name on it.
-Seriously?
-My gosh.
-Shall I put it on for you?
-Yes.
My, this will look great on you.
Here.
Here, let's do this with your hair.
-Oh, my.
-Do I look like a doctor?
My darling daughter, you look stunning.
All right.
-There.
-Thank you, Dad!
My, it looks great on you.
-It's so nice!
-I know, right?
What are you doing here?
The doctor's gown...
I'm sorry.
I came in here to check out
a few books on medical science.
Didn't the housekeeper tell you the rules?
I'm sorry.
I'll be careful from now on.
-Have a good day.
-Thanks.
I was so taken aback as well.
She walks around as if it were
her own place when you aren't home.
What are you doing here?
Once, I went into her room
to bring her food.
Hye-na.
What do you think you're doing?
I told you not to come in here.
Don't you remember what I said?
Don't come into my room!
-Get out.
-Hye-na.
Get out at once. Now!
She threw a total fit.
Does she keep gold in there or what?
She won't let me go into her room.
Kim Eun-hye?
Could Hye-na be...
No.
No way.
That's impossible.
If Eun-hye had given birth
to Jun-sang's child,
she wouldn't have been quiet
all these years.
Do I know you?
Hello, I'm Ye-seo's classmate, Kim Hye-na.
If you let me be her in-house tutor
for just three months,
I'll make sure she gets
into the intensive class.
Thank you for hiring me.
You pick her up from school
and from the academy, right?
Would it be okay if I went with you?
Hye-na, you're very smart.
My gosh.
I think
Hye-na's a really decent girl.
And she's humble and polite.
She's a poor kid
who doesn't have any parents.
You're unbelievable.
You tend to see the worst in people.
PROBABILITY OF PARENTAGE: 99.99%
This fancy room could've been my mom's.
I found this in Se-ri's closet.
You see, brainiacs also know
how to have fun.
To Mom and Dad.
Thanks for raising me until now.
Goodbye.
That woman, Kim Ju-yeong, is dangerous.
It was all a lie.
I've never done it, so I don't know.
But I heard
unrequited love is pretty tough.
My mom had unrequited love
for someone all her life.
What are you planning?
You obviously know he's your dad.
Why did you move into our place?
Do you really not know?