(The 1st episode of Men on a Mission aired on December 5, 2015.)
(The members gathered for the first time.)
(The prelude to the legend and the history)
I've never been on a show that was this unpredictable.
Congratulations on coming to Brother School.
Who's the top dog of this school?
- Come forward.
- What's going on now?
- Oh, my gosh.
- Gosh.
- We are BLACKPINK.
This is our 100th episode.
The 100th episode. It's swag.
No one thought this show would reach 200 episodes.
Did you think it would be canceled?
"In the underwear?" Two syllables?
- Two syllables.
- Stop.
- This is the 300th episode.
- That's true.
- That's so cool!
- All right!
You rebels!
This is the 400th episode. I can't believe it.
Jang Hoon, the men you know are here.
We'll root for you forever. Congratulations!
We'll live happily together.
- Congratulations.
(D-3 before the 500th episode)
(The Men on a Mission studio is under construction?)
(For the 500 transfer students who'll come for the 500th episode, )
(Brother School is also being remodeled.)
(The largest set in the history of Brother School has been built.)
(The day of the shoot for the 500th episode)
(5 hours before the shoot)
(The 500 transfer students arrive gradually.)
(The endless line of people)
(Crowded)
(The special photo zone for the transfer students)
(Cute)
(Taking a photo with their favorite members)
(And in the corner of the photo zone...)
(Striking a "V" pose)
(There's a photo booth that offers Men on a Mission photo frames!)
(The 500th episode)
(They take photos in their own unique ways.)
Look at the camera.
(We can't miss this chance.)
(The members also enjoy taking photos together.)
(Satisfied)
(Snack time after taking photos)
(Hearty protein bar)
(Tasty protein snack)
(Refreshing energy drink)
(They recharge with sweets properly before going to school.)
(30 minutes before entering)
(10 minutes before entering)
(Winking)
(The transfer students are excited.)
(Congratulations on the 500th episode of Men on a Mission.)
(They prepared their school supplies too.)
(Let's go to school!)
(The transfer students enter with cool bottled water.)
(Finally, the 500 students begin attending school.)
(1 hour before the shoot)
(The line of students entering the classroom continues endlessly.)
(All 500 transfer students are in the classroom now.)
(We've transferred to this school.)
(They're excited to meet the cast members.)
(The members arrive backstage 1 by 1.)
When you hear the cheer as you enter,
your nervousness goes away.
I feel pressured.
I'm a little nervous because this will be broadcast live.
To reach 1,000 episodes!
- Let's go!
- Come on!
Let's go for the 1,000th episode!
Move!
The shoot for the 500th episode of Men on a Mission will begin shortly.
We'd appreciate if you could wait patiently just for a while.
(The members and the 500 transfer students are all here now.)
We're ready. One, two, three.
(Men on a Mission's 500th Episode Special will begin shortly!)
(The lights on the stage are turned off.)
(Excited)
- Boom!
- What's going on?
- It's explosive.
- What's explosive?
- What do you mean?
- It's explosive.
- What's explosive?
- We got such an explosive response.
- What?
- What do you mean?
- Tell us...
- When Chungju Man came on the show,
we made a video to promote our 500th episode.
- Yes.
This is the first lesson
Don't make catchphrases haphazardly
This is the last lesson
On September 11, we're inviting 500 people...
to the JTBC Studio.
For Men on a Mission's 500th Episode Special,
- come and have fun.
- Come and have fun.
We must throw a party
Oh, I get it. You mean this, right? We must throw a party
The video we made to promote our special episode...
- received an explosive response.
- I see.
- Really?
We said we were inviting 500 people.
(The total number of applicants: 9,867)
Thank you so much...
for your attention to our 500th episode.
The members of Men on a Mission love you all so much.
See you soon.
- What did he say?
- This will be our first time.
- He said, "See you soon."
- Oh, I see.
(We prepared for today when we'd have 500 of our viewers here.)
(Body)
(We're ready to use our whole body!)
(Head)
(We even took a lesson to improve our brain power!)
(It's the factual of 6.)
(It's "factorial.")
(Brain)
(A brain that is 2 percent short)
(Comedy)
My Majesty Kang.
Hey! What are you doing?
(For the very day of this shoot, )
(we played hundreds of comedy skits.)
(We prepared this for 10 years.)
(Transfer students, are you ready to join us?)
(Do you think you can handle it?)
(The transfer report will continue until your hair turns grey.)
(10 years of love)
(We'll repay you for your love with 10 times of laughter.)
(The members will appear in 10 seconds.)
(Please welcome them with a cheer that's 10 times louder than usual.)
- Ten!
- Nine!
- Eight!
- Seven!
- Six!
- Five!
- Four!
- Three!
- Two!
- One!
(The members are here now!)
Hi.
(Shin Dong, Senior Dong)
Oh, my. What do I do? Give me a second.
I'm not lying. I'm tearing up right now.
(I'm tearing up right now.)
I mean...
It feels weird...
to hear the cheer as I enter this classroom.
Let me greet you again. Hi.
- It's nice to meet you.
Have all of you transferred to our school?
- Yes!
That's amazing. Great.
You speak casually to us on this show. Don't speak formally.
- Okay.
- You've all transferred here, yes?
(We're all friends today, so speak casually to us.)
(Yes!)
I see an elderly person here.
You don't mind, do you?
We speak casually to one another on this show.
We're all friends here. Gosh.
Wait. Am I the only one who came?
Why hasn't everyone else come?
Gosh. They're late again.
In this situation, I'll do a roll call.
When I call their names, they will probably come.
The first member of Men on a Mission we'll meet is...
Lee Sang Min!
(Surprised)
(Lee Sang Min, the happy Uncle Sang Min)
This is incredible.
It made my hair stand on end.
How exciting. Hello!
(Hello)
- Isn't this amazing?
- It's amazing.
Next up is Seo Jang Hoon!
(Seo Jang Hoon, the tall Class President Seo)
(He's really tall!)
(The tallest member impresses everyone in the audience.)
You guys...
Why aren't you wearing a school uniform?
(Class President Seo points out that they're dressing inappropriately.)
Well, for now...
the audience cheered more loudly for Jang Hoon than for Sang Min.
Jang Hoon is unbeatable now.
(Proud)
Next up is Kim Yeong Cheol!
(Kim Yeong Cheol, the guy in the front row)
Ring, ring, I am Yeong Cheol
(Kim Yeong Cheol, I love you.)
Next up is Lee Soo Geun!
Gosh. Who built these stairs?
(He starts a skit as he appears.)
Good. This is nice.
Come on in.
We have a lot of transfer students.
Lee Soo Geun!
(Screaming)
(One of Soo Geun's fans is exceptionally high-spirited.)
- He's in an upper-level seat.
- They're going crazy.
This is just how I like it.
- A lot of people came here.
- Lee Soo Geun!
- He's so popular.
(The cheer for Soo Geun won't stop.)
- Lee Soo Geun!
- You're putting pressure on me.
I'm sorry.
(He responds to his fans with a funny act.)
- Don't put pressure on me.
- That was good.
Next up is Kim Hee Chul!
(Kim Hee Chul)
Hi, everyone. It's nice to meet you all. Oh, my.
(He's really handsome.)
Hee Chul seems a little bit nervous today.
- Of course, he's nervous.
- Right.
- He's acting nice.
- This is my first comedy show...
with a live audience.
He calls this a comedy show.
- I've never done this before.
- Right.
It's your first time.
- Next up is Min Kyung Hoon!
- Kyung Hoon is coming.
(Min Kyung Hoon, the shy Ssamja)
Kyung Hoon is here.
- You see...
- He seems nervous.
Let's have fun together today.
- His ears turned red.
- His ears are red.
His ears turned red.
- By the way, we have a problem.
- Why?
- Ho Dong came up with six ways...
- of making his entrance.
- That's right.
Everyone, look forward to seeing the last member.
Let's meet him now. It's Kang Ho Dong!
Jang Hoon! Oh, my. What's going on?
What is happening?
(Kang Ho Dong, the top dog of Brother School)
Guys, what's going on here?
(The transfer students welcome Ho Dong excitedly.)
You guys. What is this?
You guys...
- Kang Ho Dong!
(The 500 people in the audience are shouting "Kang Ho Dong.")
- So...
- Kang Ho Dong!
So...
Which school did you guys transfer from?
Which school did you say?
(They've transferred from across the country.)
No one can leave early in this school.
Since you're all here now,
if even one of you leaves early,
I will hate you!
They're supposed to laugh, but they're applauding instead.
(The transfer students are touched by Ho Dong's cute act?)
- I'm a little bit nervous.
- Right?
- It feels strange for some reason.
- You see...
- Right.
- I've never felt this vibe before.
- I've only sung on stage before.
- That's right.
- A show with a live audience...
- Usually, we begin like this,
and then we welcome our guests.
But today, we have 500 transfer students here.
- Exactly.
- Right.
We're getting an amazing vibe here.
This is really nice.
Many of them came from far away.
We used to say we had a long way to reach 500 episodes,
and the day actually came.
- Exactly. This is hard to believe.
- Right.
- I'm a little touched too.
- I know.
I didn't know they'd cheer so loudly for us.
Seeing the transfer students,
I realized that all age groups watch our show.
- Exactly.
- If you look at the audience...
- Right.
- Ma'am, did you watch it often?
What did we do last week?
(He checks the affection for Men on a Mission unexpectedly.)
- Today, we...
- Look at her.
- She remembers everything.
- I saw the episode.
But major age group of our viewers are far younger than them.
- I wish little kids were here.
- Right.
I'm in high school.
- I'm in middle school.
- We have a high school student.
I'm in 12th grade!
- You're in 12th grade?
- 12th grade?
I'm in 11th grade.
That's not what I meant. We...
- What?
- Gosh, he startled me.
- What's going on?
- Everyone!
- Hi!
(Leeteuk, the special Senior Teuk)
(Oh, my. He's so handsome!)
Oh, he's joining us.
It's good to see you again!
Make some noise!
My goodness. What's going on?
- I'm the special senior student...
- This is amazing.
who comes whenever there's a special event at Brother School.
I'm not Leedeuk.
I'm not Taxi.
I am Senior Teuk!
(I am Senior Teuk.)
- What's that?
- By the way,
you brought a lot of documents. What are those?
To celebrate the 500th episode of Men on a Mission,
- you invited 500 transfer students.
- Yes.
People in all areas of the country wanted to be here today,
so we received nearly 10,000 transfer applications.
- Oh, that's a lot.
- Are those transfer applications?
Yes, they are.
We selected only 500 applicants with good grades,
and those 500 students are here.
Give them a round of applause!
- That's amazing.
- They're incredible.
Also, some of them have special stories...
- where they met one of you.
- What?
- Some of them have met us?
- They have met us before?
- Really?
- Let me hold this.
- I wonder what stories they have.
- Oh, really?
- First up! Oh, here he is.
- They all seem excited.
Where are you, Seong Hwan?
- Over there.
- There he is.
Is his name Seong Ha Na?
Seong Hwan, before we start,
- Oh, it's Seong Hwan.
- can you introduce yourself?
Hello. I'm Choi Seong Hwan, and I'm from Gangneung.
It's nice to meet you.
- Gangneung?
- If he's from Gangneung...
- Hee Chul is from there too.
- Yes, he is.
- Hee Chul is from Wonju.
- I'm from Wonju.
Which of the members have you met?
- I've met Ho Dong before.
- You've met Ho Dong?
- We have a victim of Ho Dong here.
- What?
A victim of Ho Dong is here.
(Another victim of Ho Dong is here?)
- In Gangneung...
- Did you appear on "Star King?"
- Not long ago...
- Did he, really?
Ho Dong never went to Gangneung.
- I hope that's not the case.
- Ask him if he came on "Star King."
Let's hear him out.
- How did you meet him? I'm curious.
- I mean...
- Ask him yourself.
- I never went on "Star King."
- He didn't go on "Star King."
- That's a relief.
Is it a good story or a bad story?
It's a heartwarming story.
Jang Hoon, say what you always say.
"What's the point of hearing a heartwarming story about him?"
We went to Gangneung to shoot "2 Days 1 Night."
A kid asked for your autograph,
but you told him to go away. Maybe he's the kid.
(Mysterious stories are created endlessly.)
- The guy from Gangneung...
- I didn't say that.
- I said to meet me after the shoot.
- Right.
The guy from Gangneung, I'm sorry, but sit down.
- Sit down if it's a touching story.
- Right.
- You say only bad things here.
- Let's be kind...
- and hear what happened.
- Right. Let's hear his story.
Seong Hwan, please tell us.
- How did we meet?
- How did you meet him?
Seven years ago, I worked at a sashimi restaurant.
And Ho Dong...
I saw a big man wrapped in a shirt like this...
running from the parking lot.
I looked at him, wondering who he was.
But then the restaurant owner told me to go upstairs.
- Ho Dong's family was there.
- Oh, I see.
- At the sashimi restaurant?
- Yes.
I served their table by myself.
While I was waiting, Ho Dong asked me to come.
I sat down next to him, and we talked.
- Ho Dong asked about me.
- Yes.
And I said I would enlist in the military in the next month.
Since I would enlist in the military,
he told me to be safe while serving in the military.
And he gave me 50 dollars as pocket money.
- That's nice of him.
- Right.
(He flexed on the future soldier who would go through a hard time.)
- Ho Dong, do you remember that?
- Ho Dong...
- Do you remember that?
- He offered...
- to take a photo with me.
- That must be true.
Why did he do that?
- We took a selfie together.
- Really?
(Ho Dong volunteered to take a photo with him.)
- A photo...
- You see...
I don't remember exactly what happened,
but I'm sure that I wanted to give him good energy...
- as he seemed like a nice guy.
- I see.
- Nice.
- That's nice of you.
But as far as I remember, didn't I give you 500 dollars?
- Five hundred dollars?
- You gave me fifty dollars.
(He failed to increase the amount by 10 times.)
It would've been a lot thicker.
You gave me 50 dollars.
The amount of money doesn't matter since he was so caring.
- It's nice of him.
- Of course. It's nice of him.
Thank you for remembering that.
I should be thanking you too. I spent the money...
on buying something delicious.
- That's so nice of him.
- That's nice of him.
- Thank you.
Thank you, Seong Hwan.
- It was a trivial thing, - Right.
- but it remained as a good memory.
- Let's meet the next friend.
- Next up is... Oh, it's him.
- That was really great of him.
Where is Seung Yeon? Where are you, Kim Seung Yeon?
There was an MC...
Oh, there he is.
Please introduce yourself. Which one of them have you met?
Hi. I'm Seung Yeon, and I'm from Seoul.
(Which of the members has Seung Yeon met before?)
Which member have you met before?
I have a connection with Jang Hoon.
- Jang Hoon?
- Me?
I knew this would happen.
(Jang Hoon will be tried based on the story.)
- Seung Yeon seems...
- I wonder how they met.
- Seung Yeon seems very angry.
- I wonder what story he has.
- He sounds very determined.
- Indeed.
How did you meet Jang Hoon?
It's actually my father who met him.
- My father is...
- Was he a basketball player?
a former basketball player.
- And...
- Of course.
In his school days, Jang Hoon was his rival.
- They were rivals?
- In his school days?
- But Jang Hoon doesn't think of...
- I'm sorry,
but are you sure you're not mistaken?
I never had a rival.
(Awesome)
(His confidence overwhelms all 500 audience members.)
(Chuckling)
- What kind of rivalry...
- Jang Hoon always says...
that his greatest rival was himself.
I wonder what kind of rivalry we had.
- His family name is Kim.
- Who could he be?
My father is...
- I'll just tell you his name.
- Okay.
He was a basketball player at Korea University.
His name is Kim Byong Chul.
(Korea University's basketball player Kim Byong Chul)
(The 3-point shooter who led Korea University's heyday)
(The essence of high-flying basketball)
("If Kim Byong Chul Goes Crazy, the Others Can Just Run Back and Forth")
(Flying Peter Pan, Kim Byong Chul)
Oh, I see!
- So, - Peter Pan.
I can't see you because you're too far away.
You're Byong Chul's son?
We don't really look alike.
In my family, looking like my dad is an insult.
(His son publicly insults his looks.)
Hey, your dad was such a great player.
He was the best. I really like him as a person.
But there's something that you're mistaken about.
He wasn't my rival.
Then, whose rival are you?
- Seung Yeon.
- Who is it?
Well, Seung Yeon, we have to be precise about this.
Even though you're the son of a guy I really like...
- Of course.
- "I'm me."
Anyway, I'm so happy to see you.
- Nice to meet you.
- He was taken aback.
- It's so nice to see you, so...
- Seung Yeon.
- All of us at Men on a Mission...
- That's so nice.
were fans of your dad, Kim Byong Chul.
- Oh, really?
- Yes.
- I loved him so much.
- Really.
He was a great player who represented that era.
So, you should be good to your dad. Listen to what he says.
- Yes, of course.
- Yes.
- Right. It's nice to meet you.
- You really should.
- Welcome!
- Thank you, Seung Yeon!
This is fun.
Let's meet our next friend.
Next, it's Seo Hyun. Cho Seo Hyun, where are you?
- Seo Hyun?
- Here.
- Hi, Seo Hyun.
- Please introduce yourself.
Hi, guys.
I am Cho Seo Hyun, and I transferred from Yeonsinnae.
- Nice to meet you.
- She's so cute.
- You're from nearby.
- Who do you have a connection to?
If it's Yeonsinnae...
I have a connection to Yeong Cheol...
Thanks! We enjoyed hearing from you!
Who's our next friend?
You have to stay strong and talk.
- We'll continue to root for you.
- Sit. Yes.
Seo Hyun, what kind of connection do we have?
Have we met before?
Well, actually, we haven't met in person...
- That's a relief.
- It is.
(Chuckling)
I went to college thanks to Yeong Cheol.
- What? I doubt that.
- Him?
Did Yeong Cheol pay for your tuition?
You went to college thanks to him?
Is it a touching story?
Yeong Cheol didn't pay for my tuition.
But you know know everyone has a hard time in 12th grade?
During that time when everyone feels mentally drained,
I also went through a period of struggle.
During that, I watched one of Yeong Cheol's videos...
and felt so comforted...
and was able to find my willpower again.
Do you guys perhaps remember...
the Men on a Mission Awards back in 2019?
Yes, we did that.
At the time, you guys voted for...
- the We Praise You Award.
- Right.
There was one vote for Yeong Cheol.
(Kim Yeong Cheol)
(He has started to shine!)
(Oh, no. I'm going to cry.)
Don't cry.
(The phrase that made Yeong Cheol cry in the end)
It was for the reason that...
- he has started to shine.
- I remember.
- Yeong Cheol was so touched...
- He cried.
and started tearing up.
- I...
- I'm about to cry now too.
- Gosh, what is this?
- But then...
(He gets choked up again.)
I watched that video when I was in 12th grade...
and saw Yeong Cheol's reaction.
That made me think that if I work hard as well,
there will come a day...
when the people around me...
will acknowledge that I am starting to shine too.
So, I was able to strengthen my resolve again and study hard,
which helped me successfully get into college that year.
- I remember how hard I studied.
- You're right.
(Yeong Cheol became a supportive figure in her heart in hard times.)
So, Seo Hyun, you went to college.
Which year are you in now?
I finished my second year,
and I'm taking some time off to achieve two goals.
What are your 2 goals? Finish your 3rd and 4th years?
- Those are clear goals.
- What are your goals?
- I am going to finish those, - Yes.
but first, I wanted to learn a few things...
by dedicating my time wholly.
So now, I am learning to sing.
That's so nice.
I hope you achieve your dreams, Seo Hyun.
- Good luck!
- I'll do my best.
- All right.
- I'm nervous.
Let's meet our next friend.
- I'm so nervous.
- Ddal Ki, where are you?
- Ddal Ki?
- Please introduce yourself.
Hi, I'm Yang Ddal Ki,
and I'm from Ansan, Gyeonggi Province.
- Yang Ddal Ki?
- Your name is Ddal Ki?
Actually, for about ten years,
I was a huge fan of Super Junior.
Don't you remember anything after hearing my name, Hee Chul?
- Hang on. I...
- Goodness.
- It's Ddal Ki.
- For real.
- Yang Ddal Ki. Hang on.
- He must remember. Tell us.
What connection do you have?
When I was in high school, I sent a letter to the radio show...
- that Hee Chul hosted.
- "Young Street."
- Yes, to "Young Street."
Back then, since my name is so unique,
I was under a lot of stress.
That was what my letter was about.
When Hee Chul read my letter, he said,
"If I were set up on a blind date with a woman named Ddal Ki,"
"I'd go without even seeing her picture."
"I would meet her for sure."
That was what he said.
I was really comforted back then,
- and it helped me...
- So nice. What a beautiful story.
- Ddal Ki.
- Yes?
But why do you like Hee Chul the most out of Super Junior?
Isn't that obvious? He's handsome.
(He's handsome.)
Hey.
- Shin Dong is more handsome.
- What?
(The guy in charge of good looks heads straight for Ddal Ki.)
Thanks.
(A powerful hug)
(After a hug from the guilty man, Hee Chul, )
(Ddal Ki is weak in the knees.)
Gosh, then...
- Shall we hug too?
- What?
- Gangneung?
- Look at him.
Ddal Ki, is Hee Chul the most handsome guy...
- in the world?
- We should've hugged.
That was true ten years ago.
Hey, you!
- Come on.
- You even gave her a hug.
- Okay, stay behind after the show.
- Right.
- Okay.
- Welcome!
- Nice to meet you, Ddal Ki!
- Nice to meet you!
- Gosh, this is so nice.
- This is fun.
Let's meet our next friend.
Where is Na Rae? Na Rae.
- Hi.
(The next transfer student appears cheerfully.)
Hi, I transferred from...
I Wanted to See Men on a Mission So Badly High.
My name is Lee Na Rae. Nice to meet you.
- I Wanted to See So Badly High.
- Yes.
I have quite a deep connection with Soo Geun.
Gosh, Na Rae's voice is like a comedienne.
- Na Rae.
- She has that tone.
I'm speaking with a really high tone now.
- Oh, really?
- Anyway,
first of all,
the people here probably only know Namdaemun of...
Dongdaemun and Namdaemun,
but I even know Dongdaemun too.
What? Do you know him too?
Of course. I worked with him.
- You did? At the training center?
- Yes, so...
Soo Geun worked as a recreation instructor, right?
These are the friends who were Soo Geun's junior instructors.
- You worked with the Barbarian too.
- Yes, Ji Ho.
- That's right.
- Yes, your junior team...
and I worked together for about seven years straight.
- At the training center?
- Yes.
- So I've heard a lot about you...
- There are training centers for...
from the recreation instructor field.
And I've heard so much about you all throughout my life,
so I've wanted to meet you for sure.
- Oh, really?
- Yes, it's nice to meet you.
It's nice to meet you too. My gosh.
It's so nice to meet you.
If you have the time later on,
let's dance to "Don't Make a Wry Face" together.
Oh, that's right. One, two, three, four.
(Don't make a wry face)
Three, four. Don't make a wry face
Oh, my.
They know all of the dance moves.
(She took over his duties perfectly.)
(Shaking it all out)
- All right.
- It's nice to meet you!
- She's totally a comedienne.
- She still knows it.
This is fun.
So, that's the connection we have.
This is our last friend. Let's call our last friend.
Where is Yoon Chae? Yoon Chae.
- Yoon Jae?
- Hi.
(Where is Yoon Chae, the last person with a connection?)
Please introduce yourself.
I'm Oh Yoon Chae from Cheongju.
- Cheongju.
- Oh, Cheongju.
Three years ago, on the beach of the East Sea,
I met Dong.
- Do you perhaps remember?
- You met Dong at the East Sea?
I have a connection with Dong from three years ago.
Oh, Shin Dong.
- At the beach of the East Sea?
- Yes.
- Three years ago?
- What is this?
- Dong, wasn't this...
when you were picking up girls?
- What?
- I mean, I'm afraid of water,
- so I don't go to the sea often.
- What is this?
- Three years ago?
- So, three years ago,
I was chosen to see...
a shoot with Super Junior's Leeteuk, Dong, and Kyu Hyun,
- so I went there.
- I remember that.
When I went there, I asked Dong if you could give me an autograph.
- Right.
- But you were too busy,
so you said you'd do it for me later.
You seemed really busy, so I thought you wouldn't do it,
- so I was going to just leave.
- You're all bad people.
But Dong was shouting from afar and running towards me.
You were like, "Autograph! You have to take a photo before you go!"
(Shin Dong picked up a nice story at the East Sea.)
- So, that's what happened.
- He was...
- Barely.
- running out towards me.
- You were safe but barely.
- My gosh.
You took photos with all of my friends...
and gave us autographs.
- That timing was so lucky.
- But then,
after taking a photo, I went home...
- and showed it off to my mom.
- What a huge relief.
After my mom saw the photo,
she said, "Aren't you two siblings?"
Oh, you and me?
So, I brought the photo I took back then.
Will you take a look and see if we look similar?
I can see it.
- You look alike.
- That's amazing.
- You look the same since then.
- I brought it.
(The audience stirs at how similar they look.)
I think we have similar eyes.
- I know, right?
- You do look similar.
By any chance, did you get plastic surgery on your eyes too?
I did.
(Shin Dong reveals his fan's plastic surgery history for her.)
Sure.
Oh, boy.
(Became siblings later in life)
Is it okay for you...
- to say it openly here?
- She did look younger.
- It's okay. Everyone knows.
- Do they?
- You're right.
- She's young.
- Yes.
(I found my younger sister!)
It's so nice to meet you. Thank you.
- Thank you.
- Nice to meet you.
It's so fun to see these connections.
After meeting our friends with connections,
doesn't it feel like we quickly got close with the 500 people?
- Yes.
- Right?
Now, let's begin our class.
Gosh, this is...
our 1st class in 10 years.
- Hey...
- What?
Who left me out?
- Hey.
What is this?
Who left me out of this celebration?
(The celebration expert enters.)
Hye Lyun.
(500th Episode Special Guest, Cho Hye Lyun)
Who left me out of this 500th episode celebration?
Are you Cho Jin Ah?
Nice to meet you, I am Cho Jin Ah.
("Wanted, Sexy Music, Hot Stuff" by Cho Hye Lyun)
Ho Dong made it through.
Scream!
Everyone knows the lyrics, now.
Let's sing together.
Come on.
Spin it, everyone!
("Banana Nala" by Cho Hye Lyun)
Everyone, spin!
(So Hee left)
- So Hee left.
- Everyone, together.
(Men on a Mission)
One more time.
(It's the 500th episode.)
Spin it, one more time.
Keep it spinning.
All together.
(The production crew)
It's the crew.
(Men on a Mission)
What did you say?
(500th episode)
Go like this.
(The 500th episode...)
(left.)
- Hey.
- Cho Hye Lyun.
- Today,
- to congratulate...
- the 500th episode, - Cho Hye Lyun.
- the queen of celebrations, - Cho Hye Lyun.
- the best celebration performance, - Cho Hye Lyun.
the queen of excitement,
Hye Lyun is here. Let's give a round of applause.
- They added too much to my pants.
- But hey...
My pants are too heavy.
- Senior Teuk.
- Yes?
Actually,
- Hye Lyun is practically family.
- She is.
She transferred the most times...
- among all transfer students.
- Yes.
- You're right.
- I know.
Are you crazy?
No, don't...
Please.
(Cho Hye Lyun)
Can you tell?
If you say so, I'll pick you.
To be honest, during Sisters on a Mission,
- Men on a Mission was on the edge.
- Yes.
They were barely making it through the year.
- But goodness.
- It's the 500th episode.
- No way.
Yeong Cheol made it through...
- without getting fired.
- Without getting fired.
- I did.
- And Sang Min...
- got married.
- Got married.
And Kyung Hoon...
- got married.
- Got married.
But Jang Hoon...
- hasn't gotten married yet.
- Hasn't yet.
Not yet.
You didn't.
Give us a word, as part of the family.
- 500 episodes mean 10 years, right?
- Yes.
That’s truly incredible.
- Take a look.
Take a look at the members.
- They are in their 30s and 20s.
- The members.
- The Gen Z...
- The age is amazing.
- members.
- The members.
- They really love Men on a Mission, - Right.
- and they grew up watching this.
- That's good.
- So...
- But Hye Lyun, if you have time,
- don't just leave.
- Yes.
- Play a game with us.
- That sounds good.
Yes.
- I'm here as the representative.
- Guys, should we ask her...
to play a game with us before leaving?
- Yes.
- Let's go, guys!
- We'd love that!
- That sounds good.
Your are now watching the 500th Episode Special.
Everyone, scream!
(They answer in 500dB.)
It is finally the time that you've all been waiting for.
500 transfer students versus the 8 brothers.
We will begin the biggest match of 2025.
(The big match begins!)
- Wait a minute.
- What is it?
If we're going to play a game,
then I need to be a part of the hosting.
That's right.
We are...
- Teuk-Dong Game Masters.
- Game Masters!
(Teuk-Dong Game Masters organized)
"Teuk-Dong Game Masters?"
Through the transfer forms, a lot of you have requested...
the game that you want to compete against the brothers.
We picked the top three games,
and we will play them today.
The first game will be one...
that a lot of you said you were confident in.
- Guess the Song in One Second!
- In One Second!
Hee Chul.
Let's go.
- Hee Chul - For the one-second game,
it's Hee Chul.
We can even call it...
- the "Hee Chul Game."
- That's right.
("Sonata of Temptation" by IVY)
("Me Gustas Tu" by GFRIEND)
(He just needs 1 second for Korean songs.)
(Pop)
(Did the speaker pop?)
("Be Mine" by INFINITE)
(He could even go against the search engine.)
(AI for Korean songs, Chat Hee Chul)
But today, it won't be an easy match.
- No way. It will be easy.
- What is it?
We went through strict testing...
to pick out ten contestants with the best skills.
(The preliminary match earlier)
(They came up to the stage to play against Hee Chul for the game.)
(118 people applied for the preliminary match.)
("Com' Back" by SECHSKIES)
(Screaming)
("Time of Our Life" by DAY6)
("Tomboy" by (G)I-DLE)
("Hot Summer" by f(x))
("Han" by Chakra)
(Screaming)
(The final 10 people were chosen.)
They passed the preliminary match, so they must be good.
I'm sure you must be nervous, Hee Chul?
Let's bring in the ten people.
- Okay.
- Ten transfer students,
please come out.
Please come out.
Win.
- Of course.
- There you go.
Nice.
- You have to win.
- They've got strong character.
- Hello.
- Gosh.
- Nice to meet you.
- What?
There's a surprise.
Nice.
- Hello.
- Gosh.
- Amazing.
- I think that guy will be good.
- I think so.
Wait a minute. There's a hot dog there.
- A hot dog?
- There is.
This is like Yoo Byung Jae's birthday party.
- I know.
- Yes.
- That's right.
- Yoo Byung Jae's birthday party.
Wait a minute. There are...
some famous people here.
I know one person.
- What?
- This...
- This guy is really famous.
- Who?
- Him.
- Do you know me?
This guy.
Really?
He's really famous on social media.
- Really?
- Yes.
- What is your content about?
- What does he do?
I play the character, Pick-Me Girl Saemi.
- I am a content creator, Tae Su.
- Do you know him?
I really love the members of Men on a Mission,
so I applied.
You just applied, and you got picked to come up here?
Yes, I passed the test.
And there's one more.
- Can I say this?
- Another one?
- I was so surprised.
- Who is it?
- The hot dog?
- No, this...
- Really?
- This guy.
- This guy is...
- He's similar to you.
He's my actual cousin.
- What?
- Really?
- I didn't know.
- Is he your brother?
- No, I didn't know.
- His cousin.
Are you sure you didn't give him a ticket?
No, I really didn't. I had no idea.
Why are you here?
- I came to see you.
- Speak into the microphone.
- I said that he looks similar.
- I came to see you.
This is amazing.
- Your whole family looks similar.
- Hey.
- We look similar, right?
- Of course.
We're the only fat ones in our family.
No one else is fat.
- That's amazing.
- Then how did they...
- The hot dog...
- Who is the hot dog?
Hot Dog. Who are you?
I came from Hot Dog High School.
- Hot Dog?
- Hot Dog High School?
- I'm a transfer student.
- Hot Dog High School.
- She came from Hot Dog High School.
- No viewer of Men on a Mission...
- has their right mind.
- That's right.
- Hot Dog High School.
- I'll tell you the rules.
- The rules are simple.
- Listen.
You'll listen to one second of the intro...
and shout, "Let me answer."
When I call your name, you will come out here,
- step on the white mark, - Right.
and say the song's title and its artist.
So the ten contestants will be on the same team.
- Hold on.
- Eleven.
- Eleven, including me.
- Hee Chul...
- Then it's an 11 versus 1 match.
- Nice.
You'll get 10 points for 1 question.
The team that scores 50 points 1st wins.
(The team that scores 50 points 1st wins!)
Are you confident, Hee Chul?
- Now that I see it, it's not easy.
- It's not easy.
They were on a training camp for 3 nights and 4 days.
Really?
Now, we'll begin the match!
(Guess the Song in One Second begins.)
All right.
- This is like an individual match.
- Here's the first question.
- Give us the first question!
- Give it to us!
- That was it.
- What was that?
- It's difficult.
- Wasn't it a snake?
- That was it.
- It sounded like a snake.
- It's so difficult.
- That's difficult.
(Breathing)
(Is it aespa?)
We'll play it for a bit longer. A little bit more.
Music, please.
You have one too.
- That was it.
- It sounded like a sword.
- Hee Chul.
"Prince of the Sea" by Park Myung Soo?
"Prince of the Sea" by Park Myung Soo? Incorrect.
Gosh. What is it?
- Hee Chul!
- Hee Chul.
(Did Hee Chul finally get it?)
What song and by whom?
One, two, three.
- Incorrect!
- What was that?
- We have it.
- Isn't it that song?
- Okay.
- Let me answer.
- Let me answer!
- Over here, please.
- What's the answer?
- "Lonely Night" by Boohwal?
- That's right!
- That's correct!
Correct.
(It's a pity.)
(Well done, Team Transfer Students.)
(The transfer student suddenly runs to Jang Hoon.)
- What is it?
- Could you make a Y, please?
Could you make the Y for Yonsei with me?
Yonsei University.
(Hee Chul: 0 versus Team Transfer Students: 10)
- I knew the song.
- He was so close.
- I knew the whole song.
- What is it, Jang Hoon?
Do you know what he said to me?
He said he studies at Yonsei University.
- Y?
- He asked me to make the Y.
Y like this.
- I thought it was a heart.
- Y.
They're both alumni.
But Hee Chul came to the front...
- He gave them so many hints.
- and gave the whole song.
Since many people are watching,
I get the pressure to show them something.
But you should know, the 1st team to score 50 points wins.
- It's 10 to 0.
- We can do it.
- They wouldn't have known...
- Let's go.
- if you hadn't said anything.
- We're 11 people.
- That's right.
- You gave them everything.
- A soccer team.
- We'll move on...
- to the second question.
- Let's go!
- The second question. Music, - Please!
What?
A lightbulb just fell.
We need to fix this. The lantern.
- Who puts lanterns these days?
- Really? I'm sorry.
Okay. We'll play it again.
- Music, please.
- That's not correct.
It is.
What's the answer?
- Hye Lyun.
- Hye Lyun!
"I Know" by Seo Taiji and Boys.
- That's incorrect.
- Just guess.
- Let me answer.
- Yes?
- "Supernova" by aespa?
- "Supernova" by aespa is incorrect.
- It's incorrect.
- I was so nervous...
- We have to give it a try.
thinking they would get it.
- It's this!
- What is...
I'm sorry, but can you discuss over there?
- She's right next to me and...
- I'm sorry.
- We'll play it for a bit longer.
Music, please.
- Let me answer.
(Will the transfer student answer correctly again?)
- What's the answer?
"Kill This Love" by BLACKPINK.
That's correct!
(Hee Chul: 0 versus Team Transfer Students: 20)
That's amazing.
(He shoots a bullet of love to the transfer students.)
(A shy exit)
Do more.
There it is.
(Saemi takes over the stage center.)
- He's good.
- He's good. Goodness.
- Goodness.
Goodness.
(He shoots the hearts of 500 people.)
- You succeeded!
- He's good.
- Gosh.
- Right now, Hee Chul...
- Recent songs are hard.
- is behind.
Did you have no idea? Hee Chul.
- I don't know recent songs.
- You don't know?
- I'm an old person. I'm okay.
- You can't call it a recent song.
- It was released years ago.
- Really?
It's 20 to 0 now.
- Hold on.
- You have to get 50 points.
Hee Chul isn't getting any answers.
- You might lose with no points.
- I'm sweating.
He's sweating.
- We'll continue.
- I don't sweat even at my concerts.
Focus! This is the third question.
- Music, please.
- The music.
(Clacking)
- Let me answer.
"Fiction" by BEAST.
- "Fiction!"
- Correct!
How did you know that?
Get ready.
(Hee Chul: 0 versus Team Transfer Students: 30)
(It's Saemi again.)
He's good.
(I'll hold you)
He's good. They all have talents.
(I won't let you go)
They dance well.
So well.
Well done!
He's good.
But...
(We want to live in Saemi's fiction.)
I'm sorry.
- This is amazing.
- When I can't come...
because of my schedule, he could come instead.
I think he could come.
He's so good.
- He's so good.
- Kim Hee Chul!
Answer the questions. We want to dance as well!
- "We want to dance as well."
- We practiced for one week.
We're all waiting.
Hee Chul. You're too nervous right now.
- Right.
- I'm so flustered.
He can't move his lips.
Can't you see the 500 pairs of eyes full of disappointment?
- He's too good.
- He's really good.
Please cheer for Hee Chul.
One, two, three!
(Let's go, Hee Chul!)
Let's go.
It's 3 to 0.
Next question.
- Music, please.
- We have two questions left.
What's the answer?
Say it when you're sure.
One...
- Let me answer.
- Yes?
- Na Rae.
- "Come Back" by CLON?
-"Come Back" by CLON? Incorrect.
- Incorrect.
- She's from our generation.
- No.
- No doubt.
- Let me answer!
- The answer is?
- "A Smart Choice" by So Chan Whee?
"A Smart Choice" by So Chan Whee?
- Incorrect.
We'll play the music again.
Music, please.
(They listen to it again.)
- Let me answer.
- Yes?
"Break up with Her" by Kim Hyun Jung?
- Kim Hyun Jung. Incorrect.
- Let me answer!
What's the answer?
"Bruise" by Kim Hyun Jung.
That's correct!
(Hee Chul: 0 versus Team Transfer Students: 40)
They're good.
(The stage races with a wind speed of 500km per hour.)
What's wrong with them both?
(Tapping)
- The two of them...
- They don't want to lose.
Goodness.
That's...
(Turn back my heart.)
They're good.
What's this?
(I hope you meet someone like you)
They're good.
(Their flirting bruises the transfer students.)
- Well done.
- I'm just dancing...
instead of guessing.
- You're good.
- Soo Geun...
- It's so funny.
- Soo Geun's close...
What's funny is that he didn't get any answer correct.
He just dances.
- Right.
- I just hope anyone gets it.
- I'll do my best.
- You're behind.
- Earlier...
- Try harder.
- Now...
- What are you doing?
You would all know.
If the 11 people here get 1 more question right, it ends.
- That can't happen.
- I'm sorry,
but why did Shin Dong's relative come here?
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
- We have one question left.
- We still...
- Let's keep going.
- There's still a chance.
- You can do it!
- Let's go.
- Play the next music!
- Next music, please!
What's that?
Did someone fart?
- The answer?
- Let me answer!
- But...
- Yes?
- It ends when I say it now.
- It ends.
- You can say it.
But don't you want to see Hee Chul dance?
- Hold on.
- We want to see!
This hurts my pride so much.
- We'll let you guess it.
- My pride hurts so much.
- Tell him something.
- Listen to it.
What's the answer?
- It's by Sharp.
- Sharp?
(Thinking)
I think she knows.
- One, two, three.
- Two, three.
- Let me answer.
- "Blue Blue?"
- "Blue Blue" is incorrect.
- Incorrect.
They gave him a chance.
Hee Chul. Will you take this chance?
- What will you do?
- It hurts my pride so much.
- Take it.
- What's the answer?
- Tell Me
- That's correct!
- Correct!
Come with me.
- Come with me.
- Go.
- Go quickly.
- Let's go!
- They're coming!
- They're coming.
(The classroom train is leaving!)
- Let's go!
- They prepared this.
- They're going.
- Go.
They're going.
Come on! Episode 500.
They all joined.
Episode 500!
Let's go.
- Correct!
- Success!
(Episode 500 Train runs on the transfer students' cheers!)
So many transfer students are amazing at this.
It's like a festival right here.
- For real.
- We're in a pinch, Hee Chul.
Everyone's just too good.
- They're so good, - Yes.
- They're seriously so good.
- I'm caught off guard.
Did you all practice beforehand?
On YouTube, there are compilations...
- of episodes from "Gayo Top 10."
- Yes, a collection.
- That's a good one.
- I listened to...
- Did you watch it?
- the whole thing.
- Gosh.
- Unbelievable.
- They came prepared.
- Amazing.
- You can't beat hard work.
- No.
There's still a chance to turn things around.
- Hee Chul got another chance.
- Exactly.
- He must repay the kindness.
- I'm so embarrassed.
- He owes it to everyone.
- Yes.
Even in soccer, when you're losing 5-0,
the other team helps you score a goal.
- How embarrassing.
- It's kind of like that.
My pride.
- Here we go.
- Music,
- please!
- Please!
(Playing)
Hee Chul.
(Two transfer students have a lead.)
(Hee Chul also has a lead.)
- Hee Chul.
What's your answer, Hee Chul?
- One, two!
- Hold on. Give me a second.
- One, two, three.
(Singing)
- Let me answer.
- Answer it until the end.
- Why are you...
- so bad at it?
- It's over.
- What's your answer?
- "Lupin" by KARA.
("Lupin" by KARA)
- Yes, I knew it.
- Goodness.
- You almost had it.
- Correct.
I can't remember any songs after our debut.
- She's just too good at it.
- Gosh.
- Amazing.
- How does she do it?
You're no match for them.
(Let's start the last party.)
- They're good.
- Nice.
- Was that the last round?
- Yes.
(Hee Chul: 10 versus Team Transfer Students: 50)
Gosh.
I was hoping to dance more.
- Well done.
- Success.
- Goodness.
- They're good.
- With this, - Cool.
- we have an unexpected outcome.
- That was tough.
- Yes.
- The winner...
of Guess the Song in One Second is...
- Team Transfer Students.
(Winner of Guess the Song in 1 Second: Team Transfer Students)
- Nice.
- Our contestants.
Hot Dog appeared confident, yet did nothing.
- Hot Dong.
- What's with you, Hot Dog?
I don't think she can hear clearly.
- But...
- The outfit is blocking...
- her ears.
- Exactly.
You should pull it back.
She's a celebrity.
The guy next to her is sweating buckets.
- Who?
- It's scorching hot.
I didn't get anything right, but I danced six times.
- Thank you.
- You look the most excited today.
Even though I didn't get any right, I'm having fun.
I have a personal request.
How about a showdown with Shin Dong?
- Shin Dong's junior.
- It's a festival.
- With Shin Dong, right?
- Yes.
- Play a random song.
- A showdown, please.
My nickname is Shin Dong.
- Really?
- Yes.
Anyone can see he looks like Shin Dong.
- They meet at last.
- Please get both of us in the shot.
- Actually, I'm afraid...
- Guys.
I must ask my cousin to leave. He's my cousin.
It's actually me, everyone.
- He's my cousin now.
- That's right.
All right. To celebrate today's winners, the contestants,
we have a congratulatory performance.
It's a performance with Shin Dong and one contestant.
Please give them a big round of applause.
This is...
What?
Unbelievable.
- Nice.
- He's no joke.
Shin Dong.
(Next is Shin Dong's turn.)
- Gosh.
- Yes, that's it.
(Impressed)
(A dance prodigy born from Shin Dong)
What was that?
No.
(Pinching his nose)
Very nice.
- A round of applause.
- Great.
(A performance with family-like energy)
- That was great.
- Thank you.
- Hee Chul.
- Yes?
The name "Hee Chul Game" should be...
- I'm dropping it.
- Good.
Please tell us how you feel.
I wouldn't have anything to say,
even if the internet started claiming it was all fabricated.
- What a bummer.
- Yes, I'll work harder.
Today is the 500th Episode Special.
We'll prepare this segment again for the next special,
- hoping you'll take the win then.
- Got it.
Congratulations to all of today's contestants!
- A round of applause!
- Thank you!
(The first match winner: Team Transfer Students)
- Good job.
- This way, please.
- Great work. That was amazing.
- Right?
The second match against the members...
- is the Capital Quiz.
- Quiz!
(Capital Quiz)
You all know the famous Capital King of Brother High School.
Who is it?
- Seo Jang Hoon.
- Let's go.
(Seo Jang Hoon, Brother High School's Capital King)
He's not only knowledgeable about capital cities,
but he's also full of competitive spirit.
More than anything, he hates losing.
- That's right.
- Yeong Cheol.
(Jang Hoon!)
(Beirut, Lebanon)
(What is the capital of Iceland?)
(Reykjavík)
Malta.
(Is the appearance of a Capital Queen a threat to the Capital King?)
(Not a chance!)
(In front of the competitor Jang Hoon, )
(even the top brain is helpless.)
(Soo Geun: Knowing all the capitals of the world, )
(the epic story of the Capital King's rise.)
All right. Someone will go up against Seo Jang Hoon.
- We won't go easy on him today.
- No, we won't.
And he always claims he has no rivals.
- That's right.
- Yes.
A perfect record.
- We're looking forward to it.
- I'm nervous.
- Are you nervous?
- Even during my busy days...
Did you study?
- Between my busy hours, - Yes?
- I put in the effort...
- He came prepared.
to study some of the tougher countries.
- I came prepared.
- I see.
I thought I'd be doing the quiz with 3 or 4 people,
but look at all these chairs.
In the earlier match,
you saw Hee Chul get destroyed.
- How do you feel?
- I'm really worried.
- I've been busy lately, - Right.
and despite all the studying, I'm not sure...
- I'll remember everything.
- Right.
Who will take the stage?
We selected ten contestants...
through a fierce...
- preliminary match.
- Good.
(Defeat Seo Jang Hoon? The Capital Quiz)
Only ten contestants will make it through.
(143 contestants in the preliminary match)
(Only the top 10 experts can face Jang Hoon!)
(Nigeria)
(Serbia)
(Rwanda)
(No matter how tough, the capital experts come through!)
(Can Jang Hoon defend his throne?)
The ten transfer students,
please come on up to the front.
(Come on up to the front!)
These guys are just as fierce.
- Welcome.
Please take a seat, starting from the far end.
(The 10 transfer students: Song Jong Hyun, Oh Jae Yong, )
(Hwang Eun Chan, Jo Seung Yeon, Bang Sae Hoon, Nam Chang Seok, )
(Yoo Ye Bin, Jin Gwan Woo, Choi In Kyu, Choi Jae Min)
(Keeping them in check)
Their faces are full of academic enthusiasm.
Please take a seat.
- For starters, - Let's begin.
they give off a different vibe from the earlier ten contestants.
Their faces look pretty nerdy.
- Yes.
- That's amazing.
Wait, why are you taking that end seat?
- There are 11 contestants.
- Is that so?
But you participated in my segment as well.
- You're not one of us today.
- I'm like a sidekick.
Now then, we have many contestants...
who made it through the preliminary match.
The rule of the Capital Quiz is...
When I tell you the name of a country,
you write its capital on your sketchbook.
If you get the answer wrong or leave it blank,
you're eliminated immediately.
How far will Jang Hoon last against these 11 contestants?
- That will be key.
- Yes.
- Please.
- Good.
Is the match over if Jang Hoon gets...
the first question wrong?
Yes.
The match ends right then and there.
- No cheating.
- The seats are close together.
- That's right.
I'd rather lose than cheat.
Cool.
Fair and square, Seo Jang Hoon.
- Okay.
- Play fair.
We have someone with a unique outfit.
- By any chance...
- Isn't that against the rules?
He looks like he came from a monastery.
He even has a fan. Where are you from?
(Unfolding)
Doesn't he have the capitals written on the fan?
- You should check it.
- Right, this is...
- I...
- Take it away from him.
Where are you from?
From I Draw Animals with Hangeul High,
my name is Jin Gwan Woo. Nice to meet you.
Say a word to Seo Jang Hoon, please.
It's easy peasy, isn't it?
I will beat you.
That was extreme. "It's easy peasy, isn't it?"
What a strong provocation.
All right. I will now reveal the name of the country.
- Okay.
- What's the first country?
It's...
- Romania.
- You have ten seconds.
(What is the capital of Romania?)
It's a hard one.
- Romania...
- I'm already lost.
- is in Europe.
- Yes.
(Meanwhile, the capital aces write confidently.)
(Chuckling)
(Jang Hoon is already done?)
Seo Jang Hoon is fast.
You have five seconds left.
- Okay.
- Watching them from behind,
it's like "The Golden Bell Challenge."
What is the capital of Romania?
- Three, two, one.
- Please hold up your answers.
- Your answers.
Those who left it blank are out.
Let's start from this side. He wrote, "Bucharest."
- Yes.
- It must be precise.
- "Romania."
- "Romania?"
- With a question mark.
- He drew with Hangeul...
- but failed to write the capital.
- No.
- Next, "I'm sorry."
- "Sorry I messed up."
- "I'm sorry." We also have Sofia.
- Okay.
- "Bucharest."
- We've got Bucharest.
- He wrote, "GG."
- "GG."
- "Bienerman."
- "Bucharest."
- From what I see..
- "Vault?" Where's Vault?
Romania is known for its vaulting.
(Romania is a vault gymnastics powerhouse!)
- Let's check the actual answer.
- Okay.
We'll see how forgiving we can be with the correct answers.
Anything that sounds like "buch..."
- will be considered correct.
- Yes.
We'll also accept anything that sounds like "rest."
If you got it wrong, please stand up...
- and go to the back of the stage.
- It's so easy.
- Please leave right away.
- From the very first question...
- What a surprise.
- You need to leave.
- All right.
Didn't the Hangeul guy know the answer?
- Bucharest.
- I'll do that for you after this.
- Gosh. I'm proud of you.
- Please sit closer.
- All right. Please sit closer.
- You know...
- It's okay.
- All right.
- When you...
It looks like people have underestimated me.
- He's very confident.
- People should know...
- the capital of Romania.
- Romania.
- Now, - That's impressive.
- give us the next question.
- Let's move on.
- Jang Hoon, good luck.
- Give us the next question.
The next country is...
- Ghana.
- What is the capital of Ghana?
- You have ten seconds.
- Chocolate!
- It is famous for its chocolates.
- Incorrect.
- Be quiet, please.
- I didn't get to do much...
in the previous round.
Ana, Ghana
No. That's incorrect.
"Ana, Ghana" is incorrect.
Let's check the answers.
- Good luck.
- One, two, three.
- Please hold up your answers.
- Everyone wrote something.
- Accra.
- We have Accra.
- Tome.
- One person's answer is different.
Tome.
- If Tome is correct, - Tome.
- he'll be the winner.
- That's right.
- What's the actual answer?
- The answer is...
- How is this possible?
- Accra.
- It's Accra.
- Tome is...
- Back in the day,
- you produced Accra.
- It's Shakra.
- Go and get locked up - This man...
- Ghana and get locked up - Get locked up inside me
- This man right here...
- Yes.
Why did you confidently say that it was Tome?
- I memorized the African capitals.
- Okay.
- You got confused.
- Togo's capital was...
- Tome.
- Good job, though.
- You got confused.
- Thank you for your hard work.
- The two remaining ones are strong.
- They're good.
- I'm impressed.
- One should go to the other side.
- Sit on either side.
- Sit closer to Jang Hoon.
- I think...
- Accra.
this man is extraordinary.
He's answering with confidence.
Isn't he a YouTuber who travels around the world?
- Does he travel around the world?
- No?
- Now, it's a match...
- Who will win?
- between the three contestants.
- Yes.
- Let's find out who they are.
- Let's hear from them.
Where are you from?
My name is Bang Se Hun, and I work as a team lead...
at a stock company in Yeouido.
Have you always studied the capitals?
I like soccer,
so I always memorize the players' hometowns.
- That's right.
- That's incredible.
- I guess doing that helps.
- All right.
- I'm from Seoul.
- My name is Song Jong Hyun.
- Jong Hyun.
- What do you do for a living?
- He's handsome.
I'm a graduate student,
but I'm currently on a leave of absence and looking for a job.
He talked about being a former graduate student.
- Which school did you attend?
- Spain.
- It was in Madrid, Spain.
- We went to the same school.
- Really?
- Yonsei University.
- The way he talks...
- Akaraka chi, akaraka cho.
Your facial expression changed.
His face lit up.
- I saw brightness in his eyes!
- Canada.
(I saw brightness in his eyes.)
- You can take my title.
- He knows.
You can beat me.
- All right.
- He was expressionless earlier.
You can beat me.
- I think he'll take first place.
- Thank you.
- That came out of nowhere.
Let's move on to the next question.
- Let's go.
- Give us the next question.
- Let's go to South America.
- Okay.
- South America?
- The next country is...
(Nervous)
Venezuela.
- It's a hard one.
- Venezuela?
Venezuela. You have ten seconds.
The country name is already confusing,
- so the capital name must be hard.
- It's difficult.
It's Jang Hoon versus the remaining contenders,
Song Jong Hyun and Bang Se Hun.
You should be more knowledgeable to contend against me.
They're writing with confidence.
- I see.
- He's writing a lot.
That means he either has confidence or not.
- Let's check their answers.
- Good luck.
- One, two, three.
- Two, three.
What are the answers?
- One wrote, "Sucre."
- Sucre.
But he also wrote on the top,
- "Mom and Dad, I love you."
Jang Hoon's answer is Ciracas.
- It's Caracas.
- Caracas.
- It isn't Caracas.
- And...
- "I don't know."
If the answer is Caracas,
- Jang Hoon will win.
- It's Caracas.
- Hold on.
- You know,
the match ended too soon.
Jang Hoon, you're incorrect.
Venezuela, Caracas.
- Well...
- What's the answer?
The answer is...
(Did Jang Hoon celebrate prematurely?)
(Will he defend his title as the Capital King?)
(What will be the result?)
(The capital of Venezuela)
- Caracas.
- It's correct.
(The capital of Venezuela is Caracas.)
Thus, the winner of the Capital Quiz is...
- Jang Hoon.
- Jang Hoon is the winner.
(Capital Quiz, Jang Hoon wins)
He's good.
Thank you.
(Capital King defended the pride of Men on a Mission.)
The first one was so difficult.
Thank you for your hard work.
- Thank you for your hard work.
- Thank you.
- There's a contestant...
who brought something. He kept whispering to me,
"I brought presents. May I deliver it to the members?"
- Did he bring presents?
- Yes.
- For me?
- I have one for everyone.
I'll give it to Kyung Hoon first.
I thought it was for me.
No.
- He has one for everyone.
He has one for everyone.
- He brought some gifts for us.
- He could've given it...
- to Jang Hoon first, - Right.
- but he was sullen.
- I became embarrassed.
- There is a drawing.
- There you go.
Please give the contestants...
- another round of applause.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
- All right.
- Thank you.
- I'm a fan of yours.
Thank you.
We didn't see a twist with this match.
- That's right. So far, - Yes.
- only Hee Chul is the strange one.
- Yes.
- May I ask a difficult one?
- What?
- Sure.
Brunei.
Bandar Seri Begawan.
(Impressed)
- What?
- In that case...
Vanuatu.
Port Vila.
He even knows the capital of Vanuatu.
- That's incredible.
- That's incredible. Seriously.
I played basketball with the same mindset.
Let's hurry up and move on.
- Soo Geun. Bahrain.
- Yes?
- Bahrain?
- Yes.
I've never been.
Correct.
- All right.
- Same here.
- It's Manama.
- All right, everyone.
It's Men on a Mission versus 500.
The last match is...
the best output among the games on Men on a Mission,
- Mixed Music Quiz.
- Quiz!
(The best output of the show, Mixed Music Quiz)
(A popular game that was created on Men on a Mission)
(Guessing the answer with the members is fun.)
(And the dance ceremony is another highlight of the game.)
(Many stars have enjoyed the Mixed Music Quiz.)
As you know, you need a partner...
- for the Mixed Music Quiz.
- That's right.
Now, the members will go to the audience...
and choose their partners...
- among 500 people...
- Let's go.
to play the game with.
Go out there.
- Go ahead.
- Knowing many songs...
- gives you an advantage.
- Okay.
- All right.
- You have three minutes.
- Who is good at this game?
- Someone who hasn't participated.
Over there.
(They move to the audience to find their partners.)
Someone who hasn't participated.
Are you really good at it?
Are you? Okay.
(Sang Min chooses his partner first.)
Are you really good at guessing?
I'm bad at the game.
Can you dance well?
Really?
Go!
Do you know many songs?
Really?
Hold on. Do you know many K-pop songs?
(Jang Hoon and Yeong Cheol choose their partners carefully.)
Really?
Ma'am, do you want to try it?
(Shaking her head)
- Please pick me.
- What? Okay.
You can't?
(He retreats.)
(He asks Soo Geun to pick him again.)
(After the desperate attempt)
All right. Come here.
Come here.
(Showing a V ceremony)
Who wants to try it?
(Hee Chul goes to the 2nd floor to meet the transfer students.)
I'll move to the back.
(Kim Hee Chul)
Thank you. All right.
My name is Min Kyung Eun.
- Kim Kyung Eun?
- Min Kyung Eun.
Min Kyung Eun?
Your name is very similar to mine.
(Kyung Hoon meets a partner with a similar name.)
Do you know many songs?
You're sure of it, right?
(He's the last to choose a partner.)
(All the members have chosen their partners!)
Thus, all members have chosen their partners.
- Nice to meet you.
- Hello.
Partners, please introduce yourselves briefly.
Sang Min's partner will go first.
I'm Go Chae Min.
- It's nice to meet you.
- Sure is.
Your hair looks fancy.
- Are you in the beauty industry?
- It's fancy.
I enjoy getting my hair dyed.
- I've been doing it a lot recently.
- I see.
I'm from Eunpyeong-gu. My name is Shim Gi Bo.
- It's nice to meet you.
All right. This man.
Yes. Who are you?
Hello, I'm a transfer student...
from Graduated from Soo Geun's School High.
I'm Shin Seung Ryeol. It's nice to meet you.
Which school?
I majored in recreation...
- at the Seoil University.
- Recreation.
I applied to that university only because of Soo Geun...
and got in. That was how I became a graduate.
- He's got talent. Okay, who's next?
- Over here.
Hello, I use the same character as Min Kyung Hoon.
I'm Min Kyung Eun.
- She's his sister.
- She must be from his family.
- Wait. Min Kyung Eun?
- Min is an uncommon last name.
Why didn't you come to Kyung Hoon's wedding?
I wasn't invited.
- Next.
- But she's your relative.
Hello, I'm a transfer student from Tall like Jang Hoon High.
I'm Chae Yeon Hwa.
How tall are you?
I'm 179cm tall.
- You're lying. Get up.
- You're...
My goodness.
(He's done with fact-checking.)
- I mean...
- She was right.
What do you do for a living?
I'm studying in the modeling department.
- You'll be Korea's best model.
- Good luck.
Who's next?
Hello, I'm a university student majoring in K-pop.
Hold on.
- She's formidable.
- No way.
- Seriously.
- She's majoring in K-pop?
- I'm from the Here to Conquer High.
- No.
- I'm Kim Ji Yun.
- My goodness.
- He chose a good partner.
- That's incredible.
- We get old songs as well.
- That's right.
- Not just new songs.
- I chose my partner to win.
- Who are you?
- I'm determined to win.
I'm from Pyeongtaek.
My name is Kwon Hyeok In.
It doesn't look like you chose your partner to win.
You said you knew a lot of the songs, right?
- What is it?
- All right. We'll win.
- Now, give us the first question.
- Hold on.
- Why are they sitting here?
- Hello.
We're from Met After a While Through Men on a Mission High.
- It has been a while.
- Yes. It's so nice.
- It's so nice.
- Then Hye Lyun and Teuk...
- will participate as a team.
- Okay.
For the Mixed Music Quiz, yell out, "Let me answer."
One must give the song title and artist for the melody,
and the other must give the song title and artist...
- for the lyrics.
- Okay.
- The song title and artist.
- Give them both, okay?
- Here comes the first question.
- Let's help each other.
Let's hear it.
Before leaving, you said to me
You expect too much
(Pricking up his ears)
From me
There is only thing
That I want from you
- Sweet and...
- Let me answer.
- What's the answer?
- "Loveable" by Kim Jong Kook.
- Next.
- "No. 1" by BoA.
- Incorrect.
- Recreation.
- Ho Dong.
- Let me answer.
- Soo Geun was faster.
- Recreation.
- How about me?
- What's the answer?
"Loveable" by Kim Jong Kook.
- Next.
- "Bam Yang Gang" by BIBI.
Correct.
We had the answer.
What?
You need to dance.
(His hip movements make your jaw drop.)
Go for it!
He's so happy.
I love you
- Good job.
Well done.
He's full of energy.
- Well done.
- I want to watch him dance again.
Give us some bonus points.
All right.
Thank goodness he got picked.
He doesn't need to answer more questions. He's done.
He's done. He did a great job.
That was incredible.
- Everyone.
- It was amazing.
- Here comes the next question.
- Congratulations.
- The melody is easy, but...
- Music, please.
- You have so much talent.
Someday you'll be able
To live without me
I had no response
To your cold words of parting
I only had tears, my dear
I couldn't look at you
- With each passing day - Let me answer.
- What's the answer?
- "Dumb Dumb" by Red Velvet.
- Next. One, two, three.
- She's really good.
- Incorrect. Ho Dong.
- Ho Dong.
It's Team Ho Dong's turn.
What's the answer?
- The lyrics...
- One,
- two...
- "Dumb Dumb" by Red Velvet.
Next. One...
- Incorrect.
- Let me answer.
What's the answer?
- Recreation.
- What's the answer?
- "Dumb Dumb" by Red Velvet.
- Next.
- I don't know.
For goodness' sake.
- Let me answer.
- What's the answer?
- "Dumb Dumb" by Red Velvet.
- Next.
- What?
- What are you doing?
Why are you guys fighting?
- Hye Lyun.
- "Dumb Dumb" by Red Velvet.
- Next.
- I said it first.
- No way.
- I said it 1st.
Everyone is saying, "Dumb Dumb" by Red Velvet.
I can't play this game with him.
- A singer should know more songs.
- I said Red Velvet first.
One more time.
- What's the answer?
- What was that song?
With each passing day, will I get used to this?
What was that song?
- Let's hear it once more.
- Let me answer.
- What's the answer?
- For goodness' sake.
"Day by Day" by As One.
- Next.
- "Dumb Dumb" by Red Velvet.
- Let me answer.
- Yes.
- "Day by Day" by Tashannie.
- "Dumb Dumb" by Red Velvet.
- Correct.
- My goodness.
It was Tashannie.
What?
It's strange.
- It's strange. What's happening?
- You're doing well.
(He suddenly shows his behind.)
Was he influenced by Sang Min?
(This way and that)
- Where is he going?
- It's strange.
(He suddenly lies down.)
- He's flexible.
- Correct.
- Right. It was "Day by Day."
- His dance moves were off.
It was my first time seeing someone ignore the music while dancing.
I thought he would do B-boying.
Your hair looks like a duster I have at home.
- I wondered if I had brought it.
- I see.
- It was something else.
- I have a question.
You have unique looks.
Are you an aspiring celebrity?
- To be honest, at the age of 1...
- The age of 1?
- It happened at the age of 1.
I was on "High Kick!" as a baby.
I was Jun.
- Really?
- I was that baby.
- Shinji...
- I played Shinji's son.
- I was on a documentary...
- Shinji's son.
a few years ago.
- Do you remember that time?
- No.
- Hey, what was that?
- I don't remember.
- What are you doing?
- I mean...
Sit down.
- "Dumb Dumb" by Red Velvet.
- "Dumb Dumb." I got it.
Here comes the next question.
Let's hear it.
I couldn't ask you
To join me
- For my unsteady future - I know the melody.
Because I felt bad
If you come back to me
I swear
- That I won't leave you alone - I know the melody.
When you close your eyes
In my arms
- I'll protect you always - What?
I'll wait
- I have no idea.
- I know the lyrics.
- That's the song.
- "I'll wait?"
- The lyrics...
- I just need to know the melody!
I just need to know the melody!
- "I'll wait."
- I know the difficult part.
- Do you know the lyrics?
- I know the lyrics.
Just do the melody.
- Recreation.
- What's the answer?
"Again" by 2PM.
- Next. One, - No!
- two, three. Incorrect.
- I don't know.
- Let's hear it again.
- Isn't it "Again and Again?"
- I don't know the title.
- I
- Just that one.
- Couldn't ask you
- The melody...
- I just need to know the melody.
For my unsteady future
Because I felt bad
If you come back to me
- I swear - What are those lyrics?
- I just need to know the melody.
- That I won't leave
- You alone - Let me answer.
- What's the answer?
- "I'll Be Back" by 2PM.
- One, two...
- "To You" by Shin Hae Chul.
- Recreation.
- Incorrect.
- Recreation. "I'll Be Back" by 2PM.
- Next.
Shin Hae Chul.
- You are deep inside my heart - I'm sorry.
- Correct.
- Yes!
Let's go!
(Here comes the solo dance that'll shock everyone!)
Jump!
That's good.
(Flapping)
(It's an incredible sight.)
My goodness.
- He's good until the end.
- Gosh.
- You're good.
- Well done.
- All right.
- He was like a fresh-caught fish.
All right.
He was like a fresh-caught fish.
- I'm moved by your passion.
- I'm sorry,
but why did you intimidate my partner? He can't answer now.
- Everyone.
- It was too intense.
- You know what?
- He's the main character.
His dance made everyone laugh,
- except for one person.
- Who?
Jun couldn't laugh.
He doesn't know what he'll do if he correctly answers...
- another question.
- Thank goodness I picked him.
That was incredible.
The Fresh Fish Dance was new.
He should work harder because he's with his senior.
- That's right.
- That was great.
They currently have 20 points.
- Right.
- If they answer one more question,
- they'll win.
- One more question.
Let's end this game.
Even when I see you every day
I fall for you even more
Two or three times
- I've pinched my cheek - Let me answer.
- What's the answer?
- "Eve's Warning" by Park Mi Kyung.
- Next. One, two, three.
- Why'd you say that first?
- two, three.
- Hey!
(Melody: "Eve's Warning" by Park Mi Kyung)
- Recreation.
- My goodness.
- What's the answer?
- "A Daily Song" by Hwang Chi Yeul.
- Next.
- One...
- "Eve's Warning" by Park Mi Kyung.
- Incorrect.
- What?
- Let me answer.
- What's the answer?
"Teddy Bear" by STAYC.
- Next. One, two...
- "Eve's Warning" by Park Mi Kyung.
- Incorrect.
- It's incorrect.
You answered confidently.
- I thought it was correct.
- Since you guys are struggling,
- I'll sing further.
- Okay.
- Music, please.
- It's a song by a girl group.
You need to figure it out. We have no idea.
Even when I see you every day
I fall for you even more
Two or three times
I've pinched my cheek
I feel like
I'm dreaming
Thinking about you
Makes me smile, Mr. Chu
- Let me answer!
- All right.
(Speaking nonsense)
- Everyone.
- Leeteuk said it first.
- No.
- Come on.
No. Hee Chul said it first.
- Hee Chul. What's the answer?
- Hee Chul, let's go.
"Mr. Chu" by Apink.
- Next.
- "Eve's Warning" by Park Mi Kyung.
- Correct.
- Show us!
Show us!
- Let's go.
- Show us!
Show us!
Show us! Come on!
(Dancing)
There you go!
- That's it.
- Come on!
Correct.
Well done.
That's too bad. I'm curious.
- You know.
- It was a hard one.
- Yes?
- When Shin Dong said, "Mr. Chu,"
- Yes.
I thought there was an earthquake.
I was very surprised too.
Mr. Chu
("Mr. Chu" brought on an earthquake.)
I prepared the songs the members would know well...
for the next question.
Music, please.
Like a paint
"A paint."
The sky was blue
But it already turned black
- Ho Dong.
- Ho Dong, what's the answer?
- He just goes off on his own.
- Did you figure it out?
One, two, three.
- "I'm a Firefly..."
- "Firefly" by Shin Hyung Won.
Next. One...
- He just goes off on his own.
- Come on!
- Stop it!
- Let us go next.
- Let me answer.
- What's the answer?
- "Firefly."
Come on.
- "Firefly" by Shin Hyung Won.
- Yes.
Incorrect.
"Firefly."
It must be a modern song.
The lyrics contain "A paint."
- Shall I sing it once more?
- Like a paint?
- Music, please.
- "A paint."
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
"A paint."
(Let's hear it again.)
(They can't think of the answer.)
- But it already turned black - Focus on the lyrics.
- My emotions deepen - "My emotions deepen?"
I gotta tell you
- "I gotta tell you?"
- This is a strange feeling - "This?"
Only the two of us can feel
(The more they listen, they more confused they become.)
But it's too late
I'm disappointed
- What a melody.
- It's a nice song.
- It's already 12am - Let me answer.
- What's the answer?
- Let me answer.
- "Gotta Go" by Chungha.
- Next.
- "Firefly" by Shin Hyung Won.
Correct.
(Watch me! This is the class of the K-pop department.)
Thank goodness she got to do the dance ceremony.
Good.
- Thank goodness.
What?
How does she know the dance so well?
She's dancing to the rhythm.
- She's good.
- What?
Thank goodness she answered correctly.
(Her performance is 99.99 percent in sync.)
(She will obviously win points in the K-pop department.)
- She's really good.
- Good job.
- We need to get one too.
- She gyrated her hips so well.
She gyrated her hips so well.
- Shin Dong, I think...
- Thank goodness she danced.
people who don't get to dance...
- will get sick.
- Seriously.
If they don't answer correctly,
- they won't get to dance.
- Right.
Why don't we let people dance if they want to?
We should do that.
- They can't do it so easily.
- That's right.
- Then they won't appreciate it.
- They need to answer correctly.
We can't let them do it without answering correctly.
Yeong Cheol went out to dance to "Firefly." Right?
- They didn't play "Firefly."
- It would have been perfect.
Team Soo Geun will win if they get...
- one more question, right?
- The game will end.
That's right. They just need to get one more question.
Everyone, the next question...
can be a bit hard. Please listen carefully.
- I prefer a difficult question.
- Music, please.
However, when I open my eyes alone
Early in the morning and realize
That you aren't here by my side
Tears fall from my eyes
Did nothing change?
Do you still have...
- Hee Chul!
- Yeong Cheol!
- Yeong Cheol was faster.
- Hee Chul!
- Leeteuk!
- Yeong Cheol was faster.
- What's the answer?
- We could've done it.
- One...
- "Good Man" by Toy.
- Next. One, two...
- Ho Dong.
- Incorrect.
- Leeteuk.
- Here.
- Ho Dong.
- Mister.
- "Why Calling" by Diva.
- Next. One...
- "Still Beautiful" by Toy.
- That's right.
- Correct.
- Toy.
- It's "Still Beautiful."
Let's go!
(He gets an item from Mr. Fresh Fish!)
(Let's dance.)
(Come on out.)
(Transfer students, let's dance together.)
The four partners came out.
- Come on out.
- The four partners came out.
- They're good.
- What's up with them?
What's up with them?
- Hold on.
- Correct.
- Shin Dong.
- Yes?
They know each other, right?
- No.
- I bet they came together.
- I mean...
- Did you see him just now?
- Yes, I did.
- Wasn't he impressive?
What happened to the Jun we know?
He was one year old.
- He was always lying down.
- Let's begin.
Here comes the next question.
Music, please.
Oh, my, I can't believe it
How is this my life?
I never get lucky
(The melody sounds familiar.)
An amazing girlfriend
- I know the melody.
- Who looks dazzling in my eyes?
- Do you recognize the melody?
- Everything in the world
- I'll end it here.
- My goodness.
I recognize the melody, but the lyrics are hard.
- What's the song title?
- For goodness' sake.
Seriously. Because of that note...
"An amazing girlfriend." That's the part all of us know.
- That's right.
- I'm giving you guys a chance.
- "An amazing girlfriend."
If no one answers in three seconds...
- Three. What's the answer?
- "Call Me Baby" by EXO.
Next. One, two, three.
- The lyrics.
- EXO?
An amazing girlfriend
- Who looks dazzling in my eyes?
- "An amazing girlfriend?"
An amazing girlfriend
- Who looks dazzling in my eyes?
- "An amazing girlfriend?"
- "An amazing..."
- What?
- Is that it?
- You started out well...
- and sang a different melody.
- Right?
- Let me answer. DJ DOC.
- That's it.
- One, two...
- "Amazing Woman for Me."
- Incorrect.
- Hee Chul.
- Go ahead.
- "Call Me Baby" by EXO.
- Next.
- "Murphy's Law" by DJ DOC.
- It's correct.
Correct.
Let's take the stage.
(Pay attention, everyone! Here comes a K-pop lesson!)
(A mysterious person joins the K-pop lesson.)
(A collaboration of the weird and fantastic partners)
It was "Murphy's Law."
- That's right.
- "Murphy's Law."
You know, the lyrics belonged to "Murphy's Law."
- But the melody was too intense.
- That was amazing.
Right? The melody was too intense.
The melody was so intense that I couldn't think of anything.
Only Team Soo Geun and Team Hee Chul...
- have one question to go.
- Right.
So, only the two teams...
- will have a final round.
- Okay.
- I want to answer correctly too.
- Yes.
Between the two teams, which one will win?
We need to win because they've shown something.
We're here to win in the Mixed Music Quiz.
Will Hee Chul make up for his poor performance...
with Guess the Song in One Second?
Give us the question.
My heart is full of tears because I miss you today
- I know this song.
- Soo Geun knows this.
You've visited me thousands of times
(The two teams think carefully.)
I shout out your name
But you don't give me
- An answer, why don't you know - I recognize the melody.
- That I'm waiting?
- What?
- Let's end it here.
- Just do the lyrics.
- Hee Chul.
- What's the answer?
- "Joy" by Jung Su Ra.
- Next.
"Don't You Know" by ZO ZAZZ.
- Correct.
- Yes.
- Hee Chul did it.
He did it.
Everyone, take the stage.
Dance together.
(They become one through dance.)
Wrap it up.
(The MVP of the day, Mr. Fresh Fish wraps up the performance.)
Thank you.
- That was just...
- It was the best.
Thus, the winner of Mixed Music Quiz is...
- Team Hee Chul.
- Okay.
(Team Hee Chul and Hyuk In)
(Next week)
(The festival of the 500th episode isn't over yet.)
(The members become nervous before taking the stage.)
(They practiced for 2 months to make the party grand!)
(Jang Hoon and Soo Geun, 40cm)
(Let us stay by the viewers' side)
(Sang Min, Kyung Hoon, and Hee Chul, So Much Fun)
(The dance performance takes everyone back to the past.)
(The legendary dance duo is back.)
(Ho Dong and Shin Dong, Dongdongshinki)
(The high-note hunter, Kim Yeong Cheol)
(His solo career begins to shine.)
(Special guest, Lee Chan Won)
(No party is complete without a national singer.)
(Men Match 500)
(They team up with their fans for the group competition.)
(Hold on to victory at all costs.)
(500 times the pressure, 500 times the fierceness)
(The lousy members show their lousiness before the fans.)
(They put everything on the line for the competition.)
(Why are you guys so good at this?)
(What will be the result of the nerve-racking competition...)
(of the 500 fans and the members?)
(The members perform to pay back for the love...)
(they've received over the course of 10 years.)
(They put a smile of hope on the viewers' faces.)
(They visited the viewers on 500 Saturday nights.)
(The unfinished story is coming soon.)
(Men on a Mission)