(One autumn day with pretty autumn leaves around the school)
- Oh, my.
- Let's go in.
- Let's go.
- Hey, Kyung Hoon.
- Kyung Hoon... Gosh, who is he?
- Who is he?
- Why are you standing there?
- Don't mistake me for him.
- I'm still young.
- You thought he was me, right?
- Mimi Minu is the director?
- Come on. Kyung Hoon is here.
- Is Mimi Minu the director?
- Hey, does that mean...
that Shin Dong and Hee Chul will be absent again?
- Oh, I guess that's right.
- Right. They're on a concert tour.
Class president, are they absent? Or were they fired?
- I bet they got fired.
- Were they fired?
- This is nice.
- Oh, my. This is really...
Since Mimi Minu is here, our classroom...
Hot mamas, our dear queens.
(Hot mamas, our dear queens.)
- Hi!
- Oh, they're here.
- Let's go!
- Oh, my. South America...
- What are you guys doing?
- We were worried about you.
I know, right? I haven't seen you in a long time.
- It's been a really long time.
- Exactly.
- It's been almost a month.
- One month.
- Maybe because it's been a while...
- Why is Jong Shin sitting there?
- Exactly.
- I thought I was on "Sing Again."
- We said the same thing last week.
- Did you say that last week?
- We said that last week.
- Yes, we did.
- Good job.
- He was on "No Back Tak Jae Hoon."
- Everyone.
Settle down, everyone.
I heard that we started to make a class newspaper last week.
MIYEON, who's a member of the newspaper club, came...
- and helped us make one.
- Call MIYEON here.
- Not only about us...
- She came last week,
- and we made a class newspaper.
- I see.
Share what's new with you.
Even trivial things will do.
There was something that surprised me.
- MIYEON came on the show recently.
- Yes, she did.
Before shooting that episode,
MIYEON shot a video for my YouTube channel.
(MIYEON appeared in a video on Mimi Minu's YouTube channel.)
(The crazy combination of Mimi Minu and MIYEON)
Our challenge video will have been uploaded before this airs.
(They also made a "Say My Name" challenge video.)
How was her new song?
MIYEON used to sing cheerful songs.
But her new song has a dark, gloomy vibe.
What's the song title?
"Say My Name" is the title track.
- "Say My Name."
- Oh, that's correct.
- "Say My Name?"
- That's right.
- He remembered it.
- I remembered it accurately.
- That was close, right?
- Yes, that was close.
We should write that Mimi Minu said...
that MIYEON's new song was dreary.
- No, that's not right.
- He said MIYEON's new song...
- was gloomy.
- Are you really writing that?
"Mimi Minu Says MIYEON's New Song Is Not Cheerful."
- "MIYEON's Song Is Gloomy."
- "Gloomy."
- Hey, this is...
- A news article...
- doesn't have to be like that.
- I've never heard "gloomy."
- Oh, "Rose."
- I have a story to tell.
- A few days ago, - Yes?
I went to the Philippines to shoot my basketball show.
Right. The game was held at the SM Mall of Asia Arena.
- A sports arena in the Philippines.
- Yes, that's right.
I found out something very surprising.
- Men on a Mission...
- We didn't go on the show.
- is on OTT in the Philippines...
- Okay.
with English subtitles.
Really?
- So I... Can you guys...
- It's not on the Korean platform.
- Hold on.
- I heard it was aired in Japan.
- Yes, it's aired in Japan too.
- In Japan as well.
Only a few of Korean variety shows are on the Philippines' OTT.
And the translated version of Men on a Mission is streamed...
in the Philippines.
Let's write this. "Seo Jang Hoon Becomes..."
- No, wait. Hold on.
- "Popular in the Philippines."
- No, that's not what I mean.
- That's random.
"Seo Jang Hoon Is As Popular As Sandara Park in the Philippines."
- Okay.
- No, it's not like that.
- Everyone, hear me out.
- "As Popular As Pacquiao."
- "Seo Jang Hoon Has..."
- Pacquiao came on the show before.
- Oh, that's right.
- "Fighting Match against Pacquiao."
- I...
- My gosh.
- "In the Philippines, Jang Hoon..."
- Hear me out.
- "Challenges Pacquiao To Match."
- I...
- He asked us to hear him out.
- Don't write anything yet.
- He asked not to write it down.
- Don't write it yet.
"Seo Jang Hoon Has Fighting Match against Pacquiao."
- No, that's not true.
- "Picky Seo Jang Hoon..."
"Starts Learning Pigalog."
(Unexpected news, "Picky Jang Hoon Starts Learning Tagalog")
He said "Pigalog," not "Tagalog."
Did you say "Pigalog?"
- Anyway, I found that out, - He started learning Tagalog?
- and that surprised me.
- Right.
Men on a Mission is streamed in the Philippines...
- Amid popular acclaim.
- amid popular acclaim.
- I'm really grateful.
- The viewers in the Philippines,
- Put it in the end.
- thank you.
- And Soo Geun.
- I just remembered a story to tell.
We've been holding a 20th anniversary concert tour.
To celebrate the 20th anniversary of Super Junior,
I wanted to do something to repay our fans for their support.
So I secretly made a donation to help cancer patients.
- But...
- Secretly?
But I don't want it to be a secret, so I'm sharing the news.
- What's that?
- That's so great of you.
- Indeed.
- What's that?
- He donated to cancer patients.
- "Kim Hee Chul..."
"Kim Hee Chul Openly Makes Donation."
- Exactly.
- It's not a secret anymore.
- I mean, it's really great of him.
- But he said...
I wrote that I had made a donation and bragged about it.
- It's still a great thing to do.
- Right. It's a good deed.
I counted the number of episodes of our show.
This is our 506th episode.
- Yes, it's been that long.
- That's amazing.
To tell you the truth, in the past 506 weeks,
I had naengmyeon every single week.
- What did you say?
- "Kang Ho Dong..."
- For 506 weeks, - "Kang Ho Dong..."
- I ate Pyongyang naengmyeon.
- Unbelievable.
"Kang Ho Dong Is from Pyongyang."
- Hang on.
- "Love for Pyongyang naengmyeon."
- "Turns Out To Be from Pyongyang."
- He was born in Pyongyang.
- For 506 weeks...
- We should check it out.
Don't you think he should get into the Guinness World Records?
- It's really unbelievable.
- "Kang Ho Dong..."
- He ate it for 506 weeks.
- He could set a world record.
"Kang Ho Dong Has Pyongyang Naengmyeon for 506 Weeks,"
"Will He Move to Pyongyang?"
I recently saw Soo Geun in a video.
- It was a teaser.
- "Three Idiots in Kenya."
- Yes, I saw him in the teaser.
- It's on OTT.
- He gave a giraffe physical touch.
- That's right.
- "He Gives Giraffe Physical Touch."
- On that day..
- "Giraffe..."
- "Their Tongues Touch."
I pecked a giraffe,
and that evening, the giraffe came into my room.
"Soo Geun Dyes His Hair with Squid Ink."
- "Soo Geun Sleeps with Giraffe."
- Write that he dyed his hair.
"Giraffe Ten Times Taller Than Soo Geun."
- Because he dyed his hair...
- All right.
- "Dyes His Hair with Squid Ink..."
- Jang Hoon likes the joke.
"And with Giraffe..."
- "First Night with Giraffe."
- "Soo Geun Kisses Giraffe."
"Soo Geun Turns Out To Be Ten Times Shorter Than Giraffe."
"Soo Geun Meets Giraffe Secretly."
"With Giraffe..."
("Lee Soo Geun Says He Becomes Interested in Anything Tall")
This is fun.
So he likes tall people.
I renewed my contract with my agency.
- What? Really?
- It's been almost ten years...
- "The Loyal Min Kyung Hoon?"
- since I started working with them.
- Write something like that.
- Apparently, you are...
the only active celebrity at your agency.
That's why I keep renewing my contract.
"Kyung Hoon Does Men on a Mission for Ten Years..."
"And Works with Same Agency for Ten Years."
That's true.
- Can't we get these articles...
- It's very loyal of him.
published in JoongAng Ilbo?
I hope we can get them published in JoongAng Ilbo.
- That'd be great.
- Right.
It'd be helpful for us even if only a few of them get published.
- I'll change the expression.
- Aren't they back?
Hey, guys.
Write some articles about us too.
- SUNMI!
- It's good to see you again.
- Hello.
- You're here, Chan Won.
Song Min Jun!
We met him when we shot the 500th episode.
- He came to celebrate with us.
- SUNMI's hair color is elegant now.
He came on the show to congratulate us.
- Yes, for the 500th episode.
- We thank you for that.
Which school did you guys transfer from?
- We are...
- Yes.
from Doing Fine As Solo Artists High School.
I'm SUNMI. I made my comeback as a virgin ghost.
- And?
- It must be her title track.
I contributed a little to getting the highest ratings...
in Men on a Mission history. I'm Chan Won.
Chan Won!
I'm the nobleman-like trot singer Min Jun. It's nice to meet you.
Min Jun!
(Welcome, all of you!)
SUNMI made her comeback as a virgin ghost?
- It must be her new song.
- A virgin ghost?
- Yes, I'm a virgin ghost.
- Oh, my.
SUNMI, I haven't seen you in a really long time.
I missed you.
- How long has it been?
- You're lying.
- Stop lying.
- I mean it. I missed him.
How much did you miss Ho Dong?
- I really missed him.
- When did you last meet him?
- I think she means it.
- It's because...
- It's been about four years.
- Four or five years?
- It's been four or five years.
- That long?
(SUNMI, the most beautiful one of all)
(SUNMI performed "Pporappippam" spreading beauty 5 years ago.)
By the way, SUNMI...
Shin Dong wasn't here when you came on the show, right?
I think I appeared only in Part Two when she came on the show.
She's never been here since I started being in Part One.
- Here's why I said that.
- That's right.
I saw a photo of them...
and found out that they were trained in the same period of time.
- That's true.
- We auditioned in the same year.
- For what agency? SM Entertainment?
- SM Entertainment.
One of the two of them...
was going to be the last member to join Super Junior.
And sadly, Shin Dong was chosen.
- She could've debuted then.
- She wasn't chosen as a member?
- That's right.
- I'm sorry to SUNMI.
I came in first place at the audition.
So I was hired...
- and debuted.
- That's right.
As for SUNMI, the casting team of JYP Entertainment...
- hired her.
- That's right.
- Had SUNMI came in first place, - Why...
would SUNMI have become a member of Super Junior...
and would Shin Dong have...
- joined Wonder Girls?
- That's right.
My gosh. What a shame.
- That would've been interesting.
- Exactly.
I wonder why they made that decision.
- At the time...
- You mean, SM Entertainment?
While Shin Dong and I were preparing for the audition...
There was a burger place in the neighborhood, remember?
- McDonalds.
- You remember that?
- Of course. We went there together.
- What?
- Back then, - You mean, 20 years ago?
SUNMI was... Were you in 6th or 7th grade?
- I was in sixth grade.
- Seventh grade?
She was in sixth grade,
- and I was 20.
- She was so young.
Since I was the oldest trainee,
I walked the younger trainees to the subway station.
That's right.
There were some other trainees other than SUNMI.
We were hungry on our way, so we went to the burger place.
- We ate burgers there.
- That's nice of you.
- That's really nice.
- Were they hungry too?
- Or were you the hungry one?
- That's a heartwarming story.
I'm sure I was the one who was hungry since I suggested the idea.
- So Shin Dong placed first?
- He's so nice.
Exactly. Shin Dong placed first at the audition.
- He was chosen as the funniest one.
- That's right.
- But I still don't understand...
- That makes sense.
- I mean...
- Why Shin Dong placed first?
His performance wasn't funny enough to place first.
- You placed first by being funny?
- What kind of performance was it?
- Yes.
- I'll explain to you.
There were several categories.
There were categories of appearance, singing,
and dancing as well. And I applied...
- for the dancing category.
- That's right.
But the people at the agency said...
that I would be a better fit for the funny category...
and advised me to apply for that category.
- Tin Tin Five was active then.
- They were popular back then.
The agency was planning to form the next Tin Tin Five.
There was such a rumor.
But that plan fell through, and I joined Super Junior.
But that's not important. Right now, we...
- But Shin Dong was telling us...
- Why...
- Why is it not important?
- So you were chosen.
- Why?
- It's about SUNMI, not you.
- So you placed first, right?
- Yes, that's right.
The point is that they didn't pick SUNMI.
- That's right.
- SUNMI was very young back then,
and she was shy.
- That's true.
- Right. I have no doubt.
- Shin Dong, seriously...
- But that's not important.
- Right.
- Why is it not important?
- He said it wasn't important.
- It's not the time...
- I think this will be edited out.
- for us to talk about it.
- I agree.
We all owe Chan Won the biggest apology.
- Why?
We're supposed to be too ashamed to see him.
- We should all lower our heads.
- Why?
- Why are you sorry to me?
- We should lower our heads?
- Chan Won came on the show...
- to celebrate the 500th episode.
- Yes.
(Chan Won came as a special guest for the 500th episode.)
(He celebrated the 500th episode by performing "Jinttobaegi.")
He performed a song and did an interview.
- But his interview was edited out.
- Really?
It was because of Yeong Cheol.
- I'm sorry.
- He gave a touching performance...
- which was totally unexpected.
- I performed well.
(Yeong Cheol performed "Golden," which was unexpectedly touching.)
(Even Ho Dong got teary.)
- I tried too hard...
- He performed unnecessarily well.
- He made Chan Won...
- He sang well, indeed.
That part where he was interviewed was edited out.
- The whole part was edited out?
- We must have the footage.
My interview was edited out.
Moreover, my performance was also edited out after the first verse.
- What?
- My whole performance was aired.
- - You must've been...
- The whole performance.
- surprised to find out about it...
- The interview wasn't aired.
while watching the episode on TV.
- I was surprised.
- That day...
- I can't believe they cut it out.
- It was indeed surprising.
- That's it.
- I guess we have the footage.
- There wasn't enough time left.
- Oh, they have the footage.
(I realized that Men on a Mission is still loved...)
(by many people.)
(I'd like to congratulate all of you.)
(I believe the show has been gaining so much love...)
(because the cast members maintained their chemistry.)
(Also, they never lose the beginner's mindset.)
(Chan Won showed his affection for Men on a Mission.)
(It's good that we got to see the important interview.)
My, thank you, Chan Won.
So that interview wasn't aired.
- Because of Yeong Cheol.
- He made a lot of good comments.
You can see that he wasn't here...
just as a guest singer.
You can feel his genuine love for our show.
I love all of the cast members,
but one of them is my role model.
He changed my life. He's Ho Dong.
(Ho Dong is the member who changed Chan Won's life.)
- Really? What did he do for you?
- I'm flattered.
- That's...
- That's not important.
That's not important?
- It is important!
- It's not important.
- How did he change your life?
- Why does that matter?
- Take your time to tell us.
- It's an important story.
- That's not important.
- Let's really focus on his story.
- What TV shows changed your life?
- He changed someone else's life.
- Let's focus on it.
- Hey, Chan Won.
- Yes?
- It doesn't matter. What are...
- Okay.
- the two life-changing shows?
- Let's focus on listening to him.
- What shows changed your life?
- I'm curious about it.
There have been two TV shows...
- that changed my life.
- What are those?
First, as you all must know,
- "Mister Trot."
- Right.
And the other one is...
"Star King" where I appeared...
- about 20 years ago.
- Oh, my goodness.
Come on. That's not important. The third show...
("Star King" is not important.)
- We...
- "Star King..."
- I went on the show three times.
- He said it didn't matter.
- It was an honor to get a chance...
- Really?
- to work with Ho Dong three times.
- I didn't know that.
(Chan Won appeared on "Star King" three times as a trot prodigy.)
- He came on the show as a prodigy.
- As a prodigy?
I'll tell you how much it affected my life.
Because of my loyalty to "Star King,"
I never watched "Infinite Challenge" on time.
- The shows aired at the same time.
- Yes, at the same time.
I watched "Star King" on time every Saturday.
For how long?
Until "Star King" ended airing.
- But I...
- You were there as a prodigy.
- Ho Dong must've complimented you.
- Yes.
SUNMI, you've been on the show...
- as a guest, haven't you?
- Of course, sir.
- No, I mean...
- See?
- I mean, of course.
- We all were traumatized.
- She spoke formally right away.
- The thought of "Star King..."
makes us shudder.
It makes her shudder.
Does it mean she's terrified?
- It makes her shudder.
- Even now?
- Even now.
- It was recorded every Monday.
The shoot started at noon on Mondays.
But I heard that one of our guests suffered damage...
because of Yeong Cheol, not Ho Dong.
- What?
- One of them?
- Because of Yeong Cheol?
- It must be SUNMI.
It's not me.
- I'm the one who suffered damage.
- Why?
- I suffered serious damage.
- What happened?
- It must've been financial damage.
- He must know.
- The time has come.
- He'll finally be destroyed.
It's about time we heard such a story.
- Right.
- It's about time?
Both Yeong Cheol and I appeared on...
- "The King of Active Trot Singers."
- Gosh, not again.
- I wish I hadn't been on that show.
- He was on the show as a comedian.
Yeong Cheol performed right before me.
I was going to perform after his performance.
- Singing after a comedian is hard.
- Yeong Cheol...
- That's funny.
- He got the lowest score.
- Yeong Cheol did?
- He got the lowest score ever.
Yeong Cheol got the lowest score.
- So he became genuinely upset.
- He got some points?
- My gosh.
- After his performance,
he never pressed the button.
My gosh. I can't believe him.
He went on a power trip.
The other singers evaluated one another.
The contestants cast a vote for one another.
It was called the peer evaluation round.
Yeong Cheol acts quite timid on Men on a Mission, right?
- He's like a thug on other shows.
- He's so confident on other shows.
He uses his work experience in the TV industry as a weapon...
Min Jun, you were right. I was upset.
- He rarely pressed the button...
- Let me explain.
I got 16 votes.
- It broke me mentally.
- Weren't you supposed...
to be grateful toward those 16 people?
- You got more votes than I thought.
- Gosh, come on.
- Sixteen votes are a lot.
- No, sixteen votes...
- I was 1 of those 16 people.
- Min Jun...
- Oh, you pressed the button?
- I pressed the button.
- I even danced.
- You pressed the button?
- I pressed the button.
- He pressed it.
Min Jun, how many votes did you get?
I got 24 votes.
- You got many votes.
- Yeong Cheol and I...
were in the group that could be eliminated.
- That's right.
- You could be eliminated?
Without knowing how I felt, Yeong Cheol came to me and said,
"Hey, how about we work as a group called Eliminated Boys?"
My gosh. It's getting even worse.
- He was absolutely overbearing...
- It'd be a group with four members.
- Had Min Jung gained 25 votes, - There were 4 of us.
not 24 votes, he wouldn't have been...
- in the bottom four.
- That's right.
- Really?
- That's an important point.
- Yeong Cheol is at fault.
- Can we please stop inviting...
- His work life has been too smooth.
those who appeared on "The King of Active Trot Singers?"
- I don't want them on this show.
- I heard Hwanhee came here too.
Yes, Hwanhee came here too. I want no one from the show to come.
- So many people suffered damage.
- Today,
- we'll evaluate you fairly.
- Great.
- So bring me your transfer form.
- Okay.
We'll press the button.
We'll evaluate them properly.
- Today, I will submit...
- We can't just skip it.
- our transfer form.
- What changed your life was...
"Mean Person."
- One, two, three, four.
- Pull it closely.
(Are you leaving me when I still love you?)
What kind of person?
(You're a mean person)
(Soo Geun and Chan Won showed the textbook trot-comedy skit.)
(They brought the memory back after 5 years.)
- It was almost six years ago.
- Maybe I have lingering feelings
- Chan Won played along with you.
- Exactly.
Chan Won is great.
The transfer form to Men on a Mission.
Names, SUNMI, Lee Chan Won, and Song Min Jun.
- It's good to see you guys.
- Welcome!
I was very surprised.
The first thing to check out is their peer relations.
They wrote "Wonderful."
- That's SUNMI...
- Wonderful
- "Dad's Youth?"
- It's Wonder Girls' fan club name.
- Dad's youth
- Oh, Wonder Girls' fan club?
- Wonderful
Mimi Minu knows it correctly.
- It's Wonder Girls' fan club name.
- That's correct.
- Mimi Minu, were you perhaps...
- He must've been a member of it.
I was a big fan of Wonder Girls' when I was in middle school.
We'd ask one another if we preferred Wonder Girls or Girls' Generation.
And I always picked Wonder Girls.
So you prefer Korea University to Yonsei University,
and Wonder Girls to Girls' Generation.
I don't prefer Korea University. I hate Yonsei University.
- That won't change.
- He went to Korea University.
Tell us honestly that you failed to get into Yonsei University.
Mimi Minu, were you a member of Wonderful?
I'll tell you how much I love Wonder Girls.
When you're drunk, you say your honest feelings, right?
During a livestream which many people were watching,
I danced to "Tell Me."
And apparently, the production crew found that footage.
- Hold on a second.
- My gosh.
- What's that?
- Hold on.
(Source: Twitch)
- This proves...
- When was that?
- I'm a real fan.
- Is he in his underwear?
I was hosting a livestream.
- What is he doing?
- A thousand people saw that.
- Were you alone?
- Isn't that inappropriate?
- It was 1:30am.
- Isn't that a ssireum thigh band?
They're shorts, but they're quite short.
(I never knew you'd like me back)
(He seduces his subscribers with his thin legs and sweet voice.)
(His attractive energy blooms in the cyber world.)
- Wasn't he an educational YouTuber?
- But... Mimi Minu.
- Even your underwear is red.
- Hold on.
- Mimi Minu, how many...
- Diversity is pursued in education.
How many subscribers do you have?
I have 1.87 million subscribers.
I see how hard...
- He worked so hard.
- Mimi Minu worked...
- Right.
- to get 1.87 million subscribers.
- But...
- Exactly.
He helps students with worries...
- about CSAT.
- Give Mimi Minu some love.
I can't believe he danced like that after drinking alcohol.
- He really did everything he could.
- It's an unexpected charm I have.
He's even wearing...
- Korea University underwear.
- Anyway...
- He's wearing red underwear.
- He really did his best.
- I danced to "Nobody" as well.
- But... Mimi Minu.
I also like "Two Different Tears" so much.
- "Two Different Tears" is amazing.
- He worked really hard.
- It's true.
- I'm impressed.
- Chan Won must be the same.
- But you see...
- I was a member of Wonderful too.
- People around my age...
- are all fans of Wonder Girls'.
- Absolutely.
Even Hee Chul, who worked with SM Entertainment, was a fan too.
That's right. My Internet ID was Wonder Wonder...
while Mithra's was Girls' Generation Girls' Generation.
- We hated each other.
- Right.
- If you think about it...
- It's a true story.
Wasn't it the first dance challenge in the history of idol singers?
- You mean, "Tell Me?"
- Yes.
- That's right.
- People in all areas did it.
- As far as I remember...
- It was the first dance challenge.
- We called such videos UCC.
- We called it user created content.
- A flash mob.
- Contests were held.
(The dance challenge still continues.)
- What I'm trying to say is...
- Chan Won, who was your favorite?
- My favorite member was SUNMI.
- Really?
- Oh, come on.
- I liked no one else.
- Mimi Minu liked someone else.
- Who was your favorite member?
- Tell us honestly.
- I liked SUNYE.
- Oh, SUNYE?
- You liked SUNYE?
- Sun, ye.
- Ye.
But SUNMI gave amazing performances at the Waterbomb Festival...
- and the Korea University Festival.
- That's right.
(Her performance at the Waterbomb Festival became a legend.)
(She won the hearts of the Tigers at the Korea University Festival.)
After that, I became SUNMI-mi Minu.
- SUNMI-mi Minu?
- That was a good one, right?
- She's a great solo artist.
- SUNMI-mi Minu.
- What about you, Min Jun?
- Aren't you SUNMI-min Jun?
My favorite member was An So Hee.
- So Hee?
- I see.
- So Hee? Me too.
- Was she your favorite member?
- So Hee was also very popular.
- Indeed.
- She was incredibly popular.
- Wonder Girls was so popular.
Who was your favorite member, Ho Dong?
- Sorry?
- One, two, three.
I liked them all. I mean it.
- Pick one. Ready, go.
- But...
- Pick 1 other than those 3 members.
- I can't...
- Other than the mentioned members.
- I liked every one of them equally.
Ho Dong liked Girls' Generation a little bit more than us.
That's not true.
- What makes you think so?
- Whether you deny it or admit it,
- you'll be in an awkward position.
- You're right.
- Didn't you like Girls' Generation?
- I mean, I liked them too...
You need to answer wisely.
- SUNMI, what makes you think so?
- SUNMI, what's the reason?
- When I went on "Star King,"
- Yes?
he favored the members of Girls' Generation.
Both of the groups appeared on the show.
SUNMI, could you see that?
- Whether or not it's true...
- I don't know why I did that.
- Were you all on the show?
- We starred on the show together.
- Both groups starred on the show?
- Yes.
Ho Dong helped the members of Girls' Generation stand out...
more than he helped us.
He gave them more chances to make comments too?
- I can imagine how he treated them.
- "Kwon Yu Ri of Girls' Generation!"
"My, that's amazing."
"Gosh, Wonder Girls."
"Gosh, my Taeyeon."
- He's so good.
- "SUNMI, what are you doing?"
- "Gosh!" It was almost like this.
- But...
- It's not that.
- SUNMI, you didn't look so hot,
- so I helped you rest, right?
- Because... That's right.
The Wonder Girls members were a bit timid.
- That's right.
- We were timid.
So they had completely different characters.
He discriminated against you? Oh, no.
Since there are many Wonderfuls here,
let's test them.
- I'll give you questions.
- Really?
- What is this?
I'll give them here since you guys can peek.
What do we get if we win?
- Yes, is there something?
- We didn't prepare anything, but...
A CD with Wonder Girls' autographs?
- Do you...
- A concert ticket.
(A concert ticket)
(The fans get excited at the big news.)
That's pretty nice.
I think Mimi Minu is going to use every source from here...
- and use it on his channel.
- He'll do a livestream.
- I can dance again.
- It'll be in his vlog.
- And he'll dance.
- Yes, he works hard.
- It'll be his content.
- I make Reels right away.
- You'll create content right away.
- Yes.
- Give us the questions.
Okay, I'll give you the questions.
- I want to go to her concert.
- The first question.
Let's start with a simple one.
It's a piece of cake for me.
- When did Wonder Girls debut?
- Come on.
- Isn't it too easy?
- Wait.
- Let me answer.
- Hee Chul. What's the answer?
Is it February 12, 2007?
- Hold on. I know. Let me answer.
- Wrong.
- Can I really get it right?
- Yes, go ahead.
It's February 10, 2007.
- Correct!
- Okay!
- That's the date, right?
- It's my birthday!
- Oh, really?
- That's the date.
SUNMI, you debuted on my birthday.
- Really?
- Soo Geun's birthday...
- is February 10?
- Think of me on that day.
- Okay.
- That's his lunar birthday.
- Here's why I know.
- How do you know?
- Ten years after their debut, - He knew the exact date.
on February 10, 2017,
they officially went on hiatus.
After exactly ten years.
You remember because of that.
February 10 is the last day of the lunar year. It has strong energy.
That's why you returned as a virgin ghost.
- He's serious.
- That date...
is December 31 on the lunar calendar.
You debuted on the last day of the lunar year.
Hold on.
- All right. Let's move on.
- Early in 1975.
- That's hilarious.
- Until when...
- Chan Won is really good.
- Wonder Girls...
- has so many hit songs.
- That's right.
- SUNMI.
- Yes?
Before they released this song,
SUNMI was against it to the point that she sobbed.
- Let me answer.
- There is one.
- Jang Hoon.
- "Tell Me."
- Correct.
- Goodness.
- It's true.
- How did you know?
Actually, this is...
Jang Hoon, were you a Wonder Girls trainee?
No. For a quiz like this,
- the answer ought to be...
- That's right.
- their biggest hit song.
- Actually...
- That's right.
- Actually, "Tell Me..."
- was Jang Yun Jung's song.
- Of course.
- What?
- "Oh, my."
(Fake news that makes you go, "Oh, my")
("EXchange Tell Me," trot version)
(Oh, my, say that again)
- So that's why...
- Yun Jung turned it down,
- so Wonder Girls took it.
- They changed the melody only?
That's right. They changed the melody only.
And they stuck to the original lyrics.
- But SUNMI cried too.
- Why did you...
Why did you hate this song so much?
- She even cried.
- It's because...
- She bawled.
- I was 16 back then.
I was 16,
and the concept of the song was the 80's.
- That's right. The old days.
- Right.
(The concept of the song was the 80's.)
We went for the album photo shoot.
I was 16 then, so I wanted to look pretty.
I wanted to look pretty, but they permed my hair like this.
- It became a hit later.
- I remember.
So I was really shocked.
(Intense)
Was the concept too difficult for you to understand?
- Yes, because... Of course.
- You didn't like how you looked.
- Of course.
- The outfits were weird too.
- I really didn't want to do it.
- That's understandable.
Yes, and the song had many beepy sounds.
That's right.
(The retro rhythm was too difficult for SUNMI to embrace.)
That's what makes it addictive.
- Once you listen to it.
- Jang Hoon is leading.
It'll be really funny if he goes and watches your concert.
I was going to answer too.
He'll stand out so much.
It'll be so obvious.
He won't even be able to go to the restroom.
If he does, they'll go, "Jang Hoon, don't go to the restroom."
Here comes the next question.
Before their debut, Wonder Girls...
had a different name.
- What were they called?
- It's my first time hearing it.
- The question is too hard.
- This is too hard..
- Let me answer. Wonder Women.
- What is it?
- Wonder Women? Wrong.
- Wrong.
- That's not the answer.
- He's pretty good.
What's the answer, Jang Hoon?
All right. It's JYP Girls.
- I thought it was that.
- Wrong. That's not it.
- I bet there were many candidates.
- You might not know this.
- Give us a hint.
- A hint.
- A hint?
- Initials.
There are six letters in Korean.
The last word is "club."
- "Club?"
- Ladies' Club.
- Correct!
- Yes!
I knew Sang Min was going to get this.
- Why?
- Because...
I think I heard this from somewhere.
I heard it was a really famous club...
in a bustling area.
- That's the reason for their name?
- He'd go there often too.
You were a regular there.
- You spent thousands of dollars.
- But why...
- I know.
- Why did you think I'd know?
- It seemed like...
- He's been to Ladies' Club a lot.
- Why do you think...
- I mean...
- I'd know the answer?
- Because...
- Sang Min...
- It was Ladies' Club.
They sell whiskey there.
I thought you'd be very well-versed in that culture.
- Sang Min used to work there.
- Sorry?
Here comes the last question.
The last question is a bit difficult,
- so I'll raise the score.
- Okay.
- It's worth 30 points.
- It's like a school retreat.
You raise the score at the end even for a quiz like this?
Among the songs that Wonder Girls promoted,
- there's "I Feel You."
- Yes, I know "I Feel You."
What instrument did SUNMI play during this period?
- Let me answer!
- Hee Chul was faster.
- Keyboard!
- Keyboard?
- Wrong.
- Let me answer!
Bass guitar!
Correct!
- How did you know?
- What's wrong with you?
(SUNMI learned to play the bass guitar...)
(as the song was performed with a band concept.)
I liked her music style.
- Come on.
- I see.
And I'd see SUNMI playing the bass guitar...
in the videos she uploaded on social media.
It must be so nice to get her concert ticket.
- He and his wife are invited.
- That's right.
- He's the true winner.
- Wait.
- Please give me one.
- SUNMI.
I thought you were giving only one ticket.
- Give me one.
- Yes, I'm giving only one.
- Only one ticket.
- It's just one?
- Then...
- I should pay for the other one.
- You're so popular.
For the second section, peer relations,
you wrote, "Born in the Year of the Rat."
- All three of you?
- What does this mean?
No, she was probably born...
- in the Year of the Monkey.
- That's right.
When we first got into trot,
a few of us met through the competition show.
It's a gathering of trot singers born in 1996, the Year of the Rat.
Hence, "Born in the Year of the Rat."
Did you meet through introductions?
- How did we first meet?
- We met through someone.
Someone introduced us.
- Who introduced you too?
- Young Woong did.
- Really?
- What's his Chinese zodiac sign?
He was born in the Year of the Goat.
Why would he introduce those born in the Year of the Rat?
It's because he knew both of them,
and they seemed really nice.
- Because he knew them both?
- Yes.
We wanted to know each other.
Young Woong and I were...
- on "Mister Trot 1" together.
- That's right.
But he was the winner...
of a big audition show on a regional TV station.
And I knew that already.
Min Jun, you're pretty good.
I was hoping I could get to know him and get close to him.
And he said the same thing to Young Woong.
- That's how we met.
- My goodness.
I was a fan of his, and he was a fan of mine too.
- That's right.
- When we first met.
- Right.
- Yes. Also, Young Woong wanted...
to come to our show a few times,
- but he was hurt by Sang Min.
- That's right.
He hurt Young Woong so much.
(When Young Woong put on an elegant performance...)
(on our show 5 years ago,)
(Sang Min ruined it.)
(The team in 7th place)
(Young Woong and Sang Min got the the lowest ranking.)
(Very sadly)
(Since then, Young Woong didn't come anywhere near Brother School.)
- Because he hurt him so much.
- SUNMI...
That's the reason...
- That's right.
- Young Woong can't come back.
- Young Woong's fans...
- Young Woong wants to...
- banned you from it.
- come to our show, though.
Young Woong, you should come to the show.
- That's right.
- He'll call you if you nag.
I heard this from somewhere. Chan Won...
is full of worries because of you, Min Jun.
- Why?
- You shouldn't make him worry.
Well, Min Jun...
- You hang around a lot, don't you?
- I heard it from Chan Won.
- What is it?
- He's a kleptomaniac.
- What is he saying?
- That's right.
- Goodness.
- Out of the blue?
- Right, Chan Won?
- That's right.
You know it exactly, Ho Dong.
- That's not true.
- Really?
- He doesn't know it himself.
- Are you Sang Min or something?
- That's not true.
- I shouldn't reveal it here.
From his outer appearance,
he looks friendly and kind, right?
- Really?
- But...
he recently started drinking.
I have these premium liquors...
that I collected when I went abroad for concerts.
- I have them displayed.
- That's right.
But after I had a drink with him...
After that,
a few went missing.
- This is...
- That's...
Min Jun, I'm sorry. I can't defend you.
- That's theft.
- That's right.
He'd come to Chan Won's house and he'd go, "Bye, Chan Won."
But in his clothes, he'd be hiding liquor bottles.
Then they'd fall. "Oh, no."
"Oh, no. I'm sorry." I bet that's how it goes.
- Right.
- Was he caught red-handed?
Chan Won found out.
- Did you actually take them?
- That's not it.
As far as I remember, he was pretty drunk.
- Oh, no.
- I have a hobby...
- of collecting premium liquor.
- He did take them.
I asked him for one.
- Oh, you asked.
- And he said,
"You can take this."
- But he was drunk, - So he doesn't remember?
so I thought he wouldn't know if I just took one.
- That's what occurred to me.
- That means you stole.
The more you explain, the weirder it sounds.
Actually, in his studio,
there are two liquor bottles from my house...
when he said he'd take just one.
- Right. But he knows.
- Was it buy 1, get 1 free?
He knows that I took them.
But I clearly told him to just take one.
- That's right.
- Well, first of all,
let's go over the case details.
It should begin with a civil lawsuit.
If you feel too offended, you can consider...
- criminal punishment.
- Wait.
Isn't it over if Min Jun brings them back?
We can take that into account,
but he moved the items...
with a monetary value to his studio.
Moving the items itself...
- is a criminal act.
- That's not right.
I think he could...
- get a severe punishment.
- For theft?
- It's theft.
- SUNMI, stay away from him.
- We need to edit him out.
- That's right.
- Move to this side a bit.
- The production crew...
will have a hard time.
- Celebs shouldn't get in trouble.
- He needs to be edited out well.
- That's right.
- Editing one out is really hard.
Let me ask you, Min Jun.
There must've been a few bottles of liquor.
Did you know the ones you took were the most expensive?
- No, you took them without knowing, - That's right.
but they turned out...
- to be expensive, right?
- Are they expensive?
Actually, I knew.
- Hey, that's...
- That makes things difficult.
It was very intentional.
We can't defend you for that.
- It was the most...
- So,
before you fought,
how did you become good friends?
I don't see how that could've happened.
- I don't think they're close.
- That's not real.
What we just talked about now...
was a bit exaggerated to make it fun.
We're going to edit all that out.
We'll just use the part where he stole them.
The rest...
I don't think they'll use what you just said.
They'll just show the stealing part...
and that would be all.
It was a long time ago.
When I first debuted,
at the final round of "Mister Trot,"
families of the participants were in the audience.
Only my parents couldn't come.
They were so far away.
They were in Daegu.
My hometown is Daegu. So they couldn't come.
I couldn't meet my parents for half a year because of COVID-19.
- I was also very busy.
- Right.
All of a sudden, Min Jun...
I had one day off.
He told me to come downstairs.
I went downstairs.
He said, "Let's go to Daegu," and he took me to Daegu.
He found out where our restaurant was,
put the address into GPS,
and parked the car in the parking lot next to our restaurant.
He went inside the restaurant...
and said to my parents, "Hello, I'm Song Min Jun."
"Chan Won is in the car you see over there."
- Hold on.
- When the parents go out,
he goes, "Yes!"
- This is exciting!
- The alcohol at our restaurant.
- No.
- He said, "Thank you, Min Jun,"
and Min Jun said, "You're welcome." that's what happened.
That's a planned crime.
- That's possible.
- I'm not that kind of person.
It was when even going out...
- was restricted.
- Right.
- It was difficult.
- So,
I thought the only safe place he could meet his parents...
was inside a car.
- Goodness.
- I went to a park alone,
and Chan Won's parents...
- That's nice.
- That's amazing.
went to the car and met Chan Won.
We should have heard this story first.
I keep getting suspicious.
Your parents would have cried a lot as soon as they saw you.
They wailed.
They were running a tripe restaurant.
They're no longer running it, but they used to back then.
So many fans and people who liked "Mister Trot..."
went there and waited...
like two hours.
So many people went there,
so my mom became very thin.
My father also lost around 15kg.
- Goodness.
- I also wailed after seeing them...
so thin like that.
- Goodness.
- I still can't forget that day.
The kindness I received...
and the debt of gratitude I felt at the time...
I talked about it like a joke earlier,
but it's not something I would be able to pay back...
with two bottles of liquor.
You should have given him more.
Did you hear that well, Min Jun?
- I think you can take more.
- I know, right?
I think I should go for it.
As for me,
as soon as the first episode of "Mister Trot 2" aired,
Chan Won called after my performance ended.
He cried for 30 minutes without saying anything.
- Really?
- He cried.
What went missing again?
- The story...
- You're not relating.
"Did you take this as well?"
"Seriously!"
"Please, my friend!"
- I...
- "It's something I cherish."
"I got it with a lot of effort too!"
"It's 30 years old."
- Gosh.
- You shouldn't have taken that.
Goodness.
- He kept crying.
- Stop.
"It's done now."
"You did so well."
"Things are going to work out well for you now."
He kept crying after saying that.
Did you drink that day?
I drank a lot.
(I drank a lot.)
Goodness.
- He drank.
- Or...
- He's sensitive.
- This is funny.
"Mister Trot" airs after 10pm. It's a late-night show.
It's really fun to watch...
- with a glass of soju.
- He's sensitive.
Chan Won was a contestant first.
Right. I experienced it before.
You knew through that experience.
You knew how...
- I'm happy it turned out well.
- Goodness.
Next, we have the latest news about the three of them.
- First, Chan Won.
- Yes.
What's this? "New personal record."
- "New personal record."
- Were you at an event?
- A competition?
- Isn't it like the album records?
- Album...
- Album records?
- Album records...
- He's breaking all records.
- Right. The album records.
- What...
- It's a personal record.
- I think I saw it on the news.
I released mini albums and full-length albums so far.
The first one sold 570,000 copies.
The one before sold 600,000 copies.
The recent one sold...
- around 610,000 copies.
- That's amazing.
I set a new personal record.
There were articles about that.
Three consecutive half-million sellers, right?
- That's right.
- Three consecutive ones.
- Amazing.
- Congratulations.
- Also...
- Thank you.
Chan Won...
also received the Grand Entertainment Award last year.
That's right.
- Right. On KBS.
- That's amazing.
When I received the Grand Award at the KBS Entertainment Awards,
I thought,
it was the path Ho Dong,
my role model,
walked 17 or 18 years ago.
The Grand Award at the KBS Entertainment Awards.
Ho Dong is going to cry again.
Then you must have mentioned Ho Dong in your speech.
- Of course, he did.
- Of course.
He would have been crying when he said that.
He sounds like he mentioned him.
- We have the clip. Shall we watch?
- Let's watch.
Let's watch it.
- I'm sorry...
- What?
Why isn't it playing?
He didn't say anything.
Why didn't you say anything?
Should I say it again?
I guess he wasn't worth mentioning.
No. Actually,
I was completely out of it.
I had no idea I was getting it.
I couldn't even mention my fans,
- my family, and my colleagues.
- You were nervous.
I was so nervous and shocked.
I was the MC there.
I was the MC of the live show.
I didn't think they would give it to me.
If you keep walking the path Ho Dong walked,
you'll have ssireum at the end.
Ssireum is getting popular again these days.
You should meet...
- at the ssireum tournament.
- Goodness.
I heard the recent song wasn't a classic trot song.
- The recent song...
- "Maybe Today."
- is called "Maybe Today."
- Country!
- It's a country song.
- The song is nice.
- Soo Geun heard it.
- He sang it...
on "Han Moon Chul's Dashcam Review." It's a good song.
Thank you.
The song was written by special people.
It was composed by Cho Yeong Su,
and the lyrics were by Roy Kim.
- Lyrics by Roy Kim.
- Yes.
It's different from the classic trot songs I used to sing.
- It's like a country song.
- The song is nice.
- Country songs are nice.
- It's poetic.
(We're looking forward to listening to "Maybe Today.")
Next.
It's SUNMI.
We talked about this earlier when SUNMI came.
Yes.
Your recent update is "virgin ghost."
- Are you back as a virgin ghost?
- What happened?
The concept of my new song is a virgin ghost.
- Really?
- That's amazing.
So I wear a white burial robe...
and have my hair down like this.
I also have...
- rotten nails...
- You get makeup.
- and dance like that.
- Really?
How did you do your makeup?
Do you have blood?
I also put on the black bean paste lipstick.
- The real one?
- Really?
- In the music video.
(Black bean paste lips, long straight hair)
(Makeup that resembles a ghost)
You didn't want to sing "Tell Me." Did you want to sing this one?
- I did.
- Really?
It's because she made that concept.
- Right. This...
- That's amazing.
After all, it's a song I made.
I thought it would be nice to go with a virgin ghost concept.
The virgin ghost in "Korean Ghost Stories?"
- That's right.
- It's a bit...
So this time,
this is the story of the music video.
I died in vain.
- Goodness.
- I died in vain.
- Right.
- So for 49 days...
- The 49-day ritual.
- Do you wander around?
- Yes. I wander around.
I'm being chased by a grim reaper.
So I run away from him,
but I end up getting caught and taken back.
It's like "KPop Demon Hunters."
Why did you tell us the ending as well?
You should have avoided him like this.
But it's really interesting.
This time,
I thought it would be nice to add some comic elements.
Why didn't you have one of us play the role of the Grim Reaper?
- Right.
- The Grim Reaper...
- Jang Hoon fits that role well.
- Jang Hoon fits it well.
- Jang Hoon...
- He was in "Exhuma."
The Jayu-ro ghost.
- This...
- Was Jang Hoon in "Exhuma?"
The ghost in "Exhuma..."
(The 2.5m tall Saja boy guarding the grave)
- This...
- "Exhuma."
The title of her new song is related to me.
- That's right.
- I guess you didn't know.
- How?
- The title.
The title is "CYNICAL."
- "CYNICAL."
- The title is "CYNICAL?"
It's not "Virgin Ghost?"
- It's not.
- "CYNICAL?"
- It's not "Virgin Ghost?"
- Goodness.
That's a disappointment.
- It's not "Virgin Ghost."
- In terms of being cynical,
- The title is "CYNICAL."
- am I not...
one of the top in the country?
While making the song,
I thought it would be fun if I became a virgin ghost.
I told my company about it...
thinking I'd get rejected.
- But they really liked it.
- They liked it?
They told me to go on.
I think the songs have a connection.
- Like "Full Moon" and "TAIL."
- Right.
- They had very strong concepts.
- They also have...
- the "KPop Demon Hunters" vibe.
- Honestly, when I watch...
SUNMI's performances,
the choreography is too difficult.
Is this one also a bit...
- That's right. This one...
- If Shin Dong says it's hard,
- it's really hard.
- So...
SUNMI's choreography isn't a choreography.
It's a stunt.
- Really?
- You have that in the intro?
- Yes.
- I'm saying this...
because the choreography of "CYNICAL..."
is the hardest one out of all the ones I've done.
Since the concept is a virgin ghost,
- the joints move independently.
- What?
- No. Shin Dong has bad joints.
- Do you fly?
When you do that, we can see your joints.
But when Shin Dong does it, we can't see his joints.
They turn into waves.
- I'm curious.
- So it's...
- That's why the joints are bad.
- We're seeing your stage, right?
- Will we see it today?
- Will you show us?
- Can we see it?
Really?
We have to see it.
I'll show it to you.
- I can get changed right away.
- Right.
- The song...
- I'll be right back.
- I'll be back.
- She'll even wear the burial robe?
- I'm here.
- Goodness.
- She got changed right away.
- She really did.
I normally put on hair extensions.
- It's a real burial robe.
- Let's go!
- The virgin ghost.
- Virgin ghost!
Let's go!
("CYNICAL" by SUNMI)
It does feel retro.
- It does feel like it, right?
- Yes.
She goes like this.
I think we need a physical therapist.
(Why are you so odd!)
(Her performance mesmerized the classroom.)
Gosh.
- SUNMI, it feels a bit retro.
- Your joints were like this.
This one is so...
- Gosh.
- We were...
People say that it's like a dark version of "Tell Me."
It's got a vibe.
"Dark Tell Me."
Guys, should we watch YouTube?
The Mimi Minu channel.
Mimi Minu is dancing.
- Look at him.
- Look at him dance.
Is this how I get another scene?
Look at him.
Did you do that?
Gosh.
Please give him the music.
He can't do that.
Mimi Minu.
- Mimi Minu.
- He's good.
(I'll go my own way.)
He's good.
(His dance satisfied the "Star King" guy.)
(Each movement breaks the beat through every joint.)
- Gosh, that's it.
- Yes.
- Gosh, Min Woo.
- That's great.
- Min Woo, with these things, - That's great.
Jang Hoon usually watches...
and says, "Gosh, what is that?"
But since he knows that you had a hard time,
- his face looked so touched.
- I was touched.
Why did that happen?
- Is that the Nation's Beloved Host?
- Why did you make him dance?
We watched the YouTube video.
Why would you make him dance for no reason?
- Mimi Minu is amazing.
- It really felt like "Star King."
- I felt bad for him.
- I saw his videos like that.
Next, it's Min Jun.
For his recent update, Min Jun wrote...
"Trot Young Noble."
There are a lot of people from royalty in trot.
- Everyone is royalty.
- They are.
The Trot Hero is Lim Young Woong.
- Trot Crown Prince, Trot Emperor, - Yes.
Trot Prince,
- Trot Young Noble, - There are a lot.
Trot Aristocrat...
There are a lot of young nobles.
- Aren't there a lot of them?
- There are a lot.
There are a few candidates.
- Jeong Dong Won.
- He's one of the young nobles.
- Jin Hae Seong.
- Kim Hee Jae.
- These are the young nobles.
- Right.
Are you one of the young nobles, Min Jun?
I'm one of the young nobles or crown princes.
- "Crown prince?"
- Who gave you the crown?
- He is.
- What about you, Chan Won?
- What about Chan Won?
- In the trot world.
- Chan Won Trot.
I'm relatively younger,
so I'm usually called the "Trot Idol."
- "Trot Idol?"
- Who decides that?
- The fans?
- Yes, the fans usually do that.
Min Ho is the Trot BTS, right?
- The BTS of Trot.
Before that,
- Jin Sung was the BTS of Trot, - That's right.
but Min Ho took over.
The guy who sang "At Andong Station?"
Yes, that guy. He called himself...
- the "BTS of Trot."
- Isn't he too much older for that?
He cleanly backed out after Min Ho appeared.
I heard that the young noble ran away from the royal family.
- Why?
- You're right.
I did run away.
- I used to play soccer, - You did?
but after I quit, I went to engineering school.
- You did?
- Until how old did you play?
Until I was in high school.
Ever since I was in the first grade, when I was eight years old.
You started studying again when you were a freshman in high school?
So I went to engineering school, and...
- It's hard.
- Yes.
I didn't know what I was doing there.
And I liked to sing at that time.
So I just dropped out...
and ran away to Seoul without even telling my family,
with just a bag.
I just said I'd manage rent with part-time jobs...
and try to sing.
So I attended trot contests while working part-time jobs.
Did you start singing trot from the beginning?
I used to love ballads.
But people would say I'm not a good singer with ballads.
- I'm sure you must have been bad.
- So...
It could be, since you were young.
- Yes, I was bad.
- Soo Geun, you're correct.
It's such a good thing he's singing trot.
Did people say you were bad when you were singing ballad songs?
Most of them wouldn't look at me.
Why is that so?
But when I went to trot contests, I kept winning first place.
You must be better at it.
People would clap and say that I'm good...
- whenever I sang trot, - That happens.
so I thought it was the road that I should take,
and now, I'm still singing trot.
- Do your parents support you now?
- Of course.
After I had my debut, they loved it.
- That's a relief.
- As if they had become myself,
they loved it so much.
(My parents love it the most.)
(Min Jun is loved for doing the music that he loves.)
On the next line,
it says, "Idol versus trot singer."
You are all solo artists, but your genres are different.
- Yes.
- SUNMI does dance music.
If the genre is different,
does the way you treat your fans differ as well?
- I'm so curious.
- It's very different.
- Sure.
How is it for idols?
For idols, the fans love it when I act cute.
To be honest, I'm usually not the affectionate type.
But in front of the fans, I get really affectionate.
- It comes out naturally, right?
- Yes.
- Since the fans like it?
So even when I take pictures with my fans,
I get really close...
- And take pictures?
- and go like this to them.
Then...
- You get that close?
- Gosh.
Shin Dong, let's learn from that.
- Is it okay to do that?
- Super Junior should do that,
- Yes, you're an idol.
- We should.
If we go like that, since we're too close now,
they will go, "What's wrong with you today?"
Is it different for trot fans?
- It's very different.
- How?
Recently, I went to KBS as a special MC...
- for "Music Bank."
- That's right.
For the other shows that I'm currently doing,
like "Immortal Songs" or "Special Reporter 25 Hours", I say,
"Immortal Songs will begin now!"
"Let's watch the video!"
- "Music Bank."
- But with "Music Bank", it's...
"Out with a new concept,"
"it's LE SSERAFIM."
- "Welcome."
- Yes.
"Just wait a minute." I had to go like that.
"Just wait a minute."
With the shows that I usually do,
I say, "It will be revealed soon. Please wait a minute."
- "Just wait a minute."
- That's so different.
- They make it like a conversation.
- And for us...
At "Music Bank,"
- you say, "Music, start."
- Yes.
We say, "Music, please."
Because Chan Won grew up watching "Star King."
Yes.
Ho Dong would go, "Music Bank."
No one would watch.
- That's right.
- "We need your warm applause."
"Music."
"You can't do that. It's not just any bank."
"It's Music Bank." He would say that.
You need to open it like this.
- Goodness.
- I realized that...
the main difference is the way we call them.
- The way you call them.
- Since the age is different.
We don't see those under 50 as women.
- Those under 50 aren't women.
- That's a big one.
You have the elder fans.
- That's right.
- That's crazy.
- Only the older women.
- They go only after them.
Only those over 50.
Those in their 30s or 40s are like babies.
They are babies?
We really don't see those under 50 as women.
But when they come, for example,
they are my mother's age,
- Yes.
- and those who are even older...
- could be my grandmother's age.
- Sure.
Then, usually, in normal situations,
we would call them "ma'am" or "madam."
- But they hate it when we do that.
- They don't like it.
- They feel so offended.
- Do you need to call their names?
We were showing respect, but they don't like it?
Then what should we call them?
- What do you say?
- "Older sister?"
Don't you have to call their name? "Mal Ja."
- Correct.
- Sure.
"Hi there, Gyeong Sook, born in 1944."
- That's correct.
- Really?
Soo Geun, you are correct.
We do that sometimes.
"Born in 1944?"
- "Born in 1944?"
- "Gyeong Sook, born in 1944."
- That's so funny.
- We...
We actually get messages on our social media.
They call us "darling," but...
"I enjoyed your performance today, my darling."
- The sentence structure.
- The old style.
- It's the old spelling.
- They use the old words.
I think, "She called me darling, though."
So when I see their profile picture,
she's standing like this in the flower field.
With her granddaughter in her arms.
Most of them are like that.
- They are all young girls inside.
- Yes.
Is there a memorable fan you met at the rest stop?
- I still remember where it was.
- Okay.
I was going past Geumsan, South Chungcheong Province,
- and Geumsan is known for ginseng.
- That's right.
So the name of the rest stop is "Geumsan Ginseng Land Rest Stop."
- I remember it.
- That's right.
Yes, it's Ginseng Land.
There's a Ginseng Land Rest Stop.
But usually, when I go to the restroom,
it's a bit embarrassing if someone recognizes me.
- Right. You wear a hat.
- So I usually wear a hat.
But there was no one there.
So I went to the bathroom, and I relieved myself,
and when I came out,
an elderly man saw me and said,
"Aren't you Lee Chan Won?"
He was about 70 years old.
"Gosh, I'm also from Daegu."
"It's so nice to meet someone from the same hometown."
"I was always supporting you."
"Let's shake hands."
So I said, "Thank you."
"Enjoy your time," and was about to go, but he said,
"Let me poop where Lee Chan Won pooped."
I'm serious.
(There's a reason he couldn't forget that time.)
- That's so good.
- Goodness.
- That's so funny.
- Gosh.
- Ho Dong, is he a Strong Heart?
Strong Heart?
- You got it!
- I got it!
(Chan Won got it!)
- Gosh.
- That's amazing.
That's a Strong Heart.
It's true, though.
- That's amazing.
- It's true.
Lastly, it's the Question Aptitude Test.
It's something we're promoting.
- I'm curious.
- It's "Ask Me."
Each of the students prepared a question...
that they would like to ask the transfer students.
- I will go first.
- Okay.
My question.
It's the same question for all three of you.
- If you could be reborn, - Yes?
would you choose to be the best actor or the best singer?
You guys do balance games often, don't you?
- This is hard.
- But the condition is...
that the best actor makes a bit more money.
- That really makes me think.
- I think I'd choose the best actor.
Aren't you satisfied with being a singer right now?
I'm so satisfied and happy, but...
- I'm your fan.
- Actually, I know that actors...
have their own difficulties.
They have to memorize lines and maintain their looks.
- But for singers, it's hard to...
- We have to memorize lyrics.
It's so hard to maintain our vocal cords.
- Actors are cool, right?
- It's hard for Shin Dong...
- to maintain his vocal cords too.
- Hey, singers don't have to...
maintain their condition. What are you talking about?
- Hey, maintaining your figure?
- What...
Maintaining your vocal cords? You don't need any of that.
What are you talking about?
But you've lost too much weight to be able to say that.
- Right, I have lost quite a lot.
- So, he has been...
- Compared to before?
- What did you see...
to say that he has lost a lot of weight?
What did you see to say that he has lost a lot of weight?
- Let me answer. You remember.
- Soo Geun, you know this too.
- And SUNMI? Singer or actor?
- What about SUNMI?
- I want to be the best actor.
- Over 20 years...
- Oh, really?
- Sure, you want to try...
something different...
- once you've made it big.
- You want to try another job.
- A different job...
- You want to live a different life.
This question is becoming closer to a trashy question.
No, why would you... She could be sincerely...
- It's so predictable.
- It is.
Still, I want to live as the best singer.
- Right.
- Even if the best actor makes more?
Even if that's the case.
As I live my life,
- wealth doesn't mean that much.
- He makes quite enough now.
Then, give me a few more bottles of whiskey.
Darn it.
Gosh, seriously.
Hey, you make plenty of money too!
- Chan Won, - Someone might think...
- give me some too.
- you don't make money.
- Actually, as a singer, - I want to go to Chan Won's.
I'm sure every performance is precious to you.
- Is this a question?
- Why is it taking so long?
It's precious.
- Here he goes.
- What is this question?
- Then, what?
- Any...
Any performance would be precious, but a meaningful one... So,
there's a question I asked Jang Hoon back in the day.
- Please just say what's written.
- I mean...
- Lee Soo Geun.
- Come on.
- Just listen!
- That'll take even more time!
- Back then, I told Jang Hoon...
- Please make it short.
Do you make things short?
- So, - Oh, my.
- you know, - Oh, my.
Jang Hoon... What?
- I was so scared.
- Hey, what?
Are your questions shockingly short?
What do you call that?
- Do you make sharping remarks?
- Watch your finger.
- You mean "cutting remarks."
- "Sharping remarks."
- Cutting remarks.
(Don't you mean cutting remarks?)
- Sharping...
- Soo Geun.
So, what is your question?
- That's not it. I'm sorry.
- So, what is it?
As a singer, what was the best performance of your life?
- It could be something meaningful.
- Right.
So, this was the question?
- Gosh, the buildup.
- As a singer!
Did you lay all that out up front just to ask this?
- Throughout your life...
- But...
Every performance is important.
- All performances are important,
- so choosing one...
- Yes, they're all important.
- Min Jun. Is it a trashy question?
- Just say it's a trashy question.
- What about SUNMI?
- It's close to that.
I'll pass.
Got it. Okay!
- What did I say?
- Chan Won.
Let's go, Chan Won!
- SUNMI has that one, though.
- Show them what you've got!
- Actually, the Waterbomb...
- Chan Won.
Well, you know,
I'm sure I have many precious performances,
- You're sure you do?
- But I can't forget...
the first time I was on "Star King."
- My goodness.
- He has great social skills.
- I really can't forget. For real.
- Good one.
- Great social skills.
- Isn't it "Jinttobaegi," Chan Won?
Honestly, the time you performed "Jinttobaegi" on "Mr. Trot" was...
- Honestly, it's "Jinttobaegi."
- It is "Jinttobaegi."
See? It's "Jinttobaegi!"
I was on "Star King" three times!
Nobody recognized me!
- How could that beat "Jinttobaegi?"
- Of course.
- "Jinttobaegi" is the best.
- How many views did that get?
(He may be a "Star King" kid, but "Jinttobaegi" is the best.)
- All right, now. Focus.
- Okay.
If you could switch your voice...
with another singer's voice for a day,
who would you switch with?
- That's a novel idea.
- Just one singer.
In the genre of music that I do, I choose Lee Chan Won.
I'm not the type of trot singer...
who sings powerfully and in the traditional trot style.
- What about Chan Won?
- I choose Lim Young Woong.
- Oh, Lim Young Woong.
- Hey.
Hey, you should say it's me.
Chan Won...
- I just want to win once!
- That was the real deal.
Right, he's our hero.
- Just once.
- What about SUNMI?
I choose IU.
- IU.
- That would suit you well.
- That question was nice and neat.
- It would suit you well.
- Right.
- The answers were neat too.
Then, let me keep going along the same lines.
- No, I wish you wouldn't.
- Oh, really?
Thanks for your answer. Okay, the next question.
Which song do you want to steal? I'm sure this isn't easy.
- I have one.
- Oh, Chan Won. Whose song is it?
I choose YoungTak's "Jjin-iya."
- Jjin, jjin, jjin, jjin, jjin-iya - That would suit you well.
It would suit Chan Won well.
But back then, this song...
For the final round of "Mr. Trot,"
we got to choose a song according to our rank.
- Right.
- So, in first place at the time...
during the semi-finals,
Young Woong got to choose one first.
Then, I chose one,
and YoungTak chose one next.
This song wasn't chosen by the first three people.
We didn't choose the song, "Jjin-iya."
That was because it was a little unfamiliar for us.
The intro to this song goes...
(The intro to "For Elise" wasn't commonly heard in trot.)
It started with "For Elise,"
so it felt too unfamiliar at first.
- It feels different.
- "How does this connect to trot?"
That's how it felt, so I didn't choose it,
- but my goodness.
- "Jjin-iya."
- Everyone knows "Jjin-iya."
- Right.
- Back then, I should've...
- Please sing a bit of it for us.
- Five, six, seven, eight.
- One, two, three, four.
(Chan Won's version)
(Totally the best)
(Refreshing vocals)
- That's different.
- That was amazing.
It's different...
- when you're just singing it.
- I know.
"I would've topped the charts if I sang this song."
So, my voice is kind of in the middle-low range,
- Right.
- and it sounds kind of raspy.
But IU has...
- such a clear and pure sound.
- Pure.
- Opposites attract, you know?
- You're drawn by it.
So, I love IU's voice so much.
Then, is there a song you'd like to since in that voice?
In that voice? Well,
"Gashina?"
- Well, if I sing it, it's like...
- In IU's voice?
- Are you leaving me behind?
- "Gashina" in IU's voice?
Are you leaving so easily?
If I were to sing like that,
IU would probably be like...
(IU's version)
You totally sounded like a ghost.
- Something like that.
- It is different.
- Yes, I really envy her.
- I'm glad Yeong Cheol didn't try.
Okay, I'll go this time.
- Among our members, - Yes?
is there a talent that you'd like to steal?
- I'm sure we'd all say the same.
- A talent I'd want to steal?
I choose Soo Geun's quick wits.
- Right.
- Really?
I always watched and rewatched "2 Days 1 Night."
Recently, through clips on YouTube,
- those videos are all the rage.
- Right, they're trending.
But even when I watch the same thing over and over,
Soo Geun is so funny. It almost drives me crazy.
"Hey, Soo Geun. Make us laugh."
"Do you want to see an illegal U-turn?"
- Right.
- Something like that.
He has many famous lines.
- That's legendary.
- "What is a persimmon in English?"
- "Thurbm."
"What's a tangerine?" "Shur."
That was such a long time ago.
"What are you doing? Why won't you get up?"
(Replaying Soo Geun's quick-witted moments)
(Bring a knife.)
(I'll give you a small taste.)
I would like to steal Ho Dong's muscular strength.
- Oh, muscular strength.
- His muscular strength?
- Muscular strength?
- What's that?
I guess his forearm muscles are pretty impressive.
- My forearm muscles?
- No.
Do you want to steal my forearm muscles?
Your muscular strength.
That's because...
I saw this on social media once.
What people say about Ho Dong...
"That Kang Ho Dong guy may look like he's chubby,"
- But... Right.
- "but he's not."
- "It's all muscle."
- Yes, it's muscle. That's right.
Right. There's that famous picture...
- Really?
- from when he's swimming.
- He doesn't have any belly fat.
- He's so muscular.
Really?
Do people call me "that Kang Ho Dong guy?"
It's a lawless place.
What funny people they are.
- Those people are so insensitive.
- So scary!
"That Kang Ho Dong guy?"
- No, they weren't being rude.
- Gosh, this is hilarious!
- That's really not true.
- If someone did say that...
How refreshing.
- Seriously.
- This is so funny.
To lift the mood in this segment, I took a novel approach.
Do you guys think luck is a thing?
What?
- "I'm quite a lucky person."
- All right.
- This is the worst...
- The worst question!
- That's it.
- Wait.
- I'm lucky.
- I have good luck.
- Don't you have good luck, SUNMI?
- I am lucky.
- Me too. My luck...
- I've prepared something.
- He prepared something?
- Oh, there's more?
All right. I've boiled half of the eggs here.
- No way. On the head?
- Raw versus boiled eggs?
(A raw egg random draw)
I'll smash the three eggs that you guys choose on my head.
So, we'll see if you guys really are lucky or not.
- Why would you do all this?
- Really?
- Okay, so...
- Wait a minute.
(This is the ending performance, you fools!)
They said the ending was too bland, all right?
- So, I've prepared this.
- But we're here too.
- Okay.
- You won't smash it on your head.
You choose one, Chan Won.
Soo Geun, I'll go with this one.
- Do it right away.
- Okay.
- Chan Won.
- Lee Soo Geun, let's go!
This is Chan Won's luck for this year!
I trust you!
(Chan Won gets a boiled egg!)
- All right!
- Go!
Who wants to try next? Step forward!
- Me!
- Come on!
- All right!
- Let's go!
- I'll check my luck for this year!
- SUNMI!
- Your comeback...
- with your first regular album!
- Come on!
- Everyone, gambling is dangerous!
- Let's go!
- Go for it!
- Gambling is so dangerous, people!
- With confidence!
- All right.
- I choose this one!
- All right!
- SUNMI made her choice!
- Your first album comeback!
- SUNMI, on his forehead.
- Let's go, SUNMI!
- On Min Woo's forehead!
- Yes!
(What will SUNMI and Mimi Minu's luck be?)
(SUNMI's new song is set to be a hit!)
- No way.
- Min Jun, let's go!
- Do it on my forehead.
- On Hee Chul's forehead.
- On the count of three.
- All right.
- Min Jun! Right here!
- Hee Chul, I'm sorry!
- It's okay!
- Will it be good or bad?
Will it be good or bad?
(He has bad luck.)
(Smashed Coffee)
(Reality Check Credit Card)
(Lee Chan Won and Lee Soo Geun)
(Song Min Jun and Lee Sang Min)
(Kang Ho Dong and Seo Jang Hoon)
(Mimi Minu and Min Kyung Hoon)
(Kim Yeong Cheol and Kim Hee Chul)
(And SUNMI)
(SUNMI's Avatar Blind Date)
(November, a cafe in Brother-dong)
I came to this cafe...
because I think I'll meet a beautiful partner "Maybe Today."
- Welcome. Hello.
- Hello.
Is this the cafe for the lonely singles?
That's right. You came to the right place.
Then you must be here for a blind date.
Yes, I am.
I thought I'd be alone.
Why are there so many chairs?
Didn't you know? Today, it'll be...
a 1-on-5 blind date.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
Other men should be here any minute.
There are many seats.
My goodness.
(The cafe door opens again.)
(The men who'll attend the blind date...)
(enter the cafe one at a time.)
Welcome. You're here.
- Hello.
All right. You're here.
You're smartly dressed for the blind date today.
- Please take a seat.
- I think we're down to one rival.
- Hello.
- This is awkward.
- Yes.
- Everyone, here comes your date.
- Nice to meet you.
Please come on in.
- Hello.
- Oh, my.
Please come on in.
- Hello.
- Oh, my.
Oh, my.
- Hello.
Hello.
- What?
- Thank you.
- He'll break the chair.
(Well-mannered)
- Thank you.
- It's nice to meet you.
Please take a seat.
All right. Everyone, I'll introduce the star of today's blind date.
It's SUNMI.
(Date, SUNMI)
Hello.
Hello, I'm SUNMI.
(Some people are watching the exciting first meeting.)
(They're the inner selves of the male participants.)
(The inner selves will control the outer selves in real-time.)
(When the inner selves order, the outer selves will execute.)
(The Avatar Blind Date begins now.)
Hello.
- It's nice to meet you. I'm SUNMI.
- It's nice to meet you.
- She's so pretty.
- She's so beautiful.
"SUNMI, we're wearing matching tops today."
- SUNMI, - Yes?
we're wearing matching tops today.
- Could it be...
- They're in the same color.
You're right.
What a coincidence. I guess we had a connection.
"Big sister, I love you."
(The younger man confesses his love from the start.)
- "Big sister."
- Big sister,
I love you.
You shouldn't lie.
What?
("Love Naggers," the worst thing a younger man can do)
- Big sister.
- How old are you?
- How...
- "I'm 21 years old."
I'm 21 years old.
(I'm Ho Dong, a 21-year-old.)
(I see.)
Twenty-one.
It must be the side effect of herbal medicine.
- People seem to be feeling awkward.
- Yes.
Since this is a 1-on-5 blind date,
- a self-introduction will be nice.
- Okay.
Please take turns to introduce yourselves.
Yeong Cheol. "I'm not a Canadian. I'm a comedian."
"You're SUNMI, and I'm sunshine."
I'm not a Canadian. I'm a comedian.
You're SUNMI, and I'm sunshine.
That little...
(My inner self is insane.)
I'm sorry, but...
(An inner voice came out.)
I heard something that couldn't be aired.
(Chan Won's inner self has a potty mouth.)
I...
I think I heard a swear word somewhere.
I heard something that couldn't be aired.
(The control tower is uncontrollable.)
Why don't other people introduce themselves?
It's my job to take whiskey.
He's a thief.
- I collect whiskey.
- A collector.
- My name is Lee Chan Won.
- Okay.
"I run a small business in Daegu."
I run a small business in Daegu.
I see. May I ask you what kind of business it is?
"Every item in the store is two dollars."
- Every...
- "It's two dollars."
Every item in the store is two dollars.
(Every item is two dollars.)
"I run Everything Is Here."
- I run Everything Is Here.
- Lee Chan Won.
- Everything Is Here.
- "My father passed it down."
My father passed it down.
- I see.
- It's like a pyramid scheme.
- "The price was 20 cents then."
- The price...
The price was 20 cents then.
Since the prices rose, it's two dollars now.
(My name is Lee Chan Won. My father's name is Lee Baek Won.)
- "Hello, big sister."
- Hello, big sister.
I run a Pyongyang naengmyeon place in Ilsan.
I see.
"I sell half and eat half."
- I sell half...
- Okay.
and eat half.
Isn't it cute?
You know...
(The younger man's sudden flirting skills)
Isn't it cute?
(Turning away)
It's so funny. My goodness.
"I'm sorry, but I sang..."
"at his wedding."
- SUNMI.
- I sang...
at his wedding.
- What?
- Are you...
- I thought you were married.
- a divorcee?
- Aren't you a married man?
That's too much.
"I was on 'Teenage Parents.'"
What?
"Teenage Parents."
- "I was on 'Teenage Parents.'"
- "Teenage Parents."
"I was on 'Teenage Parents.'"
I was on "Teenage Parents."
"I have a son."
- I knew it. I sang at his wedding.
- "I have a son."
I have a son.
- "Teenage Parents."
- Yes.
I'm 21 years old now.
(Unrivaled background)
Hello, SUNMI.
- Hello.
- "It's nice to meet you."
- It's nice to meet you.
- Yes.
- "I'm Mimi Minu."
- I'm Mimi Minu.
Is he ChatGPT?
- Are you AI?
- Well, I'm...
"I'm a YouTuber."
I'm a YouTuber.
"I have about 1.7 million subscribers."
Kyung Hoon, it's 1.87 million.
You should've checked in advance.
"I have about 1.87 million subscribers."
I have about 1.8 million subscribers.
- You have many subscribers.
- Your subscribers...
"To be honest, I wanted to go to Yonsei University."
"I wanted to go to Yonsei University."
(Gulping)
"After taking CSAT five times, I went to Korea University."
"I went to Korea University."
- SUNMI, to be honest, - Okay.
I wanted to go to Yonsei University.
But I watched your legendary fancam that was taken at Korea University.
After taking CSAT five times, I went to Korea University.
- I see. Really?
- Yes.
(Ho Dong's inner side is happy for some reason.)
Get up and shout, "SUNMI!"
- SUNMI!
- Yes?
SUNMI!
(My goodness)
(SUNMI becomes scared.)
"KOSPI broke the 4,000-point mark."
- What is it?
- KOSPI broke the 4,000-point mark.
"But I don't have any stocks."
But I don't have any stocks.
"SUNMI, do you?"
- SUNMI, do you?
- No, I don't.
- "That's good to hear."
- That's good to hear.
- "Let's buy them together."
- Let's buy them together.
- What was that?
- What?
Do you have any recommendations?
"Ssireum is the best."
- You know, - Stock recommendations.
the best one is...
ssireum.
Ssireum?
"Basketball is better than ssireum."
Basketball is better than ssireum.
- Okay.
- Hurry up and say it.
"Basketball..."
- "is better than ssireum."
- Come on.
- Basketball...
- Okay.
is better than ssireum.
Basketball.
- Okay?
- Seo Jang Hoon?
A dunk shot. Basketball.
Seo Jang Hoon, go back to Yonsei University.
(The electrifying taste of controlling someone)
My heart aches today.
My heart...
aches today.
"SUNMI, I'm sorry, but..."
- Hold on. SUNMI, I'm sorry, but...
- Okay.
"Would you please kick out one person you don't like?"
Among us,
- would you please kick out...
- Okay.
one person you don't like?
- Well...
- It's up to you.
Well,
Yeong Cheol...
(Yeong Cheol)
(He hasn't even said much.)
She's serious, Yeong Cheol.
Yeong Cheol, leave.
There's a reason.
- I...
- Hurry up and leave.
"I'm too annoyed to stay here."
Get up, slap Ho Dong, and sit back down.
- I'm too annoyed to stay here.
- Oh, no. I'm sorry.
(Slapping)
(Mr. Pyongyang Naengmyeon was happy.)
(Angry)
(Overjoyed)
(He returns to his seat in a natural manner.)
- But...
- "Yeong Cheol!"
Yeong Cheol!
- "She told you to leave!"
- She told you to leave!
- I was joking.
- "Then I'll sit back down."
- Then I'll sit back down.
- Firstly,
what's everyone's hobby? Chan Won, what's yours?
On my day off...
"I got out to a square..."
I got out to a square...
- Okay.
- "And sing to beg for money."
And sing to beg for money.
You beg for money. You're a beggar.
I actually like someone who can sing well.
- Really?
- Yes.
I listen to your songs often because I like them.
I see.
"Was it 'At Andong Station?'"
(3 seconds before ruining his chance)
There's a hit song of yours.
Was it "At Andong Station?"
"At Andong Station" by SUNMI?
("At Andong Station" by SUNMI)
On the day the first snow fell, gashina
Aren't those the lyrics?
(She has no idea what to make of this man.)
Well,
- you're wrong.
- Am I wrong?
My song goes...
At Andong Station, gashina
(Laughing)
I see that she's under control as well.
I was mistaken.
- She's funny.
- That's right.
"Dancing is my hobby."
Come out to the front, get down,
and do the butt dance of "24 Hours."
- Dancing is my hobby.
- Okay.
I see.
Oh, no.
Twenty-four hours aren't enough
(Yeong Cheol's hobby might not be suitable for viewing.)
Aren't enough
- "Hey!"
- Hey!
"Do it over there!"
Do it over there!
(He got asked to leave once more.)
(Thank you for stopping me.)
- Mimi Minu, what's your hobby?
- Yes?
"I like to dance."
SUNMI, I like to dance.
- In that case, - Yes?
would you show us?
- "Of course."
- Of course.
(The second dancer comes out with confidence.)
(My dear, before the full moon rises)
(Follow me)
(That's regrettable.)
I'm sorry.
(It was the worst presentation in Mimi Minu's life.)
(He runs away in shame.)
Mimi Minu.
(Mimi Minu left the room.)
I'm sorry. Hurry up and go back in.
(He overcomes shame and returns to the room.)
There are things that make a man likeable in my eyes.
I like men who are good...
at two-line poems and singing.
Two-line poems and singing?
- Yes.
- "I'll give it a go."
I'll give it a go.
- "What kind of a song do you like?"
- What will you show me?
What kind of a song do you like?
I like country music.
- I see. Country music?
- Yes.
"There's a county song I prepared."
There's a county song I prepared.
"I'll sing 'Gimme! Gimme!' by Country Kko Kko."
I'll sing "Gimme! Gimme!" by Country Kko Kko.
Was that a country song?
A country song.
(He showed his sense of humor and flirted with her.)
Maybe today,
- I'll sing a different song.
- Okay.
- "I'll sing 'Maybe Today.'"
- "Maybe Today."
There's a song titled "Maybe Today." Would you like to listen to it?
- I love the idea.
- May I sing it for you?
- Yes.
- Okay.
"I'm sorry, but would you dance?"
I'm sorry, but I have a favor to ask.
Would you be a backup dancer?
(Laughing)
- "Okay, I'll do that."
- A backup dancer?
- Please.
- "Okay, I'll do that."
- I need an appropriate dance.
No. I'm sorry.
Why aren't you following my order?
"Okay, I'll do that."
(He's dying to see his avatar's dance skills.)
- Why...
- My heart aches so much.
- Why is that?
- Do you have painkiller pills?
Seriously, I'm in a bad condition.
- I'll sing a song right away.
- Okay.
(Chan Won's serenade will deliver his sincerity.)
I love it.
I'll sing a song for SUNMI.
It's "Maybe Today." Music, please.
("Maybe Today" by Lee Chan Won)
Get up.
Walk slowly in front of the table.
(Walking slowly)
(He carries out the order without fail.)
(Even the title of the song he chose is perfect for today.)
(Will he be able to captivate SUNMI's heart with a song?)
(I promise)
(An everlasting love)
(With his melodious voice, he predicted a feel-good day.)
- He's good.
- Gosh, you're an amazing singer.
Thank you.
It's an incredible song.
- Really?
- Yes.
It's different from your usual style.
That's right. I prepared it for you, SUMI.
People who listen to the song will become very happy.
"I have a feeling that we'll end up together today."
I don't know how you'll take it,
but I have a feeling that we'll end up together today.
(The serenade boy strikes with another flirtatious comment.)
"SUNMI, I prepared a two-line poem."
- SUNMI, I prepared a two-line poem.
- What?
Mimi Minu, let's check out your two-line poem.
- Please give me the first letters.
- What will they be?
- "Your initials, S and M."
- Your initials, S and M.
Okay. S.
"SUNMI hearts..."
SUNMI hearts...
M.
"Mimi Minu."
Mimi...
- No way.
- It's okay.
- Kyung Hoon.
- Yes?
Why do these avatars keep talking to us?
Who else is confident about his skills in two-line poems?
- Are you confident?
- "I'll give it a go."
- I'll give it a go.
- Okay.
- "I'll give it a go."
- "SUNMI, I fell in love..."
"at first sight."
I'll say the first letters.
Y.
What?
- Yeong Cheol's initials.
- What?
(It's an emergency situation at the control tower.)
Yeong Cheol's initials.
Y.
(The inner self logs out.)
"I'll give a two-line poem with your initials, S and M."
May I give a two-line poem with your initials, S and M?
Of course.
- S.
- "SUNMI, I love you."
SUNMI, I love you.
(The younger man's forward confession sways her.)
- M.
- "Many apologies."
Many apologies.
(Flustered)
(Many apologies...)
(for such an inner self.)
Many apologies.
- Many apologies.
- I...
It's hard to grasp...
what kind of a man Ho Dong is.
"Would you like to have a listen?"
Listen to my inner self.
Go ahead.
Say something.
(His inner self is uncontrollable.)
SUNMI, you must be torn because of these men...
who are full of charms.
- I'm so torn.
- My cafe offers a special service.
You can get a glimpse into these men's inner thoughts.
- Would you like to use the service?
- Very much.
Then drink a cup of this floral tea.
Thank you.
(Then drink a cup of this floral tea.)
It's very pretty.
(A mysterious floral tea)
Will this tea let me see these men's inner thoughts?
It'll let you see their inner thoughts.
- Take a sip.
- Bottoms up.
Afterward, close your eyes.
Close your eyes and count to three.
Get ready. Set, go.
SUNMI, please open your eyes.
- Look around you.
- Hello.
- You must be very surprised.
A Canadian! A comedian!
- I'm Ho Dong.
I'm Yeong Cheol.
- I'm Min Jun.
- SUNMI, you're very pretty.
- You're very pretty.
- You guys look very different.
- We look very different, right?
So this is... I see.
- "SUNMI."
- SUNMI.
- Yes?
- "When you look around..."
- When you look around...
- Yes?
"I'm the most handsome, right?"
I'm the most handsome, right?
(Oh, my!)
Didn't you get married recently?
Should you be here?
"We got a divorce."
We got a divorce.
My goodness.
"It wasn't legal marriage."
It wasn't legal marriage, but common-law marriage.
- "I'm serious about you today."
- I'm serious about you today.
I see.
- You look very cool.
- SUNMI.
"I got a divorce for real."
Here it comes.
- Excuse me.
- Yes?
I...
I got a divorce for real.
Really?
(This avatar has incredible meta-cognition.)
- Did I get fooled?
- Really?
No, you didn't. I'm single now.
- I'm single now.
- You're single now.
But you lied about the last marital status.
"I had no intention to lie."
"Everyone in Korea knows that I'm a divorcee."
(He hears his inner voice from a distance.)
- What?
- Everyone in Korea knows...
- that he's a divorcee.
- I...
Everyone in Korea knows...
- that he's a divorcee.
- That was Jang Hoon's line.
(It's an electrifying moment.)
- But...
- Even my dog knows that.
(He gets his first taste of the avatar blind date.)
- "SUNMI."
- SUNMI.
- "By the way,"
- By the way...
"how about someone who got married twice?"
How about someone who got married twice?
Hold on. Right now,
I'm so confused.
Are you guys the same or different...
inside and out?
"SUNMI, did you just ask..."
"if I was the same or different inside and out?"
SUNMI, did you just ask...
if I was different inside and out?
- That's right.
- "I..."
"Can't you smell it?"
Can't you smell it?
Smell what?
"Actually, my inside stinks."
(Laughing)
Actually, my inside...
- Okay.
- stinks.
"I only believe in my good looks..."
"and clear skin."
I only believe in my good looks...
and clear skin.
Are you the same inside and out?
"Can't you tell?"
Can't you tell?
- "I'm so different inside and out."
- As you know, I'm the outer self...
- and he's the inner self.
- Yes.
We're completely different.
We're practically strangers.
"I'm a piece of garbage."
I'm a total piece of garbage.
- I'm a piece of garbage.
- "Will you be okay with that?"
Why are you laughing? For goodness' sake!
That wasn't an order.
- Hey! I'm a piece of garbage!
- That wasn't an order.
- He's saying whatever he wants.
- What are you going to do about it.
SUNMI, everyone in Korea knows...
that he's a piece of garbage.
Hey!
He got divorced.
- He got remarried.
- "At least..."
- "I don't have a child."
- He broke up.
Everyone in Korea knows that.
Why are you going off on your own?
You should receive orders.
I'm going off on my own.
In that case, have you been...
in many relationships or not?
"SUNMI, did you ask if I was in many relationships?"
Did you ask if I was in many relationships?
- Yes.
- "I'm a total player."
I'm a total player.
"As soon as I was born,"
"I dated the baby girl in the neighboring section."
As soon as I was born,
I dated the baby girl in the neighboring section.
- The neighboring section?
- Yes.
- I'm talking about...
-The incubator?
- the neighboring incubator.
- The incubator.
- I see.
- They put together...
four incubators for him.
He was too big.
(He was born a giant baby.)
Three babies couldn't use the incubators.
- Really?
- Yes.
- He used four all by himself.
- "It's true."
It's true.
(It relieves his pent-up stress.)
In that case,
can you eat your girlfriend's leftover or not?
- "I eat everything."
- I eat everything.
- What?
It doesn't matter what kind of food it is.
- You don't seem that way.
- You're mistaken.
- You're very neat.
- I eat everything.
"I'll show you right now."
I'll show you right now.
(In that case, let's see.)
(Drinking orange juice)
I can drink it.
Oh, my!
(Spitting out)
(This germaphobe faces the biggest challenge of his life.)
"I'll drink it."
Hurry up and say, "I'll drink it."
Hurry up and drink it.
- I...
- He'll drink it.
I'll drink it.
(I'll drink it.)
- Okay.
- "Thank you."
- Thank you.
- "I'll enjoy it."
(She loves his unexpected side.)
- "Thank you."
- I'll enjoy it.
- "Thanks a lot."
- Thanks a lot.
(SUNMI likes Jang Hoon, the man who's thirsty for love.)
Okay.
It's so funny.
Let's go.
(It has to be love!)
I also think...
- a man's luck is important.
- It's important.
Would you consider yourself lucky?
"SUNMI!"
"I'll show you how lucky I am using eggs!"
I'll show you how lucky I am...
using eggs!
- "Give me eggs!"
- Give me eggs!
- What?
- Eggs.
Here are the eggs you ordered.
This drives me crazy.
- "SUNMI,"
- SUNMI,
- "break egg on my forehead."
- break an egg on my forehead.
"Check and see if I'm lucky or not."
Check and see if I'm lucky or not.
If you do it gently, it won't be funny.
- Crash it on his forehead.
- Yes.
"I'm the lucky Seo Jang Hoon."
- I'm the lucky Seo Jang Hoon.
- Are all of those raw eggs?
Really? Can I really do it?
Yes. It's okay.
- Is it really okay?
- "One for me, one for Soo Geun."
- One for me...
- "Let's keep going like that."
- Come on! I'm not Soo Geun.
I'm Chan Won!
Stop with that nonsense.
- I won't do something like that.
- No.
- Let's begin.
- I won't do it.
- All right.
- Do it hard.
- One, two, three.
No way. Please.
- I'm the lucky Seo Jang Hoon.
- Are all of those raw eggs?
Really? Can I really do it?
Yes. It's okay.
- Is it really okay?
- "One for me, one for Soo Geun."
- One for me...
- "Let's keep going like that."
- Come on! I'm not Soo Geun.
I'm Chan Won!
Stop with that nonsense.
- I won't do something like that.
- No.
- Let's begin.
- I won't do it.
- All right.
- Do it hard.
- One, two, three.
No way. Please.
(Breaking)
Are you okay?
(Revenge is in the air!)
- "I love you."
- He isn't very lucky.
I love you.
- That's his luck.
- Are you okay?
- I love you.
- That's his luck.
- Oh, no.
- He's okay.
- I'm okay.
- Oh, no.
I'm okay.
Now, SUNMI got to check...
the dates' inner selves.
It's time for the decision.
Now, the male participants' inner...
and outer selves will fuse.
It's time to fuse.
- Fuse.
- A round of applause.
Now, the inner and outer selves have gathered around.
SUMI, now,
please choose the date...
with the inner and outer selves you liked the most.
- SUNMI, have you decided?
- Yes?
Do you need more time?
I've decided.
Now, please pick the date with the most beautiful..
inner and outer selves.
Gentlemen, please close your eyes.
(The male participants nervously wait to be chosen.)
Please choose one.
(She moves back...)
(and forth.)
Maybe she'll break an egg on someone's forehead.
Now, the inner and outer selves have gathered around.
SUMI, now,
please choose the date...
with the inner and outer selves you liked the most.
- SUNMI, have you decided?
- Yes?
Do you need more time?
I've decided.
Now, please pick the date with the most beautiful..
inner and outer selves.
Gentlemen, please close your eyes.
(The male participants nervously wait to be chosen.)
Please choose one.
(She moves back...)
(and forth.)
Maybe she'll break an egg on someone's forehead.
(She goes to Ho Dong and Jang Hoon.)
SUNMI chose...
(Cheering)
(Oh, my!)
(SUNMI chose Ho Dong and Jang Hoon.)
- Really?
- SUNMI has good tastes.
What's your reason?
Firstly, I like someone with a big build.
- That's right.
- Also, they pursued me...
with the most enthusiasm today.
- That's right.
- That was why...
I chose them.
All right. So that they'll cherish their love...
in an atmospheric way,
- we'll give them a mood lamp.
- Really?
- Really? A mood lamp?
- A mood lamp.
- My goodness.
- He wasn't joking.
- A mood lamp.
- Thank you.
(We'll root for your love.)
Thank you.
How was it to be on the show today?
Being an avid watcher of the show, I've always wanted to visit.
Thank you for the opportunity to be on the show. I had so much fun.
This is the seventh episode of Men on a Mission...
I've been on.
If there's another good opportunity,
I'd like to join you guys again.
I enjoyed myself fully today.
Thank you so much for inviting me today.
- "Maybe Today."
- SUNMI.
- Yes.
- The virgin ghost.
I had a fun day with the Men on a Mission members.
I always want to see you guys.
Thank you so much.
"CYNICAL."
- There isn't...
- That's right.
a bigger present.
Please invite me whenever a seat next to Ho Dong's is empty.
- All right.
- Thank you.
With your cool music and performances,
please give us good energy!
- Yes!
Forever!
(ALLDAY PROJECT, ANNIE, TARZZAN, BAILEY, WOOCHAN, and YOUNGSEO)
(The mixed-gender group that rose as the K-pop trendsetter)
(They finally came to the Brother School.)
(TARZZAN is a dancer from Ulsan.)
(Being from Ulsan, he uses a dialect.)
(Is it on fire?)
(The Gyeongsang natives become one through the dialect.)
(The genius choreographer, BAILEY)
(A legendary choreographer for Taeyang, Red Velvet, aespa, etc.)
(A special connection between Santa WOOCHAN and Soo Geun?)
(I was Soo Geun's rap teacher.)
(Soo Geun doesn't remember.)
(Because of Soo Geun, I want to be nice...)
(to younger people.)
(His punchline destroys Soo Geun)
(YOUNGSEO, is there a special story?)
(I don't think so.)
(A project to destroy Soo Geun)
(Has everyone been to ANNIE's house?)
(We went there and ate ramyeon.)
(Invite us too.)
(We'll eat ramyeon and leave.)
(ANNIE, we're here to eat ramyeon.)
(For ALLDAY PROJECT, the variety show newbies,)
(the special variety show camp begins.)
(They rack their brains...)
(and fail.)
(Nonsenses...)
(and mistakes run rampant!)
(I thought you had a good short-term memory.)
(You just need to do it like this.)
(I'm sorry, okay?)
(She isn't a bad girl, but no teasing is allowed.)
(The ALLDAY variety show PROJECT is ready!)
(Men on a Mission)
("Say My Name" by MIYEON of i-dle)