- Who says I won't come?
- That's right.
I'm right here.
- Have you guys been well?
- Yes.
We sent Shin Dong cheerful words last week. He watched it.
(While taking time off work,)
(I hope Shin Dong dates someone. From Kyung Hoon)
(The second period without Shin Dong is meaningless. From Soo Geun)
(On exciting Saturdays,)
(we need Shin Dong.)
(Shin Dong, come back soon.)
Shin Dong was touched and sent us a video letter.
- Where is he? Hey, Shin Dong.
- Hey.
Look at him. He seems much better now.
- Exactly.
- Everyone, are you doing well?
I've been doing great.
Don't worry about me.
I will be back on the show soon.
Please wait for Senior Dong.
I'll appear in Part Two very soon.
Guys, I'll be right back.
What? He got his eyebrows tattooed.
Will he perhaps show up later in the second period today?
He looks better now.
- Indeed. Right?
- Shin Dong, come back soon.
Shin Dong, I won't be your partner. So come back.
- He needs to rest now.
- It's more tiring than you think.
- No one listens to him.
- Hwang Soo Kyung.
- What?
- Soo Kyung found it stressful too.
- What was that?
- It's Yoon Su Il's song.
- What's going on?
- Is that an automatic door?
- What? Oh, my.
- My goodness.
- Who ordered Winter Games?
- Seong Jae is here.
- Did any of you order Winter Games?
Oh, my. What's going on?
- We ordered it.
- What did we order?
Hey, newlywed groom.
Seong Jae is here.
A newlywed groom and a newlywed bride are here.
(The transfer students came as the Winter Games began.)
- Oh, Seung Hi is here too.
- The gold medalist is here.
Hi.
- Hey, Yoon Gy.
- Yoon Gy.
- We see you too often.
- Yoon Gy...
- Yoon Gy has come here before.
- It hasn't been so long.
Seong Jae and Seung Hi have never been here before.
- That's right.
From which school did you transfer?
Hi. We're from United Through Sports High School.
My voice is my only talent. I'm Bae Seong Jae.
- Oh, my.
- He has a great voice.
I became busier after retiring.
I'm the gold medal level that girl, Park Seung Hi.
- Park Seung Hi.
- I'm Kwak Yoon Gy,
the master of celebration move.
(The perfect transfer students for the Winter Games theme)
Yoon Gy, you seem strange with that hair color.
Can you go and dye your hair again?
Why didn't you prepare a wig for me?
- Exactly.
- That was his signature hair color.
- That's right.
- They all are Soo Geun's friends.
- Really?
I worked with Seong Jae and Seung Hi.
And Yoon Gy is a member of the SPC.
- Oh, small...
- What does SPC stand for?
- He's the smartest one.
- Small People Club.
- Oh, SPC?
You worked with Seong Jae for a long time.
- For over four years.
- Oh, "Shooting Stars?"
- That's right.
- I commentated on games...
- in which Seung Hi played.
- He contributed a lot to the show.
- That's right.
- We were on the show together.
Yes. On "Shooting Stars," Soo Geun and I...
- You've been working together.
- commentated on games together.
Among all those whom I worked with as a sportscaster,
he's most comfortable to work with.
- Really?
- What's the reason?
- In what aspect?
- He worked very hard...
- as a commentator.
- That's right.
He kept making a prediction.
"I think they will score a goal this time."
- But they didn't.
- Wait. He made predictions?
- Did he bet money on the games?
- No.
I make predictions because I take after my mom.
Oh, that's right. His mother is...
- a great shaman.
- It's because of shamanism.
- "Because of shamanism?"
- That's not true.
Rain believes in "Rainism" while I believe in shamanism.
Shamanism
How long has Seong Jae been working freelance?
I've been a freelancer for five years.
- It's been a long time.
- That long?
- I'm a little upset with him.
- Oh, I see.
It's very common for an announcer to appear on Men on a Mission...
- after going freelance.
- That's right.
- Right.
- I'm sure...
- he hated to see one of us.
- That makes sense.
- Why didn't you come on the show?
- To be honest,
all of you made me feel like it was too much for me.
Especially Yeong Cheol...
- Me?
- drained my energy...
- whenever I met him.
- Oh, really?
I'm a bit of a quiet type.
- Both Yeong Cheol and Soo Geun...
- Right.
- drained all my energy.
- I see.
I needed to rest in the bed for two days.
We shared a green room as well.
Because Seong Jae said he hated working with me,
- I had to leave the show.
- That's not true.
- Is that why you left the show?
- He seemed happy when I quit.
- I heard that.
- That's not true.
- I cried.
- I quit overnight after five years.
No. I cried when I heard you would quit.
So the rumor that Seong Jae influenced his decision was true.
- No. That's not true.
- Exactly.
I text Soo Geun often...
- to say I miss him.
- I know.
- To say sorry to him?
- No, not that.
- To say that I miss him.
- "I'm sorry I made you quit."
- No. I swear that it's not true.
- "I'm sorry I got you fired."
What did you like about him?
- And what did you hate about him?
- You mean, Soo Geun?
- Tell us one at a time.
- He got him.
- What did you like about him?
- Soo Geun?
You got him fired because he drained your energy.
- Seong Jae said they should...
- Exactly. Now...
- fire one of him and Soo Geun.
- No.
- Stay calm.
- That's not true.
They won't stop until you say he made you uncomfortable.
- This will end only if you say so.
- But I mean...
- Right. Let's end this.
- Right.
I didn't say anything.
When I met the director, I made this gesture.
- Oh, I see.
- "Fire him."
- You made that gesture?
- This gesture would be enough...
- to fire someone. Absolutely.
- It's done now.
- I gave a hand signal.
- You didn't have to say anything.
I didn't want to speak on the phone to avoid leaving proof.
You two won the Best Couple Award...
- and worked together for long.
- Yes.
Did you know he was in a relationship?
I knew that.
- You knew?
- What?
- I heard no one knew.
- Seung Hi, did you know?
- Actually...
- You didn't know, Soo Geun?
Seong Jae created quite a twist.
- Right.
- When we worked together,
you spoke badly of your wife.
When did I do that?
Did he speak badly of his wife?
He criticized her soccer skills and said she didn't practice enough.
- Right. You told me that.
- Right. He told me such things.
- Really?
- On a cold winter day...
- I said, - He criticized her soccer skills?
"We should keep her on our team..."
- "even though she's not skillful."
- You didn't know about them.
- Wait. Hold on.
- When I said she should play,
he said we shouldn't let her play because she's not good at it.
- Unlike those words he said...
- Yes?
- So you didn't know about them?
- In front of us,
he criticized his wife,
but he was being all lovey-dovey with her behind our backs.
"You understand why I had to act like that, right?"
- That's what he did then.
- Then his wife...
- It was a smokescreen strategy.
- That means...
- he was seeing her even then?
- He deceived us. Yes.
When I was with the others... How should I put it?
- Right.
- I'm getting choked up.
I had no idea.
- He's flustered.
- I tried not to let it show.
One time, during a soccer game,
- she fell hard.
- Right.
Since I have a lot of experience as a sportscaster,
when I see a player falling down,
I can tell whether or not the player can continue playing.
When I saw her falling down,
- I thought she shouldn't play.
- You didn't care...
if the other players fell down or not.
- Back then, Seong Jae...
- Exactly. I played full-time.
- You played full-time?
- He didn't care about Seung Hi.
When he said she should be helpful to the team...
You said when he criticized her,
you talked badly of her too.
I talked badly of her too, of course.
I feel bad... I'm sorry, Da Yeong.
I did that because I didn't know about them.
- But...
- So that's why he got you fired.
- He hosted a radio show and all.
- Oh, you're right.
- He was very busy then.
- "How dare he criticize my wife?"
- That's probably why he did this.
- "I'll get him fired."
- He was the same as Kyung Hoon.
- He had a reason.
- We didn't know about him either.
- Right.
- Right. We had no idea.
- His wife would sit over there.
They must've given each other a lot of signals secretly.
- We really had no idea.
- That must've been so fun.
He danced so passionately then.
You know that, right?
Think of how different he was...
- when his wife was here.
- Really?
- Seriously, none of us knew.
- None of us knew.
- But now...
- None of us knew. Really.
- Exactly.
- Back then,
- I was trying to impress her.
- We didn't know.
(I was trying to impress her.)
That's why I danced passionately.
- Yoon Gy, it's awkward.
- Now you only dance professionally?
- Give Soo Geun your transfer form.
- Okay.
- Right.
- We haven't met Yoon Gy in a while.
I feel most comfortable around you.
- Right, Yoon Gy?
- We have the same eye level.
Exactly.
- Yoon Gy, let's hurry up and go.
- What?
(Imitating skating sounds)
Come on.
Here you go.
(Combined)
I remember that.
- Yoon Gy told us before.
- Right, he did.
- He could see behind him...
- You see...
- He said he could see the face.
- That's right.
- That was a long time ago.
- Seeing Soo Geun with Yoon Gy,
Soo Geun seemed very tall.
- I told you so.
- Exactly.
- Among small people...
- Is Soo Geun taller than me?
- Of course.
- Hey.
- How tall are you?
- I can't believe him.
- Your height...
- How tall are you, Soo Geun?
- Stand next to each other.
- I'm 165cm tall.
- He's a bit taller than me.
- Right. He's taller than you.
- Come over here.
- He seemed much taller than you.
- Soo Geun seems taller than him.
- Soo Geun is much taller than him.
I'm much taller than him.
- Do you want to keep your shoes on?
- He seems taller than you.
- Walk past me.
- That's okay. I can feel it.
- Right? You can feel it, don't you?
- Don't come near him.
I can feel the difference even from afar.
- You can feel it?
- Hey.
- Gosh. I'm dumbfounded.
- He looks much taller than you.
- Hey, I hang out with Jang Hoon.
- Wait. But this is...
- There's a big difference.
- Will you be okay?
We can stand side by side to be compared.
There's no difference.
- I see no difference now.
- They're almost the same height.
No. That's because of their hairstyles.
- Soo Geun is taller than him.
- They're the same height.
But I have good body proportions.
- As for body proportions...
- We both are small.
But your legs are this short.
- Check out my waist.
- But...
Your waist is down here.
(The secret to his victory is his long legs.)
- Those small guys are so funny.
- Soo Geun really is taller than me.
- Soo Geun's legs...
- But you have such muscular legs.
Why would we compare our heights?
- It's pointless.
- Indeed.
- It's completely pointless, right?
- Yes.
The transfer form to Men on a Mission.
Names, Bae Seong Jae, Kwak Yoon Gy, and Park Seung Hi.
Welcome!
- It's good to see you again.
- It's nice to meet you all.
First up is the peer relations.
It says they met one another through sports commentary.
- Through sports commentary.
- Do both of you...
have a connection with Seong Jae?
- Can you explain to us?
- Yes. Seung Hi and I commentated...
on the short track games at the Beijing Winter Games.
And I'll work with Yoon Gy this time.
We'll commentate on short track games in Milan.
- So you'll go to Milan?
- Yes.
I guess he's not just good at commentating on soccer games.
- He's good with every sport.
- I found out...
that Seong Jae was a sportscaster,
- and the others are commentators.
- We're commentators.
Is there a big difference between those two?
A sportscaster adds liveliness to a sports commentary...
- by describing the situations.
- That's right.
And commentators who used to be great athletes...
use their expert knowledge...
- to analyze the situations.
- They provide analysis.
- We explain what's happening.
- That's right.
- We also provide information...
- So you...
- about players.
- Basically...
I'll give you a simple example.
For example, which one would say,
"Min Kyung Hoon passed the ball to Kim Hee Chul?"
- That'd be Seong Jae.
- A sportscaster would say that.
"In a situation like that,"
"you shouldn't pass the ball in that direction."
- Right.
- A commentator would say that.
- So an expert explains...
- Right.
Oh, that's why Jang Hoon is the commentator on "Divorce Camp."
- Gosh, seriously.
- He's an expert.
- Park Ha Sun and the others...
- That's a precise comparison.
- I see. I get it now.
- You see...
- Very precise.
- He's smart.
All commentaries are delivered out of experience.
- That's why he's the chairman.
- That's right.
- I didn't realize that.
- Experience.
- That's not a precise comparison.
- You can't explain without it.
- That's not exactly the case.
- Hee Chul is right.
I'm both the sportscaster and the commentator on that show.
Because the others have no experience.
- Okay. I understand now.
- He fulfills all requirements.
Yoon Gy, is this your first time being a commentator?
This is my first time.
So I'm very nervous.
I commentated...
- for the Sochi Winter Games.
- Yes, you did.
- The Sochi Winter Games?
- He commentated on speed skating.
- I did it because... So I saw...
- So...
Lee Sang Hwa win the gold medal.
- Since it was a live broadcast, - So I...
he only shouted during the games to avoid making mistakes.
- I only said some filler words.
- Right.
I remember how Ho Dong commentated on that game.
- It was 12 years from now.
- That's right.
He commentated on the game where Lee Sang Hwa won the gold medal.
How should I put it? He commentated on the game...
as a former athlete, not as an entertainer.
- And that was really cool.
- But that disappointed many people.
- They expected a fun commentary.
- Because he's an entertainer now.
- I see. I guess he was too serious.
- They expected something different.
People said he should never have done it...
- if he was going to do it that way.
- Exactly.
He was hired because he was expected to be funny.
- But for Winter Games...
- Why did they hire a TV celebrity?
- They hired him to make it fun.
- You shouldn't try to be funny...
when it comes to Winter Games.
- But back then...
- Then Ho Dong,
- Imagine the tension.
- you should've refused to do it.
- Why did you even do it?
- I refused at first.
- You should've made it fun.
- Right.
- You should know better than that.
I'll see how well you commentate.
- Yoon Gy will be too pressured.
- I'll see how well you do, Yoon Gy.
- Seong Jae.
- Yoon Gy will overdo it.
- I'll deliver a fun commentary.
- He'll overdo it.
Seong Jae, how well do you expect Korea will do in the Winter Games?
How well will Korea do?
- Korea is very good at short track.
- They will win some medals.
- So we need them...
- To win some medals.
to win many gold medals so that Korea's ranking goes up.
That's right.
- I expect four gold medals.
- Four gold medals?
- Four or more would be great.
- That would be really great.
- That would be so great.
- I hope so too.
How many gold medals can be won...
- in short track speed skating?
- In short track speed skating...
- Nine gold medals can be won.
- How many events are there?
- How many events...
- Nine.
There are 2 in the 500m, 1,000m, 1,500m.
- And relays.
- Also 3,000m and 5,000m.
- And a mixed team relay.
- And one in a mixed team relay.
I thought you were talking about the amount of your debt left to pay.
You went on, "3,000 and 5,000..."
- I thought he borrowed more money.
- It went down a lot.
- That makes sense.
- He said, "3,000 and 5,000..."
Also... Although I won't commentate on the event,
- in snowboarding, - Right.
- Korea will likely win some medals.
- That's right.
Not many Koreans know this, but there are snowboarding events...
- Halfpipe.
- like halfpipe...
Korean athletes who will participate in those events...
- are expected to win a gold medal.
- Right.
- That's great.
- There are great snowboarders.
There are 1 man and 1 woman, who are both teenagers.
- They're very young.
- Yes.
I watched the halfpipe games in the world championship recently.
- I watched Lee Chae Un's games.
- Right.
He performed really well.
And it felt as if the other players...
had already given up on defeating him...
because they knew he'd do well. That was the atmosphere there.
- That's cool.
- It made me...
expect him to win a medal.
If he wins a gold medal in halfpipe, he'll be the first.
- Really?
- The first Korean to do so.
- It's an incredible achievement.
- Indeed.
- Curling also draws attention too.
- That's right.
- As for curling...
- Is Korea a major contender?
You should consider the team as a major contender.
Korea is good at target sports like archery and curling.
- Right.
- Korea is good at target sports.
(The national team players to play in women's events and mixed double)
We'll have to wait and see how it goes,
- but if they win 1 or 2 medals, - They'll be in the top 3?
- it will help Team Korea...
- They'll do well.
- We'll find out about them 1 by 1.
- I hope so.
First up is Seong Jae. He wrote, "veteran sportscaster."
- Well, we have to admit that.
- His family name is Bae.
- He joined SBS as an announcer...
- That's right.
- to start his career.
- Yes.
But I saw him wearing a headset more than him hosting a news show.
That image comes in my head first.
I've been mostly working as a sportscaster.
I rarely do a variety show.
I mostly commentate on sports games or host a radio show.
- So I always wear a headset.
- Right.
Seong Jae, how long have you been working as a sportscaster?
I've been doing it since 2008,
- so this year is the 19th year.
- It's been almost 19 years.
But Seong Jae, you didn't join SBS...
- as a sportscaster.
- That's right.
You joined SBS as an announcer.
Did someone recommend the job or did you want to do it?
I became an announcer...
without any plans or preparation.
I took the exam in my senior year in college, and I passed it.
After that, I had to decide what to do as an announcer.
Back then, it was called the announcer-tainer era.
- The announcer-tainer era.
- Many announcers did variety shows.
But I didn't think variety shows suited me...
because I wasn't funny.
Since I had been a huge fan of sports since I was little,
I thought I could be a sportscaster.
Back then, only senior announcers commentated for sports events.
But SBS gave me an opportunity even though I was a rookie.
So I tried it, and the result was good.
- I've been doing it ever since.
- You continued doing it.
So the network offered you the opportunity first?
Yes. They selected sportscasters among the SBS announcers...
through auditions for two years.
- You competed in an audition?
- Yes.
If you've been a sportscaster for 19 years,
how many times did you participate in Summer and Winter Games?
- "Participate?"
- No, I mean...
- He meant, "commentate."
- Right, "commentate."
- That's an athlete's point of view.
- Right.
This is my 5th time in Winter Games, and I did 5 times in Summer Games.
So ten times in total.
(He has commentated for Summer and Winter Games 10 times.)
- It's held every two years.
- He has a lot of experience.
- How many times did you go?
- He's already a living legend.
- Let's not talk about that.
- I'll do it for another 20 years.
- There's the World Cup too.
- That's right.
And the Asian Games too.
- When you commentate on a game, - He's the king of sports.
- you watch it in person.
- That's right.
I think there are many good things about being a sportscaster.
- The network sends me there.
- That's right.
- You can watch it in person.
- Yes. I'm supposed to pay for it.
But I get paid, and I get to watch it...
- in the best spot.
- That's a great benefit.
I shout and cheer while commentating on the game.
- I practically have fun.
- Right.
You do your work and make money from it.
- You get a good spot too.
- Ho Dong wanted that too, but...
(Shouting, screaming, and exclaiming)
All he did was shout.
- But I saw Ho Dong...
- Shouldn't Ho Dong...
- crying while watching the game.
- give back the money?
- Did he cry?
- Yes.
Seong Jae was touched by my sincerity.
- He had to do something.
- Right. He had to do something.
He had already been paid, but he was like...
"Oh, goodness. What do I do?"
(Crying)
- He cried because he was worried.
- Exactly.
- He thought he was in trouble.
- The game ended.
The 500m event ends in a blink of an eye.
- That's true.
- Right.
It feels as if it ended within three seconds.
- It ends within 45 seconds.
- It's a little over 30 seconds.
I was afraid I might disturb the players.
So I had to be very careful.
But before the game, I talked a lot.
- Also, Ho Dong...
- I see. It ended very quickly.
is always careful doing everything.
- I guess he was extra careful.
- But still...
"One, two! Keep going!"
- You could've cheered for them.
- Right. He could've done it.
- "Go, Lee Sang Hwa! One, two!"
- Exactly.
Baby Sang Hwa, doo, doo, doo, doo
- "Run! Go!" You could've done it.
- But hey...
- The viewers must've laughed.
- You think...
- You think you could do that...
- That's why you were hired.
- in a final match of Winter Games?
- Of course. You should've done it.
Really? Then show me how you do it.
- I didn't get any opportunities.
- Right.
- I can commentate on a soccer game.
- You were hired to do it.
- No, that's not true.
- "One, two!"
- At least sing "Baby Sang Hwa."
- "Baby Sang Hwa."
- The athletes waited four years...
- Baby Sang Hwa, doo, doo, doo, doo
for the moment of the final match.
You can't even imagine the weight of seriousness.
You wouldn't dare speak in that moment.
(He felt the weight of time spent and was careful about what he said.)
How do you get paid?
For the whole project or per event?
- Oh, I'm curious about that.
- I'm curious about it too.
- I'm curious.
- I went freelance recently.
- You were an employee.
- Before that, it was included...
in my monthly salary.
As a freelancer, I get paid for a whole competition.
- Oh, I see.
- Not per event.
- You sign for a whole competition?
- Yes.
- So they work me to the bone.
- You earn about 500,000 dollars?
- What did you say?
- Are you paid 500,000 dollars?
- No.
- Seong Jae, you are...
the main sportscaster at this Winter Games.
How many events do you commentate on?
It's similar to the past Winter Games.
I host the opening and closing ceremonies.
And I commentate on short track and speed skating.
I can't commentate on many events.
There are so many games in short track and speed skating.
- I can't do anything else.
- Really? Why?
Yoon Gy, why are you surprised?
Short track and speed skating games...
- are held every other day.
- If they overlap?
That means you work every day.
- Yes. I have to.
- Every day?
- You work every day.
- Only I work every day.
You've been working your tail off since you went freelance.
- Yes. They work me to the bone.
- To make money you couldn't earn...
- I practically get locked up.
- No wonder why...
everyone at SM Culture and Contents came here earlier.
I saw them all here.
- Surprised, I said hello to them.
- That's not the case.
- He came here to make more money.
- Winter Games and World Cup...
For Seong Jae, these sports events...
are huge opportunities, not adversity.
- Jang Hoon is right.
- It's a huge opportunity for him.
What's the hardest sport to commentate on?
- The hardest sports are...
- I think short track is hard.
- Right.
- soccer and short track.
- I think it's difficult.
- Short track is difficult.
When the viewers find the rules of a sport tricky,
it's easy for us to commentate on it.
We just have to explain the rules for most of the time.
But in soccer, for example,
players fight for the ball...
- without many clear rules.
- Right.
- What matters is making a goal.
- Yes.
That's why explaining the tactics isn't easy.
In short-track speed skating, the disqualifications are unclear.
- Totally.
- Explaining the reason...
- True.
- for disqualification is tough.
- Right.
- There should be...
clear criteria.
But at times, the player who arrives first...
- gets disqualified.
- Yes.
- Exactly.
- It's really...
Now, it's easier to tell the reason.
In the past, a certain amount of hustle was allowed.
But now, the player who starts the hustle gets disqualified.
- Then...
- Yes?
the hustle at the start might get worse.
- The start hustle...
- The players must make way.
- Really?
- The faster player must push ahead.
- Yes.
- There will barely be any hustles.
Try a hustle, and that player...
- Right.
- will be monitored again.
What about golden sayings? You know, like famous quotations.
No, I'm the type who refrains from using golden sayings.
Once I start saying famous quotations,
- Yes?
- people expect more.
That won't help my career last long.
Does Seong Jae not have any famous sayings?
- Among the ones by Seong Jae...
- Tell us some.
- that I've heard, - Yes?
isn't the Germany karaoke saying famous?
Did you go to karaoke in Germany?
No. During the Russia World Cup,
we were up against Germany...
and won, which was called the Miracle of Kazan.
- Right.
- Yes.
The game was about to end 1-0,
but about five minutes of additional time were added.
"What's going on? Are we at a karaoke?" was what I said.
- Because of the additional time?
- I get it.
- The extra time.
- The additional time?
Additional time was added out of the blue.
- That's a famous saying.
- Adding time on top...
of an existing one got me upset.
Wasn't there another one during the match with Sweden?
We also had a match with Sweden back then.
Sweden was winning 1-0, but the Swedish players...
- wouldn't get up.
- The so-called bed soccer.
They were playing bed soccer.
As Sweden is known for their furniture brand,
I said, "Is this a commercial for IKEA or what?"
Are you allowed to make comments like that?
- I just...
- He does it.
Seong Jae hits the spot...
- of the viewers.
- Exactly.
- He's a pro at knowing what to say.
- Yes.
Here's what I want to know. I don't know much about soccer.
But when I watch the games, the sportscaster knows...
- the names of all players.
- I know, right?
At times, they even say the last name.
- Do you study their names?
- There must be long names too.
Sportscasters don't only cover the World Cup.
Normally, players who are considered good in famous leagues,
like the European leagues, take part in the World Cup.
To sportscasters covering the leagues, they know the players.
The toughest moment would be...
- the preliminaries held in Asia.
- I see.
There are players we're not familiar with.
- Of course.
- For example, Vietnamese players...
or Thai players.
Seong Jae had posted something on social media.
Can you zoom in on it?
He has to mention the names of the players passing the ball.
Do you have all the names in your head, Seong Jae?
Yes, I memorized the names of the starters.
- Really?
- Yes.
But all of them have uniform numbers.
- The names are...
- Seong Jae,
read the names as if you're covering a game.
Where? I can't even read any.
- Hey.
- The pronunciations are hard.
Korea is playing against Laos right now.
- Laos?
- Come on, let's watch it.
- Turn on the TV. It's on.
- The game is on.
(World Cup Asia Preliminary, Korea versus Laos)
Here's Laos' starting lineup.
Phoutpasong Sengdalavong, Sengphachan Bounthisanh,
Vanhasith Thilavongsa, Khamla Pinkeo,
Khamphoumy Hanevilay, Moukda Souksavath,
Oudomsith Singla, Phoumai Souvandee,
Saynakhonevieng Phommapanya,
Thotnilath Sibounhuang,
- Keoviengphet Liththideth, - Gosh.
Khonsavanh Sihavong, Manolom Phomsouvanh,
- Paseuthsack Souliyavong, - Goodness.
Phouthone Innalay, Phoutthasay Khochalern,
Souksakhone Bountathip, Tiny Bounmalay,
Chanthaphone Waenvongsoth,
Khampheng Sayavutthi, Sitthideth Khanthavong,
Souk Aphone Vongchiengkham,
and Soukchinda Natphasouk.
- To actually read that?
- Amazing.
(A stunt-like lineup announcement)
- It was like a debate.
- Gosh.
- That was incredible.
- Try it, Yoon Gy.
- Go ahead.
- It's not easy.
Ready? You must say it fast.
Set, go.
Phoutpasong Sanglangdavong,
Sengphipang Bounthisanh,
- Vanhasith Thilavongsa, - It's tough.
- None is right.
- Khamla Pinkeo,
- Khamphoumy...
- Enough.
- Stop.
- Thank you to everyone...
who has tuned in.
- Bye.
- It's hard.
- It ended while reading the names.
- Listen.
You know, Lee Soo Geun?
- The comedian.
- The comedian?
He's one of the guest commentators.
Here's Laos' starting lineup.
Phoutpasong Sengdalavong, Sengphachan Bounthisanh,
Vanhasith Thilavongsa, Khamla Pinkeo,
Khamphoumy Hanevilay,
Moukda Souksavath,
and the coach is Cha Bum Kun.
- Cha Bum Kun?
- Hold on.
- The names...
- Are you just pushing ahead?
- That was him...
- Yes.
just now reading off the list. The problem is...
During passes, right?
- True.
- when the players...
- pass the ball...
- The names must be said instantly.
or when there's a foul. He has to have the name memorized.
- Exactly.
- That's the tough part.
Did you ever make a mistake?
Even if I make a mistake with names,
- the viewers don't catch it.
- We wouldn't.
Did you ever get a Korean player's name mixed up?
I sometimes did get them mixed up.
When the players are running around...
- You can't catch them right away.
- No.
- I miss the uniform number.
- Right.
It doesn't matter much when the ball is being passed.
But it'd be bad if I mixed up the names at an eventful moment,
- like when a goal has been scored.
- Exactly.
- Then...
- Mistaking the player who scored?
- The timing...
- Here's what I heard.
Some uniforms shine and are easy to read.
Totally.
But the numbers on some uniforms are similar in color,
- Exactly.
- making it hard to read.
Like is it an 8 or a 9?
- The sports legend gets it.
- Yes.
Weirdly enough,
- Right.
- current sports uniforms...
are focused on design and less on distinguishing players.
The font of the numbers changes.
The numbers are hard to tell...
if the uniform is red while the number is black.
- If it's dark.
- In the past, it was white.
Are there times when you burst into laughter mid-coverage?
- Did you ever make a blunder?
- We had...
a player named Kim Shin Wook.
- He was super tall.
- I remember.
- During the Incheon Game.
- Yes.
Kim Shin Wook had an aerial duel with the opposing team's goalkeeper.
Just when he was about to score with a header,
the goalkeeper had already caught the ball.
But as Kim Shin Wook is a big player,
- the goalkeeper was pushed...
- Together?
into the goalpost with the ball.
It was so funny back then that I couldn't...
- continue.
- Is that considered a goal?
- What?
- It's a foul play.
- A foul play.
- Was your laughter broadcast?
I said, "Isn't it two goals,"
"as he scored both the goalkeeper and the goal?" Before I knew it...
It's fine to laugh if it's funny.
- Totally.
- Yes.
- People get it.
- Seong Jae knows when to laugh.
In Europe, when a goal is scored, the commentator is like,
- "Score!"
- South America.
- It's no joke in South America.
- Is it South America?
- Argentina and such.
- Spain too, right?
South America, North and Central America.
- Countries like Mexico.
- The energy is different.
- Score!
- For real.
- Just like that.
(Score! It's a score!)
(The sportscaster has a larger lung capacity than the players.)
- It lasts for a minute.
- For real, a minute.
They say "score" for a minute.
- True.
- Really?
Score!
How long they can shout is the South American sportscasters' pride.
- Really?
- How long they can shout?
Yes, the longer, the better.
It's similar to "And it goes out."
(And it's a score!)
- Let's move on to Seung Hi.
- Next is Seung Hi.
- Seung Hi wrote, - Gosh.
"A talkative commentator."
Correct. I love talking.
Simply put, I love being a mood maker.
That's why I talk more.
Seung Hi repeats the same thing 2 to 3 times.
If something happens,
she's like, "Why? Why should I do it? Why?"
"What are we doing today? What? And why?"
She won't stop talking.
I often spoke up for the players.
You're like Kim Yeong Cheol.
I say things 2 to 3 times.
I'm not that bad.
- She hates being compared.
- No.
- You're not as bad as Yeong Cheol.
- But she likes talking.
- I'm not that bad.
- You talk way too much.
- You're not that bad?
- No.
You talk too much.
- When covering, it's better...
- Yes?
- to talk more than less, right?
- Of course.
- Yes.
- Totally.
Doing the coverage with her was great.
Most of the time, people remember...
the legendary scenes of sports games.
What the commentators shout...
during those important moments is mostly memorable.
But there are many boring moments too.
The repeated boring moments lead to one eventful moment.
Even during those boring moments, Seung Hi keeps talking.
- She does, right?
- I can't stand...
those silent moments.
- So I talk.
- Here's what Seung Hi is good at.
Seung Hi makes a guess of the next move,
- and it actually happens.
- Exactly.
Yes, I made many predictions.
- Right?
- "The player should..."
"Here they are!"
- And it happens.
- Yes.
Like an avatar blind date?
Here's what I realized about great commentators.
In sports, the situation keeps changing with time.
The coverage should change too.
But if the commentator doesn't move on...
- and talks about the old scene...
- I get it.
The scene has already changed.
Knowing when to stop and move on is important.
But to some commentators, it may be new.
So they'd keep talking in the next scene.
At times like that, Seong Jae cuts us off.
- In the past, Seong Jae...
- He stops us.
- He's a pro.
- Yes.
Wasn't there a time when Seong Jae had to pull...
a commentator down as he got too excited?
- I remember.
- Wasn't it Jaegal Sung Yeol?
- Yes, Jaegal Sung Yeol.
- As one...
- of his juniors made a good record, - Yes?
Jaegal Sung Yeol went out of frame.
So I had to pull him down...
- to his seat.
- Right?
Seong Jae pulls the commentators back in.
In the Olympics' broadcasting booth, we have a webcam.
- There's a camera...
- You can see us...
- that is shooting us.
- through the camera.
But if you stand up,
- your head will get cut out.
- It will get cut out.
So I kept making him sit down.
I should be careful. But I don't get cut when I stand up.
It's okay.
- That's right.
- For us...
- It's okay for him.
- For me and Soo Geun,
- it doesn't matter, - He really can fit.
no matter what we do.
- It's fine for them.
- Right?
How low does it get?
- He's always within the angle.
- Yes.
You’re a god-given commentator.
That's right.
Seung Hi, I heard that your nickname...
used to be "the tough guy for China."
Yes.
She really was the tough guy for China.
What does that mean?
We had an extremely intense...
- rivalry with the Chinese players.
- Sure.
- In the past.
- It was always like that.
One time, I was sick of it,
so as I was going to the track...
There's a really famous skater in China, Wang Meng.
She was the best for a long time.
I had a fight with her in the ice rink.
If you see the video clip, it looks like we're swearing.
I saw it happen, and...
He saw it from the side.
You could tell that they were fighting right there.
- Everyone came running to us.
- We were all worried,
and we ran up to stop them.
Since we had to stop the fight.
We went up, and it was really petty...
- and childish.
- We fought nicely.
"Why are you using your hands?"
"If you use your hands, it's dangerous for me."
- That's how she was fighting.
- Yes.
And it was the same with the Chinese athlete.
But the important thing is, I was using Korean,
and she was using Chinese.
- They were exchanging emotions.
- We can feel it, though.
She's mad, and I'm mad.
We could only feel the emotions,
but if you see the video, it looks very intense.
Then they stopped us, so it was over.
If a former athlete becomes a commentator,
I think you would be more emotionally engaged than others.
- It should be so much more.
- It must feel like you're there,
- and when they are being unfair...
- Yes.
When it wasn't foul play, but the referee said so.
I think that would be the hard part.
The perspective of an athlete...
- And the viewers.
- and that of the viewers...
could be completely different.
- What do you think, as the viewer?
- When it becomes emotional.
- Do you like it when we get mad?
- We swear while watching TV.
- Sure.
- Yes.
- Really?
- We get mad, as well.
And you need to do the swearing for us, Yoon Gy.
- The swearing?
- Sure.
- I told him to try swearing.
- That's what we need.
You need to think of it as your last time.
How long do you expect to do that?
And for us,
we don't really know if the judge is being fair...
or not.
- So we rely on the commentators.
- That's how we know.
Then what should we have done then?
During the Beijing Winter Games,
since Seung Hi was the tough guy for China...
At first, there were some unfair rulings.
- Since it was held in Beijing.
- Yes.
- We got so mad, - Yes.
but during those times, they weren't saying anything.
- We just become speechless.
- It seemed like they couldn't...
- vent out their emotions, - Yes.
but just held it in.
So I had to do all the talking.
Did you ever lose your temper, Seong Jae?
I do sometimes,
- but I still...
- Can you control it?
I think he thinks of it as someone else's problem.
- Is that why?
- That's why...
- He just needs to get paid.
- That's what it feels like.
That's how he thinks of it, so he can control it better than us.
- That's what it's like.
- But what about this?
Since you used to be an athlete,
can't you get into it emotionally and say,
"I can't accept this."
Can't you do that?
- What does that mean?
- I didn't understand it.
- I didn't understand...
what you were saying. what you were saying.
- What was that?
- What are you saying?
Get up and say it again.
- He won the Grand Prize.
- Ask them.
It's a very sophisticated question.
- You may be the commentator, - Yes.
but you can't get mad.
But when you do get mad,
just get into your emotions.
"If I were that athlete,"
"and if I were skating there,"
- If it were me?
- "I wouldn't have accepted it."
"I believe that this ruling was wrong."
"However, as a commentator,"
"I don't know how to put it."
- Can't you say that?
- That's a very good comment.
- It really is.
- It's about self-expression.
- That's the model answer.
- I learned one today.
- Yes.
- I should write that down.
Phrasing your emotions indirectly.
- You should use that.
- I will.
"If it were me."
Get into the emotions.
That's a good one.
Then what about...
if a younger athlete was doing so badly?
But that's not their usual performance.
Do you usually confront them later,
or do you...
Since they must be all close to you.
Even if the results were underwhelming,
I don't think I can confront them.
Because that's not up to me to tell them.
They already have their coaches...
- and many other team members.
- That's right.
- It just becomes a lecture.
- So...
they have them for that.
- What we can do is...
- We say it while commentating.
- Yes.
- During the commentating.
We just tell them, "You're doing well."
- Give them courage and faith.
- Yes.
I'm sure you've met many commentators,
but were there people who lost their temper?
Those who couldn't keep it in?
During the Jakarta Asian Games,
Coach Choi Yong Soo...
He was a coach, and it was his first time as a commentator,
so he was only used to being on the field.
Even when he was a coach,
if a player made a mistake,
he would keep looking at him until he made eye contact.
Because he had to scold them.
- So he would keep watching.
- He would be staring at him.
He kept watching even if the ball was spinning.
But even when he was commentating, someone made a mistake,
and he kept watching that player.
- He wouldn't even say a thing.
- Right.
- Coach Choi Yong Soo?
- Yes.
Why did he do that?
- He's no joke.
- So I had to...
I'm close to him.
I had to nudge him to keep talking.
"The ball is over here, so look here."
But he kept watching that player.
- He had the original Eagle Shoot.
- Yes.
- That's right.
- But then...
There must be people who cry too much.
Those who become too emotional.
Those who can't talk because of their tears.
- Those who cry?
- I think I was like that.
I know. Seung Hi is a bit soft-hearted.
During the Beijing Olympics,
- in the beginning, - It was going so badly.
- the judgements were so unfair, - Yes.
so she had pent-up emotions.
But at the 1500m,
- The gold medal.
- we won the gold medal,
and she cried.
I didn't think that would happen.
- Not much different from Ho Dong.
- I got really choked up,
- Right.
- so my voice wouldn't come out.
- Later on?
- I almost became like Ho Dong.
- That's so...
- "Like Ho Dong?"
It was a close call.
Rather than the comments,
sometimes, the silence could be greater.
- That shouldn't happen.
- It will be popular in 2026.
If something doesn't work out,
"I almost became like Ho Dong."
("I almost became like Ho Dong.")
- "It was a close call."
- "I almost became like Ho Dong."
The response was positive during the Sochi Olympics.
It was a hot topic.
- I should watch it again.
- I saw it too.
- It was famous.
- Yoon Gy, don't be like Ho Dong.
- Okay.
- I saw it too.
I saw it too.
- He doesn't watch anything.
- At that time...
KBS was in the middle,
MBC was on the right,
and SBS was on the other side.
It was really cramped because of Ho Dong.
(Shy)
- He was taking up both sides.
- He's this big.
We were sitting like this.
- Could you hear them?
- What?
- Was it soundproofed?
- You can hear everything.
- You can hear everything?
- You can hear the sounds.
I was shouting too much during the Beijing Olympics,
so they said their microphones were catching my voice.
You could hear Seong Jae's voice from other broadcasts.
Really?
My voice was in the other Korean broadcasts,
but also the foreign broadcasts.
The people in Canada heard my voice.
- That's good.
- It was so big.
It was during COVID-19,
so they stacked up acrylic boards next to me.
Seong Jae, but with you,
when you talk or commentate,
- we need to hear you, right?
- Yes.
But with you, I can see the words.
- Do you see the words?
- Yes.
- What's your secret?
- Your pronunciation is excellent.
I need to have good diction,
so I read a lot of newspapers.
- You read out loud?
- Yes.
I read out loud.
And you always bring around Hong Jin Ho...
so that your diction sounds better.
You always stick with Jin Ho.
- That's right.
- Why is Jin Ho's diction bad?
You can't understand Jin Ho even with the captions.
You can't understand him.
Jin Ho is so funny.
Even if he just reads, it's funny.
Yes.
- Yoon Gy.
For Yoon Gy, give him a round of applause.
- He wrote, "rookie commentator."
- You are a rookie.
Thank you.
That's amazing.
He was an Olympic athlete his whole life,
and now, he is the commentator.
It must be an honor,
- and a burden at the same time.
- Right. It must be a burden.
Well, it hasn't been long since I retired,
so I'm worried that I might speak too much...
from the athlete’s perspective.
I might be too much on the athlete's side.
I heard you've been preparing a lot.
What is this special preparation?
I need to see a lot of athletes...
in order to read the match well,
so I went to different international matches to watch them,
and had conversations with many athletes.
I studied them in a very immersive way.
(He worked hard to study on-site in order to help his commentating.)
I thought it would help with my commentating.
And the Olympics will be held in Milan,
so I visited the site beforehand...
and studied the vibe.
He went to the site beforehand.
(The short-track arena)
(The field where the opening ceremony will take place)
(He even met the mascot beforehand.)
Did you go with your own money?
Yes, I invested in it.
- Your own money?
- That's very cool.
This is what I think...
as a viewer.
One of those sports I stay up all night to watch...
just like the World Cup is short track.
I'm saying this as a viewer.
- That's right.
- The sport itself is very tense.
It all ends in the blink of an eye and it's nerve-racking.
- That's very touching.
- That's right.
At every Winter Games, we always say...
that short track has really leveled up overall.
- That's right.
- It has leveled up.
We always say that.
But this time, it's really true.
- That's right.
- This time, in the 1,500m,
Korea's strongest event,
there were four world tours so far.
Canada won three times,
and Korea won once.
- Before, - Canada became really strong.
- That's right.
- Korea would have won three times.
This time, things have changed,
and we're a little worried as well.
Who are the speed skaters we should pay attention to?
Speed skaters to pay attention to?
I also stepped down this time,
and there was a complete generational transition.
- The skaters to pay attention to.
- I was...
- a very old speed skater.
- Really?
Even when I was active,
I was more than ten years older than the others.
The generational transition wasn't complete because of me,
- but I...
- People have to leave quickly.
- Yes. I stayed there too long.
- You're like Kang Ho Dong.
He has to leave for the next generation to rise.
- I was there for too long.
- Trying to stay until the very end.
- Was it like that?
- It was.
(Is he talking about me?)
I get what you mean.
It makes perfect sense.
You have to leave quickly.
This time, the generational transition was complete.
The youngest skater is Rim Jong Un.
- He's so talented.
- I was...
He was born in 2007.
at the national team trials with him.
- He's just turned an adult.
- That's right.
- Were you nice to him?
- Seriously.
We were at the national team trials together.
I made my debut in 2007.
- My world stage debut was in 2007.
- That's right.
When I made my debut, I never imagined...
I would be at the national team trials with someone born in 2007.
While competing with him,
I thought I should really quit.
His speed is on a whole different level.
He's really fast.
(Yoon Gy and Jong Un)
His outside pass was incredibly fast.
I just couldn't stop him.
When I played ssireum before,
I would just go to a certain arena,
and it just felt easy and warm.
That's when you get the Chunha ssireum champion.
You definitely get that feeling.
But some arenas...
would just feel cold and intimidating.
- That's right.
- Do you feel that?
That happens.
Yeong Cheol is funny in all the other channels,
- but when he's here...
- It doesn't work out for him here.
- I wonder why.
- He's not funny here.
- There are such places.
- Should we change the studio?
In other places...
I laugh at what he says in shows like "Pinggyego."
He's good in "Pinggyego,"
- but whenever he's here...
- That's weird.
- I wonder why.
- I guess that's what it feels like.
In the Vancouver Winter Games, I was young.
The arena was the same size,
but it looked huge.
So I was a little intimidated...
even before I entered.
- Internally.
- That happens.
In Sochi, I had that feeling.
Every athlete would know it.
When you step onto the rink for warm-ups,
there's that feeling you get when your blade...
- just moves forward smoothly.
- Is it because of the ice quality?
When the ice quality and my condition are excellent.
I felt that in Sochi.
- My feet just glided forward.
- It was totally...
- It's...
- I guess every athlete feels that.
I heard Seung Hi...
- had a medal for all the events.
- That's right.
- That's the first ever.
- That's so cool.
- Please clap for me.
(You're amazing, Park Seung Hi.)
You have the medals for every event?
In women's short track, I'm the only one...
to have won medals in every event.
- She's legendary.
- Yes.
I'm also the only athlete to have competed...
in the world sporting events in two different events.
- She also did speed skating.
- That's right.
Seung Hi is really amazing.
People who are good at short distances...
aren't good at long distance races.
Seung Hi is the only one...
who is good at both short...
- and long distance races.
- She's an all-rounder.
- An all-rounder.
- That's amazing.
Seong Jae. Sportscasters...
- are mostly announcers.
- Yes.
Do you have to be an announcer to be a sportscaster?
Can't you do it if you talk well and have knowledge...
- in sports?
- So far, they were all announcers.
But later, I think anyone here could do it.
But it's hard to break a long-standing tradition.
- I'm sorry, - Yeong Cheol is...
but why did you ask that question?
- I...
- He wants to be a sportscaster.
I watched a lot of games commentated by Bang Sang Ah...
- and Bae Ki Wan.
- Yes.
I watched all of Kim Yu Na's competitions.
So I memorized all the figure skating terms...
like triple lutz, toe loop, and so on.
- But doesn't he talk too much?
- He does.
But for figure skating,
- there isn't much sound.
- It has to be calm.
It's more important to deliver the emotions.
Right. Figure skating commentaries weren't so chatty.
Let's watch Seong Jae's commentary.
- Seon Jae's commentary.
- Okay.
- We have to be quiet.
- He'll demonstrate first.
- Demonstration.
- Seong Jae.
- Now...
- It's starting.
It's the women's 1,500m final!
Let's watch it.
Hello, everyone.
The Beijing Winter Games women's 1,500m final...
is underway right now.
- Choi Min Jeong is taking the lead.
- That's right.
She's setting the pace out front.
Schulting has been pushed back!
Fontana moves up into second...
and begins the chase.
Schulting is back again.
Fontana is in second, Choi Min Jeong leads!
- The gap is widening.
- Choi Min Jeong...
has to keep the lead.
Two laps to go.
- Two laps!
- Choi Min Jeong!
- At this pace, it's doable.
- That's right.
The skaters behind are all exhausted now.
Fontana has closed in a lot,
- with Schulting right behind her.
- She has to make it until the end.
- Until the end, Choi Min Jeong.
- Quickly.
Yes. She has to stop her from overtaking her.
- Choi Min Jeong!
- Until the end!
- A gold medal!
- Gold medal!
- Choi Min Jeong!
- Until the end!
(An experienced commentary)
Korea's Choi Min Jeong in the women's 1,500m!
She becomes the champion in the end.
It was the same.
You're so good.
- But...
- That was good.
Am I the caster?
Am I taking Seong Jae's role?
I'm so nervous now that I'm really doing it.
- The ranking doesn't change.
- It starts.
We're watching the Beijing Winter Games,
women's 1,500m final now.
- I'm with commentator...
- Kwak Yoon Gy.
Three laps to go. Choi Min Jeong.
- She has to secure it now.
- While introducing themselves,
- The remaining two laps...
- it ended.
- She has to secure it now.
- While introducing themselves,
- The remaining two laps...
- it ended.
- While introducing themselves.
- With the chasers behind her,
she needs to focus on defense rather than attack now.
- It's all about speed now.
- Is he the caster?
- Choi Min Jeong. One more lap.
- Is he the commentator?
- She just needs to hang on.
- I mean...
- The others are all exhausted.
- Talk, Yeong Cheol!
- She needs to keep...
- Right.
Isn't that Fontana?
- Lee Sang Hwa...
- Choi Min Jeong!
Choi Min Jeong wins the gold,
and South Korea has claimed the top spot!
- Choi Min Jeong!
Right.
I don't think he's said anything.
Things are chaotic here. Let's change the channel.
- But...
- It's chaotic.
- Caster Bae Seong Jae...
- Yoon Gy...
- This is the Beijing Winter Games.
- Yes.
- The Beijing Winter Games,
women's 1,500m final...
has begun.
Our country's Choi Min Jeong is taking the lead now.
- Yes.
- She's left with three laps now.
- There are not many laps...
- From now on,
- she must hold her spot.
- That's right.
- They're talking at the same time.
- She must not lose her position,
and she must not look back.
Go forward
- All right.
- Go straight
Don't look back
One two, one two!
- That's right!
- Go!
She must not make a mistake here. She shouldn't make a mistake.
She must not make a mistake here.
She shouldn't make a mistake.
She shouldn't mind the person behind her!
Fontana is right behind her.
- Let's go, Choi Min Jeong!
- She shouldn't mind that.
- She must go at her own pace.
- She must keep going!
- Choi Min Jeong!
- She should just...
She should just mind her own path.
She's almost there. She raises her foot and glides!
A gold medal!
Gliding! A gold medal!
It's a gold for South Korea!
Our proud athlete, Choi Min Jeong!
Choi Min Jeong made it like this.
Choi Min Jeong did well,
but there was another athlete of our own...
who did well from behind.
- That's right. Lee Yu Bin...
- Lee Yu Bin...
also did well.
Lee Yu Bin's performance...
- also made the gold possible.
- Yes.
Thank you for watching!
- Let's go!
- He's good.
Well done.
- Well done.
- Soo Geun is good.
- He's good.
- You're good.
- Soo Geun...
- Soo Geun is shy.
- He and I were the best couple.
- Yes. He's really good.
- He's happy.
He might get contacted.
Caster Bae. Say this went live for the Winter Games.
How would people react?
He would lose all his work.
Go forward
Go straight
- I think...
- He'd get so many messages.
- I think the rating would be good.
- Totally.
At least Jadu would like it.
- You could stream that on YouTube.
- Right.
If things didn't end well after that,
- he'd get all the criticism.
- That's right.
- A ton.
Let's hear about the updates of our transfer students.
First, Seong Jae.
- He's newlywed.
- The new groom!
I never thought he'd get married.
How long has it been?
I got married in May last year, so it has been eight months.
Isn't Seong Jae in the same company...
with Ho Dong and Jang Hoon?
That's right.
But did you invite them?
Actually, I really wanted to invite them, and Soo Geun as well,
but we didn't have a proper wedding.
- Well, so...
- A wedding?
- They didn't have a wedding at all.
- They didn't.
- Seong Jae...
- Weddings cost so much,
- such as the flower arrangements, - That's true.
- wedding photos, - But...
- and a wedding dress.
- Right.
- It's the most important moment, - There is a lot.
but it felt like we were getting stressed from it.
I said that I didn't want to have a wedding if possible,
so we decided to take lots of pretty photos.
We found a photo studio that takes photos at hanok.
- We ate there with our families, - That's nice.
and we all dressed in hanboks and took pictures.
That photo studio asked,
"Isn't it too much not to have a wedding at all?"
So, they let us have a wedding march for a moment in the yard.
Still, you did everything except for the wedding.
- Right. Since we have photos, - That's good.
- the bride didn't feel upset.
- That's right.
By the way, Soo Geun,
I heard so many people from "Shooting Stars" got married.
I believe I am the 11th couple.
- That's right.
- What? Were there so many?
- So many couples.
- Eleven couples got married.
- The players become healthier.
- Oh, I see.
- Oh, because they're healthier.
- Health...
They become mentally healthier,
and that makes them have more energy for dating too.
They become physically healthier too, I'm sure.
Of course. It's all great, actually.
Also, I married someone I met on the show.
- Oh, right.
- Aren't you the only one?
- I am.
- Yes, you're the only couple.
Seong Jae,
didn't you connect Park Ji Sung's couple as well?
- Oh, a long time ago.
- Really?
That's a famous story.
I set up Park Ji Sung and a junior announcer...
- named Kim Min Ji on a blind date.
- An announcer.
They got married and had kids.
As time went on, it became even more fascinating.
That's what Bae Seong Jae considers...
to be the highlight of his career.
My greatest accomplishment in life.
(His greatest accomplishment in life)
- Setting them up on a date?
- Yes.
- The best thing I did since birth.
- Getting Park Ji Sung married.
Gosh, he's a national hero.
- Right.
- Another couple...
There's one other couple in the sports industry.
There's a baseball player named Kang Min Ho.
He plays for the Samsung Lions.
There was a weather forecaster who was a junior of mine at SBS.
It wasn't exactly a blind date,
- but I helped them meet.
- So they could meet.
By the way, was there something...
between your wife and Yeong Cheol?
Oh, on Yeong Cheol's radio show,
Da Yeong was a regular guest for a long time.
For about two years, she was a guest...
I heard rumors that you were the reason she left SBS.
But here's the important part. Did you eat with her or not?
Let me ask you this.
Has Da Yeong mentioned that she had a meal with me or not?
- What?
- You had a meal with her?
Was it lunch or dinner?
- Right, this stuff is important.
- It was dinner.
- Dinner?
- You had dinner together?
We had wine.
You had wine together?
- It was fine dining.
- Oh, my.
She told me about everyone she ever had drinks with.
But, I... Well...
- She must've been embarrassed.
- Did she consider you a squid?
- I guess she was embarrassed.
- She must've been embarrassed.
- Didn't she tell you?
- Hang on. This is...
- Because she was embarrassed.
It was because she was embarrassed.
Hey, he's still a celebrity...
She had dinner with a celebrity.
- Well, but...
- In case Seong Jae is disappointed.
Seong Jae, this is why I brought this up.
The timing was so funny.
It was back in 2024.
We kept saying, "Let's grab a meal together" as we worked together.
It was around June or something,
and she said she was kind of busy that month.
Then, before July, she said she couldn't again.
In August or so, she gave me a date she could go.
But then...
When she announced her marriage, I was so surprised.
- Why?
- Why would you be surprised?
Because it wasn't with you?
- Because it wasn't about you?
- Was it supposed to be with you?
The date she gave me for dinner in August...
was when Seong Jae was in Paris for the Summer Games.
- Oh, right.
- Yes, you were at the Summer Games.
I was away for work, so she would've been alone.
Yeong Cheol is impressive too.
You asked her to eat with you every month, didn't you?
- June, July, August...
- Maybe she didn't want to.
- No, but this is...
- Until you succeed.
Seong Jae, here's what's important.
She worked with Yeong Cheol as a regular guest for two years.
- On his radio show.
- Yes.
Then, did she ever mention Yeong Cheol to you?
Yes, she mentioned him a lot.
She said that Yeong Cheol was really caring...
- and that he's funny on the radio.
- Oh, that's nice.
But it didn't sound like she was talking about him as a man.
- It wasn't...
- It was more like an auntie.
(Yeong Cheol is more feminine than masculine.)
- It's because we're close.
- All right.
- Okay, moving on.
- She's like a little sister.
Seung Hi, for your recent update,
you wrote, "All-rounder."
- Lately, you're on variety shows, - Right.
- and you run a business too.
- I do.
- And you're raising a child too.
- Yes.
- Gosh, isn't that hard?
- Do you run a business as well?
I think I have a knack...
for making things outside of doing sports.
Something like clothing? I like fashion too.
I've had that talent for a while, so I've always wanted to try it.
They're all hard, but what do you think?
Business, variety shows, and childcare.
Which one is the hardest?
- I think childcare is hard.
- Childcare is just...
It's really hard to raise a human being.
- And it doesn't go the way I want.
- Of course.
I think that's why childcare is the hardest.
(Childcare is hard, but it brings that much happiness.)
Seung Hi, does your whole family do sports on ice?
So, there are three of us.
My older sister and younger brother went to the Sochi Winter Games too.
My brother-in-law went to Vancouver...
with Yoon Gy as well.
(Her brother-in-law competed in the 2010 Vancouver Winter Games.)
- That's us. A sports family.
- Even your brother-in-law?
- My brother-in-law too.
- Your family does winter sports.
- That's true.
- We all do winter sports,
and we've all been to the Winter Games.
You were born into it.
They should build an ice rink.
Seriously, in 2014,
all three siblings qualifying for the national team was...
- Right.
- For real.
- It must've been a blessing.
- But...
when we took our ages into account,
that year, 2014, was the year we could go together.
So, we were all hoping it would happen,
and we were so grateful that we all made the team and went together.
The national team trials for short track is pretty much...
- Right.
- If you make the team,
- you can pretty much win a medal.
- Right.
- Yes, it was like that back then.
- At the time.
- Hey, Seung Hi.
- Yes?
- Yoon Gy competed for a long time.
- Yes.
But didn't you only actively compete for a short time?
It was short.
For short track, I retired...
- at 23 or 24.
- That's so young.
- Then, I switched sports.
- You retired so early.
I competed for another four years in speed skating.
Then, I retired for good at 27.
But back then, Yoon Gy tried to convince me to stay.
- He said, "Keep doing short track."
- Right.
But ever since I was really little,
I thought I'd retire as soon as I win a gold medal.
Then, why did you switch sports from doing short track?
I don't know if you all watched, but at Sochi, during the 500m,
I fell twice and missed out on winning the gold.
Then, I really doubted myself.
"Even if I work so hard to prepare,"
"this can happen because of someone else."
That weighed heavily on my mind.
So I decided to retire and took about five months off.
Since the Winter Games were going to be held in Pyeongchang,
I wanted to compete in it, no matter what.
But I didn't want to do short track anymore,
so I was thinking, "How can I compete?"
I found out no one had ever competed in two sports at the Winter Games.
"Oh, I should try this."
That's what I thought when I switched sports.
But I think I just had a strong spirit back then.
I felt like I could do it. I think that's how I was back then.
And I'm so grateful that I actually got to compete.
(Seung Hi was the first to compete in two sports at the Winter Games.)
All right. Lastly, Yoon Gy.
Your recent update is "Retirement."
How long has it been since you retired, Yoon Gy?
- I retired last April.
- It hasn't been that long.
- Right, it hasn't been very long.
- Not even a year.
- But...
- Last April.
many people who know Yoon Gy...
may think that you already retired...
- a long time ago.
- You're right.
- He competed for a long time.
- Right.
- As they watched you on YouTube...
- Yes.
Well, ever since the 2022 Beijing Winter Games,
since I am older than other players,
many people must've assumed that...
this was my last Winter Games.
But actually, as I kept going,
I was still aiming for the Milano Winter Games.
Also, Jang Hoon and Ho Dong,
who were athletes before, may know this.
When I thought about retiring, I felt scared.
"What will I do when I'm done competing?"
"If I'm not an athlete, who am I?"
Because of these thoughts, I felt so anxious...
that I couldn't work up the courage.
So I just kept dragging it on.
Then, the trials for the Milano Winter Games drew near.
I thought, "I should do my best up to this point."
- That's impressive.
- So that final month of April...
- was the period when...
- The trials.
I participated in trials for the Milano Winter Games.
Then, if you had been chosen,
you would have been going to Milan as an athlete, not a commentator.
- I could've gone as an athlete.
- Right.
Then he'd be in Milan right now.
That's awesome.
When you retire... I've never been a competitive athlete.
Then, does your daily life pattern change entirely?
At first... It totally changes.
We usually get up really early in the morning,
and we start training right away.
Since I don't have to do that anymore,
- it was so nice at first.
- It is nice.
I got to sleep in.
- You'll suddenly grow taller, then.
- So...
But why didn't I grow taller? I got plenty of sleep.
- That's odd.
- You'll be Jang Hoon's height soon.
- Right.
- But Yoon Gy...
Take good care of yourself.
- You might suddenly grow a lot.
- I don't.
- Do you sleep through the night?
- Your knees will get stretch marks.
I sleep so deeply...
- these days. Yes.
- Do you sleep deeply now?
You gain some weight at first, don't you?
I've already gained some weight. About 8kg.
- What, 8kg?
- This is you after gaining weight?
- I've gained 8kg.
- We can't tell.
- I didn't think you gained any.
- You don't exercise as much.
When I was still competing, I weighed about 62kg.
Now, I weigh almost 70kg.
I definitely gained weight since I started exercising less.
Since you retired in April,
- it hasn't been a full year yet.
- Yes.
Have you ever put on your ice skates?
I haven't put them on yet.
There hasn't been an occasion to put them on.
I purposefully distanced myself from them.
I didn't want to put them on as a joke...
and get the urge to go back to being an athlete.
Yoon Gy, you've won many medals.
- You run a YouTube channel.
- Yes.
Do you only have 1,000 dollars in your bank account?
- I'm sure he has another one.
- No way.
Seung Hi knows this, but short-track speed skaters...
- don't make a lot of money.
- That's right.
We use more money as athletes.
Our annual income is very low.
Despite that, it takes a lot of money to keep skating.
We need the gear...
- and suits.
- That's right. They're expensive.
We need to rent the ice skating rink.
- Those things take a lot of money.
- That's right.
The blade holders cost anywhere between 400 and 500 dollars.
Ice skate boots cost anywhere between 2,000 and 2,500 dollars.
Ice skate blades cost anywhere between 700 and 900 dollars.
(4,880 dollars in a year)
Thus, I didn't save up a lot of money.
- Oh, no.
- I see.
- They have no intention to help.
- Seriously.
They just said, "Oh, no."
- Still...
- Help us, guys.
Don't you run a YouTube channel...
- and a business?
- You run a YouTube channel.
As for the YouTube channel... I thought...
I'd make a lot of money if I had one million subscribers.
- It isn't like that these days.
- It wasn't like that.
- Are there one million subscribers?
- It all depends on view counts.
Soo Geun said something...
when I visited the show 4 years ago with over 1 million subscribers.
"That won't last long. The number will go down."
I remember him saying that.
(After the match,)
(the number of subscribers rose to 1.2 million.)
(They'll be gone by summer.)
- The bubble is bursting.
- My words were based on shamanism.
- He's a shaman.
- I can see everything.
- How suspicious.
- The last one is...
the three friends' future dream.
Even when you age,
- you can still have a future dream.
- That's right.
Firstly, Seong Jae wrote,
"Longevity."
Seong Jae, are you ill?
No, I'm not ill.
In the past, I didn't think about my lifespan.
But now that I'm married to someone...
- who is a lot younger...
- You got married.
My wife worries a lot too.
- Health.
- When she came over for a date,
I always ordered deliveries.
She was very startled.
She had never ordered a delivery.
She saw my tendencies and said, "Isn't this bad for your health?"
Does your wife cook for you?
She cooks light dishes using healthy ingredients.
It's like cooking for an athlete.
(She protects Seong Jae's health.)
You eat again outside after eating those meals at home, right?
How did you know?
- How did you know? You're good.
- Really?
Compared to the past, Seong Jae lost weight.
- That's right.
- After getting married,
I lost about 7kg.
- Exactly.
- Did you lose weight?
As his future goal, Yoon Gy wrote...
I don't know what you mean by this.
He wrote, "Seo Jang Hoon."
- Do you want to marry a tall woman?
- Tall height?
- Jang Hoon is a senior...
- Seo Jang Mi.
who graduated from my college.
He's tall.
He built an incredible career in sports.
He's really good at shows too.
I'm also jealous...
of his honesty.
He can speak his mind to people.
Since I'm not good at that,
I'm jealous.
Speaking one's mind isn't for everyone.
- It isn't for you.
- If you do it,
- you'll get into a fight.
- Personally...
Speaking one's mind without holding back...
is something you need to be born with.
- That's right.
- I agree.
- It isn't easy.
- If you copy it recklessly,
- you'll get an unpleasant surprise.
- I agree.
It isn't easy to be impatient.
I think there's only one in the world.
- There's only 1.
- Only 1 in the world.
- There he is.
- Only one in the world.
If you copy him, you'll get into trouble.
Don't copy something like this.
If you copy it, your fingers might get broken.
(Copy me if you can!)
All right. Seung Hi.
Seung Hi is next.
What's this? "Type A life?"
Type A life involves...
- many things.
- She's a Gen Zer.
There are many things I want to do.
I was going to write Jang Hoon or Ho Dong's name.
I respect former athletes...
- who are in the show business.
- That's right.
- It isn't an easy transition.
I want to follow in the footsteps of the seniors...
- who paved the way.
- That's right.
Seung Hi, is your style more like Ho Dong's or Jang Hoon's?
I don't think I can take on Jang Hoon's style.
- Why not?
- Not everyone can do that.
- There's only one in the world.
- Hey.
- It isn't easy.
- Criticism isn't for everyone.
- Hey, I'm sorry, - He'll be a national treasure.
but if there's no one like me in the world,
how about him?
There's no one like him in terms of appearance.
There are many people like him in Mongolia.
- Seriously.
- There are many in Mongolia.
- There are many in Ulaanbaatar.
- You're right.
- That's right. The athletes.
- He's the only one in the world...
- with that TV show style.
- The Mongolian athletes.
Hello, viewers.
The 2026 Winter Games...
has begun in Milano Cortina.
I announce the beginning...
of the first Neighborhood Games on a Mission.
(The 1st Neighborhood Games on a Mission has begun.)
Team Kwak Yoon Gy,
please enter.
Let's go.
Please enter. All right.
Hello.
Next comes...
Team Park Seung Hi. Please enter.
(Booing)
Yoon Gy!
- Seung Hi!
- What's this?
- Who's that?
Seung Hi!
Team Blue!
- Park Seung Hi!
- Seung Hi!
- My dazzling one
- Park Seung Hi!
- I love you - Park Seung Hi!
That's exactly what you shouldn't do.
What should I do then?
And I'm the referee and host,
Kim Hwan. It's nice to meet you.
- Kim Hwan!
- Clap, clap, clap!
The two of them are former coworkers.
- That's right.
- Seong Jae and me?
We're a senior and a junior in the announcer circles.
We were a senior and a junior in high school as well.
Did you guys know each other in high school?
- We didn't know each other.
- No.
Hwan was in the baseball club.
I just studied the liberal arts.
Hwan worked for SBS alongside Seong Jae in the past.
- But Seong Jae took all the jobs.
- That's...
- Were you there as well?
- Hwan lost his temper.
- Listen.
- It's a rumor.
- It's just a rumor, okay?
- You were in a different field.
Let me explain. Since Hwan played baseball,
he wanted to be a sportscaster.
- But Seong Jae took all the jobs.
- Correct.
- So Hwan became angry.
And Bae...
- I can call him by his name here.
- Sure.
- Bae Seong Jae...
- You're the teacher.
- Call him Bae Seong Jae.
- I mean...
- Bae Seong Jae!
- Hey.
- Bae Seong Jae.
- What?
- Hwan is the teacher.
- So I joined SBS...
when Seong Jae was there.
Seong Jae went into sports broadcasting...
and commentated on the Premier League games at night.
So he stopped doing the miscellaneous tasks...
rookie announcers had to do.
- I had to do all of them.
- You had to do all of them.
Because of that, I'm not close to Seong Jae.
- I don't really like him.
- He doesn't know the full story.
What's that?
At first, they wanted me to take...
both soccer and baseball.
But I said, "I think baseball should go to Hwan."
You gave up a job.
- But he couldn't take it.
- For goodness' sake.
- You practically gave it to him.
- That's right.
- I gave it to him, - You gave it to him.
- but he didn't show up.
- It's a story...
- of Seong Jae's good deed.
- He didn't show up.
Although Seong Jae joined SBS first,
Hwan went freelance first.
- Exactly.
- I went freelance first.
Hwan, as a senior freelance announcer,
do you think Seong Jae is doing well?
Seong Jae mocked me when I went freelance.
- What?
- Me?
- "Will you be able to do it?"
- Yes. "Will you be able to do it?"
"Announcers don't make it big when they go freelance."
Then he went freelance as well.
("Bae Seong Jae Leaves SBS and Gains Confidence on the First Day")
Do you know what's funny about Seong Jae?
- I wasn't going to share this.
- Okay.
When I was in SM C and C, I told him that he should join.
- But he didn't do that.
- Okay.
When I left, he joined right away.
("Bae Seong Jae Signs a Contract with SM C and C")
- Hey.
- It made me go, "Shoot."
- Seong Jae is like that.
- Then he joined "Shooting Stars."
Seong Jae is like that.
I talked to the CEO of SM C and C.
- No way.
- You told him to fire Soo Geun.
I got fired twice because of him.
- He's an expert.
- I talked to the CEO of SM C and C.
Soo Geun got fired from "Shooting Stars..."
as well as SM C and C.
In any case, today,
- I'm the host...
- Okay.
- and you guys are the athletes.
- Okay, Mr. Kim.
Winter Games are the most important,
so please do your best.
The first event is...
the game that created a craze...
at the 2018 Winter Games in Pyeongchang.
- "Yeong Mi!"
- I'm sure everyone remembers.
- Uiseong.
It's curling.
In this year's Winter Games, the Korean team had...
the first match in the mixed doubles curling.
Thus, the Neighborhood Games on a Mission will begin...
with a game that requires delicate breathing control...
and strategy.
It's the Blowing Curling.
(Blowing Curling)
Okay.
Now, one player from each team will come out...
and use a straw to blow a bottle cap toward the circles.
You can only locate the cap behind the red line.
You'll receive the points that correspond with the circle...
on which the cap lands.
- Team Kwak will attack first.
- Okay.
- Let's take five wins.
- Team Park will attack second.
(Team Kwak Yoon Gy versus Team Park Seung Hi)
- The first player, Sang Min.
- It'll fall off.
Team Kwak's Sang Min.
Go when you're ready.
Four, three, two, one.
(It's nerve-racking.)
- Next.
- It was so close.
- Kyung Hoon, blow gently.
- Here I go.
- Team Park's first player is...
Kyung Hoon.
(Gosh!)
- It's getting nerve-racking.
- I'm nervous.
- All right.
- Ho Dong.
- Next.
- Hung Kam Po.
- He's on the same team.
The same team.
- It's in.
- Ten points.
The same team.
- It's in.
- Ten points.
- It's in. Ten points.
- All right.
- Okay.
- That's good.
- Push it off.
- We're at a disadvantage.
- We can push it off.
- Push it off.
The straw is shaking.
It's short.
- There you go.
- Well done.
- He doesn't disappoint.
- I'm good at this.
- Well done.
- I made them lose ten points.
- All the caps fell off.
- If we block the path,
we won't be able to score.
- Okay.
- We need to put one in there.
- Let's score first.
- You're a good sportscaster.
"Goni? He was the best gambler I knew."
Let's go.
- Put one in there.
- Let's do that.
"I can blow it!"
I'll score 40 points.
- Hee Chul.
- Oh, my.
- What was that?
He lacks the strength.
- Oh, my.
- Hee Chul was nowhere close.
- Next.
- It rolled.
It's blocking the center.
Will Jang Hoon be able...
- to put it past this point?
- I'll blow hard.
- Send it to the side.
- Seo Jang Hoon.
- What?
You can set it up again, Jang Hoon.
- Jang Hoon.
- You can set it up again.
- This is the red line.
- Behind the red line.
Put it behind the red line.
He doesn't know because he doesn't have a wife.
It's understandable. We'll let you off just once.
You don't have a wife.
- Let's see.
- Send it to the side.
(He was too enthusiastic.)
It was too strong.
I can't do this
- I can't do that - We found something he's bad at.
- I know.
- Seong Jae.
Among the sportscasters I know, he's the least athletic.
- It's meaningless.
- Really?
His body tells me that he doesn't have an athletic bone.
- He's bad with his body.
- It'll fall off.
- His nickname is Big Nose.
- Your body - Focus.
It was nowhere close.
- Soo Geun.
- He's good at pool.
Since this calls for a hook shot,
- I'll use the number four straw.
- Okay.
- Number four straw.
- I think it's too big.
If it goes in, it'll stay there.
Lee Soo Geun.
There you go.
It was short.
- There you go.
- For goodness' sake.
- No way. It went straight.
- Well done.
- I mean...
This is the last chance.
Yoon Gy.
- Good.
- Good. Let's go, Timon.
- I'll show the Timon vibe.
- Do it like Timon.
The team that puts a cap on the circles will win.
Go with the hunch and put it there.
- Yoon Gy.
- Will he be able to wrap it up?
Kwak Yoon Gy.
It was short.
It's okay. It can be a tie.
- It was short.
- Seung Hi, you should do something.
- I know. I should do something.
- You're the captain.
I'm so anxious right now.
You can either hit another cap or put yours here.
Okay.
- Move it! She'll be startled.
- If it goes in...
- He's so big.
- Put it in Jang Hoon's mouth.
- If it goes in, you'll win.
- Seung Hi, let's do it.
Let's do well, Seung Hi.
My goodness.
(Out)
It's a tie.
- It's a tie. Who is good at it?
- It's out.
- It's time for a sudden death.
- Now...
- It's time for Round 2.
- Team Park will go 1st.
- Make them go 1st.
- Blow.
- If you go first...
This is a sudden-death playoff.
The team that scores first will win.
- Okay.
- Okay?
Go.
All right.
- All right.
- Ho Dong, let's go.
- It isn't easy.
- Go.
- All right.
The record-holder...
- of the bottle cap games, - He's the worst at this game.
- Kang Ho Dong.
- He can't sit down.
I'm sorry, but this is a five-minute game.
- Kang Ho Dong...
- The flying pork cutlet.
has the most number of records for the bottle cap games.
- Stir-fried pork.
- All right.
Kang Ho Dong.
- Kang Ho Dong.
- You got this.
So close!
- It's out.
- Seung Hi is next.
- I'm sorry.
Seung Hi is next.
Do it without looking.
- Park Seung Hi.
- Close your eyes a bit.
- That's one way to do it.
Senior Park.
Park Seung Hi.
There you go.
- It's hard.
- Yoon Gy.
It's bound to go out.
- Timon.
- See?
If you look, it goes out.
- I feel like it'll work.
- Yours was short...
- since you didn't look.
- Kyung Hoon.
- Kyung Hoon, don't look.
- Do we remove the caps?
- No.
- Kyung Hoon, do it without looking.
- Because...
- Shall I close my eyes?
- A bit.
They know that...
Kyung Hoon.
- He closed his eyes.
- Good.
Which way should I go?
Okay. All right.
- Okay. All right.
- Why did you close your eyes?
- It was nowhere close.
- I couldn't see it.
It was nowhere close.
It isn't easy to send it to the target.
- It flies past it.
- Sang Min.
- There you go.
- If it goes in, your team wins.
- Just send it to the target.
- If it goes in, the game ends.
- Come on.
- It'll hit another cap.
- No one has succeeded in it.
- Sang Min.
- A cap of a different color.
(The cap flew off.)
- Yeong Cheol.
- It's impossible.
- It's Yeong Cheol's turn again.
- I'd hit another cap.
- Send it to the target.
- Shall I hit the one at the front?
- No.
- It's better to hit it.
- Don't hit it.
- Hit it.
- Just put it here.
- That's right.
- Here. There's a lot of space.
- Push it off.
- Push it off. There you go.
(He listened to Coach Lee and hit the cap at the front.)
(But the cap stopped right before the mark.)
Did it work?
- Hit it once more.
- It's 1cm short.
- We can score next time.
- I sent it close. Do it well.
- It was a bit short.
- Seong Jae.
- Seong Jae, go ahead and score.
If it goes in, the game ends.
Among the sportscasters I know, he's...
- the least athletic.
- It's the final goal.
Bae Seong Jae.
Seong Jae, you're good with your mouth.
- Yes.
- Summer and Winter Games.
- For goodness' sake.
- What's wrong with you?
(Blowing)
- For goodness' sake.
- What's wrong with you?
- I knew that it wouldn't work.
- Move.
- Jang Hoon.
- Jang Hoon, hit this cap.
Jang Hoon, seriously. I did all the work.
- The caps will disperse.
- For goodness' sake.
I did all the work. Just hit my cap gently.
- Just hit my cap gently.
- If his aim is that good,
he should just send this to the mark.
- And...
- Send it to the center.
Hit this cap. Jang Hoon, listen to me.
Just hit it, Jang Hoon.
- Jang Hoon, blow hard like before.
- He might do that again.
- Will he succeed in it?
- Jang Hoon will fail.
- Jang Hoon.
Jang Hoon hates being frustrated.
- Jang Hoon, blow hard.
- All right.
- Jang Hoon.
- Control your breath.
- There you go.
All done.
- Jang Hoon.
- There you go.
(Embarrassed)
- All done.
- Jang Hoon.
(It was nowhere close.)
- All done.
- You did well.
We found something Jang Hoon is bad at.
You should send it as far as your height.
Your breaths are short.
How do you do this?
- I mean...
- I can't believe him.
- There's something he's bad at.
- Seriously. Hey!
- What was that?
- My expectations were too high.
- I mean...
- He blocked the path.
Earlier, the cap went too far.
- There are so many roadblocks.
- Jang Hoon, it's okay.
- We can do it.
- It's okay.
Here I go.
- Let's go.
- Hee Chul.
- Teamwork.
- I received so much energy.
- The game will end...
if Team Kwak's Hee Chul scores.
The game will end if my cap goes in, right?
Hey!
(Oh, no.)
(A blue cap lands on the circles.)
- Team Park won.
- We won.
Team Park won.
(He gets a headache.)
- I can't believe it worked.
- Seung Hi, dance.
- What do I need to do?
- Dance.
- I can't believe it.
- What a picture.
(Hee Chul did all the work, but Team Park Seung Hi scored.)
I can't believe it.
(It's electrifying to win through someone else's work.)
Thus, Team Park won.
Nice!
- Nice!
- It was set up nicely.
I can't believe he hit that cap.
Short-track speed skating is one of the Winter Games events...
that brings many medals to Korea.
- Yes.
- Let's hope for the golden race...
from the Korean skaters.
The second game at the Neighborhood Games on a Mission is...
- the Foot-Track with a Foot Baton.
- A Foot Baton.
- Touch by touch - A Foot Baton.
- This is a relay...
- Dance
in which you only use your feet.
A player will enter from each team and put on toe socks.
Between the toes,
a flag baton will be inserted.
The players will walk that way.
During the race, their feet must continue touching the floor.
Here's the most important rule. At the finish line,
- they'll use the toes only...
- Must we pass it with our feet?
- to pass the baton.
- Okay.
If the baton falls during the race, they must pick it up with the toes.
- Okay?
If you drop the baton,
you need to pick it up with your toes.
- I know.
- If you drop it, it's over.
- You can't pick it up.
You need to pick it up with your toes, so don't drop it.
- Okay.
- If you drop it, you lose.
- Don't do that.
- Don't use the hands.
It's better to take it from the above.
- Yes.
- That's right.
- Take it from the above.
- Okay.
Did you hear me? It'll be one way for every skater...
- except one skater.
- I'll hold it,
- so take it from the above.
- The last skater.
- The next skater will take it.
- The last one makes a round trip.
- All right.
Let's do a cheer for the Korean team at the Winter Games.
The Korean team at the Winter Games,
- let's go!
- Let's go!
- Get ready.
- Let's go.
(The members stand on the ice rink for short-track speed skating,)
(the flower of the Winter Games.)
(The two legendary skaters' names are on the line.)
- Get ready.
- Let's go.
Set.
- All right.
- Good.
- Skaters, let's go.
- Hee Chul.
(The starting skaters are Hee Chul and Jang Hoon.)
- Play it safe.
- Hee Chul.
- Put it between the toes.
Put it between the toes.
No.
We need to do it like this. No, like this.
- Slowly.
- No, like this.
(Team Park takes the lead.)
Ho Dong, skate.
(Going at full speed)
- Ho Dong, skate.
- Be calm.
- All right.
- Ho Dong.
- Come on.
(Kyung Hoon passes the baton to Yeong Cheol.)
- Ho Dong, skate.
- Yeong Cheol will cause trouble.
Good.
- Slowly.
- Yeong Cheol.
I'll turn around.
Pick it up.
(Soo Geun's sense of foreboding comes true.)
- That little...
- Pick it up.
(Ho Dong arrives during the other team's accident.)
Hold on.
(The baton successfully goes from Ho Dong to Yoon Gy.)
They caught up.
Yoon Gy.
(A baobab of the Korean short-track speed skating scene)
(I'll show you how to pass. Hold on tight.)
(Yoon Gy gets ahead by a round and arrives at the finish line.)
- All right.
- Seong Jae, hurry up.
Pick it up.
(They're still passing the baton.)
Pick it up gently.
What are we going to do?
- Oh, my!
Hurry up. Stand here, Seong Jae.
Stand here, Seong Jae.
(Team Park protests since the flag baton isn't upright.)
- You can't do that.
- Come on.
- It needs to be upright.
- Fix it.
- Don't use your hands.
- Use the other foot.
Go behind the line.
Use the other foot.
(The flag baton falls off when the team is leading.)
(Sang Min got affected by the psychological attack.)
(I can't believe it!)
- He dropped it.
- Hold on.
- All right.
- What are we going to do?
(During the flag fiasco on the other side)
(Seung Hi's foot helps.)
- You can't pick it up that way.
- You can't do that.
- It needs to be upright.
- It's too...
Grab the bottom. There you go.
- Don't use your hands.
- There you go.
Go behind the line.
(Thanks to Seung Hi's help, he begins to skate again.)
Let's go!
(Team Park chases after Team Kwak with the power of teamwork.)
- He dropped it.
- Let's go.
(Sang Min is still struggling to pick up the flag.)
- All right.
- There you go.
- It's a tie.
- That's right. It's a tie.
- Let's go.
(They set off at the same time.)
(They charge toward the last skaters together!)
(Both teams are nervous.)
- It's a tie.
- Let's go.
- I need to make a round trip.
- Skate.
(They arrive at the return point at the same time.)
- Hold on. All right.
- Good.
- Now, make a round trip.
- Hold on.
(The last skaters receive the flags of fate.)
- Now, make a round trip.
- Hold on.
- Go.
- Seung Hi, go.
(The outcome depends on the last trip.)
(The last skaters need to make a round trip.)
(The two of them hit the halfway point.)
The last skaters.
- The last skaters.
- Go!
(Seung Hi missteps and slips.)
There's a distance between them.
(Even a sportscaster can outskate a professional skater.)
(Who will skate until the end and seize the medal?)
- The last skaters.
- Go!
(Give it your all until the end, Park Seung Hi!)
(Block her so that she won't pass you, Bae Seong Jae!)
- The last skaters.
- Go!
- What?
We won.
- The last skaters.
- Go!
- What?
- We won.
(She turned the tables.)
- The last skaters.
- Go!
- She won! Seung Hi won!
- We won.
(The tables are turned.)
- Team Park won.
- We won.
(Team Park wins gold in the Foot-Track with a Foot Baton.)
(Team Kwak missed gold right before their eyes.)
(The unpredictable result is the charm of the sport.)
She wrapped it up.
- Seung Hi, did you do this?
- The Korean team won.
The Korean team won.
- We won, right?
- Seriously.
- You won.
- It was a great match.
She won by pushing her foot forward.
At the very end, Seong Jae had...
one more step to go.
She pushed her foot forward before that.
I feel so hot.
- She pushed through until the end.
- Well done.
- Seung Hi pushed her foot forward.
- She was fast.
An athlete sure is different.
- It was unbelievable.
- It was a great match.
She was good.
It couldn't be more dynamic.
Because of Sang Min's mishap,
Seong Jae was going faster.
- I know.
- He was going faster.
I'm glad the nice team won.
- The mean team lost.
- Thank goodness.
The two teams that worked hard today...
will receive a prize that has been made to commemorate...
- the Milano Cortina Winter Games.
- What's that?
It's the Italian-style...
five-ring-shaped pasta.
- Pasta.
- Here's the important thing.
It's a limited-edition product, so there are only 550 boxes...
- in the entire world.
- Not many boxes have been made.
- It's a limited-edition product.
- Show us.
Keep it a family treasure.
Why are they getting a prize when we won?
Seriously.
We get one too.
- Thank you.
- Five-ring-shaped pasta.
- It goes to both teams.
- Come on.
It's for the two teams that worked hard today.
I said that earlier.
- Pasta.
- You guys lost.
Isn't it a Milan-edition cellphone?
- It should be something like that.
- Hey.
- Listen.
- It's pasta.
Why would you give a prize to the team that lost?
- Listen.
- I don't want it.
It's for the two teams that worked hard today.
- In that case...
- Let's give them a prize.
In that case...
It's for the two teams that worked hard today.
- That has never happened.
- What was the point of the games?
- Everyone worked hard.
- It's the five-ring-shaped pasta.
That's right.
- It's a festival.
- That's right.
What was the point of the games?
How was it to join the shoot today?
Transfer students, please say a few words each.
- It was nice.
- I had so much fun.
I felt like I was participating in the Winter Games ahead of time.
- I had fun.
- Oh, my.
To be honest, I was a bit scared of the members.
After today, I won't be scared of them.
- I'll take them more lightly.
- Will you go that far?
The Winter Games will continue on, so please cheer on the athletes.
- Let's go.
- Good.
Don't be scared of me. Pat my head.
(Ho Dong the beast wants to be friends with him.)
- Thank you.
- Seung Hi is last.
- Seung Hi.
- I also had a lot of fun.
Please pay attention to the Winter Games.
Let's go.
Watch the Winter Games on JTBC.
- Don't change the channel.
All members of the Korean team,
- good luck!
- Good luck!
(Thrilling and diverse! Watch the Winter Games on JTBC.)
("Culinary Class Wars 2" Special,)
(Chun Sang Hyun, Yun Na Ra, Lee Mun Jeong, Song Hoon)
(Recruitment of these chefs is a miracle.)
(I'm the only Blue House chef who receives a pension.)
(The former presidents' soul food gets revealed!)
(Let's delve into the Blue House dishes...)
(with the chef who has served the presidents for 20 years.)
(Chef Song Hoon got eliminated at the sea squirt match.)
(It bruised my ego.)
(I'm Song Hoon.)
(A behind-the-scenes of the match against Culinary Monster)
(This little...)
(Don't get so annoyed. Calm yourself.)
(I didn't believe it then.)
(I thought they'd call me when I got home.)
(How the nervous Witch with a Wok overcame elimination)
(Why are Chinese cuisine chefs so full of anger?)
- I think...
- Wait.
(Mafia boss, Witch with a Wok)
(Brewmaster Yun became popular around the world.)
(Brewmaster Yun's tips on winning on "Culinary Class Wars!")
(If my ingredient was a dried pollack,)
(I attempted to converse with it.)
(Where are you from?)
(Did the dried pollack answer?)
(Sure.)
(I'm a dried pollack from Noryangjin.)
(The return of the School Meal Wars)
(School Meal Wars is back as competitive as ever!)
(Will Brewmaster Yun win as she always does when she's nervous?)
(They use all sorts of skills they couldn't use on the show!)
(I see that Chef Song Hoon is...)
(a pretty talented chef.)
(Annoyed again)
(Sous-chef who works despite an injury)
(What comes after cucumbers?)
(For now, my work...)
(ends here.)
(The tasks will be divided evenly among the teammates.)
(Who will become the winner of the School Meal Wars?)
(School Meal Wars, School Meal Class Wars)
(Men on a Mission)