(A familiar rhythm is played at Brother School in April.)
(Groaning)
Is it straight? Is it hung all right?
- Hey, Ho Dong. What are you doing? - What's going on?
- What's with that clock? - Hey, what's up?
- Isn't that a clock? - Hang on a second, guys.
Oh, I recognize that clock.
- Okay. It's working. - Oh, Hyeon Jong from KIA Tigers.
Our friend Hyeon Jong sent us this clock.
(Hyeon Jong gave them the clock as a gift.)
- Oh, I see. That looks cool. - It just came out, apparently.
- KIA Tigers. - It looks great.
Oh, I get it. This is...
- to celebrate their victories. - They won 12 times.
That's right.
(KIA Tigers' celebration clock to celebrate their 12 victories)
(That means KIA Tigers' time goes on forever.)
(Oh, my. I got goosebumps!)
- Those emblems are cool, right? - Yes.
- That's so cool. - That's really cool, indeed.
- Did he really send this to us? - From their first victory...
We can make our own clock...
after doing this show for two more years...
since it's been ten years.
- That's true. - To celebrate 12 years...
- But in my opinion, - We should start preparing.
- we should step up our game a bit. - Why?
- It seems to me that Sang Min... - Yes?
Gets less screen time than Yeong Cheol does these days.
- I want him to step up a little. - But he keeps...
- Go for it. - What's the matter with you?
He keeps saying that he's possessed by a ghost.
- He's now invisible like a ghost. - Right. Don't say that anymore.
- I mean, he's a main host. - Sang Min, no more ghost theme.
- They're right. - Never do that again.
- He should never do that again. - You must never say it again.
- Oh, and... - What if the ghost possesses me?
You see, I...
At least a photo...
- What's that? - What's going on?
(While they chat and laugh, the best spring song starts.)
- What is this? Whose song is this? - Is this Lee Moon Sae's song?
- Is this Lee Moon Sae's song? - Oh, my goodness.
(As the transfer students appeared, the clock fell off.)
- The clock fell off. - That one fell off.
The clock fell off.
My goodness.
Welcome, you all!
- The clock on that wall fell off. - Right, it fell off.
(The fierce transfer students begin by breaking a clock.)
Hi.
Are you guys restless?
Or is it because you don't have someone you love?
Why are you guys so noisy?
- He's teasing us. - He's acting.
From which school did you transfer?
Hi, everyone. We're from...
Love-Beyond-Borders High School. And I am...
Saya's husband, Hyung Tak.
(Saya's husband, Shim Hyung Tak)
- Shim Hyung Tak! - And you?
Hello, gentlemen. Let me introduce myself.
Thirty years ago,
I married Choi Min Soo, the beast.
- I am June Kang, the beauty. - I see.
But now, I am the beast.
And it's all thanks to my husband.
I think you're not supposed to speak formally here.
What? Oh, right.
- You speak casually here. - Right. I forgot.
Well... I'm sorry. I'll speak casually now.
- Who are you? - I am June Kang.
- Welcome... - And...
Thirty years ago, I married...
- Are you repeating what you said? - You don't have to repeat it.
- Oh, really? I don't have to? - You don't have to repeat it.
- Okay. I see. That's all. - You can rest now.
I stay calm in front of a goalpost,
but I'm sweet in front of my love.
I'm Anna's husband, Park Joo Ho.
(Anna's husband, Park Joo Ho)
Their love transcends borders. Am I right?
Their love stories are just like movies.
June.
- "I thought I could have you..." - Hold on.
"if I did what I did."
- Oh, my. - He should breathe while talking.
- Hold on a second. - Min Soo would hate it.
- Ho Dong. - I think he'll hate it so much.
He's Pig Min Soo, not Choi Min Soo.
- Ho Dong. - Min Soo...
didn't say that line like you just did.
- He didn't, obviously. - I see.
You sounded like you had too much saliva in your mouth.
- Hold on. Do it for us again. - Okay.
"What's your standard of right and wrong, you punk?"
(What's your standard of right and wrong, you punk?)
He's so good at this.
(Choi Min Soo Geun copies even Min Soo's nostrils.)
- That was good. - "What's your standard..."
- "of right and wrong, you punk?" - That was really good.
That was the best celebrity impression...
- that Soo Geun had ever done. - That was good, right?
"I thought I could have you if I did what I did."
- This is such a famous line. - That's right.
- Indeed. - Has he ever said it to you?
He has never said those words to me.
He hasn't said it to me,
but I've always felt that vibe.
He's always given off that vibe.
He's always been like he's saying, "Can you live for me?"
- I've always felt that vibe. - Amazing.
- Oh, my. I wonder how that feels. - He's such a romanticist.
- It put a lot of pressure on me. - Because he expects a lot?
- You see that, right? - The most important thing is...
that June has more catchphrases than Min Soo does these days.
- Really? - Right, that one.
- Right. So... - "Mine is mine."
- I said, "Mine is mine." - "And yours is also mine."
- "And yours is also mine." - "Mine."
I always live my life with that mindset.
So everything is mine.
- Right. It's a famous catchphrase. - Everything is mine.
There's another one. "Yoo Sung's dad, be quiet."
- "Yoo Sung's dad, be quiet." - She calls him "Yoo Sung's dad."
- "Yoo Sung's dad." - "Yoo Sung's dad?"
"Yoo Sung's dad."
- "Yoo Sung's dad." - That's right.
- That reminded me of something. - That's funny.
Let's give a round of applause!
- Why? - Why? Oh, right. I know why.
- We should congratulate Hyung Tak. - Hyung Tak?
- He finally became a dad. - He became a dad.
- Right, he had a baby. - That's right.
- I became a dad. Yes, I did. - He suddenly said to applaud.
(Hyungtak-emon became a dad.)
Before I tell you about my son,
- I'd like to say something. - What?
- I'll say a word before starting. - To whom?
Viewers, I know what you think.
"That punk talks about nothing but Saya."
"Couldn't he be on a variety show if he didn't have Saya?"
"There's nothing special about him."
- He's possessed by a ghost. - You must be saying these things.
But that's the theme of this show.
Hyung Tak, Sang Min just said,
- "He's possessed by a ghost." - "He's possessed by a ghost."
- I mean, I'm so frustrated. - The ghost moved into his body.
- Acting like he's possessed is bad. - The ghost...
- He's possessed by the same ghost. - The ghost...
- The ghost moved into his body. - The ghost moved to him.
- The ghost possessed Sang Min... - When he walked in,
- and is now possessing Hyung Tak. - the clock fell off.
- The ghost moved to him. - That's when it moved to him.
- Oh, a ghost? Yes, that's right. - The ghost is now possessing him.
For how many years have you been talking about your marriage?
- For 2 years. - For 1 year?
- No, for two years. - Two years.
We've been talking about divorce for ten years.
- Two years is nothing... - That's true.
- Two years is not long at all. - I lost.
- Anyway, I had a baby. - Let's congratulate him again.
- Let's congratulate him again. - What's your baby's name?
His name is Shim Ha Roo.
- Ha Roo? - Yes.
- You're Ha Roo's dad. - Yes, Ha Roo.
- He takes after his mom, right? - He takes after your wife, right?
- Yes, he takes after his mom. - Right.
- He looks like his mom. - He must be adorable...
- no matter whom he takes after. - He must be adorable.
- He must be really cute. - He must be so adorable.
That's why my wife told me not to say...
that he looks like Jung Kook of BTS on this show.
- You just said that. - Yes?
Oh, I just did.
- Many people said they hoped... - He's so peculiar.
That my baby would look like Jung Kook.
But I promised not to say it here.
You just said all the things you promised not to say.
That's because looking after a baby is exhausting.
- How old is he now? - That's true.
He's a little over 80 days old.
Babies wake up once an hour.
Last week, he started sleeping...
- through the night without waking. - He sleeps all night now?
- Right. I see. - I look after him...
through the night from 10pm to 7am...
without sleeping at all.
Joo Ho,
are Na Eun, Gun Hoo, and Jin Woo doing well?
- Yes, I know. - Actually, I thought...
that this would be brought up after we talked about other things.
- But it was brought up right away. - Right.
To tell you the truth,
I was a professional soccer player for 16 years...
and a national team player for 11 years.
But one year of appearing on a show with my kids...
- increased my fame... - He became more famous.
- I became more famous. - Indeed.
- That happens. - It's different now.
When people see me, they're like, "He's... What was her name?"
- "Right. He's Na Eun's dad." - Na Eun's dad.
Right.
Does Gun Hoo give people his autograph these days?
- His kids are like fairies. - Gun Hoo...
When people approached us,
I could tell my autograph wasn't what they really wanted.
They actually wanted my kids' autographs.
But they couldn't get them, so they asked for mine.
But as the kids grew up,
when they saw me giving people my autograph,
they knew people actually wanted their autographs.
So they created their own autographs.
So these days, they give people their autographs too.
- His kids give their autographs. - I...
- I can give you my autograph too. - They're so cute.
- They're really cute. - Not their dad?
You said you respected one of us. Who...
That's so obvious. I mean...
As a former athlete,
he must respect his senior athletes.
- This is too... - Right. It's obvious, indeed.
- Isn't it obvious? - Exactly.
I met Joo Ho before,
and he told me things like that.
- Of course. - He said it when we met.
You can take your time and tell us about it.
- The person... - Since when have you respected us?
- The person I respect is... - Yes.
- Yeong Cheol. - What?
(It's Yeong Cheol.)
What?
The ghost is busy today...
- possessing several people here. - I'm serious.
I'll tell you why.
I want to become like Ho Dong and Jang Hoon.
They're my role models. I want to pursue that goal.
But I can't.
It's not easy.
It's hard for me to make a character for myself.
- I want to be on many TV shows. - Right.
I retired from being an athlete, and I want to pursue a new career.
- But it's not easy. - Okay.
So you're saying you don't think you can be like the two of them,
but you think you can reach Yeong Cheol's level.
- Yes, that's what it sounded like. - What does he mean...
You think you can easily reach his level, right?
- No. I respect Yeong Cheol. - I can't believe this.
- I mean it. Trust me. - It became complicated for me.
No. I really mean it.
Yeong Cheol is the only one...
- I'm following on social media. - But you know...
- Listen to me. - I've been following him...
for a very long time.
- Oh, really? - But...
- Then let me ask you a question. - Okay.
Sang Min always calls Min Soo "my dear big brother..."
- when he talks about Min Soo. - I see.
There's a famous story about them.
It happened when Sang Min announced his divorce.
That's right.
(Sang Min's press conference on his divorce on September 22, 2006.)
"Now, say a word."
What do you think about that?
To be honest, whenever I see Sang Min,
- I feel apologetic toward him. - Oh, my.
- Why? - I always feel bad.
And I have to carry the burden for the rest of my life.
It's because Min Soo, who Sang Min calls a big brother,
often shows up at places that he's not supposed to.
He often attends events he's not invited to.
It should be the other way around.
It was a very important time in Sang Min's life.
Why would he show up there?
- What a coincidence. - Exactly.
Did you find out from the news articles?
I found out what happened from the news articles.
He was riding his motorcycle without a destination.
- Then he saw reporters he knew. - He saw reporters.
The reporters said hello to him.
So he stopped his motorcycle in front of them...
and inquired after them.
And then the reporters...
- They escorted him. - escorted him to the venue.
- "Where are you taking me?" - To Sang Min's press conference.
- Yes. He asked where he was going. - Yes.
- No way. - He agreed to follow them.
- Right. - They all made way for him...
to the inside of the room.
Min Soo had no idea where he was going.
When he went inside the venue,
Sang Min wasn't even there.
And Min Soo was seated at the table in the front.
- He wasn't even wearing a suit. - He was in a biker outfit.
- He was in a biker outfit. - A biker outfit. Right.
- With a bandana, sunglasses, - And sunglasses.
And a lot of accessories including earrings.
While being seated, he asked...
what the event was about.
- You mean, the press conference. - What it was about.
He had no idea what was going to happen there.
While Min Soo was sitting at the table,
he was told about the situation...
from those who were in the room.
He told the reporters that it wasn't right...
of them to meddle in Sang Min's personal affair.
He said it was wrong of them.
While he was lecturing the reporters,
- Sang Min came in, I think. - He spoke for Sang Min.
Sang Min, how did you feel? Be honest with us.
Did you not know he was there?
- Of course, I had no idea. - How would he have known?
- It wasn't to announce my divorce. - He held a press conference.
- I needed to explain myself. - Right.
So I entered the room.
Let's say this is the seat I was supposed to sit in.
(Min Soo was sitting in his seat.)
Min Soo was sitting right here.
When he saw me entering the room, he said,
"Come on in."
(Come on in.)
Imagine that Choi Min Soo was there.
How did that happen? The timing was so weird, right?
It sounds like a prank video.
I was even more dumbfounded when he said,
"I heard everything."
"Turn your cameras toward me, please."
"Sang Min, you shouldn't be like this."
"Meet her again and try to make things work."
- I mean, he said that... - "You shouldn't be like this."
- He said that... - "You shouldn't be like this."
"Meet her again and fall in love again?"
(The advice filled with the big brother's love)
- He made a well-wishing remark. - But...
- That's why I always feel bad. - That was so funny.
And that's why I really wanted to see Sang Min here.
Sang Min, I'm always sorry.
- You know I'm always sorry, right? - But... Yes, I know.
It seems that you guys have a lot to say here.
Didn't you bring anything for us?
- Oh, I forgot. - He's carrying a backpack.
- He didn't bring a Doraemon bag. - Exactly.
This isn't what I brought from home.
I'm getting ready to pass on my Doraemon merchandise to my son.
- You do have Doraemon bags at home. - Okay. Thanks.
- Right? - Are you a fake fan of Doraemon?
- You show off what you have on TV, - Right. It's only for TV shows.
- but you don't cherish them? - He doesn't actually like Doraemon.
- Why didn't you bring it? - His facial expression changed.
That's not true.
(Don't doubt my love for Doraemon.)
- You can have a seat now. - Here's their transfer form.
June Kang, Shim Hyung Tak, and Park Joo Ho!
(Names: June Kang, Shim Hyung Tak, Park Joo Ho)
- Welcome! - I really like them.
We'll talk about the topic "The first encounter."
First up is June.
- You won the Canada regional round. - That's right.
The marriage between a popular actor and a Miss Korea contestant...
- was famous when we were younger. - It's so famous.
- Over the phone... - It drew a lot of attention.
- It was 1993. - Oh, my.
In 1993, I came to Korea as the winner...
of the regional round of Canada.
You said earlier that you had been telling the same story...
- for two years. - Yes.
I've been doing that for 30 years.
(I've been doing that for 30 years.)
(I have a long way to go.)
Even so, so many people still don't know the story.
- Their story is always fun to hear. - Earlier on...
I've been telling the same story for so many years.
The story about their love that transcended borders...
- was the talk of the town. - Right.
As far as I remember, you two met when you went for a tour...
- around the MBC building. - That's right.
- Yes. Here's how we met. - So you met him in that building.
We first met on the stage...
- of Miss Korea. - At the Miss Korea contest.
- At the contest? - So we first met...
- on the stage. - At the contest.
How would I have known?
How would I have known this man?
- Growing up in Canada, - Of course, you didn't know.
I never watched any Korean TV shows.
- There were no streaming services. - Exactly.
It was the day of the rehearsal.
He showed up for the rehearsal.
- There were 51 contestants. - That's a lot.
The other contestants went wild.
I didn't know who he was,
but I could tell he was very cool and successful.
- He had that kind of aura. - Right.
"I am cool."
He walked across the stage,
and all the other ladies whispered,
- "Oh, that's him." - They must've been excited.
- They must've screamed too. - So I kept watching him.
And he seemed to try hard to look cool.
- He must've acted so cool then. - Right.
- Yes. Right. - Yes. That's for sure.
I could just see how hard he tried to look cool.
That day, I was proud of myself because I won an award.
As I was leaving the stage,
I saw him on the stage...
- in a suit designed by Andre Kim. - Right.
- I didn't even know him then. - I remember that.
He was wearing a very flashy tuxedo,
testing the microphone.
And as soon as he saw me,
he said, "Good job," reaching out for a handshake.
So we shook hands.
I was down the stage while he was on it.
I said the same thing and left.
And he could tell...
that I didn't recognize him.
He could tell that I didn't know him.
- He must've figured it out. - Yes. He figured it out.
So I left after we met.
A week later, on the day before I left for Canada,
I was invited to the MBC building...
by the director of the show.
The director offered to give me a tour around the building...
before I went back to Canada.
- He offered to give you a tour? - That's right.
The drama called "Mother's Sea..."
- was being filmed... - It was aired around the time.
- at the time. - It was aired then. Right.
The director introduced me to Min Soo behind the set.
"Min Soo, one of the contestants of Miss Korea..."
"who came really far from Korea is here."
"Let me introduce her to you."
But Min Soo didn't look at me.
He just fiddled with his hair.
I reached out my hand,
and he saw my hand.
Then he finally looked at me.
He asked me if I was the one whom he met...
- at the contest. - He remembered her.
And we parted ways there.
I asked the director...
if he could get Min Soo's autograph for me.
He said he'd ask if Min Soo was there when we left the studio.
When we came out, Min Soo was...
doing an interview with some reporters.
So I went up to him and asked...
if I could get his autograph.
And then Min Soo...
asked me to go somewhere to have some coffee with him.
There was a cafe in the MBC building.
We had coffee at the cafe.
But my Korean was not very good.
I spoke broken Korean,
and he spoke broken English.
- So we talked to each other. - "Broken Korean?"
Three hours later, he held my hand and said,
"I'd like to propose to you."
That quickly?
- Only three hours later? - Three hours later?
He proposed to you after talking to you with his broken English?
He must've felt some kind of supernatural energy.
Right. We spent three hours together at the cafe.
He delayed the shoot because of me.
He walked around in the building,
- holding my hand. - Right. Of course.
People we ran into asked him if I was his wife.
I thought to myself, "That's not my name."
- "Why does everyone say that?" - You didn't know the word.
- Kang Hyung Soo. - "Hyung Soo."
- K.Will's real name is Hyung Soo. - If she didn't know the word...
- I thought people confused me... - With some other girl?
- with some other woman. - That's what she must've thought.
- Not K.Will, though. - Because that wasn't my name.
I was 23 years old then.
And I had one semester left to graduate college.
So he was holding my hand,
and I thought that he was so famous...
- that he held every woman's hand. - That's possible.
You thought he was a playboy.
That thought crossed my mind for a brief moment.
Also, I looked into his eyes,
and I had this feeling that I would see those eyes...
for the rest of my life at that moment.
It gave me goosebumps.
I couldn't even describe that feeling.
But I didn't think it was right.
I didn't think it was possible.
I didn't think...
I could give up my life in Canada and move to Korea.
So I decided to leave it behind as a good memory.
Min Soo gave me about five different phone numbers.
- He asked me to call him... - He must've fallen hard for her.
Before leaving the day after that.
- But I didn't call him. - Right. I remember the story.
- Gosh. - Oh, no.
So I was at the Gimpo International Airport.
On the day of leaving Korea, at the Gimpo International Airport,
- He must've come to see her. - I was having naengmyeon...
with my family on the second floor.
- We were going to say goodbye. - I see.
But then, there was a man coming to us from far.
He was wearing sunglasses...
- and had this hat on. Right. - Anyone can tell it's Min Soo.
- So... - Seriously.
Don't you think this story is just perfect for Min Soo?
So he was coming up.
- He didn't go to his schedule. - I was looking down, thinking,
"Goodness. It can't be."
"Did he really come all the way here? It can't be."
But it seemed like it was him.
I was standing at the end of the escalator when he suddenly said,
"June, I asked you to call me. Why didn't you give me a call?"
He said he came all the way there because he was so concerned.
- Did he say that... - So...
- with his broken English? - Well...
- "Hey, June! Call me." - He said everything in Korean.
- "Call back. Why not call back?" - He had this...
He brought this box in which he put...
all his photos all night. And on the backs of these photos...
- There was no social media then. - Right.
He wrote all the stories...
- from his life there. - His stories.
- He wrote his stories there. - Stories to introduce himself.
As he handed me the box,
he gave me this letter that said,
"This is our birthday."
"Can you live your life for me from this day forth, June?"
He wrote that in the letter.
And it creeped me out.
I mean...
- What is that? - It was all too fast.
- It was like a threat. - She would have thought,
- "Is this what celebrities like?" - "Can you live your life for me?"
- Living my life for someone else? - She must've been scared at first.
- I was only 23 years old. - Right.
I didn't even know who I was back then.
So he wrote this letter...
- and gave it to me. - My gosh.
After we parted at the airport that day, he came to Canada...
four times. Every weekend in a row.
He shot a drama during weekdays.
And he flew for 17 hours on weekends to Canada.
- And then he flew back to Seoul. - That's really amazing.
He did that four times in a row.
- That's unbelievable. - I know.
Listening to their story so far reminds me of this.
A drama that Min Soo starred in that we watched when we were young.
It's like "Sandglass."
- It's like a story from his drama. - That's right.
- The story and characters are... - The leading role.
It's just like a story in which Min Soo plays the leading role.
There's one more thing to add.
- When he arrived at the airport... - Right.
Andre Kim sponsored a lot of clothes...
- at that time. - Right. Andre Kim.
- He came in those clothes? - When he arrived...
When I saw him arrive at the airport from far...
He was standing out too much.
Was he wearing Andre Kim's clothes?
- Andre Kim's clothes are... - They are so fancy.
- Seriously? - His clothes are...
Do you know how fancy they are?
- They're so fancy. - Right?
- The logo represented the clothes. - The logo?
He wore one of those clothes from fashion shows?
- There was this logo. - He took a 17-hour flight in them?
- Right. With this huge golden logo. - I know.
I was flustered.
With his long coat...
When he took off his coat at my house,
he had on his suit with the same logo.
When he took off his jacket,
there was a vest with the same logo.
Hold on. How long will this go on?
(There are endless logos.)
When he took off that vest,
- his shirt had that logo too. - He's so amazing.
- Even his shirt. - That's unbelievable.
- That's a full package. - He had about five layers...
- of Andre Kim's clothes. - Gosh.
That was when he came to Canada for the first time.
(Min Soo's first arrival was quite impressive.)
My gosh.
How about your parents?
When Min Soo visited Canada so frequently,
- did they approve of him? - The thing is...
I was an only child for them.
For my parents,
if there had been any man who would have asked me to marry,
it would have been a really tough situation for them.
I always thought about this.
I thought it might be impossible for me...
to marry a Korean guy.
- And I think... - There was a cultural difference.
That's what my parents had in mind back then.
And then they met this very traditional Korean guy.
A traditional Korean man who should have been born 200 years ago.
(A man who was born in the wrong era)
- Isn't that right? - Right.
- Seriously. - That was spot on.
- You know what I mean, right? - Like a general from the old days.
He was like the character from "Highlander."
He was born at the wrong time.
Right? I met this guy who should've been born 200 years ago.
The scene of my parents...
talking to him...
It was something I couldn't imagine.
Also, Min Soo and my parents...
- got along so well. - He did?
My parents were enjoying his company,
and they looked so happy. As I was watching them...
"Gosh, I can't believe this is happening."
"How could they accept him like this?"
I have a question. According to what you just said...
It sounded like your parents said yes,
- but you didn't yet? - I wasn't... Right.
I didn't have a chance to say yes.
Things just happened so suddenly.
I was at the wedding hall all of a sudden.
I saw him and thought,
"I guess it's a little late to tell him no."
- Gosh. - That's what you thought?
There were so many people that I didn't know at the church.
So then, I had so many thoughts in my head.
"How did things turn out like this?"
That's what I thought.
- So that's what happened. - Then I want to ask what was...
- You got married at 23. - I got married then.
You were so young then.
What was the ideal type of man...
that you wanted back then?
- Well, it's... - Compared to Min Soo.
It wasn't him.
- So it wasn't him. - He's different.
- It wasn't him. - Your ideal type wasn't him.
- My ideal type of man was... - So it wasn't him.
I didn't want someone who had a strong personality.
I wanted to meet...
someone calm and who studied while focused.
That was the type of man...
- Like an adorable dork? - I liked back then.
- I see. - But...
- he's someone I couldn't imagine. - He's the polar opposite.
- That's who I got married to. - He's a man from 200 years ago.
Right. A man from 200 years ago.
This is just like, "Guardian: The Lonely and Great God."
- Gosh, from 200 years ago. - A man from 200 years ago.
- Hyung Tak, you like this story? - Next.
- Let's listen to Hyung Tak. - Next is Hyung Tak...
- who worried so much. - Right.
About your first meeting with your wife, you wrote,
"An accident while digging?" What do you mean?
- "An accident while digging." Yes. - You were digging something?
I went to shoot a show called...
- "Nanaland." - "Nanaland."
This was the purpose of this show.
It was to let people know about geek culture.
It was a show for that.
- So there were geeks on the show. - Right.
- They asked me to join the show... - I see.
As a geek who represented Korea.
So I accepted the offer.
That night, I was sleeping,
I had this dream. There were five dragons flying in the sky.
- Goodness. - Then the dragons turned around...
and became a one big dragon, and it charged toward me.
I woke up as it came into me.
- Isn't that a conception dream? - It sounds like a conception dream.
- Five dragons become one? - They became one?
Didn't you have morning sickness?
That sounds like a conception dream.
- Hyung Tak. - It sounds like...
you're going to have a king or something.
Hyung Tak, so you went to Japan to shoot,
and you were sleeping in Japan.
No. It was before going to Japan for a shoot.
- The day before departure? - My goodness.
- This is amazing. - You had this dream then?
We finished shooting at the Doraemon Museum.
The next day, we went to a robot cafe to shoot an episode.
That day, there was this one person who was in charge of the robot cafe.
To help us shoot the show, she was there.
And I couldn't take my eyes off of her while shooting the show.
- She was so beautiful. My goodness. - Who became your wife.
- Goodness. - So she was the dragon.
"I won't get married if it's not her."
- That's what I thought. - You felt it like that?
That's what I thought while I was shooting the show.
- You meet the one just like that. - I guess you somehow know it.
Right. So when the shoot was over,
when the staff members were having a meal,
I went to her who was standing at the entrance.
I wanted to ease the atmosphere...
and wanted her to see me as a funny guy.
So in Japanese, I said,
"I'm a handsome actor from Korea."
"I'm a Korean actor."
- "Handsome guy." - "Handsome guy."
- It was broken Japanese. - Right.
- Right. It was broken Japanese. - My goodness.
So the language should be broken...
- for you to get married. - You fall in love when it's broken.
So when I said that, her face looked awkward.
(She had a straight face when she heard him.)
Later, I asked her about it.
She told me that...
she thought I was a serious narcissist.
- I see. - Someone who loves himself.
She said that she didn't like it.
So I went to the local coordinator...
and asked if I could get her social network ID.
He got it somehow,
and I sent her a message on that day.
"Thank you for your hard work today."
Then she replied back.
"You did great today. Did you go back to Korea safely?"
I said, "I did."
And she didn't reply after that.
And the next day, when I got up, I send her messages like,
"I had breakfast. Did you have lunch?"
"Did you have dinner? You did a great job today."
"I'm going out for a shoot."
I kept sending her messages,
but I wouldn't get a reply. She would read and not answer.
She kept reading and not answering.
After that, it went on for about two more weeks.
(He sent her messages for 2 more weeks.)
And then I finally got a reply.
- It came. - I got a reply.
"Do you remember me?" That's what the reply was.
As soon as I got it, I said,
"No, I don't remember. So I think I should go to Japan."
- "I'll be right there." - Gosh.
So I went to Japan,
- and that's how we started dating. - Gosh.
That's amazing.
With this story,
you seem like Min Soo, although you're different.
Yes, well...
Only the flight time is different.
- As I was listening, - Yes.
It felt like I had become Min Soo.
But why didn't she answer your messages?
The reason she didn't answer...
was because I was an actor.
- She thought my life... - That you were a playboy?
- would be like that. - That you were like that to women?
Yes. So...
She was very worried...
and was determined not to date me.
But I kept knocking.
I kept sending her messages,
and they say a bridge will fall down if you keep knocking at it.
So she let down her wall.
- A bridge won't fall if you... - Will a bridge fall if you knock?
- That should not happen. - Is that not it?
You need to knock on it before you cross.
Oh, you're supposed to cross it.
He's similar to me.
His knowledge is similar to mine.
I thought you were correct for a second.
You said the bridge would fall.
Will it fall down if you knock on it?
Are you talking about the tree that won't stand still...
if you strike it ten times?
- Yes, that's it. - Right?
I struck ten times.
You said the bridge fell down.
So what happened when you went to Japan?
- I went there and we met, - Yes.
- and I suggested that we eat. - Yes.
So we ate,
and after eating,
she said she had plans with her friend and left.
That's so sad.
And then we met again the next day...
and had coffee.
Usually, after that,
it's common to go somewhere else after that, right?
She just had coffee and went home.
- She left again? - Gosh.
So when did your wife open up to you?
About that...
She was on the subway with me...
in Japan. It was packed,
so I held her hand so she wouldn't fall over.
She told me that she usually hated it...
when someone touched her.
But when I held her hand,
she said that she didn't mind it at all.
So she thought I might be a good match,
and she searched online.
She searched my name online to see who I was in Korea.
She kept searching,
and it said that I was a wholesome actor...
and that I was good to my parents.
That's what it said on the news.
So she decided to open up to me after that.
And after that, we had a drink for the first time.
- Two draft beers? - Yes.
- Two. - Yes, two.
- Two. - Two.
- Two draft beers. - Yes.
- Two draft beers. - I understood that.
After all that coffee.
(I understood that.)
So we went for a drink that day,
and I knew it was time.
We went for a drink at 4pm at a Japanese bar...
and kept drinking.
We had draft beers.
I escorted her home in a taxi...
and sent her home.
- Did you have the feeling that day? - Yes.
I sent her home, and she liked that.
She realized what a gentleman I was.
How many times had you gone to Japan at that point?
That was about five months later.
- Five months? - Five months? Really?
It's so interesting that you didn't give up for five months.
- That's amazing. - That happens when you're in love.
- It just had to be her. - I know.
So at that time,
I actually told Hee Chul.
During a shoot,
I said, "I have a Japanese girlfriend."
"I heard you do, too."
- Oh... - So...
Did you?
(Oh... Did you?)
I didn't know.
- Oh, I... - We don't know.
He had a Japanese girlfriend back then.
- He did. - Yes.
I thought he would have forgotten about that.
- He has a good memory. - The thing is...
You forgot about the bridge,
but you remembered this story.
- Sure. I remember it all. - I'm curious about Joo Ho.
He said they first met at FC Basel.
I know that really well.
That was your team back then in Switzerland.
- FC Basel in Switzerland. - Yes.
I was a soccer player in Japan,
and I was transferred to FC Basel.
So I was a soccer player back then.
I was playing in games,
and my wife was a college student.
She had a part-time job at FC Basel during the weekends.
But we had no one in common back then.
My wife traveled to Korea...
during her college years,
and she was on the plane...
back to Switzerland.
My family was also on that plane,
and they were coming to visit me in Switzerland,
and my little brother's seat...
was next to my wife, Anna.
- What a coincidence. - What?
- Gosh, - Really?
Is there such a thing as destiny?
He felt so awkward,
so he showed her my picture...
and said that his brother was a soccer player.
With his broken English.
It has to be broken.
He told her, with his broken English,
and she thought he was just a fan.
She thought he was a fan of FC Basel.
So they parted like that.
Anna was working during the weekend,
and my family came to see my game.
They were in the VIP family area,
and Anna was working there.
That's destiny.
My mom was trying to ask for a blanket...
and some drinks,
but it wasn't working out well.
My wife saw her,
and since she knew a bit of Korean,
she gave it to her.
The items she was asking for.
Through that incident, my little sister...
became friends with Anna,
and they kept staying in touch.
So I just knew her as my little sister's friend...
- for about a year. - Your sister's friend?
Yes, my little sister's friend.
But then, my team won,
and we had a celebration party...
until late in the night,
and we had a motorcycle...
to take us into the downtown.
And my wife was standing there when it was late at night.
She said, "Congratulations on your victory."
- In Korean? - In Korean.
- What? - In Korean. "Congratulations."
So I realized that she had been waiting there...
late in the night...
- to congratulate me. - You must've been grateful.
So I asked my sister for her number...
so that I could treat her to dinner.
That's how we had our first date.
(That's how the couple had their first date.)
And then...
Who wanted to go steady first?
I think it was my wife.
- What? - It was my wife.
We have to listen to her story, too.
A lot of men lie like that.
- Listen. - "She liked me more."
Listen and see if I'm right.
For a while, we just met up sometimes...
to have dinner and go on walks.
But I had to keep talking in English,
and it became a burden.
So I stopped contacting her for a while, but then she said,
"Am I a woman to you or just a friend?"
(Am I a woman to you or just a friend?)
- That sounds significant. - Gosh.
That is a confession.
You should have been witty and said, "You're my girlfriend."
So?
- So I... - You weren't witty, were you?
- I wasn't. - What?
- What did you say to her? - What did you say?
What did you say?
"We're friends, but you're a woman,"
"so you are my woman friend."
To be honest, from a woman's perspective,
isn't that the worst answer?
- Yes, it's not this nor that. - Right?
Yes, does he like me,
- or not? - You should go to Canada...
- like Min Soo did. - Yes.
You should have held her hand. "You're my woman!"
(You are my woman!)
The reason I said that back then was because...
I had never even thought of dating a foreigner,
or even marrying a foreigner.
- Not at all. It was ruled out. - Sure.
That's possible.
That's how it was,
but after she asked me that,
she was cute,
- and she was pretty. - She's so pretty.
Yes. So that's how...
I asked her out.
- That's how it went. - He likes it.
Look at his smile when he's talking about it.
He liked her first.
- Joo Ho... - He liked her a lot.
- You're right. - But the important thing is that...
Joo Ho probably spoke in broken English back then.
- You're right. - So he wasn't clear about it.
- You're right. - That's right.
So that's how it became a love story.
- You're right. - She didn't catch what he said.
Broken languages bring people together.
- Yes. - Listen.
Yeong Cheol is good at English, so it never works out for him.
I should have been bad at it.
- I should have been bad at English. - He is... June.
Yeong Cheol is good at both...
- English and Japanese. - I speak English and Japanese.
- That's why it doesn't work. - Sure.
- He is ready to be like Min Soo. - It has to be broken.
- It has to be broken. - We will now study the couples.
I am really curious about this as well.
Is the process for marriage registration different,
- compared to us? - Marriage registration?
- It depends on the country. - How does it differ?
Do you do it in both countries?
- Is that how you do it? - Do you register on both sides?
- You register on both sides. - Right?
You register in Japan and Korea?
- You register in Korea and Japan. - Yes.
- Do you go to a district office? - Yes. A district office.
- Really? - The parents should be witnesses.
The witnesses should be there.
You need witnesses in Korea as well.
- Right. - They just need to fill the form.
Right.
In Japan,
the day you get married...
- isn't the wedding anniversary. - Then?
The day you register your marriage...
- is the day. - The day you fill in the forms?
That's the day...
- you really got married. - That's the day.
- What about Joo Ho? - That...
Since I'm Korean,
I was going to register the marriage and have a wedding ceremony.
But my wife said, "We don't need to register our marriage..."
"or have a wedding ceremony."
- She had a foreigner's mindset. - What was the reason?
I don't think it's a foreigner's mindset.
- I think that's her mindset. - Is it?
That's what I felt at the time.
She said, "This is all meaningless..."
"if we break up."
"So, we don't need to do it,"
"and if we need to, we can do it when the need arises."
- "That's not what's important." - Still.
- "That's not what's important." - But...
That was dumb of you. Even if she said that...
- You should have still done it. - You should have celebrated it.
- What do you think is right? - She said it was meaningless.
- Who do we have to ask? - According to her perspective...
- What's important... - Who should we ask?
- is that the two of you live well. - Right.
- Someone, please explain. - She didn't want a wedding.
She said she really didn't want a wedding.
- I thought she was joking. - She's a realist.
- Someone, please explain. - She didn't want to stand...
in front of people at the wedding.
- Still. - She really hated it.
- Did you register your marriage? - We got registered later.
We registered our marriage in Switzerland too.
What do you think...
about having no wedding ceremony, June?
That's really hard to judge.
- People have different values... - Values.
- regarding this. - That's right.
As for me, I had...
- a picture in mind. - Your fantasy.
- Didn't you hold a grand wedding? - As for us...
- Everybody came. - There were reporters.
Of course, there were very many reporters,
and we held it at a church.
That was in Korea.
The official wedding in Korea took place at a church.
In Canada, it happened a few months earlier.
We held a sort of an engagement...
and wedding ceremony in Canada.
Then we received a certification...
- saying we were... - You signed it.
- legally married. - The marriage registration.
When I got married,
there was a married life that I had imagined.
I wanted certain situations...
and a certain lifestyle.
I wanted my husband to do the groceries sometimes.
There were such pictures I had in mind.
But when I got married,
just one of those dreams came true.
This is what it is. I wanted...
to get in our wedding car...
wearing my wedding dress...
and leave like that.
(The moment her dream came true)
Only that part came true.
Nothing else came true.
What's interesting is...
- this is what true marriage is. - Nothing came true?
We all have things we hope,
- Right. - but when you get married,
they all break.
What I was worried about at first...
was that he could cause trouble...
because he was such a famous actor.
Trouble in terms of women.
In that area.
So, I was 23 years old back then,
and he was my first love.
So I thought, if this man...
had any issues that involved women,
I wouldn't be able to deal with that.
I thought I should just quietly leave.
- That's what I thought. - Quietly leave?
I thought I should leave with a cool attitude.
That's what I had in mind.
- You were preparing yourself. - Right.
I lived with him,
but that was the only problem that didn't happen.
All kinds of troubles happened.
(Troubles that weren't on her mind happened.)
Everything except issues with women.
What June is saying is,
the problem...
- she was most worried about... - Right.
- didn't happen. - That didn't happen.
- You know what I'm saying, right? - Only that didn't happen.
All kinds of problems happened.
Whenever they happened,
I thought, "This isn't it."
"This also isn't it."
I lived 30 years like that.
It was vague for her.
- She had no cause to leave. - I mean...
Somehow, I was waiting for that one thing to happen.
- Women issues. - But it didn't happen.
- It didn't happen. - It didn't happen.
I saw a video on YouTube...
where you said you would marry Min Soo even in your next life.
- You said that. - Right.
I would choose this man even in my 1,000th life.
Why?
Yoo Sung's father has a unique character.
- Actually, - Right.
He's someone who told me who he was...
in only three hours after we met.
People gave him many titles in Korea...
like "tough guy" and everything.
I think he's a true "tough guy."
He's really tough when he needs to be.
But to me,
- he's really gentle. - Right.
- He treats me well. - He's gentle to his wife.
I'm the only one who knows that side of him.
The world doesn't know.
So I thought there wouldn't be...
such an amazing man whom only I knew...
- That's so cool. - in this world.
At the time,
he was surrounded by such beautiful women.
- There were so many. - That's right.
- An ocean of beautiful women. - I wondered why he loved me...
and trusted me so much.
He appreciated my charm...
more than anyone else, and he cared about me...
even more than my parents.
- That's amazing. - That's cool.
- I just want to brag a little. - It's so sweet.
- That man... - I'd want to brag so much.
Said I had so much to learn from...
and always looked at me.
Of course, I would marry him 1,000 times.
Even if you are born again.
That's amazing.
- Then... - In the end,
Min Soo did a great job...
- Of course. - finding June.
- It happened really quickly. - That's right.
How could he find...
- such an amazing person... - I'm really grateful.
In such a short time?
- That's right. - Thank you so much,
Seo Jeong. I appreciate it.
- Seo Jeong. - Seo Jeong.
It's okay. That's about right.
- But... - You often speak broken Korean.
You can call me however you want.
Seo Jeong.
What about Hyung Tak?
Would you marry your current wife even if you are born again?
Of course.
- Of course. - Of course.
What about Joo Ho?
I would marry my wife again no matter what.
My wife was born in Argentina,
and I was born in Korea.
(They were born in opposite ends of the world...)
(with a 12-hour time difference.)
It's amazing that we're living together now.
That's true fate.
We had Na Eun, Gun Hoo, and Jin Woo.
We have to get married and have children...
to meet these three.
- Right. - That's why...
I have to get married to her again.
Food is also a part of culture.
It would be difficult to have different tastes.
- That would be the hardest. - Did you have trouble with that?
You were 23 when you got married, June.
You would have had no chance to make Korean food...
- before coming to Korea. - Didn't you practice?
That's right.
I had never made it before.
I met Min Soo in the last semester...
in university.
I had never cooked Korean food...
- in the dormitory. - Right.
Even more, I had never cooked rice before.
After I got married,
I realized this man should have been born 200 years ago.
He thought...
all women would be able to make Korean food.
He expected that.
At the time,
I heard the word "baekban..."
from this man.
I thought, "Korea is a terrible place for women."
One hundred side dishes?
- That was what baekban meant to me. - One hundred side dishes.
Is that why it's baekban?
- I thought there wouldn't be... - No.
- No. That wouldn't be. - a more disgusting word than that.
- Then, were Korean women... - Baekban.
- You could think like that. - supposed to make...
- one hundred side dishes? - Right.
I couldn't see the end.
When would I have the time to make baekban?
I bought a Korean cookbook written in English.
- That's amazing. - It was written in English.
I learned how to make radish soup,
rice, and everything.
I learned everything from the beginning.
I looked at the seasoning containers every day...
and wondered, "How do I make it?"
From 1 to 100,
- it was the hardest task for me. - Unbelievable.
The kitchen was a battlefield for me.
I learned and tried one thing after the next.
But you know how picky this man is.
If it didn't taste right, he told me outright.
- "This isn't it." - Like that.
"It's not like how I remember it."
- That must've really hurt. - It's not that one.
Min Soo must've been like...
- Dae Bal... - Dae Bal.
- from "What Is Love" at home. - Dae Bal.
- I watched... - A total patriarch.
Several episodes with Dae Bal in it.
I instantly knew it wasn't acting.
He was himself for real.
(Method acting full of real life)
- He wasn't acting. - Right.
- But many acknowledged him for it. - A patriarch.
When I watched it, I thought, "That's just Min Soo."
When it comes to rice, there's mushy rice,
- hard rice, - Half-cooked rice.
- and so forth. - Right.
I feared that the most.
After I cooked the rice and served it to Min Soo,
he said, "Today's rice is wrong."
That made me think, "What's the right rice?"
(What's the right rice?)
I can laugh with you all today.
- But back then, I cried... - It must've been hard.
In front of the rice cooker every day.
The rice alone was already tough.
And as Min Soo is an actor,
he eats three meals a day when not acting.
- Right. - When...
Breakfast, lunch, and dinner.
- He's incredible in many ways. - He won't have...
the same menu for the next meal.
I sometimes change the order of the side dishes.
I switch places and add another sauce.
But he notices it right away...
and doesn't eat it.
He doesn't.
And snacks.
I have to prepare those annoying snacks.
Min Soo eats snacks in between meals.
But it's impossible to know...
what kind of snacks he's craving.
After something spicy,
- he might want a sweet snack... - Something sweet.
Or a cold one.
I learned the ropes.
Now that I've done it for 30 years,
(After cooking for 30 years)
I know my husband's appetite like the back of my hand.
When I ask what my husband had for lunch...
and he tells me,
I know what he'll like for dinner.
With that, Min Soo always says,
"How do you know what I want, June?"
It's because I've been suffering for 30 years.
Since it's been 30 years,
I've become an expert in him.
And my husband became an expert in me.
That has made us...
into a loving couple now.
I never thought a day this happy could happen.
Right. But to come this far,
eating habits are one thing,
but what about language?
How did you overcome the language barrier?
It's a challenge even to this day.
Compared to the past, we're doing much better.
- It's problematic when we fight. - When you fight.
There's a sudden moment when the air turns heavy...
in the middle of a conversation.
It's when I use the wrong word.
- When you talk in English? - When we use English.
- Because... - Your wife.
What language did she use...
in Switzerland other than English?
Switzerland doesn't have its own language.
The people use English, German, French, and Spanish.
- All four? - Yes.
Goodness.
Here's an example.
Something like, "You're bored, right?"
I was going to ask if Anna was bored.
But I said, "You're a boring person."
- That must've caused a big fight. - Right?
Boring and bored.
I mixed up the words, causing a fight.
I had to explain myself,
but the mood wasn't right.
At a time like that, I use a translator.
- You use it? - Yes, right away.
- I show it to her... - It's hard to communicate.
And let her know what I mean.
Things calm down again with time.
Fighting with my husband was very difficult.
He only talked about his side of the story,
regardless of whether I understood or not.
And that would go on for hours.
You know it, don't you?
When he starts talking, there's no end to it.
- Min Soo is like that. - Right?
I ended up forgetting the reason...
we started this fight.
Here's the idea that stuck with me.
Because my husband talks so much,
I should get a notebook...
and write what I want to say...
while he talks.
Then, I wouldn't forget the points I wanted to make,
even if my turn to speak came later.
When we were in an unpleasant situation,
- I went and got my notebook. - During a fight?
After that, I said, "Please talk."
- While fighting? - That's scary.
But my husband would be enraged.
He'd ask, "June. What are you doing right now?"
"Because you talk for quite a while,"
"I'll forget again."
"I'm writing whatever I want to say down."
His response to that was, "This isn't necessary."
"I'll make sure you understand everything,"
"so you don't have to jot down anything."
- He refused to listen. - I thought it wasn't easy.
Living such a life would be a challenge.
Since then, I started drawing comics.
I put all my words into the speech bubbles...
and made a comic.
Back then, Min Soo started shooting "Sandglass."
If he wasn't at home at night, I left...
the comic I drew on his pillow.
My husband would read it.
Everything, even curse words, was there.
Although my spelling was all wrong,
my message got through.
- Even curse words? - After reading that,
Min Soo realized I saw the whole picture...
and had my own stance.
He was deeply moved.
Do you still have the comics with you?
There's only one left.
(The comic June drew back then)
If you had kept a collection and published it,
it would've made a bestseller.
We have a different sense of humor.
In Korea, people say,
"You're so ugly."
- Like, "Gosh, you're so ugly." - Yes.
We say that even when someone is cute.
- Whenever Min Soo said that, - It's an ironic expression.
- I thought... - It must've been a shock.
He criticized my looks as he worked with beautiful actresses,
like, "Why are you so guly?"
- It would hurt. - That'd upset you.
There I thought, "How can he say that while smiling?"
"How heartless of him."
He kept calling me ugly.
It must feel cruel to someone who doesn't know.
We had such situations.
But later on, I realized that was...
- expressing affection. - An expression of love.
- He meant you were cute. - "How ugly."
- Exactly. - "You're so ugly."
That caused a big misunderstanding.
There was one time when I had the biggest fight with my wife.
On the day I introduced my wife to Soo Geun at the funeral hall,
- Did you fight that day? - I drank...
- Why? - until 4am.
As we were in the province, my wife had to drive,
but she couldn't understand that.
She said, "You shouldn't have drunk."
But she's not good at Korean.
I refuted by saying, "How is it bad that I drank?"
I'm sure my wife didn't understand that,
but I went on and on all alone.
There was one word that set me off.
- What was it? - My wife said,
"What's this?" in Japanese.
At that moment, I was like, "What?"
I believed it was offensive,
and so did my wife.
What's this?
- In Japanese? - "What's this?" in Japanese.
(What's this?)
The two kept going, "What's this?"
What's this?
Because there's a language barrier,
- the fights... - There are cultural differences.
- Misunderstandings are common. - We laugh it off.
Even the funeral culture must be different.
Here are the last keywords of the three.
First, June is on a roll with this.
It says, "Jennie of the home shopping world."
- Jennie. - Jennie of the home shopping world.
The annual sales are said to be 60 million dollars.
You made over 20 million dollars in 1 hour.
- Really? - In one hour?
Words that it happened...
- have been going around. - Yes.
I've been doing it for eight years now.
But I still can't believe it.
I'm not someone with experience...
to host home shopping.
When I was given the offer, I thought I couldn't do it.
I'm not skilled. That includes Korean.
What's more,
it's a two-hour live show.
There were times when I made slight mistakes.
After all, it was a live home shopping show.
If I were to tell you a story,
we had a salted seafood master on the show.
A male who was quite old.
- It's already funny. - There were...
- I'm already worried. - various types of salted seafood.
And he was such a gentle master.
So, I said to the camera,
"I've tried many kinds of salted seafood,"
"and this master's is the best."
(A naughty compliment for some reason)
That's funny.
That happens. It's not a wrong expression.
When we talk about salted seafood,
you don't say the whole word.
- You say salted. - Yes.
- Right. - So I said, "I've tried..."
"all kinds of salted seafood,"
"and the best of all was the master's."
With our arms crossed.
- I was wearing an in-ear. - "In-ear."
- Yes. - In the in-ear,
the producer couldn't say anything.
I heard him laughing so much.
Yes.
Cameramen were...
- It's not exactly wrong. - The cameramen...
The cameramen were sitting on chairs.
They all fell from their chairs.
Right at that moment.
They were laughing so much.
I was flustered.
I have one more story.
When I first came to Korea,
I tried to learn...
the titles for married women.
- The titles. - And I was told...
"Nyeon" in Korean was...
a bad word.
You shouldn't call any women...
- "Nyeon." - No.
It wasn't appropriate.
But I thought there were exceptions...
like married "nyeon."
I thought I heard married "nyeon,"
so I thought that was okay.
When I was introducing myself officially,
I said, "Hello. I'm June Kang."
"I'm married 'nyeon.'"
I often said that.
Everyone froze every time.
This word "nyeon" was so difficult...
because my husband said,
"I shall get this relationship."
- "Relationship?" - Yes, so I was like,
"This nyeon?"
"What are you talking about?"
"Did you just call me nyeon?"
You thought he was disregarding you.
When he said, "I shall get this relationship,"
why was it okay for him...
- to say that? - Right.
- That slight difference. - June.
When you were on home shopping,
didn't Min Soo suddenly barge in...
like he did to...
- Yes. - Sang Min's press conference?
- So... - Really?
During the live show.
It was very important.
To be honest, I feel great responsibility...
- during those two hours. - Right.
While I was hosting,
on the other side of the studio,
I saw him entering.
- I saw him entering. - You saw him.
He was walking around...
when I was doing a live show.
There must be securities.
There are people who can and can't come in.
Why did they let him in?
(Why did they let him in?)
I started sweating.
So I was hoping...
since he was a broadcasting expert,
he wouldn't come in here.
- You doubted it. - My husband would...
- know that much. - Right.
Then he slowly started approaching me.
Then he stood...
- next to me. - Really?
And the stew pot.
- I can see him. - You know how greedy I am?
- Were you looking at him? - Yes.
- Your eyes... - You just made eye contact.
(Her eyes are suddenly shaking.)
- My goodness. My husband is... - Yes.
Here in this broadcasting station.
(Laughing)
This bowl.
- Oh, my. - I prepared...
- "Oh, my." - a pot for stew.
- You're not laughing... - I hope...
- because you want to. - he doesn't come in here.
- My husband's in here. I'm sorry. - The show is...
(Min Soo is here.)
(Laughing)
(Min Soo appears on his own.)
(Trying to be smooth)
- I'm here. - Yes, honey.
(Be quiet if you want to survive.)
- She... - Yes?
Couldn't sleep...
- last night. - No.
I was worried about you.
My goodness.
- Okay. - On my way...
- "Okay." - to work,
I suddenly missed her so much,
so I decided to come without a shower.
- Oh, my. - How nice of you.
- Oh, my. - Honey,
- you can go now. - How romantic.
I have something to say.
- Gray's sold out. - All I see is the look on her face.
- "Sold out." - You didn't know what to do.
- Hurry up and leave. - Can you tell?
(Please get out.)
- You weren't glad to see him. - You weren't glad to see him.
We made a promise...
after that show.
Never...
And to the securities, never...
- Don't let him in. - let him in.
Unless I allow it,
- never let him in. - I see.
- That day, - That's funny.
- did you sell out? - It went well.
- Yes. - It went well.
Even now,
it still makes me sweat.
It was so uncomfortable.
Joo Ho.
- He shouldn't come in. - That is...
(June's social media posting at the time)
(Min Soo is never predictable. Min Soo is dynamic.)
(He shouldn't be allowed in broadcasting stations.)
Oh, right. YouTube.
How did you start YouTube?
Actually, my husband...
I've been saying the same thing for over 30 years.
You know that. I'm sorry.
I said it 30 years ago...
on Um Aing Ran and Lee Taek Rim's show.
That long ago...
It was 1995 or something. Anyway,
I'm saying...
the exact same thing I said on that show now.
It gives me the chills.
You should be prepared.
You have to say the same thing for the next 30 years.
You shouldn't be offended already.
- It's amazing that it works. - That's not the point.
No matter how much you say it,
- some people don't listen. - Of course.
- Yes. - Of course.
- It doesn't work on everyone. - That's normal.
- I'm here for a good lesson today. - So...
For 30 years,
I kept talking about my husband.
I realized maybe I have something to say about myself too.
- My own story. - That's why you started YouTube.
That's how I began YouTube.
It's "Kkangjune."
- "Kkangjune." - "Kkangjune."
I became wild June Kang.
(It's about her life as June instead of Choi Min Soo's wife.)
(I got married when I was 23.)
(But I don't recommend it.)
I want to talk about myself.
- It's your new challenge. - That sounds fun.
- Yes. - All right.
Next. Hyung Tak, you wrote...
"Back to my career."
- Yes. - Are you starting a new series?
- Or... - What is it?
It's "Reverse."
- "Reverse?" - "Reverse."
- Starred by Go Soo. - Go Soo.
I'm back to acting after four years.
I have a thirst for acting.
I'm a detective in this series.
On set,
people are complimenting...
that I'm a real actor.
It gives me pleasure.
- It's different. - Yes.
I'm like, "I was born to act."
"This will be my last variety show."
Are you abandoning variety shows?
If I get paid,
I'll still do it.
You're abandoning variety shows...
and Doraemon.
No. Says who?
You're abandoning everything.
Why would I abandon Doraemon?
Do you still have them at home?
They're in the storage room.
- That's sad. - In the storage?
To make a room for my baby,
I managed the construction...
from the start to the end including the wallpaper.
I even built the shower booth in the restroom...
to take a bath with my baby.
I built a wall,
- so we can play in the water later. - Oh, my.
I filmed the construction.
- That's amazing. - Yes.
I heard you were selling Doraemon on the Internet.
I sell everything except Doraemon.
- What? - Everything except Doraemon.
- Everything except Doraemon? - Everything except Doraemon.
Everything except Doraemon.
Because it was his best friend...
- when he struggled the most. - Yes.
Except Doraemon,
- I sold everything online. - What did you sell?
I'm trying to sell as much as I can.
It occurred to me.
"I could get something better for my baby with this money."
When that thought occurred to me,
- I guess that's what dads do. - I started emptying the storage.
That's what you should do. Good job.
Joo Ho's last related word is...
the sports entertainer.
There are many sports entertainers in Korea.
Have you made up your mind to focus on variety shows?
I want to, but it's not that easy.
After I retired, my first variety show was...
- Ho Dong's show. - I see.
- "Strong Heart." - Oh, "Strong Heart."
I was planning...
to become...
an entertainer...
by appearing on that show.
But it wasn't as easy as I thought it'd be.
- No. - I told my kids,
"Although I'm not a soccer player anymore,"
"I'll appear on many TV shows..."
"and get you something delicious."
Na Eun said she'd give me a heart...
every time I appear on TV.
She said she'd add a heart next to my name...
- on her phone. - I see.
At the time, I started two.
"Shooting Stars" and a YouTube show.
("Shooting Stars" and a YouTube show)
- Okay. - But I still have two hearts.
Just two?
I'm worried because there are...
- Ho Dong and Jang Hoon. - Won't she give a heart for this...
since you're only a guest?
- She won't give a heart for this. - It's a pretty major show.
- He needs to be a regular. - I'm only a guest.
- A regular. - I need to be a regular.
- This one should count. - A schedule.
- He needs to be a regular. - Yes.
- He's a guest today. - YouTube didn't count at first,
but she changed her mind later and gave me a heart.
Your children grew up a lot, right?
- Of course. - How old are they now?
- They're 11, 9, - My goodness.
- and 6 years old. - That's incredible.
- Children grow up so fast. - Do they talk about their dreams?
Do they talk about what they'll become in the future?
Na Eun talks about it with more seriousness.
She entered elementary school.
She's interested in musicals these days.
(The daily life of an aspiring musical actress)
(I see bugs around me)
As for Gun Hoo and Jin Woo,
- they've watched me play soccer. - Of course.
So they want to be a soccer player.
Gun Hoo in particular wants to be...
Korea's national soccer player who's better than me.
- I told him to go ahead. - It won't be easy.
I told him to give it a go.
- Jin Woo is different. - What does he say?
He wants to be a national soccer player.
But he doesn't know if it'll be for Argentina,
Switzerland, or Korea.
(Torn between Argentina, Switzerland, and Korea)
- He can choose. - After all,
he can choose thanks to his mom.
- That's right. - He wants to be a global star.
I found it funny.
I told him to work hard.
- I see. - I listen to their dreams.
How does your wife, Anna, raise...
the children?
- Does her way move you? - Really?
Her way moves me on many occasions.
She's living in a foreign country.
- Seriously. It's a foreign country. - Just as June moved to Korea...
at a young age,
- Anna did the same. - Totally.
Because of that, she learns the Korean culture...
through books...
and people's words.
She stresses the Korean culture and morals...
to the children.
Thus, she teaches them traditional Korean games.
Our children have played yutnori from a young age.
Gun Hoo really likes yutnori.
- I see. - Seriously.
She has played them "Arirang" from a young age.
Because of that,
our children are accepting the Korean culture rather well.
- That's nice. - There's one more thing.
Since I worked as a soccer player for many years,
I was away from my children often when they were little.
- It diminished our connection. - That's right.
There was little communication.
But whenever she bought them something,
she said that it was from me.
- "It's from Dad." - "We're doing this Dad's money."
- "Dad sent this from Korea." - "He worked hard."
- "Dad thought about you guys." - It's so nice of her.
- How nice. - I was so moved.
Whom do the children like better, Mom or Dad?
The answer is still Mom, right?
- The answer is still Mom. - That's right.
Their answer is Dad when they want something.
- That's right. - It's always Mom.
- It can't be helped. - It's Dad when they want something.
Still, Na Eun is on your side.
No, she isn't.
I thought that too.
She's on her mom's side.
She's either her mom's ally or a mediator.
- I see. - You make me want to get married.
(Still, Joo Ho's family is very happy.)
Hold on. We're doing something very special for an art class.
- We need to get ready. - Let's go.
- An art class? - Let's go and get ready.
- Let's go. - An art class.
- Was there an art class? - An art class?
Didn't your heart flutter...
upon listening to the transfer students' stories...
- about love and family? - That's right.
Of course.
Today, you'll make...
- the best present for your spouse. - What?
- Only a few of us have a spouse. - What if we never had one...
or lost one?
- Seriously. - I thought about the former,
but not the latter.
- How about those who lost one? - Let's do this then.
- I'll sort it out. - Imagine your future spouse.
If you're married, make it for your spouse.
If you're in a relationship, make it for your lover.
If you're single, make it...
for your future lover and spouse.
- When... - Now, you can write a poem.
- For goodness' sake. - You can make a drawing.
You can write a letter.
You can make a wish coupon.
- A wish coupon? - Do what you want freely...
in order to make...
the best present for someone special.
June, there must be many things...
you want to give to Yoo Sung's dad.
There's just one.
- Just one? - Yes.
He took too many things.
- What should I do? - Everything is yours.
Everything is mine.
- Yours is mine. - Go ahead.
- Mine is mine. - Mine.
Perhaps I should make a drawing of my favorite moment.
That would be nice.
You can also make a drawing of the desired future.
Okay.
(Everyone becomes serious.)
- I thought of what to do. - Let's begin.
I'll write the words too.
(He writes down his sincerity.)
Kyung Hoon, your wife must be expectant.
"What will Kyung Hoon make?"
I forgot that Kyung Hoon was married.
- He was married. - He got married recently.
Kyung Hoon is putting so much care into it.
In the past, he focused on making something funny.
He'll actually take it home.
(The single man, Yeong Cheol)
Whenever Yeong Cheol puts so much effort into such a thing,
my heart aches.
I really hope he'll get to use it.
(We hope Yeong Cheol's effort won't be in vain.)
He should hurry up and meet someone nice.
- You won't carry your wealth... - Seriously.
- to the grave. - Seriously.
(The man who finds love harder than investment, Jang Hoon)
- It's time to wrap it up. - Okay.
Please wrap it up.
(He finishes putting his heart into it.)
All right. It seems like everyone is done.
- Yes. - Good.
- You'll now take turns and present. - Do we need to go to the front?
Ten single staff members...
will vote for the person they're the most jealous of.
There's a prize for someone who made the best present.
Hee Chul will begin.
I thought about what would be best.
But she must've received a lot of flowers.
Thus, I prepared something she can use all day long.
I prepared a card.
I plan to give it to her.
- It's realistic. - Yes.
To make it look realistic,
- I drew my actual card. - It's so nice.
- He drew his actual card. - What's the limit?
What will you do if she buys a car?
Well, we'll ride it together.
She can buy anything...
without a limit for a day.
- I'll end it here. - Okay.
- It's nice. - It's nice.
It's a VVIP card.
The only thing I remember making with paper...
- in childhood... - It's a plane.
Is the paper airplane.
I connected it with life.
The title is "Life Airplane."
- "Up in the air is an airplane." - My goodness.
"Fly, fly."
"Fly high up in the air,"
"airplane of our lives."
My goodness.
(Let's fly.)
Hold on.
(It's the shortest flight.)
- You failed. - You failed.
- The end. - Is that the end?
- You failed. - Hold on.
- That was... - What was that?
- What was that? - It was so halfhearted.
Wasn't it plagiarized?
- No! - Is that for your wife?
I want her life to take flight...
like an airplane.
Is that for your wife?
- Right now... - Ho Dong.
I want her life to take flight.
For goodness' sake.
("Life Airplane" by Kang Ho Dong is a life's story...)
(that's riddled with joy, anger, sorrow, and failure.)
Kyung Hoon did a great job.
- It's game over. - I saw it.
- As you know, - He did it stealthily.
It hasn't been long since my wife and I got married.
Thus, I think that we still lack...
wisdom regarding a married life.
I'm not talking about fighting.
I wanted to make something...
that could be used to forgive the other unconditionally...
when something big happened.
He put a lot of work into it.
It's called the special pass.
No matter the situation, I'll forgive her...
- if she uses this. - My goodness.
It can be any situation.
- That's... - How many times can she use it?
- Once. - Just once?
- Will you do the forgiving? - Yes.
- My goodness. - If my wife does something...
and shows me this special pass,
I'll overlook her wrongdoing.
How big of an incident can it be?
Will you be okay if the scale matches that of Yoo Sung's dad?
This special pass can forgive anything.
- Anything? - Anything.
Simply put,
he isn't offering to do something for her.
He's saying,
"I'll forgive my wife no matter what she does."
- Aren't you a narcissist? - No.
- It's harder to forgive. - That's right.
- Can she lose the entire fortune? - Yes.
- It excuses everything. - Can she have debts like Sang Min?
It excuses everything.
- Everything gets a pass. - Wouldn't Yoo Sung's dad be better?
It's another family, so I don't know.
- "It's another family." - I prepared a special pass.
Well done.
("Special pass" by Min Kyung Hoon excuses even Sang Min or Min Soo.)
I made this. Back when...
I was a professional athlete,
my wife always hid a small card...
in my wallet or bag as a surprise...
for a match or something.
- But I never wrote a letter. - Oh, my.
I felt like this was a good opportunity.
This is the Love Special, after all.
I decorated it with flowers for a reason.
My wife was born in May. Peonies are her favorite.
It might be hard to tell, but these are peonies.
(His DIY peonies are one of a kind.)
- It's hard to tell. - These are peonies.
- It's hard to tell. - I added our three children.
- My goodness. - I see.
- I added our three children. - So sweet.
- I wrote a simple letter. - Okay.
- I'll read it. - She'll be so happy.
Yes.
"Anna." That's how it begins.
"It isn't a big present."
"It's so hard to write about all the things..."
"you've done for me in a single letter."
"Thank you so much for coming to a foreign country and making..."
"an effort to make a happy family."
"Thank you for raising the children in a healthy and happy manner."
"You might've loved me more at first,"
"but I love you more now. You know that, right?"
"Let's continue to spend our days in a simple and happy way."
"My best friend."
- "My best friend." - "My best friend" is cool.
("DIY Peonie and Letter" by Park Joo Ho...)
(contains his family including Anna, Na Eun, Gun Hoo, and Jin Woo.)
- It's flattery. - You stressed...
that you didn't love her first.
It's a man's useless ego.
It's ego.
Jang Hoon comes next.
- There was nothing to do. - How about a letter?
So,
for my future lover...
- A building. - For my future lover,
I wrote a letter.
- She must be watching. - No.
We'll be able to tell...
- if there's a lover. - Yes, there is.
- He makes video calls at times. - We'll definitely be able to tell.
- "To my future lover." - Okay.
"I wasn't going to date you."
Please smile as you read it.
"I don't know how this happened."
What? Are you Lee Min Ho?
Why... Are you Lee Min Ho?
- How could he say that about love? - Seriously.
- You... - Is he Lee Min Ho in "The Heirs?"
You need to be quiet, okay?
- Hey, I can't do anything. - I...
- I'll be quiet. - I'll start over.
- I'll start over. - "I'll be quiet."
"To my future lover."
"I wasn't going to date you."
"I don't know how this happened."
"For starters, I'm sorry..."
"about various things."
"I don't know what will happen in the future,"
"but I'll be good to you."
"I'm less difficult than people imagine."
"And don't worry about cleaning too much."
"I'll clean the house."
"Let's make this work. I'm sorry."
"Thank you."
"Hoon."
- It's a good letter. - Yes.
Jang Hoon, you'll place first.
- I just put my heart into it. - Yes.
"I wasn't going to date you."
Will Senior Dong present as well?
I fantasize about a married life.
I don't know why, but I've always pictured...
a happy family in a certain way ever since I was little.
I've always pictured...
mom, dad, son, and daughter eating fruits in the living room...
at noon on Sunday.
It has always been such a happy image in my mind.
- That's right. - Perhaps it's because...
my family wasn't well-off.
There's the happiness of being together on the weekend.
I want that to exist in my family, so I made a drawing...
and a poem.
- Here's the drawing. - He's good at drawing.
- My goodness. - He's really good at drawing.
All of them are big.
That's right. It can't be helped.
It can't be helped since we eat a lot.
No one is skinny.
- He's good at drawing. - The title is...
- It's cute, right? - "Four Pieces of Happiness."
"The four of us gather in the living room..."
"under the morning sun of the weekend."
"Mom, dad, daughter, and son."
(The four of them are enjoying the relaxing weekend morning.)
"We laugh with fruit in our hands."
"Even without words, the warm gaze..."
"and small smile contain big love."
"It's the most precious moment I've dreamed of."
(Shin Dong dreamed of having a warm moment with his family.)
That's the poem.
Hey, you'll place first.
("Four Pieces of Happiness" by Shin Dong shows...)
(the family's small happiness Shin Dong has always dreamed of.)
The thing is, my wife had the most amount of fun...
when we went on honeymoon.
She wanted to go there again,
but it didn't happen in ten years.
- Where did you guys go? - Macau.
She couldn't go because of you.
It was an unexpected place.
- He got into trouble for gambling. - Even when she tried to go alone,
people asked her if she had to go there.
When we went to a Korean restaurant...
and ate tteokbokki and other Korean dishes,
- my wife was the happiest. - I see.
"Can we go there sometime?"
- She used to ask me that. - Just go.
I feel bad for my wife.
There was a time she showed me the second-happiest smile.
She asked me, "Did you see that?"
My wife's favorite flower is the sunflower.
That's why there are many sunflower paintings at home.
We get many sunflowers as presents.
- It's a sunflower. - It's pretty.
- You see this arrow, right? - Does it represent money?
- The stock price went up once. - That's right.
She smiled the most brightly back then.
The stock price went up...
by 68 percent.
- Was it the Korean stock market? - In an excited voice,
she went, "Honey, we finally got the principal."
She smiled the most brightly...
- back then. - I see.
- The rising stock price... - This flower follows the stocks.
Makes the sunflower smile.
Many people who invest in stocks are feeling down.
Good luck.
(Let's hang in there.)
The Korean stock market.
Did you only get the principal even after the 68-percent rise?
Now, we're in the negative.
(The stock price went down.)
- It's minus 89 percent now. - Let me see it.
It's minus 89 percent now.
Even the sunflower is crying.
("Stock Sunflower" by Lee Soo Geun shows his hope...)
(to make his wife smile again with successful investment.)
Lee Sang Min.
I became serious while making it.
Isn't it a Christmas card?
(He pulls out a letter from the envelope.)
I wrote a letter.
- Really? - There must be someone.
Who is it for?
(Inside the envelope with a big heart, )
(he wrote a two-page letter with neat handwriting.)
"This is Lee Sang Min's future love story..."
"that's being written in the studio of Men on a Mission."
My goodness.
"You'll come to me like a four-leaf clover..."
"that represents luck."
- "I've never seen one..." - Is this a chain letter?
- "in my life." - A chain letter.
(I've never seen one...)
(in my life.)
"I probably haven't seen it..."
"because you're the four-leaf clover."
"You're probably the one I'll love all my life."
"Where are you?"
"I'll wait for you."
"Please come to me this year."
(There's more to the present.)
- What? - It's like "Love Actually."
Let's see it.
(The sketchbook performance continues.)
(The friends wait for the next page.)
(Today as always, Sang Min waits for the woman he'll love the most.)
(He doesn't turn the page.)
- Next page. - He made it well.
(Today as always, Sang Min waits for the woman he'll love the most.)
("Love Story" by Lee Sang Min shows his longing...)
(for the other half who resembles good luck.)
- It was serious. - There must be someone.
- The four-leaf clover is telling. - Both Sang Min and Jang Hoon...
- have someone. - Listen.
- I thought it was a chain letter. - It was...
- All right. - Hyung Tak.
Right before...
the wedding, my wife...
worked on her tablet PC for over a month.
She made an artwork for me as a present.
- It was an animated video. - My goodness.
- "Until We Began Dating." - She can draw really well.
("Until We Began Dating")
- She can draw really well. - She made the drawings.
- Why don't we watch it? - My goodness.
("Until We Began Dating")
(Let's begin!)
(The first meeting)
She can draw really well.
(It's an animated clip with the cute drawing style.)
It's what actually took place.
(Hyung Tak and Saya's love story was mentioned earlier.)
(Filming in Japan)
(The dazzling woman caught his eye right away.)
(You're pretty.)
(I'm a cool actor from Korea.)
(Hyung Tak wanted to approach her in a witty way.)
(Did he call himself handsome? What?)
(Is he a narcissist? I don't know about him.)
"Did he call himself handsome?"
"Is he a narcissist?" I see.
(Still, we began talking!)
(That was how the two of them began to contact each other.)
(I'll see you in Japan. Good night. Have a nice day.)
(Did you have dinner?)
(I'll keep messaging her. He's persistent.)
(Not we, but Mr. Shim...)
(sent many messages...)
Mr. Shim.
(whenever he had time.)
(Mr. Shim came to Japan often by himself.)
(Once or twice a month)
- That's right. - Really?
Gosh, it's so nice.
- We met at the karaoke... - How cute.
In Akihabara, the place where we met first.
It went like that.
(Why did you come to Japan?)
- Draft beef. - He's taking a photo of the beer.
"We always communicated..."
(We always communicated through a translating app.)
(After a few months, )
(I finally opened up to Mr. Shim.)
"I finally opened up to Mr. Shim."
"There was a reason."
(There was a reason.)
(In the subway, )
(Mr. Shim held my hand!)
- It's what he said. - Seriously.
- My goodness. - That's true..
(The moment when Saya opened up)
(It's crowded and rough, so it can't be helped.)
(What?)
(I didn't dislike the hand-holding.)
(I didn't dislike it.)
(What's the meaning of this?)
(He keeps contacting me.)
(He doesn't give up.)
(Maybe I don't dislike him.)
(We began dating that way and continue to live happily.)
- I see. - My goodness.
It's like a confession.
(Our story continues on.)
Yes. That's it.
When she gave me that present,
I was so touched.
I also wanted to give her a drawing as a present,
so I drew.
- You can draw well. - How cool.
- It's like "Dragon Ball." - Yes.
This is like "Dragon Ball."
- This is like "Crayon Shin-chan." - "Crayon Shin-chan."
This is "Doraemon."
- I drew the three of us. - Right.
She gave me a family,
- so I'm really happy. - It's so lovely.
"My lovely family."
"I'll be sure to protect this happiness."
- Of course. - I wanted to protect it,
- so I made this drawing. - Okay. That's nice.
- Thank you. - I think he'll place first.
His drawing doesn't deserve first place,
but his wife's animated video does.
- The animated video. - Why did you bring a professional?
- This is for the amateurs. - Seriously.
Will the animated video be included in the score?
- It shouldn't be. - It shouldn't be.
("My Lovely Family" by Shim Hyung Tak...)
(turned the family members into the cute characters.)
- Yeong Cheol is next. - Shall I go next?
You guys might not believe it,
but I think that my strength lies in my literary skills.
For my future wife,
I prepared a poem.
I was born in Ulsan,
- a city by the sea. - Ulsan.
- That's right. - Seaweed is famous there.
Seaweed is the specialty.
- Listen carefully. "Sweet Seaweed." - It's a poem.
"I won't be a husband who makes the seaweed soup..."
"once in a year."
"I'll be sweet 365 days a year."
"I'll be a husband like Yang Gwan Sik."
"For goodness' sake! Where are you?"
"Who do you think you are?"
"You need to be by my side..."
"so that I can make you seaweed soup. Come on."
"Where are you? For goodness' sake."
"For goodness' sake."
(Yeong Cheol's love runs away the more he looks for her.)
- "For goodness' sake." - "For goodness' sake?"
Didn't you guys watch the drama, "When Life Gives You Tangerines?"
- We watched it. - We're disappointed...
- because we watched it. - I parodied the drama.
Earlier, I told you guys...
- that I respected Yeong Cheol. - "For goodness' sake."
May I change my answer?
(The man Joo Ho respected and liked)
(The role model of number 7, Yeong Cheol)
The man he respected.
It didn't even last a day.
(Clapping)
Oh, my.
All right.
("Sweet Seaweed" by Kim Yeong Cheol is a poem that hopes...)
(for the one who will make waves in his sea of singlehood.)
- All right. - For Yoo Sung's dad.
It's for Yoo Sung's dad.
By the way, how does everyone have...
the drawing skills?
Your drawing skills are the best.
It's impressive.
I feel like the competition is fierce...
- in this classroom. - That's right.
We can do most things well.
Oh, my. Okay.
- Everyone prepared well. - Competition.
The thing is, my husband and I have spent 30 years together.
That's a long period of time. It's 30 years.
Thus, we've experienced...
all sorts of situations.
We've experienced them...
and overcome them.
But when I think about it now...
Since it has been 30 years,
I keep thinking about the meaning of love.
What I can do for my husband is...
Since it has been 30 years,
I keep thinking about the meaning of love.
What I can do for my husband is...
I drew a pinky promise.
Let me tell you what this promise is.
During the journey...
that remains in our lives,
I...
really want to take care of him.
When my husband proposed to me...
three hours into our first meeting,
it must've contained...
- so many hopes. - Yes.
I want to keep that promise in our latter years.
So that we can live happily...
with our family in the future,
- I'll take responsibility. - Yes.
That's the promise.
("Promise" by June Kang shows the beautiful promise...)
(that'll protect each other.)
- Okay. - Okay.
(The presents were full of love.)
Now, let's find out who made the best present...
that moved the hearts of the ten single staff members.
Let's begin the vote.
Vote for the present...
that made you the most jealous.
They're voting for real.
- It has been a while. - They're gathered around there.
- My goodness. - Let's see.
- But... - The staff members...
voted very carefully.
- Really? - Yes.
The single staff members must be serious about this.
(Which one was voted as the best present?)
- All right. - We...
Gosh, this person...
(Which one was voted as the best present?)
- All right. - We...
Gosh, this person...
- This is incredible. - Who is it?
The one whose present made them the most jealous is...
- Seo Jang Hoon. - Why?
Seo Jang Hoon.
(Jang Hoon's present is the best.)
- What? - It's game over.
The atmosphere is nice.
- Why? - For goodness' sake.
- Everyone. - I can't believe it.
You guys lack sentimentality.
(Deep emotions were hidden behind his haughtiness.)
You failed to read the empty and lonely emotions.
- That's why you don't get it. - The best present.
Since Jang Hoon made the best present,
he'll get vitamins...
with the family he loves.
The present is a fruit set.
- A fruit set. - Really?
- Thank you. - Why did Jang Hoon win?
Why did Jang Hoon win?
We prepared a present for the guests as well.
- Congratulations. - Thank you.
(The transfer students get a present as well!)
- This is nice. - Thank you.
Thank you so much for giving me a chance to express...
my love for Anna. Thank you.
I learned a lot today.
Most importantly, it gave me...
confidence to talk about my wife and how we met...
- for 30 years... - Yes.
- to come. - That's right.
We had an opportunity to converse...
and help each other.
I'm so thankful for an opportunity from Men on a Mission.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
We hope you'll grow old with your family.
- We'll root for you guys. - We'll root for you guys.
(Actual children are here.)
(Guys, let's go.)
(The young guests enter one at a time.)
(Park Sung On, Kim Tae Yeon, Hwang Min Ho, )
(Lee Cheon Mu, Lee Su Yeon, Oh Ji Yul, Rhy Ji Woo)
(Ho Dong, your behaviors are very cute.)
(Ji Yul is the same.)
(Beat me if you can.)
(It was a bit scary, Mr. Kang.)
(She suddenly used a polite tone.)
(A story of IU's good deed)
(On the other hand, Jang Hoon only gets scary stories.)
(It's not that I don't want to do it.)
(The acting prodigy copies Jang Hoon perfectly.)
(He uses the bending technique to deliver the sorrowful vibe.)
(The trot prodigies are here.)
(Are you actually 46 years old?)
What?
(He has never heard such a thing in his nine years.)
(You're here as the leader.)
(Sung On grew up so much.)
(I'm an adult just like him.)
Oh, my.
(Men on a Mission, let's party.)
(Passionate performance)
(A performance by Sung On, the boy who became a man)
(The master of bending, Su Yeon)
(Field Day on a Mission for the Children's Day begins...)
(with Mr. Do Kyung Wan.)
(Red light, green light)
(If you don't want to ruin the vibe, keep going.)
(It's the Children's Day, so go easy on the children.)
(Some generational gaps can't be bridged.)
(The flower of the field day, the group horseback riding)
(The Men on a Mission members...)
(and the cuties will work together.)
(The rowdy Children's Day Special is coming soon.)
(Men on a Mission)