(Cleanliness and hygiene matter in March.)
- It faded from washing so much.
- As the Beautification Officer,
I'm going to straighten our hygiene standard.
- You're going to discipline us?
- Are you checking our nails?
- Show me your nails.
- I cut them short.
- My nails.
- Did you wash your hair?
I always wash my hair.
(Checking the smell)
It's nice. It really is.
- I always...
- Let me see your nails.
- Who doesn't wash their hair?
- My nails are neat.
- I wash my hair every day.
- Isn't that an expensive watch?
- No.
- Wait.
- It's Hermes. Minus five points.
- No.
- Why?
- Hey.
If you wear something expensive, others will feel out of place.
- What?
- That's banned. It's too expensive.
What does the watch have to do with hygiene?
The gap between rich and poor is...
- too great.
- Yes.
Think about Sang Min.
- Should I wear something else?
- He'd want that too.
- Right.
- Can you take a look at me?
Take a look at him.
See if I need to get hemorrhoid surgery.
- Okay.
- Let me see.
- Come here.
- That's disgusting.
Why are you...
(Minus 500,000 points for disgracing school)
- Let me see.
- If you want...
Why are you trying to see it?
Nothing can stop Lee Soo Geun.
Can I report you all and get you five penalty points?
- What was that?
- My goodness.
Wait. They're real doctors.
- And he's a fake doctor.
- Wait.
- What's going on?
They look like the Oompa Loompas next to Seo Jang Hoon.
Why did you have to stand next to Seo Jang Hoon?
- Right.
- If there's a problem, it's a joke.
They remind me of "The Lord of the Rings."
Where are you from?
Hi, we're from...
We Wish To Be Your Friendly Doctors High.
I have JTBC fright.
I'm the psychiatrist Oh Jin Seung.
- Nice to meet you.
- Wait.
You all know me from Netflix.
- "The Trauma Code..." - What?
I'm the writer of "The Trauma Code."
(The writer of the famous series, "The Trauma Code")
I somehow have three jobs. I'm the ENT doctor Lee Nak Jun.
(The ENT doctor with three jobs, Lee Nak Jun)
- Awesome.
- Cool.
- I read your book.
- I've seen him.
I've seen him reviewing "Home Alone."
- Yes.
- A few years ago.
I'm an internal medicine doctor who has to say everything on his mind.
I'm Woo Chang Yun.
(3 doctors visit Brother School.)
(3 medical professors started "Doctor Friends.")
(The History of Menses)
(The YouTubers with 1.33 million subscribers)
(They don't only deliver medical information,)
(but they're also performing in various fields.)
(3 all-around doctors)
Nak Jun, you're not a surgeon, but an ENT doctor?
- Yes.
- I really enjoyed...
watching "The Trauma Code."
- There was nothing about the ENT.
- Right.
There's nothing about it.
But...
Let's be honest. Are you curious about the ENT?
- You've all been there before.
- Exactly.
No one wants to know how much the ENT doctor...
sucks your snot or how carefully he examines your ears.
- But the ENT...
- Nak Jun, I have a question.
Let me ask you this first.
Will there be Season Two?
- Hey.
- Isn't that a secret?
- It's obvious.
- Hey.
- He's not supposed to say it.
- I...
- Did you watch it?
My only hobby is watch good series...
- at once.
- Right.
- I finished watching it in one day.
- Me too.
- People watch everything at once.
- Yes.
- Will there be Season Two?
- I'm sorry,
- but I don't know either.
That means Season Two is guaranteed.
Because a global OTT signs a contract...
for confidentiality.
I'm not telling you...
- because it's a secret.
- Nak Jun.
- I really don't know.
- Time out.
- I...
- If Season Two comes out,
- It's suspicious.
- can you make it long?
- I agree. When I watched it, - Okay.
- I thought it was too short.
- Yes.
- It was a bummer.
- It was over so fast.
We'll soon find that out.
Why are you three here together?
- Are you close?
- The three of us...
We're close,
and we talk on YouTube for a living.
- I think that's why.
- I'm curious.
- Are you really doctors?
- We are doctors.
- You're on YouTube together?
- I thought Woo Chang Yun was...
a YouTuber.
He's a YouTuber.
- You have the YouTuber impression.
- He's a YouTuber.
- He kind of looks like Pani Bottle.
- Yes, I can see that.
- I can see it.
- Pani Bottle?
- Pani Bottle is very handsome.
- He's cute.
Anyway, there was someone you wanted to meet among us?
- Woo Chang Yun?
- Seo Jang Hoon and Ho Dong.
The production crew ordered you.
- No, I'm serious.
- It's true.
Listen to me first. I'm a big fan of basketball.
So I was really... And he's also very tall.
I'm jealous.
To be honest, when I became a doctor,
I only wanted to work for 10 to 15 years...
then try something else...
afterward. I had that urge.
You two reached the peak in your careers.
To be honest, it's a big challenge...
- to move to a different field.
- That's true.
Yet they pulled it off.
I want to try something else one day...
- like them.
- Good one.
So were you a fan of ssireum or basketball?
- He liked basketball.
- I still like basketball.
- You think he's fit for ssireum?
- Do I look like I'm fit?
- But...
- I'm not even fit for basketball.
I'm not even fit for basketball.
Chang Yun. You seem...
like a reliable doctor.
- Come on.
- I only say the truth.
- I can never lie.
- Come on.
What's your position in basketball?
The guard, obviously.
He can't play the center. What do you think?
It wasn't your choice, was it?
I've only played the guard in my life.
- What's there to choose?
- Either the guard or nothing.
Jin Seung, who did you want to meet?
I wanted to meet Jang Hoon too.
- Time out.
- Are you repeating after him?
I wanted to meet Jang Hoon too.
- Time out.
- Are you repeating after him?
- This is crazy.
- I bet the production crew said,
"Please. Please say you wanted to meet Seo Jang Hoon."
- "I already told you." - "Please."
I often talk about Jang Hoon to my patients when I see them.
Really?
What do your patients say?
Why would you...
- Are you...
- This is what my patients say.
"Because I don't enjoy working,"
"I'm afraid I won't be successful."
One must enjoy their work...
- to be good at it and be the best.
- Right.
"But I can't find the joy with what I'm doing."
"So I'm thinking about finding a new career."
Jang Hoon said this...
- in a show before.
- Yes.
The one who makes an effort cannot beat the one who enjoys it.
He said he hated...
- that phrase the most.
- Yes.
(It will work out well if you enjoy what you do?)
(That won't get you anywhere.)
(If you have a goal,)
(that's complete nonsense.)
(If you only enjoy it, nothing will happen.)
So I tell them about Jang Hoon.
In order to reach the peak,
it can't be fun.
- When I say that, - Right.
my patients go, "You're right."
So there's nothing weird...
about not enjoying working hard.
I use Jang Hoon as an example...
- to explain it to them, - You use it as an example.
and they all understand it.
Jin Seung, which university did you go to?
- Korea University.
- Out of nowhere?
- I mean...
- The same position...
Korea University has many wonderful doctors.
- I mean Korea University...
- I didn't see that coming.
- Right.
- Korea University...
Korea University also has many wonderful doctors.
- It's not easy to enjoy it.
- What matters is that...
just like how Chang Yun admired the center position...
while playing the guard,
everyone has the desire...
- for what they don't have.
- Of course.
- I can see...
that Chang Yun looks unstable standing.
- He's standing on something.
- We...
We should miss our old days as members of the fellowship.
Honestly, I don't hide it.
After spending time with Seo Jang Hoon for seven years,
everyone who's taller than 180cm looks like nothing.
- Hey, you should...
- Okay.
- Honestly...
- What's your height?
- If I join them...
- Are you the tallest?
I will be...
- You're not confident, are you?
- I am confident.
You know what matters?
No one ever took their shoes off when I told them to.
- Right.
- Bring it on.
- I'm taller than you think.
- Are you sure?
- You go first.
- I led the fellowship...
- and carried the leg.
- You go.
- No.
- Take your shoes off.
- They're about the same.
- He'll be so much shorter...
with his shoes off.
My goodness. Are you sure about it?
- My height is the standard.
- He already checked.
- No, the shoes...
- Nak Jun and Jin Seung...
are clearly shorter than me.
- Hey! Bring it on.
- But I...
- Come on.
- Let's not do this.
- You got so much shorter.
- I'm...
- Come here.
- Let's check.
Soo Geun...
(Now he finally remembers his time in the fellowship.)
Come here, Chang Yun.
- Come here.
- Come here, Jin Seung.
- Your socks look weird.
(The next person gets off from his shoes.)
- You're nothing.
- I'm taller.
- Come here.
- Why am I here?
- Is this necessary?
- Come here.
- You...
(The man who fights gravity)
- You remind me of Park Sung Kwang.
- His shoes...
- Park Sung Kwang...
- What are you wearing?
- Hey, let's be honest.
- Come here.
- Is this necessary?
- Gather up.
This journey will be...
(The Lord of the Shoe Lift: In Search of the Ruling Shoe Lift)
- Should we stand like this?
- This is bad.
- I really don't like this.
- It's nice to stand with you all.
- It's nice.
- By the way...
As if they had promised in advance.
- They look so cute.
- Nak Jun, out of us all,
Soo Geun feels most familiar to you, apparently.
- He looks so much like my dad.
- You said he seemed familiar.
- With whom?
- My dad and Soo Geun look alike.
- They look alike?
- His appearance...
- Can you put it on the screen?
- Really?
- You even brought his photo?
- Show them, please.
- Is he your father?
- They both have under-eye fat...
- I think he looks like me.
- He looks so young for his father.
- In this photo, he looks...
- Your father...
May I ask what he does for a living?
- What's his occupation?
- Is he a YouTuber?
- I think he's in Vietnam.
- He's a pastor.
- He's a pastor?
- He's a pastor, and he...
That photo was taken while he was eating fried chicken.
- Nak Jun.
- He posed like that.
- He's very funny.
- You have something for your dad?
- Right, Nak Jun.
- Oh, yes, I'll give it to my dad.
Didn't you bring anything for me?
- Of course, I prepared it.
- Bring it to me.
Call him "Dad."
- But...
- Nak Jun, give it to me.
- What's with that pose?
- Their eyes seem similar.
(I'm your father.)
"Dad."
- Dad, here you go.
- Nak Jun, I'm sorry.
- It's genetic. I'm sorry.
- It's okay, Dad.
I wish I'd married a tall woman, at least.
- I'm really sorry.
- Exactly.
- He wishes he'd married a tall one.
- I wish I'd married a tall woman.
Why didn't you try? Gosh.
- You guys are doctors.
- Should we sit down?
- No, we should stand...
- You believe it's genetic, right?
- Sorry?
- I'm talking about height.
- Oh, height?
- Is height genetic?
- Yes, it's genetic.
- Oh, is it?
- It's mostly genetic.
- That's right.
- I told you so.
- But some people...
succeed in increasing their height through efforts...
to stimulate growth plates.
I ran a lot too.
- Pardon?
- I made a lot of efforts too.
I did a lot of jump ropes and drank a lot of milk.
- You've tried everything.
- I've tried everything.
I know more than anyone about how to grow taller.
No one in your family is taller than 180cm, right?
- No one is. That's impossible.
- No one?
- Right?
- What are you talking about?
When someone in my family is taller than 160cm,
we think that's tall enough.
- That's the average height...
- We say, "He's tall enough."
- of your family, right?
- Right.
- No need to explain.
- You said 180cm? Come on.
Here's their transfer form for Brother School.
Names. Woo Chang Yun, Lee Nak Jun, Oh Jin Seung.
We welcome you all with open arms!
First up is the group that our transfer students belong to.
- And they wrote, "Doctor Friends." - Right.
That's the name of our YouTube channel.
How did you start your YouTube channel?
We were friends before that.
And we enlisted in the military.
There was nothing to do to spend our free time.
You served in the military as doctors, right?
- Yes, as medical officers.
- We served as medical officers.
- Then it's totally different.
I've always wanted to write a novel...
since I liked genre fiction so much.
I've read martial arts novels since I was little. You saw my dad.
He looks unusual, right?
Whenever I turned a certain age, he recommended a book to me.
"You're now old enough to read 'Hero Gate.'"
He recommended the book.
"Now it's time for you to read 'The Smiling, Proud Wanderer.'"
- He gave me the book.
- Those are Kim Yong's novels.
That's how I started to read martial arts novels.
And I've always admired such novels.
When I became a grown-up, I started to think,
"How about I write my own novel?" So I wrote my novel.
Since it's about medical science,
people willingly paid to read my novel.
I mean, I didn't make much money from it, though.
That gave me an idea. Since YouTube was very popular,
I thought that if we made videos about medical knowledge,
our channel could become popular.
So I chose two of my friends who liked to talk the most.
- I suggested the idea.
- Oh, that's how you started it.
There was something I realized. During the university years,
your friends are not so useful.
- You just hang out with them.
- That's true.
- I agree.
- You just hang out with them.
You wonder if they could even do their part after graduation.
- Exactly.
- You can't be sure.
But now that they're specialist doctors,
whenever I have a health problem and ask for their advice,
- they seem okay. Indeed.
- They're so smart.
"Oh, he's smarter than I thought he was."
They were stupid, but they became smart.
- They doubt one another.
- He said they had been stupid,
- but they became smart.
- Also,
it doesn't feel like I'm seeing a doctor.
They tell me only the key points in a way they speak to friends.
- That's right.
- And I really like that.
Since we went to med school,
we have friends in every medical specialty.
But not many people have friends who are doctors.
- Most people don't.
- Many don't have such friends.
So I suggested we should be their doctor friends.
That's why we named our channel "Doctor Friends."
We decided to dress casually, without wearing a doctor's gown...
and to just chat with one another in our videos.
So we recorded our videos at my house.
How long have you been running your channel?
We began in 2018, so...
- It's been 7 years.
- It's been 7 years?
- Hello. We're Doctor Friends.
- We're Doctor Friends.
(They've been all Koreans' doctors for 7 years.)
- It's been 7 years.
- It's been 7 years?
- It's been a long time.
- Did you know...
that you'd do it for so long when you started it?
To tell you the truth, these two had a big ambition.
They would talk with their spittle flying...
about how our channel would become successful.
Nak Jun even said we'd get 100,000 subscribers within a year.
I was the only one...
who didn't think it would be successful.
But I still wanted to hang with them.
We were very close.
- So I decided to give it a chance.
- You decided to join them.
I was going to quit after one year, to be honest.
Since the videos would remain,
I thought I could upload them...
on the website of my clinic when I opened up my own.
- Right. As a former YouTuber.
- Oh, I see.
- You had the biggest ambition.
- That's a great idea.
- He had the biggest ambition.
- You had that thought back then?
You had a different goal.
Yes, I had a different goal. So we started our channel.
And it became more successful than I thought.
How many people subscribe to your channel?
- About 1.4 million?
- About 1.32 million?
Who edits your videos?
The editor should also...
have enough medical knowledge.
At first, my wife...
Oh, she was my girlfriend back then.
She was my girlfriend back then.
- She majored in multimedia.
- It was smart.
She told me about YouTube...
and suggested we upload our videos on YouTube.
- You didn't know about YouTube.
- We didn't know what it was.
Since she knew how to edit a video and create a thumbnail,
I asked her to edit our videos.
- You were lucky to meet her.
- Yes.
Right. That's how we got married.
- Editing videos for YouTube...
- That's how you married her?
That doesn't sound so good, you know.
- That's how you got married?
- It sounds like you married her...
- for a business purpose.
- That's not true. We fell in love.
- She even edited your videos.
- If she hadn't edited your videos,
you might have broken up with her? Is that it?
- Right. That's possible.
- No.
- Come on. Give me a break.
- He hosts "Divorce Camp."
He's called the Divorce Chief on the show.
- I've been enjoying your show.
- He might scold you.
So don't be like that.
- I'm just asking. That's all.
- You might see him on the show.
- But you see...
- He's Dr. Oh who plays basketball.
My answer is no. It became successful unexpectedly.
Which of your videos got the most views?
It's about the reason why fentanyl addicts...
walk like zombies.
- Oh, I watched that video.
- I've seen such people in person.
It went viral because it became a serious issue.
As far as I remember, Korea used to be a drug-free country.
- Right.
- True.
I heard this from my friends.
The number of drug offenders is increasing sharply.
- It's so scary.
- Many cases are tried in court.
The more serious problem is that a lot of teenagers use it,
- and the number is increasing.
- Right.
That's not it. Fentanyl is a medicine...
that I prescribe to cancer patients.
- Is that allowed?
- You actually prescribe it?
It's a prescription medicine for pain relief.
What is it used for?
- It's for cancer patients.
- To relieve severe pain.
- Because they have severe pain?
- That's correct.
If you apply too many patches,
you could die of a side effect of fentanyl.
It could stop you from breathing. It happens to the elderly.
Some elderly people think it's a pain relief patch...
and apply more than one patch,
- It's dangerous.
- which causes breathing difficulty.
So they're taken to the emergency room.
- It's a patch form of drug.
- So you put it on your body?
Yes, you put it on your body. It's absorbed into your skin,
- and it lasts for three days.
- It spreads slowly...
to prevent patients from becoming addicted to it.
- Exactly.
- So the effect of the medicine...
But since this drug is cheap,
it's been spreading among adolescents.
- They have easy access to it.
- Yes.
- It became an issue in the US too.
- Right.
It's because it's cheap.
So many people got addicted to it, which became a serious issue.
We explained how serious of a consequence...
- it could bring...
- That's great.
and the cause of the phenomenon and the scheme behind it...
- in that video.
- That's informative.
- The age group is getting younger.
- Yes.
But when people start using fentanyl,
no one thinks they'll become addicted to it.
- That's right.
- They do it out of curiosity.
- Curiosity and suggestion. Yes.
- Suggestion from friends?
It's called "peer pressure."
Adolescents have this desire to stay in the group they belong to.
- Right. They do.
- Okay.
- So this...
- Hey, don't use a difficult term.
- Well, it's...
- We know what that means.
- It's what made Jin Seung join you.
- We understood.
- Hey, Nak Jun.
- Precisely. That's what it means.
- You think we're stupid.
- I'm sorry.
- Anyway...
They don't want to be left out.
And some people make money from selling this drug.
Such people use this tendency of adolescents...
- They're evil.
- and suggest the drug.
- That's right.
- They offer a low price at first.
After kids get addicted, they bring money for the drug.
- They use their parents' money.
- That's right.
Therefore, it has become a very serious social issue.
I'll tell you how harmful fentanyl is.
It damages your brain.
To perform a certain action,
- you need to generate dopamine.
- Right, dopamine.
If dopamine receptors are removed from a rat's body,
the rat stays still...
- until it starves to death.
- Oh, gosh.
Even if you put food in front of it, it wouldn't go and eat it.
Because it has no motivation.
But if you put food into its mouth, it would enjoy the food.
This is how important motivation is when we perform an action.
And here's what makes narcotics scary.
They take motivation to do anything from you.
- That's right.
- I see.
You reach the point that nothing in the world but drugs matters.
- What keeps us going in life is...
- That's scary.
- our desire for happiness...
- That's right.
and desire to do something we like.
When drugs become the only thing that makes you happy,
you become like some kind of machine.
A machine whose only purpose is...
- to use drugs.
- Right.
When people use drugs, they usually change.
For example, a family-oriented person...
who works hard suddenly starts doing nothing but using drugs.
This person used to feel joy and satisfaction...
in daily life with his or her family,
- He doesn't feel happy anymore.
- but that joy is gone now.
The person can't do anything but using drugs.
- Once he started...
- I had no idea.
I'm amazed that once he started talking about the issue...
He's amazing.
- He's really incredible.
- Indeed.
- Chang Yun, you see...
- He seems smart now.
I knew it was dangerous,
but I didn't realize that it causes such serious problems.
- It's really dangerous.
- Exactly. I know that now.
You guys review medical dramas as well.
- Yes, we do.
- When you review a medical drama,
you can tell whether or not...
- it's medically accurate.
- I'm curious.
- I'm really curious about this.
- You can tell, right?
- I'm a huge fan of medical dramas.
- Me too.
- I'm a huge fan too.
- I watch almost all medical dramas.
Jin Seung must have something to say when it comes to that.
One of the realistic, accurate dramas is the Netflix drama...
called "Daily Dose of Sunshine."
It's about the psychiatry department in a hospital.
Actress Park Bo Young acted in it.
The drama realistically depicted what it feels like...
to live with panic disorder or depression.
There's a scene where a male character...
gets a panic attack at work.
He has difficulty breathing, feeling like he's drowning in water.
He feels suffocated. There are such scenes like this,
and those scenes were created very realistically.
There are a few dramas I hate...
- as a psychiatrist.
- Yes.
In those dramas, doctors date their patients,
- and they get married, even.
- That's what I hate the most.
- There are some dramas like that.
- I hate such dramas the most.
He talks about this every time it's brought up.
- He talks about this every time.
- Right. A doctor...
is told that his patient is suffering.
Then he runs out of his office.
And he goes around to find her.
- "Where is this patient?" - He's acting again. He always does.
Whenever I see a scene like that,
I wonder, "Then who treats the scheduled patients?"
That's one of the thoughts that come to my mind.
That's the mindset of a hospital director.
You must see patients in the consulting room,
not outside.
One of the reasons "The Trauma Code" succeeded was that...
- it had no love story.
- Yes.
- That's why I love it.
- No romance.
What got me anxious while watching the drama was the possibility of...
Baek Kang Hyuk and Cheon Jang Mi falling in love.
- Same here.
- If they did...
- I expected romance.
- They get to know each other.
- It never happened.
- The two don't date.
I can't write romance stories.
- He gets along with Han Yu Rim.
- I suck at it.
- How accurate is the depiction...
- Yes?
of "The Trauma Code" on a scale from 0 to 100?
Take this into consideration.
When watching "The Avengers" series,
we don't say...
it accurately depicts martial arts.
- No.
- Right? Because...
Baek Kang Hyuk's physical strength is that of "The Avengers,"
and he has extrasensory perception, particularly in his vision.
Can't he shoot a missile with a gun?
Yes. Baek Kang Hyuk can shoot an RPG missile with a gun.
That's the original setting.
He can stop the bleeding at once...
because he looks at...
the intensity of the blood's color as it collects.
And he can see the blood vessels swell just by looking at the eye.
That's far from an accurate depiction of a doctor.
This isn't an issue of an accurate depiction.
I had no plan to make an accurate depiction.
That was why it was fun.
- It's a medical superhero drama.
- A medical superhero.
You're right.
Because of my mom,
I had to visit the hospital for three years...
and take care of her.
Watching the drama brought out my empathy.
- Like Baek Kang Hyuk.
- Right.
- He fixes everything.
- Yes.
The drama satisfies the viewers' hopes...
- of him fixing everything.
- I agree.
It was fun writing it. As a doctor,
seeing the health of the person...
I wanted to save deteriorate beyond control is upsetting.
Imagining how amazing it'd be if there were a doctor...
like Baek Kang Hyuk as he'd save everyone made writing the work fun.
I have a question.
In a drama or a movie, why are genius main characters...
like doctors and such so arrogant?
As a writer, writing a fun story...
with a genius character...
who even has a perfect personality is tough.
When the character is a genius, they need at least one flaw.
Like Seo Jang Hoon with a twisted personality.
- Only then does the work...
- "Only then?"
- Listen.
- get fun.
He's a genius basketball player...
- but lacks in personality.
- Seriously.
- Like him.
- He's normally like,
"It's okay. Don't worry about it."
But here, he's frowning, right?
- That's what makes him interesting.
- Yes.
- That's Seo Jang Hoon.
- That's how...
he became a charming entertainer.
Does that mean he deliberately came up with that personality?
- Of course.
- I see.
- He's a genius entertainer.
- That's not 100 percent true.
(The Enraged Code)
- Okay, let's go.
- Next,
we'll check out the areas of expertise of the transfer students.
Chang Yun's expertise is internal medicine.
Nak Jun is ENT.
- And Jin Seung is psychiatry.
- Correct.
Choosing your department of expertise.
Is it based on grades...
- I'm curious, too.
- or something?
I just happened to graduate in second place.
- He's annoying.
- I did.
And as you mentioned, grades do play a role in it.
Some departments are quite popular.
I had to decide on my department first.
If the person in second place chose my desired department,
I'd have to change my own choice.
- He needed to decide quickly.
- I see.
- Is that so?
- There's a ranking system.
I was going to choose dermatology as recommended.
But I initially studied medicine...
to see the mix of emotions...
at the peak of life and death.
Dermatology didn't seem like the department for it.
Of course, it's a great and useful department.
Can't the 2nd and 3rd places both choose the same department?
Dermatology was recruiting only one doctor.
- Some departments are like that.
- It has limited openings.
- After I turned down dermatology, - It has a fixed demand.
I thought about it for 2 to 3 months...
- before choosing internal medicine.
- Right.
When I chose internal medicine,
I looked into Korea's biggest hospital,
applied to my current hospital, ASAN Medical Center,
and specialized in internal medicine.
Doesn't Ho Dong have something to do with ASAN Medical Center?
- Yes.
- His name is on there.
- Influencer.
- I saw it.
- "Influencer?" - At the entrance...
- "Influencer?" - In the lobby...
Was he an ASAN Medical Center influencer?
- His name is there.
- He's a donor, not an influencer.
- A donor.
- Such news should be known.
- He's a donor.
Ho Dong made a huge donation.
There's a big plaque of Ho Dong.
- Was he an influencer?
- You can see Ho Dong's name...
in the lobby.
- A hospital ambassador.
- An ambassador?
He donated a large sum.
- Ho Dong does many good deeds.
- No.
The plaque size depends on the donation amount,
- and Ho Dong's is huge.
- It's big.
- Ho Dong is an enterprise.
- We donated,
- but ours is quite small.
- It's small.
You need to look closely for ours.
As expected from an influencer.
Influencer. He should be praised.
Ho Dong helps out...
whenever children get sick.
That's because he's an influencer slash ambassador.
So you went back on your decision.
Yes, but he changed his mind more than me.
- He...
- Because Nak Jun...
changed his department several times,
he was nicknamed the traitorous rose.
- He was?
- He's a bad example.
During practical training in my student days,
I had become tired both mentally and physically.
I decided to specialize in rehabilitation.
I wanted to spend a stable...
and relaxing...
residency in rehabilitation.
But in March, my practical was in the ER.
- And working in the ER was fun.
- Really?
The practical made me realize...
I enjoyed such departments...
and made me think of choosing an active department.
Back then, ophthalmology was popular.
Ophthalmology.
- Ophthalmology?
- You won't see any blood.
Ophthalmology is quite an active department.
With that, I chose ophthalmology.
I applied to it and worked in the department.
But ophthalmology turned out...
- to be too meticulous.
- It's very meticulous.
- Of course, it is.
- They use cotton swabs.
- That's to be expected.
- In other departments,
like during invasive surgeries,
a suction device is used when the patient bleeds.
In ophthalmology, a cotton swab is used when there's bleeding.
But I couldn't do it.
- You must be delicate.
- It was too delicate.
You had to be precise with the cotton swab.
Don't ophthalmologists always use a microscope?
Personality-wise, I'm not that meticulous.
Ophthalmology wasn't for me.
I told the professor,
"I can't do ophthalmology."
After every practical, he gives up on that department.
After changing my mind twice, not many departments were left.
The internal medicine professor, who gave me a scholarship,
suggested internal medicine if I had nowhere to go.
I told him I'd consider it.
The next day, I got a call...
from an ENT senior working at Samsung Hospital.
"Our ENT will have an open position."
"Do you want to come?"
"We can't hire an intern from a different hospital,"
"but we might this time."
He told me to apply for it.
Until then, ENT was out of my interest.
The thing was, my ex-girlfriend,
who is now my wife, was an intern at Samsung Hospital.
I had a few dates in that hospital.
Samsung Hospital is big and nice.
- Totally.
- I've been there.
- Right.
- And the hospital food is amazing.
The food was good when I was there.
For example, if our university hospital...
was serving bossam,
- which was very rare, - Bossam?
we were served two pieces per person.
- It was a special meal.
- Indeed.
But in Samsung Hospital, bossam was...
- served buffet-style.
- For real?
(Bossam was served buffet-style.)
- It's insane.
- Really?
- Seriously?
- You can eat as much as you want?
- Ho Dong.
- It's served buffet-style?
ASAN Medical Center isn't bad either.
Why don't you make a donation?
Let's get a plaque.
- You can grab a meal.
- Make a donation.
I was invited to a place...
with good memories, so I visited.
The professors were really nice, too.
With that, I decided to study ENT.
It was in "The Trauma Code," too.
The character abandons proctology.
- So...
- Each person develops on their own.
- It's about you.
- It's from your experience.
You're the character.
Come to think of it, in "The Trauma Code,"
ENT seems to be the tough department,
while rehabilitation is an easy gig.
- Don't say it's an easy gig.
- No.
Rehabilitation is a vital department.
There's a criterion when looking at departments.
It's whether the resident is wearing dress shoes or not.
- Usually, - Right.
- in sophisticated departments...
- They usually wear slippers.
like rehabilitation and radiology, they wear dress shoes.
It's not often that they need to run around.
Everyone is very gentle.
The professors let you go home when it's time.
When it comes to ENT,
we're wearing bloodstained rubber slippers.
All of us are wearing scrubs.
No one wears plain clothes.
The difference is if the department has emergency patients or not.
It's not common for rehabilitation to have emergency patients.
"Rehabilitate that patient quickly."
- No doctors go like that.
- It doesn't happen.
- Rehab has steps.
- If that's the case,
isn't psychiatry...
- the best?
- He wears dress shoes.
Speaking of departments, from what I know,
didn't Jin Seung choose psychiatry because of BoA?
It's not like I chose psychiatry because of BoA.
But I did go to medical school because of her.
- BoA?
- What?
I was playing games at an internet cafe back in middle school.
"The Star of Asia, BoA, conquers Japan."
- Right.
- And she spoke several languages.
It made me feel pathetic about myself.
I was playing computer games in secret and such.
I thought, "BoA is promoting the nation's glory."
- That's possible.
- "The least I can do is study."
As a result, I went to medical school.
It's thanks to BoA that I went to one.
- Nice.
- That means...
Jin Seung was smart.
Hold on. How did you know about it, Yeong Cheol?
- Me?
- He knows me well.
Jin Seung was on my radio show.
- Was he?
- He was a guest.
Did Yeong Cheol ask for your number that day?
- After we exchanged numbers, - Right.
I was shocked.
- Why?
- Yeong Cheol is enthusiastic...
and talkative on shows.
But privately,
- I thought he'd be quiet.
- Right.
He's worse.
- He's much worse.
- He's too much.
Other than when I dated my wife,
he was the first I texted all day long.
For real. You have to stop the conversation.
Yeong Cheol and I made plans to meet up.
He treated me to meat and wine...
I had been craving.
I treated Jin Seung to a meal, right?
He promised to treat me next time but hasn't texted me since.
- You'd text nonstop.
- He got sick of you.
Back then, Yeong Cheol invited my wife as well.
- Really?
- Yes.
- We went together.
- You really lucked out.
I'm sure your wife got sick of Yeong Cheol that day.
My wife brings it up sometimes.
Why do they say people would've gotten sick of me?
- What did I do?
- What does she say?
What did I do to make you sick of me?
If we get treated to food,
- we'd pay...
- They claim...
- for wine.
- the guests got sick of me.
The guest is talking right now.
- But I...
- You'd better cut it short...
when the guest is talking.
But I'm a regular member of this show.
(Annoyed)
You should have let him talk first.
You just kept talking even when you knew he had to say something.
But Jin Seung must be used to being a good listener.
I bet he'd be tolerable enough to listen to Yeong Cheol for two days.
Actually, I'm very talkative too.
- Jin Seung talked a lot too.
- To be honest, I was...
Yes. I'm not always a good listener.
- Right. He kept talking.
- Jin Seung is really talkative.
- He won't just sit back and listen.
- Right.
- So he's a little...
- He won't give in.
- So he's very talkative.
- Right.
Speaking of which, do doctors develop habits from work?
Well... When I worked as an intern...
We always wear surgical gowns when going into the operating room.
When nurses hold up the gown like this,
- you wear it from the front.
- That's right.
- I see.
- Like this.
- So it closes at the back.
- Right.
Come and stand over here.
- Why do you make me stand up?
- I was at a hair salon, and...
- They shampoo your hair, right?
- A gown at the hair salon?
Hold up the gown for me. And I approached it like this.
My goodness.
(Hug me.)
And I approached it like this.
(An unexpected flirting)
- My goodness.
- Seriously.
- They were all taken aback.
- They must have been flustered.
They were startled and stepped back.
- This is very common for surgeons.
- And then, I would be like...
- That's so funny.
- It's really common.
- How about you, Nak Jun?
- We hold surgical tools...
- as we hold pencils.
- Yes.
We get scolded a lot because of this.
We would get hit right away when we held it in a different way.
- Why can't you hold it differently?
- When we operate...
It helps you operate more delicately.
You can also put your elbow and wrist like this...
so that the operating tools don't move.
- You shouldn't let it move...
- Like this?
- for accurate cuts.
- So that's how you hold it.
So when otolaryngologists have a get-together,
they hold tongs as if holding a pencil when they grill meat.
- Like this?
- They grill meat quite delicately.
And it's really hard to hold tongs like this.
My mother is a dentist.
- Dentists only care about teeth.
- Only teeth?
- No wonder.
- Right. They only care about teeth.
When I introduced my wife to her for the first time...
When you ask your mother how your girlfriend was,
most mothers would say that she was nice or she looked pretty.
- But all of a sudden, she said, - Something about her teeth?
"She needs to get braces."
You asked her about your girlfriend,
- and she said she needed braces.
- "She needs to get braces."
What kind of doctor is your wife?
- My wife is a radiologist.
- I see. She's a radiologist.
So she's... Wait. She gets confused between left and right.
- It's the opposite in pictures.
- It's the opposite.
The right side is always on the left side of the scan.
So when I told her to turn on the left turn signal,
she would turn on the right one.
(She turned on the right turn signal.)
- So she gets confused.
- Always...
Don't you hold the steering wheel like this when you drive?
Hold it like this?
What about Ho Dong? Does it have something to do with sand?
- Is it related to sand?
- Ho Dong is...
He always says this when he's at the beach.
Is there a famous raw fish restaurant nearby?
- It came from his profession.
- Since it's the sand beach.
- Whenever he sees the sand.
- Right. When he sees the sand.
- He looks for a good restaurant.
- I always crave food...
when I'm on the sand.
- Just like that.
- Right. When I go to the beach.
- Here's what I heard about doctors.
- Yes.
To our surprise, many doctors get sick.
- You get treatment from each other?
- There are a lot.
I hear Chang Yun is treated by Jin Seung. Is that right?
- Well...
- Why?
They say you can't see right under your nose.
- We were making videos...
- Yes.
- about various diseases.
One of them was ADHD in adults,
- which is a hot topic these days.
- Right.
I was explaining what I had prepared for this video.
And then I realized that something was going on between these two.
Their jaws dropped.
Come on. It wasn't like that.
I was so shocked then.
Nak Jun said he finally came to a conclusion...
considering all the behaviors Chang Yun had shown us.
- That he has ADHD?
- He has ADHD symptoms.
I've known him for more than 20 years.
- And he's always late.
- No, not anymore.
- You were late today.
- Today...
He was ten minutes late today.
- See? He always makes excuses.
- I see.
- There are some kids who are...
- Who gets distracted?
easily distracted, have difficulty paying attention, or often daydream.
They wander around the classroom during class.
They interrupt while teachers are talking.
Half of these kids get better naturally...
- as they grow up.
- I see.
But for some people, these symptoms continue into adulthood.
- Like Chang Yun.
- Right.
- Chang Yun is one of them?
They are not as distracted as when they were young, but...
This is how they manage time.
They have difficulty estimating time.
For instance, they only think about...
the optimal time they need.
- Five minutes to take a shower.
- Right.
Take the elevator right away.
The subway arrives without delay.
And they conclude that...
- To be honest...
- it would only take 30 minutes.
I can understand him now.
It was because he was sick.
He was sick.
Can adults with ADHD be cured?
Well... Medication can reduce symptoms a lot.
- So you need to take medicine.
- So medication helps. Amazing.
- Here's what I heard.
- What is it?
- Adults with HED...
- It's ADHD.
I hear people with ADHD can make...
great ER doctors.
- Emergencies keep coming up...
- They need to focus...
- in the ER.
- on each moment.
- I see.
- When you're focused on one thing,
if something happens around you,
you might miss it because you're occupied in already.
- They don't miss a thing.
- But they can hear everything.
I hear that they think of it as a mission.
- They finish them 1 by 1.
- "I should finish this 1st..."
- "and move on to the next fun." - I see.
Many celebrities and artists have ADHD.
- Of course.
- Let me explain.
When people without ADHD are working,
if something comes up to their minds,
they can ignore it and focus on your work.
But people with ADHD...
don't miss those things that come up to their minds.
That's why many creative people...
- have ADHD.
- Because they don't miss it.
- I have a question then.
- When you're focused...
There are people who can't focus...
- compared to others.
- Of course.
Then, are you saying all those people have ADHD?
- No. Well...
- I don't think so.
It's not just about concentration, but there are looseness,
forgetfulness, and so on. We check on all those things.
Also, by measuring brain waves,
we check if they have a certain brain wave...
- of an ADHD patient.
- Of course.
- That's how we identify them.
- So there are things to check.
Next, there are correlated keywords.
- Correlated keywords.
- For Nak Jun...
- What's this? "Hansan Lee?" - "Hansan Lee?"
I'm from the Hansan Lee family.
- So you're from Hansan Lee family?
- When I played online games,
that was what I used as my ID.
When I was writing novels, I used that name like an ID as well.
- And that went on for years.
- I see.
As "The Trauma Code" became a drama and a webtoon,
it became known to people.
- "Hansan Lee." - When did you start the novel?
- Which one?
- "The Trauma Code."
"The Trauma Code?" I started it in 2019.
So it has been 5 to 6 years.
- You did it back then.
- I did it a long time ago.
And I stopped treating patients about five years ago.
Then remove your name tag. It says you're an otolaryngologist.
- Why? I still have my license.
- He can't see patients now.
- Then...
- You're not working at a hospital?
- you don't work at a hospital?
- But he still has his license?
- Now, he...
- I don't work at a hospital,
I don't have my own clinic, and I don't treat patients.
- So you're a writer now?
- I am...
- Right.
- Yes. I'm a full-time writer.
- So you're a writer.
- I wrote some before coming here.
We're "Doctor Friends," and he's just a friend.
- We're the doctors.
- So you two are doctors, and...
- Well, I...
- So he's just a friend.
I see. He's just a friend of the doctors.
But don't your family members or friends miss you being a doctor?
- I know.
- It wasn't easy to become one.
You had to betray others to do so.
Right. I don't feel good when I think about it.
But in the case of my father...
He really wanted to write something,
and his son is doing it now.
- So he loves it so much.
- But he would have regrets too.
My wife likes it too since I can spend more time...
- with the family.
- Your family still has a doctor.
- Right. We still have one.
- I see.
Which one is better in terms of income?
- Well...
- At the moment?
Actually, I was an intern, resident, army surgeon,
and a part-time doctor for about a year and a half. That's all.
So I've never earned much as a doctor.
So compared to that, being a writer is much better.
Nak Jun, so you started this novel five years ago, right?
But I'm sure you couldn't have even imagined...
- it becoming popular like this.
- Right.
It must have been like this.
"What? Ju Ji Hoon is going to be in it?"
It became real as you went through this kind of process.
- Can you tell us about it?
- But you can't, right?
- He can tell us now.
- Now I can do that.
- I can tell you now.
- He couldn't back then.
- He couldn't tell us back then.
- Because of the embargo.
- It was confidential.
- I was dying to say it.
He must have wanted to tell others...
- when things went well.
- You can't tell anyone, right?
I can't tell anyone about it.
Not even to your psychiatrist?
He's the worst at keeping a secret, so never.
He would make announcements in the chatrooms.
It's been so long.
- It's an old one.
- The novel came out in 2019.
At the end of 2019,
Naver made a commercial featuring Actor Kim Yun Seok.
A commercial of my novel.
It became a big hit,
and I signed a drama contract right away in 2020.
- So it was five years ago.
- Gosh. That's so long ago.
And at the end of 2020, they said Netflix made the contract,
and they told me not to tell anyone about it.
Because if I did, it could be canceled.
So I couldn't tell anyone about it, and I had to wait.
In 2022, Ju Ji Hoon...
- was finally cast.
- He made a contract.
A staff member told me it would be released to the public the next day.
They told me that.
- But it didn't.
- It must've been delayed.
So I asked about it,
and they told me that we had to keep the embargo for more.
They told me I shouldn't tell others again.
So I had to keep it to myself for a while.
And six months later, it was released to the public.
- So simply put...
- Then, are you writing now?
- The series is still on.
- "The Trauma Code" ended.
There's a prequel of Baek Kang Hyuk.
It's about when Baek Kang Hyuk was an intern and a resident.
There's "A.I. Doctor" which is about an internist.
And there's "Dark Haired British Doctor."
He writes many novels at the same time.
- I'm writing three at the moment.
- Really? That's interesting.
- A sequel...
- What if you get confused?
to "The Trauma Code" will come out then.
There's still a lot left in the original story.
- Because the novel is long, - I see.
- there's still more left.
- You're not writing again, right?
- It was only part of it.
- It's been published already.
- Nak Jun.
- Then...
Let's say it's the day when the drama will be revealed.
Okay.
It would feel different on that day.
- Thinking about people's reactions.
- It was no joke.
(How did you feel on the day when the drama was released?)
- I couldn't sleep the day before.
- Of course not.
I couldn't sleep. I went home right away at 5pm.
I called my children to watch it together,
- "Let's watch it together." - and I played it.
It was my first time watching it,
and after a few minutes, I could feel it.
- It's interesting.
- "It's going to become a hit."
"This is interesting."
I looked up on the internet, and people seemed to like it.
- How did you feel...
- It was...
when it won "Squid Game 2" and became the number 1 show?
- There were many articles about it.
I was out of my mind.
I couldn't sleep at night.
- For about two weeks.
- He couldn't sleep.
The English title of the show is...
"The Trauma Code: Heroes on Call."
- "Seru" means interesting...
- I see.
- in Indonesian.
- "Seru."
The Indonesian fans commented that a lot.
- People liked it.
- He must have loved it.
Recently... Nak Jun just talked about it.
He said he felt great joy from it.
- Seriously...
- How could it be...
I really enjoyed "The Trauma Code."
But this won against "The Trauma Code."
It's "Divorce Camp."
- That's right.
- It's...
Yes, it's amazing.
- I mean...
- But...
I was wondering what he was trying to say.
- I'm...
- Seriously.
not lying.
- When I saw that, - Okay.
I felt great joy from it.
It's the severe divorce center.
- But...
- Squid...
Everyone I know watches it.
About Jin Seung.
People here might not like this.
He says he has a JTBC trauma.
- Why?
- What did they do wrong to you?
- JTBC didn't do anything wrong.
JTBC didn't do anything wrong.
In 2020,
there was a JTBC show called "Normal Family."
- They asked me to join it.
- Yes.
- What happened?
- We had high hopes then.
At the time, there was a senior psychiatrist...
who was asked to join first...
- Why can't you talk?
- What's wrong?
- He still has the trauma.
- Do you want some water?
- He hasn't overcome it yet.
- It was Dr. Oh Eun Yeong.
- She's so powerful.
- She was cast first.
The writers cast me next to her.
She talked really well.
I told them, "I don't think I can do it." And the writer said,
"You can do it."
- "The battle of the old and new." - The battle of the old and new.
- "And your surnames are both Oh." - That's right.
- There's that mood.
- Oh versus Oh.
- Right.
- So..
- Former Oh and Next Oh.
- Oh versus Oh.
And the two...
I joined and I was in the show.
I still remember. We did the shoot in Paju.
Dr. Oh Eun Yeong came and said,
"I'm Oh Eun Yeong."
- She's really nice.
- "You can..."
"always feel free to cut me off."
"Just cut me off when I talk."
You're doing a good impression of her.
She was preparing for it.
"Cut me off anytime."
So I did so confidently.
But as soon as she started talking,
(Exclaiming)
- I realized...
- You lost.
I didn't have anything to say.
I had nothing to say.
She was professional and talked really well on TV.
- That's right.
- She said,
"Do you know why this child is like this?"
- Right. That's...
- You should have answered it.
You should have answered it.
But I was curious too.
(I want to be the first to know.)
Jin Seung.
- That...
- I had no guess.
You're an expert.
"I'm an expert too."
"Do you know why this child doesn't eat fried rice?"
"Do you know?"
The MC was curious.
The celebrities and client were also curious.
- I was curious as well.
- You shouldn't be curious.
You should have said, "I know."
I'll tell you after watching the VCR.
I wanted it to end quickly.
- You want to hear it quickly.
- The VCR.
I became...
an audience.
I couldn't say a word for four hours.
My lips got dry...
- and I felt exhausted.
- You couldn't say a word?
The kind MC asked me something...
- and made it flow well.
- A question to you.
I was speaking after two hours.
The MC said, "Dr. Oh Seung Jin."
- The name is wrong.
- Oh Seung Jin.
(He heard a strange name after the wait.)
Oh Seung Jin.
My name was forgotten.
That's possible.
- Dr. Oh Seung Jin.
- They didn't have name tags.
- They didn't.
"What do you think, Dr. Oh Seung Jin?"
They didn't care about you even a bit.
- Jin Seung or Seung Jin.
- Who was the MC?
- Yoon or Park.
- So,
I have that trauma.
That year, in 2020, there was a JTBC drama...
- called "The World of the Married." - Right.
That drama was so successful...
that they made "The World of the Married Special."
They talked about the behind-the-scenes of the drama.
And there were experts...
analyzing Lee Tae Oh,
- a character...
- "Love is not a crime."
played by Park Hae Joon.
- "Love is not a crime." - Right.
(The line that put many viewers in shock)
Is it a crime or not?
They asked that question to four experts.
- So?
- I wanted to make up...
for what I did.
- You should.
- It's a battle.
- It was there.
- You had the desire.
I should overcome my trauma.
It is a crime...
- because he cheated.
- Yes.
But I thought I wouldn't have...
so much screen time if I said it was a crime.
You were smart.
- Since everyone says it's a crime.
- Yes.
You were thorough.
- You had to talk.
- He wanted to say something.
- You were thorough.
- Yes.
There was a lawyer among them.
The adultery law had been abolished.
- Right.
- So when you look at it...
from the legal point of view, it's not a crime.
So I thought, "The lawyer will say it's not a crime."
"The rest of the people will say it's a crime."
"If I said it wasn't a crime,"
- "I'd get some screentime." - Yes.
"I should explain..."
- "after saying that." - You should explain.
But I was the only one who said it wasn't a crime.
- Hold on.
- Jin Seung was the only one.
- But...
- Amazing.
- The whole nation...
- Jin Seung.
said Lee Tae Oh was a horrible person.
- Lee Tae Oh...
- He is innocent.
And the explanation got cut out.
What?
It was edited out.
You just became a weird person.
I became a weird person.
(Lee Tae Oh is guilty.)
(Lee Tae Oh is innocent.)
- The psychiatrist...
- Innocent.
There should have been further explanations.
So the subscribers...
- They commented.
- sent me messages.
So we urgently gathered...
- to explain why I said that.
- On YouTube?
- We made a video.
- It was your greed.
(Why did you say he was innocent?)
(I'm sorry.)
(Why did you cause a controversy?)
(Lee Tae Oh is innocent...)
(and Oh Jin Seung is guilty.)
Jin Seung,
you're talking about your trauma about JTBC.
You seem to have overcome it...
- through Men on a Mission.
- I know.
- Really?
- Your talks...
are getting better responses than you thought, right?
It's funny.
You'd know, Jin Seung.
If you hadn't said that you liked Ho Dong and Jang Hoon,
you'd have formed a new trauma today.
- Do you know...
- A new trauma.
- how the production crew...
- Well done.
I think people would know my name now.
They'd know Oh Jin Seung for sure.
- Next, Chang Yun.
- Yun Chang.
Chang Yun's related keyword...
is Mr. Always Right.
- Mr. Always Right.
- This is...
Is this something like the Cursing Granny?
Someone who always says the right thing?
- The right thing.
I say warm nagging words in hopes...
that people could be healthier.
- It's not warm.
- We rarely get nagged...
in life. So I say...
lots of right words that could be helpful on various social media.
Nak Jin says they're too right.
That's because...
- What...
- He keeps...
That's called a boomer.
There's something I still remember.
"The only thing that gets relieved from eating is your belt."
It doesn't relieve your stress.
- No. That's not right.
- I read that...
and thought...
What about eating spicy food?
- People relieve stress with that.
- It wasn't nice.
- So many people do that.
- Right.
When you eat spicy food,
the spiciness enters as a whole.
You made these two angry.
- So, naturally, - You're dead.
- I really...
- endorphins come out...
- to make you happy.
- The happiness from eating...
- is a blessing.
- But it's good...
if you eat good food.
But if people eat ultra-processed food,
that acts as a pain killer.
It reduces the pain of that moment,
but you also get addicted and build tolerance.
"Don't add white rice to ramyeon."
- How?
- That's totally right.
"But making two portions of ramyeon..."
"is worse than eating it with rice."
"If you really want to eat it,"
"add some multi-grain rice with beans."
"The best things to add..."
"are green onions and eggs."
Then one person commented,
"Wouldn't it be okay to add white rice..."
"since it wouldn't be white anymore in the ramyeon soup?"
- That's right.
- That's logical.
- White rice...
- That person is logical.
Then it keeps coming.
"What about white rice with mala xiang guo?"
- "What?" - "Since eating two portions..."
"isn't good, I'll have three from now on."
"I added lots of green onions..."
"and eggs to the ramyeon."
He asked, "Is this for ten people?"
That's too many.
- That's Ho Dong's.
- That's...
This is good. "Then I'll have rice with beans..."
"but I won't eat the beans."
- "Question marks again." - He keeps commenting that.
The last one. "Did you drop it in by mistake?"
Isn't that too weird?
It looks like the ramyeon was dropped in the rice pot.
But it's not right to put rice with beans...
- in ramyeon.
- That's right.
But when you eat carbohydrates,
- your blood sugar levels shoot up.
- Right.
- Since that's bad,
you should eat it with proteins.
So if you can, eat it with eggs.
I'm giving such alternatives.
I ate ramyeon,
but I had to shoot a show in the morning,
and I shouldn't have a swollen face.
I hear it helps if you drink water.
If you add two spoons of white milk,
you swell a little less.
Is that true?
- I don't know.
- I don't think so.
- You have to consider some things.
- Really?
People only think about the saltiness.
If it's salty, salt will absorb water,
- which makes you swell.
- Right.
But when you eat sweet things, you swell.
When you eat sweet food, your blood sugar level goes up.
- Right.
- When that goes up,
insulin, which lowers the blood sugar levels,
- is produced.
- Insulin.
- That insulin...
- It...
makes you get swollen.
Even skinny people get swollen ankles...
when they get an insulin shot.
Right.
That's stressful.
My blood sugar level is dropping.
- But...
- You have to eat sugar...
- when it's going low.
- No.
People keep saying "I'm losing my blood sugar."
- We say that when we record.
- That's why...
you always have snacks in the studio.
- Like chocolate.
- We have them in our waiting rooms.
- I really hate that.
- Why?
What do we do when we're low on blood sugar?
- It doesn't go low.
- Why not?
- People...
- You're making it shoot up.
- It went up.
- It didn't drop?
- This...
- I'm really losing blood sugar.
- This is a misunderstanding.
- Hypoglycemia...
There are only a few illnesses...
- that cause hypoglycemia.
- What?
- Our brain only absorbs glucose.
- Really?
So it maintains a steady level of glucose.
The brain doesn't even store glucose.
The glucose gets stored in the liver.
Your blood sugar level doesn't drop even if you starve for a day.
- What?
- Right.
- But your hands shake.
- Yes.
But that's because when you get stressed or dehydrated,
the sympathetic nervous system gets become active.
When the blood sugar level increases, it stimulates the brain.
- That creates dopamine.
- This is what I think.
When I eat chocolate, I feel better...
- and my vision gets clear.
- Yes.
You're saying we shouldn't eat that.
But what about the stress...
and shaking hands caused by that? Are you saying we should enjoy that?
- The shaking hands?
- No.
What should we do? The psychiatrist should tell us.
- This...
- Oh Seung Jin!
- What should we enjoy?
- Say something, Oh Seung Jin.
- Oh Seung Jin.
- Instead of chocolates or snacks,
- Water?
- drink water or eat nuts...
- or Greek yogurt.
- Eggs.
Eat eggs or protein shakes.
Is water better or sports drinks?
Water is better.
Why?
Sports drinks are really good.
- Sports drinks are good.
- Yes.
Sports drinks...
I'm curious about this the most.
What can you drink instead of water?
These two are just...
really curious.
- I'm really curious.
- Tea?
- Americano is good too.
- Carbonated drinks without sugar.
I don't recommend carbonated drinks without sugar to Shin Dong.
- Why not?
- Carbonated drinks aren't good.
Carbonated drinks aren't the problem.
Sparkling water is fine.
- When you drink it sugar-free...
- Diet Coke.
- If you drink those...
- I love them.
As for Shin Dong,
you normally eat lots of sweet food.
Why are you saying it with such certainty?
- Hey!
- What?
Why would you say that?
- Don't listen to him.
- Wait.
- It could be his body constitution.
- Calm down.
- His body constitution.
- Forget about it.
- The type that easily gains weight.
- Don't be so sure of it.
- You can't judge people.
I'll correct myself.
- You normally enjoy eating food.
- Yes.
- Yes, I do.
- That's still...
- I do.
- It's true, though.
- It is.
- It's because...
with zero drinks,
there's a discrepancy in compensation.
When we eat something sweet, the blood sugar level has to rise.
- Right?
- Yes.
But if it doesn't rise even after eating something sweet,
two things will happen.
Shin Dong's body will prepare itself to absorb all the glucose...
that will come in next.
- It's waiting?
- Yes.
- To be prepared.
- And the brain thinks,
"I'm eating something, but why isn't it sweet?"
So it boosts the appetite.
We're like Pavlov's dog.
We feed Pavlov's dog while ringing a bell.
- I know. Then it will drool...
- Then if we ring the bell...
- when a bell rings.
- That's right.
It will drool.
But if we don't feed it, the dog will get angry.
Sure.
But as for Shing Dong,
- his blood sugar level rose...
- Hey...
- Why would you...
- when he had something sweet.
Shin Dong's brain likes blood sugar.
His tongue tasted the sweetness.
For his whole life,
- his blood sugar level rose...
- It can cause a problem.
- when his tongue felt sweetness.
- His words make sense,
- but why do I feel offended?
- Chang Yun.
What I'm saying is, people think it's completely okay...
to drink zero-sugar drinks.
Of course, it's better than regular drinks with sugar,
but it does disrupt our metabolic system.
- I see.
- Yes.
- I have a question. You're married.
- What can we drink then?
- Could this be why...
you had a crush for so many years?
If your girlfriend says, "I have a headache today,"
and you say, "Your blood sugar level is low."
- That could be why.
- "You ate this, didn't you?"
It wasn't a crush for 11 years.
- It was a crush.
- How does that go on for 11 years?
- Sure, I did like her.
- For 11 years?
- But...
My wife was 20 and I was 22 when we met on a group blind date.
And we got married when I was in my 30's.
- Really?
- We dated for a year.
I heard Nak Jun was the host for your wedding ceremony.
I was the host.
And you were scared to death?
- He was there as a guest as well.
- Yes.
- I was so scared.
- I arrived there,
and they said I had to announce the entrance of the bride.
We were exchanging signals, and the staff said,
"Now," so I said, "The bride will enter."
- But the door wouldn't open.
- Oh no.
- The bride wouldn't enter.
- What?
She wouldn't come in.
And the adults in the front started to have these faces.
- People were whispering.
- "What's going on?" - When that happens,
- usually, the bride ran off.
- "Did she run off?"
Or her ex-boyfriend came and took her away.
- At the last moment...
- I remember that the bride...
didn't look too happy...
- in the waiting room.
- She didn't look happy.
- Somehow.
- She was so happy.
- She didn't look happy.
- She somehow didn't look good.
The bride's face had zero emotions.
Thankfully, the door opened and she came in.
That took about ten minutes.
- What was the reason?
- Why?
It turned out that...
the venue...
- was his family's hotel, - What?
and they didn't have experience with weddings.
- The venue was his family's hotel, - What?
There was miscommunication.
- Chang Yun...
- "His family's hotel?"
- What is that supposed to mean?
- What do you mean?
- He lives in a hotel?
- What are you saying?
- You're saying it so simply.
- What is his family's hotel?
My father runs a hotel.
Gosh.
(The Second Son of a Hotel Family)
If it has a hall big enough to hold a wedding...
Where is it?
- It's in Mokpo.
- His hometown is Mokpo.
His nickname is the Mokpo Prince.
(The Mokpo Prince who became a doctor)
He was amazing.
- Shin Park Hotel?
- Shin Beach Hotel.
- Shin Beach Hotel? Gosh.
- You know it?
- How did you know?
- Is it famous?
Doesn't it have a nightclub?
- How did you know?
- There used to be a nightclub.
I performed there, as Roo'Ra.
- Did you?
- We performed there.
- As Roo'Ra?
- Yes.
- Roo'Ra had a show there?
- Roo'Ra went there often.
Shin Beach Hotel. The one that has a beach.
- That's it.
- Shin Beach Hotel.
They have a lot of good restaurants there.
That's right.
(It suits Ho Dong's taste.)
- It's the biggest in Mokpo.
- They have small octopuses.
- Small octopus is amazing.
- Gosh.
- He's amazing.
- That's cool.
During vacation,
he invited us to Mokpo, since his family had a hotel.
Usually, when your friend says they own a hotel,
you usually expect a bed and breakfast,
- or a motel.
- Sure. That's what you think.
We took the KTX and got there,
and there was a car to pick us up.
We got in the car,
and it was an actual hotel.
We were only 20,
so we didn't have much experience going to a hotel.
It had over ten floors.
Gosh.
We went in, and his father greeted us with a kind smile.
He was wearing a suit.
Is it the biggest hotel in the area?
- It's the biggest in Mokpo.
- The best in Mokpo?
I should ask Dong Hae if he's been to it.
And you got so close to him after that, Nak Jun?
I stuck right next to him.
(They have been best friends for 15 years since then.)
It was so memorable because they had...
a Chinese restaurant at the top floor.
And it had the table that spins.
Gosh, only the expensive places have that.
It was my first time seeing that.
- We were students.
- It was a Chinese restaurant.
- Everything was so good.
- All the employees were saying, - I'm hungry.
"Welcome, Young Master."
They did not do that.
- "Young Master?" - Young Master.
- They never said that.
- I can see why...
There's a reason why...
Nak Jun and Jin Seung waited...
even when Chang Yun was an hour late.
Everything makes sense now.
- That's why.
- I get it.
His family owns a hotel, so he can be late.
- No.
- They can wait at the hotel.
My wife cried at that time.
That day. Because...
- She loved it?
- "Gosh, this is all mine?"
"Gosh, this will go to my child?"
No, that's not it. My father only runs it.
The employees are all calling him "Young Master."
My grandfather's younger brother is rich.
The owner is his grandfather's younger brother.
- His father operates it.
- He operates it.
- Still.
- For us, it's the same.
- It's the same.
- Who has that?
It's your family's.
And when it ended, the employees were in a panic,
- since there was a problem...
- Sure.
- at the Young Master's wedding.
- Not just anyone.
So when the groom and bride were marching out,
I said, "The bride and groom will march,"
- and they had the confetti shots.
- I remember that.
They hit the chandelier.
The chandelier was shaking.
(Gosh, Young Master!)
- It was so...
- That's funny.
- I was the host, but...
- I remember that.
I was scared that it would fall.
- I was wondering what was going on.
- I can imagine.
Did Chang Yun go like this...
Then the employee would say, "Gosh, Young Master."
- "Please have mercy." - What are you talking about?
"Young Master, you have a presentation today."
- Okay.
- "Young Master, may I proceed?"
Let's go to the presentation class.
(Woo Chang Yun's Presentation Class)
I prepared a fun experiment today.
Just tell us more about your hotel.
What experiment? It's no fun.
So are you going to inherit it?
This is a really important story.
As we get older,
we want to die while living...
a normal life at home, right?
No, we want to die in a hotel.
- That could be.
- A hotel.
The reason I'm saying this is because...
- we're all in our middle years.
- Yes.
Among men over the age of 75,
one out of four or five men...
will have to go to a nursing home.
It's because they can't manage daily life.
Think about it. What is daily life?
Going to the bathroom, taking a bath,
having a meal, moving around,
using the toilet,
and getting dressed.
Among these six things,
if you can't handle more than two,
you say you can't manage daily life.
- That's so sad.
- This feels so far away, right?
Among men over the age of 75,
one out of four or five of them can't do this.
It's coming soon for Ho Dong.
The important thing is that...
- we seem to age the same as others, - Yes.
but this is due to age, not illness.
- Sure.
- But...
some age one year,
while others can age half of that amount.
- You can extend your youth?
- Yes.
It was to be that way,
if we want to die healthily...
at home when we age,
instead of spending several years in a nursing home.
Anyway, the first test we are doing...
- is the cracker test.
- What is that?
- We eat a lot of snacks, right?
- Yes.
But it seems unfair.
Some people eat snacks...
and don't move, but they don't gain weight.
- Yes.
- Yes, Eunhyuk.
- The body constitution?
- Yes.
Body constitution actually exists.
- It's unfair.
- What it means is...
there are people who can use carbohydrates...
as energy in their muscles faster.
(Some people can use it as energy in their muscles.)
Then they will have a less chance of having high blood sugar.
- Yes.
- These people...
can have some more snacks.
Those who can't lower their blood sugar levels...
also have a way.
They can take a walk after eating.
But then we get hungry and eat again.
Does that happen to you?
I'm talking about Ho Dong!
But Ho Dong does have an advantage.
He can burn much more calories than us...
even if it's just a walk.
- Since I am built bigger?
- Yes.
- Since he's a pig?
- Since he's bigger?
Pigs only have 15 percent of body fat.
- Pigs?
- That's right pigs are quite...
- That's so thin.
- I'm sure he's quite similar.
- Am I a pig?
- No.
I'm saying you don't have much body fat.
Take one each.
- So...
- Are we eating that?
- Don't eat it right away.
- Okay.
First...
Why are you saying that only to me?
- Why just me?
- No.
No.
- He has a lot of muscles.
- Now...
Gather some spit in your mouth.
And then...
put the cracker in your mouth...
and start to chew when I tell you to.
Raise your hand when you start to feel the sweetness. Okay?
See how fast you can taste it.
I'll begin, okay?
Begin chewing.
(The test begins!)
Five seconds.
I don't taste the sweetness.
Is this sweet?
Okay. Ten seconds.
Good.
- I don't taste the sweetness.
- I don't taste it.
- Isn't it sweet?
- It's been 15 seconds.
- It's so sweet.
- I taste salt.
- Me, too.
- The cracker is salty.
- I don't taste the sweetness.
- The sweetness?
- I don't taste it.
- It's sweet?
It's so sweet.
- It came fast.
- I don't taste it.
It has been 30 seconds.
- Really?
- It has to do with blood sugar.
- Shin Dong was the fastest.
- Yes.
- This is...
- Being fast is good.
The tongue has a lot of genes for amylase,
the enzyme that breaks down carbohydrates.
Generally speaking.
I noticed that people who break down carbohydrates quickly...
starting from the mouth tend to use carbs more efficiently as energy,
so they're less exposed to high blood sugar.
So as for Shin Dong,
he either eats a lot...
I eat enough to overcome that.
The issue isn't so much related to snacks, but rather high-fat diets...
or overall calorie intake.
- You're accurate.
- That's right.
- The overall calorie.
- I eat a lot of rice.
Who are the people who didn't feel the sweetness until the very end?
- Me.
- I see.
You need to cut back on snacks a bit.
- Oh, I see.
- Who took more than 20 seconds.
You might tend to use fatty acids...
- as energy more often.
- Fatty acids?
You know those foods that suddenly spike your blood sugar.
Things like soft bread or drinks get absorbed quickly...
and skyrocket your blood sugar.
With this kind of blood sugar, someone like Shin Dong...
can burn energy by walking a bit,
but you're more likely to be exposed to high blood sugar for longer.
It's important to take a walk after a meal.
- I see.
- After meals.
- If someone like you takes a walk, - In the end...
they can prevent having high blood sugar.
- So how...
- Shin Dong actually...
If you eat, walk, and do some activities,
you have a strong system...
- with carbohydrates.
- Is that so?
That's why he can lose weight easily.
- That's possible.
- I see.
He fluctuates for about 30kg.
- That's...
- Isn't that too much?
- That's too much.
- Isn't that the case?
It's 36kg to be precise.
- That's too dramatic.
- It's for real.
You say doing a simple exercise is good for us after having a meal.
How long should we walk?
People assume walking 20,000 or 30,000 steps would be better.
But that's not the case.
Older people might not benefit...
- from walking too much.
- It might cause plantar fasciitis.
Yes, we recommend walking 8,000 to 10,000 steps.
- In a day?
- Yes.
The average Seoul citizen walks about 5,000 steps a day.
If you walk for 20 minutes...
after meals twice a day, that adds up to 8,000 steps.
- But...
- Let's walk home.
isn't it okay for people whose blood sugar level increases...
and then drops right away?
We call that blood sugar spike.
When you drink a beverage, your blood sugar rises quickly.
A sudden spike in blood sugar is unusual.
So the pancreas secretes too much insulin...
because our body still thinks we've gone on a massive binge.
That's how your blood sugar level drops drastically.
But here's the problem.
Since the body secreted too much insulin,
it drops even lower than the baseline.
So you feel hungry again 30 minutes or an hour after drinking them.
Since the blood sugar level drops,
the brain thinks about the time when we were happy...
and wonder why our blood sugar level is dropping.
It orders us to eat more.
How could we lie to our brains?
We'll eat if the brain asks us to.
Then we go for a snack.
If the blood sugar level fluctuates a lot,
metabolic disorders can easily develop.
What if we take pills regularly to reduce the blood sugar levels?
Diabetic patients do that.
The pills make the diabetic patients...
to reduce the fluctuations of their blood sugar levels.
It's great that they get to avoid high blood sugar levels.
Anyway, we need to stay active...
to send blood sugar to our muscles...
so that they function.
Blood sugar has to go to the muscles.
That's the best.
For older people,
if high blood sugar keeps recurring, they lose muscle mass...
and eventually end up getting sick.
Then their appetite decreases,
so they eat less and lose more muscles,
making it hard to carry out daily activities.
Then they have to go to a nursing home.
Thats why being a little chubby when youre older...
helps you live longer.
- Ho Dong will have a long life.
- Because it means more muscles.
- It contains muscles.
- But being very chubby...
- isnt good, right?
- That isn't good.
- But...
- About going on a diet.
Some people go on a diet even though they don't need to...
for their health. But 2 out of 3...
- will stop eating carbohydrates.
- That's right.
That's very dangerous.
- Is it dangerous?
- Normally...
- I want you to tell us about it.
- I hear plain white rice is bad.
- They don't eat rice at all.
- You're right.
They stop eating noodles too.
- They only eat the side dishes.
- They can eat brown rice.
- Yes.
- There are two things.
- Okay.
- Honestly, in the 21st century,
why are we eating snacks?
- Because it's tasty.
- Right?
We eat for pleasure.
We tend to seek pleasure...
when we're stressed.
If we don't have enough sleep, we seek for chips.
Our brain gets stressed when...
glucose isn't supplied consistently.
People say you become edgy when you stop taking carbohydrates.
- It's true.
- My goodness.
Does that mean Jang Hoon never took carbs in his life?
- He doesn't enjoy it in real life.
- Right.
- That's why his personality is...
- I eat a lot.
We can lower our stress levels with 100g of carbs every day.
How much is 100g of carbs?
- Two bowls of rice.
- One spoon for you.
You need to eat two bowls of rice a day in terms of carbs...
to minimize the stress on your brain.
Secondly, it's not suitable for the elderly.
Among the elderly patients, especially for women,
there are people with too little muscle mass.
The insulin produced from eating carbohydrates helps build muscles.
So you can't gain a lot of muscles if you don't eat carbohydrates...
and without insulin.
Muscle is your lifeline, everyone.
What I want to say is...
you need to exercise to gain muscles.
When you grow old,
- you tend to just go for a walk.
- Right.
But that's wrong. Mid-aged men...
need to exercise to gain muscles...
to secure your hormones too.
- Yes, I heard that from others too.
- We need to do strength training.
If you maintain your male hormones, your stomach flattens,
your vitality improves, and you feel more energetic,
which makes you naturally walk more during the day.
- Thats how we can stay...
- Sleeping is important too.
at home until the end,
surrounded by loved ones,
even as we age...
or well just live forever through AI.
- I see. It went viral once.
- I have one question.
When you catch a cold,
should you go to an ENT doctor or an internal medicine doctor?
- I wonder about this too.
- An internal medicine doctor.
- I'm very curious about this.
- Look.
- I go to an ENT doctor.
- What do we fear about a cold?
- I'll give you a chance.
Answer first.
Okay. You caught a cold.
But the scariest part is that it could turn into pneumonia.
An internal medicine doctor can see if it's pneumonia.
Considering the risk of it worsening, you should visit...
- Visit an internal medicine doctor.
- an internal medicine doctor.
Pneumonia is a lower respiratory tract infection.
- Lower.
- It rarely happens.
A cold is an upper respiratory tract infection.
The most common complications of a cold...
- are sinusitis and otitis media.
- That's right.
Sorry, but the author should stay out of this conversation.
- My friends are doctors.
- Let me talk to a doctor.
- Five years ago.
- He suddenly...
Isn't it true that the mind governs all illnesses?
Tell me, doctor!
- Mental strength.
- The mind governs all illnesses.
- Doctor Oh Seung Jun!
- Right?
If your mind is healthy, your body becomes healthy too.
IYMHYBBH!
(IYMHYBBH: If your mind is healthy, your body becomes healthy too.)
- Exercising after meals is vital.
- Yes.
- Having regular meals.
Sleeping is important too.
It's because even for people in their 20s,
we tried making them sleep two hours less every day for a week.
Their male hormone levels...
dropped to those of men...
- about 10 to 15 years older.
- Is that so?
Securing male hormones will lead to an increase in muscle mass.
- Yes.
How long should we sleep?
- Seven to eight hours.
- It's a must.
- Six hours isn't enough, right?
- It's not enough.
It might be the worst.
Sleeping six hours makes you feel all right.
- Yes, but I'm tired.
- But the problem is...
your stress level will be higher regularly.
If your stress hormone level is high,
it helps you to stay active.
Stress hormones keep increasing visceral fat...
and breaking down muscle in our bodies metabolically.
It constantly consumes your body just enough to keep you going.
(I'm getting stressed!)
In modern civilization,
we have this desire to live longer and healthy, right?
So I think we need to enjoy the benefits of medicine...
while also having the awareness to recognize what could harm us.
Then we can live longer.
My goodness.
I want to be friends with you!
He's like the class representative.
Lee Nak Jun.
- Yes.
- Hi.
You're more interested in medicine than I imagined.
- Right?
- Our age makes us interested.
I should've gone with some information on ENT.
Today, Im planning to give a lecture about web novels.
Please tell us about allergies!
Allergic rhinitis!
- I'll give you a private one later.
- I cough.
I keep coughing.
Nak Jun isn't lecturing about medicine?
He can't.
- He's an author.
- You're right.
- He's not confident.
- I kept thinking about it.
I thought if I should've lectured about medicine.
Does anyone read web novels here?
- I read webtoons.
- Webtoons.
- I read a lot.
- "Solo Leveling." It's a web novel.
- There's "Solo Leveling."
- It's so popular.
- I'm reading it. It's so fun.
I wrote my first web novel in 2016.
How much do you think the total annual sales of web novels was?
- For a year?
- Total sales.
- I don't think it's a big number.
- Everything all together.
- Maybe 30 million dollars?
- Is it 500 million dollars?
- Maybe 500 million dollars.
- Did you say 30 million dollars?
- It's lower than that.
- My gosh. It was lower?
- Then 20 million dollars.
- It was between those numbers.
This is an approximate number. They didn't calculate it back then.
It was too little to sum up.
How much do you think Korea earns with web novels?
- Now, it's very high.
- Is it 100 million dollars?
It's web novels.
Only web novels without the webtoons.
- Web novels only?
- No webtoons.
- About 200 million dollars?
- That high?
- We have 200 million dollars.
- Maybe 500 million dollars?
- Anyone more?
- Are you the auction guy?
- I'll say 700 million dollars.
- Okay, 700 million dollars.
- I'll say one billion dollars.
- One billion dollars.
- Did you say 1 billion dollars?
- I'll say 100 million dollars.
His name should be Lee Auction.
Ho Dong got the closest number.
- What?
- My gosh.
We earned more than one billion dollars.
- How is that possible?
- Seriously?
It has grown by almost several dozen times.
To put it in perspective,
web novels generate more revenue...
than the publishing industry and bookstores combined.
Because of that,
a lot of writers entered the web novel industry.
- How nice.
- Look at me, for example.
I stopped treating patients...
- and began working as an author.
- That's right.
Among the production crew members, I bet there's...
Among them?
I bet there's an author who writes web novels under a pen name.
- I see.
- That might be the case.
TV writers are very interested in the web novel industry.
- Screenwriters too.
- Of course.
- There are many such people.
- If it's over one billion dollars,
they won't stay in TV writing.
There must be more than you expect.
Many people are flocking to the industry.
Because of that, the quality of the web novels began to go up.
- That's right.
- My nickname is...
Web novel Missionary.
Web novels are entertaining,
so I ask people to read them.
Do you know what the biggest setback is?
Let's say you enter a web novel platform...
and go through the bestsellers.
Then the titles stand out first.
- That's right.
- Yes.
They turned quite descriptive.
- Yes. The titles are descriptive.
- They're long.
They're long.
Do you know what the biggest trend is?
It involves hiding.
"The Protagonist Hides His Power."
Is that a title?
"The Genius Actor Hides His Charisma."
"The Genius Batter Hides the Fastballs."
- That's right.
- That way...
- Are those the titles?
- I didn't make them up.
They're the actual titles of famous web novels.
- Really?
- If you look up "Hide,"
hundreds of web novels will pop up.
- Really?
- Characters keep hiding things.
- They hide things.
- I see that there are trends.
There are such trends.
"Leveling Up Alone."
- Many characters do things alone.
- There are many such web novels.
"Monopolizing the Lucky Coincidences Alone."
- They do things alone.
- Many characters go back in time.
Many web novels involve going back in time.
So people take one look at the titles and go,
"Nak Jun told me to read them, but they don't look interesting."
Then they close the platform.
Since there are such misunderstandings,
I want to explain to you...
why the titles became that way.
In Korea, authors usually write novels...
by making a literary debut...
on the Spring Literary Contest.
They usually need permission from the literary circles.
That system has a strength.
The works become high-quality.
- Then what's a weakness?
- They're selected works.
The works reflect the tastes of the literary circles.
They might be different from what the public wants.
But web novels don't have such a system.
I went, "Shall I begin writing?" I wrote a web novel that way.
Since there are no limitations,
so many novels get published.
Because of that, it's really hard to survive.
It's especially true now.
Newbies need to compete against me,
TV writers,
- and screenwriters.
- You're right.
That's what you face when you write for the first time.
Let's say Ho Dong writes a web novel about a ssireum athlete...
- who travels back in time...
- "Ssireum Athlete Alone."
titled "Shoulder Throwing Alone."
- "Shoulder Throwing Alone." - No one else can use the technique.
- He's the only one.
- No one else can do it.
"The Ssireum Athlete Hides His Outer Reaping Throw Skills."
That's a good title.
"Seo Jang Hoon Hides His Dunking Skills."
- It'll be a novel about a sport.
- Yes.
But no one will read it.
That was why intuitive titles became popular.
If the protagonist is hiding his strength,
you can predict the overall plot.
The very strong protagonist is hiding his strength.
Then what will happen in the future?
The readers can predict the answers. Let me give you an example.
If it's a web novel about Ho Dong transferring to a new school,
the title will be "Ho Dong Hides His Strength."
In his previous school,
Ho Dong was the boss.
He was the boss of the region.
- He was the strongest.
- And he hides his strength?
- He beat everyone.
- How will he hide his strength?
But his parents told him,
"You can't live this way."
"In your next school,"
"you should live as an upright student."
It sounds fun already.
(The intro is intriguing.)
- Thus, - Blossoming Blade High School.
he hides his strength in order to be a good person.
Ho Dong, can you open your eyes as a good person would?
- Hello.
- How scary!
My goodness.
Soo Geun is sitting behind him, right?
He doesn't know that Ho Dong is hiding his strength.
So he throws eraser dust at Ho Dong.
I can't see because of you.
He goes, "Hey, what are you doing?"
- He trips Ho Dong.
- That's the usual pattern.
- That's right.
- So...
- He picks on him.
- That's...
- Sang Min, punch him. That's it.
- It's scary.
- He won't be able to hide it.
(He can only take so much.)
- My goodness.
- The title...
- Please suppress yourself.
- Stop it.
- Listen.
- Ho Dong.
We should change the title.
"Ho Dong Hides His Strength, But Everyone Knows."
There's such a title.
The title can be "Ho Dong Doesn't Hide His Strength."
But if he hides his strength, it leads to a certain expectation.
The readers have already witnessed Ho Dong's strength in Episode One.
If Soo Geun torments Ho Dong,
what will they look forward to?
"Soo Geun will die."
- Ho Dong...
- It's cathartic.
- Ho Dong's rebellion.
(That's what we want!)
"Soon, he'll get beaten up really badly."
Then Soo Geun gets beaten up.
But Ho Dong remembers his parents' words.
"I should've hidden my strength. Why did I beat him up?"
At that moment, a delinquent senior student comes.
Ho Dong can't let him know that he beat up Soo Geun.
So he switches places with Soo Geun...
and puts a cigarette in his hand.
"Act like you're tormenting me."
Then the senior student comes and harasses Ho Dong again.
What will the readers think?
The part in which Ho Dong beat up Soo Geun was fun.
- The next target is up.
- The senior student.
- "He'll get beaten up now."
- That's the expectation.
- Yes.
- Senior Shin Dong.
That way, Senior Sin Dong and Jang Hoon get beaten up.
- One at a time.
- So the act of hiding...
- brings a set of expectations.
- Right.
- It's fun.
- If the title contains the word,
- It's fun already.
- people look forward to that fun.
- The boss becomes stronger.
- You should write it.
People have expectations...
- when they begin reading.
- I see.
Let's think about Luo Guanzhong's "Romance of the Three Kingdoms."
- Has anyone not read it?
- I bet everyone read it.
- Many people read it.
- Everyone enjoyed it, right?
Everyone in our generation enjoyed it.
- Let's say the novel came out...
- Guan Yu, Zhang Fei, Liu Bei.
- amidst the sea of titles...
- Dong Zhuo.
about hiding and not hiding strength.
Then who would choose to read "Romance of the Three Kingdoms?"
- It needs a new title.
- When you actually read it,
the novel by Luo Guanzhong is fun.
- But the title isn't intriguing.
- You're right.
Had Luo Guanzhong been born now,
he should've picked a title such as,
"The Mat Seller Hides His Bloodline."
Liu Bei hid his bloodline as a royal member...
- when he was a mat seller.
- That's right.
- That title is intriguing.
- "Is the mat seller a royal?" - A mat seller.
"Is that why he's hiding his bloodline?"
- Lee Mal Nyeon's version.
- It makes you curious.
- It gives you expectations.
- That's right.
That's the power of hiding.
Web novel writers don't work haphazardly.
- That's right.
- The competition is fierce.
We sell ten-cent episodes...
- to make a living.
- Ten cents.
- Cookies.
- We need to write well.
- We buy episodes with Cookies.
- Much thought goes into the titles.
You're spot on.
This show's writer, Hwang Seon Yeong is hiding something.
She's hiding Yeong Cheol.
- "Yeong Cheol Hides His Ad-libs." - She plans to use him later.
- She has hidden him for ten years.
- Ad-libs.
"Sang Min Hides His Debt."
That's right. That's a good example.
Everyone in here can be described with such a title.
"Min Kyung Hoon Hides His Wife."
For goodness' sake.
- "His Marital Status." - I shouldn't hide her.
- "His Marital Status." - "Kyung Hoon Hides..."
"His Marital Status."
- Has he ever hidden it?
- That sounds fun.
- He shouldn't hide it.
- I want to read it.
Earlier, you said that all web novels were...
- about going back in time.
- That's right. It's a trendy theme.
Do you know what that theme is about?
What is it about?
- Returning.
- Going back.
- Many webcomics and web novels.
Let's say that I die.
I go back in time.
Why does this theme get used in web novels?
Why does it get used so often?
- It's a fun theme.
- Regret or repentence?
Regret. That's right.
When do we want to go back in time?
- It's a chance to live again.
- Bitcoin.
- It's when we have regrets.
"I should've bought Bitcoin."
"I should've sold Bitcoin yesterday."
That's when you want to go back.
"Reborn Rich" was the same.
- That's right.
- The webcomic had that theme.
- You know, - Was it based on webcomics?
the character goes back...
to the time when he or she was at the lowest point.
- That's right.
- It isn't fun...
if the situation isn't the most wretched.
Otherwise, going back would be pointless.
So what's nice about using this theme?
The moment this character goes back,
the reason of death in the previous life...
- become the goal in the novel.
- That's right.
In "Reborn Rich," the protagonist was killed by a rich family.
So what became his goal?
It became his goal...
to take over the rich family for revenge.
It's very convenient for a writer.
The work doesn't waver.
Often, novice writers get confused...
because they want to write about this and that.
But the moment the protagonist goes back in time,
- the goal becomes clear.
- You have to go in that direction.
So you go in that direction.
Nak Jun, if you write a novel about going back in time,
you should partner up with me among everyone in this room.
- What?
- You?
- He's possessed. I'm sorry.
- He's possessed.
Sang Min's life fits the theme.
- Everything can be a material.
- That's right.
- Yes.
- A material for a novel.
- How interesting.
- I see.
There's another one. It's possession.
- Possession.
It's very popular. Many characters possess another one's body.
- The bodies get switched.
- "Ghost..." - They possess another one's body.
- "Ghost Doctor." - Yes.
It's very popular. In web novels, it connects to the title.
"Hikaru's Go."
"A Rich Family's Troublemaker."
"A Martial Arts Family's Troublemaker."
There are many such titles.
- Many characters are troublemakers.
- Troublemakers.
What's nice about possessing a troublemaker's body?
in Episode One, the protagonist leads a normal and diligent life.
- That's right.
- Then...
you end up taking over a troublemaker's body.
That's right. A bully or garbage.
After the possession,
people praise you for getting up...
early in the morning.
- That's right.
- "Nak Jun woke up in the morning!"
"What's up with that troublemaker?"
A servant brings you water...
and you don't hit him.
Not hitting people is the norm, right?
- That's right.
- It goes without saying.
But when you don't hit a servant,
he goes, "Young Master didn't hit me today."
"I think he has changed."
Koreans grow up without receiving much praise.
Teachers and parents don't give much praise.
- That's right.
- They're stingy with praise.
- If the protagonist gets praised...
- They always point out the flaws.
It's sad because the readers really like that.
People who didn't receive praise...
- live vicariously through it.
- That's right.
In a web novel about a troublemaker, it's easy to praise the protagonist.
So that's one template.
That's right. Then they turn over a new leaf.
Before I heard his explanation,
I thought that writing was hard.
But I realized that it was a genre anyone could attempt...
- with hard work.
- It's hard, but you can do it...
if you learn the rules.
- I see.
- But you guys...
should focus on your main job.
- Just read the popular ones.
- Purchase Cookies...
- and read my web novels.
- Let's purchase Cookies.
So Nak Jun is like...
the modern-day Guiyeoni.
- That's right.
- You're right.
- He has that vibe.
- "Do Re Mi Fa So La Ti Do."
- "Temptation of Wolves." - Guiyeoni.
I want to try writing it.
"Ho Dong Hides His Outer Reaping Throw Skills."
"Outer Reaping Throwing Alone."
- It'll be so fun.
- "Ho Dong Hides Lee Soo Geun."
- It'll be a ssireum drama.
- When such things didn't exist...
- "Ho Dong Hides the Satba." - Soo Geun might torment me.
That's right. It'll be a web novel about going back in time.
- My goodness.
- It was entertaining.
(The 2nd Guiyeoni, Nak Jun's presentation was helpful.)
- It was fun.
- Seriously.
My mind changes with his lecture.
Now, a doctor is up again.
It's a doctor again.
- What? It's Oh Seung Jin.
- What you receive...
I'm Oh Seung Jin.
I'll use this time...
to analyze...
the members of Men on a Mission.
- That sounds fun.
- Sometimes...
- Members?
- There's a company I know.
This company...
examines and analyzes the members of another company...
to see if they suit the organization...
and find out what their core values are.
As for the members of Men on a Mission,
which values do they think are important?
The key of a psychiatric treatment...
is knowing the state you're in.
That's the key.
The writers of the show told me...
that the members didn't believe in MBTI.
- We believe in horoscopes.
- So I heard.
- Blood types.
- Right.
With such information in mind,
I came up with an analysis on each member...
- even though it might be lacking.
- Tell us what you saw.
- Please go ahead.
- It'll be fun.
I'll start...
with the core values the members think are important.
Ho Dong comes first.
Ho Dong is the leader of the team.
- He has so much energy.
- He's the boss.
Even though he has been in the show business for many years,
his energy has remained the same.
(Ho Dong has been responsible...)
(for the Brother School's energy for 10 years.)
Ho Dong is an achievement-oriented person.
He wants to make sure the show has a certain level of quality...
- because he feels responsible.
- I feel responsible.
Every person has a room...
- for improvement, right?
- Yes.
What Ho Dong should work on is this.
He's very controlling.
- So...
- He's like a communist.
That's right. He wants the members...
to go along with his program.
That's why he scolds...
and nags at the members.
(Do something! Don't just sit there!)
(I'm sorry.)
(Ho Dong doesn't hesitate to scold someone for teamwork.)
I value teamwork.
- You value teamwork.
- Harmony that comes from teamwork.
But it's your idea of teamwork.
- Others might disagree.
- That's right!
- It's your idea of teamwork.
- People are beginning to talk.
- It's what you think.
- We might be different.
- That's right.
It'll be nice to improve yourself on that matter.
Soo Geun was born to be an entertainer.
- That's right.
- Soo Geun.
- He has quick ad-libs and wits.
- That's right.
He adjusts the vibe of the show.
Because he has worked alongside Ho Dong for many years,
they have incredible teamwork.
He plays the role of a sidekick very well.
- It's a must.
- A sidekick.
This is what he needs to improve on.
He isn't very interested in what other people have to say.
- He...
- He's spot on.
- Seriously.
- Oh Seung Jin.
- You're a great doctor.
- You're the best.
- How do you know so well?
- Really?
- He's a great doctor.
- What a great doctor.
- Didn't he listen to Jang Hoon...
- before coming here?
- No.
- He only focuses on his punchline.
- That's right.
He doesn't listen to people when they're talking.
He thinks about the ad-libs he'll say later on.
He's doodling while listening to this great lecture.
(Soo Geun is a doodle artist.)
Although he has an incredible talent,
he should be more interested in other people...
so that he can receive more love and applause.
Then he won't be a sidekick. He could take Ho Dong's position.
(Two men's game of throne)
- Listen.
- I had this thought about Soo Geun.
"Does he volunteer to be a sidekick..."
"because he doesn't want to steal Ho Dong's position?"
- Is it loyalty?
- Ho Dong crushed me...
in my younger days.
- I see.
- That's why he can't grow.
- Ho Dong did that.
- Seriously.
That makes sense.
I need to make that energy flow again.
Ho Dong crushed him.
Ho Dong did a thorough job...
- on "2 Days 1 Night." - A thorough job.
Make sure you don't pay attention to other people!
Just be funny by yourself!
Focus on yourself!
- "Think only about yourself." - Understood?
He crushed Soo Geun.
Jin Seung doesn't seem like a psychiatrist, but a shaman.
Seriously.
- As for Jang Hoon, - Jang Hoon.
he's a nagger.
He's straightforward and cynical.
(His cynical way of thinking even led to a catchphrase.)
But when he gives relationship advice,
he notices what other people miss because of emotions.
He's someone who makes people face those problems.
(You should say things as they are!)
(You're the type who talks a lot about the things...)
(you don't need to talk about.)
He's indifferent about most of the things.
I think it's a bit of a defense mechanism.
If he gets too close to someone...
and takes in all the emotions,
his feelings will get hurt.
So he pretends not to feel anything.
- He's soft-hearted.
He's someone who always cries at home.
He's like that.
I thought it was raining, but Jang Hoon was crying.
His tears fell on me directly.
The pool of his tears came up to Soo Geun's ankles.
- He's soft-hearted.
- Yes.
It might be unexpected, but he has a soft spot.
When the production crew or writers ask him to do something,
- he'll complain and mumble a lot.
- He does that a lot.
- But he'll oblige in the end.
- That's right.
He complains a lot.
But when a TV writer or someone gets married,
he gives a lot of money as a wedding gift.
- He gives 100,000 dollars.
- Say such things more often.
(Say such things more often.)
You don't want me to stop.
- Often.
- Do it more often.
- If you listen to Jang Hoon,
he'll appear as someone who has no care for how the others see him.
But when people praise him or share stories of his good deed,
he loves it.
- That's right.
- Yes.
- He's soft-hearted.
- He loves it.
You're spot on.
Shin Dong is last.
In a sense, he's the perfect character.
- He makes a full hexagon.
- A hexagon.
His body is shaped like a hexagon.
(His body is shaped like a hexagon.)
He's good...
- at dance and music.
- Yes.
With his chubby body and funny facial expressions,
- he does slapstick comedy.
- Slapstick comedy.
His skills make up a hexagon.
But that hexagon is a bit small.
Hold on. Is he a psychiatrist?
- Seriously.
- Isn't he a shaman?
(Dr. Oh curses the members without hesitation.)
- Is he analyzing our tendencies...
- Seriously.
- or critiquing the variety show?
- I mean...
But the hexagon can become bigger.
- That man...
- Seriously.
He had a traumatic experience on JTBC.
- All right.
- But he's sitting here.
- He's so...
- He isn't small.
Anyone can see that he's big.
Jack of all trades,
- master of none?
- No.
- He's so...
- He isn't small.
Anyone can see that he's big.
Jack of all trades,
- master of none?
- No.
He's good at most of the things.
But when people think of Shin Dong,
nothing comes to mind. He isn't at that level yet.
He's so... Hold on.
- There are people...
- He's like...
- who do things better.
- Lim Jin Mo.
Oh Jin Mo. Oh Dong Jin. Oh Pyeong Sik.
(Channeling Critic Lim Jin Mo)
- That was fun.
- Thus,
these members have various tendencies.
I think that's why...
Men on a Mission has survived...
- to this day since 2015.
- It's been 10 years.
You guys should examine each other more...
and think, "How can I help him?"
I had that thought,
so I prepared this presentation.
(Examine each other and offer appropriate help.)
It helped a lot.
Please give a round of applause...
to the transfer students who gave nice presentations.
- All right.
- Tell us how the experience was.
Visiting this show with "Doctor Friends" members was...
- something I had never imagined.
- Right.
It was so fun to meet the members in real life.
I was able to get over the traumatic experience...
I had on JTBC today.
- You got over it.
- You totally got over it.
It was nice to be called Jin Seung, not Seung Jin.
We never thought that we'd visit...
- a variety show together.
- Seriously.
- But we suddenly got invited.
- I know.
We thought it'd be the first and last time.
Everyone was nice to us, so we had a lot of time.
- It was nice meeting everyone.
- Yes.
Okay. "Doctor Friends" forever!
(The preview of next week's episode will be revealed soon.)
(SUNYE, Jo Kwon, Song Ga In, Kwun Hyuk Soo)
(Jo Kwon and SUNYE are best friends who go back 25 years.)
Even when I was young...
(The two friends overcame the time of hardship together.)
(SUNYE's family was staggering too.)
(The strange way of thinking makes him stagger.)
(The other pair becomes quiet due to the lack of stories.)
(As Ga In listened to the stories, she became anxious.)
(I wanted to visit the show with my real friend, Yoo Hee Kwan.)
(But he was more suitable for the show.)
(You guys should've planned things.)
(That was why we met up yesterday.)
(They became best friends for the episode.)
(Have you guys met outside of work?)
(We meet at the karaoke.)
(We'll prove our friendship through a duet performance.)
(The best friends of 25 years take the stage.)
(Flippant Kwon still has it.)
(The best friends reveal the top secrets.)
(Stories that have been buried for 25 years)
Please reveal the answers.
Let's see the answer.
(What kind of a show...)
(was "Star King?")
Seriously.
(To his crush,)
(Hyuk Soo even did "Blank.")
(They expose each other without prior agreement.)
(They come close to ending the friendship.)
(I pray that we won't fight.)
(I pray that we'll become closer through the Best Friends Special.)
(The lively best friends will visit the show.)
Dramaday.me
(Men on a Mission)