(A blistering July day)
- No, you're totally mistaken!
- I'm right about it.
No, you're wrong about it.
- Gosh, this is frustrating.
Listen to me.
To be honest, I look better in person.
I look much bigger on the screen.
That's why I look better in person.
That's what I think, but Ho Dong disagrees.
I believe everyone looks better on the screen.
Just like Jang Hoon.
He looks like a total wreck in person.
It's a total mess.
But he has grown on me over time. Now, on the screen,
- he even looks charming.
- But...
Yeong Cheol, what do people say about you?
Do they say you look better in person or on the screen?
He looks better on the screen.
Everyone gets surprised when they first see me in person.
- Let's change the subject.
- Seriously...
- We shouldn't change the subject.
- I don't want to hear that.
Are we looking at you on the screen right now?
On the screen, I look...
Aren't we looking at him in person?
- No, he's on the screen.
- Is that so?
- You see...
- If you look at your smartphone...
We are i-dle, and we look pretty both on screen and in person.
- Oh, my goodness.
- Hi!
(i-dle, with their top-tier beauty, are here.)
Welcome!
- They're really pretty.
- Indeed.
(The excitement level goes up.)
(i-dle is back to take over Brother School again this year.)
- Hi.
Hi, everyone.
We're from We Want More Love High School.
I'm Nicha Yontararak also known as MINNIE.
I'm Princess MIYEON.
She introduced herself as a princess.
- Hold on, SOYEON.
- She's at it again.
- SOYEON, why are you so surprised?
- I'm sorry. Was it your turn?
That's not it. Today, I want to be the princess.
I'm Princess SOYEON.
- All right.
- They have the same concept.
- Let's both be princesses.
- That's right.
- We're princess sisters.
- You're royal sisters.
I am... Well, there's no need to explain myself.
I'm Superstar YUQI.
- YUQI!
- Okay.
I am SHUHUA because I'm pretty.
That's even more intense than being a princess.
- She's SHUHUA because she's pretty.
- It's a battle of the princesses!
- You're at war against one another.
- That's unbelievable.
Actually, i-dle came on this show many times before.
- That's right.
- Yes, we did.
They make their comeback just to be on this show, apparently.
Oh, I see.
Just to transfer to this school.
- Just to be here?
- That's right.
- They prepare for their comeback...
- No way.
- before they're invited here.
- My goodness.
- What do you like so much about us?
- They're honest.
Firstly, I'm going to turn 30 next year.
- Oh, my.
- I like being here...
because I get to wear a school uniform.
- She's right.
- I agree.
- That's right.
- What about you, MIYEON?
I like being here because of Ho Dong.
- As if it were strictly business.
- Exactly.
- What was that?
- I heard that clearly.
- Ho Dong...
- I'm sorry. I admit it.
- I was taken aback...
- She said, "because of Ho Dong."
because Ho Dong suddenly talked to me.
- Oh, is that the case?
- I'm sorry.
I believe you don't need a reason to like something.
(Her words impressed everyone.)
- It's a great comment.
- It's awesome.
There's no need to explain.
You just need to understand one thing.
- She speaks fluent Korean.
- That we love this show.
You guys came back here after a year.
- That's right.
- Don't they seem different?
- Exactly.
- Their vibes...
- I have something to tell you.
- Take a guess.
- What has changed about us?
- MIYEON, what is it?
- Shin Young.
- Yes?
- I used to be in your position.
- Oh, that's right.
- That's right.
(8 months ago, she appeared, giving off her refreshing vibe.)
(The queen bee at Brother School)
(MIYEON secured the front seat back then.)
(MIYEON's presence can still be felt in the front seat.)
Oh, right. MIYEON was sitting there.
- I used to sit where you are now.
- Oh, I see.
But I'm sorry to disappoint you.
This is my seat now.
- Things have changed. I'm sorry.
- She's so cool.
- How did it happen?
- It is what it is.
Why don't the other members...
tell them the benefits of having me on the show?
That's difficult.
- Hey, Soo Geun.
- He says it's difficult.
- Soo Geun, are you being serious?
- Didn't I do a good job?
Why is it difficult?
- SHUHUA, - Wait, Ho Dong.
what do you like about Men on a Mission?
- Ho Dong.
- Yes?
Get it together.
I really didn't want to use force this time.
- I was desperate.
- You scared me.
- You deserved it.
- You have no seat now.
- Shin Young.
- Shin Young, come here.
- I'll show you what happens now.
- Come here.
- Come join us.
- Hi. I'm Princess Shin Young.
- They look great together.
- It's the first time...
a girl group has been on the show with their manager.
- What did you say?
- It's unusual.
Why would you say I'm their manager?
This is "Omniscient Interfering View."
- "Omniscient Interfering View?"
- How could you say that?
- That makes sense.
- "Omniscient Interfering View?"
- Put a name tag on your chest.
- That's hilarious.
(Shin Young looks more like a manager than an idol singer.)
My gosh.
MIYEON, when Shin Young came here as a guest,
- She really showed off her talent.
- Really?
She showed off all kinds of unique skills.
So she was cast unanimously.
- That's right.
- MIYEON...
MIYEON, can you do an impression of Lee Gye In?
- Can you show me first?
- She can absolutely do it.
Hello.
I am Princess MIYEON of i-dle.
- Can you do it?
- I'll give it a try.
- Hello.
- Good.
I am Princess MIYEON...
of i-dle.
- That was perfect.
- MIYEON...
- MIYEON did a perfect job.
- You did a perfect job.
- I want that seat.
- MIYEON did a perfect job.
- Let's put it to a vote again.
- MIYEON did great.
- Jang Hoon also thinks she did...
- She did a perfect job.
- Jang Hoon... My gosh.
- I vote for MIYEON.
- Can you do anything else?
- Show us something else.
Is there anything you can show us?
(Walking rhythmically)
- Soo Geun.
- Yes?
Let's do our best as always.
(Let's do our best as always. Yes, yes, yes.)
You desperately pushed that catchphrase before.
(In Episode 483, MIYEON's cute act turned the class upside down.)
(Yes, yes, yes.)
(MIYEON's cute act drew jeers from the other members.)
(MIYEON, you're almost 30.)
(She pushed that catchphrase once again.)
Ho Dong.
Let's do our best.
- Let's do our best.
- She did the same thing last time.
MIYEON created this dance move.
- It's hard to copy that dance move.
- MIYEON created it?
- You did well.
- SOYEON also...
- Whenever you look in the mirror...
- You should do it.
Let's do our best.
I'll be off.
What are you doing?
(She returns after turning the classroom upside down.)
She's incredible.
You have strong joints.
- Indeed.
- I still have strong joints.
The transfer form to Men on a Mission.
Names, MIYEON, MINNIE, SOYEON, YUQI, and SHUHUA!
- Welcome!
- Welcome.
- They came here many times before.
- That's right.
Our five guests wrote down their nicknames.
First up is SOYEON.
This nickname sounds legit. It's Jeon So Bal.
- Right.
- That sounds legit.
People would call you, "Hey, So Bal."
- Yes, that's right.
- "Hey, Jeon So Bal."
I got a lot of nicknames...
- after I made my debut.
- That's right.
There are many cute nicknames, and I like all my nicknames.
But "So Bal" is the nickname given by my friends...
- back in elementary school.
- Right.
- So I wrote that nickname.
- It's an authentic nickname.
- Please call me So Bal.
- So Bal.
- "Hey, So Bal." Like this?
- I hear SOYEON has an alias.
- She has an alias?
- One for songwriting.
- What is it?
- It's your new persona.
- It's icebluerabbit.
She went by her alias.
- She's genuinely surprised.
- Icebluerabbit?
- Isn't it her songwriter alias?
- A blue rabbit?
- Exactly.
- That's correct.
- We released "Mono" before this.
- That's right.
It's my first producer alias that I used when I wrote "Mono."
Right. It's her alias as a music producer.
(SOYEON hid her identity while working as a songwriter.)
Here's the thing.
While making and producing i-dle's songs,
I felt the desire to try something new as a music producer.
But I felt like I was stuck in a box because of my name SOYEON.
So I combined the words I hated to make my alias.
- What? The words you hated?
- The words you hated?
I mean, I'm more like a hot girl.
- I'm a hot girl.
- Yes.
- And...
- "Blue."
I look better in red or yellow than in blue.
I think I have warm-tone skin.
- Because you have warm-tone skin?
- Yes. And...
I look a little bit like a cat or a puppy.
- She does look like a cat.
- Yes.
I don't think I have a rabbit face.
You chose the opposite words.
I combined all the opposite words to describe myself,
and that's how I came up with the name icebluerabbit.
- She went for an opposite concept.
- It's the complete opposite...
- of your image.
- Correct.
You want to create music that's the opposite of you.
- Exactly.
- Right.
I see.
(SOYEON's new persona icebluerabbit will show a different side of her.)
As far as I know,
before settling on the name i-dle,
there were some other names...
- you had to choose from.
- That's right.
We had another name to consider, which was "Anicolor."
- "Anicolor?"
- Anicolor.
It's a compound word of "animal..."
- "Ani" as in "animal?"
- Yes.
- And "color."
- It's a 4-syllable word.
- Right, it's a 4-syllable word.
There was a superstition...
that a girl group with a four-syllable name...
- always becomes a big hit.
- It always becomes a big hit.
- Just like BLACKPINK?
- TWICE.
- Red Velvet.
- Apink.
- So our agency...
gathered ideas for a four-syllable name.
Did you come up with your stage names as well?
Yes, each of us had a stage name.
- What? Really?
- As the members of Anicolor?
My stage name was Pink Mouse.
- "Pink Mouse?"
- Mine was...
- That was your stage name?
- Oh, boy.
- That was my stage name.
- I see.
Mine was Green Crocodile.
- My gosh. You guys...
- "Green Crocodile?"
- It would've been a disaster.
- That's how much she liked it.
Exactly.
- We thought we needed...
- "Pink Mouse."
- to draw attention.
- We wanted to draw attention.
- Those are cute names, though.
- You were looking for names...
that combines an animal and a color.
My stage name also had four syllables.
It was Yellow Seahorse.
- "Yellow Seahorse?"
- A seahorse is also...
- A seahorse is also unusual.
- That's right.
- Yes.
Ours were quite good. Mine was "Blue Sky."
- "Blue Sky" sounds good.
- Yes.
- But sky is not an animal.
- It's not an animal.
- MIYEON's was "Green Crocodile."
- Oh, that's right.
- Why "Blue Sky?"
- "Blue Sky" sounds so different.
- Oh, that's right.
- Those are such different names.
I'm the only one whose stage name wasn't an animal.
- What about you, SHUHUA?
- SHUHUA, what was your stage?
- Mine was "White Butterfly."
- Right.
- "White Butterfly" isn't bad.
- "White Butterfly."
- These two had such good names.
- Exactly.
- Seahorse, crocodile, and mouse...
- And mouse.
- Well, but...
- Whose idea was it, SOYEON?
- The former director at the agency.
- Right, the former director.
- Does that person still work there?
- He left the company after that...
- No, the director left the company.
- Because of that...
He left the company because of that.
- They always leave a legacy.
- So it was his idea.
- I bet he quit because of that.
- I heard he was demoted...
- just because of that suggestion.
- Because of that...
I mean, "Green Crocodile" is not cool.
- Exactly.
- Let's move on.
- SOYEON's nickname is Jeon So Bal.
- It's a relief.
And MIYEON's nickname is Princess Noodle.
- "Princess Noodle?"
- Noodle.
- "MIYEON" sounds similar to noodle.
- You like noodles?
It's because she loves noodles.
Do you like ramyeon? How many servings do you eat at once?
- I usually eat two servings.
- That's not bad.
- Right. I don't really...
- Hold on, MIYEON.
Do you mean you cook two servings at the same time?
No, I cook another serving after finishing the first one.
- But you don't look like...
- That would be better.
you could eat two servings.
- You're so skinny.
- I'm jealous of her for that.
- It's because MIYEON...
- I eat more than I look like I do.
- She doesn't gain weight easily.
- I've seen it.
Instead, I move around a lot.
Soo Geun!
You seemed so active, with all that jumping.
- You move around after eating.
- That's right.
- That makes her different from me.
- She moves around a lot.
I heard MIYEON's princess syndrome got worse.
- Who are you talking about?
- You, MIYEON.
- That's not true.
- You compliment yourself...
whenever you look in the mirror, apparently.
- Really?
- Is that true?
- It didn't get worse.
- MIYEON, every morning,
when you wash up and look in the mirror,
- it makes you happy, right?
- Yes.
I'm not sure if it's because of my appearance,
- Yes?
- but I'm always in a good mood.
But we...
avoid looking in the mirror...
- because it ruins our vibes.
- But makeup...
- Why?
- Not me.
- I like the way I look.
- I avoid looking in the mirror.
Hey, you...
- I'm quite satisfied with my looks.
- Really?
- It's not bad.
- Right, it's not bad.
- If you...
- I just wish my face was shorter.
- Your skin feels smooth.
- If you say so, I won't argue.
(He respects Yeong Cheol's self-love.)
The mirror gets foggy,
- which makes you look prettier.
- It makes things look a bit blurry.
- Exactly.
- What do you say to yourself?
First, I put on a pretty face.
I see.
(Her pretty poses are totally justified.)
I bet it helps you start your day in a good mood.
Yes. That's how I start my day.
- Self-compliments are good for you.
- Indeed.
Have you guys seen MIYEON talking to herself in the mirror?
- Have we seen MIYEON doing that?
- I've seen her doing that.
- You saw it? What was she doing?
- Yes.
After getting makeup done,
she was like, "I look pretty."
- Really?
- So...
- Watching her doing so, I thought, - Hold on.
- Yes?
- "Are there cameras here?"
"Are there cameras here?"
- But there were no cameras there.
- She complimented herself...
- even when she wasn't on camera?
- She was just talking to herself.
- I don't do that on camera.
- "I look pretty."
- Really?
- I do it just for myself.
It's actually to boost my self-esteem.
- Right.
- That's a healthy habit.
- I can't do it when I'm on camera.
- Really?
You see, I was watching SHUHUA.
With her arms crossed like this,
she was quietly observing MIYEON.
I don't really care. I just...
- Whatever those below you do.
- I don't look in the mirror...
I just... Yes. I'm number one.
I'm number one.
(The pretty SHUHUA just dropped a bombshell statement.)
- "I'm number one."
- "I am the queen."
- I am number one.
- Hey!
- She's the queen.
- I think I'm the prettiest too.
MIYEON's self-esteem...
- needs to go even higher.
- Exactly.
- Where is my mirror? Where is it?
- Right.
Ho Dong, do you also think...
- your appearance is number one?
- He's very happy with his looks.
- Yes.
- He's totally happy with his looks.
- He's worried he might lose weight.
- But we have Kyung Hoon.
- He's worried so much. Right.
- He's lost a lot of weight.
I won't say I'm number one, but I honestly think I'm up there.
I think I'm up there too.
(Brother School Appearance Tiers: Top, Middle, Bottom)
He looks like he'll live a long, stress-free life.
- Those with that mindset...
- He looks like he'll live to 150.
usually live a long, healthy life.
- I mean, it's because...
- He's a narcissist.
It's because I've grown fond of myself...
- Of course.
- after watching myself for so long.
- He gets cuter over time.
- He's so modest.
- I've grown attached to my face.
- Right.
That's true.
It's fascinating.
That you've grown attached to yourself.
- It's because he's old.
- Right.
- He has no one else to rely on.
- You're too young to know that.
- MIYEON, haven't you...
- You're still too young...
- to get attached to yourself.
- Right? I've never thought of that.
- You'll know when you're his age.
- You should be at least 50.
MIYEON, haven't you grown attached to yourself?
- I've never thought that way.
- Right?
I'm also... How should I put it?
I'm happy with my appearance.
- Because he's on the older side.
- He sounds confident.
- He's grown attached to himself.
- Everyone over 50 feels that way.
- Right.
- Try looking in the mirror often.
- It helps to feel more confident...
- He must look in the mirror often.
(Uncle Sang Min looked in the mirror as often as possible.)
- I think I'll live a long life too.
- We have so many weirdos here.
Kyung Hoon, what do you think when you look in the mirror?
- Nothing.
- I'm jealous.
- I only check my nose hair...
- I think nothing crosses his mind.
and pluck long nose hair. That's all.
- Handsome guys act this way.
- Right.
But these guys who aren't handsome love their looks.
- I'm satisfied with my looks.
- But I don't think...
- it's fair of you to say that.
- I mean, it's so...
What do you mean? I said I didn't look in the mirror.
- You don't look in the mirror?
- As I always say,
- I see myself very objectively.
- Really?
I learned to do it when I was little.
My parents always told me...
that I was ugly.
- For real?
- That's not true.
- But you're tall.
- He is ugly, indeed.
- MIYEON, tell us honestly.
- Okay.
- Can you be honest with us?
- Of course.
- Look at Jang Hoon. Is he ugly?
- Okay.
- No.
- Really?
- SOYEON, is he ugly?
- No.
- You guys should know...
- He's cool.
that lying can become a habit.
- YUQI, be honest with us.
- YUQI, give us your objective view.
- Is Jang Hoon incredibly handsome?
- He's quite good-looking.
- You guys will go to paradise.
- They have...
- They have warm hearts.
- We used to make that joke as kids.
- "You'll go to paradise."
- You guys will go to paradise.
- They have such warm hearts.
- Exactly.
- Right.
- You guys are old teammates.
- Yes.
Even though you've worked together for a long time,
you still don't fully get each other, do you?
We embraced our differences, though.
That's right. We've agreed...
- to disagree.
- How long has it been?
- We're okay with that.
- SOYEON, what about them...
was so hard to understand?
There's something about YUQI that always fascinates me.
- You see...
- I'm getting nervous.
(She's nervous for no reason.)
- She says it fascinates her.
- We make music for a living.
- Music is indeed part of her life.
- Right.
- That's right.
- She always brings her speaker...
to the green room.
- Her own speaker?
- Yes, she carries it everywhere.
- She plays music loudly.
- She always plays music loudly.
- Yes, I do.
- Sometimes, I pray...
that YUQI forgets her speaker.
(She dropped a shocking confession.)
- I...
- Is it that loud?
- I always think of hiding it.
- You see...
- You think of hiding her speaker?
- Yes.
(The green room footage from YUQI)
(You do play music loudly.)
(This proves that their green room is always loud with music.)
- I'm sorry, but I...
- Don't be.
I don't like being in a quiet place.
- You prefer the noise.
- It suffocates me.
I have a story about that...
that involves SHUHUA. She likes being in a quiet place.
- That's right.
- She likes a dark, quiet place.
- I like a bright, loud place.
- You two are opposites.
One time, my manager was too busy to give me a ride,
- so I rode along in SHUHUA's car.
- I see.
- Her manager didn't say a word.
- Exactly.
- Her manager didn't say a word?
- I can't stand being quiet.
I connected my phone to the car and played music.
- And I turned it up.
- You turned the volume up.
SHUHUA's manager didn't say anything about that.
But later, I heard from another manager...
that SHUHUA's manager asked my manager...
if I had hearing issues.
- Because it was too loud?
- That's hilarious.
- You blasted it too loud.
- It was too loud.
- He thought I couldn't hear.
- Elderly people play music loudly.
- Yes, it rings in your ears.
- Perhaps you developed some issues.
- I love cranked bass.
- Maybe she has a lot of earwax.
- I don't know.
- Maybe she needs to clean her ears.
So I took a health check-up.
My hearing is perfect.
- Really?
- She just loves music.
- I love music.
- I've ridden in YUQI's car once.
- YUQI's car?
She and I were sitting in the backseats.
And I saw a huge mirror on the back of the front seat.
- A huge mirror?
- Really?
It was attached to the front seat back.
It was too much for me...
- to keep looking at my own face.
- You had to stare at it.
That's right.
- I really like...
- I can't ride along in her car.
- You love mirrors too.
- I love mirrors so much.
- It's true.
- A huge mirror?
The mirror was this big. I had no choice...
but to look at myself the whole way.
I have a large mirror in my car.
- Why? What do you do with that?
- You have a mirror in your car...
- and play music loudly.
- Doesn't it have lighting too?
There is lighting in the car too.
- In the car?
- It's true.
- It's like she's on stage.
- It's fascinating.
- It's cool.
- That's what happened.
Since we're talking about YUQI, let's check out her nickname.
Just as she said earlier, her nickname is Superstar.
- You want to become a superstar?
- I want to become a superstar.
And I always try to live like a superstar.
Then shouldn't you go solo?
I've been doing a lot of work as a solo artist.
- She released a solo album too.
- Yes, she did.
I never stop working.
I don't really like taking a break.
I think I'm that type of person.
- You're already successful, - True.
so just how much more do you want to be successful?
My ultimate goal is...
to go down in the history books.
She wants to be in a historical biography.
- Children and juniors...
- Yes?
one hundred years later would be like,
"You know, YUQI from the 21st century?"
There used to be a legendary singer...
- So in history...
- named YUQI.
- Exactly, that's what I want.
- An historical figure.
Dreaming big is amazing.
- I have a big dream.
- What's the story behind...
YUQI visiting the bank more often than TV stations?
As I'm a foreigner,
I do think managing your money is a must.
Since we pay different taxes,
there's a lot to study.
Every week...
When it was often, I went to banks twice a week.
- What did you do there?
- You're practically a bank clerk.
I'd get my business done,
ask how to manage money,
- and buy...
- Right.
- recommended bank products.
- I see.
- Like a branch manager.
- Are you also interested in ETFs,
leverage, funds, and such?
- Do you buy stocks?
- I don't.
Well, barely.
When it comes to funds, I'm quite a scaredy-cat,
- so I'm not really into them.
- Then what do you do?
I guess I simply like going to the bank.
- Aren't you going for the AC?
- VIP customers...
- Or stock futures.
- I get a lot of gifts.
She wanted to chit-chat.
- Is it to chit-chat?
- Are you bored?
- To chat with someone.
- She has no one to talk to.
- So to banks?
- My manager...
would give me gifts whenever I stopped by.
- Right.
- Like socks.
I'm offered drinks every day...
- and coffee vouchers.
- If you use NongHyup Bank,
they give you cooking oil, cabbage, and such.
- Cabbage?
- For real?
- Are you a NongHyup Bank VIP?
- Yes.
- Just how much...
VIPs get gifts every time.
- I better visit banks often.
- "Here's a gift."
- You get more the more you visit.
- Imagine...
- Organic.
- how much Sang Min...
- must've used...
- Right,
- the bank to pay off his debt.
- I paid off my debt.
I paid off my debt...
- through that bank.
- Right.
It seems like YUQI has a thing for the bank clerk.
- How strange.
- Really?
Did you promise to call him "Manager?"
While giving you socks, did he say,
- "Call me Manager..."
- Manager!
"for the time being."
Which bank is it? I'll look into it right away.
- "Okay, I'll call you Manager."
- Sorry to disappoint,
- but she's a mother with a baby.
- She's a mother.
- She likes me.
- A mother.
She treats me like a daughter.
- MINNIE.
- Yes?
Her nickname sounds like a real name.
- What is it?
- Tararak.
- Tararak? What...
My full Thai name is...
My first name is Nicha, and my last name is Yontararak.
- Yontararak.
- Yontararak is the last name.
So in Thailand,
Nicha Yontararak is a common name.
But when I introduce myself in Korea,
everyone starts calling me Tararak.
- Tararak?
- Tararak pops out.
People didn't call me MINNIE. When I was a trainee,
- the others called me Tararak.
- Tararak?
- Because it's your last name.
- Tararak.
- Since Tararak is my last name.
- Interesting.
- I heard MINNIE was famous...
- as Thailand's princess.
- Just how many princesses...
do you have?
- Let everyone be princesses.
- Princess i-dle.
- Be princesses.
- Princess special.
Apparently, your parents were shocked...
when they visited the house...
- where you stayed as a trainee.
- Right.
My dad came with me to Korea...
and visited the house for the first time.
- But he was genuinely shocked.
- Your dad?
"My daughter?"
"Here? Really?"
- Your dad?
- He really said that.
- He was shocked.
- Where was your house?
The house wasn't that bad.
- No.
- It was the rooms.
MINNIE's house in Thailand is just grand.
- She lives in a castle.
- A castle?
- Relatively, okay?
- I don't.
- You live in a castle?
- For real?
- "Really? My daughter?"
- No, listen.
In Thailand,
- people live in houses.
- Houses.
That's why I hardly ever lived in apartments.
It was an apartment...
with three rooms...
but numerous trainees.
That's why the apartment looked small.
- Four to five...
- It was an old one too.
- must've shared one room.
- Exactly.
Four per room.
Did your dad return after voicing his concern?
- So my dad...
- Did he go back?
Here's what my dad told me.
I came to Korea after my junior year of high school.
"I already paid for your senior year tuition fees."
"Come back if you can't do it."
- Return whenever you want.
- If it's too tough.
Yes, since my dad had already paid the tuition fees.
- How reassuring.
- Oh, my.
My dad was extremely worried.
It was going to be her home.
Have the other members visited...
- MINNIE's house in Thailand?
- Have you?
- We have.
- How was it? Was it a castle?
- Was it a castle?
- It was really nice.
- The house even had a gym.
The house had three buildings.
- The house had three buildings?
- Three buildings?
- Yes, three separate buildings.
- Three separate buildings?
- It's literally a castle.
- Totally.
How many members does your family have?
It's a big family. Eight.
- Eight members and three houses.
- Eight?
One house is my aunt's.
The other house is for my grandparents and my parents.
The last house is for my older brother and me.
(Living in separate houses is novel.)
Our maid has a separate room.
(An antique-style living room with a high ceiling)
(There are floors above and below.)
(A secondary living room on every floor)
(A gym exclusively for MINNIE)
- Nice.
- Where's your house?
- Which city is it? Bangkok?
- Yes, Bangkok.
- Bangkok.
- May we visit your house...
if we ever go to Bangkok?
Yes, come over.
We have rooms for you to stay in.
- Wait.
- You do?
Jang Hoon, we don't have to visit her house.
I heard MINNIE's family ran...
- a resort.
- Yes, they do.
MINNIE has a resort?
Yes, my mom is currently running it.
(A historic resort in Thailand run by MINNIE's mom)
- That's...
- We should shoot a special there.
I've never been to Thailand.
I won't believe it.
I contacted Pacquiao when I went to the Philippines,
- Right?
- but he acted like a stranger.
(Cutting him off)
I also went there because of Pacquiao.
- No, she's for real.
- He promised to give me a tour.
Pacquiao will be taken aback if he watches the show.
- Pacquiao, that little...
- Stop it.
(Pacquiao, we were friends, weren't we?)
(Let's meet in the Philippines one day.)
- Enough.
- If we ever...
- shoot a Bangkok Special, - Right.
let's go to MINNIE's resort and...
- Use your own money.
- Right?
- Aren't you too wealthy...
- You're more than rich.
to go to MINNIE's resort?
- Come over.
- A couple of days in Bangkok...
won't hurt,
- Gosh.
- At first, he wanted to stay...
- at MINNIE's house, not the resort.
- Right?
- Staying at her house is wrong.
- I've had enough.
To stay in one of the rooms...
- in MINNIE's house?
- I wanted...
- It's not like you're poor.
- a tour.
What I meant was a house tour.
I didn't say anything about staying over.
Go to the real estate listings.
- It's all on YouTube.
- Exactly.
- There's no need to drop by.
- How funny.
Seeing it in person is different.
MINNIE is fine with it.
- Come over to our resort.
- Okay.
What about your house?
- My house...
- No?
There are quite a lot of people.
- True.
- How come?
Let's go to the resort since we have so many people.
Next.
SHUHUA's nickname is...
SHUHound.
- SHUHound?
- Does it have to do with that dog?
I gave her the nickname SHUHound.
Doesn't it look like Jang Hoon?
- Don't they look alike?
- The two look alike.
- No.
- I'm reminded of Jang Hoon.
That's when Jang Hoon is lying face down.
Isn't that Jang Hoon's first birthday?
- First birthday photo?
- First birthday photo.
- Both of you look like it.
- I see Jang Hoon in the dog.
If a big dog with such features shows up,
It's all you.
most of them look almost identical to me.
- It's because...
- A big dog in the countryside...
is Jang Hoon.
- Exactly.
- Right?
It's not the face that looks like SHUHUA.
- The white fur.
- Yes, it's the white fur.
- It looks like SHUHUA.
- SHUHUA,
did you never bask in...
Have you never photosynthesized in your life?
Your skin is really pale.
It's UV rays!
- People might misunderstand.
- Photosynthesis.
- That's photosynthesis.
- It's photosynthesis.
- He's right.
Ho Dong said photosynthesis because he didn't know about UV rays.
Photosynthesis is his nickname.
(In scarlet letters)
I don't like the sunlight.
- You don't?
- I hate the sunlight.
But you need a certain amount of sunlight every day.
That's why my vitamin D...
- Vitamin D?
- levels are really low.
Supplements.
- Are you taking vitamin D?
- I am.
Were you always that pale?
- Yes.
- She's always been pale.
Interesting.
- Isn't SHUHUA goofy at times?
- She is.
I heard you ran away from home,
leaving just a piece of tissue behind.
- I didn't run away from home.
- What?
- But she did leave home.
- I did leave home.
- Just after we debuted, - Yes?
we lived in different houses.
I lived with SHUHUA back then.
It's usually noisy in the mornings, but it was quiet that day.
When I left my room, I saw a piece of tissue...
- on SHUHUA's room door.
- A tissue?
Yes, she had stuck a tissue on the door.
The tissue said, "SHUHUA is traveling."
When I opened the door, nobody was in the room.
She disappeared out of nowhere,
so I gave her a call, and she was on a trip.
- Where did you go?
- Where did you go, SHUHUA?
I just took a bus without a specific destination.
- Really?
- Just anywhere?
- Why?
- Why? Were you upset?
I wasn't upset.
- For no reason?
- No.
I simply wanted to leave.
When did you return?
- When?
- In the evening?
No, it was 5pm or 6pm.
- The same day?
- That's just an outing.
- Come on. That wasn't a trip.
- How short.
- That's an outing.
- It's a picnic.
But SHUHUA barely goes out.
- To me, it was...
- She doesn't even like the sun.
You could've just told MIYEON.
Why did you leave it on a tissue?
- It sounds like a travel show.
- MIYEON was sleeping.
- Since she was sleeping.
- Since she was sleeping?
You didn't want her to get worried?
- She was being considerate.
- Gosh, how nice.
Soo Geun ran away from home when he was in middle school,
and his parents didn't know for three days.
- Really?
- Yes.
It wasn't three days. I returned after a week,
and my dad said, "Aren't you going to eat?"
- He didn't know.
- I knew it.
So I realized that my parents weren't that interested.
I hadn't been eating for six days,
- Gosh.
- and we met on the seventh day,
- Unbelievable.
- and he asked if I would eat.
- So I said, "No, I'm not eating."
- Gosh.
- A long time ago, Soo Geun was...
- That's amazing.
going to run away to Seoul from Yangpyeong...
- with his friend.
- Yes.
But when he was leaving to meet him,
- he didn't have any bus money, - That's right.
- I ran away.
- so...
- he couldn't run away...
- Actually...
- and returned home.
- To be honest,
- back in 1980, - That happens.
I almost immigrated to the US.
- Really?
- During the Team Spirit exercise,
there was this American that I knew and he asked me to come.
- Did you almost follow?
- If only I had gotten on that tank.
- A tank?
- I could have become an ARMY.
- An ARMY?
- ARMY.
I could have had lots of C-rations...
- and chocolate.
- The U.S. military.
You don't know what that is, do you?
We have those memories.
(Soo Geun's Back in the Days, Runaway Episode)
- Next question.
- That was funny.
We will look into the transfer students' recent activities.
They wrote here,
"Gimme Dat Love."
- "Gimme Dat Love."
Is that the title of your new song?
- That's right.
(The title song of their 9th mini album, "We made")
- This song is...
- Yes.
- Well, it's the summertime, - Yes.
and during the summer,
we used to release refreshing songs...
- like "Klaxon."
- Yes.
But this time, we prepared a hotter song...
- so that you can beat the heat.
- Gosh.
It's about real love.
- Totally about love?
- Yes.
Did you not have any complaints about line distribution this time?
- Vocal part distribution.
- Between you guys.
- Last time, MIYEON said that...
- You guys had...
- it was unexpected.
- lots of complaints last time.
(Honestly, I'm not happy with SOYEON's line distribution.)
(Our Thai member!)
(The two foreign members were especially dissatisfied.)
(Speechless)
(She has the most lines!)
(The team is facing a crisis.)
This can be a sensitive topic.
- Well...
- The line distribution...
This time, when we were making the title song,
I contacted SOYEON for the first time.
- Did she?
- Yes, she contacted me.
- What did she say?
- I mean...
My part was so little.
- So...
- What?
- Then you should call her.
- No, it's...
- Yes.
- It's true.
It really was my first time contacting her for that.
- What did you say?
- I thought about it all night.
- Did you?
- I listened to the song, and...
I thought to myself, "I'm a main vocalist."
"This just doesn't feel right."
So I wrote it and deleted it over and over again.
I sent her a really long message.
- Yes, it was really long.
- So...
I asked her if I could get a few more lines,
so she gave me a bit of hers.
- Really?
- She's nice.
- Really? I didn't know that.
- Instead of the others?
There was a rap-like part in the middle of the song.
It used to be a rap line when I sang it,
but I switched it to a melody...
and let her sing.
(She gave her part to MIYEON by changing it into a vocal line.)
- Last time, MINNIE said that...
- That's so nice.
she didn't have many lines,
so she was upset. Are you okay this time?
It's really great.
- Is it true?
- I didn't say anything this time.
- You didn't?
- Just me.
- Because...
Because this time, I got to sing the intro again.
- Did you?
- The intro is really important.
(The vocal tone is so unique, so it's even more memorable.)
(MINNIE's intro is a true work of art.)
(The relaxed low voice is so charming.)
- The intro is really important.
- It is.
- It's been such a long time.
- It captivates.
- That's why I didn't say anything.
- So I...
- Were you okay, - SHUHUA.
- YUQI and SHUHUA?
- Are you okay?
- I'm totally satisfied.
- SHUHUA is satisfied?
- What about YUQI? Be honest.
- Oh, yes.
- Wait.
- What? YUQI has something to say.
- YUQI has something to say.
- No, I don't.
- YUQI...
- No.
I think YUQI doesn't like having many lines.
- Right?
- No...
She has to go to the bank.
She can't practice.
- She wants to shorten the time.
- She's busy.
It's right next door.
- She has to go.
- Because...
The bank is cool during the summer.
Banks are the best place to be during the summer.
- But YUQI...
- That's right.
- Yes?
- Last time, YUQI...
- She had many things to say...
- Yes, she did.
- about her lines.
- That's right.
You didn't contact me this time.
- Are you okay this time around?
- Why not? Were you satisfied?
I'm really okay with it all, because...
I realized this.
Rather than the number of lines,
bringing that part to life...
and making it a killing part is up to me.
- That's it.
- Gosh.
And because...
The reason YUQI is this comfortable is because...
she became the first foreign idol member...
to become a full member of the Korea Music Copyright Association.
- Really?
- Shouldn't Sang Min say it?
- It's true.
- She did.
- She's the first foreigner.
- That's why she's laid back.
Full members have a lot of benefits.
That's why I'm okay here.
No wonder.
The important thing is, there's a new president now,
- so the pension has changed...
- What?
from 700 dollars to 1,000 dollars monthly.
- I mean, from 600 to 1,000 monthly.
Sang Min, I'm sorry, but do you have a role there?
- He must be the president.
- Is Sang Min a full member?
I have a question. If you are a full member,
I heard that you got gifts...
during the holidays.
- They send gifts.
- They do.
- I got fish once, - Yes.
- What?
- and even meat.
- Really?
- What?
- And...
- What? I only got seaweed.
- You only got seaweed?
- The ex-president liked seaweed.
It must have been from the new president.
- Is that so?
- The president has changed.
The president changed?
- Yes.
- That's why.
- No wonder.
- I got it this time.
- Really?
- Is he from a different place?
(A reliable source of information)
- He must be from elsewhere.
- No way.
- But if YUQI got the gifts, - Gosh.
then SOYEON should get the same gifts.
- She should...
- I didn't...
If you don't attend the regular meeting three times,
- Do you get kicked out?
- you get removed.
You need to attend them.
- I...
- Maybe you got kicked out.
- You must have gotten kicked out.
- I think you got kicked out.
I must have gotten kicked out. I only got seaweed.
Then I'm the only full member?
That must be so.
Goodness.
- She's laid back.
- SOYEON got kicked out.
- I should work hard.
- That's why YUQI didn't complain.
And there's something else that we need to congratulate them for.
So, i-dle is attending Lollapalooza,
- Lollapalooza?
- and...
they were selected as one of the teams...
- on Forbes' 30 Under 30...
- What?
- Asia 2026 list.
- Gosh.
- Let's clap.
- Among 30?
- Yes.
- It's 30 Under 30.
- Gosh.
- In Asia?
- Then do they contact you?
I saw it through the news.
- Me, too.
- Do they contact you?
- Maybe they called the office.
- They don't.
- I don't have any ties with Forbes.
- They must not do that.
- "I don't have any ties."
- I don't.
- Do you know them?
- I don't have any personal ties.
I thought that you would have been selected.
- I don't.
- I really am so grateful...
- Yes.
- for it.
It's good to be on it as an individual,
- but to be selected as a team...
- I know.
It must be an honor to be recognized as a team.
- It really is.
- It's an honor.
It's amazing. Can we perhaps see that amazing performance here?
- What?
- Yes.
- Yes, you can.
- You didn't understand, did you?
- You can see it.
- Can we see the performance?
- Yes.
- You can see it.
- Wait.
- Can you show us your performance?
- That was...
- I heard it as, - You can see it.
"Can we see that Forbes here?"
- It's right.
- Yes.
- It's a performance.
- I thought that...
- they brought the magazine.
- Yes.
Can we perhaps see that amazing performance...
- that made i-dle so influential?
- "Performance?"
- You can.
- Yes.
- Let's see it.
- Performance.
I thought he said, "Forbes."
- I heard it as "peddler."
- I'm sorry.
"Peddler?"
- Let's go.
- Good luck.
("Mono" by i-dle)
Her voice is amazing.
Gosh.
It's so cool.
It's "Crow" next.
The song is really good.
("Crow" by i-dle)
Come on.
(A powerful synchronized dance)
(They have transformed into a dark concept.)
- That was the black crow.
- This is the new song.
("Gimme Dat Love" by i-dle)
It's MINNIE.
Hey!
(i-dle gave us a deeply moving moment.)
Seriously.
Unbelievable!
(We'll give every word of praise we have.)
Give me that!
- You're really good.
- Give me that!
They wrote down...
- what they wanted to do.
- Let's go.
This is a must-do for the regular transfer students.
Guess Which One is the Lie!
We'll guess them!
It's going to be fun.
- Haven't you forgotten something?
- Forget?
We forgot it.
(Dancing right away)
What?
(Screaming)
He's off the beat.
(He just goes on with the old-school dance moves.)
- You're off the beat.
- He's off the beat.
- Okay.
- That's...
- He's good.
- Bongsan mask dance, right?
- It's i-dle's dance.
- It's that dance.
- It's Bongsan mask dance.
- He's good.
- Isn't that right?
- What do you think, SOYEON?
- Right.
- That's our teacher.
Well, he's good.
- I'm the teacher.
- You're good.
I'm the teacher. You should say it politely.
- You're good, sir.
- Anyway...
I just hate lies.
You know that, right?
From now on, they'll come forward one by one,
and share three fun facts...
- about themselves.
- Yes.
One of them will be a lie,
and those who guess well will get a gift as usual.
- Yes!
- Who wants to go first?
SOYEON!
- SOYEON.
- I'll go.
Let's go.
Sit wherever you want.
MINNIE's father is watching, right?
I'm MINNIE's deskmate.
How nice.
Hold on.
- When we go there...
- He's going as well.
We're going to Bangkok together.
(He joins wherever he can.)
We'll just stay in our rooms.
Please don't slam the door in our faces.
- Superstar.
- Remember us.
Let's have SOYEON first.
How am I going to do this? I'm not good at lying,
- but I'll give it a try.
- Okay.
- That's...
- Where...
Hey!
- Just be yourself!
- She's good!
She already lied, right?
- That's already a lie.
Why?
- I'll give it a try.
- Okay.
- Number 1.
I received a massage to get taller when I was young.
(1. I received a massage to get taller when I was young.)
- People get them.
- That's possible.
It's possible she got massages.
- People get massages on the knees.
- It exists.
- Yes. Growth plate massages.
- That exists.
- It exists.
- Her age...
She's old enough to have gotten those massages.
- I...
- Right. Number two.
- Number two.
- Okay.
I cried after shaving my head...
during the "Good Thing" promotions.
(2. I cried after shaving my head during the "Good Thing" promotions.)
You cried after shaving your head.
She had her head shaved.
- Right. Her hair was very short.
- She cried.
- I think she laughed. That's a lie.
- No.
She would have wanted to shave her head.
- Number three.
- It's not easy.
- It's crazy.
My dream as a child was becoming a circus performer.
- A circus performer?
- That was my dream as well.
- Your dream...
- Here...
Let's ask her questions about those statements...
- and guess the false one.
- The first one.
- Again...
- When did you get the massage...
to grow taller?
It was when I was in grade 6 going over to grade 7.
- In between.
- Yes.
It was a thing in our neighborhood.
Until I was in grade three,
my height was around average.
But it remained the same even until I was in grade six.
So Mom heard some rumors from around...
about the massage that makes you get taller.
- There was a package deal.
- That's right.
She sent me to get one of those.
- That time...
- Where do they massage?
It's a full-body massage,
but they focused around...
the growth plate on the knee.
- Did you get taller?
- Was it effective?
No, it didn't work.
Did it feel good?
- It felt good.
- That's good, then.
"That feels good."
I've never heard of this before.
- Me neither.
- Back in the day...
- Mothers these days...
- Right. It's a thing.
get very stressed about their children's height.
So there are all sorts of things.
So you didn't get taller.
Didn't you complain to that company?
- She said it felt good.
- That's it?
- Didn't you...
- They notified in advance...
that it could make you taller.
- "It could."
- Right.
- "It could make you taller."
- They say that.
- On the contract...
I also had an appointment with them,
and they said it could make you get this tall,
but there are no guarantees.
- Did you get them as well?
- I went there because of my kids.
- I went there...
- Soo Geun...
Soo Geun...
There were no appointments back then.
He couldn't go to Seoul because he had no bus fare.
I didn't know I was short when I was young.
All the kids in my neighborhood were around my height.
We all ate similar things,
so we were about the same height.
I realized it when I went to high school...
that people could be so tall.
How many sessions did you get?
I got 10 sessions for 1 package.
- Ten sessions?
- That's a lot.
I ended up getting 20 sessions.
I don't think it was actually a height-growth massage.
I think it was a scalp massage.
That's possible because...
- her hair...
- Ever since you were young...
- We've cleared number 1.
- Number 1...
- Number 2.
- Let me ask you about number 2.
- Okay.
- Number two.
Did you write that song?
- "Good Thing?"
- Yes.
- Then number two would be a lie.
- Why?
- You shaved your head...
for a song you wrote.
- After shaving your head...
- As a producer...
At the time we were making "Good Thing,"
- we had a new visual director.
- That's right.
That new director convinced me...
that it would be nice...
to have a character...
like Miley Cyrus for a song like that.
When I first heard it, I thought,
"That's right."
"I could pull off a cool character like that."
But on the day I shaved my head...
- They shaved my head with clippers.
- With clippers?
The moment I heard the clippers buzzing, I thought,
- "Something is not right here."
- "Oh, no."
"What have I done?"
My heart started pounding from that point.
Then my head got shaved.
- Are you tearing up now?
- No.
- My head got shaved.
- You got emotional.
Did you feel sad?
Yes. I found myself...
tearing up.
- So...
- It's bringing back the memories.
- I mean...
- It would bring back the memories.
I think she laughed after shaving her head.
- On the contrary.
- It suited her well.
- In amusement.
- Because it suited her so well.
I think she laughed because it was funny.
I think she loved...
- being herself at the moment.
- That's right.
If it wasn't her song,
and someone else was producing it, she would cry.
I know because I told Ri Na to wear a turban, and she cried.
"The Angel Who Lost Wings..."
- For "The Angel Who Lost Wings?"
- Yes.
- That's right.
- She cut her hair short,
- almost like she shaved her head.
- Right.
She said she wanted to look pretty too...
- since she's a woman.
- That's right.
- "No, you should go with hip-hop."
That's what I said.
But when she started producing later on,
she did the exact same thing.
She gave such directions.
So since SOYEON is professional,
- she wouldn't have...
- She wouldn't have cried?
- She didn't cry?
- She didn't cry.
- Somehow...
- She could have cried.
When I filmed "Decision to Leave," Director Park Chan Wook said,
"How about cutting your hair a little?"
"How about trying a new look?"
So I acted cool...
- and said, "Yes,"
- "Okay."
"I'll do that for the movie."
The reference was Anne Hathaway.
- In "The Devil Wears Prada."
- Yes.
I get what you mean.
I cut my hair at the salon with that reference.
I couldn't wear the Prada.
I just looked like my dad.
I saw someone who looked exactly like my dad.
I'd had a bob haircut for 20 years.
People started teasing me.
"Welcome, Father."
"Welcome, Lee Jae Po."
I know what it's like. I felt a bit sad.
- That's right.
- It's a thing.
- Now...
- Number three!
Number three.
Your childhood dream was becoming a circus performer?
She would have watched something on TV.
Many children have such random dreams.
My dream was becoming a circus performer.
What inspired you?
- There must have been a reason.
- Dongchun?
- It wasn't Dongchun.
- She would have been...
- too young.
- It was Cirque du Soleil.
- It would have been that.
- The Cirque du Soleil.
- After watching...
- On a trip.
Cirque du Soleil,
- I sent an email...
- It's amazing.
- to a circus school in Montreal.
- Goodness.
- And?
- How did it go?
Did you get a reply?
- An audition video...
- They sent a price list.
Price list?
- The money...
- Informing the tuition...
and things like that.
- The tuition fee.
The tuition fee.
She wanted to become a circus performer,
but ever since she was young, she was afraid of heights,
- so she had to give up her dream.
- That's...
- No, she mentioned tuition.
- She did dream of it.
- She talked about the free.
- Because it was her dream.
- Did she want to be a ringmaster?
- Canada was too far.
- That's right.
- I couldn't do it...
- because Canada was too far.
- What about her height?
- Okay.
- Let's make a decision.
- Everyone will choose number two.
- This is hard.
Number one, she received a massage to get taller...
when she was young. Who thinks that's a lie?
Raise your hand.
No one. There's no one.
Now, number two.
- I cried...
- During "Good Thing."
after shaving my head during the "Good Thing" promotions.
Raise your hand if you think that's a lie.
This one has the highest chance of being a lie.
- So many of you chose it.
- Five of you chose it.
Number three.
"My dream as a child was becoming a circus performer."
Raise your hand if you think that's a lie.
- Three.
- She could've considered it...
- once in her life.
- Back then,
- you couldn't have dreamt of it.
- Right.
- I knew it.
- Number one bothers me.
Okay, then.
Which one of the three fun facts was a lie?
(Which one was a lie?)
Please reveal it.
Which one is it?
(She would've never cried.)
Why do you say that? The answer is number two.
(2. I cried after shaving my head during the "Good Thing" promotions.)
See? That one was obvious.
An artist wouldn't have cried.
- Of course not.
- That's true.
Even yesterday, I thought,
"I want to shave my head again."
- That was what I thought.
- Really?
That's why we've prepared hair clippers.
(Hair-shaving ceremony while everyone is watching)
It will help boost your album sales.
- Good.
- Let's do it!
- Bring in the clippers.
- Bring them.
Okay. Let's go.
How could you...
- I thought you read my fortune.
- Also,
- You're so sharp.
- we...
- She almost got me.
- I know!
- She's a great actor.
- SOYEON is...
- like a captain.
- Yes.
She wouldn't have cried after getting her hair cut.
When you looked at yourself after cutting your hair,
you were satisfied with yourself for your courage,
- Yes.
- right?
"Gosh. Am I pushing myself this far?"
"That's amazing."
(Today, she's really getting a buzz cut.)
(Nervously cutting her hair)
- No. Do it.
- Should I?
(I look cool now.)
(Loving herself)
- Let's go, MINNIE.
- MINNIE.
- Go, MINNIE.
- It's me.
- Okay.
- Nicha.
- I'll do it.
- I'll try it.
- Tararak.
Number one.
I eat meat...
every day, seven times a week.
Sounds delicious.
- In a week?
- Amazing.
Once a day?
- That means every day.
- She thinks...
Seven times a week?
- You ate a lot.
- That's every day.
- Number two.
- Okay.
I cry every other day.
(2. I cry every other day.)
Do you cry every other day?
- She cries every other day?
- Why?
- This one is tough.
- Now...
- Number 3.
I have psychic abilities.
(3. I have psychic abilities.)
- Psychic abilities.
- Psychic abilities?
- She has psychic abilities.
- Can you foresee the future?
- I got it.
I have prophetic dreams.
- Prophetic dreams?
- Prophetic dreams.
- Prophetic dreams. Yes.
- Really?
Having prophetic dreams is a lie.
Which one is a lie among these facts?
- First...
- Okay.
- You've seen stuff.
- Let's start with number one.
- Why do you eat meat?
- Which meat do you eat all week?
I take turns.
- What do you mean?
- I eat beef most frequently.
- Beef.
- Beef. And...
pork and lamb.
I usually grill it to eat.
- Do you grill it?
- Yes.
Meat is the only thing...
- she doesn't eat.
- She's Thai.
- I love meat.
- It's a lie.
- No, you don't.
- Thai people love meat.
- She grew up...
- She does love meat.
- in a wealthy family.
- She said meat, not just beef.
She must've had a lot of meat.
- When I say meat, - She acts like one.
- I mean grilled meat.
- Grilled meat?
You have an allergy, though.
What allergy?
- What?
- A meat allergy.
- That's me, fool.
- Is that you?
You're a team, right?
- YUQI.
- Also,
I studied it.
- About what?
- I'm blood type O.
- Your blood type is O.
- Blood type O is good...
at digesting meat, especially red meat.
I don't get fat when I eat it.
- Is there such a thing?
- I've never heard of it.
No. I'm also blood type O, and red meat makes me fat.
- You do when you eat a lot.
- Not me.
- I...
- I get fat when I eat it.
- He's type O too.
- What about yukhoe?
- It's a lie.
- He shows...
that it's not true.
- It's a lie.
- You work out,
- so you have meat every day.
- I do.
- Why do you cry every other day...
- Meat doesn't make you fat.
when you eat meat every day?
Are we moving on? Okay.
(We'll move on, then.)
- That was seamless.
- First of all,
my MBTI type is INFJ.
And I'm over 90 percent type F.
- Really?
- Kyung Hoon is also an INFJ.
Really?
- So, I'm very sentimental.
- Do you cry every day?
- You're sentimental, then.
- Does she cry?
I cry easily.
Does she cry the most in your group?
- Yes.
- Have you seen her cry, SOYEON?
I see.
- I've seen it often.
- She cried while eating.
- What? Why?
- Right. That wasn't long ago.
- And when she talks.
- She cries while she talks too.
- What kind of story is it?
- It's...
- I talk about my worries.
- While sharing her concern,
- she cried, - MIYEON said,
"You're not crying, are you?"
- "Don't." And I cried.
- She cries when she hears that.
I thought it was hilarious, so I took a photo.
- That's right.
- You shot her crying.
- I just can...
- They're true friends.
I can cry. Yes.
- What about the psychic abilities?
- You're emotional.
- Number three.
- As for my psychic abilities,
in Thailand, we're very much into superstitions.
- And I love my fortune told.
- I see.
There is someone who always reads fortune for us.
- Our fortune-teller is really good.
- Really?
My members know how good she is.
She gives me goosebumps.
One day, she told me...
not to come to have my fortune read...
- so frequently.
- Why not?
Because some people are more susceptible.
She told me I could be initiated as a shaman.
That's why...
- my mom visits her...
- She's very sharp.
to have my fortune read.
- It's so scary.
- Or I talk to her on the phone.
- After I've become an adult, - Do you see the future?
I get this sensation from time to time.
- What kind of sensation?
- When I'm home...
and about to sleep,
someone whispers like this.
- What?
- Really?
- So I can't sleep.
- Wasn't it a mosquito?
- You have to see a doctor.
- She hears voices.
- That's...
because you have...
- a stone in your ear.
- It's tinnitus.
Go see a doctor.
Wait. What kind of prophetic dreams do you have?
- Right. The prophetic dreams.
- It's like this.
One day,
I dreamt of my friend getting in an accident.
It felt so real, so I felt uncomfortable.
So, I told my friend...
- And what did your friend say?
- to be careful.
- And she got in an accident.
- Did she get in an accident?
- Really?
- What kind of accident?
A car accident.
- A car?
- A car accident?
I said this already in another show,
statistically,
everyone gets in a car accident...
- once or twice a year.
- Seriously.
It happens.
- At that right moment, - He's a type T, indeed.
MINNIE was able to have...
- that dream.
- He's ruining it.
- Quiet.
- Number one.
"I eat meat every day, seven times a week."
Raise your hand if you think that's a lie.
- I have no idea.
- She might not eat meat at all.
She doesn't eat meat.
- Doesn't she?
- She's a vegetarian.
A total of six. You can put your hands down.
"I cry every other day."
Raise your hand if you think that's a lie.
- Some people cry like that.
- I think it's true.
- "I have psychic abilities."
- That's strange.
- Raise your hand if that's a lie.
- It's a lie.
- Two.
- It's...
- Didn't she say it before?
It's strange. She said so before.
Which one was a lie?
- She has her fortune told.
- Tell us.
- Please reveal the answer.
- She's good at this.
I...
(She can't be psychic, can she?)
(She must be a vegetarian.)
(MINNIE's lie was number 3!)
- It's number three.
- Nice!
But you have your fortune told.
I like my fortune told, but I don't have psychic abilities.
- It's because...
- You like your fortune told.
- She always sees a fortune-teller.
- As for the meat,
I've seen it...
- in many documentaries.
- She fooled me.
People in Southeast Asia...
consume surprisingly large...
- amount of meat.
- That's right.
I have a question.
- Can I ask the question?
- They don't eat kimchi.
- SHUHUA.
- Yes?
Why did you shout, "You have a meat allergy?"
But do you have it.
I told you it was me.
She has the allergy.
- I already told you.
- Since a while ago,
she said, "It was me."
Hold on. You do have an allergy.
- I tested for allergies before.
- Okay.
I'm allergic to chicken.
- I told you.
- Really?
- She said it herself.
- I'm not allergic at all.
She only mentioned beef, pork, and lamb.
As for chicken,
- she didn't mention it.
- Right.
- That's true.
- But I do eat chicken.
- She does eat chicken.
- But you're allergic.
I'm going to talk about something else.
Dubai chewy cookies were in trend recently.
Yes, DCC.
I think I had...
- two a day, right?
- Right.
- I loved them.
- They're so good.
I didn't feel anything at the moment.
But back then, people said I looked like a Moomin.
- You were swollen.
- I apparently looked swollen.
- Really?
- She was swollen.
- Because of DCC.
- Yes, I was.
- Why?
- I thought I gained weight.
- Okay.
I thought, "It is what it is."
- But then, I had a medical checkup.
- Okay.
I'm allergic to pistachios.
- Are you allergic?
- I'm highly allergic.
It was in the red zone.
I didn't get fat back then. I was just swollen.
You had an allergic reaction.
- My cheeks were this big.
- It's true.
But you didn't get fat. It was an allergy.
- I did...
- She did gain weight too.
- Actually...
- Should I get tested for allergies?
I gained weight after having DCC too.
I must be allergic to something.
To be honest...
- Okay.
- Thank you for being honest.
- YUQI.
- Next is YUQI.
Now, a quiz on me.
- Number 1.
I was once the top student...
in my grade.
With what? With your grades, of course?
- With my grades.
- With your grades.
When?
When I was in middle school.
Weren't you a trainee back then?
- That's high school.
- Come on.
Hold on, SHUHUA. Can we trust you or not?
Don't do anything.
- Okay.
- Were you a trainee back then?
(Are you a friend or a foe?)
In that case, she didn't have time to study, right?
- I'm sorry, - She's just sitting there.
but I came to Korea after graduating high school.
She came to Korea after graduating high school.
I was talking about my middle school days.
- Number 2.
My MBTI is type J.
I'm a super planner.
So, I pack a week before I go abroad.
- I see.
- That's me.
- You pack your stuff that early.
- That's for the show.
If she's a J type, it's understandable.
- I do that too.
- Still, it's too much.
I pack two weeks before the trip.
- And...
- Do you do that too?
- Number 3.
- Here's number 3.
I eat too many eggs,
so I have high cholesterol.
- You ate too many yolks.
- That's possible.
- Does the level go up...
- That can happen.
just because you ate eggs?
- "Eating eggs..."
- If you eat yolks.
"will increase your cholesterol level."
I heard that was the biggest misconception we have.
- Really?
- That's right.
- It's a wrong concept.
- You're right.
- I'm correct, right?
- They say it has nothing...
- to do with eggs.
- By the way,
- starting from number 1, - From number 1.
tell us about the facts.
Let me tell you where I'm from.
I went to Beijing 101 Middle School.
- Beijing...
- As for my school,
only the ones with good grades can enter.
- How good do you have to be?
- Top five percent.
Only students in the top five percent can get in.
- I was a science major.
- Okay.
In China,
you have to take an exam before entering a school.
Your class is decided according to the test result.
- It's based on the result.
- And I got into Class One.
For your information, there were a total...
- of 14 classes.
- That means...
- I got into the top class.
- You were the top student...
- in the top class?
- I ranked first.
- I was a fan of Super Junior.
- Super Junior.
So I wanted to go to their concerts.
I asked my mom what I could do to go to their concerts.
She told me to become the top student.
"If you rank first in your entire school,"
"you can go to their concerts."
Yes. That was why I could go to their concerts often.
Being the top student is understandable. Moving on,
- she's a J type.
- She is...
She's always well-prepared, but when it comes to packing...
She packs on the morning of the departure.
- She packs on the day of the trip.
- And haphazardly.
Some J-type people are like that.
I'm also like that.
I'm a super ISTJ type.
When you search it online,
I'm an example of the ISTJ type.
That shows that I'm an extreme J type.
Still, I don't pack a week before a trip.
- It's...
- Hold on. YUQI.
Do you make notes before you pack?
A list of things you have to bring.
I make notes every day before I go to bed...
on the things I have to do the next day.
- You have many concerts abroad.
- I can't do that.
You have many performances.
Basically, I'm overseas all the time.
That's why I pack in advance. As for the suitcases,
- The way she says it...
- I have about seven.
Suitcases for Europe.
- Suitcases for the US.
- That's right.
We go to different countries...
- for the tour.
- They tour around.
For your information,
my suitcases are divided into tops, bottoms,
skirts, and glasses.
I have separate pouches for each.
- That's possible.
- It can happen.
- Okay.
- But...
- Now, the eggs!
- Did you ask all your questions?
Eggs. Let me talk about the eggs.
I'm a huge fan of eggs.
Have you ever had eggs...
- for all three meals?
- I do that most of the time.
Up to how many eggs have you had in one go?
When we go abroad, we have breakfast at the hotel.
- I eat raw eggs.
- Okay.
I have scrambled eggs.
- And those...
- Fried eggs?
- fried eggs.
- Okay.
- And half-boiled eggs?
- Yes.
And I prefer the yolks over the egg whites.
Yes, the yolks are the yummy part.
Four years ago, I had my first medical checkup...
- in Korea.
- Four years ago.
I also had high cholesterol back then.
The doctor said it can't be that high at my age.
Your body screams low cholesterol.
That shows how many eggs I have.
How many can you eat at most?
I think over ten eggs a day.
- Over 10 eggs?
- Over 10 eggs.
- Ten eggs?
- As various egg dishes.
- Hong Yun Hwa eats 30 eggs a day.
Do you know...
- a tomato and egg stir-fry?
- She eats a whole carton.
(A tomato and egg stir-fry is a well-known Chinese dish.)
- One serving includes five eggs.
- That's right.
- T and E stir-fry?
- With the yolks?
- You do eat a lot of them.
- T and E stir-fry.
- But her body doesn't seem...
- I'm confused now.
- to have high cholesterol.
- Hers can't be high.
- You haven't seen the body...
- But...
- with high cholesterol.
- You're wrong.
- You're an idol.
- People who take medicine for it.
Why would you talk about your high cholesterol?
- Exactly.
- Because mine is very high.
I find it unbelievable too.
- She's never been the top student.
- Let's do this.
But I have no way to prove it.
- Okay.
- She insists on being one.
I do have proof for it.
Okay. YUQI.
Number one, "I was once the top student in my grade."
Raise your hand if you think that's a lie.
- It's possible.
- Not even once.
- It might be true.
- Maybe only in her class.
But not the entire school.
Now, number two.
"I'm a J type."
"So, I pack a week before I go abroad."
Raise your hand if you think it's a lie.
- It can't be true.
- She doesn't pack anything.
She borrows clothes from her members.
She goes to the stores nearby.
- I lent you my shoes before.
- She'd be the last one to unpack.
- I lent her my shoes.
- She doesn't pack anything.
- SHUHUA tattled on her again.
- Even if she's a J type,
- "I lent you my shoes."
- she just travels too much.
- Did you lend your shoes to her?
- I did.
SHUHUA lent her shoes to her.
It was just once, girl.
- "Girl."
- Number 3, "I eat too many eggs,"
- Number 3.
"so I have high cholesterol."
- I choose this one.
- I'm torn between 2 and 3,
- but I choose number three.
- It isn't just because of eggs.
- Number 3 is more likely.
- There are 4 people.
This time, it's evenly split.
- I think it's number three.
- You can put them down now.
Now, what was YUQI's lie?
Tell us now.
The lie I made was...
- The lie was...
(Her cholesterol level can't be high.)
(You go on a trip without packing.)
(YUQI's lie was...)
- number one!
- Goodness.
- Really?
- Gosh. Really?
- Yeong Cheol.
- I got it.
- I got it right.
- YUQI, what is it?
- What?
- She was never the top student.
- You were shocked, right?
- Come on.
- She was never the top student.
- YUQI,
- were you a bad student?
- It didn't matter.
- No.
- You didn't go to that school.
You're wrong. What I said was all true.
I just ranked 5th, not 1st, in the entire grade.
You ranked fifth in your school.
- That's still amazing.
- That's an amazing job.
You ranked 5th, but you changed it to 1st.
I was going to choose number one,
but I trusted YUQI.
- That's right.
- So she could brag about it.
That's why you shouldn't be too quick to trust others.
Gosh. Are we in Busan all of a sudden?
- Where are you going?
- I know.
- Okay.
- Yes.
- Good.
- Good job.
Next is SHUHUA.
I think hers will be tough.
- Yes.
- Right.
- Number 1.
I once fell into the water...
and stopped breathing when I was little.
- You stopped breathing.
- After falling into the water,
- you stopped breathing.
- Yes.
Okay. Number two.
Number two. Because I had small ears,
I had ear contouring surgery.
- What?
- Ear contouring.
- Ear contouring surgery?
- Yes, I had one.
- Is there such a thing?
- Because you had small ears?
- People get ear surgery these days.
- That's right.
- Number 3.
- Okay. Number 3.
- Number three.
- It's surgery.
I received one too many chocolates...
back in the school days...
that it took a whole week to take them home.
- Liar. You weren't popular at all.
- When you were young.
When you were in elementary school.
- What's wrong with Soo Geun?
- Back in school,
you weren't popular,
so you bought chocolates yourself...
- and handed them to others.
- That's right.
You're so negative, Soo Geun.
- Number three is a lie.
- Just like others.
Number one is possible.
- I know. Now, number 1.
- But... Number 1.
You stopped breathing after falling into the water when you were young.
Was it an accident?
- Was it?
- You went to a pool, right?
- No, it wasn't a pool.
- Then?
- It was a lake.
- A lake?
- She stopped breathing in a lake.
- My aunt's house...
- was in the mountains.
- Okay.
I went to the lake with my siblings.
- To have fun.
- And I fell into it.
And? How were you rescued?
I don't remember.
- That's right.
- Because I was dead.
- Hold on.
- Well...
Are you talking about reincarnation all of a sudden?
- She was dead for a while.
- For a while.
- You lost consciousness.
- Yes.
- She blacked out.
- But...
She fainted.
- She didn't die.
- You lost consciousness.
So were you taken to the hospital?
- I was.
- Did an ambulance come?
(She was taken to the hospital after getting rescued.)
- I went to the hospital.
- Okay.
I was hospitalized for a month.
- That was long.
- Yes.
- That's why she's scared of water.
- I'd talk about it all the time.
- Actually, it's...
- I'm aquaphobic.
- She's aquaphobic.
- Are you still aquaphobic?
- Yes.
Okay. Number two.
What's wrong with your ears?
- Were they too small?
- They were too small.
Were they smaller than now?
They used to be smaller.
It's the contour of my ears.
- Do you mean the shape of them?
- When I...
When we have concerts, we have to wear...
- in-ear monitors.
- Right.
But they wouldn't fit.
- In-ear monitors wouldn't fit.
- But...
- the in-ear monitor maker said...
- What happens when they don't fit?
they made them small for me already.
So, if they make them smaller,
the sound quality would decrease.
- That's right.
- It would sound bad.
- Her auricles...
- I'm looking at her ears now.
- I've never heard of it.
- Her ears are...
SHUHUA's ears are...
not that small.
- They are small.
- The canals might be small.
- Show your...
- MINNIE, come here.
- You can't extend your ears.
- Mine are small too.
You didn't broaden them, did you?
They are really small.
Is she saying she made this part bigger?
I think she has cut the inner part of the ears.
- Did she cut the inner part?
- She injected something in there.
When did you get the surgery?
- Is it a procedure or surgery?
- When?
- Before the tour.
- You had surgery?
- This year?
- This year.
- You had it this year?
- I had it this year.
- It was a quick procedure.
- Why didn't you tell the members?
Why bother?
(Why bother to tell them?)
- Sounds like type T.
- She's amazing.
- You are type T, aren't you?
- So cool.
- Aren't you type T?
- Goodness!
- "Why bother?"
- She's definitely type T.
- "Why tell them I had surgery?"
- That's what I always say.
- I knew.
- "Why bother?"
- You knew, SOYEON?
- I knew.
- She lied about the chocolates.
- Did she have a lot of...
- In school...
- But it's a true story.
- So, number three.
- No.
Back in school days, you received one too many chocolates...
- that it once took you...
- Yes.
- a week to take them home.
- It's true.
They were lockers at the back of the classroom.
- Yes.
- The lockers.
- My locker overflowed with candy.
- I'm sure it happened.
- Below the chair...
- On Valentine's Day?
- Wait.
- On Valentine's Day.
- I received tons of candies.
- What grade were you in?
Grade Five.
- Grade 5.
- Was this Grade 5 onwards...
or was it only in Grade Five?
Only in Grade Five.
- How come?
- Why were you popular then?
- That's a bit sad.
- Grade Five...
- Why were you popular only then?
- Why were you popular then?
I guess that's when I became pretty.
Oh, I... Forget it.
- Tell us.
- What is it?
She was going to tell us how popular she was then.
It was a provincial school.
So I must've stood out more.
- When you're in Grade Five, - Right.
you don't have enough chocolates to put in your own mouth.
That's not true.
- That's not true.
- That's when you were young.
- She wasn't born in the 1970s.
- I got a week's worth.
It's not the same as when you were little.
- You must've starved.
- Older students could afford that.
Middle and high school kids...
could afford that, but grade school kids are too young.
Because they are young, chocolates are all they got.
- They are cheap.
- Right.
That's their way of expressing love.
Now, let's figure out which is a lie.
One, she once fell in the water and stopped breathing...
when she was little. Raise your hand if you think this is a lie.
- I think that's a true story.
- Did she want to be a swimmer?
- For some reason...
- I will go with it too.
- Sorry, I choose one.
- Next.
Two, she had an ear contouring surgery because she had small ears.
Raise your hand if you think this is a lie.
- I choose this one.
- She's thinking about it.
- But she's coping with it.
- It has to be this one.
Three, she received one too many chocolates back in school days...
that it took her a whole week to take them home.
- "One too many" is a lie.
- If you think it's a lie...
The kids didn't have money to buy "one too many" chocolates.
(The kids didn't have money to buy many chocolates.)
- There were many kids.
- They are grade school kids.
- Let's find out what the lie was.
- Hers is hard.
Tell us.
(Never heard of an ear contouring surgery.)
(There's no way she would've gotten so many precious chocolates.)
Tell us.
(Her lie was...)
Two.
(The three men picked the ear contouring surgery story!)
- I knew it. I knew she was lying.
- Wait.
- You said you knew about it.
- What happened?
(SOYEON said she knew about the surgery.)
You were helping her, weren't you?
(SOYEON's assist tricked everyone.)
- She was helping her.
- She must have bad ears.
- SOYEON was just helping.
- I thought it was real.
So I got my in-ear earphones fixed many times.
- So you do have small ears.
- Perhaps she almost had it?
- But you didn't have surgery.
- I didn't have surgery.
- You didn't.
- Then...
- tell us about the chocolates.
- Tell us.
I received too many chocolates...
that my grandpa got really upset.
- Why?
- He wondered what I did...
- What you did to get those?
- "Why did you get so many?"
- That's what he said.
- Did he eat all the chocolates?
- I told him, "I'm just popular."
- So...
Grandpas love chocolates.
- So Grandpa got a cavity.
- I...
- gave them away to my friends.
- He ate one by one.
- You gave them away?
- Yes.
Imagine you go to a quiet provincial school,
and there's SHUHUA in your class.
- Then all the kids would love her.
- Right.
Even if they didn't go to a quiet school, i-dle members...
- must've received a lot of candies.
- Soo Geun.
- How about the other ones?
- SOYEON, did you receive a lot too?
- How much did you receive?
- I didn't get anything.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Same here.
- You too, MIYEON?
- I wasn't popular.
Shin Young, have you received chocolates in life?
- I used to be like SHUHUA.
- When?
- Let's stop this conversation.
- When I was in middle school.
You wouldn't say that if I were Lee Hyo Ri!
I would've believed it if you were Lee Hyo Ri.
- I would've.
- So you received...
- the chocolates and...
- What?
- You received the chocolates and...
- I'm telling you, in just...
- They were confessing love?
They were love confessions.
- Wasn't it a girls' middle school?
- Love confessions.
- It was a girls' middle school.
It was a girls' middle school.
- You have to listen until the end.
- She must've been very popular.
- It was a girls' middle school.
- Only for girls?
It was a school only for girls, and I was too popular.
- I went to a girls' school too.
- Right. So...
my desk was always stuffed with bread.
I couldn't put my hands inside it.
On my birthday...
- This is funny. This isn't a lie.
- I went to a girls' middle school.
Does it mean among all of us here,
I am the one who received the most amount of chocolates in life?
- What are you talking about?
- There's Kyung Hoon.
- He received them a lot too.
- What are you talking about?
- What do you mean?
- Cover up your past stories.
Don't even bother listening to the old stories.
- Wait.
- What are you saying?
Don't even bother listening to the old stories. Let's pass.
That was the funniest thing he said today.
I assure you.
- You wouldn't understand it, - Soo Geun is ignored.
i-dle.
I don't understand what you mean.
- In the past, I...
- She doesn't understand it.
I'm not talking about now.
- In the past, when I...
- Yonsei University.
- When I played basketball, - He used to play basketball.
the team I played for...
was the most popular basketball team in Korea, one time.
- You mean then.
- So...
- I know when that is.
- That's understandable.
"Give it to Woo Ji Won." And he went...
No.
"I'm sorry, but can you give it to Sang Min?"
"Give it to Jang Hoon."
That happened too.
- But even so, - You must've received a lot.
- Of course.
- we received a truckful every day.
A truckful?
It wasn't just on Valentine's Day. It was every day.
It's very surprising to hear, isn't it, SHUHUA?
- She missed the timing to return.
- When can I return to my seat?
(Jang Hoon's chocolate story made her miss the timing.)
Well done, SHUHUA.
She missed the timing.
- Well done.
- Good job.
Next is MIYEON.
I'm really bad at lying.
One, I actually don't think I am a princess.
(I am not suffering from a princess syndrome.)
I got the answer.
- It's number 1.
- Number 1.
- Number 1, for sure.
- It's a lie.
- I pick number one.
- Number 2.
I go to the bathroom more than ten times a day.
- More than ten times?
- That's possible.
- Perhaps to check herself.
- Three.
Three. I was originally a rapper.
You used to be a rapper?
(3. She was originally a rapper.)
She must've been good.
- She's done.
- MIYEON the rapper!
Let's talk about One first.
You're not suffering from a princess syndrome?
- What is it?
- What's your condition then?
- How do you explain that?
- Condition?
- What condition is it then?
- Perhaps you will say,
"I'm a real princess."
- You know, when I was...
- "It's not a syndrome. It's real."
- I don't think she's that.
- on this show last time,
I said a lot of things as if I was suffering from a princess syndrome.
(I am pretty though, aren't I?)
(A real princess doesn't suffer from a princess syndrome.)
(Princess MIYEON had said many impressive things.)
- But that was just a concept.
- It's a concept.
- Of course.
- Just to be funny.
- It just got out of my hands.
- It was just a joke.
But you look in the mirror often,
and you talk to yourself,
"You are so beautiful." Isn't that a symptom?
You said you look in the mirror and talk to yourself every morning.
- So...
- "You can do a good job."
She's not suffering from a princess syndrome.
Define princess syndrome.
Here's what I think.
Truly loving yourself doesn't mean you are suffering...
from a princess syndrome.
If you are really suffering from the princess syndrome,
you should have seven men like me on your side.
- Right?
- I should be by your side too.
Right? Please composite Soo Geun next to me.
- Then I'd say you have it.
- Right?
Here's why I say this.
The concept is fun, and I am enjoying it.
- That's true.
- I think I am beautiful.
But everyone around me, including my parents,
are very worried about me.
"Is MIYEON all right?"
- "She should be humble."
- As long as you don't overdo it.
MIYEON, you're claiming that you don't have the condition.
Doesn't it prove that you are suffering from it?
(Does it prove that she is suffering from the princess syndrome?)
Does it?
- That's what I am saying.
- That's sharp.
- He's very insightful.
- No matter what she claims,
If people around her claim she's got it, she's got it.
Those who seriously suffer from it don't call it a "syndrome."
- Right.
Did you suffer from it too, Shin Young?
- Then it isn't a lie.
- I've never suffered from it.
I suffered from food poisoning.
Stop it.
- I really did.
- Don't go that far.
You shouldn't eat raw meat.
- You use toilet ten times a day.
- This is true.
What's number two about?
I drink a lot of water.
I think my body absorbs only a little portion of it.
So it comes out right away.
I always thought of the toilet...
as a comfortable space.
There's a mirror in the toilet.
I look in the mirror too.
It sounds like you are suffering from the princess syndrome.
- Just checking.
- You look in the mirror.
Some go to the toilet when they are nervous.
- Some people go often.
- Right.
- Kyung Hoon.
Whenever I go to the toilet, there's always Kyung Hoon.
- Really?
He's in the toilet more than he's in the waiting room.
- I hide in the toilet.
- Don't you poop...
about five times whenever you're here?
- You do number two?
- He's comfortable here.
- MIYEON.
- Well, some people...
- have a very active bladder.
- I go to the toilet very often.
- Very often.
- He goes to the toilet very often.
When you say you used to be a rapper,
you mean you worked as a rapper at some point.
At first, I used to belong to...
- another agency, not this one.
- Right.
That agency was well-known for hip hop.
I had joined that agency in the first place...
because I was into RnB.
During the first audition,
- I sang.
- Right.
- And they asked me to rap.
- Rap?
The producer said I had a rapper's voice.
- She's good.
- So I improvised it on the spot.
The rumor spread in the agency.
- That I am the next CL.
- CL?
I read it on the internet.
- Really?
- She's lying again.
- She's lying.
- Are you lying?
- I really saw it.
- It was popular.
- I don't trust you now.
- This is true.
- You have to show them.
- You said you saw...
- Then they won't question you.
- SHUHUA's ear after the surgery.
- She's a good liar.
- No.
There's a community...
of trainees.
- Right.
- There is a community.
She was famous.
- Let us hear it.
- She was famous.
- Just do a short one.
- We heard you're the next CL.
- We just want to hear your tone.
- What...
- But if I show you,
- it would be too...
- What was the first lesson?
They corrected my tone.
- Really?
- Your tone?
I hate rapping now.
- Why?
- I don't like it.
- You don't have a good memory.
- She can't...
- She can't rap at all.
- I am now...
- a lead vocalist now.
- She can't rap at all.
Recently, SOYEON keeps asking me to rap.
- Is that right?
- Now...
- I get it now.
- No, the professionals...
- YG's songs...
- Yes?
You have to sing and rap.
- Right.
- Most of their songs are like that.
They wanted to make MIYEON debut,
- But she could only sing.
- but she could only sing.
And she couldn't rap.
So her debut kept getting delayed,
and in the end, she moved to this agency.
- She hated it.
- SOYEON,
I hated rapping, didn't I?
You hated rapping.
But you were originally a rapper. Why hate rapping?
Because I am not a rapper anymore.
- I think she's telling the truth.
- It's nothing serious,
- but I can't be sure.
- Okay.
Let's see what's a lie.
One, she's not suffering from a princess syndrome.
If you think that's a lie, raise your hand.
- This is true.
- I think her parents asked her.
If her parents call her...
Her mom must've asked her to stop it and said...
- that her neighbors were upset.
- Well...
Two, she goes to the toilet more than ten times a day.
- People do that.
- It's normal to go ten times.
If you think it's a lie, raise your hand.
- I do that too.
- I think it's true.
- Sang Min is the only one.
- It's possible.
She's originally a rapper.
If you think it's a lie, please raise your hand.
- Let me just get one right.
- Let me just get one right. Sorry.
- Start.
- I have to get this one.
- Five people.
- Goodness.
Now...
Let's find out which was a lie. Tell us, MIYEON.
- The lie was...
- What was the lie?
(She must've been a singer from the beginning.)
(Perhaps she's right about the princess syndrome?)
- It's Three.
- Yes!
That was it.
- Right.
- It was an easy one.
- Tell us about it.
- Tell us about this one.
- Right.
The agency is big, and I had been...
- a trainee for a long time.
- You didn't get one right.
So people took photos of me...
going in and out of the office several times.
At the time, I dyed my hair blonde.
And I loved wearing leather jackets.
- So people thought I was a rapper.
- You looked like a rapper.
"She must be a rapper."
You looked like one.
And the rumor spread that I was talented...
enough to be the next CL.
I heard that rumor too.
It was all over the internet.
- But I was never a rapper.
- No.
I'm curious.
When you rap,
you can make a mistake with the words.
Have you ever experienced getting away with such a mistake?
When I just debuted...
and got awarded the Rookie of the Year award,
I had to perform on a big stage,
and I forgot the entire section.
- The entire section?
- I forgot the entire section.
You were that nervous.
- What did you do?
- I was too nervous.
But fortunately, it was fine as long as I got...
the rhyme right.
- How?
- Is it all about confidence?
Right.
Don't be lazy, approach me baby
Time is too short, and this is too basic
(The version with the forgotten lyrics)
This is how I did it.
She looks...
- She's got swag.
- totally cool.
(I may forget the lyrics, but I never lose my swag.)
- Look at her.
- It's all about the attitude.
- Right.
- It covers up the mistake.
People watching don't know the lyrics anyway.
- They don't know.
- Amazing.
Only we knew because we were listening through the earphones.
Right.
- I even thought about...
- We knew she was nervous.
collapsing on stage.
You wanted to do that?
- That comes up in your mind.
- Yes.
I thought about pretending to be unwell.
You think of all kinds of things.
But nobody knew.
- Nice.
- Well done.
Now...
The person who spotted the lies the best is...
Jang Hoon.
- He will be gifted...
- Amazing.
with the signed album...
that was just released on July 6,
i-dle's mini ninth album, "We Made."
(Bowing)
- I am jealous.
- The signed CD.
- You were...
- I'm so jealous.
- I envy you.
- But seriously,
- Only I get to have this.
- Congratulations.
- Don't give them.
(Brother School)
(The classroom is empty before the start of Period 2.)
I knew it. We're the first to arrive.
- We're the first to arrive again.
- Goodness.
- They are late.
- They are.
I hate waiting.
Remember what happened last year?
We came to take this classroom,
and we lost to them miserably.
I remember.
(Last year, i-dle came to take over Brother School.)
(But they lost brutally to the brothers.)
We are determined to take over the classroom this time.
- Yes!
- We got this.
- In 3, 2, 1.
- Go, team!
We are determined today.
- We got this.
- Amazing.
- We won.
- Why...
is it so loud here?
- Teacher!
- Hey!
- Come in.
- We are taking over this classroom.
- All right.
- I thought you went to Jeju Island.
- You did?
This classroom is ours.
Why did your attitudes change so much?
People might think you're here to take over the school.
We are.
You think we're here for no reason?
We even prepared our very own secret weapon.
You did?
- Come on out.
- Come on.
(Shin Young the Secret Weapon enters.)
(She's full of energy from the beginning.)
I guess this is possible with Shin Young.
- Of course.
- She can do this.
Hello, I am a former member of the girl group Celeb Five,
I am the new member of i-dle,
Shin Young. Hello, everyone.
(The guest member of i-dle, Shin Young)
From now on, we are...
- i... Big i-dle!
- Big i-dle!
They are not in sync.
- They are out of sync.
- They are not in sync.
There's obviously a power struggle.
Now, it's time for the classroom turf war...
between Team Big i-dle and Team Adults.
The game title is...
"Challenge! Describe the Dance."
It's actually quite hard.
- It sounds hard.
- "Challenge! Describe the Dance."
- Describe the dance.
- Describe.
You have to watch a clip and describe the dance.
Then your teammates will listen and try dancing it.
They score a point when they get the singer and title right.
Yes.
- Let's begin with the brothers.
- Okay.
Shall we begin with the adults?
- Let's go!
"Challenge! Describe the Dance."
I think it'll be very frustrating.
- Now... Start.
- All right.
Listen to me well.
The clip is not playing yet.
You open your pinkie finger and use it as a mic.
- Lee Jung Hyun.
- "Wa" by Lee Jung Hyun.
You got it.
Did you see that?
- All right.
- Raise your right hand...
up.
And jump.
(Second song, "I'm Your Girl" by S.E.S.)
- Jump. Move to the left.
- No.
- And move to the right.
- Don't move your body.
- Stay still.
- Don't move.
What's the song by S.E.S.?
"I'm Your Girl."
"I'm Your Girl." Correct.
- Okay.
- No way.
This is...
("Coming of Age Ceremony" by Park Ji Yoon)
Your arm... No, your elbow.
- The right elbow...
- Yes.
- No, raise your arm.
- Raise your arm.
Raise one arm.
And grab your elbow with the other arm.
Then move your wrist...
- left and right.
- Like this?
- That's it.
- Like this.
- There's a dance like this?
- That's it.
- There's no dance like that.
- And move your hip.
- This is it.
- That's it.
"Abra..."
- "Abracadabra" by Brown Eyed Girls.
- No.
- No?
Be precise.
- No.
- "First Love."
Lie on your stomach. Soo Geun.
- And your hips...
- Miss A.
- No, don't go all the way down.
- Okay.
Just your arms.
- Like this?
- Move your hips up and down.
(A rather inappropriate gesture)
That's it!
- What is this?
- Miss A.
- "Dancing Bad Girl" by Miss A.
- No.
- Pass.
- Next is Jang Hoon.
Jang Hoon.
This is difficult.
(What's the fourth question?)
He is stuck.
- This is...
- Hurry! Don't be so slow.
- He sounds so scary.
- Hurry!
- Your legs.
Stretch and bend your legs over and over again.
- Stretch and bend.
- And move to the side.
Move to the side while doing it.
"Gee."
"Gee" by Girls' Generation.
- "Gee."
- He's good.
"Gee" by Girls' Generation.
- Why are they so good?
- "Gee" is correct.
Pass. Come here.
Twist your two fingers...
and bring them together in the air.
- Bring them together.
- Like this?
- Twist your fingers.
- Twist?
"Baby One More Time" by Jewelry.
- Wrong.
- It's wrong!
- They say it's wrong.
- Wrong.
"One More Time" by Jewelry.
- Correct. That's right.
- Okay!
- He said, "Baby One More Time."
- There's no "Baby."
(They missed the right answer by a whisker.)
You know me, right? All right.
- Has it begun?
- It's begun.
- Hurry.
- My goodness!
(The sixth question, "Two of Us" by Chaeyeon)
- Your one arm.
- One arm.
Extend one arm out to the side.
- To the side.
- That's right.
And keep punching back and forth with your other hand.
- Go lower.
- Lower?
No. Move it horizontally. Back and forth.
And circle your other arm around.
It's too difficult.
Circle it around.
Don't move your left arm, you punk.
- I'm sorry.
- Ho Dong. You should do it.
- Circle your right arm.
- Spin it?
- Move back and forth.
- I get it.
- "Genuine" by KOYOTE.
- No. Move back and forth.
- Back and forth?
- Make it bouncy. The right arm.
How do we make it bouncy?
- With your right arm!
- Hang on.
Isn't Kyung Hoon an inflatable tube man? Wrong!
- Time's up.
- We can do this.
- I see. This is it.
- We can do better.
- We did well.
- It's too difficult.
Time's up.
- It was Chaeyeon.
- Okay.
- This is it, right?
- All right.
- So, Team Brothers...
- It's tricky.
- got four questions right.
- Four.
Team Big i-dle.
- It will be difficult.
- Now, we will begin...
Challenge! Describe the Dance.
(Challenge! Describe the Dance begins.)
All right. Left.
- With your left hand, - Left hand?
make a fist.
(The first question, "Catch Catch" by Choi Ye Na)
Push it down.
Diagonally.
Push it down diagonally.
- The Marine Corps.
- And the right.
- Do the same with the other hand.
- "A Real Man."
"A Real Man."
No. One at a time.
- This is good.
- One, two.
- I get it. "Catch Catch."
- "Catch Catch?"
- Is this it?
- Choi Ye Na.
- Correct!
- Okay.
- "Catch Catch" is correct.
- You go.
- Go.
- Next.
Well... Shoot a gun to one side.
(The second question, "Mr. Chu" by Apink)
Shoot a gun to one side.
- With one hand...
- "Gotta Go" by Chungha.
No. With just one hand.
- SUNMI.
- Hang on.
Then first, give a salute with one hand.
Give a salute with one hand and then shoot a gun with the hand.
No. To the other side. In the direction you saluted.
- Shoot a gun. Right.
- World War II.
"Gashina" by SUNMI.
- Incorrect.
- No.
Shoot a gun while making a "woo" sound.
- Woo.
- I see.
- Give a salute.
- Give a salute and...
- "Hoot" by Girls' Generation.
- No.
- What is this?
Give a salute and shoot a gun.
- Pass.
- You go.
- Okay.
- YUQI.
All right. With your right hand,
grab your left shoulder.
And shake cutely.
- Right.
- This is...
- No, this is...
- I see.
- What?
- It's... What's the title?
- Yes!
- Isn't this it?
- I get it.
- "Overdrive."
- "Overdrive" is correct.
- TWS.
- Okay. Go.
- Good. "Overdrive" is correct.
And...
Oh...
(The fourth question, "Red Flavor" by Red Velvet)
Spread your hands out wide.
- Spread my hands.
- I mean, bend your arms.
- Bend.
- Yes. And...
Bring your hand to your mouth one by one.
- What?
- One by one.
Eat it, Shin Young.
- "Something Happened in Bali."
- Step to the beat.
- With excitement.
- Yes.
- What?
- That's it. With your hands open.
Shin Young's moves are close.
But flip your hands back and forth.
- Flip back and forth.
- Flip back and forth?
Flip my hands? Is this it?
"Bboom Bboom" by MOMOLAND.
- No.
- No. That's not it.
Move your hands side to side.
Side to side. Pass.
- Turn around.
- Turn around?
(The dance is getting more and more mysterious.)
That's it.
- What?
- What is this?
- Pass.
- All right.
- MINNIE.
- Next.
- Hurry.
(The fifth question, "Boom Boom Bass" by RIIZE)
All right.
Brush your shoulder with your left hand.
- You're not supposed to dance.
- Brush your shoulder.
- My shoulder with my left hand?
- And...
Open your legs wide...
and move back and forth.
- That's it.
- Don't show them the moves.
Yes. That's it.
- Left hand?
- Like that.
(The fifth question, "Boom Boom Bass" by RIIZE)
All right.
Brush your shoulder with your left hand.
- You're not supposed to dance.
- Brush your shoulder.
- My shoulder with my left hand?
- And...
Open your legs wide...
and move back and forth.
- That's it.
- Don't show them the moves.
Yes. That's it.
- Left hand?
- Like that.
- Okay.
- That's it. What song is this?
- Then jump over here.
- It's so easy.
"Anacana" by Cho Hye Lyun.
- "Anacana?"
- No?
(A pretty reasonable deduction)
No.
Play the guitar.
- What is this?
- It's RIIZE!
- "RIIZE."
- "Play The Guitar."
- "Get a Guitar."
- No.
- What?
"Boom Boom Bass!"
- "Boom Boom Bass" is correct.
- Okay.
- Correct.
- You go.
- We have one question left.
- SHUHUA.
- You're running out of time.
- All right.
- Stretch both your arms.
Stretch both my arms.
(The sixth question, "Supernova" by aespa)
- Fold them.
One at a time.
- One at a time.
- Yes. Fold it one at a time.
- Your elbow.
- Elbow.
- Elbow?
- Bend your elbow one by one.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
- Like this?
Take one out.
Okay!
"My Bag" by i-dle.
- No.
- Time is...
- I get it.
"Kung Ddari Sha Bah Rah" by Clon.
No.
What do you do with the legs?
- You move your legs, one at a time.
- Don't dance.
- One at a time?
- Don't move.
What do you do with the legs?
- You move your legs, one at a time.
- Don't dance.
- One at a time?
- Don't move.
Yes. That's close.
- TWICE!
- Time's up.
- All right.
- So close.
It was so close.
The last question was...
- "Supernova" by aespa.
- It's "Supernova."
(They narrowly missed the last question.)
- It was "Supernova."
- Supernova
This is it.
So, the winner of this game is...
Team Brothers!
(Team Brothers wins the Class Contest.)
You won't be on TV.
- This won't go on air.
- You're the stars.
You can't be on TV.
(The unbothered Queen Card energy despite the loss)
(They failed to take the classroom, but they did captivate NEVERLAND.)
We're not good at this.
- All right.
- It was so close.
Our team only has vocalists.
- It's too difficult for foreigners.
- You're no match for us.
- You did well, though.
- Hey.
How was today?
Now that we're here on Men on a Mission,
it finally feels like we're really making our comeback.
Thank you so much for today.
We will come back again with our next album.
(We look forward to the next Classroom Contest.)
We hope your new song will be a great hit again.
We will always cheer for you.
- Okay.
- Let's go!
- Good luck!
(The K-pop Leader Special)
(U-Know Yunho, Seo Eun Kwang Hyojung, Jaehyun)
(Congratulations on transferring!)
(The original "Congratulations!")
(Its sister product is "I'm Sorry!")
(Jaehyun must be amazing as well.)
(I can't do that.)
(Accurate meta-cognition from the Gen Z leader)
(I'm a wimpy leader.)
(Even the leader turns into a wimp in front of her agency.)
(Who's BTOB's main vocalist? Seo Eun Kwang versus Lee Chang Sub)
(Chang Sub can't sing "Golden.")
(A crisis for the vocal-type leader)
(Shaky eyes at the appearance of an unexpected rival)
(My specialty?)
(Young people these days don't do that.)
(The Gen Z leader is different from young people these days.)
(Leader Myeong's specialty show)
(This is the 2nd-generation slapstick!)
(Let's see how flexible you are.)
(Yes, sir.)
(I like that attitude.)
(Am I going to join Ho Dong's clan?)
(Leader Myeong successfully joined Ho Dong's clan.)
(I can't get away from the idol leaders.)
(The best leaders with different colors are coming.)
("Wicked Game" by USPEER)