- Stop talking nonsense.
- What's going on?
- That's ridiculous.
- No, it's not.
Now that the seasons have changed,
we should eat some seasonal food to boost our energy.
What are you guys talking about?
Eating three meals a day keeps you healthy, don't you think?
- Do you eat at regular times?
- Be quiet!
- The big sisters are here.
- Oh, my. Hello!
- What's going on?
- No matter what they say,
laughter is what really keeps you healthy.
(Laughing)
(It naturally boosts everyone's energy.)
- Did you...
- Laughter brings good luck.
Did you plan this while waiting outside?
- No, we didn't.
- Did you plan...
- to laugh together?
- No, we didn't plan it.
- What are you talking about?
- Let's do it again.
No matter what they say,
laughter is what really keeps you healthy.
(Laughing)
(They make everyone feel invigorated again.)
- Did you really not plan this?
- No, we didn't.
- You didn't?
- We didn't.
They have such good teamwork when they didn't even plan it.
- Of course.
- They're just amazing.
- We can read each other's mind.
- Guys.
- Let us introduce ourselves.
- Okay.
- We are...
- Yes.
from We Are Moms High School.
- My joints still work perfectly.
- I see that.
- She's still got it.
- I am Kim Ji Sun.
I'm back here after a long time. I'm Lee Kyung Sil, Gangnam Legs.
(Gangnam Legs Lee Kyung Sil)
- She's here.
- Hi. Let me introduce myself.
Today, I left my testosterone behind and came here as a feminine lady.
- I'm Cho Hye Lyun.
- A feminine lady?
A feminine lady?
- A feminine lady.
- A feminine lady?
- Hye Lyun, what happened?
- A feminine lady.
You lost a lot of weight. Okay. Let's move on.
No need for a long explanation.
I'm your forever pretty little girl.
I'm Kim Hyo Jin. It's so good to see you all.
I'm so happy to see you all.
I see many people I haven't seen in a while.
- It's been a while.
- It's been a while, indeed.
Kyung Sil and Hye Lyun came here not long ago...
Hye Lyun came on this show many times before.
Kyung Sil has been on this show before as well.
But Ji Sun and Hyo Jin...
have never been here before.
- Ho Dong.
- Is this their first time here?
- I understand why he's angry.
Your blood vessels might burst due to high blood pressure.
I guess you didn't want to see us at all.
Don't be ridiculous.
I'm the one who should be saying that.
- Why?
- Exactly.
You should've invited me before.
- That's right.
- Even though we invited you...
You're the boss here.
Aren't you the one who decides...
- who should be invited here?
- Exactly.
- That's right.
- You should've invited me here.
- Because you never invited me, - Right.
- I couldn't be here until now.
- Right.
That's not the case. I heard how things worked here.
Ho Dong doesn't pick the guests.
But he receives the list of potential guests...
and filters them. "Don't invite Kim Ji Sun."
- "Remove Kim Hyo Jin too."
- Really?
- That's how things work here.
- You haven't changed at all.
- His face shows his answer.
- You did that...
when you hosted "Strong Heart" too.
- You haven't changed at all.
- She must be one of his victims.
Hold on. The two of you...
- He did it to us too.
- He did it to us on "Star King."
- He did it on "Star King."
- He never changes.
- Hyo Jin, I was nice to you...
when you were on "Strong Heart."
That's true. He adored me.
I worked with Ho Dong on "Star King..."
when I was pregnant and...
- when I was back to a flat belly.
- You had babies back-to-back.
My belly went from big to flat...
- so many times.
- Big to flat.
Ho Dong and Kyung Sil met on "Experience Life."
- That's right.
- Yes, that's true.
- Ho Dong was one of the guests.
- Oh, right.
- He came on the show as a guest.
- That was a really long time ago.
- She hosted "Experience Life."
Kyung Sil was the MC...
when I went on "Experience Life,"
where I carried a lot of briquettes on my back.
- So he's dressed like a briquette?
- It was a one-day work experience.
- Yes. I did my best.
- It's a nostalgic old show.
The guests rode a unicorn prop on "Experience Life," right?
- Ho Dong couldn't.
- Why?
- The unicorn broke.
- Really?
- The unicorn broke?
- Yes.
- It couldn't handle his weight.
- The guests went up into the air...
to put the money into the donation box.
- Actually, Hye Lyun...
- Yes?
We didn't know this either.
She has appeared on the show...
- more than any other guest.
- That's right.
- Really?
- I didn't know that.
- How many times has she been here?
- Twelve times.
- Twelve times?
She has joined us as a guest for both our regular episodes...
(She was in 14 episodes, including her time as a special guest.)
- and special segments.
- Oh, my.
- Hyo Jin.
- Yes?
You must be very close to Hye Lyun.
- That's right. Yes?
- Since she came here 12 times,
she could've brought you here at least once.
- Exactly.
- She definitely could have.
- But she only cares about herself.
- You see...
That's not the case.
You can't ask for such a thing when you're invited to this show.
- What do you mean...
- If I had brought her with me,
I could've been taken off the guest list.
- I might have lost my spot too.
- Really? You shouldn't ask for it?
- She fell victim.
- That's right.
- You could've asked at least once.
- No.
Shin Young, you're a regular cast here.
If someone asks you to help them get cast, would you do it?
- I wouldn't.
- It's hard.
- Indeed.
- We wouldn't do that.
- That hurts my feelings.
- Is that so? I see.
- By the way...
- The oldest one.
- Oh, he was here?
- Hi.
- He's still on this show.
Sang Min, you and I used to be like co-workers.
- Yes.
- Really?
- We worked with the same agency.
- That's right.
- Oh, I see.
We hung out at team get-togethers and had a great time.
- Right.
- Since you left the agency,
it hasn't been doing so well.
- It's struggling a lot.
- Of course.
Give the CEO a call sometime. Seriously.
- Now we know its current status.
- That's right.
- I see what that means.
- I didn't know that.
- To be honest, Yeong Cheol...
- Yes.
- I'm forever grateful toward him.
- Why?
He prevented all the accidents I could've been in.
- What? What accidents?
- While driving,
you feel tired or sleepy...
- sometimes.
- That's right.
You can just call Yeong Cheol when you feel that way.
Then he will keep talking to keep you awake...
for however long it takes.
He always brings up new topics.
- He keeps you awake?
- Yes.
- I go to Cheonan once a month.
- Right.
I give him a call whenever I drive there.
- She always calls me.
- "Are you going to Cheonan again?"
"All right. You see, Yeong Ja..."
- He tells me a lot of stories.
- He's amazing.
She must've heard that about me from someone.
One day, she called me. I said, "What's up, Ji Sun?"
She said, "Hey, I don't know exactly what it means,"
"but I heard I just had to call you when I was stuck in traffic."
"What does it mean?"
So I started chatting with her.
"Where should I begin? Shall I tell you about Yeong Ja?"
After talking on the phone for 45 minutes,
she said, "Olympic Highway is all clear now. Bye."
- Then she hung up the phone.
- It's so good.
- By the way, Hyo Jin...
- Yes?
Pretty Little Girl, didn't you miss me, the little Soo Geun?
What's going on between you two?
Of course, I missed you.
Goodness. Be patient.
Just wait. I have something to give you.
Oh, my. Really?
- That was such a seductive comment.
- We share a bond.
Little people like us understand each other.
- Two little people met.
- Exactly.
I've never seen Soo Geun blushing before.
- His face turned red.
- He likes it.
- Here we go.
- What are they doing?
- You should see that in person.
- Soo Geun.
- He must be so happy.
(He's become a big fan of Hyo Jin's.)
- That's our transfer form.
- Thank you.
Please approve our transfer.
- They look great together.
- You should see it in person.
- Exactly.
- That's her trademark.
- Her timing is impeccable.
- Indeed.
I've been doing the same move for a long time.
- She also told me not to get angry.
- Are you giving that to me?
- Shin Young is now a regular cast.
- Right.
- I'm very grateful toward her.
- I see.
Kyung Sil and I host a segment called "New Woman" on YouTube.
- Right. It became a big hit.
- Our subscriber count...
- wouldn't go over 100,000.
- Right.
We just couldn't wait to get past 100,000 subscribers.
Not long ago, Shin Young joined us as a guest.
After that, we finally hit well over 100,000 subscribers.
- And it got over 1.5 million views.
- Exactly.
- Thanks to Shin Young?
- That's right.
- By the time this episode airs, - We owe it to her.
- the views will go up even higher.
- That's right.
- She talked about her grandmothers.
- Shin Young.
- If you have some free time...
- Yes?
Ji Sun and I also co-host...
- a YouTube channel.
- That's right.
Can you please appear in our video so our channel can take off?
I'm going to give it a shot and do my best.
- Thank you.
- Oh, my.
- Hey.
- I should do it like this.
Can you do "Honey?"
- Oh, "Honey?"
- "Honey."
I shared a story about the song "Honey."
You see, "National Singing Contest..."
- is shot even in freezing weather.
- She used to host that show.
- That's right.
- "National Singing Contest."
They shoot the show even when it's boiling hot...
or freezing cold outside.
There are always elderly people in the front row.
- That's right.
- They were supposed to say,
"Singing Contest..."
- when I said "National."
- That's right.
- But they never seemed excited.
- They must've been cold and tired.
Even when the singer kneeled down while performing,
- they seemed unenthusiastic.
- They showed no reaction.
- But when Park Joo Hee sang...
- Park Joo Hee.
- The singer of "Honey."
- She's the singer of "Honey."
- Honey, did you not know?
- Right.
She came up on the stage.
- She was wearing revealing clothes.
- A sexy outfit.
She wears a dress even in the dead of winter.
- Even in the dead of winter.
- Even in the cold weather.
- In front of elderly people.
- She was wearing a jacket over it.
"Hello! I'm Park Joo Hee!"
(Singing)
(Shouting)
(Honey, did you not know?)
When she started performing,
- those elderly men...
- They seemed unenthusiastic, but...
(They would open their eyes widely.)
(Their energy was instantly recharged.)
(Dancing)
They suddenly seemed so excited.
(They magically forgot all about the weather.)
(Honey, do you now know it's love?)
- "Park Joo Hee!"
- Elderly men were always like that.
They were just amazed.
Park Joo Hee's "Honey" is like...
- a defibrillator for them.
- The song...
Since she shared this story,
the song has been making a recovery.
- It's been making a comeback.
- It's been blowing up again.
- It's "comeback," not "recovery."
- Oh, it's not "recovery?"
- Doesn't it recover from an injury?
- It's "comeback."
The transfer form to Men on a Mission.
Names, Lee Kyung Sil, Cho Hye Lyun, Kim Ji Sun, and Kim Hyo Jin.
(Names: Kim Ji Sun, Lee Kyung Sil, Cho Hye Lyun, Kim Hyo Jin)
First, they wrote down their nicknames.
Kyung Sil's nickname is Hogirl Sister.
I used to run my YouTube channel called "Hogirlsister."
- It has now closed down.
- Right.
When I uploaded videos regularly on that channel,
- people called me Hogirl Sister.
- Hogirl Sister.
- That nickname suits you.
- Indeed.
She has such a hearty and refreshing laugh.
- That's right.
- It makes you happy.
- And she's so cool.
- She has a loud, refreshing voice.
Next up is Hye Lyun.
What's this?
You wrote, "Barbie."
- Does it mean food?
- No.
- Food is the best medicine.
- It's Barbie as in...
- No, that's not it. Listen.
- Food is the best medicine?
- Food is the best medicine.
- Food keeps her energetic.
- It's Barbie as in doll.
- Let's let her explain.
- What?
- Barbie, the doll.
- Barbie?
- When I first met my husband...
- I've never heard that nickname.
- I mean, while we were dating, - Yes.
I did my makeup nicely.
- He told me I looked like Barbie.
- Really?
They really are meant to be.
That's exactly my point.
They call each other nicknames that nobody else calls them by.
- Barbie, the doll.
She's in that phase where she craves food.
No, that's not what the nickname means.
- It doesn't mean food?
- No.
Next, Ji Sun's nickname is...
- What does this mean?
- What is it?
- What does "BB" mean?
- What's "BB?"
- BB.
- Is it a Japanese word?
- I think it's a shortened word.
- You gave me this nickname.
- I did?
- Just brushing against each other,
my husband and I end up having a baby.
- That's what "BB" means.
- Oh, right.
- "BB?"
- Yes.
- BB.
- I gave her another nickname.
It's BU that stands for blessed uterus.
- "BU?"
- She gave me that nickname too.
- I have so many nicknames...
- It's better...
than "the queen of fecundity."
I'm called the queen of fecundity,
- the queen of childbirth, - Right.
and the queen of having plenty of eggs.
- She has a lot of eggs.
- What does it mean?
- It means she has a high egg count.
- It means I have a lot of eggs.
- She means her ovarian reserve.
- Eggs.
- She has a high egg count.
- It means she's very fertile?
- I'm also called...
- It's the best.
Childbirth-Cassandra...
- and Reproduction-Cassandra.
- "Reproduction?"
Reproduction-Cassandra?
- And BU.
- I have many of such nicknames.
- She has a lot of such nicknames.
- Ji Sun used to be called...
the queen of fecundity.
But now, we should call her the "original" queen of fecundity.
- Why?
- It's because...
- Jung Ju Ry gave birth...
- Oh, that's right.
- to her fifth child last year.
- Oh, I didn't know that.
- She has 5 sons.
- You have 4 kids.
- I have four kids.
- She broke your record.
- Then have another baby.
- Ju Ry has one more child.
I'm out of eggs now.
- What does that mean?
- Now she has a closed uterus.
- Her uterus is closed for business.
- I'm out of eggs now.
She should be called No Eggs.
- Eggs...
- She has no eggs now.
- "No Eggs?"
- I'm out of eggs now.
It was a total ruckus uterus.
- She has no eggs.
- "Ruckus uterus."
- These ladies have no filter.
- He's feeling shy.
- Why?
- Ho Dong, laugh.
- Ho Dong.
- What's wrong?
- I...
- We're only telling the truth.
- What's wrong with that?
- All of our uteruses are closed.
- I don't understand...
- I just don't...
- Ho Dong...
usually gets embarrassed when we talk...
- He gets embarrassed.
- about things like this.
- He feels shy.
- I don't understand such jokes.
- Okay. We'll talk about food later.
- You don't understand?
- Wait just a little longer.
- On a side note...
- Since I was pregnant...
- Even when you were on "Star King."
- Yes, I was pregnant.
- When she was on "Star King..."
This might be a little bit of an exaggeration,
but she came to the shoot...
- a week before her due date.
- Exactly.
- Then she took a break.
- Right.
- She came back only in a week.
- That's right.
- I was really amazed.
- You see...
- She had a natural birth.
- I thought she was amazing.
- Didn't you...
- Didn't she need time to recover?
stay at a postpartum care center?
Yes, I did. I stayed at a postpartum care center.
I went into the delivery room to have the baby.
- I walked with my pregnant belly.
- Yes.
I groaned from the labor pain while walking in.
I saw an elderly lady sitting in front of the delivery room.
Her daughter-in-law was in the delivery room,
having been in labor for four hours.
- There were several delivery rooms.
- Right.
It took me only 35 minutes to have my baby.
Then I walked out of the delivery room.
- My goodness. Really?
- And...
The patient rooms were right across the hall.
The elderly lady asked, "Didn't you just go in there?"
I said yes.
She asked, "You came out already?"
So I said yes.
- Her daughter-in-law was in labor.
- She said, "My daughter-in-law..."
"has been in there for five hours."
- She had childbirth experience, - That's right.
- so the runway was wide open.
- Exactly.
"The runway was wide open?"
I had my first baby, second baby
- Third baby, fourth baby - Third baby, fourth baby
- The runway was open wide - Then your uterus was closed.
- It was like a paved road.
- It's like a children's song.
Here's the thing about Ji Sun that I find truly amazing.
- She has four children.
- Yes.
- She delivered them all naturally.
- That's right.
- And she breast-fed all of them.
- Really?
Breast milk is packed with all the nutrients...
- that a baby needs to grow.
- It has all the nutrients.
- Absolutely.
- I heard...
colostrum was amazing for babies.
Since I heard it was best to breast-feed a baby,
I bought a freezer...
only to store my breast milk.
There were five sections in the freezer.
And I packed all of those five sections...
with my breast milk.
- You produced a lot of breast milk.
- It must've been thick and sticky.
- Oh, I see.
- When you freeze breast milk,
- it turns yellowish.
- That's right.
One day, my mother-in-law came over to my house...
and opened my freezer. She was surprised.
"Hey, why did you buy so much beef bone soup?"
She thought it was beef bone soup.
There must have been a crazy amount of breast milk.
- How much can you pump...
- She thought it was beef bone soup.
- Because it was milky.
- It looked like beef bone soup.
- It's a little bit yellowish.
- It looks like beef bone soup...
- It's milky.
that has been simmered for a long time.
- Frozen breast milk?
- She froze some in advance.
- But it was only possible...
- Right. Exactly.
because she produced a lot of breast milk.
I produced too little breast milk.
- Really?
- It just wouldn't come out.
When I pumped, I had to squeeze out every last drop...
just like getting the very last bit of toothpaste.
(She never gave up, filled with motherly love.)
- It was hard.
- Ji Sun can imitate the sound...
of a breast pump so well.
- Indeed, yes.
- I think she imitates it so well...
- because she did it four times.
- No one in Korea has ever done it.
When you turn it on, a breast pump sounds like this.
(Imitating a gurgling sound)
(Imitating a breast pump's sucking sound)
(It's working well.)
- This is what it sounds like.
- That's right.
- You see...
- You really pulled it off.
- This is the world's first attempt.
- I had to pull it off.
I've never heard that before.
- You've never heard it before?
- No.
It sounds like this when breast milk flows really well.
And it sounds like this when breast milk doesn't come out.
It's completely different.
(Both my breast pump and I cry.)
- Today's guests are hilarious.
- People don't change.
- It refuses to pump anything out.
- Hyo Jin is...
It'd be hilarious...
- if they do it together.
- Oh, my.
Laugh, Ho Dong.
- The one who laughs is first-class.
- That's right.
Hyo Jin's nickname is what I expected.
- What is it?
- It's a legendary nickname.
- Pretty Little Girl.
- It'll be her nickname forever.
- It's my forever nickname.
- It suits her perfectly.
- Pretty Little Girl.
Hyo Jin, I heard you got a new nickname too.
- Really?
- Yes, I got pregnant naturally...
- at the age of 45.
- I see.
- So I'm known...
- Congratulations.
- as the icon of late-age pregnancy.
- That's right.
I got a new nickname, which is LPU.
- What does it stand for?
- Late-Age Pregnancy Uterus.
(Late-Age Pregnancy Uterus)
- I got the nickname LPU...
- Today...
- I got that nickname on the spot.
- She's incredible.
- Ho Dong, are you tired?
- Today's shoot is very tiring.
- Are you tired?
- Ho Dong usually...
- You should pull yourself together.
- He usually gets embarrassed...
- when we talk...
- Ho Dong, get it together.
- Get it together.
- What's wrong with this topic?
- What's wrong with it?
- I mean...
I just heard three years' worth of it.
- It makes him feel so embarrassed.
- But why?
- You came out...
- Why would you be embarrassed?
- of your mother's womb too.
- Right.
- Don't be shy. It's natural.
- It's a beautiful thing.
- You were born from there too.
- That's right.
- I was?
- Of course.
- Perhaps he hatched from an egg.
- Just like Bak Hyeokgeose?
I just popped into existence all by myself.
- You had the baby at a later age.
- Yes.
- How did your oldest child respond?
- Exactly.
- Well...
- They have a large age gap, right?
- They have an 8-year age gap.
- An 8-year age gap?
- How old is your oldest child?
- She's a seventh grader.
- She must be sensitive about it.
- Actually,
I couldn't think about having another baby...
- because my oldest child...
- I bet she was sensitive about it.
didn't want a younger sibling.
Usually, only children...
- want a younger sibling.
- That's right.
But my daughter was totally against the idea.
- She wanted all of our love...
- Right.
- for herself.
- That's right.
She saw some of her friends with puppies...
- and asked for a puppy.
- Right.
- She always said things like that.
- That's right.
- After I found out I was pregnant, - Oh, boy.
- I was so afraid to tell her.
- Of course.
- She might be shocked.
- That's right.
- I was afraid she might be shocked.
- She must've been shocked.
So my husband and I carefully picked the perfect day...
and told her the news very cautiously.
- When she was in a good mood?
- Yes.
"I El, Mommy has your younger sibling growing in her belly."
We broke the news to her really cautiously.
She reacted just as we had expected.
- She cried and made a scene.
- Really?
- She cried her eyes out, saying, - She wailed?
- "When did I ask for a sibling?"
- Right.
- "I never asked for a human."
- "A human?"
"Give birth to a puppy for me instead!"
"Give birth to a puppy for me!"
- "I don't need a human."
- That's hilarious.
- "I don't want a younger sibling."
- "I said..."
- "I wanted a puppy."
- Exactly.
- She wanted your love for herself.
- She didn't want a sibling.
You went overboard.
- You're lying.
- No.
- It's a true story. It's true.
- She asked you to have a dog?
- Jang Hoon, I would never...
- I know Hyo Jin.
She never goes too far.
- Exactly. I'm a pastor's wife.
- Jang Hoon...
He claims...
- I...
- That's true.
- I swear to the Almighty.
- Her husband is a pastor?
- "I swear to the Almighty."
- Really?
I'd never lie about my child, Jang Hoon.
- You see, Jang Hoon claims...
- My husband is a pastor.
Jang Hoon claims that you made it all up,
- but you just exaggerated a bit.
- Did you exaggerate a bit?
- You kept exaggerating it.
- You said she asked for a dog...
I said it to make people laugh, you know.
(Do you want me to be serious on a variety show?)
- Was I supposed to be serious?
- That's hilarious.
Calm. You're a pastor's wife.
- Wasn't I supposed to be funny?
- You're a pastor's wife.
- You just spiced up the story.
- She didn't make it up, though.
- It's a true story.
- She just spiced up the story.
- You exaggerated just a little bit.
- It really is a true story.
- You see, this is...
- I wanted the story to be funny.
Records are constantly broken in the entertainment industry.
Hyo Jin got pregnant naturally at the age of 45.
- That's amazing, right?
- Yes.
But recently, Han Da Gam...
- That's right. Han Da Gam...
- Han Da Gam...
got pregnant naturally at the age of 47.
- She's pregnant?
- Yes.
- She's pregnant.
- Da Gam is 47 and pregnant.
Tang Wei got pregnant...
- at the age of 48.
- Really?
- It was all over the media.
- That's right.
- Sang Min should have a baby.
- Hyo Jin.
- It's possible.
- Sang Min is trying...
- not to be too desperate.
- I understand.
Give him some good tips.
I shared my energy on "Strong Heart..."
- since many people wanted a baby.
- Yes!
- Yes, you did.
- Some people told me...
they actually got pregnant...
- thanks to my energy.
- Really?
But the important point is...
- that you should touch me.
- Like people touch dolhareubang.
You know Comedian Lee Byeong Jin, right?
- Comedian Lee Byeong Jin?
- He and his wife couldn't conceive.
- I ran into him at SBS.
- Right.
He was worried because he hadn't had a baby for a long time.
So I put his hand on my belly...
- You prayed for him.
- I prayed for him.
I prayed sincerely that he'd have a baby soon.
- Then his wife got pregnant.
- Hurry up and step forward.
I also met Jung In...
- when we starred on the same show.
- Right.
Here we go, here we go
Take my energy, receive it
- I shared my fecundity energy.
- That's right.
- Come on. Step forward already.
- Then she got pregnant.
- Share your energy with him too.
- Share your energy with Sang Min.
- Go and touch her belly.
- Instead of touching her belly...
Ji Sun, shoot your energy beam at Sang Min.
- Go ahead.
- Don't you have to hold his hand?
- Hold his hand.
- That works,
- but my energy works too.
- Of course.
- Join me.
- Give him support.
- Yes, support.
- Good vibes.
- Moral support.
Hold on. Move aside,
- or we'll get the energy.
- Go closer.
- The energy isn't for us.
- Let's go.
Go ahead, Jang Hoon. You never know.
When I give you the energy, suck it up. Okay?
Please open the door to a baby
- Here it goes - Here it goes
- Here it goes - Here it goes.
Take it!
(Gulping down)
- It'll work.
- Nice one.
- Let's go.
- Hold his hand.
- Yes, please.
- It'd be great...
- Open the door to a baby.
- if it actually works.
- Please.
- It...
You'll be blessed with good news this year.
- We...
- I'll pray for it to happen.
If we hear news about...
Sang Min having a baby, it'd be amazing.
- For real.
- Totally.
To everyone...
who's trying to have a baby later in life, including Sang Min,
- I hope you take courage from us...
- Yes.
- and receive good news.
- Nice.
Have lots of children.
Have many babies since Korea has a low birth rate.
- Yes.
- Please have lots.
Next, our transfer students...
wrote about their team.
- It says, "I Love You, Mom."
- Yes.
Isn't it the title of a play produced by Hye Lyun?
- Correct.
- Yes.
- Wasn't it about two years ago?
The play was with Kim Ji Sun, Kim Hyo Jin,
- Kim Hyo Jin.
- Jung Ka Eun, and me.
- It was a big hit back then.
- A major hit.
- Around 30,000 people...
- Didn't you go overseas?
- came to watch our play.
- They did a tour.
We even performed...
- in Sydney and LA...
- They went overseas to perform it.
and won the Grand Prize...
- at the Chuncheon Theater Festival.
- The Grand Prize.
We went on a nationwide tour.
- The play is still ongoing.
- Yes. The theater is where...
I also performed...
- "Educating Rita."
- Right.
I took over that theater.
- Did you take it over?
- Yes.
- Rent?
- I'm actually renting it.
- But it was a big hit.
- At times...
When talking about plays,
- Cho Hye Lyun's eyes shine.
- Right?
- It's because...
- She brightens up.
Only when we talk about plays does she become formal.
- I'm sorry. It just happens.
- Suddenly?
- Cho Hye Lyun is...
- For real.
She's "The King's Warden" of the play industry.
- Yes, "The King's Warden."
- Hye Lyun's passion is...
If there's Cho Hye Lyun in "I Love You, Mom,"
there's Jang Hang Jun...
- in "The King's Warden."
- Jang Hang Jun.
You're right.
Hyo Jin, Ji Sun, and Hye Lyun...
used to be in "I Love You, Mom."
This time Kyung Sil has...
- She's a new mom.
- Yes.
I'm curious.
Were you cast or was there an audition?
I was hoping for an audition, but there wasn't one.
But...
If there had been one, she might not have passed.
- Kyung Sil...
- But she's the best.
- Of course.
- The best.
She's the actress...
- from "Love and Ambition."
- Listen.
- A legend.
- She's a legend.
- Hye Lyun is the director, right?
- Yes.
How she treats Ji Sun and me is quite different from...
- how she treats Kyung Sil.
- Totally different.
- After all, she's a senior.
- To us,
she's like, "That's not right, Hyo Jin."
"Put in more emotions. Try again!"
To Ji Sun, she says, "That's not the right dialect."
- "Get it together, Ji Sun!"
- That's harsh.
- What about Kyung Sil?
- To Kyung Sil...
"Kyung Sil, everything was great, but..."
- In a small voice.
- She's right.
- "Everything was great, but..."
- Right?
- What about the hands?
- "How about like this?"
"Are you free tomorrow?"
"May I give you advice on how to act?"
- Oh, my.
- That's how she talks to Kyung Sil.
The problem with Kyung Sil is that she's from Jeolla Province.
She has to speak in the Gyeongsang Province dialect,
like one spoken...
- at Jagalchi Market in Busan.
- How?
- The dialect is tough.
- Of course.
- Is that so?
- Gyeongsang Province is like,
- "Did you eat? No? Let's eat."
- Right.
- It's hard.
- It sounds like this.
- The tones are like Mandarin.
- The intonations are different.
But Jeolla Province is more like,
- "What was that?"
- Correct.
Changing her dialect was tough for her.
- It's really tough.
- Of course.
It was a big challenge.
- She's from Gyeongsang Province.
- I see.
Ji Sun is also from Jeolla Province.
- I went through...
- We are from the same province.
the same tough process...
- in 2024.
- Correct.
A lot of trial and error.
(Speaking Mandarin)
"Did you eat?" I used the intonation...
- as if I were speaking Mandarin.
- She's amazing.
- Ji Sun learned the tones.
- Listen.
Kindergarten.
The intonation starts from the bottom.
- Yes.
- Kindergarten.
Correct. But when it comes to "mom,"
- it goes like this.
- The last letter goes down.
- So why say...
- Some words...
- "kindergarten" from below...
- start with a completely...
- and then say "mom" from the top?
- different intonation.
It drives me crazy.
Can't we start from the bottom, not the top, for "mom?"
- No.
- Why not?
- Mom.
- That's it.
- If I say it in a different tone...
- Mom.
- But...
- What difference does it make?
The feeling they give off is different.
But in the end, both of them...
- are good at it now.
- Totally.
- I'd ace the North Korean dialect.
- You'd be on a roll.
- Exactly.
- Please show us.
Come now, Cheol Dung. It is time to get up.
If you do not get up now, I will get angry.
- That's it.
- If you do not,
I could beat you to a bloody pulp.
Hurry up and get up.
Or else, I will launch a missile.
- I could totally do it.
- Amazing.
The North Korean dialect...
- would be so easy.
- Totally.
Of course.
- But that's not the case.
- I totally get it.
My grandma from my mom's side is from...
- Jeolla Province.
- I see.
- It's different, right?
- My grandma from my dad's side...
- is from Cheongdo.
- Oh, my.
- How is it?
- My Cheongdo grandma rarely cries.
- Gyeongsang Province grandmas.
- So how?
"My dear Shin Young had it tough from a young age, so she..."
(Cheongdo grandma)
(Leaving without finishing the sentence)
- She just leaves.
- Right.
- What about Jeolla Province?
- And Jeolla Province?
- My Jeolla Province grandma...
- Yes?
"My poor child. Really."
(Full of emotions from the very start)
- "Oh, dear."
- Seriously.
- The sentiment is different.
- She'd grab my arm...
- and start crying.
- Totally.
- And Cheongdo grandma?
- Cheongdo grandma.
- Cheongdo grandma...
- Are you crying, Grandma?
"No matter who comes, I don't care."
"As long as Shin Young gives it her best..."
"and sees it through..."
(Saying no more)
(A teasing manner of speaking)
(A master of emotional push-and-pull)
She just holds back.
- In short...
- The dialects differ.
The two overcame the difference between the Jeolla...
- and Gyeongsang dialects...
- They're different.
and accepted each other.
- Correct.
- How about...
- keeping the script as is...
- Yes?
- but changing the dialect?
- Right.
For example, performing in the Jeolla Province dialect this time.
- And in the Seoul dialect.
- Here's the thing.
- In Jeolla Province.
- You can just change the dialect.
That'd be a lot of work, Jang Hoon.
- Even without it...
- Jang Hoon,
are you willing to do it?
- Jang Hoon.
- In a different dialect.
- Sorry.
- You try it, Jang Hoon.
- Isn't your husband a pastor?
- Sorry. I apologized.
- Hye Lyun.
- I apologized, okay?
- Don't bully Jang Hoon.
Here's the thing. It did cross my mind.
What if we perform...
- in that region's dialect?
- Right.
- That'd be fun.
- Actually, the story...
is based on part of the writer's experience. It's about him...
- Mom.
- and his mom working...
at Jagalchi Market.
That's true.
- His mom?
- "Come."
"Look around. Grab a bargain."
- Yes?
- It's the key line.
"Come."
- "Look around. Grab a bargain."
It's weird, isn't it?
(But it's entertaining.)
- "Come."
- "Look around. Grab a bargain."
It's the trademark phrase...
- of Jagalchi Market.
- Right.
- How is it...
- It's weird.
- in the North Korean dialect?
- In North Korean dialect?
"Come. Look around. Grab a bargain."
- That's funny.
- It's like watching the news.
(Ho Dong is unstoppable.)
- It's too funny.
- "Come."
- "Look around. Grab a bargain."
I could sell Kaema Plateau potatoes in just one morning.
(Mr. "Star King" is having a blast.)
- It's too funny for a play.
- Exactly.
We can't get into character.
Getting into character is impossible.
What I recall is that...
my youngest sister is 12 years younger...
- than me.
- I see.
- Your younger sister?
- A North Korean woman...
looked after my sister...
as a babysitter for five years.
During those five years, my other younger sister...
You know how there's running in a track meet?
My other sister was bad at running.
My youngest sister was raised...
- hearing North Korean, right?
- Yes.
"Push ahead, sister!"
- It was so embarrassing.
- Come on.
- That's a lie.
- I'm serious.
- Impossible.
- No, I swear.
Do you swear?
- I swear.
- You swear?
- Yes, I totally swear.
- "Push ahead?"
Did she say "Push ahead?"
Push ahead!
- It's actually a thing.
- Someone...
dated a North Korean defector.
He kissed that North Korean defector.
After the kiss, the woman was like,
"Hey, I like this move."
It's real, okay?
- "Hey, I like this move?"
- "Hey, I like this move."
(Evaluation of the kiss: Excellent move)
I like this move.
- North Koreans actually say it.
- Right?
- Seriously?
- That's hilarious.
- Oh, dear.
- Funny, right?
- The dialects are so different.
- For real.
Next is about the four...
- This is a totally new item.
- What is it?
The transfer students...
- drew their friendship diagram.
- Friendship diagram?
- We got it ready.
- I see.
Here it is.
- What?
- That's the friendship diagram.
We drew one.
- If we take a look at each one...
- Okay.
First off, Hye Lyun and Kyung Sil's friendship.
- I see.
- Hye Lyun wrote "life mentor."
- That's right.
- Life mentor.
But weren't you two on different TV stations?
As for TV stations, I was at KBS...
- while Kyung Sil was at MBC.
- Right.
I met Kyung Sil...
- Hye Lyun.
- after I transferred to MBC.
People only remember Hye Lyun was in MBC...
- and not in KBS.
- True.
She was there for a while.
- I was in "My Mom."
- Right.
In what way is she your life mentor?
You see...
She got divorced first.
She also got remarried first.
(My dear mentor.)
- She did everything first.
- Kyung Sil...
- Ho Dong doesn't know how to react.
- She's done many firsts.
- She's not wrong.
- You...
- Ho Dong doesn't know how to react.
- My bad.
- Close your mouth, Kang Ho Dong.
- Close it.
She got divorced first,
- First?
- and then I got one.
She remarried...
- before I did.
- Before you did.
- And when bad things happened...
- Right.
Remember all the things she went through?
- When I was in a tough spot...
- Right.
The way she overcame it.
- No matter how hard times were, - Yes.
I saw how she overcame them in a wise way,
- That's right.
- and I followed in her steps.
- Since she is wise.
- That's right.
But when you're going through a really tough time,
a few words from someone who's already walked that path...
can be a huge source of comfort and strength.
- Yes.
- That's a gem.
Not long ago, I had a call with Kyung Sil.
- We talked about this and that...
- Yes.
and she said, "Fine, I will be your aunt."
And that was the most reassuring thing in the world to me.
Then she asked me to be her aunt from both sides of the family.
Because she looks more like a paternal aunt.
- She has paternal aunt vibes.
- Does she?
- She's a paternal aunt, for sure.
- That's right.
- Not like a maternal aunt.
- I know.
- She asked me to be both.
- But she said...
I told her that I would be whatever she wants.
That's so reassuring.
Next is Hye Lyun and Hyo Jin.
- Hyo Jin.
- With Hye Lyun.
- She wrote, "Awkward relationship."
- What?
- Why is it awkward?
- In the past.
- You did a lot of things.
- You had so many shows.
- It's in the past.
- Even that show.
- In the past, there was a man...
- In the past.
- that we competed over.
- Oh, that's right.
But the important thing is, he doesn't know that we loved him.
- He has no interest at all.
- He has no idea.
- Not even now?
- He has no interest at all.
- He doesn't even know?
- That's right.
- During "My Mom,"
- It was during that time.
- Seo Gyeong Seok played...
- What?
- My son.
- Hye Lyun's son.
- They were mother and son, - Gyeong Seok?
- and I played his girlfriend.
- The pretty one.
We both had a crush on him.
- Both of us.
- Back then, I was single.
I was single as well. We were all single.
(Oddly emphasizing that she was single)
- What was that?
- Why weren't you married?
- Do you think I was married?
- Right.
- We were all in our early 20s.
- But...
- Gyeong Seok was so popular.
- Yes.
- He has a smart image.
- That's right.
My character was a lady from a poor family with dark makeup.
"Gyeong Seok."
My lines were, "Endure it and tighten your belt."
Then one day, my makeup started getting prettier.
- She did that.
- She wanted to be pretty.
- Since you liked him.
You wanted to look pretty for Gyeong Seok?
- She wanted to look pretty.
- You wanted to look pretty?
I did not know that she had a crush on Gyeong Seok.
But something did seem off during our show.
- How?
- Her makeup started getting bright.
- When it was dark?
- It got brighter.
- She started wearing beauty makeup.
- Really?
- And her clothes started getting...
- It was...
- tighter to show her figure.
- a bit tight.
To show her shape?
The look in her eyes wasn't a motherly one.
- When she looked at him?
- Yes.
- She was supposed to say, - "Gyeong Seok."
"Gyeong Seok." But she started saying,
"Gyeong Seok."
- No way.
- That's how she went.
- Come on.
- That's a good one.
- She started holding his neck.
- "Gyeong Seok."
- Since she also liked him, - Yes.
- That's it.
- her instincts could tell.
- And I didn't want to fall behind.
- Sure.
- I used to draw tons of freckles, - Yes.
- but I got rid of all of them, - They all disappeared.
and my hair was in a tight ponytail.
And the funny thing is, when we had meals together,
I could tell that she liked Gyeong Seok.
- I could feel it as well.
- Yes.
But the important thing is,
- Gyeong Seok had no idea.
- None at all.
- He was doing fine.
- We're the only ones...
- having a tense exchange.
- Maybe he enjoyed it.
- No.
- It's not that?
- Did he find out?
- He had no idea?
- Sure. He found out later on.
- Oh.
- He got annoyed.
- Yes, later on,
he told me, "If you liked me that much,"
- "you should have told me."
- What?
- That gave me butterflies.
- That does.
Would it have been different if I had told him?
"If I had told you, would things have been different?"
"Nothing would have changed."
- "It would have been the same."
- He's a total T type.
- He should still know.
- "I can hear about your feelings."
- What makes him so attractive?
- What?
- Gyeong Seok?
- He's highly educated.
He's an elite.
- Seoul National University.
- He's an elite.
As a comedian back then, that was the best.
- He's a gentleman.
- He has good manners.
- He's very kind.
- He's a gentleman.
- He's a good guy.
- That's right.
- Yoon Seok is an elite as well.
- Yes, and...
- Yoon Seok is tall and is an elite.
- Yoon Seok is too tall.
The problem with Yoon Seok is that he smells of oriental medicine.
He smells so much of oriental medicine.
- You're right.
- You can't breathe next to him.
- I'm crying.
- When you're in the hallway,
if you smell oriental medicine from somewhere,
then you know that Yoon Seok has arrived.
- If you open up his bag, - Come on.
you can see that he has all kinds of medicine.
That's why he met a wife who is...
- an oriental medicine doctor.
- Right.
Thanks to his oriental medicine doctor wife,
- he can stay healthy until now.
- Sure.
- He would have died.
- Yoon Seok is hanging in there.
- He keeps getting acupuncture.
- Yes.
But if your makeup kept getting prettier,
- then didn't...
- Yes, so...
Eventually, the producer called us both in.
"What are you two doing? Are you kidding me?"
"Go back and get black stains on yourselves."
- So we went...
- Producer Ahn.
- We got in big trouble like that.
- Gosh.
- When did the crush end?
- Yes.
- For me, there was a reason.
- What?
Around that time, I was shooting the drama "All About Eve."
-Sure, we know that show.
- Yes.
The main leads were Jang Dong Gun...
- and Han Jae Suk.
- Han Jae Suk.
- Two of the most iconic...
- Gosh.
- handsome stars back then.
- The best.
- That must have been so easy.
- Yes.
- Then you can let Gyeong Seok go.
- So I...
- I went to the shoot, - Sure.
- and the dazzlingly handsome men...
- Sure.
- were so kind...
- Really?
- and so full of manners.
- Yes, sure.
They said, "Hyo Jin, I'm such a fan,"
- and held my bags...
- Goodness.
- and opened the car door for me.
- Gosh.
Can you imagine how wonderful it is?
- I was so happy.
- Sure.
And when I went back to the "Today Is a Good Day" set,
Gyeong Seok, Myung Soo, Yoon Seok, and Hyun Chul were there.
Such scruffy-looking guys.
- That's what it felt like.
- The sudden gap.
- It's a bit harsh, but...
- Their faces...
- She has high standards.
- Yes.
- I know, it's just...
- It's personal preference.
She's close to them,
- so she can say that.
- They are...
- great people, - Yes.
- but back then...
- Sure.
Think of it, you guys.
- After seeing Jang Dong Gun...
- Of course.
- and Han Jae Suk,
- Kim Hyun Chul.
- even the shining Gyeong Seok...
- Sure.
- could be forgotten completely.
- You need to broaden your horizons.
- Exactly.
- What about things...
- Anyway...
- between you and Hye Lyun?
- Yes?
Did you stay awkward until recently, or...
Sure. So we were a little awkward around each other...
- after both liking Gyeong Seok.
- Yes.
But somehow, we ended up...
going on a trip abroad together.
- I asked her to come with me.
- The two of you?
She asked me to come with her.
- To Saipan.
- Yes. I was scared that...
she would hit me if I didn't go.
So I went there with her.
- "Come with me, Hyo Jin."
- Yes.
- So, we went.
- Just the two of you?
- Just the 2 of us.
- Yes. Just us.
- It was because...
Jung Sun Hee was supposed to come,
but she said she couldn't,
- so it was just the two of us.
- Yes,
- it ended up being just us.
- She was very awkward.
- It must have been fun.
- But...
something happened that worsened the relationship.
- Why?
- While you were on the trip?
Back then, Hye Lyun's diet Tae Bo video...
- The diet video.
- blew up,
and she was preparing a second season.
I was getting in shape.
- So, in order to get ready, - Yes.
she would practice...
- I needed to get the form down.
- every night.
But she did it with absolutely nothing on,
all naked.
- Why?
- All naked.
- Why would you?
- Before going to bed.
- She was naked, and went...
- Why?
"Jjo."
- Really?
- I'm wearing a skirt right now,
but she would lie in bed and go, "Jjo."
- "Jjo."
- Censor it.
- You need to censor it.
- Are your knees okay?
- Right next to you?
- I know.
- Next to you?
- We were awkward back then,
- but she did that naked.
- I know.
- But...
- I felt so bad.
I was so embarrassed,
- and didn't know where to look.
- But we had ambient lighting.
- Whatever.
- It was dim.
Can you not see if it's ambient lighting? I saw it all.
- You can see it all.
- So I said,
- "Hye Lyun, at least put on..."
- You guys were awkward.
"some underwear," and she said,
- "Who cares? We're both women."
- Really?
(She couldn't escape the Tae Bo trap.)
- Come on.
- But then...
- I'm sorry.
- Then what?
- It was too much.
- I can imagine it.
- So...
After that trip, there was a clear distance for a while.
- Is that so?
- We recently got much closer...
- with "I Love You, Mom."
- Gosh, you guys are finally close.
- Yes.
- You're like friends.
- That's so funny.
- It was so hard.
Next is Hye Lyun's relationship with Ji Sun.
- What?
- She wrote,
- "Someone I want to be like."
- What?
This is... Actually,
there was a show called "Seo Taisoon and Boys."
- Yes.
- I danced there.
And then, at that time,
- I got an offer as a DJ...
- Oh, this one.
- at a nightclub.
- That's it.
I will tell it. This is how it happened.
At that time,
- I was performing at a nightclub.
- Right.
- My manager back then said that...
- Yes.
I needed to watch Ji Sun's show, no matter what.
- Really?
- So...
I brought my notepad with me...
and went to the Capital Nightclub in Itaewon.
- "Capital?"
- I needed to study it.
- She came out with a water bottle.
- Yes.
"Come out with a water bottle."
- She did the wave.
- The wave.
"Do the wave."
- You wrote it down?
- She went like this...
and shook her shoulders.
- I wrote it all down.
- You wrote it?
Yes, and I tried it, but it didn't work for me.
I couldn't, so I just did this.
- Like this?
- But...
- I couldn't do the wave.
- It's like this.
She did that. Show us how you did it.
- She was amazing back then.
- She did that.
As soon as you get out there...
- We have the turntable.
- The turntable.
- There's a turntable, so...
- She's so good.
"Ladies and gentlemen,"
"please don't hesitate to get on the floor."
"And make yourself fantastic."
(Going crazy)
- The water.
- What?
Goodness.
(Grabbing)
(This is the Summer Swag of the 1990s.)
(It feels like she is drenched in alcohol, not water.)
- Goodness.
- "Study it."
- Like this.
- I went like that.
- Gosh.
- Go on.
- That's how I went.
- So...
(The Wave Queen turned the classroom into a nightclub.)
- You're so...
- I really splashed that.
- The scholarly Hye Lyun.
- I studied that.
I didn't say, "Ladies."
"Shake it."
- "Noona body shake it. One, two."
- "Noona body shake it?"
And then I had nothing to do next.
- What next?
- I just went, "Jjo."
Someone threw a cherry tomato at me.
- They threw it like this?
- So I went...
Like this.
(Swiftly gulping it down)
- Come on.
- It's true. I really ate it.
- You're lying.
- It's true.
- Seriously.
- You ate it like that?
It's true. I ate it.
- That's because...
- That's why...
Goodness.
You can do that because you can dance.
I envy you.
Kyung Sil always said this...
because I could do the body waves well.
"Ji Sun, if I could dance like you,"
"I'd be dangerous."
- I envy people who dance well.
- Right.
Next up is the relationship...
between Hyo Jin and Kyung Sil.
This is what's written.
- "My fists are itching."
- Why?
- Who wrote that?
- You say this when you're mad.
- "My fists are itching?"
- You guys are not close?
"My fists are itching?" I never wrote that.
I would have said,
- Goodness.
- "My fists are itching."
- Why?
- This is an old story.
When I was just starting out as a rookie,
I worked with Kyung Sil on a segment in "Today Is a Good Day."
- Back then, I used to drink often.
- She'd drink so well.
She would mix drinks.
We drank together.
You're the one who mixed those drinks.
I had a huge get-together after another show,
and then came straight to shoot "Today Is a Good Day."
My stomach was burning like crazy.
Because you drank so much.
- I was in so much pain.
- Right. The hangover.
"I wish I could just..."
- "have some spicy soup."
- Right.
- "If I could just..."
"have a sip, my stomach would feel better."
I was desperate for it.
Then it was lunchtime.
We were going to order lunch,
and people were choosing what to eat.
The restaurant we were going to order from...
had a spicy kalguksu dish.
I didn't want any of the noodles.
- I just wanted to have the broth.
- Just the broth.
So I ordered that.
I called Kyung Sil. "You should also have lunch, Kyung Sil."
"What would you like to have?"
She said, "I won't have lunch."
"You can go ahead and enjoy."
So we ordered several dishes, and the food was delivered.
We had a variety of food.
I was about to eat...
when I noticed her peeking around in the back.
Goodness.
- So I...
- The smell spreads out.
- The smell of food.
- Yes.
She was doing that.
So I said, "Don't just stand there."
"Come and eat at least a bit."
So she reluctantly said,
- "Should I?"
- "Should I? What did you order?"
Then she came and sat with us.
There were various dishes, so she tried one and said,
"This is too sweet."
She tried another and said, "This is too salty."
"I don't like delivery food..."
"because it's too intense."
Then she spotted the dish I ordered.
"What's that one?"
"It's kalguksu." "Is that so?"
"This one tastes good."
Then she took my food and...
- She gulped it down.
- Don't do it.
- Gosh.
The broth!
Yes.
- Seriously!
- It would have been really good.
(She lost her hangover soup.)
"This is the most tolerable one."
"I left the noodles, Hyo Jin."
- She didn't need the noodles.
- She was...
- She didn't want the noodles.
- I just wanted the broth.
- My fists are itching.
- I was upset.
Right.
"Goodness. I don't care even if she's a senior."
"Should I just blow up and quit the industry?"
"Leave the industry."
- "Should I just do it..."
- It's been a while...
"and go back to my hometown?"
- That briefly crossed my mind.
- I guess you didn't do it.
- Of course.
- The kalguksu.
- I...
- I had that urge briefly.
- I felt really bad.
- She's a good senior.
- Now...
- That's the conclusion.
- Yes.
Finally, the four friends wrote what they wanted to do.
What's "To the Eagle" here?
- "To the eagle."
- What's "To the Eagle" here?
That's my new song.
- A song?
- I...
Is this an adaptation as well?
- This is a rally song.
- Right.
We have the World Soccer Games...
- and the Asian Athletic Games.
- Right.
Everyone's lives are tough right now too.
So it's a song...
- that encourages our people.
- That's nice.
- Why the eagle?
- There are many other birds.
- Eagles symbolize...
strength and spirit.
- Power.
- If you read the Bible, you find...
that the eagle’s embrace,
strength, and spirit...
are a great source of comfort...
- It's encouraging.
- and encouragement.
- So I wanted to sing about that.
- Hold on.
Jang Hoon is looking at you with a proud smile.
It's his favorite bird.
- Eagles!
- Right! Yonsei University.
- That's right.
- Right!
- From Yonsei University...
- The symbol of his university.
Didn't they invite you to the Yonsei University festival?
The university festivals are going on these days.
- Didn't they invite you?
- It's festival season right now,
but I haven't been invited that much.
- The song was just...
- It was just released.
- When it gets famous, - Right.
- But...
- they will ask you to come...
to the Yonsei University festival.
You have to make that happen.
- Me?
- You should arrange that.
- Should I call the university...
- Who else can do this?
- Shin Young...
- Okay.
I'll contact them.
She made a clear goal.
Our viewers of Men on a Mission...
- should see it too.
- They should!
- Let's watch it!
- I have many dancers as well!
It's a chant. I'm the cheer captain.
- "To the Eagle."
- Here's some water.
- Play the music.
- Goodness.
It's starting.
("To the Eagle" by Cho Hye Lyun)
This is exciting.
(Beat your wings)
(With all your might)
(A lively melody that will awaken the weary)
Come on!
(A song of encouragement for all the sleeping eagles of the world)
Yes!
Help me get some gigs.
Jang Hoon!
- Well done, everyone!
- Get me some gigs.
- What?
- What's going on?
(Anacana canari cani kipeowei)
Goodness, is he also...
Guess which one is the lie
That's funny.
You have to jump around.
- Jump around with Hye Lyun.
- Dance with Hye Lyun.
Go, go!
(Immersed)
Are we joining?
Make a line.
(Hopping)
(Uncle joins in a little late.)
(The Anacana train is leaving.)
Get me a gig!
I'm sorry!
Right. It's my fault.
I think it's my fault.
The eagle...
It's undoubtedly a great song.
Anyway,
- the transfer students today...
- Yes.
all brought very tricky questions.
They all brought very tricky questions.
One by one, they'll come up, and each tell us three TMIs.
One of those will be a lie.
It will be a lie.
Those who answer well get gifts, so don't forget that.
- Okay!
Nice.
Number one.
I'm a specialist in emceeing of 60th birthday parties.
(1. I'm a specialist in emceeing of 60th birthday parties.)
- Ji Sun?
- She'd be really good at it.
Is Ji Sun a specialist in emceeing of 60th birthday parties?
You've gone from nightclubs...
to specializing in 60th birthday parties?
She'd probably be ridiculously good at it.
Number two.
I almost died...
while acting in "I Love You, Mom."
- Really?
- We were there together.
- Did that happen?
- At least she's still alive.
Number three.
I had a crush on one of the members...
of Men on a Mission.
- Goodness!
- What?
- Which one do you think is true, - That's totally a lie.
- and which one is a lie?
- Come on.
- Number 3!
- Number 3 is a lie.
Firstly, let's ignore number three.
- Number three might be true.
- Someone she was...
romantically attracted to...
She'd be nice to the person.
- Let's talk about them 1 by 1.
- Explain each of them.
I was called to a lot of 60th birthday parties.
- To a lot of 60th birthday parties.
- Really?
The first of those parties...
was for Insooni, Shin Hyung Won,
- Noh Sa Yeon.
- and Noh Sa Yeon.
- These three are the same age.
- They are...
- So Lee Sung Mi said, - Right.
"Ji Sun."
- "Are you available on this date?"
- She was selected like that.
Her tiny voice.
- Tiny voice.
- "Why do you ask?"
"It's the 60th birthday of Insooni,"
"Noh Sa Yeon, and Shin Hyung Won that day."
"We're planning to throw them a party."
"I want you to prepare something."
- You're good at impersonating her.
- That became the start.
I also was the MC of Hong Lyol's 70th birthday party,
- Yang Hee Eun's 70th birthday.
- Hee Eun's 70th birthday party,
Ahn Mun Suk's 60th birthday party,
Mun Yeong Mi's 70th birthday party,
- You hosted so many of them.
- and many others.
Recently, I hosted the 60th birthday parties...
- of Jee Seok Jin and Kim Soo Yong.
- Kim Soo Yong.
- Really?
- You also hosted...
Kyung Sil's 60th birthday party.
- You hosted that.
- Right, I did.
We hosted it together.
- Right?
- What I normally do...
is wear a hanbok...
and sing "Hundred Years Life."
- I prepared one in Ho Dong style.
- What did you prepare?
- "Hundred Years Life."
- Really?
- That's amazing.
- Ho Dong...
(If they come from the afterlife)
(To take Ho Dong at 60)
There you go!
(Tell them)
(He can't go yet)
(Because there's still too much he wants to eat)
(If they come from the afterlife)
(To take Seo Jang Hoon at 70)
(Tell them)
(He can't go yet)
(Because he's still growing)
This is it.
(The reason why they must live to be 100)
This is how I customize the lyrics...
- for each person when I sing.
- It sounds very plausible.
- I bet this is true.
- She can even have a concert.
- What?
- This must be true.
- It's true.
- Sure.
Now, number two.
You almost died while acting in "I Love You, Mom?"
- What is it? What does that mean?
- This is...
- I've never heard of it before.
- While acting in "I Love You, Mom."
You know, I gave birth to four children.
- And I'm not that young anymore.
- Right.
But out of nowhere, I suddenly developed BPPV.
- Oh, no.
- I was doing "I Love You, Mom."
It's dark backstage, you know.
So I was fumbling my way in one day,
but because I was so dizzy,
I couldn't tell where the wall was.
- It can happen.
- So, before the show,
I ended up bumping my head against the wall.
- Oh, no.
- I had to perform that day.
I had no idea.
And my vertigo was so bad.
In the play, there's a scene...
- where the mom dies.
- Right.
And I'm supposed to lie on my side in the scene.
But the worst thing for BPPV is lying on your side.
- Really?
- I heard that.
- Lying on your side...
- So she started lying on her back.
Lying on your side makes you dizzy?
- When I lie on my side, it makes...
- It must be dizzy.
the whole world spin like this.
- It makes you really dizzy.
- The world is spinning.
So, when it's bad, it can even make you throw up.
- It's really bad.
- Right. You feel queasy.
So I had a hard time.
I didn't know that.
- We knew she had BPPV, though.
- I think this one is also true.
- It can be dangerous.
- She wouldn't lie about this.
Then, number three must be a lie.
- I also think it's number three.
- Yes. A member of Men on a Mission?
- All right.
- I'm curious about number three.
- You had a crush on a member?
- I did.
It is possible if it happened in the past.
Was it before you got married?
Of course, it was before I got married.
Back in the 1990s?
- Yes, in the 1990s.
- Then...
- In the 1990s.
- She probably watched basketball...
- Is it Jang Hoon?
- Or ssireum?
- Ssireum?
- Ssireum.
Did you like ssireum?
I like it a lot.
(She ended up blurting out her feelings?)
- I...
- Since when?
If you see my husband,
you'll get what I mean.
I like guys who are healthy...
That's right.
- and have a big build.
- It must be Ho Dong.
(Someone as well-built as her husband)
And actually, my husband...
used to be a singer.
- That's true.
- What? A singer?
- That's right.
- Rock.
I love people who sing well.
- It could be Sang Min.
- Is it Kyung Hoon?
- Kyung Hoon?
- But it was in the 1990s.
- It was before she got married.
- It has to be Lee Sang Min.
- Roo'Ra.
- It's Sang Min.
- Exactly.
- It has to be Sang Min.
- Sang Min was...
- So who is it?
- Tell us.
- Who did you have a crush on?
- Who is it?
- Who?
- There's only one person.
- Actually...
The truth is?
- Why are you so shy?
- She's so shy.
- Hang on.
- She liked him for real.
- She's so shy.
- Wait. Yeong Cheol.
What's with you?
- Is it Yeong Cheol?
- Why are you so anxious?
- What?
- Don't get ready, Yeong Cheol.
- It's okay to be anxious.
- Yeong Cheol?
No, don't get ready for this, Yeong Cheol.
Go ahead and tell us.
- Who is it?
- Who's your first love?
(The man who made Ji Sun's heart flutter back then)
(Ho Dong, the Ssireum Bulldozer?)
(Sang Min, the Deity of Music?)
(Kyung Hoon in the glory days of his looks?)
(Yeong Cheol with a mind-blowing twist?)
Who is it?
It's Sang Min.
(Ji Sun's final choice is Sang Min.)
(It was Sang Min who captured Ji Sun's heart.)
- It must be a lie.
- Why?
I knew it.
(Shy)
- Was it Sang Min?
- I see.
That's possible.
Sang Min was really popular back then.
- Right.
- He was so popular.
This is possible.
- Roo'Ra.
- Exactly.
I made my debut...
in the 1990s.
Back then, he was a member of Roo'Ra.
- He was the best.
- And I was performing...
as Seo Taisoon and Boys.
- That's right.
- They were very popular.
I performed at various events...
- back then.
- Right.
Back then, artists didn't really have...
a place to promote their albums.
It was even before...
- the term "cover dance" existed.
- That's true.
And around that time,
I did a cover of "I Know" by Seo Taiji and Boys...
- and many other songs.
- She did.
- It was crazy.
- I also did...
- "The Angel Who Lost Wings."
- It's "The Angel Who Lost Wings."
- I did a cover of the song.
- It was insane.
- So...
so many artists started bringing their albums to me,
- asking me to help promote them.
- I see.
- That's what happened.
- It helped promote their albums.
That's how we did some TV shows together.
We met many times.
(And that's how their relationship began.)
- And...
- Sang Min is crossing his legs.
It's a detailed story.
- And...
- Sang Min is crossing his legs.
- It's a detailed story.
- Kim Ji Hyeon is a friend of mine.
- That's right.
- She is.
Ji Hyeon and I are friends.
- You two could've connected.
- Exactly.
You could've had four children with him then.
Maybe. If things worked out for us.
If it had happened, they wouldn't have been living together now.
- Seriously...
- Hey, then are you saying...
- Hey, what's that supposed to mean?
- Come on.
- The story is quite detailed.
- But why...
Roo'Ra had many members.
And there were many artists back then. Why did you like Sang Min?
Why Sang Min of all people?
- He's attractive.
- The thing is...
- You know, I'm full of talent.
- Yes.
And talent recognizes talent.
(Talent recognizes talent.)
- So, to be honest...
- That's true.
- I could tell he was different.
- Is it true?
I have a question. You never asked him out?
I seriously thought about...
- asking him out through Ji Hyeon.
- Really?
Yes. But think about it.
It'd be fine if things worked out well...
and we ended up...
- in a good relationship.
- Right.
- But if you broke up...
- But if things went wrong...
Considering my personality,
I felt like one of us would have to leave...
the entertainment industry for good.
I didn't think...
- I could keep seeing him at work.
- I understand that.
So I kept debating...
whether to tell Ji Hyeon about it or not.
- Were you that serious?
- What would happen if she did?
- She's talking too long.
- It's good that she didn't.
So it should be a lie.
In the end, you're happier now anyway.
- What?
- Hey.
- Why do you keep ruining...
- You never know.
our beautiful memories?
- We can't tell.
- You don't know that.
- Why are you ruining it?
- All right. Let's go.
- Then...
- What's the answer?
Guess which one is the lie.
Number one. I'm a specialist in emceeing...
of 60th birthday parties. Raise your hands.
- This is...
- It has to be true.
- Sang Min...
- Look at him.
- He's the only one.
- He's raising his hand high.
Number two. I almost died while acting...
in "I Love You, Mom."
- This is...
- Raise your hands.
- I don't think she almost died.
- I also think...
- I think this is a little...
- Then,
we wouldn't have been able to perform together.
I had a crush on one of the members...
of Men on a Mission. Raise your hand.
- I think it was someone else.
- This can't be true.
- I agree.
- Maybe Jang Hoon.
- It was Jang Hoon.
- Was it Ho Dong?
- It wasn't me.
- I'm sure...
- it was Jang Hoon.
- Jang Hoon.
All right then. What is the answer?
Which one is the lie?
(You can't almost die from BPPV.)
Tell us.
(There's no way she had a crush on Sang Min!)
(Let me keep our memories beautiful.)
You guys don't know me.
- What? Really?
- Is it number one?
- The answer is...
- The lie is...
Which one is the lie?
- It's number three.
- I knew it.
(Number 3 is the lie.)
- Look at him.
- It's impossible.
(I dance hip-hop when I'm sad.)
- It wasn't Sang Min.
- There's no way it's true.
(Singing)
Look at him.
- Digirib, digirib - I knew it.
(I kick the ball of love way out of bounds again today.)
(Even if it's all in vain.)
It was the lie.
- Look at him.
- There's no way.
- The whole thing is a lie?
- If it's not Sang Min, who is it?
- How much of it is a lie?
- Right. Tell us.
Sang Min is a little...
The people I really had a crush on...
were Jeon Yeong Rok and Lee Seung Chul.
- But...
- They're totally different.
- They were idols back then.
- Right.
I didn't hate Sang Min, though.
- Of course not.
- Do you know what I was imagining?
- What?
- When she gave me the good energy,
Jang Hoon told her to hold my hand,
but she refused to hold it. I thought that was why.
(She didn't hold my hand because she had a crush on me?)
Come on.
(When he got the good energy for fertility earlier...)
(Holding hands is good, but sending an energy isn't so bad.)
(Why wouldn't she hold my hand?)
(A swamp of delusion)
- No way.
- He's insane.
- He's drunk.
- That's too much.
(Ji Sun's lie was that flawless.)
- Next.
- Let's move on.
I can tell when Hye Lyun lies.
- I can tell Hye Lyun's lies.
- She's a bad liar.
No, I'm not.
- All right. Number one.
- Okay.
I placed third in a beauty contest against Shin Bong Sun...
- and Jung Ju Ry.
- Right. That's possible.
- This is true.
- It is.
- It's a fact.
- What are you talking about?
- Shin Bong Sun?
- This is a fact.
- Shin Bong Sun and Jung Ju Ry.
You made the top three, anyway.
- There are only three.
- Who won?
- Congratulations.
- Who placed first?
It's the bronze medal.
- Number 2.
- Wait.
I deleted Kyung Sil's number one time...
because she was too much.
-That's possible.
- Really?
- It can happen.
- You said she was your role model.
- Number three.
- She keeps changing her words.
Actor Park Jeong Min and I check in with each other often.
- No way.
- Actor Park Jeong Min?
- It's possible.
- She was on "Pinggyego."
- Did you ask him?
- This is it.
The thing is...
- Jung Ju Ry...
- Let's begin with number one.
- It's possible.
- Tell us more about it.
Here's the thing.
It was when I released "Nuit de Folie."
For the music video,
- the three of us had bobbed hair.
- Right.
- Cleopatra.
- Ju Ry, Bong Sun,
and I belonged to the same agency back then.
(Their concept was an another level transcending the time and space.)
(Humanity isn't ready for this song yet.)
(I'm from the year 2089, and humanity still isn't ready.)
We were having a meal together one day.
We started talking about our looks.
- I see.
- I thought...
I looked better than them.
It was before Bong Sun had the nose job.
Before the nose job.
Sometimes Ju Ry looks gorgeous...
like a model,
- but other times, her look...
- Right.
is just hopeless.
It depends on the angle.
- Ju Ry has a nice figure.
- She has a nice figure.
- That's right.
- She has a really nice figure.
My facial features look pretty if you study them separately.
- That's right.
- Thus, I had confidence.
But they were like, "Hye Lyun, stop with that nonsense."
- They were serious.
- In the end,
- we decided to make some calls.
- It's understandable.
- Did you call people?
- We called a few people.
I remember getting that call.
- We called you, right?
- Yes, I remember.
We called Soo Geun.
- That's right.
- We also called Gu Ra.
He got so annoyed.
- Of course.
- "Hey."
- Gu Ra speaks honestly.
- Like he couldn't be bothered,
he went, "Shin Bong Sun places first."
"Jung Ju Ry places second."
"Cho Hye Lyun places third."
- Really?
- He was correct.
- Was that how you placed third?
- It's plausible.
- I believe it was the opposite.
- I believe Hye Lyun placed first.
- It's plausible.
- Really?
- I think I picked Hye Lyun too.
- No.
- Try to remember what happened.
See? It's suspicious that she is denying it outright.
No. I actually placed third.
- It was upsetting.
- How many people did you call?
I called about 4 to 5 people.
- And 4 to 5 people...
- Did you call 4 to 5 people?
All of them got annoyed. Lee Gyeong Gyu got annoyed.
Soo Geun too.
Soo Geun didn't give a definite answer.
Gu Ra gave us a clear answer.
- That was how it happened.
- Right.
- I see.
- It was a fun event.
- Number 2.
- Let me explain number two.
- Okay.
You deleted my number?
I deleted your number.
- Really?
- Yes.
I don't care if it's true or false.
I'm so annoyed.
(No matter what it is, I'm so annoyed.)
- That's right.
- Even if it's a lie...
- What are you going to do?
- It's the past I can reveal.
- The past you can reveal.
This happened before I learned about Kyung Sil's depth.
- It was before that.
- Kyung Sil...
always pointed out my flaws.
- She always nagged at me.
- Right.
- She wanted you to succeed in life.
- She had so much energy.
Once, I arrived at my waiting room in a tracksuit because I was busy...
and washed my hair there. She went, "Hey."
"Hey, what kind of a celebrity wears a tracksuit?"
- That's right.
- She nagged at me.
- She complained.
- She didn't even brush her teeth.
I brushed my teeth in the waiting room.
- She did it for five minutes.
- That's right.
That wasn't all.
When I had a scar on my face from a dog bite...
- A dog bite.
- The scar has faded a lot.
I guess it's thanks to Kyung Sil.
As soon as she met me at MBC,
she asked me if it was a stab wound.
She asked that to a celebrity.
- A stab wound?
- She had to check.
- It was right here.
- I had never been stabbed.
- It was a dog bite.
- That's right.
How did you get that scar?
When I was seven years old,
- I fought against a dog.
- She got bitten by a dog.
- A dog?
- It was a dog bite.
It's like "A Werewolf Boy."
- No way.
- She got bitten by a dog?
There was a pregnant dog...
- in Dangdong, Goseong.
- Okay.
I cherished the dog very much.
- Not knowing it was sensitive, - That's right.
- I went, "Puppy."
- Pregnant dogs get sensitive.
Then it bit my face.
It bit my face...
and left a big wound.
- I see.
- My mom just put doenjang on it.
- That's right.
- The wound became infected...
- and didn't close properly.
- Oh, no.
- Kyung Sil went, - So you had a scar.
- "Your scar is too big,"
- "Get it treated."
- "so get it treated."
- I see.
I got it treated thanks to her,
but I was a celebrity getting nagged by another celebrity.
- I hated it so much.
- It's understandable.
- Then...
- I had my pride.
- That's right.
- So I deleted her number.
- You deleted my number.
- I deleted her number.
When I got a call from an unknown number,
I screened it since it could be Kyung Sil.
(A celebrity's retaliation for all that nagging)
- You know, - I screened all those calls.
I did nag at Hye Lyun a lot.
- That's right.
- I did that...
- because I liked her.
- You cherished her.
I wanted to succeed in life.
Hye Lyun just rolled out of bed...
and arrived in a tracksuit and a cap.
Back in the day, the waiting room came...
- with a shower.
- Yes.
But many people changed clothes there.
- But Hye Lyun...
- She actually took a shower.
brushed her teeth and showered during lunchtime.
Sometimes, she shaved her armpits.
- I needed my armpits to be clean.
- She shaved her armpits.
Why did you bring up the past?
- You let Kyung Sil expose you more.
- That's right.
- She exposed you more.
- I still want to delete her number.
- Let's move on to number 3.
- Number 3.
Actor Park Jeong Min and I check in with each other...
often.
- Does he want to ask for a favor?
- I really like...
- Actor Park Jeong Min.
- That's right.
In "Keys to the Heart,"
- he pulled off the piano scene...
- He played a pianist.
even though he was a total novice.
Listening to that story made me admire him a lot.
Then I went to watch "Life of Pi."
Park Jeong Min was so touched...
that he came to watch my play, "I Love You, Mom."
That was how we became close.
- And one time, - What a nice man.
- I visited "Maebul Show."
- "Maebul Show."
I needed to talk about movies on the show,
so I wanted to tell him that I'd talk about "Keys to the Heart."
But I made a mistake and called it "Dogs to the Heart."
- The title.
- That's so different.
Why did you do that?
- It was a mistake.
He replied, "I'm glad you enjoyed the movie."
- What a nice man.
- "I'm in Japan right now."
I realized what I did and messaged, "It's 'Keys to the Heart.' Sorry."
He replied, "It's okay."
"I'm just thankful that you watched it."
He is like that.
- In any case, you're the one...
- That's right.
- who messages him first?
- That's...
- I always message him first.
- That's right.
- That statement is true.
- It makes sense.
- Then it's plausible.
- He has no choice but to reply.
- Now, let's guess the answer.
- All right.
Number one, "I placed third in a beauty contest against..."
- "Shin Bong Sun and Jung Ju Ry."
- It's the most confusing one.
- You said you got that call, right?
- It's...
I bet Hye Lyun brought this story...
- since she placed first.
- Yes.
- I see.
- That's right.
- I bet.
- Anyway, I said Hye Lyun was...
- the prettiest.
- Thank you.
- Yes.
- Also...
I'm raising my hand for number one...
because it'll be upsetting if number two is correct.
Eight people who picked number one, please put your hand down.
Number 2, "I deleted Kyung Sil's number 1 time..."
"because she was too much."
- I bet she just screened the calls.
- I bet she didn't delete it.
- Her phone number...
- I bet she didn't answer the calls.
- She didn't answer the calls.
She didn't delete her number.
- Let me change my answer.
- She didn't answer the calls.
- Change your answer? Okay.
- Yes.
Number three, "Actor Park Jeong Min and I..."
"check in with each other often."
- No one.
- It's true.
Why would this be a lie?
I saw her message him.
That's right.
- All right.
- Then which one is Hye Lyun's lie?
- Tell us.
- What if it's number three?
- The correct answer is...
- What is it?
(Did she place 1st, not 3rd, in the beauty contest?)
(Kyung Sil just doesn't like number 2.)
It's number two.
(Cheering)
That's right.
- Thank goodness.
- It's number two.
- My goodness.
- That's right.
- Seo Jang Hoon.
- I knew it.
- Thank goodness.
(Jang Hoon has a good hunch.)
- I was worried...
- That's right.
- that it wouldn't be number two.
- Thank goodness.
- I'm glad. Who cares if I'm wrong?
- I know.
I've never deleted Kyung Sil's number.
I heard...
that you cast Kyung Sil for a play because you hated her nagging.
- It's true.
- What's that about?
I wanted to get my revenge.
- But she got the better of you.
- The dialect.
- She wanted to nag at Kyung Sil.
- I knew...
- that there was one empty spot.
- Okay.
I wanted to cast Kyung Sil...
because I could do whatever I wanted...
as a director.
- That's right.
- So I cast her.
- My goodness.
Do you know why I felt that way?
Throughout my life,
Kyung Sil tormented me too much.
- She wanted revenge.
- Thorough revenge.
- I nagged at her too much.
- She had it all planned out.
- So...
- I look much better now, right?
- It was the best revenge.
- Yes.
- You look much better.
- I'm so happy.
- Was that the reason?
- That was the reason.
- I'm so happy.
She looks much better.
Do you know what has improved?
I began to see Kyung Sil as the same person.
She isn't so perfect either.
You're right.
That's right.
- Seriously.
- I'm so happy...
that I'm on cloud nine.
That's right.
- Well done.
- All right.
(She unfolds the eagle's wings after getting her revenge.)
So...
you did place last in a beauty contest.
That's right.
You're right.
- You're right.
- That's right.
- We expected that much.
- I see.
I'll give you a quiz this time.
- Okay.
- Listen carefully.
- Number one.
- Okay.
- When my girls learned to speak, - Okay.
they began with "Mom" and "Dad..."
and moved on to "Honey."
- "Honey?"
- "Honey."
- It's plausible.
- Both of my girls.
- That's right.
- It's plausible.
- Children copy their surroundings.
- That's right.
We say "Honey" often.
- They must've used it often.
- Let's move on to the next one.
- Number 2.
- My girl thinks...
- Okay.
- I'm talking about the youngest.
She thinks I'm 20 years old.
- She thinks Mom is 20 years old.
- Okay.
- Number three.
- It's plausible.
- It's the last one.
- Okay.
My last manager used to go home...
in an expensive limousine after work.
- Really?
- Yes.
What do you mean? After dropping you off?
Maybe her manager got bored...
- and worked out of curiosity.
- How unusual.
- Let's start from number one.
- Let's go.
- Number one.
- Did your daughters learn...
"Honey..."
- right after "Mom" and "Dad?"
- Yes.
Both my husband and I talk a lot at home.
We call each other "Honey."
"Honey, have you eaten?"
"Honey, come here and do this."
They heard "Honey" so many times.
So after learning "Mom" and "Dad,"
- they learned "Honey."
- "Honey."
- So...
it was very embarrassing.
They went to my in-laws' place and called my father-in-law...
- "Honey."
- They did that to their grandpa.
- So cute.
- That's so cute.
- The adults went,
- "How cute!"
- Yes.
- The compliments excited them.
- They used it even more.
Even at a church, they called the pastor "Honey."
- I was so flustered.
- You know,
- So they learned "Honey."
- there was that joke.
- It makes sense.
- What joke?
After "Mom" and "Dad," children learn...
"Laundry!"
- Children learn that next.
- There was that joke.
- People said that.
- That's right.
- There was that joke.
That's right. There was that joke.
- Come on.
- It's true!
- Seriously.
- There was that joke.
- That's right.
Trucks from a laundromat circled the neighborhood back then.
- They did that.
Then which one is the lie? How about number two?
- Number 2.
- Number 2 isn't...
- My youngest daughter...
- She thinks you're 20 years old.
She thinks I'm 20 years old.
- You lied to her.
- As you know,
children don't have the correct sense of age.
- That's right.
- Hyo Jin looks young too.
I guess they talked about Mom's age at the daycare center.
- "Mom is such-and-such years old."
- Right.
- I guess they talked about it.
- Okay.
So she came home one day and asked,
- "Mom, how old are you?"
- I see.
I was a bit flustered.
- I had her at a late age.
- You're over 50, right?
I gave her an honest answer.
"I'm 50." Then my daughter went,
"Don't lie!"
"That's Grandma's age!"
(Don't lie! That's Grandma's age!)
- How cute.
- It's understandable.
- She had her at the age of 45.
She knew that it was Grandma's age.
It was so shocking.
- My daughter...
- How smart.
was so certain that it was Grandma's age.
- That's right.
- Telling her my actual age...
- would've hurt her feelings.
- You couldn't do that.
I asked her, "How old do you think I am?"
My daughter went,
- "Are you 20?"
- My goodness.
"That's right. I'm 20." That was how it happened.
- To this day, she thinks I'm 20.
- She thinks you're 20.
- It makes sense.
- I figured it out.
- This one is a lie.
"How old do you think I am?" "You're 50."
- No.
- That must be it.
- Soo Geun!
- "Mom, how old are you?"
- She said she was 20.
- That's right.
- Then her daughter went, "No."
- "No."
- "You're 50."
(Is number 2 a lie that contains Hyo Jin's wish?)
- No.
- I look nice for a 50-year-old.
Some children become proud...
when their parents are older.
- "My mom is older."
- That's right.
- "My dad is older."
- While it's true...
- "My dad is a police officer."
- It happens.
- That's right.
- "My dad got caught by the police."
That's right. That happens.
- That happens.
- They think it's better.
- Children are like that.
- In any case...
- I'm not sure about number three.
Most managers drop off the celebrity with the company vehicle...
and drive off in it.
- Some agencies work differently.
- Some managers don't do that.
- It was my own car.
- Some agencies work differently.
- Right.
- It's plausible.
- How did you find out?
- Maybe she came from a rich family.
- You know,
I saw it with my own eyes.
Apparently, my manager came from a rich family.
- She came from a rich family.
- Okay.
- When my work finished late, - Okay.
she called someone when we were...
near my place.
"Mister, I'm nearly there."
"You can come now."
- No way.
- That's impossible.
- When I got home,
- I saw a long, black limousine.
- It doesn't make any sense.
- My goodness.
- So...
Hey, you should've looked after her.
- Seriously.
- Right.
- After a while...
- You should've been the driver.
I guess it's human nature.
- Once I learned that she was...
- That's right.
- from a prestigious family, - You couldn't treat her with ease.
I became wary of her reactions.
- Of course.
- Seriously.
- If my work dragged on, - Your name wasn't that big.
- I went, "You must be tired."
- "Your name."
"Why don't you go home?"
(Polite)
- You did that to your manager.
- "Aren't you hungry?"
- I became wary.
- You did that to your manager.
- Still...
- For how long was she your manager?
- For about two years.
- Two years is a long time.
- For experience...
- Her dad promised...
to open a shop for her...
- if she got some work experience.
- It happens.
- So she became my manager.
What does she do now?
- Do you guys keep in touch?
- It was many years ago,
- so we don't keep in touch.
- That's right. Hyo Jin was young.
- What does she do now?
- I'm sure she is living well...
thanks to her successful dad.
- That's right.
- When I was on "Star King,"
there was... Do you remember?
There was a son of a family that ran a big corporate.
He worked as a floor director.
- Really?
- You remember, right?
- Such things are common.
- Yes.
He did it for experience.
- I remember him. He wore glasses.
- Yes.
- He did it for experience.
- I think it makes sense.
- At an award ceremony...
- A limousine came to pick her up.
- All right. Let's go.
- She explained number three.
Number one. "When my girls learned to speak,"
they began with "Mom" and "Dad" and moved on to "Honey."
Raise your hand if you think it's a lie.
- I think it's number one.
- One person.
- One person thinks it's number one.
- Okay.
Number two. "My daughter thinks I'm 20 years old."
Raise your hand...
- if you think it's a lie.
- I think it's this one.
- I bet she just said, - She is 50 years old.
"That's Grandma's age!"
- I think it's true.
- That's right.
Now, number three.
"My last manager used to go home..."
- "in an expensive limousine..."
- It might be true.
- "after work."
- No way.
- It sounds excessive.
- All right.
- That's right.
- I bet she had her own car.
And it's ridiculous that she called the driver before arrival...
and asked him to come.
- She wouldn't have done that.
- It makes no sense.
- She would've kept quiet.
- Yes.
- Which one is Hyo Jin's lie?
- Which one is it?
- Tell us.
- It's number two.
- The correct answer is...
- Number three?
(Is the unrealistic story of a former manager a lie?)
(Is the statement Sang Min chose by himself, number 1, a lie?)
It's...
- number 1.
- Number 1?
(Only Sang Min is correct!)
- Really?
- When my girls learned to speak,
- they didn't move on to "Honey..."
- It seemed like a lie.
- right after "Mom" and "Dad."
- Only Sang Min answered correctly.
Which word did they learn next?
- If it wasn't "Honey..."
- Which word did they learn next?
- "Darling?"
- Let me tell you.
- It wasn't "Honey" or "Darling."
- "Let's go to bed."
- No.
It was "Don't come."
- "Don't come?"
- Why?
- Why "Don't come?"
- Let me explain.
- "Don't come?"
My husband rivals Jang Hoon...
- In cleanliness?
- in cleanliness...
and sanitation. When it comes to safety,
- he is a bit obsessive to a fault.
- He is a bit like that.
When our children were born, he got worse.
He chased around the children going,
"It's dangerous! You'll get hurt!"
- "Don't touch that! That's dirty!"
- "Don't come!"
He chased them around, saying those things.
One time, our daughter was playing in the bedroom.
- My husband was boiling water.
- Okay.
There was quite a distance between them.
- She wasn't coming to the kitchen.
- It was fine.
But he still went to the bedroom to tell her,
"Come over here."
"I'm boiling water in the kitchen."
"It's very hot. It's dangerous."
He is like that.
- What's wrong with him?
- One time,
- our daughter was having fun.
- He doesn't want her to get hurt.
Being naturally curious, she was absorbed in playing.
When her dad came over to tell her something,
she went, "Don't come!"
- "Don't come!"
- "Dad, don't come!"
- A little girl did that.
- She said it so hurriedly.
- My goodness.
- This is her specialty.
- It isn't like that.
Our second daughter did the same.
When her dad began to come, she went, "Go away!"
She did that.
- My husband was too much.
- In that case,
was there an instance...
that made you watch your words while raising children?
Back when I did the Gollum skit...
- Did they copy you?
- I went, "My precious."
- It aired on TV.
- No way.
Then my children did "My precious" while they were going to...
- the restroom.
- No way.
- That has to be a lie.
- It's true.
- Hye Lyun.
- Seriously.
- They went, "My precious."
(Believe it or not, they did the Gollum Show at home.)
- It's true. Don't be like that.
- Maybe it happened.
There is a characteristic...
- comedians' children share.
- That's right.
When comedians read children's books,
- we imitate animals...
- We make it sound realistic.
- in a realistic manner.
- Yes.
When my daughters went to the daycare center,
the instructors taught them how the ducks go, "Quack, quack..."
and pigs go, "Oink, oink."
"What sound do the pigs make?" Then my daughters went...
(Oinking hard)
They did that.
- It totally makes sense.
- They're good.
- They got that from me.
- They made it realistic.
- "What sound do crows make?"
(Cawing)
(What sound do crows make?)
- That's right.
- My daughters did that.
- The instructor praised them.
- My goodness.
(Hyo Jin's every story was as interesting as a lie.)
- Hyo Jin is the best.
- It was funny.
She is the best.
Kyung Sil is next.
- Kyung Sil.
- Gangnam's legs.
Number one.
- When I was 6, - When you were 6?
I got trampled on by a cow.
- A cow.
- Oh, my.
- Trampled on by a cow?
- This is too...
Hye Lyun got bitten by a dog...
and Kyung Sil got trampled on by a cow.
- A cow?
- This is too much.
- A cow.
- Seriously. These stories...
- It was a bull.
- A bull?
- Yes, I got trampled on by a bull.
- These dogs and cows are too much.
- Seriously.
- Number two.
- Okay.
- When I was a rookie, - When you were a rookie?
I almost died while cleaning the outside of the 63 Building...
- for a show.
- What?
It's plausible. MBC filmed many shows there.
- Number 3.
I don't make appointments.
- You don't make appointments.
- I don't do it.
Hye Lyun... I'll start with number three.
Hye Lyun is the type to start things.
People think...
- I'm very extroverted...
- That's right.
- and charismatic.
They think I make the juniors gather around.
If I ask them to meet up with me,
- they won't say no.
- That's right.
You're wrong. They'll say no.
If people invite me somewhere...
or offer me a job,
- I comply.
- That's right.
- But I don't take the initiative.
- She is introverted.
- Kyung Sil is introverted on MBTI.
- I'm introverted.
It might come as a surprise, but she is very introverted.
- She is introverted.
- Okay.
You got trampled on by a bull at the age of six?
- Yes.
- What do you mean by that?
- Then she would've died.
- She would...
- That's right. Bulls are huge.
- It happened...
in the year of 1971.
In the year of 1971, I lived in a village down the hill.
On top of the hill was a village with a bullock cart.
- A bullock cart.
- Back then,
a bullock cart in the upper village...
was led around by a grandpa to do the field work...
- Which grandpa?
- and deliver...
- sacks of rice.
- Okay.
Around 5pm to 6pm,
- it got off work.
- It needed to rest.
- It headed home.
- Grandpa was leading it home.
- It had a fulfilling day.
- Since I was young,
I was happy to see the bull.
You saw it around.
- I...
- Did you think of it like a dog?
- Of course.
- I was playing when I saw the cow.
- "It's a cow!"
- "It's a cow!" I ran over.
"Cow!" I ran over.
I was happy to see the cow,
- but it wasn't happy to see me.
- Of course not.
- It was going home.
- I ran over to the cow.
- I don't know what happened next.
- My goodness.
- It kicked you.
- No, the cow trampled on me.
- Oh, my.
- Maybe the grandpa hit you.
- What?
Grandpa was hanging upside down and hit you.
- Seriously.
- "Don't come!"
"Don't come!"
I ran over to the cow...
and I remember it coming toward me.
- Then I have no memory.
- You fainted.
When I woke up later,
my leg and arm were...
in a cast.
- Oh, my.
- So...
back then, we wore rubber shoes.
When a girl wore red shoes,
I found them so pretty.
And I envied her even more...
when she walked on cement...
- because her shoes clicked.
- Right.
I envied her so much for it.
But when I walked with a leg cast,
- I made clicking sounds.
- You made clicking sounds.
I wondered why you were going with this story.
- I was young.
- Seriously.
- You treated it like a high heel.
- I was like, "I have a high heel."
- Seriously.
"I have a high heel." I remember saying that.
- You can't make up such a story.
- There can't be any lies...
- in this story.
- It's impossible.
That's right.
Thank goodness you didn't get hurt more.
Let's move on to number two.
- Number 2.
- Number 2. You cleaned...
- the 63 Building as a rookie.
- I was a rookie.
- I think I was in my second year.
- Okay.
Back then, it was my goal to show my face on TV.
- Any show was good.
- That's right.
Back then, rookies often worked as a reporter.
- I worked as a reporter.
They needed someone to clean the outside of the 63 Building.
- They said it was totally safe.
- They reassured you.
So I went to the 63 Building...
- and wore the safety gear.
- Okay.
As the professional cleaners went down,
- they took me with them.
- Right.
- They told me not to look down.
- Okay.
- It was too scary.
- You were at a dizzying height.
- They told me not to look down.
- How scary.
I was cleaning the wall like this.
- That's right. You were hanging.
- I was cleaning the wall like this.
But once I got used to it, I wanted to look down.
- That's right.
- Right?
- Right.
- While I was hanging from the rope,
I looked down.
(Gasping)
- It was insane.
- At that moment,
- I froze.
- Right.
- It's understandable.
- I froze...
- and slumped like this.
- My goodness.
I couldn't help it.
At that moment...
- I talked before that moment.
- Right.
But I couldn't talk anymore. My lips froze.
She doesn't have a fear of heights.
Did it end like that?
- She doesn't have it.
- I said I couldn't do it.
- I bet she did better...
- I could've...
- than the professional cleaners.
- become a regular,
but they fired me because I did so badly.
But when I thought about it afterward,
how could they make a rookie do such a thing?
- Had it happened now, - Right.
that director would've gotten fired, not me.
- How could they do that?
- Back then,
- they made rookies do such things.
- Back then...
After experiencing that,
- I couldn't go on.
- Didn't you get paid?
- Of course not.
- It didn't get aired.
They couldn't film me.
- I see.
- They couldn't film you?
After a short while, I couldn't go on.
When my friend was a rookie reporter,
they asked her to go skydiving.
Thankfully, she could do it...
with a professional on her back.
- She had a pilot on her back.
- That's right.
- A diver was going to jump too.
She hadn't tried skydiving once.
She just ended up jumping...
- with the other diver.
- That's right.
She screamed and reached the ground.
The director did this.
- He made this gesture.
- What did he mean?
- What?
From screaming, she had drooled everywhere.
(Her salivary glands worked freely while she was skydiving.)
She had drooled everywhere.
- It was all over the place.
- Of course.
- She had screamed.
- Spit went upward.
- So...
- it had traveled up the face.
- That's right.
So she went, "I landed safely."
- The camera was right there.
- Yes.
The camera was right there.
"I landed safely."
- That's right.
- "Although it was nerve-racking..."
- Rookies do it all the time.
- That's right.
That's right.
Let's vote for the lie.
- I have no idea.
- It's so hard.
Number 1. "When I was 6,"
- "I got trampled on by a cow."
- But...
- her story was so detailed.
- I bet it actually happened.
- Seriously.
- How could it be a lie?
I doubt it was a cow.
It wasn't a cow.
- I bet it was a car.
- Four people.
- A car?
- You can put your hand down.
Four people?
"When I was a rookie, I almost died..."
"while cleaning the outside of the 63 Building for a show."
- I think it's this one.
- I think I watched the video.
- I bet she exaggerated.
- It can't be...
- number three.
- She said it didn't air.
- Such things were common.
- Number three.
- Seriously.
- "I don't make appointments."
- I'm sure...
- there are rules.
- Raise your hand.
- Kyung Hoon.
Kyung Hoon doesn't make appointments.
- Why not?
- He doesn't make appointments.
- He doesn't make appointments?
- It's too pressuring.
- Then which one is Kyung Sil's lie?
- All right.
- Number two.
- Tell us.
- Number 2.
- I think it's number 2.
- Please. Number 2.
(I bet it was a car, not a cow.)
(There is no way she is an introvert like me.)
- Number 2.
- My lie is number 2.
- That's right.
- Number two.
(When I was a rookie, I almost died while cleaning the outside...)
(of the 63 Building for a show: False)
- You know, - You cleaned all the walls, right?
- I didn't clean anything.
- Did you clean all the walls?
I never cleaned the outside of the 63 Building...
- for a show.
- Really?
- No?
- No.
But I had a similar experience.
- You talked about skydiving, right?
- Yes.
I went paragliding.
Now, you do it with an expert behind you.
- You can be confident...
- That's right.
- since the expert does everything.
- You have the expert.
But back then, I had to go paragliding alone.
- Really?
- Yes.
My first attempt failed.
- My second attempt worked...
- Okay.
and the wind carried me upward.
- Did you fly?
- I ran, and the wind carried me up.
- I couldn't help but scream.
- Okay.
- It felt really nice.
- Really?
- I thought she was flying now.
- I felt the wind everywhere.
It felt really nice.
I thought, "This is easy." I could go to the right...
or the left as I wanted. I thought, "I can do this."
- But suddenly...
- Okay.
It felt really nice. I thought, "This is easy."
I could go to the right...
or the left as I wanted. I thought, "I can do this."
- But suddenly...
- Okay.
- I told you winds were crucial.
- Yes.
- The winds stopped.
- My goodness.
- The winds stopped blowing.
- What did you do?
- The winds stopped.
I couldn't change directions.
I just fell downward.
I ended up sitting in a tree.
In "Crash Landing on You,"
- Son Ye Jin...
- That's right.
ends up going to North Korea in a paragliding accident.
- It can happen.
- That's right.
The production crew went crazy.
I sat in a tree, going,
"Is anyone there?"
My goodness.
- "What should I do?"
- That's scary.
- That's dangerous.
- I didn't get hurt.
- That's right.
- They came and rescued me.
Her story reminded me of something.
Back in the day, I was on an SBS show...
- titled "Grand Sports Adventures."
- Okay.
For that show, I went paragliding with UN.
- UN?
- I did it with UN.
We went to Mount Pilatus in Switzerland...
and jumped separately.
We have a walkie-talkie.
When we went,
the expert told us to go right or left.
- That was how we took off.
- Okay.
So I ran down.
I was running, but I didn't hear any instructions.
I had dropped my walkie-talkie.
- Oh, no.
- I didn't know what to do.
- I was flying in Switzerland.
- Swiss eagle.
(Swiss eagle comes back.)
- My goodness.
- Swiss eagle.
She brought back the eagle.
- Power lines and cars...
- She is something else.
were below me.
I was like, "Which way do I go?"
"What should I do?"
I just had a strap, not a walkie-talkie.
- Oh, no.
- It was insane.
- Of course, it was.
- A celebrity was about to die.
Also, in Switzerland...
- Power lines and cars...
- She is something else.
were below me.
I was like, "Which way do I go?"
"What should I do?"
I just had a strap, not a walkie-talkie.
- Oh, no.
- It was insane.
- Of course, it was.
- A celebrity was about to die.
Also, in Switzerland, the route is very long.
- That's right.
- In Korea, it's short.
- So what happened?
- Did an expert follow you?
- So an expert...
I bet an expert followed you.
- Did an expert come?
- He caught the wind...
and followed me.
"To the right!"
- Up in the sky, - There was no walkie-talkie.
his voice was distorted.
- That's right.
- "Which way?"
"To the right?"
"To the left" was shorter.
"To the left!"
(She used her wits to understand and came back safely.)
I did this.
(Eagle, eagle)
(She wraps up her story with the eagle.)
The ones who did a good job of identifying the lies,
Shin Young, Sang Min,
- Jang Hoon, and Yeong Cheol...
- it's my first time winning!
will receive a ticket to see...
the funny and touching play, "I Love You, Mom."
(The prize is a ticket for "I Love You, Mom.")
- Congratulations.
- It's my first time winning!
It's my first time winning! Yes!
- I'll watch it many times.
- Also, the transfer students...
- who worked hard for the quiz...
- Yes.
will receive a red ginseng set so that they'll star in a play...
in a healthy manner.
I love it.
(They'll receive a healthy red ginseng set.)
Thank you.
- Thank you.
- It's pretty.
- It's so nice.
- Nice.
"I Love You, Mom" is a play the entire family can watch.
- Let's go and watch it!
(The preview of next week's episode will be revealed soon.)
(Brown Eyed Girls, JeA and Narsha)
(fromis_9, Chae Young and Ji Heon)
(RESCENE, Woni and Minami)
(Baby DONT Cry, Yihyun and Beni)
(Kids these days keep running!)
(Men on a Mission, hurrah!)
("Hurrah" is here thanks to the algorithm.)
(Hurrah)
(Ho Dong tries the latest trend.)
(Ever since I was little, it was my dream...)
(to meet Ho Dong.)
(Dreams come true.)
(Ho Dong, you're really strong.)
(The girl in-laws love versus The girl in-laws hate)
(Same team, different vibes)
(She debuted 1 year ago, but she is as daring as a veteran.)
(The youngest ones give a parade of daring specialties.)
(A Japanese member, Minami shows off her Korean skills.)
(Her fluency is on another level.)
(A contest for the throne of the Pikki Pikki Dance)
(Channeling her inner PSY)
(PSY, are you watching this?)
(A match to improve the dormitory)
To the left.
(They lose reasons in front of prizes.)
(Older girls, sorry!)
(Older girls, ramyeon is yours!)
(Hey!)
(From the 1.5th to the 5th generation!)
(Let's delve into the grand unity between girl groups!)
(Men on a Mission)