[English subtitles are available.]
What do you mean? What feelings?
When I kissed Kang Woo,
I didn't feel anything.
What?
I think something is wrong with me.
I like Ms. Joo Seo Yeon.
I came to say that.
I ended up hearing something
that I didn't have to hear.
And you ended up...
saying something
you didn't have to say.
I thought it needed to be said,
although you probably already knew.
Bad news for you.
Seo Yeon already likes me.
Do you feel confident?
Yes.
Okay, then.
I thought you got that for me.
I did.
But come to think about it,
why should I do that for you?
You are concerned about him,
aren't you?
And you think about him too.
When he says he likes you,
don't you feel
all tingly right here?
I think so.
Then why didn't you feel anything?
What are you doing?
I was wondering
if you're more like Won Seok...
but just haven't realized it yet.
- No, that's not the case.
- Are you sure?
Gosh, then there's only one reason.
It means Kang Woo has
absolutely no skills.
What?
I mean he's an awfully bad kisser.
A man with zero skills.
Isn't that it?
I'm not sure.
I don't think
I'm particularly good either.
Figures. You and Kang Woo are
both love-shy.
I can see what happened.
How is it supposed to feel?
How am I supposed to explain this?
It's as if a firework goes off
from the tip of your toes,
goes through your body,
then out through your head.
- Let's go.
- Where to?
There's no use
in explaining this to you.
What's important is the real deal.
Ho Dol.
Hey, why did you
want to see me here?
What's wrong? Why not?
Oh, this isn't just a pub. It's...
I know.
- I'm a regular here.
- What?
Wait, you didn't notice?
I knew what you were like at once.
Do you know what happened to me
after you ran away with the deposit?
And what now? You need money?
What does your awesome man ever do?
Don't ever call me again.
You and I aren't sisters anymore!
Darn it.
You have no money to get it fixed.
- What are you up to?
- What?
It looked like you were spacing out.
Do you want to eat?
I'm going to make bibimbap.
No, I'll eat later.
How can you turn the lights off
knowing I was in there?
Sorry. I got confused.
Didn't you do it on purpose?
No.
I really didn't.
Man, you surprised me.
Seo Jun.
I'm going to tell Ms. Joo...
that you've been acting weird.
- I think she should know...
- She does know.
Then you wouldn't mind
even if I told her.
Who do you think you are?
Do you think you are...
a part of our family
just because you live here?
You're just living off us.
You're just a stranger.
So don't get involved
with our family matters.
Just stay silent and leave quietly,
as soon as possible.
What? What do you want me to do?
You need to kiss someone else...
to find out if you're the problem
or if it's him.
You're insane.
This is a very important matter
between a couple.
No matter
how much you like each other,
if you don't hit it off this way,
you two can last only a few months,
no, not even a few days.
And you expect me to get any guy...
and ask him to kiss me?
This is the best place to kiss
without any feelings attached.
What are you up to?
Seo Yeon needs to work
on her kissing skills...
No, we aren't up to anything.
We came for the free drinks.
Give us some drinks.
Drinks. Alcohol.
Keep your mouth shut, okay?
Okay.
Yes, let's do this.
Let's try it.
Let's do it.
- What?
- Let's do it.
What are you talking about? Do what?
What is it?
That was so sudden.
Let's do it again.
What?
How much...
did you drink?
What?
If you're going to black out,
I'm going to stop here.
It's okay. I'm not that drunk.
You started it first,
okay?
I think...
Yes?
I'm going...
to marry Mi Kyung.
What?
You're insane.
How could you say that?
Why am I like this? Why?
What do you think?
Since you've been avoiding
handsome guys,
your nerve cells just don't react
when you're in front of them.
Stop drinking.
- I'm a lunatic.
- You're right.
- I'm a fool.
- Did you just realize that?
I'm worth less than the dirt
in my toenails.
- I'm the most worthless thing.
- Exactly.
But I'm uselessly resilient.
So even during the apocalypse,
I'll survive...
and live this idiotic life
once again.
Probably so.
I don't benefit this world
by the slightest bit.
I'm a total idiot.
I should get her exorcised.
Why are all the guys around her
so flawed?
My gosh!
What are you doing?
I almost fainted.
So why was Seo Yeon okay?
Are you talking about her again?
That's why I advised you
to date some women.
You make it obvious
that you've never dated anyone.
How could your emotions depend
solely on her?
Kang Woo, life is extremely short.
It's such a waste to cling
onto a woman.
If you don't think it's meant to be,
just end it.
"Meant to be"?
I decide my own fate!
Me! Seo Yeon! That's the end!
What kind of crazy, one-sided love
is this?
You're frightening me.
One mistake, and you'll be put
behind bars.
What in the world
did she say to you?
She wants to marry Mi Kyung.
My gosh.
What?
I don't know who you are,
but you're dead meat.
I'm coming for you.
- Hey, it's me! It's me!
- Die! Die!
Stop it! It's me!
- Get out! Get out!
- Give me a minute!
Look at this...
Gosh, I love it.
You've chosen to use toilet paper
instead of box tissue.
You're so economical.
Oh, my.
Look at that. You reused the dishes.
You're saving water fee
and the environment at once.
Why are you here?
You said you never accepted things
from guys without a reason, right?
Reason? I can give you one.
What? What is this?
You're mine from now on.
- What? Grandma.
- Gosh.
Goodness, sir.
I had absolutely no idea that
you were her grandson.
I'm truly sorry
for inconveniencing you.
What are you doing?
Stand up. What's going on?
You.
- Did you abuse your power?
- What?
Goodness, not at all, ma'am.
I should've been more obedient,
but I focused more
on my principles and beliefs.
It is entirely my fault.
Sir.
Here. I'm kneeling down.
Stand up.
Please show me mercy just this once!
We are truly sorry!
Please forgive me!
Please think of my family!
I'm sorry.
Not at all.
It's my fault for forcing you
to do this.
From what I heard,
you made a servant...
out of a contract teacher.
That's not it...
The higher your position,
the more people
become interested in you.
You should've been careful.
I don't think this is
the right position for you.
- You can stop.
- What do you mean?
I don't need to wait for a year.
You won't be able to hold out
for a whole year.
Come to the headquarters.
Grandma.
I will hand over this position
to someone who's more fitting.
What is going on?
You told me to do what I wanted.
So? You've chosen to be
the chief director?
- Yes.
- So...
you have no ulterior motives?
No, I do.
But isn't that the same case
for you as well?
You know very well...
that I'll do a better job than you.
Do what you want. Don't be chained.
Grandma isn't that conservative,
you know?
Hey, this is huge.
- Kang Woo was abandoned.
- What?
He's no longer going to be
the chief director.
But is it possible...
for him to be kicked out
of his family's school?
What happened?
It's true that I was on a bit...
of a power trip.
"A bit"?
It's a bit more than that.
Darn it.
Is it that hard to just lie
and comfort me?
I feel bad about lying.
Is she turning into Min Hyuk?
Perhaps, it's for the best.
Mi Kyung told me.
If it wasn't for you,
Seo Jun would've been in trouble.
It's going to be great.
You know my older brothers
look like models, right?
I'll make them wear your clothes
as often as possible.
If I see someone wearing
one of your clothes,
I'll tell them
that my friend made it...
and that they should be honored.
So don't be too sad.
Okay?
Are we just friends?
Whenever...
I think of you,
I feel butterflies.
When you're in front of me,
I think I'll go crazy.
You know, I...
That's how I feel.
So please...
like me.
Show me some affection.
"Don't look for me."
"I met someone nice
and am leaving with him."
Do whatever it takes to find her.
I'll pay you however much you want.
You dare to...
elope with a man?
Whenever...
I think of you,
I feel butterflies.
When you're in front of me,
I think I'll go crazy.
Jang Mi.
Seo Yeon.
Why...
I was mistaken.
Seo Yeon, about Seo Jun.
Come here.
Choi Ho Dol.
Why are you avoiding me?
Well...
I didn't know that you were...
So what? Are you disappointed?
Gosh, no.
It's just a bit sudden.
I like you.
- What?
- What do you think about me?
Well...
So...
Is there...
someone else?
No.
Shall we date?
- What?
- What do you say?
It's a bit...
No pressure.
Let's take our time.
Did you see that?
This will be a hit on social media.
What a masterpiece.
- Are you all right?
- Poor you.
- Is he crying?
- Look.
- You look nice. Smile for me.
- I didn't know this about you.
What's wrong?
- Come on.
- Hey, hey.
- Talk about it.
- What's wrong?
What's the matter?
Did you really think
I'd be like you?
Hey. Don't you work today?
Don't you have a lesson today?
Usually yes, but not today.
- Why not?
- Mr. Choi called.
He has other plans
and can't come today.
Plans?
- What plans?
- I don't know.
I made a friend.
He's really cool and kind.
Don't look at me like that.
I'm here as a customer.
- Hey.
- How are things these days?
What do you mean?
Don't you need medication?
No. I'm fine.
Tell the truth.
About what? I said I'm fine.
If you're that worried,
raise my allowance.
I never have enough money...
Seo Yeon.
What are you doing? It's not funny.
Don't do this.
Seo Yeon.
Seo Yeon!
I said don't do this!
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
I'm okay.
I'm fine if I live
where it's bright.
You're not well yet.
Let's see a doctor.
I'm sorry.
It's my fault.
No, it's my fault.
I'm sorry, Seo Jun.
Darn it!
I didn't tell you because
I knew you'd be like this!
Darn it.
Where are you going?
Out!
That idiot.
Send him back to
the doctor he used to see.
He listens to you
more than he does us.
He acts like I'm invisible.
He calls himself a guy
and doesn't want Seo Yeon to worry.
I pleaded with you.
I told you not to tell.
What?
Oh, by the way...
The day of Mom and Dad's accident.
Was I not at home?
I think I left to see someone.
Why do you ask?
I just wanted to check.
Do you remember something?
No, not really.
No, don't bother, okay?
Is Seo Jun very angry?
Did you tell?
Well, I just...
I thought Seo Yeon would be worried.
Did I mess up?
No.
You did right.
It was the right thing.
"Why isn't she coming?"
"She said she had something to say
and asked for my address."
"Why isn't she coming?"
"Does she think I'm a joke?"
That's what I thought.
What did I have to say?
If I said I'd see him at night,
it must've been important.
You're home. You're late.
Yes.
So...
You found out?
Joo Seo Jun...
The truth is,
when you weren't home,
there was a power cut.
That time too...
He reacted?
I'm sorry.
I wanted to tell you...
It's okay.
Seo Jun would've stopped you.
May I ask you for the reason?
On the day of my parents' accident,
as soon as we got the call,
we quickly headed over
to the hospital.
We forgot about baby Seo Jun...
who was sleeping alone in the room.
Mom.
Mom...
He was there all alone
until the morning.
It must've been awfully scary.
He just woke up from his sleep
like any other day,
but Mom and Dad were gone...
forever.
It must've been tough for you too.
But...
it gets better...
over time.
It may be a slow process,
but it will...
get better.
[Episode 10]
Should we tell her?
At this point?
I'm not sure if it's a good idea
to keep hiding this.
- If she finds out...
- What if she remembers?
Wouldn't that be worse?
We should hope that she doesn't.
[Ms. Lee Kang Hee]
Hello?
Right now?
Oh, yes.
I have to go out.
Who is it this time?
I saw new shirts and suits
all over your room.
There's still a woman
who would buy those for you?
It's not like that.
Enough is enough, Won Jae.
I said, it's not like that.
What are you doing?
Is this all yours?
I can't really say
that it's completely ours,
we possess the most shares
for this company.
I can't believe I became a servant
for a family of a conglomerate.
You aren't a servant.
We're in a contractual relationship.
Let's go.
Let's make it more casual.
It looks so expensive.
Do you have business meetings
at this hour of the day?
It's like a power move.
They're going to put me down
with alcohol.
Put you down?
You use scary words.
See you later.
- Goodness.
- I'll see you next time.
Yes, let's do that.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
- See you next time.
- All right.
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
Yes, I'm fine.
You aren't a heavy drinker, are you?
I'm sure you have other chauffeurs.
Why did you ask me to come?
Because they work for the company.
They have to make a report
to their bosses.
I don't want Grandma or Dad to know
that I do these things.
Why do you work that hard?
If I don't do it,
my dad will have to.
My dad loves to paint.
He used to do that from time to time
when I was younger.
I still remember...
how happy he was.
But after my uncle said
he won't take over the company,
my dad couldn't say
that he doesn't want to.
He's too nice.
So I have to cover for him
with the things I can do.
Ms. Lee, you're
more warm-hearted than you look.
You look awfully cold-hearted
on the outside.
Do you usually
compliment people that often?
You called me
pretty and warm-hearted.
People don't usually say that
to each other's faces.
I can say anything
to hit on a woman.
Are you still hitting on me?
If I do, will you fall for it?
It depends on what you do.
- What?
- You too.
You're more warm-hearted
than I thought.
We should keep the working hour
written on our contract.
Let me know if you get home
after midnight.
I'll pay for the extra time.
I'll drop you home.
It'll only take 10 minutes on foot.
I'm going to take a walk
and try to wake up.
I don't want my parents
to be worried.
As you all know,
Chief Director Lee has resigned
from his position...
due to personal reasons.
But fortunately,
an even wonderful and amazing person
has taken the position.
Let me introduce him to you.
It's Mr. Lee...
I mean,
it's Chief Director Lee Min Hyuk!
No way.
My name is Lee Min Hyuk.
Applaud!
Congratulations, sir!
Everyone, get ready for class.
Congratulations, sir.
Sir, hold on.
Did you see that?
Everyone started
treating me differently.
Are you...
upset at me?
This wasn't what I meant...
when I said I wanted
to work with you for a long time.
Do you think...
Kang Woo is more suitable
for this position than I am?
Or do you want him
to keep his position...
because you've chosen your greed
over your students?
It is true that the position
makes the person.
You said others changed.
But in my eyes,
you're the one who's changed.
I must go to class now.
Are you in the middle of a war?
Why are you devouring your food?
My gosh.
Here.
What's wrong with you?
What do you mean?
One drop of water on your pants,
and you'd freak out
and take them off.
Seo Yeon will be here soon.
He's not a human, but a dog.
What is he doing?
Hold on.
If Seo Yeon is getting off work,
then Mi Kyung must be as well.
[Kim Mi Kyung]
Don't call me! Don't!
I love it.
I got to hear your voice,
so I'm happy.
What a cutie.
Are you sick?
I'm sorry.
I was too rude back there.
Honestly speaking, you deserve
that position the most.
You were right.
I placed my greed over my students.
I'm sorry.
Maybe I need to apologize as well.
I took this position
because of my greed.
I wanted Kang Woo to disappear
from your sight.
What?
You see,
I like you.
Kang Woo, I'm in front
of your house. Where are you?
Me? I'm in front of yours.
What? Why are you there?
Since when were you there?
Never mind. Stay put.
You're such an idiot.
You should've called first.
I blurted it out without realizing.
You see,
I like you.
I've been liking you a lot...
for a very long time.
I...
I like Kang Woo.
That's right.
I like him.
I blurted out that I like Kang Woo.
- What are you doing there?
- My gosh!
Hey.
What are you doing here?
I was thinking
about picking you up...
but thought it'd be embarrassing
to run into someone.
What about you?
Why were you at my house?
I wanted to ask you out on a date.
What?
I thought about it.
How about we start off
by doing things that others do?
It was so messy up until now.
Let's go on a date.
Let's go.
What did you just say?
Let's hang out together.
No, you said something else.
No, that's what I said.
- That's not true.
- Just get inside.
Let's hang out!
[Seo Yeon, let's hang out!]
- Isn't it pretty?
- It sure is.
I've never been
to such a place before.
Do you want to take a photo?
1, 2, 3.
I'm excited! Spin it!
- I want that one.
- Which one?
- That one.
- That one?
The one inside.
I think I can do it.
You can't do it.
Did you see that?
Darn it!
What was that? You're good.
Here.
Isn't it good? You eat so well.
- Should we go inside?
- Yes.
It looks similar...
to your wedding dress.
You remember that?
Hey, Kang Woo.
Hey, man. You look so nice.
Are you getting married?
My gosh.
Oh, no.
The groom usually wears
something like this for a wedding.
No, it's...
I was wondering if
the baby groom is getting married.
Looking sharp, man.
You look great.
This would go with that dress.
There's this wedding dress
that I dream of.
I'm done.
Really? Show me. Now. Now!
You can't make fun of me.
No, never. I totally promise.
Yes, this is it.
This is what I've been dreaming of.
Thanks, Kang Woo.
You're a genius.
Why are you so good at drawing?
Thank you.
I thought about this, and...
This time, about what?
You thought about
a lot of things today.
Did something happen?
I think I wanted
to say this to you 15 years ago,
on the day
I asked for your address...
saying I have something to tell you.
You remembered?
No, I tried to guess.
What is it?
That I like you too.
What?
Okay, here we go.
Look forward.
In 1, 2, 3.
Honey!
It looks like he went through
so much trouble lately.
That mysophobic kid
left the dishes undone.
Who am I talking to?
Hey, honey. Where are you?
What are you doing there?
What? Nothing. Honey, we should go.
Why?
Kang Woo isn't here.
There's no reason to stay.
- Let's go.
- Goodness.
- You're acting weird.
- I'm not. Let's go.
- It's weird.
- Move.
- Honey!
Honey, honey! No! Babe!
No...
What do I do now? What should I do?
What do I do? Darn it.
Gosh, honey. I hurt my shoulder.
Honey, my shoulder!
Honey!
- Honey, my shoulder. I pulled it!
- Goodness, Kang Woo.
What in the world is he doing?
I think I fractured my shoulder.
I have to go see a doctor.
Let's go to the hospital.
Let's just go.
Will you be quiet?
- Goodness, my shoulder.
- What's all this?
- Honey, look.
- Goodness!
Honey.
It hurts so much...
She's...
Min Hyuk!
Who is she?
Right.
What?
Don't tell Kang Woo.
Okay.
Are you done crying?
I'm not crying!
So why did you want to see a movie?
Watching a movie is the essence
of dating. Don't you know?
Watching a movie is
the essence of dating?
You always see that on TV.
When there's a scary scene
in the movie,
the woman goes, "Goodness".
And she falls into the guy's arms.
Did you think that would work on me?
Darn it. I knew it wouldn't.
That's why I chose a sad movie.
If you cry,
I was going to wipe your tears,
hold you in my arms,
and comfort you too.
Yes, so did you think
that would work on me?
Are you sure it wasn't sad?
The dog ran miles
to look for its owner...
while getting abused
and mistreated by humans.
It was sad. I was heartbroken.
But still, I don't cry.
I see.
You're tough.
You're such a tough woman.
I can't.
I can't cry...
no matter what happens.
No matter how sad
a movie or a book is,
it won't make me cry.
I'm really sad right now.
I just need to shed
one teardrop, please?
But...
it gets better over time.
It may be a slow process,
but it will...
get better.
I never cried...
ever since that day.
Not even once for the last 15 years.
I'm a really dry person...
with a lot of faults here and there.
Are you sure that's all right?
What do you mean?
May I take what you just said
as how you want to...
start dating me?
Can you take someone like me?
It took us...
15 years to get a new start.
Back then, it may have ended
with an awful misunderstanding.
So do you think I'll lose...
my second chance?
You're dead,
Seo Yeon.
So you became the chief director
of Shinhwa High School.
Yes.
I see. That position
might be much better...
for you than Kang Woo.
But Kang Woo was
supposed to do that for a year.
Why couldn't you wait a bit longer?
Is that why you called me
at such a late hour?
I found that at Kang Woo's house.
Isn't she the woman who was with you
at the department store?
She is.
I thought she was dating you.
Right.
Aren't you dating her?
No.
Then wait,
is Kang Woo...
In times like these,
it's not all that bad...
that I cannot lie.
I can make an excuse and tell him
that I had no other choice.
You can ask me, Aunt.
I will tell you.
What is her relationship...
with Kang Woo?
He likes her.
He probably wants to marry her too.
Okay. I see.
Thank you for telling me.
I like Kang Woo.
That's right. I like him.
I thought so.
I can't give you my support,
but I won't come between you two.
Thank you.
And...
I'm sorry.
Mr. Lee, you're a nice person.
I told you that I'm not nice.
That I like you too.
I'll look at Seo Yeon
as soon as I wake up.
I have something to say.
What's your address?
I'll go there right now.
Mom!
Help us.
Do you want some?
I was there.
I was there too. I was.
What?
I asked them to go.
Hey, what's wrong?
I told Mom and Dad...
that I need to go out.
Right now?
Yes, Kang Woo
just sent me his address.
Like you two said,
I'll go see him face-to-face...
to say that I'm sorry
and that I didn't mean it.
Then he might forgive me.
Can't you do it at school tomorrow?
Tomorrow is my school trip.
I have to apologize today
to hang out with him tomorrow.
Please? Please?
Come on, Mom.
Okay. I'll drive you.
Really?
Goodness, you had a glass of beer.
You can't drive.
Oh, right. I'm sorry, Seo Yeon.
Mom...
Okay, fine. I'll go with you.
I'll come with you.
Why?
I want to see who this guy is.
I need to see this guy
who's giving you so much trouble.
Let's go.
- Let me grab some clothes.
- Okay.
What about Seo Jun?
He just fell asleep.
He should be fine for three hours.
Let's hurry.
- Won Jae.
- Let's go.
Won Jae,
we're going out with Seo Yeon.
Keep your eyes on Seo Jun.
What? Okay.
Seo Yeon, what are you doing?
Come on out.
Okay.
Seo Yeon.
Wake up.
Dad...
It's okay.
It's okay, Seo Yeon.
You never know...
when a man should
protect the people whom he loves.
So you should learn...
how to tie your shoelaces
so that they don't come undone.
Oh, right.
Seo Yeon.
So do you think I'll lose
my second chance?
I asked them to go.
It's because of me.
They passed away because of me.
Because of me.
There was...
no second chance for us.
[Love With Flaws]
I never knew anything.
I'll wait quietly.
I'll hold myself back
even when I miss you.
Did you get sick of me?
It looks like this is great timing.
Don't lay a finger on him.
If you keep doing that,
it'll make me feel very awful.
Did you just see Joo Hee?
Look at yourself. What's with her?
Let's call off the contract.
Have you seen someone like this?
What's going on with this family?
What are you doing?
Don't let your guard down.
As soon as you make a mistake,
I won't miss my chance.