[English subtitles are available.]
[Episode 8]
I'm sorry.
What?
For everything in the past,
what happened recently,
right now,
and even in the future.
I'll continue to be sorry.
I'll make you concerned.
I'll get on your nerves.
I'll make you think about me.
What do you mean?
I'm sorry...
that I like you.
Seo Yeon!
Seo Yeon, wait!
Hey, stop!
Seo Yeon!
Why is she so fast?
Gosh, side cramps.
It has been forever since I ran.
I haven't worked out lately.
Kang Woo,
what's your plan this time?
Back in middle school,
it was your misunderstanding,
Seo Yeon.
I didn't ask you out...
because of that stupid bet.
The wine bar?
Yes.
It's true. I blamed you...
for what happened back then. But...
when I confessed my feelings
the third time,
I meant it.
Actually,
I had no idea that Hyun Soo...
came up with that lie.
And of course,
I meant everything I said...
to you...
this morning.
What do you think?
Man, you're so clingy.
Clingy?
No.
I didn't mean clingy.
It's just too long.
You should have
resolved the misunderstanding...
as soon as things happened.
I didn't know...
that I still,
even now,
liked her...
so much.
Don't try to make excuses
about what happened in the past.
Keep showing her
that you are sincere.
I'm sure the misunderstanding
will get resolved naturally.
Then how do I show her...
that I'm sincere?
Hey.
- What?
- Are you ill?
You aren't feverish.
Even dogs don't mess with you
when you eat.
How dare you?
Hey, why aren't you eating?
Where are you going?
Seo Yeon.
Goodness, they're unbelievable.
That's it.
Yes, you should follow her.
You can do it, Mr. Lee.
[Idiot]
The receiver cannot be reached.
You will be directed to voicemail.
How dare you ignore my call?
The receiver cannot be reached.
Forget it. I'm done.
I'm done! It's over!
Are you all right, Mr. Park?
What is it?
I just heard some noises.
If you're fine, please excuse me.
Gosh, darn it. Where's my privacy?
Where's my phone?
What am I doing right now?
Why should I avoid him?
Are you all right?
The chief director
did something again, didn't he?
Not yet.
I don't know what's going on,
but if you don't plan
on staying here forever,
come with me.
Why not?
Do you plan on staying here forever?
It's not that.
My legs fell asleep.
Oh, gosh.
Goodness, that feels good.
Gosh, my legs almost killed me.
Why don't you put
some spit on your nose?
Come on, do you think I'm stupid?
You only did it twice.
You have to do it three times.
You're lying.
I'm serious.
You can't do that
as the school doctor.
Tell me what I should do.
I learned this in med school.
Seo Yeon.
You avoided me
all day long, didn't you?
But what can you do?
You'll have to report to me
about the training anyway.
What time is it? Okay.
In 5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
This is the training journal
for the track team today.
From Joo Seo Yeon.
Unbelievable!
[Baekga Corporation
sexual harassment]
["Fifth Son of Baekga Charged with
Drug Abuse and Sexual Assault"]
You aren't afraid, and you're bold.
You're an amazing woman, Ms. Lee.
Tell me about the car.
Sure, ma'am.
How did you find me?
Your name and number were
all left with the police.
Isn't it illegal to search up
information about a stranger?
I heard it is.
Which one is the most expensive?
I'm thinking about buying one.
What are you doing?
I mistook you.
Yes, as a criminal.
That's why I'm going
to give you money as my apology.
This is you apologizing?
Isn't this better
than just saying it?
My gosh.
Gosh.
It looks nice.
My secretary will come later.
It'll be a full option.
What a cool brat she is.
Did you see the news about
that brat Gook Hwa?
Thanks to him,
the chairman is enraged.
How great would it be
if you could cheer him up?
Right?
Remember the guy who had
30 million dollars?
Despite your rude actions,
he wanted to see you again.
Treat him better this time.
I can't avoid him forever.
What are you scheming, Kang Woo?
Nothing.
How did you come here?
Does Lee Joo Hee live here?
She recognized me
and opened the door.
Your room is quite tidy.
How cute.
What is it? Tell me.
What do you want from me?
Why are you doing this?
What do you mean?
You said you liked...
Why did you say that strange thing?
"Strange"?
- About how I liked...
- Yes, that.
I was just being sincere.
Just act normally.
If you start thinking about me,
then that's good news.
Do you think I'd believe you?
What? What is it?
I finally got to see you.
I'm happy I did. I'll be going now.
What?
Mr. President?
"President"?
No. I'm the chief director.
What?
"Joo Seo Jun"?
You're Seo Yeon's younger brother?
You're handsome.
What was that?
He's the chief director
of our school.
"Chief director"?
Then why did he come to our company?
No. Why did he come to our house?
I think he came to see Ms. Joo.
Why did he come to see her?
What is going on?
Hey.
Are you really not going
to tell her?
What? Tell her what?
I don't know
what you're talking about.
Hey, could someone
who has always lied...
be telling the truth?
Kang Woo confessed, didn't he?
I knew there was something
going on that night.
And all that ruckus at the school
as well.
- "That night"?
- Yes, there was one night...
when I met him.
What did he say?
Well...
I doubt he's telling the truth.
It is the truth.
Gosh, I don't want to put him
on a pedestal.
I'm on Team Hangook Medicine.
But on second thought,
Kang Woo seems slightly better.
Are you drunk?
Yes. They should fight
fair and square...
and let the stronger one win.
You are drunk. Let's go.
All that drama with Park Hyun Soo
was Hyun Soo's doing all along.
Kang Woo had no idea.
So he was being sincere
when he confessed that time.
Brace yourself.
It seems like you'll be surrounded
by guys soon.
It is a pity
that they're both good-looking.
Winter is coming, you wench.
It's coming.
This is Hi-Seven's last title song.
It's about the ardent...
and innocent one-sided love
of a man.
The title is "Sincerity".
What do you say?
Gosh, doesn't this sound too old?
Who commits to such
one-sided love these days?
It's all about obsession
and possession.
"You're mine!" Things like these.
Don't you agree?
So?
What happened to the two?
What?
A song needs to have a plot.
Does the singer get
a happily-ever-after?
I hope...
you can stay by my side,
Seo Yeon.
I'll make you concerned.
I'll get on your nerves.
I'll make you think about me.
I'm sorry...
that I like you.
So he meant all that?
Did you think I was that low?
Like a jerk
who asks girls out on a bet?
Do you really think that's who I am?
Even that time as well?
Seo Yeon?
Why did you come here?
How long have you been waiting?
You should've called.
Oh, right.
I didn't think about that.
You weren't home,
so I just thought I'd wait...
until you did.
What is it? Did something happen?
It'd be rude of me
to keep avoiding you.
I'll bring something to drink.
I have a question.
I want to know what happened
that day 15 years ago.
I'm starting to think...
that there's more to it
than what I know.
Were you being...
sincere?
Okay, this time, it's Joo Seo Yeon.
You take all this money...
if she says yes
when you ask her out.
If you get turned down, you lose it.
So who wants to ask her out?
What if she really says yes?
- Then I'll...
- No!
Seo Yeon...
is my friend.
What are you blabbering about?
Don't do it. If you need more money,
I'll bring more.
So don't do this.
Wait.
- How much is that?
- Don't do that.
I wasn't strong enough,
but I had a lot of money.
I could stop them for that time,
but I didn't know
when they'd try to do that again.
I wanted to protect you
by your side.
But...
I don't know
why I felt so confident that day.
I had no idea
that you would reject me.
I don't like you...
because you're ugly...
and fat.
About the lie
that Hyun Soo was dating you.
I heard you didn't know about it.
Is that true?
Well, that's...
I was the bad one here.
I misunderstood you,
judged you,
and came up with my own idea.
No. I could understand
how you could've misunderstood it.
It's my fault for not explaining
to you properly.
It's my fault.
No, you did your part...
15 years ago,
that day,
and now as well.
I'm sorry for not giving you
my answer all this time.
I'm sorry...
for hurting you.
And...
I'm sorry...
about this too.
Why?
Okay.
I know that this is a petty
and childish thing to ask.
Why?
I've been too mean, right?
You know, I did that on purpose.
I was immature.
I was immature, so that's how
I wanted to get your attention.
- That's not why.
- What if I'm nice to you?
What if I treat you really well?
There's no point.
Is there...
someone else?
Is it...
- Lee Min...
- I can't...
ever like someone
who has your looks.
- What?
- I don't like handsome guys.
- I got sick and tired of people...
who look like you my whole life.
Wait.
What?
Kang Woo will understand too.
What have I...
been doing all this time?
Joo Seo Jun of Class 4
in 11th grade.
Please come
to the chief director's office.
Immediately!
Did you want to see me?
Take a seat.
May I ask why you wanted to see me?
Seo Jun.
Yes?
Why on earth did you do it?
Why did you bother
your sister so much?
- Pardon?
- So you're a trainee...
at HS Entertainment.
Well, I...
I'm going to put
your life in pure torment!
Hey. You...
I can take this out
for a test-drive, right?
Why did you lead such an awful life?
What is this crazy jerk saying?
You crazy jerk. Stop the car!
Pull over now!
Why did you bother Seo Yeon?
Why?
Why did you do it?
Why did you make it so hard
for Seo Yeon?
Why?
- Sit down.
- Okay.
Don't lurk around Seo Yeon.
That's none of your business.
I don't have much to lose in life.
Seo Yeon's abnormal prejudice
against people's looks...
is partially our fault,
but it's not completely our fault.
There's something deeper inside.
Somewhere deep that you don't
even know where it's hiding.
So she will never like you
with that face of yours.
What is that?
Finish that and go.
There's something deeper inside.
Somewhere deep that you don't
even know where it's hiding.
It's a problem after a problem.
No, will there even be a problem
for me to resolve?
I don't even have a chance.
Hello?
She doesn't like good-looking men.
- Pardon?
- My face.
It's my face.
She doesn't like my handsome face.
She doesn't like me...
because I'm handsome.
Come on!
If you don't like that face,
give it to me.
He always calls me when I'm eating.
Hang in there. Just a bit longer.
I can't eat this
because it's too soggy!
How many days has it been
since he came to work?
Will he never come to work?
Get a grip.
This isn't the time
to be distracted.
Seo Yeon!
I got my rank up by 100 places!
Good job, my boy.
Ho Dol! I did it!
Come on.
Darn you.
100 places!
Joo Hee.
Let me see your report card.
My gosh.
How many places did you go up by?
You did so well on the tests,
Joo Hee.
Thank you.
It's all thanks to
the tutoring classes you got me.
Your tutor is an awesome teacher.
It must've been hard
to teach Seo Jun.
Ms. Joo.
Seo Jun...
Mom...
Don't tell Seo Yeon.
Why? Is Seo Jun bullying you again?
- That little jerk.
- No, that's not it.
I wanted to tell you
that Seo Jun tried very hard.
Right? I guess he's dying
to become a celebrity.
Great work, Joo Hee.
Get changed and come out.
I should have told her.
Are you okay?
Hey, stay focused.
I'm sorry.
Do you think you're all good
now that your grades barely passed?
No, I'm sorry.
As you all know,
Hi-Seven will be performing
on a big stage very soon.
And two of you will be chosen
as their backup dancers.
You know how important it is
to have experiences, don't you?
It's your chance to perform
before thousands of people.
So pull yourself together, okay?
- Yes.
From the top.
Get ready.
See you tomorrow.
- See you.
- Goodbye.
I really want to be
a backup dancer for Hi-Seven.
Don't you?
- Hey.
- What?
Get a hold of yourself.
Jung Ho, may I sleep
at your place tonight?
What? All of a sudden? Why?
Just because.
I don't want to go home.
- Did you run away?
- No?
No, you can.
But why?
Because something is giving me
an allergic reaction at home.
Do you have a dog?
What?
You're right.
Something like that.
Hey!
Why haven't you been
coming to school?
I've been busy.
Why? Is someone looking for me?
No, not really.
Darn it.
You.
What are you doing?
You two are here.
Mother, will you have a taste?
- Sure, let me see.
- Okay.
- Hey.
- Give me a moment.
Stop standing around and help out.
- Yes.
- Yes!
That jerk.
Hey, I think Min Hyuk is
dating someone.
Can you sound him out?
Why should I?
His parents don't really care
about him,
so I want to step in as his aunt.
Mom. Ms. Oh. Please.
I want to be concerned
about my own children,
but there's nothing to meddle with.
Happy?
You might have to be concerned
pretty soon.
Goodness, are you seeing someone?
I never stop seeing someone.
Tell me.
What's your ideal son-in-law like?
Goodness, forget it.
Is he doing all right?
Honey?
First, it's Kang Woo,
and now Min Hyuk too?
Those old women are
going to go crazy.
Ta-da.
What do you think?
It's my beloved recipe.
Honey.
What do you think, Mother?
I already had a taste before.
Oh, right. What do you think?
It's good.
Beef, mint chocolate,
and soy sauce marinated crab.
Everything he used is delicious.
Of course, it has to be good.
That's Director Lee of Shinhwa Food!
Gosh, don't you think
I'm the best cook ever?
I'll serve.
Goodness, it's so delicious.
My gosh.
In times like these,
it's a wonder
that our company functions well...
without any huge trouble.
Min Hyuk.
Yes, Grandma.
I let Kang Woo work
as a chief director for a year...
to see what he can do.
It's your turn.
Think about a position
that you want.
Will you really...
stop working as a doctor?
Probably.
Is there anything else
you want to do?
Not yet. What about you?
I have something. That's why
I said yes to Grandma's offer.
I'm jealous that you have
something you want to do.
Didn't you want to be a doctor?
People said
only the best can become one.
I wanted to see
if I was one of the best or not.
My gosh.
You're such a show-off,
but what you said is true,
so I can't even say anything.
Hey.
If you don't want to do it,
then don't.
You know
that Grandma isn't that uptight.
You should have a talk with her.
Look, Won Seok.
My face looks so funny.
He won't ever
talk to me again, right?
He probably
doesn't even want to see me.
Good. You don't like him
because of his looks.
It'll be great to not see him.
Hey, go home.
You only do
as you please, don't you?
What?
- Seo Yeon?
- When did he call you again?
Hey, you shouldn't do that.
Don't appear and disappear
as you like, okay?
See? Doesn't that make you angry?
What? I'll...
It's me, Won Seok.
Seo Yeon had a drink.
Did she have a lot to drink?
A bit.
Bye.
How are you going to deal
with the humiliation later?
Okay, you should
just erase it from your memories.
[Call history, delete]
I'm the one who got turned down.
Why are you doing this?
Hey.
You came back.
Not yet.
Give me a little more time.
I'm only human,
so I need some time,
Seo Yeon.
You're going to vanish
for 15 years again?
I won't.
You promised.
Yes.
That was a dream, right?
[Recent Calls]
Yes. It was.
When I heard that
you were working at a hospital,
I thought you had gone insane.
This is Shinhwa Food's, right?
Yes.
So you're planning
to slowly climb up the ladder?
What do you mean?
You're the eldest son
of Shinhwa Food,
but you have an older brother.
That's going to cause
some issues, right?
Leave if you're going
to spew nonsense.
I didn't know you had a visitor.
I'll come back later.
What? Isn't she that lady
from the party?
Gosh, they say women transform
when they get dolled up.
I almost didn't recognize her.
Get lost.
What?
I said, get lost.
I'm sorry for barging in.
Did you hear everything?
It'd be strange if I said no.
I'm the chief director's...
I mean, I'm Kang Woo's cousin.
I'm sorry for deceiving you.
You didn't. You just didn't tell me.
And...
I already knew.
What?
That day, when we went
to that party...
How did you seduce him?
What?
You're quite talented.
Are you pregnant?
But then again,
he's such a responsible guy.
No wonder it worked.
Is she on the phone with someone,
using wireless earphones?
I'm talking to you.
Me?
I had no idea since I didn't get
what you were saying.
As a fellow woman,
I'm utterly humiliated.
I know he's the grandson
of Shinhwa Food,
but how could you grab
onto him by using your body?
Are you talking about Lee Kang Woo?
Do you know him?
Who?
You were talking
about the grandson of Shinhwa Food.
Min Hyuk.
I'm talking about Min Hyuk.
What? Mr. Lee?
You knew?
- Then why...
- Why didn't I tell you?
I didn't feel the need to.
And it doesn't change who you are.
Whether you're the grandson
of Shinhwa Food or not,
it didn't matter to me.
Should I have told you about it?
Did I make a mistake?
No.
Every time people knew...
about my family,
they treated me differently.
Thank you for being different.
I'm truly happy that...
you're a faculty member here.
Let's continue working here
for a very long time.
The uniforms look great on you!
You look dazzling!
[Shinhwa High School]
Now that the midterms are done,
let's focus on the upcoming
track and field match.
Also,
the chief director has
high expectations for you...
and even volunteered
to become a sponsor.
So let's make sure
we can return his favor.
Let's do it!
1, 2, 3.
- We can do it!
- Let's do it!
- Let's go.
[Address Book]
[Call Lee Kang Woo]
What right do I have?
You're so cold-hearted.
How could you not send
a single text when I haven't...
been showing up for days on end?
What? What?
Thanks...
for coming.
Sure. If you're thankful,
buy me some food.
What?
Okay.
Where should we go?
What are you craving?
I'm not sure.
This is it?
I'll treat you to something nicer.
Just tell me what you want.
Is it possible for you
to buy something more expensive...
than I, the conglomerate heir, can?
Well... No.
This is what I'm craving right now.
It's actually quite good.
Is this your first time eating that?
You are indeed a conglomerate heir.
I just didn't want to get fat.
But then again, it was all useless.
By any chance,
did you lose weight
because of what I said...
15 years ago?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Hey, don't be ridiculous.
Thanks to you, I became handsome.
Everyone except for you
loves this face and body.
Here. Eat.
Isn't it good?
It really is.
- Hey.
- I've never had this before.
Should I teach you
how to peel an egg?
Yes.
Didn't you break the egg?
Bye.
You're going
to the match tomorrow, right?
Was it for two days?
What? You remembered.
Good luck.
Thanks. I'll make sure
we live up to your expectations.
Don't overwork the kids
and cause injury.
Don't worry.
Mr. Lee is coming as well.
Bye.
Min Hyuk is?
Baek Jang Mi?
What happened?
Where have you been?
I told you to call me
if anything happened.
I lost your number.
Where are you staying at the moment?
Are you even staying anywhere?
What is this?
Are we running a welfare center
here or what?
Whatever.
People
on the second floor should...
take care of whatever happens there.
I'm going to work.
I'm fine with it.
It's settled then.
You should stay here
for the time being, Jang Mi.
Hey, look.
I'm right here.
Can't you see me here?
Who are you?
Are you sure you live here?
Seo Yeon, this isn't right!
You didn't come home
for the past few days.
How dare you talk back to me?
If you sleep somewhere else
one more time,
you'll be dead meat.
- Okay.
- Okay?
Okay.
Let's go. Come on.
This is so annoying!
You'd better pick that up!
My gosh, this is so small.
It didn't seem this small
from outside.
What?
I've never shared a room
with someone before.
I see. Okay.
How could you let a stranger
into your home?
She has a pretty sad story.
Are you serious? What if
she decided to stay there forever?
I don't know. I'll think
about that once I come back.
Okay. Tell Joo Hee
I'll be rooting for her.
Call me once you get there.
Something is definitely fishy.
How did Baek Jang Mi know
where Seo Yeon lived and wait there?
Why does this jerk keep calling me?
The receiver cannot be reached.
She was on the phone just now.
But she's dodging my call?
She's not answering my calls
on purpose, right?
Pardon?
It's nothing.
The flight leaves at 6 p.m. tonight.
Who's coming on this trip?
Backup dancers for Hi-Seven,
you, and me.
The stylists will be coming
before the concert tomorrow.
Okay.
Are you waiting for a call?
No, I'm not waiting.
Yes, Mr. Seo.
- Did you pack everything?
- Yes.
Make sure
you didn't forget anything.
- Yes, ma'am.
- Hello.
Hey, you.
What brings you here,
Chief Director Lee?
What do you mean?
Am I not allowed to tag along?
I can come, right?
- Yes.
Where's Min Hyuk?
He had to do something,
so he'll come tomorrow.
Is that so?
- Guys, let's go.
- Okay.
[Shinhwa High School]
Do you want it?
You look...
Are you all right?
I've never been...
on a bus over in 15 years.
Goodness, you're so frail.
Why are you so frail?
All of your muscles are for nothing.
Look out the window.
It helps a bit when you get carsick.
[Baekjejang]
This is the place?
That's our accommodation?
Yes. Why?
We're here!
Don't get off!
Get back on the bus.
What are you doing?
This is unacceptable...
by the standards of Shinhwa
Foundation and High School.
I had no choice
if I was going to meet the budget.
Get in.
Don't get off!
- Get in.
- Why?
You'd better go back in.
Get in.
[Shinhwa High School]
Hey, isn't this over our budget?
It's up to me.
Guys, go unpack.
- Yes, sir!
But still.
Just think about your students.
To do well tomorrow,
they need to eat well,
have a nice place to wash,
and sleep well.
Don't you agree?
[Shinhwa High School]
Goodness.
- Father.
- No, sit down.
Why did you choose
such an expensive place?
It's been a long time since
you returned. I wanted to treat you.
Okay.
I wished Mother came back with you.
I came back to raise donations.
I need to go back tomorrow.
That soon?
You're not even going to meet
with Grandma?
Well...
She's healthy, right?
Yes, she's well.
Father, have a drink.
No.
You're never...
going to be a doctor again?
There are countless people...
who can't be a doctor
even if they want to.
Giving up on it is
that easy for you.
You have never given me
your compliment for 28 years.
But it didn't take you five minutes
to scold me.
Are you not interested in...
why I quit?
Whatever the reason is,
it sounds like an excuse to me.
If you're going to quit,
join Doctors Without Borders.
You ought to see it for yourself
and experience it yourself.
And you'll realize that
you're being ungrateful.
You are...
missing out
on so many things in life.
"Ungrateful"?
Mr. Lee.
We changed our accommodation.
I'll send you the address.
I know
what I've been missing out on...
because of my meeting with you.
Enjoy the meal.
It's expensive.
So don't leave any food.
What do you think?
Isn't this really nice?
My goodness,
Kang Woo is really loaded.
But I don't know
if I should let him do this.
Hey, he wants to spend his money.
Just let him spend his money.
I should've tagged along.
You should come now.
My room is really big!
- Should I then?
- Are you really going to come?
It won't take long
if I take the plane. Wait for me.
What?
Goodness, she's the best
when it comes to taking initiatives.
This is nice.
Are you a fool?
And you call yourself a runner?
You couldn't even dodge that.
Did you just dodge that?
Not again!
You did that on purpose, didn't you?
Now that you're here,
keep your eyes on those.
Don't let anyone steal them.
Look at how excited you are.
Hey! Come in
and put your feet in the water!
The sea may look
very clean on the outside,
but it's filled with microorganisms
that aren't visible in our eyes.
Stop it. Don't do it. Don't!
Come at me, waves!
Hey!
Goodness, I knew you would do this.
If you knew, why didn't you stop me?
Always making excuses.
Hey!
Anyway, isn't it fun?
I got all wet.
I'm sorry you got wet because of me.
It seemed like
you were feeling under the weather.
You'll catch a cold.
Let's go back inside.
I'll stay like this...
so that...
you won't have to see my face.
Please let me stay like this,
Seo Yeon.
Ms. Joo.
I'm at the accommodation,
but you aren't here.
Where are...
Grandma.
There's a position I want.
So that...
you won't have to see my face.
Please let me stay like this,
Seo Yeon.
Is it really over?
Who do you think you are?
Who do you think you are
to annoy me?
Why do you make me concerned?
Why do you make me think of you?
Why do you make me see you
when I don't want to? Why?
If you don't want to see me,
you don't have to.
Just stay there.
I'll make sure
you won't have to see me.
[Love With Flaws]
Seo Yeon is concerned about me.
This is great.
- Did you like it?
- I didn't feel anything.
Do it with me. Let's do it once.
- Let's do it.
- Right now?
You move your body well.
I can totally tell
that you're bad at dating.
You're my woman from now on.
You crazy idiot!
Who do you think you are?
What's wrong?
Do you remember?
Mom and Dad passed away
because of me.