[tense music playing]
I want a divorce.
I don't want to stay here.
Where will you go, Varee?
You really think you can run from me?
[gun cocks]
You think I couldn't find you?
Our daughter is leaving with me.
- I'm not letting you go.
- [gunshot]
- [unsettling music playing]
- [Varee breathing shakily]
[door creaking]
[gasps, muffled sobs]
[breathing shakily]
Based on the evidence we have,
we can't conclude that you brought
your daughter here with you.
Wait, what's wrong with you?
[breathing shakily]
- You think I'm lying?!
- [glass shatters]
I said she was in the back seat,
but the camera didn't catch it.
Don't you understand!?
That bloodstain is yours, isn't it?
We'd like to check your dress.
Check why? What for?
We want to confirm that the blood
on your dress is really yours.
What are you thinking?!
Are you out of your mind? I'm her mother!
I'm her mother, goddamn!
We're really sorry for having to do this.
This is to prove your innocence.
- [tense music playing]
- [Varee sniffles]
Happy now…
Officer?
Ms. Varee…
did you happen to hurt your daughter?
[foreboding music playing forcefully]
[Varee hyperventilating]
[gasping for breath]
[gasps, muffled sobs]
[Min crying]
[panicked breaths]
[panicked breaths continue]
[whimpering, sniffling]
[sobbing]
[line ringing]
[Yutthachai] Hello?
Hey. [crying]
You came here and took our daughter.
[sobbing] You came here and took her away.
Tell me you came here.
You took her away, didn't you? [sobbing]
What are you talking about?
Where are you now?
How on earth are you taking care of her?
[continues sobbing]
Yes, hello.
Hello?
Who are you?
I'm with the police.
I'm questioning Ms. Varee as we speak.
What's your relationship to her?
What's going on?
Explain to me what this is about.
Do you know
where your daughter presently is?
With her, of course.
Why are you asking me this?
[Varee sobbing softly]
You insist Ms. Varee
brought the child with her?
Yes.
So, did your daughter
appear to be normal when they left?
What do you mean?
What's happened to the child?
We have a report from Ms. Varee
that your daughter is missing.
What? What did you say? Min is missing?
Well, then, could you send us
some photographs of your daughter?
We'll get back to you
as soon as there are any new updates.
Why are you asking me for her photos?
Doesn't her mother have them?
Put my wife on the phone, please.
[Varee whimpering]
You're on speaker. She can hear you.
Ms. Varee is sitting with us.
Varee, if you can't cope, come back here.
What kind of a mother are you?
You can't even take care
of a single child.
Please cooperate and send us the photos.
Don't waste our time.
Before you start ordering me around,
I'd like to know what your rank is
and what division you're from.
I'm guessing
you still don't know who I am.
- I do.
- [Varee sniffles]
You're someone who likes to hurt women.
That's why she ran away
with your daughter.
[sobbing softly]
[phone chimes]
[unsettling music building]
[music fades out]
[opening theme music playing]
DON'T COME HOME
[shaman chanting in Thai]
[Fah] Do you think she hurt her daughter?
I don't know.
She doesn't seem to be that kind of type.
A victim of abusive behavior
can often become violent at times.
So do you pity her or suspect her?
[dark music playing]
[shaman continues chanting in Thai]
[somber music playing]
[firecrackers exploding deafeningly]
[birds cawing]
[man 1] Min!
Where are you? Can you hear us?
[Fah] Min!
[somber music playing]
[dog whines]
[man 2] Min, are you there?
[man 3] Min!
Hello, Min!
[man 2] Min!
[volunteers continue shouting for Min]
[man 2] Min! Are you there?
[volunteers continue calling for Min]
[man 2] Let's check again.
[man 4] Maybe she fell into the water.
Sir, where does this stream run to?
[man 4] It runs all the way to the canal.
[Fah] Tae, send a team to check it out.
Sure.
[man 2] Min!
[Tae] Aof, do you copy? Aof?
Prepare a car and a team
to check out the canal. Copy?
Have you had any sleep?
Please leave this to the police now.
You need to get some rest.
[Natee] Ms. Varee, Inspector,
why don't you wait at the house?
I will keep looking with the others.
[Fah] Sergeant Nui.
[Nui] Yes, ma'am?
- [Fah] Over to you now.
- [Nui] Yes, Inspector.
[Tae] Are we gonna find her?
[Aof] Something you need, Captain?
[thunder rumbling]
[thunder crashes]
You and your daughter are lookalikes.
[Varee] Mm.
Everybody says that.
It's my fault.
I shouldn't have brought her here.
It's your husband's fault.
You did the right thing by running away.
Not all mothers could do what you did.
[melancholy music playing]
How far along are you?
Over six months.
What does your husband say
about you working?
A child…
can live with just a mother.
Don't you think?
[thunder crashing]
[rain pouring]
Walk that way and turn right.
A little further,
there's a bathroom on the right.
Thanks.
[window bangs]
[lock clicks]
[thunder continues rumbling]
[uneasy music playing]
[thunder rumbling]
[music darkens]
[Fah] Ms. Varee!
Ms. Varee!
[lightbulbs flickering]
What is it?
[thunder crashing]
[cell phone vibrating]
- [terrifying sting]
- [eerie creaking]
So have you found her?
No, nothing.
If she fell into the water,
the body won't float for a while.
Hey, hold on.
What have you found?
[rain pouring]
Hey, what is it?
Looks like there's a body stuck over here!
What body?
[thunder crashing]
[man] This way, sir.
[unsettling music playing]
[Tae gagging]
What body, Tae?
It's just a cow.
It's not a child's body.
[Fah] Mm.
It's not her. It's not your daughter.
Have you searched all of the rooms?
I've searched everywhere.
This room?
- [thunder crashing]
- [mysterious music playing]
Is the key somewhere else?
There's only these.
[door rattling]
Just wait here.
[thunder crashing]
[unsettling music playing]
Stand back.
[grunts]
There's a room downstairs.
[mysterious music playing]
[music intensifies darkly]
[Varee coughs]
[Fah coughing]
[Varee coughs, clears throat]
[eerie music playing]
[Fah grunts]
[metal clanks]
[lightbulbs flickering]
What room is this?
I don't know.
It looks like some kind of laboratory.
My mother must have built it.
[ominous music playing]
[Fah exhales]
What's this stain?
Is it a blood stain?
[grunts] Thank you.
[grunting]
[dark music playing]
Who was your mother?
MISSING GIRL
[man] Min! Min!
[dogs panting]
[Nui] This is the crime scene here.
Right here.
Okay, so we'll start searching right here.
- Oh-- Thank you.
- Yes, sir.
- That's good.
- Great, thank you.
Let's get some coffee in us first.
[engine idling, turns off]
- [vehicle door closes]
- [indistinct conversations]
[camera beeping, clicking]
Tae, do you think that's a bloodstain?
Looks like it.
But it's all dried up. It's old.
Ms. Varee, has anyone come down
to this room before?
I don't know.
I haven't lived here
for more than 30 years,
and this is the first time
I've ever been to this basement.
[Aof] Inspector, Captain,
have a look here.
What's that mark?
Interesting.
The result of a short circuit.
Maybe, but why is it circular?
Weird.
Ms. Varee, what's the room above this?
The living room, I think.
- [electricity buzzing]
- [dramatic music playing]
[camera beeping, clicking]
[Fah] Who is that?
[Varee] That's my great-grandfather.
He built this house.
He was a Westerner.
He was Portuguese.
He was an engineer.
He operated a mine here.
[camera clicks]
- Let me help.
- Let me.
[Fah breathing heavily]
[Fah grunts]
[grunts]
[Fah] Damn.
[foreboding music playing]
[Varee] What mark is this?
I think it's gotta be a burn mark.
Based on what we've seen
in the other rooms,
it's fair to say these marks
have been here for a while.
What does all this
have to do with my daughter?
[mysterious music playing]
I don't know.
What's with this house?
Before your daughter disappeared,
she was sleeping on this bed, right?
Yes.
[Fah] What about you?
Where were you sleeping?
I was sleeping on the bed with her.
Tae, check the bathroom,
and see if there's a kid's toothbrush.
Yes, Inspector.
Here.
[Varee hyperventilating]
[Varee moaning]
MISS MINTIRA
Ms. Varee.
Are you okay?
[breathing heavily]
Aof,
run this for DNA,
along with the stuff from yesterday.
Very good, Captain.
[Varee breathing shakily]
Why don't you get some rest now?
Let the police and the villagers
look for the girl.
[exhales mournfully]
[sniffles]
- [Fah groans]
- Let me help.
Yeah, it's okay.
[retching]
[coughing]
[pants]
[sniffles]
[grunts, breathes deeply]
You should get some rest too.
[ominous music playing]
[Fah] Whose car is that?
Who is that?
[Tae] It's a luxury car.
Not a villager.
- Oh shit.
- What?
An appointment. I forgot.
[door closes]
[engine turns over]
[woman on PA]
508, please come to the second counter.
Number 508,
please come to the second counter.
[doctor] How are you feeling, Inspector?
You look very exhausted.
Lack of sleep.
Inspector, you must get enough rest.
The mother must be strong
for the baby to be strong.
[gentle music playing]
[doctor] Your baby boy is healthy.
All his organs are developing properly.
He's reaching
all the correct pregnancy milestones.
He's now 28 weeks old.
[horn honks]
[Danai] What did the doctor say?
We're all good. Both me and the baby.
[gentle music continues]
Did the doctor tell you the expected date
or any nutritional needs?
Things you shouldn't do?
Why didn't you come in
if you had so many questions?
[music stops]
[Danai sighs]
[Danai sighs again]
[Danai] I have other business
to take care of.
With senior officers.
Fah, you should go home and get some rest.
[Fah grunts]
[melancholy music playing]
[keys jingling]
[exhales heavily]
["Time Machine" by Moderndog
playing in Thai]
[Tae] Ms. Varee.
Both the officers
and the volunteers from the village
searched the forests
surrounding the house.
But we didn't find your daughter.
We think it's very unlikely
that the girl is in the forest.
We have to consider the possibility
that she may have been
taken somewhere else.
You all must be exhausted.
Please go home and rest.
["Time Machine" continues playing]
[sobbing]
[song ends]
[Varee crying softly]
[lightbulbs flickering]
[Varee gasps]
[sniffles]
[footsteps running on stairs]
[eerie music playing]
Min.
Is that you, dear?
[footsteps running]
[Varee gasps]
[window slams shut]
[ominous music playing]
[breathing heavily]
[cell phone vibrating]
Hello?
[Varee] Officer,
there's someone inside my house.
[Fah] Ms. Varee, what happened?
[Varee] I said there's someone
inside my house.
Huh? What did you say?
Are there still officers at your house?
[Varee] They all left
earlier this evening.
Ms. Varee, find a place to hide for now.
Don't do anything now.
Wait until I get there.
Maybe it's my daughter.
What if it's not?
I have a gun.
Where did you get the gun from?
Don't do anything. Wait for me!
- [Varee panting]
- Ms. Varee!
[window slams, squeaks]
[window squeaks, slams]
[window slamming]
[Fah] Ms. Varee, can you hear me?
Ms. Varee!
What happened?
[window banging, squeaking]
[Varee grunting]
[window continues slamming]
[sighs shakily]
[window banging, squeaking]
[Varee breathing heavily]
[ominous music playing]
[Fah] Can you hear me?
Ms. Varee!
Hello?
- [Min] One.
- [Varee screams, grunts]
[Min] Two.
- Three.
- [phone beeps off]
[Min] Four.
- [Varee panting]
- [Min] Five.
Six.
- Min! Min! I'm here, dear!
- [Min] Seven.
Eight.
Nine.
Ten.
Eleven.
Twelve.
Thirteen.
Fourteen.
Fifteen.
Sixteen.
- Seventeen.
- [Varee] Min!
[Min] Eighteen.
- Min, is that you?
- [Min] Nineteen.
- Twenty.
- [terrifying musical sting]
[Min laughs]
Wait!
[creepy music playing]
Min!
Min, stop!
[panting] Min! Min, stop!
[terrifying sting]
Min! Min!
Min.
Min, quit playing already.
Min?
- [Varee gasps]
- [ghostly whoosh]
- Min, are you in here?
- [furniture creaking]
- [discordant notes playing]
- [Varee panting]
[ghostly whoosh]
- [electricity buzzes]
- [Varee] Min.
- [Min yells]
- [Varee screams]
[loud bang]
[crashing sounds]
[phone vibrating]
[echoing breaths]
[water gurgling]
[electricity crackling]
[gasps]
[lightbulbs flickering]
- [metal clanks]
- [foreboding music playing]
[music stops]
[closing theme music playing]