Hello.
Long Pao, Ton-Hom, See-Eiw.
Is there's anything that we could help, let us know.
I will be here to support you guys.
Nate.
You don't have to worry anymore.
Your kids will be fine.
Ms.Natenapa Supsakul.
Born: 13 JAN 1961
Death: 17 OCT 2012.
Sister.
Brother.
Do you guys think she can hear us?
Is she gonna be able to see us right now?
She is.
She isn't going anywhere.
She's still with you, Eiw.
She still with Pao.
She still with me.
She's not going anywhere.
We will always miss her, Eiw.
Listen to me.
She's not going anywhere.
Both of you,
please don't leave me.
Don't leave me behind again.
Stay with me forever.
I don't wanna lose anyone anymore.
We're not going anywhere.
We will be with you.
Taking care of you.
We will be your home.
Listen to me, Eiw.
Everything shall pass.
All three of us...
will be okay.
Trust me.
We'll be fine. We can live even she's gone.
Eiw.
Hey Kung, what are you doing here?
I'm here to help. Here.
Thank you so much.
Give me that.
It's okay. I can carry it.
Hey!
Have you been eating?
Seems like you've been losing weight,
you know that right?
I don't really have the appetite.
I understand.
But you should try to eat more.
Everyone worries about you.
Thank you.
Eiw.
You still have me, Fee, and Noey.
We are always here to listen.
Okay?
Thank you so much.
Let's go.
Are you alright there?
It's not heavy at all.
- You can leave it here.
- Yes sir.
I will go help up there.
Is this all we need?
Um there's some more sandalwood at the hall.
I will go get it myself.
- Sis.
- Hmm?
Are you okay, sis?
Um.
- Take care of the rest for me.
- Sure.
I will be back.
- Do you need my help?
- It's fine. Not that heavy.
You should go.
Let me help.
Doesn't matter whether it's heavy or not.
I wanna help.
Thank you.
Mom.
Rest in peace, mom.
You don't have to worry about us.
You don't have to worry.
I'll take care of them for you.
Yeah you don't have to worry mom.
I will take care of everyone.
Why is he here?
I'm going home,sis.
Do you wanna talk to dad first?
I don't.
There's nothing to talk.
Eiw.
Why?
Why do you wanna talk to him so much?
He left mom!
Isn't she die because of him?
If he didn't smoke, mom would still be alive.
Eiw.
But he's still our dad.
What kind of dad?
He never come back to us.
You still call him dad?
Eiw...
Cake.
Could you take Eiw home?
I will handle some stuff here with Hom first.
Sure bro.
Let's go home with me.
See you at home. Eiw.
Yes.
I'll follow you in a bit.
Eat something.
- I'll handle it. You can go help Eiw.
- Sure.
Here, let me help.
thank you, Cake.
Eiw.
Me and Pao will go pack some of mom's stuff in her room.
Do you wanna come help?
Pack what stuff?
Kinda put it away and make the room neat.
put all important stuff in the box,
and put all the documents in the folder.
Sure sis.
I'll go help you.
I wanna help her.
Shall we go?
Let's go.
Sis.
It's medicine.
Medicines.
There are lots of medicines.
Why do we have no idea?
She must have been exhausted.
Eiw.
Cake.
I found so many medicines from mom's room.
She was probably...
So painful.
She was probably coughing a lot.
She knew for so long
but she never told us.
When I was sick,
she still took care of me.
And why...
did I have no idea that she was sick.
Why did I leave her to fight on her own?
It's okay.
She rests in peace now.
She's not in pain anymore.
Why sis?
Don't cry, Eiw.
Go. Go get some rest.
Go. Stop crying.
Cake.
Yeah?
Take care of him for me.
Sure.
Don't worry. He will under my care.
About my dad,
do you feel the same way as Eiw?
I don't know.
I'm actually angry with him too.
Because he himself...
is really the cause why my mom is gone.
But I think...
there's no point of of holding the grudge.
Cause right now,
she's no longer here.
My dad is still my dad.
He is still my father.
Hom's father.
and also Eiw's.
I do understand.
I don't expect
Eiw to talk to him like nothing happened.
For me,
I don't expect to consider our father as a family.
I just don't want him keep being angry
and hold onto the hatred.
If my mother knew,
she wouldn't be happy if he's like this.
Well...
I will try to talk to him for you about this.
Please take care of him, Cake.
Me and Hom tried to convince him already.
If it's not you,
I don't know who else I could ask to help.
I will try, bro.
Thank you for loving Eiw.
I will take care of him in the best possible I could.
I promise.
Where were you, Cake?
I was talking to Pao.
Are you sleepy?
No, I'm not.
Can we talk for a bit?
No...
...if you wanna talk about that.
I'm not gonna talk.
Please talk to me.
Please.
No I won't.
I won't.
Please.
No.
Please my sweet boy.
Please.
What do you wanna talk about?
I'll just listen.
- Can you stop being angry with your father?
- No I can't.
Don't just answer right away.
I just can't.
You don't have to love him the same.
But just don't be angry with him anymore.
"Mama Dim Sum"
Did you know...
since I was young
all I remember...
was me asking my father to quit smoking.
On Father's Day,
I made a card...
and asked him to quit smoking.
On my birthday,
I also asked him that.
I let him know that I love him
worry about him
but he has never actually done it.
I tried every way.
because I was afraid that he could die from smoking.
You know it, Cake.
That cigarette is dangerous.
But he couldn't do it for me.
I always tell everyone.
to stay way whenever he smokes.
But I never knew,
that third hand smoking is a thing.
If I knew better, mom would still be here, right?
It's not your fault, Eiw.
She is resting in peace now.
The more you blame yourself, the more hurtful I feel.
Your siblings also feel hurtful.
And if your mom saw this, don't you think she's gonna feel hurtful too?
I'm sorry.
For so many times,
I also questioned myself that
'why does mom has to go back and talk to dad?'
Am I a bad person?
Not at all.
It's okay.
Parents are also humans.
They can be wrong.
Can make mistakes.
When they do something wrong,
it might make us mad or feel bad,
It's totally normal.
It's probably the same with us, when we do something wrong.
Parents might be mad at us, but they never hate us.
Do you hate your father, See-Eiw?
Do you hate him?
Then stop being angry with him.
Whatever has passed, you should let it go.
Talk to him too.
You don't have to talk a lot or meet him often.
Don't part from each other
with such bad feelings like this.
Don't you agree, sweet boy?
Aren't you gonna feel better?
Even if mom's not around anymore,
you still have your father.
You should go talk to him tomorrow.
Please?
Thank you.
I will leave you to talk to him first.
So...
We will leave now then.
Good bye, dad.
We'll be waiting in the car.
Follow us to the car when you're done.
Sure.
Let's go.
I'll go wait over there.
Good bye sir.
I'm sorry.
I know all about it now.
I know that I am the reason for all these to happened.
I can't do anything,
if you're gonna be mad and hate me.
If I could exchange my life with hers, I would.
I didn't think that way, dad.
Even I was really mad at you,
but I never wanted you to die instead of her.
Do you regret?
Having me as your father?
Since I was young,
I never asked anything from you,
never asked for any toys,
or any luxurious stuff.
Don't cry son.
There's only one thing I've always asked you...
just one thing.
I asked for it every festivals
every holidays,
ever special occasions,
to stop smoking.
I asked you to love yourself.
To take care of your own health
to stay with me forever.
But you've never done that for me.
Did you know...
I asked myself
every time...
why haven't you tried to do it for me?
Is it because you never loved me?
I never...dad.
Never asked you to have things like other fathers
or be better than anyone.
I just want you to love yourself.
Love mom.
Ton-Hom.
Long Pao.
and love me enough to quit that useless cigarette.
But you've never actually done it.
You did not only left me,
but you take mom away fro me too.
If I have to say I'm not sad,
then that would be a lie.
I'm sorry.
I'm the worst father.
For never actually do things as I said.
But I love you a lot. Really.
Dad.
I'm not mad at you.
I'm not mad at you anymore.
I never hate you.
Thanks son.
From now on,
if you struggle,
or is there anything that we could help.
you can always tell us.
If I graduate and got a job,
I will give you money every month.
That's fine.
I never want any money from you.
Just talking to me...
is more than enough.
It's okay dad.
Just take it...
as if I give the money to mom for me.
Please just take it, I'm begging you.
Thanks son.
Thanks for coming back.
Well...
I gotta go now.
Pao and Hom are waiting.
I'm gotta go.
Good bye.
See-Eiw.
Can I hug you for once?
Wow you've been growing a lot!
So heavy.
Catch me. Catch me.
Gotcha! I catched you.
Dad, you are my hero.
Wow!
Are you gonna say this still when you're grown up?
See you tomorrow.
Hey!
How do you know where's my company?
Am pretty good huh?
What are you doing here?
I wanna talk to you about something.
What is it that you wanna talk?
Why do you have to come all the way here?
You.
I'm a grown up now.
In university already.
Even that's the case,
I still can't live up to your standard.
When I was in high school,
you were in uni.
When I'm in uni,
you're working already.
I have no idea...
what it means to be a grown up to you.
Bur for me,
I've been ready to take care of you
and be someone you can rely on for so long.
What do you think or how do you feel
you can just tell me.
Don't keep it to yourself.
You're not gonna say something to me?
Peak.
you have improved so much at acting.
You..
So...
Is that a yes?
I guess.
What do you mean 'I guess'?
Yes.
- Hom will be off from work around 5.30-6.00 pm
- If she has not to work over time tho.
- Ok
- We have talked.
- Thank you, Eiw.
Peak.
Do you wanna leave?
Sure let's go.
What were you doing?
Nothing.
Cake.
Still asleep?
Cake. Cake. Cakeee.
Cake! Wake up!
Mom!
since the day you're gone,
it's been a year already.
Everything is still the same.
I about to graduate this year,
Cake is gonna be a fourth year student this year.
Just a blink of eye,
we're almost real adults already.
- Lots of jam.
- Are you gonna eat?
- I will eat anything.
Because you made it for me.
Actually,
I have so many things I wanna tell you.
It's really my last year
of being a university student.
Thinking about it make me nervous.
I'm still uncertain with my future, mom.
Why are you smiling, Noey?
What smiling?
Just study.
What am I gonna do?
Where am I gonna work?
It's another time where I wonder,
if you're still here,
I would probably be clingy with you,
complaining about stuff on your lap.
- Did you wait for me for so long?
- Not at all.
That looks good.
You always have some stuff on hands.
- One bite.
- That's fine.
Let's just go.
You eat it.
I bought it for you.
Aaaam here.
Ok ok.
That' good.
I already ate. Your turn.
Big bite.
you used to have the bread
- This is of a bite.
- That big?
How big?
- Like this.
- Come on! Eat.
Please.
Cake!
About Pao and Hom, you don't have to worry about them.
They work so hard.
They've got someone to take care of them as well.
Wow.
Even we don't see each other as often
as we used to like when we were young,
but we still manage to have a meal together every week.
Eat at our home like we always have.
Oh there's one thing that's changed, mom.
We contact dad more often.
- Dad's calling, sis.
- Dad?
Dad is calling, bro.
So...
there's nothing that you have to worry.
We live our best lives  like we promised you.
Please watch over us from up there.
I miss you the most.
Hey!
- Eiw!
- Hello, Eiw.
- What's up.
- You guys are here!
- Yeah we are.
The famous writer.
Really good at mocking people huh.
Congrats, Eiw.
This is from the three of us.
- We really handpicked this specifically for you.
- Thank you.
May your book sells really well.
It already is, isn't it?
These two bought 4-5 books each.
whenever they go to malls, they always buy.
You're acting like you didn't buy.
Yeah.
Thank you all so much.
I didn't expect it to sells so well.
If readers like it, that makes me happy already.
I read half of it,
and i was in tears.
I'd dare to say,
that you must have cried while you wrote.
Stop talking.
How do you know?
The content is very touching.
I didn't expect to turn out like that.
I was also confused how did I wrote.
When we finish reading it,
I'll discuss with you about it again.
Sure.
Yeah even we haven't finished it,
we still have so many points to discuss with you.
You two still haven't finished it?
You did?
-
Yeah, finished many books already.
- For real!?
What are the names of the book?
The New Eiw.
- The New Eiw.
- That's a good one.
Actually,
How did you come up with the back cover part?
It's so good.
Agree.
- It's really good. It made me cry.
- Right?
What does it say?
The chooser who's never been loved
is not equal to the the lover who got chosen.
Do you wanna become a writer? You should write.
Where's Cake thought?
Cake? He'll be here shortly.
He went to pick up Cream.
- At her dorm?
- Yes.
Since she got in uni,
Cake is a bit more protective, isn't he?
He should be.
The more she's grown, the more beautiful she's become.
Normally, Pao picks her up every Friday.
But he's been super busy lately. Always do OT.
Speaking of this still suprises me.
Pao ended up dating Cream.
- Yeah yeah.
- Me too.
Isn't that a good thing?
2 couples from the same families match each other.
Cake and See-Eiw. Pao and Cream.
So cute!
Stop embarrassing me.
There's no matching.
Just one couple and it's not mine.
It's Pao and Cream.
Aren't you gonna get married with him?
Ugh...what are you talking about?
Stop talking. That's enough.
How can I get married?
Let's talk about something else.
Eat.
Oh Eiw, can you sign the book for me?
Me too.
- Where's the pen?
- Really?
Don't forget your friends when you're all famous.
Huh? What's your name again?
Here.
"The Person Who Cannot Choose"
Cake.
Hmm?
Have you ever heard of this column,
the possibility that you could
be successful with your first love.
Never.
I read it
when we were in high school.
I don't remember the details
but they said
The chance that you could be successful
is only 12%.
Why is it so little?
I thought so too.
Too little and that makes me annoyed.
But it sounds believable, don't you think?
Cause people always say
first love usually ended up disappointed.
I heard that a lot too.
But you are my first love, Cake.
Yeah.
So...
I'm 1 of the 12% that annoying?
Do you wanna know why?
Why?
Because the possibility that you'd be successful with your first love
for once and only...
is not just 12%.
- Can I ask you something?
- Huh?
- No.
Cake!
Cake it's tickling.
I'll make your cheek bruised.
I love you, Cake.
I love you too, Eiw.
A lot.
But there's one thing that I don't know.
Hmm?
For me,
You are the only one out of 100%
And it's the only 1% that I will love.
I'm hungry now.
Stop it.
You always change the subject
when you blush.
No I don't. I just wanna go in side.
Fine. We'll go inside.
But first of all,
let me hug you for one more minute.
Yeah where the hell is Cake now?
So damn late.
He said he's almost here.
Almost here as in...
'Just left'
Ugh.
Hey!
You guys...
can I have one?
Hey!
Why did you throw it away? That's a lot left.
The whole pack.
I'm gonna quit.
You just realized that?
You showed up out of no where!
Why? You got a problem?
Let's go.
I'm hungry. Let's eat.
You came late but still dare to complain.
I haven't eaten anything since this morning.
You're the one who complains.
Don't run away. Come here.
Get up.
Hey Palm! There's shit on your ears.
- Wait for me!
- Palm! Come on!
- What should we eat?
- I don't know.
So hungry.
- What are you hungry of?
- The food!
Thank you.
What should we eat? Soup or no soup?
When you spend more than 1000 Baht,
get a chance to win a prize to go see Pisa Tower...
Hey it's in Italy?
Isn't it in France?
Stop being stupid.
How can it be in France?
Cause...
Shit...Ta.
I'm sorry.
I thought you knew.
I knew since after I got home on that day.
You remember? The exam?
Shit maybe that's why when I ask girls out on a date,
no one's going with me.
Do you wanna know why?
Why?
Because you're dumb.
and retard.
Hey let's go eat. It smells like someone stupid here.
Go go.
Ugh so smelly.
What about my Italy?
Go check it out by yourself.