Class dismissed.
Thank you.
Kung. Wake up.
It's lunch break.
Where shall
we have lunch today?
The teacher let us go early
... canteen?
Probably not a lot of people yet.
I actually wanna have Suki.
What do you think Eiw?
Um. We can go to the canteen.
Um Ok.
Let's go.
Come on Eiw!
Before there'll be lots of people.
Go.
Err...I changed my mind.
I better go buy
some bread from the school mart.
Why?
We've arrived here.
I'm not that hungry.
You guys go ahead and eat.
I gotta go.
Hey Eiw!
He only eats bread
from the mart.
Let's go.
Let's have some Suki.
- Eiw?
- Hm?
How are you?
Are you alright...?
- From the sickness?
- Um.
I'm better,
but still taking some medicines.
Where's Fee?
He went to the his club room.
Why do you look
so tired today Kung?
I saw you napping
this morning too.
What did you do?
I stayed up late
watching a movie.
What movie?
The movie from Theme Movie channel.
They put on some good shows.
I might stay up late again tonight.
Hey.
Hm?
What are you guys
fighting about?
Who do you mean?
With Cake.
No.
We're not fighting.
- Really?
- Um.
And why did you walk away then?
No. I just wanna have some bread.
That's all.
Wait.
I haven't told you
when exactly did you walk away.
Are you having
a guilty conscience?
Hmm?
Would you be able to do the fitness test,
eating only this?
Ugh!
I don't wanna do the test, Kung.
No. Just eat up.
You need to eat a lot. Come on.
You won't have the strength.
Thinking about it is already
making me feel weak.
Eat up.
After finishing this one,
go buy another one.
Eat.
Ready. Set.
Go!
Next.
See-Eiw. Toffee.
And Peak.
Ready, Eiw?
Ready.
Set.
Go!
Hey!
Hey.
Don't gather around.
Get someone from the infirmary now.
You got any inhalers?
I didn't bring any.
- I don't have it.
- Is the teacher here?
Don't gather around him.
Please get someone from the infirmary.
Are you ok, Eiw?
Are you awake?
How are you?
Did you know that you fainted?
Headache.
Of course you are.
Kung told me
you didn't have a proper lunch.
But I did eat.
The bread.
Was it enough?
If it was enough,
you wouldn't be here.
Are you guys done with the test?
Um.
All done.
I'm about to go home.
Hey.
Why don't you
go back to the class?
I'm worried about you.
Then I'll go back
to the class then.
No. No.
Lay down.
- Lay down.
- I'm feeling better.
No. Class is almost over.
I'm fine.
I'm better.
Better?
You look pale like
some boiled chicken.
What time is it now?
2-ish.
What?
And how come you're here?
The teacher didn't
tell you to go to class?
I did go to the class,
but I just asked
to go to the bathroom.
So I decided to stop by.
I'm here for a bit
and you're awake.
You wait here.
I have to go back to the class now.
I'll come pick you up
when the class is over.
We can just meet
at the bus stop.
No. I'll come get you, ok?
Go to the class.
Are you scared being here alone?
I'm fine.
You can go.
I can stay here by myself.
- I'll be back.
- Um. I know.
You should go
to the class already.
Why are you crying?
Your mom is home.
Um. She's here.
I'll go to my place first.
I'll just go get my stuff
at yours later.
That's fine. I'll bring your stuff over.
I'll spend a night with you today.
Why?
I've got something
to talk to you.
See you after dinner.
Wait Cake!
I think I'm gonna watch
something from Theme Movie.
I don't think
I can talk tonight.
You watch this channel too?
There's only movie.
No cartoon.
Um. I will watch it.
You don't have to come over.
I...
will watch with you.
I like that channel anyway.
See you then.
Mom!
Oh. You're home.
I miss you.
How's grandma?
She's better now.
She's been taking medicine and has to rest a lot.
Go change and come down for dinner.
I stopped by at Siang's Duck on the way back.
For real!?
I better share some with Cake!
Actually. No.
Hey why not?
I bought a whole lot.
No.
I'm gonna go change now.
Are you guys fighting again?
Pround's Bakery
It's a Thai movie today.
Horror type too.
Let's just not watch it?
No, I wanna watch it.
You might not
be able to sleep.
Cake!
If you're sleepy then go ahead,
take a shower and go to bed.
Telling me to go away huh.
- Boo!!
- Ugh!
Cake!
Just stop watching it.
Go to bed.
No.
I want to finish this.
How?
You cover your
whole face like that, huh?
Leave me alone.
Do you wanna sit with me?
I don't understand why you watch it,
if you're so scared.
What's wrong?
What did I do that make you mad hm?
I'm not.
If you're not mad,
then what's the matter?
What's wrong?
I don't know.
Stop avoiding me first.
If I know what's wrong
then you can be mad ok?
We never actually fight.
There's nothing
we have to fight, right?
It's true, isn't it?
You're ok then?
Should we stop watching it?
Should we?
Talk to me in the first place,
then we wouldn't have to watch this for so long.
Go take a shower.
- Cake.
- Um?
Take me to
the bathroom, will you?
- What?
- Should I take you or not?
- Go with me please.
- Should I go?
It's dark.
The bathroom
is super creepy too.
Cake!
Ok. I'll go with you.
Go get your towel.
I'll wait in front of the bathroom.
You come with me.
- Hey!
- Ugh!
- Cake!
- Um?
I will leave the door open a little bit.
Don't go anywhere.
Yeah. I won't go anywhere.
- Do not prank me either.
- Ok. I won't.
Go take a shower.
- Wait here.
- Um.
- Boo!
- Hey!
See. I haven't gone in
and you already prank me.
Just go shower.
- Cake
- Hmm?
Cake?
I'm here.
- You're done?
- Um.
- You can shower next.
- Ok.
You want me to wait for you?
That's okay.
You can wait for me up there.
Ok.
Cake.
Eiw?
Shit. That was not him.
Cake.
Cake. Cake. Cake. Cake.
- Cake. Cake. Cake. Cake.
- Eiw!
This is for me?/  This is for me?
Yes.
I think it's time for you guys.
Me and Proud bought you two cellphones.
Just in case of anything,
you can call each other.
Hey. Hey.
Don't use it during class.
Sure!
Manage the time to use wisely.
For the phone bill,
you need to top-up yourself,
so you won't over spend.
Sure.
Thank you mom.
Cake.
Hmm?
Are you that happy?
I am.
This is my first phone.
You're not happy?
Umm...
I am.
But I don't know
who I'll use to call.
To call your friends.
You can send messages too.
I don't have any friends
I would like to call or text to.
Are you gonna play games?
No.
I'm on MSN, talking with Rin.
I told her to be
on MSN at 6.
I wanna play checkers.
Now?
Um. I wanna play.
I already told Rin to be on MSN.
If I'm not online,
she might wonder where am I.
That's fine then.
I will go play with you
in an hour or two.
- Is that ok?
- Um ok.
He's so addicted to his phone.
He doesn't even eat.
Wow.
Don't blame it on him, Peak.
I don't think it's the phone.
If not the phone...
then what is it?
I guess...
it's probably
the person he's texting to.
You guys are so good.
Good at knowing
what you're up to?
Good at being nosy.
Really good at being nosy,
my friends.
What about you Ta?
You wanna sleep over
at my place tonight?
Sure.
We have to be here super early.
I could be late.
So what?
Are you going home with me after school?
I will go later.
My family will drop me off in the evening.
Ok.
Shit.
What?
Dude. I'm going to see Rin.
What about your lunch?
I'm not gonna eat anymore.
Put the plate away for me.
See you at the football field.
See ya.
- It's so nice my friend being in love. - Why?
Why?
Extra egg for me.
Pay the same amount.
I will punch you.
I want that.
- No.
- Let me have it.
- I wanna have the egg, please let me have it.
- No.
You've got boiled egg.
I wanna have the sunny side up.
The yolk is dripping!
I have very little food on my plate.
You've got the boiled egg.
Didn't you just
top-up the other day?
I used it all.
Why so quick?
Umm..I call and text a lot.
But I already signed up
for free call after 10pm plan.
What time is
Ta going to be here?
Umm...He said...
He's going back home first.
He will be here shortly.
My text box is full again.
Delete it.
No.
I don't wanna lose it.
Rin texted me with lots of
cute messages.
Which one should I delete?
You have to pack your bag today.
We're going to
the camp tomorrow.
Sure.
You've been procrastinated
for so many days, Cake.
Aunty Proud asked me
to force you do it.
Um.
Cake.
Huh?
Why are you so loud?
Because you're
constantly on your phone.
I asked you questions
and you mumbled as an answer.
If you do not care,
I will go home now.
Ok. Ok.
I'm not on my phone now.
Where?
Let's pack our bags.
Are you mad?
I'm not.
I will go take a shower.
Wait.
You're mad.
I'm not.
Yes you are.
See you are.
Stop playing with my hair.
I'm just gonna go shower.
Stop being mad at me first?
I told you
I'm not mad.
I'm goin' to shower
for a min.
Ok.
Come back
when you're done.
Hurry back.
I'm goin' to shower then.
Do I have everything?
4 shirts and pants
(4 outfits, towel, soap, shampoo, toothbrush)
Seems like missing something.
I'm letting you win
I'm closing one eye.
Look at your HP.
Oh the flashlight.
Cake. Cake.
Cake.
- I like to move it, move it. How's that?
- Cake.
Hmm?
You've got any flashlights?
Flashlight?
It should be in that cabinet.
This shithead.
You took advantage huh?
This cabinet?
Pay attention to Eiw.
Go help him find it.
Where is it? Top or bottom shelf?
- Go play SuperMario.
- It's not here Cake.
- Pay attention to him!
- Huh?
There's nothing.
Is there something pile on top of it?
Hey Cake I can't see!
Cake I cannot find it.
I will go find it myself.
Then you go find it ok?
I will fold all the clothes.
Yes sir.
Hey don't cheat.
I can't press the button.
Is your joystick broken?
- You're not good at all. You cheated
- My Friend. My little friend.
You never teach me
and cheated on me.
I closed both of my eyes for you already.
How did I cheat?
You did cheat.
Stupid!
Ok. I'll give you one more game.
Cheater.
If you won another round,
I'll let you slap me.
- For real?
- Yeah.
- Cake I prepared everything for you already.
- But if you lost, you're done.
- You are. Not me!
- And I only get to slap?
Cake.
- Huh?
- Don't forget to check your stuff.
Ok sure thing.
- Mosquito!
- Cake.
Mosquito?
I'll kill it for you.
Cake. It's all packed.
- Hmm??
- It's all packed. Only the flashlight left.
Ok.
I will look for it myself.
I will go to bed then.
Hmm?
- I said I'm goin' to bed.
- Sure.
You can turn off the main light.
I will play quietly.
- You cheated. Cheated on me.
- You are.
- Can I have
- Sure.
You guys should go to bed too.
Sweet dream.
Should we stop
and go to bed?
Ok.
I'm also sleepy.
If we don't go to bed,
Eiw will scream at me in the morning.
You guys are super close.
Um. We are.
We've been together
since we were born.
He takes care of you so well.
Yeah. That's Eiw.
That's awesome...
having a friend
as your neighbor next door.
I'm so damn lonely.
All my neighbors are not our age.
I think me and Eiw
is not only next door neighbor.
He's both my friend...
...and my brother.
It's like he is
another half of me actually.
Um. I believe you.
Um Let's go to sleep.
- I'll turn off the light for you.
- Hey. Hey.
Can we leave it on?
I'm scared of the ghost.
Why do you have to beg me?
I can leave it on for you.
See you in the morning.
Um.
Err..Cake hasn't come down?
Um. He hasn't finished showering.
I finished first,
that's why I came down first.
This is good.
You're full, Eiw?
Oh yes.
I am.
I already ate a few.
What about...
Eiw's bag?
Here.
The bag...
Hey what group are you in?
Is it the same group with Cake?
Um.
Yes.
I'm in the same group with Cake.
Let's go.
I'm done.
Eating like that you might
freaking choke to death.
Want some water?
Cake!
I'm choking.
Let's go.
What are you playing?
Can I play too?
Hey guys.
Hey.
So damn sleepy.
Don't know why do we have
to be here super early.
Yeah. I didn't...
wanna wake
the hell up this morning.
But you're the latest one here.
This idiot woke up late
for sure.
I had no sleep.
You asked me to play game all night.
Actually...
You lost so many times
and kept asking to play again.
He sucks at playing games.
Dude.
Did you bring any toothpaste?
No.
I'm actually gonna borrow someone.
You family is quite well-off.
Buy it sometimes.
Shit. I only have the toothbrush,
but not the toothpaste.
What about you Ta?
You have it?
- Me?
- Yeah.
I don't even have a toothbrush.
Wow.
- Cake.
- Did you brush your teeth,
spending a night at my place?
Cake I was just kidding.
- Don't talk to us.
- I was kidding.
Cake has it.
I saw See-Eiw packed and put it in his bag.
- Couldn't ask for more.
- Fuck you.
Why didn't you pack it yourself?
You guys are talking a lot,
you don't get to use my toothpaste.
I will look for you first thing
in the morning Sweetie.
Yeah. You go sleep next to him.
Sleep next to my feet first.
- Call me sweetie? Come check out my feet.
- Sweetie.
Come on.
Shit. Hey. Why am I involving?
Or should I stand on the table?
Where's Fee?
I'm here!
What happened?
Woke up late?
Yeah. My mom woke me
but I fell back asleep.
I thought
I was not gonna make it.
The traffic is so bad.
It's okay. If you're late you can
have someone drives you like last year.
My dad would kill me.
It's so hot.
Go. Go.
Are you texting a report to your parents?
Yeah.
Are you guys like together?
Not yet.
But close.
Are you waiting for someone
to make it official for you?
Official your ass.
I better eat some Fisho.
- Dude.
- Hmm?
Do you think...
Eiw doesn't like me or something?
Why do you ask?
This morning I talked to him...
He only answered me a few words.
He didn't even look at my face.
Yeah.
You don't have to worry.
He's like that.
Not good at talking to people.
But I actually do worry about him.
About not good at talking?
Um. That too.
He's afraid of people.
He doesn't like making new friends.
I'm worried.
But he has Fee and Kung right?
True.
But is it enough just that?
Lots of people
only have a few friends.
But if he runs away
when there're a lot of people,
don't like new changes...or....
doesn't like going to unfamiliar places...
isn't that a bad thing?
It kinda is.
And what does his family say?
Youngest son kinda thing.
Pao, his brother,
spoils him like rotten.
You're dare to say this?
It's you who spoil Eiw.
Don't you dare say that.
But I think...
when he grows up,
He'll have more friends.
You don't have to worry.
It's not like
you can be with him forever?
You need to have
your personal space too.
But we never had personal space
to each other.
We'll see whether you'll say that
when we're grown ups.
Yeah. You're so grown up much?
No I'm not.
But you have Rin now.
What about her?
If you guys end up as a couple,
you'll want to be together.
Want to spend time together.
Are you going to tag Eiw along...
as a third wheel,
isn't that weird?
"Vajiravudh Scout Camp 1962"
Yay!
Come on down.
Hi!
So slow.
Button up please.
Wear your beret properly.
Come on.
- Let's go.
- Hey you. Wear your beret.
Here wear it.
- Go.
- I can't see shit.
Peak come here.
Let me hold that.
Yeah let's go!
What do we do?
Do we have all the veggies?
Need anything else,
let me know.
- No. No. I'll carry that
- Hey.
You can't carry this by yourself.
And why you're here?
Why don't you help them making omelette?
There're a lot of people
over there already.
Your hands are all dirty, let's go wash.
You face too.
How can you make such a mess?
Look at your face first.
It's all over down to your cheek.
- I've got something on my face?
- Yeah.
- Where?
- This side and that side.
No. No.
This side.
Up a bit.
Here. Down here. No.
This side.
Go to this a bit.
This side?
Here.
Is it gone?
Off my face?
It's gone?
Then why are you laughing?
Here.
My hands are all dirty.
So when I tried to clean it for you,
I made it worse.
You pranked me?
No I did not.
- You did.
- I did not. Really.
- I didn't.
- Stop smiling...
...then I'll believe you.
See!
You look like
you're from some tribe.
You wanna be
on the same tribe with me?
No. I don't.
Cake!
What's on your face?
You'll be itchy.
No.
Really.
Are you jealous?
No.
Do they think they're here
just the two of them?
Where have you been Cake?
Why didn't you tell me. I'm worried.
I went to talk with Rin.
What's the matter?
Am I still important for you?
You're always important to me Eiw.
Always...
There's no such time
where you're not important to me.
Aren't you tired,
sitting here waiting for him everyday?
That's fine. I can wait.
I want to wait.
I'm comfortable being like this.
Hi. I'm Sand.