Xiangshan He Shun Film Co., Ltd.
Sister.
Are you okay?
You're not feeling well, right?
Sister, what's going on? I haven't...
You...
Waiting for you to save me.
I'm cold.
I'll get changed later.
That's my sister.
Where's Ye?
He's so young.
Why is he called Ye?
I didn’t know Lin Che called me that.
Oh.
Over there
I like pork elbow very much.
Really I'll ask the chef to cook for you
Great.
Your clothes are not right.
Do you think so?
You have to wear it like this.
You have to put this here.
That's cool
Thank you.
I knew it.
I'll sort it out for you.
I can do it myself.
That's cool
You look good in it.
Go back to work.
I'm leaving.
Bye.
Come with me.
What?
Oh no, I forgot about this.
What's wrong?
You go first.
Go to the rice shop first. Who will take me away?
Leave me alone.
What about you?
Okay.
That's a decoction to relieve the poison.
I'm afraid you don't have many days left.
I'm so mad.
I was about to save the hero.
I don't know where Wen Youcai came from.
The idiots I hired
who I hired.
I shouldn't have saved that much.
I should hire some strong men.
Have you
Have you noticed anything?
That's quite something.
Tell me.
Come on.
Lin Che is actually strong.
and muscular.
He has a strong body.
More importantly, he has internal strength.
Interesting.
You took credit to His Highness
to save your life, right?
Of course not.
The Crown Prince is a smart man.
How could I use such a foolish method
to test your IQ?
It's just that the poison is coming.
I deliberately set a trap for you.
Please protect me.
so that I won't let you down.
Please tell me.
I will raise the rice price
in Lin Che’s name
and ruin his reputation.
Okay.
You exchange the results with me for the antidote three days later.
Yes.
It's so expensive.
Stop arguing.
Hit him.
Beat him!
You want us to die?
Shameless!
What’s going on?
Mr. Che ordered it.
What?
Yes.
Why did you raise the rice price?
Three days have passed.
Have you made up your mind?
Why did you raise the rice price?
To make money.
I asked the rice shop to supervise the rice price.
That's your conspiracy.
I won’t do it.
Lin Che.
Uncle Qi just sent off his daughter
and sent his daughter away.
He regretted it.
Because he didn't know until the last moment
his daughter kept lying to him
to give him food.
Now he's dead.
That's Miss Zhao.
She has nothing to eat.
So there's no milk.
I had no choice.
She can only feed her child
with her own blood.
And him.
He...
They…
Why, Lin Che?
It’s unnecessary.
It's really unnecessary.
A few taels of silver
may be a cup of new tea
or some snacks.
But for them,
a few taels of silver can save their parents and siblings.
Do you know him?
Is that the point?
There are so many poor people in this world.
Can you help them all?
Are you not helping because you can't?
Besides, you're different from them.
You are the son of His Highness.
You have the responsibility to protect one side.
You should be the people's food and clothing.
to protect them.
But now?
you ate the grain they took for the royal family
and hurt your people.
I was right about you.
I'll help you ask His Highness for credit
and fulfill your wish.
Don't work for Lin Feng anymore.
Also,
don't get involved in this dispute.
You...
Look.
It's time to see people's hearts.
Ye.
It's Young Master.
Take it easy.
Lin Che
raised the grain price
the grain price of all rice shops in Yongzhou.
Some shops are out of greed.
Some don't dare to offend you.
and raised the price.
I shouldn't have trusted him.
I told you.
A man's mouth
A liar.
I...
Just tell me what we should do now.
We have to change the plan.
I'm afraid stealing the rice shop will become a target.
Steal a private bank?
If refugees have money,
they should buy grain.
No one can control us.
Youcai, search our goal.
Let me see who is the lucky one.
Jiu Si Private Bank is notorious.
and made a fortune.
After the refugees from the North infiltrated Yongzhou,
increased the interest by three times.
and double the profit.
He even put up the blood mark.
Okay, it's him.
Get ready.
The bandit family has opened.
You want to leave?
Sure.
Take me with you.
Roada Xu who made a wish.
Wen Youcai, Han Haotian.
Lin Rou, Chen Chuqi.
Lin Feng Yi, Jin Wangwang.
Lin Yan and Yang Jun.
Lucky, Tan Yinmin.
Qian Youfu Yi, Guo Chang.
Zhao Mingzhu, Liu Lingling.
Lin Dao Cheng, Feng Wusheng.
Ye Zi, Yi, Yi, Yi.
A Lian, Xu Shiyao.
A Lian and Xu Shiyao.
The Crown Princess, Xiong Jiayi.
One bear plus one.
Meng Heng Yi, Bai Haoyan.
I'm an honest person.
Li Yixuan, guard of the granary.
Baldy painter, Yang Xingliang.
Guard Wang Shuixin.
A maid, Xu Huiting.
Magistrate Chen Tianci
MC Chen Fukuguo
Liao Haipeng.
Girl, one for Wai.
Girl and Wai
Guard 1 Zhu Haitao
Jing and Fang Xin.
One for maid, one for Liu Sisi.
One for maid, one for Liu Sisi
A maid, two, one, Xia Ying.
Maid, 31, Bai Bingqi.
maid 41, Dong Jun Yi.
Five for maids, one for Tianyi.
Five for maids, one for Fu Yi.
A little wish for one, Yue Ying.
Make a wish, foster mother, recite a bamboo.
Make a wish, foster mother, one bamboo.
The boy made a wish, Yang Bao'er.
The procuress, Li Hong,
Liu Bu, Wang Rumeng
A painting of Manru
A mural of Manru
Yuan Hong, the greasy male lead
Ms. Zhao has a sea breeze.
The heroine of yarn is Zhou Xian Yue.
The heroine of yarn, Zhou Xian Yue.
The first eunuch, Yuan Ying,
A maid, Lü Xinyang.
A servant, A, 1, Yang Doudou.
My servant is Jia Yi, Yang Doudou.
My servant, Yi Yi, He Gui.
The servant, Yi Yi, He Gui.
Ye's Yi Ji Ling.
Lin Che, Guo Wupeng.
Lin Che and Guo Wupeng.
The Fifth Prince, Wang Yongdi.
One refugee, Xu Weiqiang.
Trainee 1 Deng Dongmen
Refugee A 1 Deng Dongmen
The refugee is Yi Zhou Zhou.
The refugee, Yi, Zhou Zhou.
The vendor, Jia Yi, Yan Qinghui.
The vendor, Yi, Zeng Bin Bin.
The vendor, Yi Yi, Zeng Bin Bin.
Passenger A, Yang Jinhai.
Passenger A 1 Yang Jinhai
Doctor, Liu Jianming.
Lin Zhen, Liang, Zhao Nan.
Lin Yan, Ji Chenxuan.
The maid Jia Yi, Jin Meng Meng.
The maid, Yi Yi, Li Wenwen.
Extra.
He Wei, Wu Mingfeng, Gao Jian, Li Zu-ju. Li Mingyu, Chen Lei, Wang Jianmin, He Jianjun. Guo Xiaomin, Wu Yandong, Zhao Kaichao.
He Wei, Wu Mingfeng, Gao Jian, Li Zu Jui Li Mingyu, Chen Lei, Wang Jianmin, He Jianjun, Guo Xiaomin, Wu Yandong, Zhao Kaichao,
Zhu Meng, Duan Bofeng, Huang Yi, Zhou Bin Bin. Chen Yue, Lu Shun Hui, Shen Xianshu, Chen Fu Guo Zhu Haitao, Zhang Jiahui, Du Yan,
Zhu Meng, Duan Bofeng, Huang Yi, Zhou Bin Bin. Chen Yue, Lu Shun Hui, Shen Xianshu, Chen Fuguo, Zhu Haitao, Zhang Jiahui, Du Yan,
Tian Weitao, Wang Xiang, Yan Ziyan, Yu Huadong Xi Hanfeng Zhu Jixing Li Jianjun Yang Yun Niu Ruijun, Gao Yi, Party Jie.
Jin Yichun, Tang Bo, Zhu Kun Fei, Liu Tao. Bai Xuefeng, Zhu Zhongyin, Chen Meizing, Zhang Xue, Liu Fu Qiong, Wang Zheng, Liu Shuai, Chen Wei.
In the woods, Ruoying Zhang, Huang Wenting, Liu Dongsheng Wang Yilin, Zhang Yijia, Zhang Zhitao, Jin Xuyang Zhang Lu, Huang Bo, Wang Wei,
Pang Shion, Hu Zhenchuan, Song Jiada, Zhang Xiaojia, Hao Weilin, Nong Zhangbo, Chen Feijun, Zhang Jiayu. Liu Xiaolong, Li Hongxia
Yi Zhongxiang, Tan Yuting, Song Jun, Li Hongtao Meng Yi, Jiang Luze, Liang Manru, Yuan Hong Liu Ling, Li Bai Hui, Wang Li, Fang Fang Fang.
Sun Jiao Li, Feng Yanhang, Yan Yan, Cheng Qian. Chen Fei, Yao Qingteng, Siu Rufeng, Wei Tie Jian Chen Fu Guo, Lu Shun Hui, Feng Shihu.
Sun Jiao Li, Feng Yan Hang, Yan Yan, Cheng Qian Chen Fei, Yao Qingteng, Siu Rufeng, Wei Tie Jian Chen Fu Guo Lu Shun Hui Feng Shihu
Wang Meng, Liu Qiuhong, Chen Hongwei, Liu Miao Miao Marshal Tu, Han Bin, Yang Yinlong, Xu Xueqing Yang Yanhong, Zhang Jie, Geng Yueqiao
Zhang Xue, Wang Jinzhi, Shi Jingcheng, Yao Jinkang Lang Junsheng, Han Yongjie, Pu Zisong, Zhou Jiang Zhou Zhou, Marshal Liang, Zhu Yan
Ma Zihang, Zhao Hang, Wang Xiangzong, Gui Yang Ren Yuan, Luo Wei, Zhong Yong, Li Bohui, Ding Yun. Deng Song, Zhang Weihui, Wang Xiyou
Ma Zihang, Zhao Hang, Wang Xiangzong, Gui Yang Ren Yuan, Luo Wei, Zhong Yong, Li Bohui, Ding Yun. Deng Song, Zhang Weihui, Wang Xiyou,
Liu Ling, Li Ruiqi, Ge Zhang Xin, Liu Jinliang. Deng Dongmen, Zhao Long, Huang Wenting, Yi Zhongxiang Liu Shaohui, Wang Wei, Zhao Bin.
Wu Ke, Zhang Qian, Yang, Li Wenming, Guan Xiaolong, Guan Xiaolong, Gao Ziqiang, Lin Guifang, Tang Bo, Liang Jie.
Zhou Bin, Ren Kexin, Li Jianjun, Wu Yandong. Zhu Haitao, Xu Yun, Xie Guihua, Huang Yi. Lu Ruiqing, Jin Meng Meng, Li Wenwen.
Staff.
Director team.
Director, Jacky Zhang.
Director Li Haofei
Director Gu Changfu
Record: Li Zhuo.
Producer Hu Chuxuan
Writer/Chief Planning Hsu Hui-ting
Producer team.
Chief Producer Zhao Wenxue Zheng Huixi
Producer Zhang Jianyong Xiao Tianren
Kevin Chow, Ding.
One Ding.
Producer assistant Ye, Li Junhan
Producer Director Zhou Weibin
Outdoor producer, Liu Deyeong.
Life producer, Commander Shang, Susu.
Live Producer Zhao Anfeng
Executive Producer Li Longchuang Xu Jinglin
Executive Producer Li Longchuang Xu Shanlin
The venue team.
Mr. Lee Jun-han.
[Team Manager Lee Jun-han]
Agent.
Bao Cai, Geer, Wei Tie Jian, Zhang Yikang. Geng Junhai.
Wang Chengyu, Yang Haoran, Rex, Li Fei.
Photography team.
Photographer Li Kwan Qun
Photographer, Li guan Qun.
Photographer Chen Tie.
Photographer Chen Tie
Focus on Chen Quan, Luo Peiqiang
Photographer assistant Xiao Ran, Chia Le
Lighting team.
Lighting instructor, Xu Siu-biao.
Lighting instructor, Xu Xiaobiao.
Lighting Daisuke, Li Yunlong.
Lighting assistant, Li Yunlong.
Lighting assistant.
Hou Yaogeng, Xu Xiaomang, Li Lekai, Shi Bingyi.
Hou Yaogeng, Xu Xiaomang, Li Lekai, Shi Soldier
lantern, Solo.
The lighter, Solo.
The styling team.
styling instructor, Lin Jia Jin.
styling instructor, Lin Jiajin.
Makeup instructor, Liu Qian Qian.
Makeup team leader Duan Zhengnan
Makeup artist Mark
Lim Ying, the makeup team leader.
Makeup on site.
Cao Ruipion, Shi Meizhen, nice to meet you.
Cao Ruipion, Shi Meizhen, Gao Yan is good.
Costume team leader Han Zhan.
Costume team leader, Han Zhan.
Costume main focus, Li Ruowen Yan.
Costume assistant Lai Biyun.
Costume assistant, Lai Biyun.
Costume assistant Zhang Ya Ning.
Art team.
art instructor, Li Shuai.
Deputy art Jingjing
Props team
The prop team.
The prop team leader, Han Jin.
A prop for the play, Wang Ming.
Scene. Fan Yongle. Hu Xiang.
The props at the scene, Fan Yongle, Hu Xiang.
Development team, Head of Development, Han Wei.
Agent.
Wei Zhihua, Sun Fu, Li Shaogang, Zhou Wanyu.
Wei Zhihua, Sun Fu, Li Shaoqiang, Zhou Wanyu
Zhou Bing, Gao Xiangfei, Yang Lin Xi.
The recording team.
Recorder Lee Xiaohu
The recording assistant
Car team.
Car Unit.
Car keeper Jang Gun-young.
Agent.
Zhao Cheng, Cui Ligang, Lu Jun, Wei Min,
Zhao Cheng, Cui Ligang, Lu Jun, Wei Min.
Zhang Haiqiang, Ding Mingyang, Qiao Luifeng, Luo Guo.
Yu Zhenping, Liu Xiaohu, Li Longping, Zhang Ai Zhi
Yu Zhenping, Liu Xiaohu, Li Longping, Zhang Aichi
Yuan Xiao Jun, Tian Dasheng, Shen Baohman
Yuan Xiao Jun, Tian Da Sheng, Shen Bao Man.
The audition team.
audition studio.
The audition studio.
Team leader, Ding.
Acting director, Ma Xiaohua.
Actor assistant director, Jinqian.
Actor assistant director, Jinchang.
Action team, action instructor, Honghu.
Liu Ning, PR Director.
PR team members, Ren Jia Qi, Zhang Xuan.
PR team members, Kiki Ren, Zhang Xuan.
Film photo group, drama photographer, Xinxin Wu.
Side photographer, Wu Xinxin, Li Songyuan.
Finance Unit.
Yu Fang.
Product.
Product?
Li Hao Fei, Bi Zhi Peng, Qi Haixia, Wang Dan Li Tianhong.
A co-producer.
Qin Yinxuan, Sun Lei, Wang Qi Yun, Huang Yuan Lin Jiajin, Xiao Shengnan, Chen Huixiao,
Qin Yinxuan, Sun Lei, Wang Qi Yun, Huang Yuan Lin Jia Jin, Xiao Sheng Lan, Chen Huixiao,
Later production.
Beijing Central Film and Global Media Co., Ltd.
Beijing Central Film and Global Culture Co., Ltd.
Late-production Producer Cangu Xinhao
Late-production, Wang Rui.
Editing advisor Cangu Xinhao
Color, Li Yunkai, me.
Color Li Yunkai I
Packaging, Dong Zi.
Procedure: Wang Han, Song Jian.
DI, Xiaoqi.
The dialogue subtitles, Tie.
Proofreader, Guang.
Quality check Good
CG production.
Director Zhang Yiqi
Chen Jian Ping Li Wenhao.
Chen Jian Ping Li Wenhao
Voice production.
Kuck Time (Beijing) Cultural Media Co. Ltd.
Voice Director, Zhang Yuhong.
Voice Director Zhang Yuhong
Voice coordination Xiaoyi
Recorder Liu Jinming.
Mr. Bai, Zheng Xinyuan.
sound effect design, Zhou Xian.
Foley, Shi Yaqing.
Music Editor Joo Hyun
Music editor, Joo Hyun.
Voice director Ma Cheng Li Xuejiao
Babymonster Li.
Dubbing Top. BrantB.
Dubbing actor.
A dubber?
Make a wish with a monument
Lin Che Yi Jiang Qiu
Wen Youcai Yi, Lu Siheng.
Lin Rou Yi, Bu Bu Qu.
Lucky Du, Chen Yifan.
Qian Lai Fu and Zhang Jiahui.
Lin, the wind is clear.
Zhao Mingzhu, Dong Yue,
[Lin Dao, Yi, Yang Xiaoran.]
Lin Dao becomes one, Yang Xiaoran.
Ye Ziyi, Dong Can.
Li Xuejiao.
Other dubbers
Other dubbers?
Theme song: "What I Want".
Singer: Wanxin, Yi Lingli
Song: Zhu Langyu.
Song: Zhu Dangyu.
Lyrics: Wang Yijie.
Lyrics: Wang Yijie
Arrangement: Polaris Zhang Xuchen
Guitar: Zhang Xiaoyue.
Mix/mother belt: Tujy.
[Mix/Mother belt: Tujy]
Recorder: Woo Jung-hee.
[Studio: ASE stadio]
Audio.
Thank you.
Lemon tea. Lemon tea.
A product company.
Hu Happy Film Co., Ltd.
Zhejiang Huahua Film and Culture Co., Ltd.
Zhejiang, Huahua, Film and Culture Co., Ltd.
Nanjing Xigou Culture Co., Ltd.
[Nanjing Xigou Culture Co., Ltd. Ltd. Ltd. Ltd. Ltd. Ltd. Ltd. Ltd. Ltd. Ltd. Ltd. Ltd. Ltd.]
Joint production.
BEIJINGNULANNING SHUUAHOUUXIAI
Beijing Noram Movie Culture is limited
BEIJINGNULANNNING SHUNHUAYOUXIANGSI
Beijing Noram Film.
Beijing Nolan Film.
Ace.
Asia Starry Sky Entertainment.
CANDYISTAGE.
Qingdao Drama Candy Culture Co., Ltd.
Production company.
Zhejiang, Zheng Zheng, Film and Culture Co., Ltd.
Xiangshan He Shun Film Co., Ltd.
Thank you very much.
Hengdian Film Center.
Hengdian World. Studios.
Hengdian Film and TV City.
Hengdian Film Studio?