Xiangshan He Shun Film Co., Ltd.
Although I'm weak and sick,
but it's my personal hobby.
But you know martial arts.
Father.
What you said is true.
One rice shop can solve the problem.
I'm all ears.
Can you make a bet with Bao?
Why do you want to bet?
This concerns the court.
You're a girl.
Don't talk nonsense.
I just want to contribute to the Lin family.
If we succeed,
can we ask His Highness for a wish?
As long as I can help His Majesty,
I have more than one wish.
Since you want to gamble,
I should keep a sense of mystery.
Father, I don't think it's appropriate.
It concerns the dignity of the royal family.
Bao'er is a woman.
She didn't go to the court.
I didn't know that the court was in turmoil.
It's dangerous.
If something happens,
will you take the responsibility?
Yes.
Okay.
I accept the bet.
Please.
There are bandits who learn from each other.
and learn from each other.
At that moment, I thought
this is the man who protected me.
Stop talking nonsense.
Tell me.
What do you want a rice shop for?
Move the money to the government.
and fight against poison with poison.
Be specific.
I used to...
It's hard to explain.
Just leave it to me.
Thank you for your words.
for giving up your life for me.
Thank you.
How are you going to thank me?
A drop of water should be repaid with a spring.
How do you want me to thank you?
I think it's simple.
You
spend the night with me.
Ah.
No way
Again?
Have you found out what you asked?
Is it as I thought?
Bao’er
She did hire a group of robbers.
But she didn't do it for you.
but to act.
It was someone else.
switched the robbers to a servant who killed you.
As expected,
she was used by Lin Feng.
Ziye.
Maybe Zhao Bao'er can be used by us.
But Young Master,
you've exposed your kung fu skills to save her.
I don't want to see your long-planned plan
to be ruined by her.
Maybe
I can make her tell the truth.
You're awake.
Let me tell you first.
There is silicone powder in the wax oil.
It's highly poisonous.
Ye and I have taken the antidote in advance.
So it's fine.
The less you talk,
the longer you live,
Understood.
Ye.
Lin Che, this is the second time you drugged me.
And you are strong.
and strong.
Why do you always pretend to be weak?
How dare you say that?
If it wasn't for saving you,
I would have exposed my martial arts.
Yes.
You're guilty of catching me.
Ye.
It's double poison now.
I said
A piece of crap.
What do you want me to say?
Why did you take the credit?
His Highness is the Supreme Lord.
It's normal for me to please him.
If my wish is fulfilled,
it'll be gold and silver.
and a great fortune.
I'm just a weak woman.
I just want to live.
Cut the crap. I know who you work for.
Let's make a deal.
She wants to make a deal with me.
I don't think you know what's going on.
You're in no position to negotiate with me.
My people are still in the mansion.
Even if I die,
someone will still tell Lin Feng
you're pretending to be a pig and eating a tiger.
Actually, I had no choice.
I was poisoned by Lin Feng.
Many things are not what I want.
As long as you are willing to detoxify me,
I'll do whatever you want.
I'm willing to do anything.
How do I know this is not a trick?
I haven't settled with you
I haven't got even with you yet.
I don't have time to waste.
I'll give you three days.
If I don't have an answer within three days,
it's up to you.
Female motto.
The Classic of Filial Daughter.
Why isn't there a male virtue motto?
It seems that we chivalry women have higher status.
Physics.
Is it comfortable?
It's uncomfortable, right?
Are you going to the toilet?
Because you're thirsty.
You need water.
So you're going to the toilet?
Hey.
even if you're thirsty,
you don't need to go to the toilet.
I have
I have food
and drinks.
What about you?
Just drink whatever you want.
Oh, right.
Your mouth is sealed.
I don't think you can drink it.
But it's okay.
I'll drink it for you.
to receive people with a letter.
The world believes
[If you don't believe in people,]
My wife is suspicious.
Oh no, Miss Rou loves this book so much.
she must have acknowledged these principles.
If she knows my real identity,
and knows I lied to her,
Fool.
Miss Rou.
Why are you here?
What are you looking at?
Nothing.
Male virtue.
It teaches a man to obey a woman with three obediences and four virtues.
A man should obey three obediences and four virtues of a woman.
Yes.
Why haven't I seen
Which three, which four virtues?
Exactly.
I'm not married yet.
I'll marry and be my wife.
A wife dies from a daughter.
Anyway, the wife must follow her when she goes out.
You must obey the wife's order.
My wife is wrong.
You have to obey blindly.
I've never heard of such rules.
Rules?
Rules are set by people.
I made such a rule today.
and I will follow it.
I’m just not as famous as Ban Zhao.
Otherwise, I'll write a book
and let all men obey it.
Fool. Yes.
Even if you wrote it,
no one will obey.
Why?
not what they want to do?
Why do they recommend it?
You're indeed a princess.
You're right to the point.
You're amazing.
Fool.
But...
Rou.
If I lied to you,
will you blame me?
Liar.
Hurry up and confess.
I don’t want you to suffer if I find out.
Actually, Jo Bo-ah is my sister.
Make a wish.
Bao.
No.
The wish girl is your sister.
Yes.
My brother locked her up.
What?
Lin Che, Meng En.
Xu Zi Yin made a wish.
Wen Youcai, Han Haotian.
Lin Rou. Chen Chuqi.
Lin Rou Yi, Chen Chuqi.
Lin Feng Yi, Jin Wangwang.
Lin Yan and Yang Jun.
Lucky Du, Tan Yinmin.
Qian Youfu Yi, Guo Chang.
Zhao Mingzhu, Liu Lingling.
Lin Dao Cheng, Feng Wusheng.
Leaf, one, one, one, one, one, one, one.
A leaf will lead to a war.
A Lian, Xu Shiyao.
The Crown Princess, Xiong Jiayi.
One bear plus one.
Meng Heng Yi Bai Haoyan.
The green one is Lian Mingyang.
Special appointment.
Li Yixuan, guard of the granary.
Baldy painter, Yang Xingliang.
Guard, Wang Shuixin.
A maid, Xu Huiting.
Magistrate Chen Tianci
Directress Chen Fuguo
MC Chen Fukuk
Liao Haipeng.
Girl, one Wai-wai.
Guard 1 Zhu Haitao
Jing and Fang Xin.
One for maid, one for Liu Sisi.
A maid, two, one, Xia Ying.
Maid, 31, Bai Bingqi.
maid 41, Dong Jun Yi.
Five maids for Tianyi.
Five for maids, one for Fu Yi.
One Little Wish for Yue Ying.
A little wish for Yue Ying.
Make a wish, foster mother, sing with bamboo.
The boy made a wish, Yang Bao'er.
The procuress, Li Hong,
Liu Bu, Wang Rumeng.
The greasy male lead, Yuan Hong.
Ms. Zhao has a sea breeze.
The heroine of yarn is a Zhou Xian Yue.
The first eunuch, Yuan Ying,
First Eunuch, Yuan Ying.
A maid, Lü Xinyang.
My servant, Jia Yi, Yang Doudou.
My servant, Yi Yi, He Gui.
The servant, Yi Yi, He Gui.
Ye's Yi Ji Ling.
Lin Che, Guo Wupeng,
The Fifth Prince, Wang Yongdi.
One refugee, Xu Weiqiang.
Trainee 1 Deng Dongmen
The refugee is Yi Zhou Zhou.
The refugee, Yi, Zhou Zhou.
The vendor, Jia Yi, Yan Qinghui.
The vendor, Yi Yi, Zeng Bin Bin.
Passenger A, Yang Jinhai.
Doctor, Liu Jianming.
Lin Zhen, Liang, Zhao Nan.
Lin Yan, Ji Chenxuan.
A maid named Jia Yi, Jin Meng Meng.
Jia Yi, Jin Meng Meng.
The maid, Yi Yi, Li Wenwen.
Extra.
He Wei, Wu Mingfeng, Gao Jian, Li Zu Juan Li Mingyu, Chen Lei, Wang Jianmin, He Jianjun Guo Xiaomin, Wu Yandong, Zhao Kaichao,
Zhu Meng Duan Pao Feng, Huang Yi, Zhou Bin, Zhou Bin, Lu Shun Hui, Shen Xianshu, Chen Xiangguo, Zhu Haitao wants Du Yan.
Tian Weitao, Wang Xiang, Yan Ziyan, Yu Huadong. Xi Hanfeng, Zhu Jianxing, Li Jianjun, Yang Yun. Niu Ruijun, Gao Yi, Party Jie.
Tian Weitao, Wang Xiang, Yan Ziyan, Yu Huadong. Xi Hanfeng Zhu Jixing Li Jianjun Yang Yun Niu Ruijun, Gao Yi, Party Jie.
Zhang Ruoying, Huang Wenting, Liu Yici, Zhang Zhitao, Zhang Xuyang, Zhang Yiyang, Huang Bo, Wang Wei.
Pang Shion, Hu Zhenchuan, Song Jiada, Zhang Xiaojia Hao Weilin, Nong Zhangbo, Chen Feijun, Zhang Jiayu Liu Xiaolong, Li Hongxia
Pang Shion, Hu Zhenchuan, Song Jiada, Zhang Xiaojia, Hao Weilin, Nong Zhangbo, Chen Feiyan, Zhang Jiayu. Liu Xiaolong, Li Hongxia
Yi Zhongxiang, Tan Yuting, Song Jun, Li Hongtao. Meng Yi, Jiang Luze, Liang Manru, Yuan Hong. Liu Ling, Li Bai Hui, Wang Li, Fang Fang.
Yi Zhongxiang, Tan Yuting, Song army, Li Hongtao. Meng Yi, Jiang Lu Ze, Liang Manru, Yuan Hong. Liu Ling, Li Bai Hui, Wang Li, Fang Fang.
Sun Jiao Li, Feng Yanhang, Yan Yan, Cheng Qian. Chen Fei, Yao Qingteng, Siu Rufeng, Wei Tie Jian Chen Fu Guo Lu Shun Hui Feng Shihu
Wang Meng, Liu Qiuhong, Chen Hongwei, Liu Miao Miao Marshal Tu, Han Bin, Yang Yinlong, Xu Xueqing Yang Yanhong, Zhang Jie, Geng Yueqiao
Zhang Xue, Wang Jinzhi, Shi Jingcheng, Yao Jinkang Junsheng, Han Yongjie, Pu Zisong, Zhou Jiang Zhou Zhou, Marshal Liang, Zhu Yan Yan
Zhang Xue, Wang Jinzhi, Shi Jingcheng, Yao Jinkang Junsheng, Han Yongjie, Pu Zisong, Zhou Jiang Zhou Zhou, Marshal Liang, Zhu Yan
Ma Zihang, Zhao Hang, Wang Xiangzong, Gui Yang Ren Yuan, Luo Wei, Zhong Yong, Li Bohui, Ding Yun. Deng Song, Zhang Weihui, Wang Xiyou
Wu Ke, Zhang Qian, Zheng Yang, Li Wenming. Guan Xiaolong, Gao Ziqiang, Lin Jiangjiang, Luo Sheng Lin Guifang, Tang Bo, Liang Jie,
Wu Ke, Zhang Qian, Soldier Yang, Li Wenming Guan Xiaolong, Gao Ziqiang, Lin Jiangjiang, Luo Sheng. Lin Guifang, Tang Bo, Liang Jie.
Staff.
Director team.
Director, Jacky Zhang.
Director Li Haofei
Director Gu Changfu
Director Gu Changfu.
The journalist, Li Zhuo.
Producer Hu Chuxuan
Writer/Chief Planner Hsu Hui Ting
Writer/Chief Planning Hsu Hye-ting
Production team.
[Chief Producer: Cho Moon Seol, Jung Hui Hee]
Chief Producer Zhao Wenxue Zheng Huixi
Producer Zhang Jianyong Xiao Tianren
Kevin Chow, Ding.
Zhou Kaibin.
Producer assistant Ye, Li Junhan
Producer Director Zhou Weibin
Outdoor producer Liu Deyeong
Life Producer, Commander Shang, Susu.
Live Producer Zhao Anfeng
Executive Producer Li Longchuang Xu Ganlin
The venue team.
[Team Manager Lee Jun-han]
Agent.
Bao Cai, Geer, Wei Tie Jian, Zhang Yikang. Geng Junhai.
Wang Chengyu, Yang Haoran, Rex, Li Fei.
Photography team.
Photographer Li Kwan Qun.
Photographer, Chen Tie.
Photographer Chen Tie.
Focus! Chen Quan! Robert Keung!
Focus, Chen Quan, Luo Peiqiang
Photographer assistant Xiao Ran, Chia Le
Lighting team.
Lighting instructor, Xu Xiaobiao.
Lighting assistant, Li Yunlong.
Lighting assistant.
Hou Yaifeng, Xu Xiaomang, Li Lekai, Shi Bingyi.
The lighter, Solo.
The styling team.
styling instructor, Lin Jiajin.
Makeup instructor, Liu Qian Qian.
Makeup instructor Liu Qian
Makeup team leader Duan Zhengnan
Makeup artist Mark
Lim Ying, the makeup team leader.
Makeup on site.
Cao Ruipion, Shi Meizhen. Nice to meet you.
Costume team leader, Han Zhan.
Costume main focus, Li Ruowen Yan.
Costume assistant, Lai Biyun.
Costume assistant Zhang Ya Ning.
Art team.
art instructor, Li Shuai.
Deputy art Jingjing
Props team.
The prop team leader, Han Jin.
Props team leader, Han Jin.
A prop for the play, Wang Ming.
Scene. Fan Yongle. Hu Xiang.
Development team, Head of Development, Han Wei.
Agent.
Team members.
Wei Zhihua, Sun Fu, Li Shaoqiang, Zhou Wanyu.
Zhou Bing, Gao Xiangfei, Yang Lin Xi.
The recording team.
Recorder Lee Xiaohu
Recording assistant
The recording assistant.
Car team.
Car Unit.
Car Supervisor Jang.
Car Supervisor Jang Gun-young.
Agent.
Zhao Cheng, Cui Ligang, Lu Jun, Wei Min,
Zhang Haiqiang, Ding Mingyang, Qiao Luifeng, Luo Koo.
Zhang Haiqiang, Ding Mingyang, Qiao Luifeng, Luo Guoguo.
Yu Zhenping, Liu Xiaohu, Li Longping, Zhang Ai Zhi,
Yuan Xiao Jun, Tian Dasheng, Shen Boman
The audition team.
The audition studio.
Team leader, Ding.
Acting director, Ma Xiaohua.
Actor assistant director, Jinqian.
Action team, action instructor, Honghu.
Liu Ning, PR Director.
PR team member Ren Jia Qi and Zhang Xuan.
Film photo group, drama photographer, Xinxin Wu.
Side photographer Xinxin Wu Songyuan Li
Photographer, Wu Xinxin, Li Songyuan.
Finance Unit.
Yu Fang.
Product.
Product?
Li Hao Fei, Bi Zhi Peng, Qi Haixia, Wang Dan Li Tianhong.
A co-producer.
Qin Yingxuan, Sun Lei, Wang Qi Yun, Huang Yuan, Lin Jiajin, Xiao Shengnan, Chen Huixiao,
Later production.
Midfilm Spiral.
Middle Shadow Circuit.
Beijing Media Co., Ltd.
Re-production Producer Cangu Xinhao
Late-production Producer Cangu Xinhao
Late-production, Wang Rui.
Editing Advisor Cangu Nene
Color, Li Yunkai, me.
Color Li Yunkai I
Packaging, Dong Zi.
Procedure: Wang Han, Song Jian.
DI, Xiaoqi.
The dialogue subtitles are shaking.
The dialogue subtitles, trembling.
Proofreader, Guang.
Quality check Good
Good.
CG production.
Director Zhang Yiqi
Chen Jianping, Zhang Yifeng, Zhu Ke Pen, Jin Xiaowei Lee Moon Ho.
Voice production
Voice production.
Kuck Time (Beijing) Cultural Media Co. Ltd.
Voice Director Zhang Yuhong.
Voice coordination Xiaoyi
Voice count Xiaoyi
Recorder Liu Jinming.
Mr. Bai, Zheng Xinyuan.
Audio design, Joo Hyun.
Foley, Shi Yaqing.
Music editor, Zhou Xian.
Voice director Ma Cheng Li Xuejiao
Dubbing Top, BrantB.
A dubber.
Make a wish
Make a wish. Zhang Yunmeng.
Lin Che, Jiang Qiu.
Wen Youcai Yi, Lu Siheng.
Lin Rou is a group of people.
Lin Rou Yi.
Lucky Du, Chen Yifan.
Qian Lai Fu and Zhang Jiahui.
The wind is clear.
The forest breeze is clear and clear.
Zhao Mingzhu, Dong Yue,
[Lin Dao, Yi, Yang Xiaoran.]
Ziye Yi, Dong Can.
Ziye Yi Dong Can.
Li Xuejiao.
Other dubbers
Sun Zhihao, Li Qiaoyun, Zhang Qianzheng, Weng Tangtang. Guo Xinlei.
Theme Song: "What I Want".
Theme song: "What I Want".
Singer: Wanxin, Lingli
Singer: Wanxin, Yiling Li
Song: Zhu Langyu.
Lyrics: Wang Yijie.
Lyrics: Wang Yijie
Arrangement: Polaris Zhang Xuchen
Guitar: Zhang Xiaoyue.
Mix/Mother belt: Tujy
Recorder: Woo Jeong-hee.
Recorder: Woo Jeong-hee
[Recording Studio: ASESTUDIO]
Thank you.
Lemon tea, please.
A product company.
Hu Happy Film Co., Ltd.
Zhejiang, Zheng Zheng, Film and Culture Co., Ltd.
Nanjing Xigou Culture Co., Ltd.
It's a joint product.
Beijing Nolan Film Culture Co., Ltd.
BEIJINGNULANNNING SHUNHUAYOUXIANGSI
Beijing Nolan Film Co., Ltd.
Beijing Nolan Film.
Look at you. Look at you.
Ace.
[Asia Starry Sky Entertainment]
Asia Starry Sky Entertainment.
CANDYISTAGE
CANDYISTAGE.
Qingdao Drama Candy Culture Co., Ltd.
Production company.
Zhejiang, Zheng Zheng, Film and Culture Co., Ltd.
Xiangshan He Shui Film Co., Ltd.
Thank you very much.
Hengdian Film Center.
[Hendonian World] Studios.
Hengdian Film and TV City.