Xiangshan He Shun Film Co., Ltd. Ltd. Ltd. Ltd. Ltd. Ltd. Ltd. Ltd. Ltd.
First of all,
Who is a pervert?
Of course it's you.
Why did you make me unconscious?
I'm afraid you'll harass me.
What did you say?
You carry the painting with you
I look like Elder Tsu
Of course I'm afraid you're up to no good
Ridiculous.
You were the one who wanted to knock me out
and hurt me.
Did I do anything to you?
Didn't you notice?
I...
How would I know?
Besides, since you're married to me,
you're mine now.
It's fair and square for me to kill you.
What lecher?
I...
What?
There is only one reason for me to do this.
I don't want to touch you.
but I'm afraid you'll be sad.
Since you don't want me to touch you,
That's great.
We can get along peacefully.
Don't act like a thief.
Who knows what your purpose is?
Maybe you have a special fetish.
Young Master.
The carriage is ready.
I'll remember this.
I'm not a vegetarian.
Father.
Mother.
Bao and I are here to greet you.
This arm...
Father, Mother.
Please have some tea.
Che.
Thank you, Father.
Bao.
Here.
Thank you, Mother.
By the way, Bao,
when is your birthday?
I let people remember.
Mother.
I've made up my mind.
Since I married into the Lin family,
I'm a member of the Lin family.
I'm a ghost of the Lin family.
My birthday...
Let's call it yesterday.
Your Highness.
Look how smart this new wife is.
Yes.
I've been reading the Analects lately.
I heard that you are well-versed in Confucius and Mencius.
and read a lot of books.
I admire you.
I have something I don't understand.
May I ask you something?
Sure.
The three armies can seize the commander.
A man cannot steal his ambition.
What do you mean?
How would I know?
It sounds like a man.
Then let him take the blame.
Okay.
I can't tell you.
This sentence describes my husband.
His Highness is quite handsome.
Your wife has sharp eyes.
I can see that even if Che is ill,
he’s still ambitious.
You’re right.
Che does have
in making incense.
I know you're not Zhao Bao'er.
Thank you, God of Bandits.
God of Bandits is really a deity.
Don't be nervous.
I've asked the warehouse
the jewelry you stole.
Thank you.
I don't mean to offend you.
I'll leave tonight.
Please check the accounts.
I'll make it up for you.
No need. Just stay at home.
There are many refugees lately.
If you weren't desperate,
you wouldn't have gone this way.
I admire your generosity and foresight.
But I won't stay for long.
Thank you for your kindness.
You're welcome.
Actually, I have a favor to ask you today.
You flatter me.
I'm indebted to you.
How can I not help him?
Lin Che has been coveting my position for a long time.
I’m deeply surrounded.
Although he was weak and sick,
I still think he's pretending to be a pig and eating tiger.
I feel uneasy.
Can you keep an eye on him?
The third rule of the family.
you can't participate in court disputes.
I will do my best.
I chose Jo Bo-ah
because he and Lin Che are doomed to opposition.
and poor family.
and the Zhao family
can be used by us.
This wild girl doesn't seem to be easy to control.
Thank you for your tea, Your Highness.
Goodbye.
Since you don't trust me,
I won't beat around the bush.
I poisoned the tea you just drank.
As long as you keep an eye on Lin Che.
and report our whereabouts,
I can give you an antidote every 15 days.
I guarantee you won't go crazy and laugh to death.
Despicable.
Shameless!
How dare
in the royal mansion.
Haha.
Your Highness.
I was joking.
There’s a deep gap
between Lin Che and me.
and a huge grudge.
Even if His Highness doesn’t say it,
I won't stand against him.
Don’t panic, Your Highness.
I’ll keep an eye on Lin Che.
Thank you, heroine.
I'll kill him.
Not to mention there are masters in the mansion,
I've tried my trick twice.
No hair.
He's taller than me.
Oh.
Not tall.
Anyway, to get the antidote,
we have to use wisdom.
They give me the antidote every 15 days.
When they give me the antidote,
we will know where the antidote is.
By then...
Okay.
Before that,
we all need to be valued by the Lin family.
Yes.
One more thing.
Did Lin Che do anything to me
after he knocked me out.
I thought I was cunning enough.
But compared to them,
I'm just a sheep
and entered the King of Hell.
The King of Hell asked me how I died.
I had no idea.
According to my experience,
Lin Che is still a kid
He’s still a kid.
I know you best.
This is the first time for a man.
he wants to do it twice.
But if he hates you,
and doesn't like you,
he won't have a second time.
He will feel rejected.
What do you mean?
If he takes advantage of my sister,
he has to be responsible.
Who wants him to be responsible?
Stop arguing.
I have an idea.
to determine if he is a gentleman.
You pretended to be drunk
and see if he will take advantage of us.
Jing.
The ginseng soup the young master and princess made for you.
Why do you look so pale?
Okay, I'll take it inside.
Yes.
The Linglong Liquor of the Lin family is really smooth and not greasy.
It's sweet and delicious.
Why are you in my room?
Who asked you to come?
Such a good wine.
Are you sure you don't want a sip?
I said get out.
Fine.
You said you wanted me to leave,
but your body is quite honest.
Why are you pulling me?
Lin Che, one Meng En.
Xu Zi Yin made a wish.
Wen Youcai, Han Haotian.
Lin Rou, Chen Chuqi.
Lin Feng Yi, Jin Wangwang.
Lin Yan and Yang Jun.
Lucky Du, Tan Yinmin.
Qian Youfu Yi, Guo Chang.
Zhao Mingzhu, Liu Lingling.
Lin Dao Cheng, Feng Wusheng.
Leaf, one, one, one, one, one.
A leaf will lead to a war.
A Lian, Xu Shiyao.
One bear plus one for the Crown Princess.
Meng Heng Yi Bai Haoyan.
Green Er, Lian Mingyang.
Special appointment.
Li Yixuan, guard of the granary.
Baldy painter, Yang Xingliang.
Guard, Wang Shuixin.
A maid, Xu Huiting.
Magistrate Chen Tianci
Directress Chen Fuguo
MC Chen Fukuk
Liao Haipeng.
Girl, one Wai-wai.
Guard 1 Zhu Haitao
Jing and Fang Xin.
One for maid, one for Liu Sisi.
A maid, two, one, Xia Ying.
Maid, 31, Bai Bingqi.
maid 41, Dong Jun Yi.
Five maids for Tianyi.
Five for maids, one for Fu Yi.
One Little Wish for Yue Ying.
A little wish for Yue Ying.
Make a wish, foster mother, sing with bamboo.
The boy made a wish, Yang Bao'er.
The procuress, Li Hong,
Liu Bu, Wang Rumeng.
The greasy male lead, Yuan Hong.
Ms. Zhao has a sea breeze.
The heroine of yarn is a Zhou Xian Yue.
The first eunuch, Yuan Ying,
First Eunuch, Yuan Ying.
A maid, Lü Xinyang.
My servant, Jia Yi, Yang Doudou.
My servant, Yi Yi, He Gui.
The servant, Yi Yi, He Gui.
Ye's Yi Ji Ling.
Lin Che, Guo Wupeng,
The Fifth Prince, Wang Yongdi.
One refugee, Xu Weiqiang.
Trainee 1 Deng Dongmen
The refugee is Yi Zhou Zhou.
The refugee, Yi, Zhou Zhou.
The vendor, Jia Yi, Yan Qinghui.
The vendor, Yi Yi, Zeng Bin Bin.
Passenger A, Yang Jinhai.
Doctor, Liu Jianming.
Lin Zhen, Liang, Zhao Nan.
Lin Yan, Ji Chenxuan.
A maid named Jia Yi, Jin Meng Meng.
Jia Yi, Jin Meng Meng.
The maid Yiyi, Li Wenwen.
Extra.
Come on. Come on.
He Wei, Wu Mingfeng, Gao Jian, Li Zu Juan Li Mingyu, Chen Lei, Wang Jianmin, He Jianjun Guo Xiaomin, Wu Yandong, Zhao Kaichao,
Zhu Meng Duan Pao Feng, Huang Yi, Zhou Bin, Zhou Bin, Lu Shun Hui, Shen Xianshu, Chen Xiangguo, Zhu Haitao wants Du Yan.
Tian Weitao, Wang Xiang, Yan Ziyan, Yu Huadong. Xi Hanfeng, Zhu Jianxing, Li Jianjun, Yang Yun. Niu Ruijun, Gao Yi, Party Jie.
Tian Weitao, Wang Xiang, Yan Ziyan, Yu Huadong. Xi Hanfeng, Zhu Jixing, Li Jianjun, Yang Yun. Niu Ruijun, Gao Yi, Party Jie.
Eight Jin One Spring Tang Bo Zhu Kun Fei Liu Tao Bai Xuefeng, Zhu Zhongyin, Chen Meibing, Zhang Xue, Liu Fu Qiong, Wang Zheng, Liu Shuai, Chen Wei.
Zhang Ruoying, Huang Wenting, Liu Yisheng, Zhang Zhijia, Zhang Xuyang, Zhang Yiyang, Huang Bo, Wang Wei.
Pang Shion, Hu Zhenchuan, Song Jiada, Zhang Xiaojia Hao Weilin, Nong Zhangbo, Chen Feijun, Zhang Jiayu Liu Xiaolong, Li Hongxia
Pang Shion, Hu Zhenchuan, Song Jiada, Zhang Xiaojia, Hao Weilin, Nong Zhangbo, Chen Feiyan, Zhang Jiayu. Liu Xiaolong, Li Hongxia
Yi Zhongxiang, Tan Yuting, Song Jun, Li Hongtao. Meng Yi, Jiang Luze, Liang Manru, Yuan Hong. Liu Ling, Li Bai Hui, Wang Li, Fang Fang.
Yi Zhongxiang, Tan Yuting, Song Jun, Li Hongtao. Meng Yi, Jiang Lu Ze, Liang Manru, Yuan Hong. Liu Ling, Li Bai Hui, Wang Li, Fang Fang.
Sun Jiao Li, Feng Yanhang, Yan Yan, Cheng Qian. Chen Fei, Yao Qingteng, Siu Rufeng, Wei Tie Jian Chen Fu Guo Lu Shun Hui Feng Shihu
Wang Meng, Liu Qiuhong, Chen Hongwei, Liu Miao Miao Marshal Tu, Han Bin, Yang Yinlong, Xu Xueqing Yang Yanhong, Zhang Jie, Geng Yueqiao
Zhang Xue, Wang Jinzhi, Shi Jingcheng, Yao Jinkang Junsheng, Han Yongjie, Pu Zisong, Zhou Jiang Zhou Zhou, Marshal Liang, Zhu Yan Yan
Zhang Xue, Wang Jinzhi, Shi Jingcheng, Yao Jinkang Junsheng, Han Yongjie, Pu Zisong, Zhou Jiang Zhou Zhou, Marshal Liang, Zhu Yan
Ma Zihang, Zhao Hang, Wang Xiangzong, Gui Yang Ren Yuan, Luo Xuan, Zhong Yong, Li Bohui, Ding Yun. Deng Song, Zhang Weihui, Wang Xiyou
Liu Ling, Li Ruiqi, Ge Zhang, Liu Jinliang, Deng Dongmen, Zhao Long, Huang Wenting, Yi Zhongxiang Liu Shaohui, Wang Wei, Zhao Bin,
Liu Ling, Li Ruiqi, Ge Zhang Xin, Liu Jinliang. Deng Dongmen, Zhao Long, Huang Wenting, Yi Zhongxiang Liu Shaohui, Wang Wei, Zhao Bin,
Wu Ke, Zhang Qian, Zheng Yang, Li Wenming. Guan Xiaolong Gao Ziqiang Lin Jiangjiang Luo Sheng Lin Gui Fang, Tang Bo, Liang Jie.
Staff.
Director team.
Director, Jacky Zhang.
Director Li Haofei
Director Gu Changfu
Director Gu Changfu.
Record: Li Zhuo.
Producer Hu Chuxuan
Writer/Chief Planner Hsu Hui Ting
Writer/Chief Planning Hsu Hye-ting
Producer team.
[Chief Producer: Cho Moon Seol, Jung Hui Hee]
Chief Producer Zhao Wenxue Zheng Huixi
Producer Zhang Jianyong Xiao Tianren
Kevin Chow, Ding.
Zhou Kaibin.
Producer assistant Ye, Li Junhan
Producer Director Zhou Weibin
Outdoor producer Liu Deyeong
Life Producer, Commander Shang, Susu.
Live Producer Zhao Anfeng
Executive Producer Li Longchuang Xu Ganlin
The venue team.
[Team Manager Lee Jun-han]
Agent.
Bao Cai, Geer, Wei Tie Jian, Zhang Yikang. Geng Junhai.
Wang Chengyu, Yang Haoran, Rex, Li Fei.
Photography team.
Photographer Li Kwan Qun
Photographer Chen Tie.
Focus, Chen Quan, Luo Pei Keung
Focus, Chen Quan, Luo Peiqiang
Photographer assistant Xiao Ran, Chia Le
Lighting team.
Lighting instructor, Xu Xiaobiao.
Lighting assistant, Li Yunlong.
Lighting assistant.
Hou Yaifeng, Xu Xiaomang, Li Lekai, Shi Bingyi.
The lighter, Solo.
The styling team.
styling instructor, Lin Jiajin.
Makeup instructor, Liu Qian Qian.
Makeup instructor Liu Qian
Makeup team leader Duan Zhengnan
Makeup artist Mark
Lim Ying, the makeup team leader.
Makeup on site.
Cao Ruipion, Shi Meizhen. Nice to meet you.
Costume team leader, Han Zhan.
Costume main focus, Li Ruowen Yan.
Costume assistant, Lai Biyun.
Costume assistant Zhang Ya Ning.
Art team.
art instructor, Li Shuai.
Deputy art Jingjing
The prop team.
The prop team leader, Han Jin.
A prop for the play, Wang Ming.
Scene. Fan Yongle. Hu Xiang.
Development team, Head of Development, Han Wei.
Team Leader. Yes?
Team members.
Wei Zhihua, Sun Fu, Li Shaoqiang, Zhou Wanyu.
Zhou Bing, Gao Xiangfei, Yang Lin Xi.
The recording team.
Recorder Lee Xiaohu
Recording assistant
The recording assistant.
Car team.
Car Unit.
Car Supervisor Jang.
Car Supervisor Jang Gun-young.
Agent.
Zhao Cheng, Cui Ligang, Lu Jun, Wei Min,
Zhang Haiqiang, Ding Mingyang, Qiao Luifeng, Luo Koo.
Zhang Haiqiang, Ding Mingyang, Qiao Luifeng, Luo Guoguo.
Yu Zhenping, Liu Xiaohu, Li Longping, Zhang Ai Zhi
Yuan Xiao Jun, Tian Dasheng, Shen Boman
The audition team.
The audition studio.
Team leader, Ding.
Acting director, Ma Xiaohua.
Actor assistant director, Jinqian.
Action team, action instructor, Honghu.
Liu Ning, PR Director.
PR team member Ren Jia Qi and Zhang Xuan.
Film photo group, drama photographer, Xinxin Wu.
Side photographer Xinxin Wu Songyuan Li
Photographer, Wu Xinxin, Li Songyuan.
Finance Unit.
Yu Fang.
Product.
Product?
Li Hao Fei, Bi Zhi Peng, Qi Haixia, Wang Dan Li Tianhong.
A co-producer.
Qin Yingxuan, Sun Lei, Wang Qi Yun, Huang Yuan, Lin Jiajin, Xiao Shengnan, Chen Huixiao,
Later production.
Midfilm Spiral.
Middle Shadow Circuit.
Beijing Media Co., Ltd.
Re-production Producer Cangu Xinhao
Late-production Producer Cangu Xinhao
Late-production, Wang Rui.
Editing Advisor Cangu Nene
Color, Li Yunkai, me.
Color Li Yunkai I
Packaging, Dong Zi.
Procedure: Wang Han, Song Jian.
DI, Xiaoqi.
The dialogue subtitles are shaking.
The dialogue subtitles, trembling.
Proofreader, Guang.
Quality check Good
CG production.
Director Zhang Yiqi
Chen Jianping, Zhang Yifeng, Zhu Ke Pen, Jin Xiaowei Lee Moon Ho.
Voice production
Voice production.
Kuck Time (Beijing) Cultural Media Co. Ltd.
Voice Director Zhang Yuhong
Voice coordination Xiaoyi
Voice count Xiaoyi
Recorder Liu Jinming.
Mr. Bai, Zheng Xinyuan.
Audio design, Joo Hyun.
Foley. Stone should be clear.
Foley. Stone.
Music editor, Zhou Xian.
Voice director Ma Cheng Li Xuejiao
Dubbing. BrantB.
Voice actor.
Make a wish
Make a wish. Zhang Yunmeng.
Lin Che, Jiang Qiu.
Wen Youcai, Lu Siheng.
Lin Rou is a group of people.
Lin Rou Yi.
Lucky Du, Chen Yifan.
Qian Lai Fu and Zhang Jiahui.
The wind is clear.
Zhao Mingzhu, Dong Yue,
[Yang Xiaoran]
Ziye Yi, Dong Can.
Ziye Yi Dong Can.
Ah, Green, Li Xuejiao.
Other dubbers
Wang Jiaying, Ma Jialin, Yang Xi, Yan Hui. Yuze.
Sun Zhihao, Li Qiaoyun, Zhang Qian Zheng, Weng Tangtang. Guo Xinlei.
Theme Song: "What I Want".
Theme song: "What I Want".
Singer: Wanxin, Yi Lingli
Song: Zhu Langyu.
Lyrics: Wang Yijie
Arrangement: Polaris Zhang Xuchen
Guitar: Zhang Xiaoyue.
Mix/mother belt: Tujy.
[Mix/Mother belt: Tujy]
Recorder: Woo Jeong-hee
[Studio: ASE stadio]
Thank you.
Lemon lemon tea.
A product company.
Hu Happy Film Co., Ltd.
Zhejiang, Zheng Zheng, Film and Culture Co., Ltd.
Nanjing Xigou Culture Co., Ltd.
Co-produced products.
Beijing Nolan Film Culture Co., Ltd.
BEIJINGNULANNNING SHUNHUAYOUXIANGSI
Beijing Nolan Film Co., Ltd.
Beijing Nolan Film.
Ace.
Asia Starry Sky Entertainment.
CANDYISTAGE.
Qingdao Drama Candy Culture Co., Ltd.
Production company.
Zhejiang, Zheng Zheng, Film and Culture Co., Ltd.
Xiangshan He Shui Film Co., Ltd.
Thank you very much.
Hengdian Film Center.
Hengdian World. Studios.
Hengdian Film and TV City.