Xiangshan He Shun Film Co., Ltd. Ltd. Ltd. Ltd.
I hope Zhao Bao'er
is not as bad as the rumor.
This maid...
No, Sister.
We can't touch the dowry.
According to our family motto,
rob the rich and help the poor.
They only want to be rich and merciless.
You can't do that. You can't do that.
It's not a big deal. It's not a big deal.
The Zhao family seized it.
by the Zhao family.
Besides,
Zhao Bao'er was almost forced to die for love.
The Zhao family deserved it.
Can this birthmark work?
It's fine.
The Lin family has never seen what Zhao Bao'er looks like anyway.
Once we enter the Lin Mansion,
we'll be free.
Sister, I trust you.
Jo Bo-ah is saved.
and the refugees.
We can kill two birds with one stone this time.
Why is there an orange on the ground?
Yes.
Dear.
Cui has been an ordinary girl since she was young.
She personally cares about it.
Please don't expose her and break her heart.
Don't worry.
A girl should respect her heart.
Let me see what is the treasure in the Zhao family.
What is it?
Nothing.
Jo Bo-ah
is not that ugly.
Look at his figure.
Look at this. Look at this.
Yes.
Bring me what you dropped.
Do you really want to read this wooden book?
Let's see what the Zhao family is hiding.
to hide.
I'm doing this for your own good.
If I do,
you might be different.
It turns out that the Zhao family's dowry
is used to teach their daughter and son-in-law.
Here.
I didn't expect a woman like you
to see such a dirty thing.
Sister.
After he goes into the bridal chamber alone,
you'll create chaos.
I'll take the chance
take this pill.
they will think
really killed herself.
That way, Zhao Bao'er can be fulfilled.
Filial piety and filial piety.
We won't hurt the Zhao family in the Western State.
Understood.
I always advise
women shouldn't be too indulgent.
But I think
everyone has a secret affair.
It was my fault.
You're right. You're right.
I don't have that kind of desire.
I can't explain.
I'll hang up now.
But there's one thing
I don't understand.
What is it?
Although I'm called Master Tsu
you can't be like this
My wife asked me to go back and look at the bronze mirror.
I did.
From any angle,
it's still perfect.
You're still a gentleman.
You...
You drugged me.
Mother.
What are you doing?
Look, look, look, look.
I forgot.
to pick up my sister.
Don't worry about your sister.
She is known as
known as the God of Bandits.
She'll be back soon.
Sleep.
Okay.
I lost my virginity.
Why don't I feel anything?
Monster!
You pervert!
Be careful. Be careful.
Vicious.
So evil.
Sign the card before you die.
Okay.
I made my wish.
Today, I will enforce justice on behalf of heaven.
and see who will die today.
Young Madam.
You're awake. What are you doing?
Your son...
Where is my husband?
Young Master is waiting for Young Madam in the study.
to serve tea to His Highness and Her Highness.
Okay.
Lend it to me.
Young Madam, where are you going with the feather duster?
Lecher, kill me!
How dare you!
Bastard!
Madam, stop it.
I didn't expect
you know kung fu.
None of your business.
Lecher.
First of all,
Who is a lecher?
Of course it's you.
Why did you make me unconscious?
I'm afraid you'll harass me.
What did you say?
Roada Xu who made a wish.
Wen Youcai, Han Haotian.
Lin Rou, Chen Chuqi.
Lin Feng, Jin Wangwang.
Lin Yan and Yang Jun.
Lucky Du, Tan Yinmin.
Qian Youfu Yi, Guo Chang.
Zhao Mingzhu, Liu Lingling.
Lin Dao Cheng, Feng Wusheng.
Lin Dao becomes one. Feng Wusheng.
Ye Zi, Yi, Yi, Yi.
A Lian, Xu Shiyao.
The Crown Princess, Xiong Jiayi.
One bear plus one.
Meng Heng Yi, Bai Haoyan.
I'm an honest person.
Special appointment.
Li Yixuan, guard of the granary.
Baldy painter, Yang Xingliang.
Guard, Wang Shuixin.
One, two, three. One, two, three.
A maid, Xu Huiting.
Magistrate Chen Tianci
You're here. You're here.
MC Chen Fukuk
Liao Haipeng.
Girl, one for Wai.
Girl and Wai-wai
Guard 1 Zhu Haitao
Jing and Fang Xin.
One for maid, one for Liu Sisi.
One for maid, one for Liu Sisi
Girl, two, one. Xia Ying.
A maid, two, one, Xia Ying.
Maid, 31, Bai Bingqi.
maid 41, Dong Jun Yi.
Five maids for Tianyi.
Five for maids, one for Fu Yi.
A little wish for one, Yue Ying.
Make a wish, foster mother, sing with bamboo.
The boy made a wish, Yang Bao'er.
The procuress, Li Hong,
Liu Bu, Wang Rumeng
A painting of Manru
A mural of Manru
The greasy male lead, Yuan Hong
A greasy man. Yuan Hong.
Ms. Zhao has a sea breeze.
The heroine of yarn is Zhou Xian Yue.
The heroine of yarn, Zhou Xian Yue.
The first eunuch, Yuan Ying,
First Eunuch, Yuan Ying.
A maid, Lü Xinyang.
A servant, A, 1, Yang Doudou.
My servant is Jia Yi, Yang Doudou.
My servant, Yi Yi, He Gui.
The servant, Yi Yi, He Gui.
Ye's Yi Ji Ling.
Lin Che, Guo Wupeng.
Lin Che and Guo Wupeng.
The Fifth Prince, Wang Yongdi.
Fifth Prince, Wang Yongdi.
One of the refugees, Xu Weiqiang.
Trainee 1 Deng Dongmen
Refugee A 1 Deng Dongmen
The refugee is Yi Zhou Zhou.
The refugee, Yi, Zhou Zhou.
The vendor, Jia Yi, Yan Qinghui.
The vendor, Yi Yi, Zeng Bin Bin.
Passenger A, Yang Jinhai.
Passenger A 1 Yang Jinhai
Doctor, Liu Jianming.
"Lin Zhen, Liang, Liang, Liang, Liang."
Lin Yan, Ji Chenxuan.
A maid named Jia Yi, Jin Meng Meng.
Jia Yi, Jin Meng Meng.
The maid, Yi Yi, Li Wenwen.
Extra.
He Wei, Wu Mingfeng, Gao Jian, Li Zu Jui Li Mingyu, Chen Lei, Wang Jianmin, He Jianjun, Guo Xiaomin, Wu Yandong, Zhao Kaichao,
Zhu Meng, Duan Bofeng, Huang Yi, Zhou Bin Bin. Chen Yue, Lu Shun Hui, Shen Xianshu, Chen Fu Guo Zhu Haitao, Zhang Jiahui, Du Yan,
Zhu Meng, Duan Bofeng, Huang Yi, Zhou Bin Bin. Chen Yue, Lu Shun Hui, Shen Xianshu, Chen Fuguo, Zhu Haitao, Zhang Jiahui, Du Yan,
Tian Weitao, Wang Xiang, Yan Ziyan, Yu Huadong. Xi Hanfeng, Zhu Jianxing, Li Jianjun, Yang Yun, Niu Ruijun, Gao Yi, Party Jie.
Tian Weitao, Wang Xiang, Yan Ziyan, Yu Huadong. Xi Hanfeng Zhu Jixing Li Jianjun Yang Yun Niu Ruijun, Gao Yi, Party Jie.
Jin Yi Chun, Tang Bo, Zhu Kun, Liu Tao, Bai Tao, Zhu Zhong Yin, Chen Mei Bing, Zhang Xue, Liu Fu Qiong, Chen Wei.
In the forest, Ruoying Zhang, Huang Wenting, Liu Dongsheng Wang Yilin, Zhang Yijia, Zhang Zhitao, Jin Xuyang Lulu Zhang, Huang Bo, Wang Wei
Pang Shion, Hu Zhenchuan, Song Jiada, Zhang Xiaojia Hao Wei Lin, Nong Zhangbo, Chen Feijun, Zhang Jiayu. Liu Xiaolong, Li Hongxia
Pang Shion, Hu Zhenchuan, Song Jiada, Zhang Xiaojia Hao Weilin, Nong Chiu Bai, Chen Feijun, Zhang Jiayu Liu Xiaolong, Li Hongxia
Sun Jiao Li, Feng Yan Hang, Yan Yan, Cheng Qian. Chen Fei, Yao Qingteng, Siu Rufeng, Wei Tie Jian Chen Fu Guo Lu Shun Hui Feng Shihu
Sun Jiao Li, Feng Yan Hang, Yan Yan, Cheng Qian Chen Fei, Yao Qingteng, Siu Rufeng, Wei Tie Jian Chen Fu Guo Lu Shun Hui Feng Shihu
Wang Meng, Liu Qiuhong, Chen Hongwei, Liu Miao Miao Marshal Tu, Han Bin, Yang Yinlong, Xu Xueqing Yang Yanhong, Zhang Jie, Geng Yueqiao
Zhang Xue, Wang Jinzhi, Shi Jingcheng, Yao Jinkang Lang Junsheng, Han Yongjie, Pu Zisong, Zhou Jiang Zhou Zhou, Marshal Liang, Zhu Yan
Ma Zihang, Zhao Hang, Wang Xiangzong, Gui Yang Ren Yuan, Luo Wei, Zhong Yong, Li Bohui, Ding Yun. Deng Song, Zhang Weihui, Wang Xiyou
Four, Wu Ke, Zhang Qian, Yang Zhenghun. Li Wenming, Guan Xiaolong, Gao Ziqiang, Lin Jiangjiang Luo Sheng Sheng, Lin Gui Fang, Tang Bo, Liang Jie
Zhou Bin, Ren Kexin, Li Jianjun, Wu Yandong. Zhu Haitao, Xu Yun, Xie Gui Hua, Huang Yi. Lu Ruiqing, Jin Meng Meng, Li Wenwen.
Staff.
Director team.
Director, Jacky Zhang.
Director Li Haofei
Director Gu Changfu
Director Gu Changfu.
Record: Li Zhuo.
Producer Hu Chuxuan
Writer/Chief Planning Hsu Hui-ting
Production team.
Chief Producer Zhao Wenxue Zheng Huixi
Producer Zhang Jianyong Xiao Tianren
Kevin Chow, Ding.
One Ding.
Producer assistant Ye, Li Junhan
Producer Director Zhou Weibin
Outdoor producer Liu Deyeong
Life Producer, Commander Shang, Susu.
Live Producer Zhao Anfeng
Executive Producer Li Longchuang Xu Jinglin
Executive Producer Li Longchuang Xu Shanlin
The venue team.
Mr. Lee Jun-han.
[Team Manager Lee Jun-han]
Come on. Come on.
Team members.
Bao Cai, Geer, Wei Tie Jian, Zhang Yikang. Geng Junhai.
Wang Chengyou. Yang Haoran. Li Fei.
Wang Chengyu, Yang Haoran, Rex, Li Fei.
Photography team.
Photographer Li Kwan Qun
Photographer Li guan Qun
Photographer, Chen Tie.
Photographer Chen Tie
Focus on Chen Quan, Luo Peiqiang
Photographer assistant Xiao Ran Chia Le
Lighting team.
Lighting guide, Xu Xiaobiao.
Lighting Daisuke, Li Yunlong.
Lighting assistant, Li Yunlong.
Lighting assistant.
Hou Yaifeng, Xu Xiaomang, Li Lekai, Shi Soldier
lantern, Solo.
The lighter, Solo.
The styling team.
styling instructor, Lin Jia Jin.
styling instructor, Lin Jiajin.
Makeup instructor, Liu Qian Qian.
Makeup instructor Liu Qian
Makeup team leader Duan Zhengnan
Makeup artist Mark
Lim Ying, the makeup team leader.
Makeup on site.
Cao Ruipion, Shi Meizhen, nice to meet you.
Cao Ruipion, Shi Meizhen, Gao Yan is good.
Costume team leader, Han Zhan.
Costume main focus, Li Ruowen Yan.
Costume assistant Lai Biyun.
Costume assistant, Lai Biyun.
Costume assistant Zhang Ya Ning.
Art team.
art instructor, Li Shuai.
Deputy art Jingjing
Props team
The prop team.
Han Jin, the prop team leader.
A prop for the play, Wang Ming.
Scene. Fan Yongle. Hu Xiang.
The props at the scene, Fan Yongle, Hu Xiang.
Development team, Head of Development, Han Wei.
Agent.
Wei Zhihua, Sun Fu, Li Shaoqiang, Zhou Wanyu.
Wei Zhihua, Sun Fu, Li Shaoqiang, Zhou Wanyu
Zhou Bing, Gao Xiangfei, Yang Lin Xi.
The recording team.
The recording team
Recorder Lee Xiaohu
The recording assistant
Car team.
Car Unit.
Over here! Over here! Over here!
Agent.
Zhao Cheng, Cui Ligang, Lu Jun, Wei Min,
Zhao Cheng, Cui Ligang, Lu Jun, Wei Min.
Zhang Haiqiang, Ding Mingyang, Qiao Lufeng, Luo Guoguo.
Yu Zhenping, Liu Xiaohu, Li Longping, Zhang Ai Zhi,
Yuan Xiao Jun, Tian Dasheng, Shen Baohman
Yuan Xiao Jun, Tian Dasheng, Shen Boman.
The audition team.
audition studio.
The audition studio.
Team leader, Ding.
Acting director, Ma Xiaohua.
Actor assistant director, Jinqian.
Actor assistant director, Jinchang.
Action team, action instructor, Honghu.
Liu Ning, PR Director.
PR team members, Ren Jia Qi, Zhang Xuan.
PR team members, Kiki Ren, Zhang Xuan.
Film photo group, drama photographer, Xinxin Wu.
Side photographer, Wu Xinxin, Li Songyuan.
Finance Unit.
Yu Fang.
Product.
Product?
Li Haofei, you're right. You're right. [The show is about to start.] [It's a symbol.]
A co-producer.
Qin Yinxuan, Sun Lei, Wang Qi Yun, Huang Yuan Lin Jiajin, Xiao Shengnan, Chen Huixiao,
Qin Yinxuan, Sun Lei, Wang Qi Yun, Huang Yuan Lin Jia Jin, Xiao Sheng Lan, Chen Huixiao,
The post-production system.
Later production.
Middle Shadow Circuit.
Beijing Media Co., Ltd.
Re-production Producer Cangu Xinhao
Late-production Producer Cangu Xinhao
Late-production, Wang Rui.
Editing advisor Cangu Xinhao
Color, Li Yunkai, me.
The color, Li Yunkai, me.
Packaging, Dong Zi.
Procedure: Wang Han, Song Jian.
DI, Xiaoqi.
DI.
The dialogue subtitles, Ah Tie.
Guang.
Quality check Good
CG production.
Director Zhang Yiqi
Chen Jian Ping Li Wenhao.
Chen Jian Ping Li Wenhao
Voice production.
Kuck Time (Beijing) Cultural Media Co. Ltd.
Voice Director, Zhang Yuhong.
Voice Director Zhang Yuhong
Voice coordination Xiaoyi
Voice count Xiaoyi
Recorder Liu Jinming.
Mr. Bai, Zheng Xinyuan.
Audio design, Joo Hyun.
Foley, Shi Yaqing.
Music Editor Joo Hyun
Music editor, Joo Hyun.
Voice director Ma Cheng Li Xuejiao
Babymonster Li.
Dubbing. BrantB.
Dubbing actor.
A dubber?
Make a wish
Lin Che, one for Jiang Qiu.
Wen Youcai Yi, Lu Siheng.
Lin Rou Yi, Bu Bu Qu.
Lucky Du, Chen Yifan.
Qian Lai Fu and Zhang Jiahui.
Lin, the wind is clear.
Zhao Mingzhu, Dong Yue,
[Lin Dao, Yi, Yang Xiaoran.]
Lin Dao becomes one, Yang Xiaoran.
Ziye Yi, Dong Can.
Ziye Yi Dong Can.
Li Xuejiao.
The other dubbers
Other dubbers?
Wang Jiaying, Ma Jialin, Yang Xi, Yan Hui. Yuze.
Theme Song: "What I Want".
Theme song: "What I Want".
Singer: Wanxin, Yi Lingli
Song: Zhu Dangyu
Lyrics: Wang Yijie.
Lyrics: Wang Yijie
Arrangement: Polaris Zhang Xuchen
Guitar: Zhang Xiaoyue.
Mix/mother belt: Tujy.
[Mix/Mother belt: Tujy]
Recorder: Woo Jung-hee.
[Recording Studio: ASESTUDIO]
Thank you.
Lemon lemon tea.
A product company.
Hu Happy Film Co., Ltd.
Zhejiang, Zheng Zheng, Film and Culture Co., Ltd.
Nanjing Xigou Culture Co., Ltd.
Joint production.
BEJINGNULANNNING SHUNHUAYOUXIANGSI
Beijing Noram Film Culture Co., Ltd.
BEIJINGNULANNING SHUNHUAYOUXIANGSI
Ace.
Asia Starry Sky Entertainment.
CANDYISTAGE.
Qingdao Drama Candy Culture Co., Ltd.
Production company.
Zhejiang, Zheng Zheng, Film and Culture Co., Ltd.
Xiangshan He Shui Film Co., Ltd.
Hengdian Film City.
Hengdian World. Studios.
Hengdian Film and TV City.