[BLEND FEELINGS: Episode 4]
This is what my boyfriend gave me
on Valentine's Day.
Is it beautiful?
Excuse me.
This is my guest.
Miss Jian, hello.
I'm Gao Yi.
Hello.
There's something
I may not have made clear to you.
The position you're hired for
is not a perfumer.
You'll work as my assistant.
You?
I'll be the special assistant's assistant?
[President's Office]
This is your workstation.
This looks like it was set up temporarily.
Mr. Gao, I'm here to apply for
the perfumer position.
Don't think that it's beneath you
to be the special assistant's assistant.
You should know that
this position is highly sought after
by many people.
Those who can handle it will become
Chairman Gu's trusted subordinates.
Trusted subordinates?
Yes.
So you're very important. Understand?
These are Chairman Gu's preferences
and restrictions.
Please read them carefully.
Don't be late.
Don't use strong perfumes.
No flattery or brown-nosing.
Don't eat durians in the office.
This boss has such strange requirements.
The chairman can't eat spicy food.
Even the smell of chilies in the air
is not allowed.
Hello, Chairman Gu.
I've already infiltrated into
Gu Jingshi's inner circle.
Next, I'm going to get closer to him.
How do you think
I can make a good impression on him?
Finally, you're showing some sense.
It's right for you to ask me.
Men all like fair-skinned beautiful women
with long legs.
Men are so shallow.
However,
what kind of man is Gu Jingshi?
He has seen all kinds of beautiful women.
Look.
Gu Jingshi, the President of Yaoge Group,
donated one million yuan
to the Stray Animal Rescue Center.
Please!
Just cooperate with me.
Once I succeed,
I'll reward you
with some small dried fish. Okay?
Meow.
What are you doing?
Chairman Gu.
Here's the thing, Chairman Gu.
Today, I saw a stray kitten
standing alone in a busy street,
looking extremely helpless.
I thought it must be very scared.
It had no home,
and no one looked after it.
So I took the liberty
of bringing it back here.
Mimi, don't be afraid.
I'll be your family from now on.
Chairman Gu, look.
Look. Isn't it very cute?
Wow! It actually meowed!
It is said
that cats are the most spiritual animals.
Chairman Gu, your warmth and kindness
must have touched it.
Why isn't he showing any reaction at all?
Maybe I didn't flatter him enough.
Actually, when I was a kid,
I had a cow cat‌ named Mimi.
We were best friends,
eating and sleeping together.
But one day,
Mimi suddenly disappeared.
When I found it,
it had been hit by a car and died.
So when I saw this cat,
it was like seeing my childhood cat,
Mimi, again.
And I just wanted to bring it back here
to give it a warm home.
Your childhood cat, Mimi?
You two ate and slept together?
But you're allergic to cat hair.
Jian Xiangxiang.
Your lying skills
are just so awful.
Life is hard,
and it all depends on your acting skills.
Remember to take some anti-allergy drugs
before you lie.
Actually,
this calico cat‌ was picked up by the boss
on the street last year.
The boss had no time to keep it,
so he gave it to Mr. Liu,
the building manager,
with a large sum of money for its care.
If I were her,
I'd be too embarrassed to stay there.
Chairman Gu, you know this cat, huh?
Not only do I know it.
but I'm also quite familiar with it.
This cat belongs to Mr. Liu,
the building manager.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
I'll take it to Mr. Liu right away.
He must be extremely worried.
This is bad for me.
I must have made a terrible impression
on him.
I hope that he won't fire me.
I didn't perform well.
Chairman Gu.
Gao Yi has something urgent to do.
Call the driver and ask him to pick me up.
Okay.
Mr. Gao isn't here.
Isn't this a good chance
for me to distinguish myself?
The driver didn't answer the phone.
Try again.
Okay.
Why did he suddenly turn off his phone?
Chairman Gu.
How about I drive you to your destination?
I have a driver's license, too.
It's true.
And my driving skills are very good.
Go get the spare key
from the reception desk.
Okay.
Here's my chance.
[Xiangxiang]
Hello, the number you've dialed is busy.
Please try again...
Since she has already found out about it,
why are you still trying to contact her?
I haven't obtained
the Eight Methods of Fragrance yet.
If I break up with her now,
won't all my previous efforts be wasted?
Are you reluctant to give up
the Eight Methods of Fragrance,
or are you reluctant to give her up?
What do you mean?
Jiacheng, I...
Fine.
If you can't make the decision,
I'll make it for you.
Go home.
No way.
I need to seize this great opportunity.
Chairman Gu, I'm feeling a bit dizzy.
I might need to drink some sugar water.
I'll leave when I feel better.
Leave.
Close the door on your way out.
I'll close the door on my way out
and leave at once.
Well, Chairman Gu, I'm leaving.
You really don't know
how to treat a lady properly.
And I even took you back home.
Do you really think
you're a handsome cool man?
I don't believe that
I can't win you over.
Who are you?
Don't come any closer!