(Byeon Woo Seok)
(CEO)
(10 missed calls from CEO)
(Kim Hye Yoon)
(Lovely Runner)
Sol!
Move over, you idiot!
Get lost!
I think he fainted.
Sun Jae!
Sun Jae.
Please come to your senses.
- Check on him. - Okay.
Kim Young Soo, you're arrested for attempted serial kidnapping.
Kim Young Soo!
Sun Jae.
Don't you think you should wake up?
Wake up.
I like you.
I thought I would regret it...
if I left again without telling you how I felt.
I like you, Sun Jae.
Sol.
Snow will fall across the capital area until tomorrow morning.
Please drive in the snow safely.
This is the next breaking news.
The suspect in the Gangnam Serial Kidnapping Attempt case...
has just died while trying to escape during the apprehension.
The suspect had a previous conviction...
for attempted murder...
at Juyang Reservoir in 2008 and served 6 years...
- in prison. - Juyang Reservoir?
Being chased by the police in the heart of Seoul,
- Is he perhaps... - he rushed onto the road...
and was hit and killed on the spot by an oncoming dump truck.
- Kim Young Soo is dead? - The police went to...
- the taxi company he worked for. - Sun Jae.
- What about Sun Jae? - He ran away after seeing them.
And the police chased him after that.
(Sun Jae is hit by a car! The road is closed because of the accident.)
A car accident?
(Oh, my gosh, what's going on?)
(My poor Sun Jae)
- Gosh, Sun Jae is hit by a car. - Was he really hit by a car?
- This is horrible. - I...
I went to the Wooshin University Hospital emergency room...
and saw Ryu Sun Jae being brought in.
"Wooshin University Hospital?"
Let me get out here.
Sun Jae!
(Wooshin University Hospital)
I'm sorry.
He's not hurt.
What a relief.
Why were you running like that?
Sun Jae, now,
it seems everything is over.
Did you perhaps come to see me,
thinking that I was involved in a car accident?
No, I was just passing by.
If you didn't,
why are you crying?
I wasn't crying.
I'll get going.
Did you cry like that every day...
when you were alone?
Missing the person...
who forgot everything about you?
I was right.
I told you it'd be a sad ending.
Do you still not want to change the ending?
- What are you talking about? - But what do we do?
I think it has changed already.
Sol.
I remember everything.
What?
It's impossible. How?
Why did you do that?
How could you erase yourself from my memory?
How could you let me live without you?
Did you think it would be possible?
Sun Jae.
Don't cry. Okay?
I'm sorry I'm late.
I'm sorry...
I forgot.
(The final episode)
Until when are you going to do this?
Just a little more.
- Do you want to stay up all night? - Yes.
I can stay up all night long.
You're not a baby. Don't act like one.
I don't want to spend a single moment without you from now on...
because it was so wasteful to live forgetting you.
Let's do it then.
Let's stay together even in our dreams.
I will not forget...
anything about you from now on.
Even if you try to erase my memories again,
I'll remember again like that no matter what it takes.
I'll never do that again.
When I think about it,
it seems like I never forgot you.
I never forgot you.
Sun Jae, the shooting is beginning soon.
Are you crying?
We're not filming any crying scenes today.
Sun Jae!
You cried?
It means my heart remembered you...
even if my brain forgot you.
This is what my grandmother said.
"Memories don't disappear."
"They're smeared into your soul."
Is that true?
It came back to its place now.
By the way,
I guess you've been putting necklaces...
on many women for 15 years.
You were fumbling last time,
but you can do it at once now.
I told you. I'm an expert at romance dramas.
I did it many times for dramas.
I'm dumb if I still can't put a necklace on you properly.
It's okay.
You forgot me for so many years.
I understand if you met someone else.
What are you doing? You get jealous too?
I said I wasn't.
You had so many dating rumors.
After doing it several times, you become good at...
You're doing this because you have nothing to say.
You said men and women...
can't be friends.
Go on.
I don't know. I forgot.
I love you.
I love you, Sun Jae.
(Wonbook, the safest city, Wonbook Police, the respected force)
Why the long face?
What are you doing in our station?
I came to see you, punk.
The case you're in charge of is the talk of the town.
Dozens of murder weapons were found in the trunk of his cab.
Murder was his intention.
I knew it.
When I arrested and sent him to the court in 2008,
I said he would recommit a crime when he was released...
so many times.
You can't reform a jerk like him.
He's evil.
Don't call him evil and try to make it seem like he's something special.
He's a social misfit and a loser. Not a monster to be afraid of.
You experience all sorts of things when you work...
as a detective for a long time.
I'm saying this just in case.
It's not your fault.
It was his fate to die.
Someone who was destined to die might be alive thanks to his death.
That would be the case, right?
(Sweet Coffee)
Darn it.
(One month later)
(She lost something precious...)
(in return for changing a lot of things.)
When are you finished?
I don't know.
I don't think I'll be able to finish it today.
What?
(My Destiny)
Does it mean we can't meet today either?
Gosh.
(Does it mean we can't meet today either?)
I should send it by tomorrow. I'm busy.
I'll contact you when I'm done.
See you tomorrow.
I miss you too, Sun Jae,
but I have no choice.
He won't be upset, right?
- Isn't he Sun Jae? - Sun Jae?
- It's Sun Jae. - Hey, it's Sun Jae.
- Oh, my gosh. - It's really him.
- It's Sun Jae. - He's here.
He winked at me.
He has a small face.
I came because I wanted to see you.
He must be crazy.
I'd like to order.
I didn't order this.
- Sun Jae... - Sorry?
I told him not to make it obvious.
Paid for this for everyone.
Pardon?
Sun Jae is so sweet to his fans.
Take a picture of this for proof.
Are you really going to do this?
I thought you might need some sugar.
Eat while you're working.
Do you think I can work?
Do you want to play with me instead of working then?
He's killing me.
How can I work?
- Sun Jae. - Thank you.
- Me too. - Sun Jae, please.
- I love you. - It was so delicious.
I love you.
(Sweet Coffee)
Why did you come all the way here?
You won't meet me because you're busy.
So I had to come and see you.
What if someone recognizes you?
I covered my face completely. Who will recognize me?
Be quiet. Go back to your work.
I'll be reading a book quietly.
You said you would be quiet.
By the way, doing this feels like...
when we were in college.
What?
That's true, though.
Having a secret relationship isn't so bad, is it?
Do you think this is a set?
If you want to have a secret relationship,
would you please go outside?
Mr. Ryu Sun Jae.
He's not Ryu Sun Jae.
He's my older brother.
I'm Im Sol, and he's Im Geum.
Many people say my brother and Ryu Sun Jae look alike.
Brother, let's go.
Put the book back, brother.
Here. Let me carry it for you.
Where should I work now?
I can't work because of my cute nephew and niece.
Take your time when you write it.
I'm going to say I want to take a break this year...
and film the movie next year.
That's impossible.
I promised to submit the script by tomorrow.
Someone might see you again. You should go right now.
Do you want to go to a quiet place...
where you can focus with your brother then?
What?
Where?
What? The place where I can focus on my work...
is your house?
Of course. There's no place that is quieter than my house.
I knew it.
He wants to stick with me whenever he can.
Aren't you coming?
Why is he in a rush?
He's ridiculous.
Attention!
Actor Im Geum's debut drama...
is starting soon!
Are you overreacting again...
about being an extra?
I know.
His senior said he would cast him in a legal drama, but it's canceled.
- Is it? - This time,
there's nothing to be ashamed of. I had an audition and was cast.
I played the role of the lead's husband,
the son of a rich family.
Oh, my. Are you serious?
You're the husband of the lead of the daily drama?
My honey, how come you played such a big role?
All right. Check it with your eyes.
- It's starting. - Let's watch.
("While My Husband Is Sleeping")
- It's him. - What?
It's him.
That guy over there? The one who is lying on the bed?
You're right. He's my son.
You're right.
This is wonderful, honey.
It was worth having the dream of becoming an actor for over a decade.
I told you.
I said I would make it one day.
I know. This is why you should live long.
I can't believe I'm watching my son starring in a drama.
Be quiet. Let me watch the show.
("While My Husband Is Sleeping")
Can we do this?
Don't worry.
My husband will be sleeping for the rest of his life.
How dare you meet someone else...
when my son is alive?
You should admit it.
Look. My husband, your son,
is no better than a dead person.
You evil witch!
She's horrible.
- What? - Gosh.
That's it?
You didn't wake up even once.
Being wrapped up in bandages like that,
I can't tell if it's you or someone else.
- When are you taking them off? - I'm not.
I'll be lying like that until I die in the last episode.
Look at the title. "While My Husband Is Sleeping."
The drama ends when the husband wakes up.
- What? - Why?
Why?
Right.
It's your very first drama in your life.
That's quite amazing.
Right?
This is the beginning. If he works hard,
- he'll have another opportunity. - Yes.
But honey, how could you make it look so real...
when you were lying like a corpse?
I was acting like I was in a deep sleep...
until I was splashed with water.
Then I tried to make it look like I was in REM sleep.
Did you notice the subtle change?
Of course, I did.
I saw your eyelids twitching...
- slightly. - That's what I'm saying.
You looked amazing on TV.
Your nose looked good even when you were wrapped in bandages.
Really?
No wonder why the director said...
he liked my look the most.
Really?
Gosh, you guys are a perfect match.
What's going on?
I thought he might bother me so much as he took me home.
Why is he doing nothing?
I knew it.
Should I play with him even for a moment?
Eat while you're working. I won't bother you.
Hurry up and go back to your work.
What?
He really wants me to work.
(This is the first draft of "The Time of Walking Memories.")
What? Where did he go?
Oh, my gosh, I'm done!
Yes! It's finally over!
What's going on?
Sun Jae.
Why? Are you finished?
What?
- Yes. - See?
You could finish it today because you were focused.
You're right. I thought I had to stay up all night.
I knew it.
It's finally happening.
I guess you liked the bread.
Let's go. I'll drop you off.
"Let's go?"
Already?
Why does he act like that suddenly after clinging to me all day?
Did you get all your stuff?
Let's go. It's late.
"It's late," my foot. It's only 11pm.
Does he think we're 19-year-olds?
Gosh. My goodness.
Everything fell out.
Right. My car key.
Put back your stuff. I'll be back.
He intends to drop me off even when the world ends.
I'm done with my work, though.
I can stay longer.
How about leaving tomorrow after sleeping here tonight?
- What? - Sleep here tonight...
and leave tomorrow.
I knew it.
Okay. If you insist.
I'll spend the night here.
Hey. What do you mean...
you'll come here tomorrow after getting some sleep?
Everyone's here.
Come at once.
Well... I...
There was a misunderstanding.
I'll just grab a cab.
Where are you going?
I said you'd spend the night here.
Well... I thought...
you were talking to me.
If I was talking to you,
were you going to stay here tonight?
What I meant by that was...
Right.
Since we couldn't go on a date because I've been busy,
we could have something delicious, watch a movie,
and have some fun.
And then?
After that, we can...
Right. Yes.
We can catch up on the variety shows we missed.
We can talk a little too.
And then?
And then it must be late.
Instead of going home that late,
I'd get a good night's sleep here. That was what I meant.
So, that means...
you'll sleep here tonight.
What I said "sleep," it means...
Okay.
Do everything you want to do.
Eat something delicious, watch the movie,
catch up on the variety shows, and what was it?
- Talk? - Yes. We talk.
Sure. Let's do them all.
- But... - What?
First things first.
Sun Jae.
I love you too.
Are you up?
No, I'm still sleeping.
Come on. You're already up.
You said you'd go tomorrow. Go back to sleep.
Tomorrow has come already.
Not before we open our eyes.
I know you're using a shallow trick...
to stay like this for longer.
Stop it. I'm up.
I surrender. It tickles.
I surrender.
Why are you staring at me like that?
Do I have something in my eyes?
Yes.
What?
I was kidding.
You're unbelievable.
I stared at you because you were pretty.
It doesn't feel real.
Can it be...
a dream?
I feel the same.
Sometimes, it scares me.
That...
you'll leave for another timeline again.
I'll...
forget about you again.
That won't happen again.
Are you sure?
I'm sure.
I can't go back even if I wanted to.
I don't have the watch anymore.
That's right.
By the way, where's that electronic watch?
I don't know.
I think I lost it a long time ago. I don't know where it is.
It's abandoned somewhere,
or someone must have picked it up.
Gosh. It's a shame when I think I bought it for 3,000 dollars.
I should have picked it up.
You don't need it anymore anyway.
We'll be glued together like this.
- I'll be glued to you all right. - Yes.
But don't we really have to get up now?
No. Just five more minutes.
No. Ten more minutes.
No. Thirty more minutes.
Mom.
Why are you standing over there? Let's go.
Okay.
Wait for me, sister.
I'm going to take a shower. Get out.
Okay.
Should we shower together?
Get out!
- Get out. - I get scared when I'm alone.
- Okay? - Okay.
Sun Jae, I'll get going.
Without having breakfast?
Ms. Lee wants to see me in the morning,
so I have to go now. I'm sorry. Bye.
Hold on.
- Here. Eat this on your way. - Okay.
I said I can drop you off.
The neighbors will find out again if we go out together.
- Bye. - Wait.
What is it?
You're not going to keep it on, are you?
You're right.
I'm really going this time.
Wait.
What?
Didn't you forget something?
You good?
By the way,
we look like newlyweds, don't we?
I'll get going.
Bye.
"Newlyweds?"
What? I can't tell how she looks.
"A date in the library?"
She must be a right-minded, smart woman.
If he took her home,
Sun Jae must be madly in love with her.
I don't know who she is,
but her beauty pierces through the screen...
though she was blurred out.
I can see why Sun Jae is crazy about her.
I was told he never even fell for the beautiful women of the century.
I can tell she's not pretty just by looking at her silhouette.
Goodness. He has a bad taste in women.
Did he go crazy over an odd woman?
Sun Jae, until when do we have to do this?
My fingers are falling asleep.
It's because nothing fits perfectly with my Sol's image.
What on earth is your Sol's image?
Look.
You might be blinded by her glow.
Watch your eyes.
Here we go.
What? Hey.
Your girlfriend looks familiar to me.
It feels like I saw her before.
How could you meet someone as shiny as her?
Let me see.
How dare you? Don't touch her.
This one is nice.
- I'll get this one. - Okay.
Please wait a second.
But Sun Jae.
About the gift for your girlfriend,
I don't care what you buy for her.
The rumor about you seeing someone was published today.
So, you can't be doing this right now.
Do you want them to start a rumor that you're about to get married?
- What if it won't be a rumor? - Right.
What?
What do you mean?
Are you really planning to announce that you're going to get married?
Does Mr. Kim know about this?
He'll know about it...
- when you tell him. - Right.
Are you serious?
Are you really going to get married?
I don't want to stay away from Sol even for a moment.
That's what you think.
Dating is one thing, but marriage is another thing.
I know that. I'm not an idiot.
That's why I'm going to propose to her properly.
Do you think everything will go well once you proposed?
Did you get the families' approval?
No.
For goodness' sake.
Hey.
How are you going to live without me?
Have you gotten married before?
You haven't even done it yourself.
- Yes, Sol. - Where are you?
Me? I'm here for the...
Recording! At the recording studio.
In Hyuk's studio.
I'm here to help with In Hyuk's recording.
Can you hear it?
I'm running to you
- You are... - I need to see you right now.
(Ryu Sun Jae on a Library-Home Date with a Mysterious Woman)
What are we going to do?
Gosh. They should have touched up the photo more nicely.
They just blurred everything out.
- Does the touch-up matter now? - No one will know it's you.
They covered your pretty face.
That's not important right now.
Don't worry. I'll take care of everything.
How are you going to take care of it?
- Of course, I'll... - Do you know...
what's the most important part of proposing?
Keeping the secret.
Once she finds out you are about to propose,
the moment is ruined.
So, before you propose to her,
keep your mouth tightly shut even though you don't want to.
Keep this in mind.
Keep it a secret.
Well, I'll try this and that.
I'll make sure you won't take a hit.
It's not about me.
I'm worried this will be bad for you.
Did you rush here because you were worried about me?
Yes.
Gosh. Should I make you worry from time to time?
Forget it. We might get photographed again.
Go now.
Don't get out.
You're going home now?
What? Tae Seong!
What brought you to my place?
I heard Jae A's first birthday party is tomorrow.
I just dropped off his gift.
I see. I bet the kids were thrilled to see you after a while.
Why do you care about your friend's nephew's first birthday?
I'm friends with Sol's sister-in-law too.
I took care of my friend's son's birthday.
Gosh.
What are you doing here, Mr. Ryu?
What a coincidence!
I can tell that you're acting.
The article about the dating rumors was on the news this morning.
- It was you, wasn't it? - How did you know?
How come I found out about my friend's boyfriend on the news?
Aren't you going to introduce him to me?
What kind of a top-star dates in public like this,
spreading the rumors all over the neighborhood?
Don't tell me you're jealous.
I'm worried.
I'm not saying this because you worry me,
so don't get me wrong.
You're just...
her ex-boyfriend who briefly passed her by. Got it?
What?
I don't want you to cling to her...
after dating her for a mere two weeks a long, long time ago.
Ex-boyfriend.
Current boyfriend.
Current boyfriend. Ex-boyfriend.
Okay?
What are you talking about?
I've never dated Sol.
You've never dated Sol?
Did she say I dated her?
What?
Right.
What is it?
Are you losing it?
Why are you laughing?
No. It's nothing.
I'm glad that was changed.
I'm so relieved!
What did you talk about that made you laugh like that?
- Come and sit. - Yes.
I have no idea.
Is your boyfriend crazy?
What?
I told you to put this on. Why did you take it off?
It's okay. Everyone in Korea knows that I'm seeing someone.
Still.
There's no one here.
No one's watching.
Gosh.
Here.
Let me pour you a drink.
How long have you been seeing each other?
- It's been 15 years. - It hasn't been long.
What?
Actually, we've known each other for a long time.
He used to live right across from my house.
Is that so?
Then...
the one you can't forget until you die.
Is it him?
- Yes. - I thought so.
When she got drunk,
she called your name desperately.
Be good to my Sol.
She's a friend I deeply care about.
By the way,
when are you going to stop calling her "My Sol?"
I thought so the last time too,
but Mr. Ryu tends to be very jealous.
I get more than jealous.
Be more sensitive from now on.
By the way, we've never drunken like this before, right?
Don't go
I wish it was me
No way.
We didn't even know each other before.
That's true.
Do you drink well?
Tell me in advance if you can't handle it.
I don't drink makgeolli because my body can't handle it.
Other than that, I drink it very well.
I've never gotten tipsy.
Why?
Does the detective get surprisingly drunk?
No way.
Then...
should we drink with this?
Is he terribly drunk?
- Will you take him already? - Okay.
Sun Jae. Come on. Let's go.
- I'm sorry. - Bye.
Sun Jae. Let's hurry. You're so tall.
Let go of me.
Hey, Kim Tae Seong!
"Hey, Kim Tae Seong?"
Excuse me, Mr. Ryu.
You can't do this right here.
Thank you.
Thank you...
for catching the perp,
Kim Young Soo.
Well, it's my job, so you don't have to thank me.
Sol said the same thing too. What's with you two?
You put an end...
to the ill-fated relations.
I sincerely...
want to thank you.
- Oh, no. - Sun Jae.
I'm sorry.
Let's hurry.
Why are you so tall?
Hey. Don't let your boyfriend drink.
Okay. I'll get going. Thanks.
Yes. Goodbye.
Gosh. You haven't changed all these years.
You can't even drink that much.
I'm not drunk.
If you're not drunk, get up.
Let's say that I'm drunk, then.
Gosh. I'm tipsy.
For goodness' sake.
So, your nephew's first birthday party is tomorrow.
Why didn't you tell me?
Didn't I tell you?
Even if I told you, so what?
Do you think everything will go well once you propose?
Did you get the families' approval?
I should be there.
It's not even a party.
My family will just get together and eat.
In that case, I have to be there.
What?
- Let's go. We're here. - Let's go.
- Gosh. What is it? - Get out now.
What is that?
Let's take a look.
Okay. Come here.
Come on. Why are you wearing sunglasses?
Gosh. You're totally overreacting by wearing the sunglasses.
You were in bed, wrapped in a bandage.
No one would recognize you.
Some old women with keen eyes did recognize me.
Is this where we're holding his first birthday party?
You said it was a galbi restaurant in Seowol-dong.
It's Seowol-dong, isn't it?
Hey, Geum.
Of all places, why did you book this place?
You said the owner lived across from our house back then.
He'll treat us better if we used to be neighbors, right?
Darn it.
Your family is on their way, right?
They'll be a little late because of the traffic.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
- Come on. - Let's go.
Let's go and have...
- your first birthday party. - Let's go.
Go.
I'm in Seowol-dong. Which restaurant is it?
Don't come here.
What? Why not all of a sudden?
Just don't come here when I told you not to.
I'll let you meet my family some other time. Okay?
Gosh.
Everything is ready, right?
The silk thread, the stethoscope...
Why is water dropwort here?
For them to grow healthy and well,
they put it on the table for the first birthday.
- This is the judge's gavel. - They're here.
- Hello. - They are here.
- Gosh. Welcome. - Hello.
We've just finished setting up the table.
The ones hosting the first birthday of their baby is...
Hello.
Don't you remember me?
I'm Im Geum from Gold Videos across from your house.
I vaguely remember you.
Yes. Thanks for coming here on your happy day.
Please check if anything is missing from the table.
Okay.
Thank you.
- Let's take a look. - Gosh.
Now that you're dressed up like this, you're so...
So...
Forget it.
I know I look good in hanbok.
Thank you.
Sure.
Gosh.
She must be your sweet, drop-dead gorgeous daughter.
- Hello. - Yes.
I might have seen you back then,
but it strangely feels like I saw you yesterday.
Right?
Because she looks so nice,
many people say that.
Now that you see her in person, it's a shame you missed her, right?
"It's a shame," my foot.
Did you read the articles on my son's date?
I'm about to have a beautiful daughter-in-law.
Well, my daughter's boyfriend...
is coming here too.
He wants to come to our family's occasion.
That means she'll also get married soon.
- No, I won't, Mom. - What?
I see.
It seems our kids found their partners.
You're right.
- Excuse me, then. - Okay.
My husband!
My son!
What's going on?
Are you here to see me?
My goodness.
What brings you here?
Oh, my.
You know, about the other night...
I'm so sorry. But thank you for bringing my mother home.
How silly of me for not recognizing such a famous actor.
Oh, my. I'm a huge fan.
My goodness. Ryu Sun Jae? The famous actor?
- It's Ryu Sun Jae! - Hey.
- I saw him on TV. - Okay.
What took you so long?
- Wait. Ma'am. - Gosh.
Ma'am, you can't just hug him...
- like that without his consent. - Mom.
- Mom, come here. - Okay.
I'll make sure you guys get autographs later.
Please go ahead...
- and start your birthday party. - Okay.
Gosh. Let's go.
Here.
What? For me?
Hello, Mother.
What?
- What? - What?
- "Mother?" - "Mother?"
Gosh. I told you not to come. Why did you show up?
You surprised everyone here.
Why? It's nice. Your family and my family get to meet this way.
But still.
Then the mysterious girl...
in this picture is my daughter, Sol?
Yes.
Gosh, Mom. This is Sol.
- How pretty. - That's Sol.
Oh, my. This is too bad, sir.
Your son is completely...
head over heels for my daughter.
I guess so.
Then when did you two start dating?
I had a huge crush on her...
since high school.
What?
You guys have been dating since then?
I don't remember you telling me about him.
Don't tell me...
this was one-sided love!
I can't believe this!
Back then, I was so nervous that I couldn't even talk to her.
As you know, Sol is so stunning.
Come on.
You look pretty especially today.
- He's already blinded by love. - By the way,
because both of our families are sitting together like this,
it feels like we're here to discuss their wedding.
Right?
Why don't we just talk about their wedding since we're at it?
I'm all for it!
Oh, my. That love-blinded fool.
We're going to begin...
- What could they be doing... - the doljabi...
- to have this much fun? - for the baby prince.
All right. Take a close look at these items.
A gavel, a stethoscope,
a soccer ball, a microphone,
a pencil, a book, and a ball of thread.
We're missing one item here.
- Yes. - What could that be?
- Me! - Cash!
That's right! Cash is missing here.
Is there anyone who would like to be the first person...
to give Prince Jae A an allowance?
- Over here! I got 50 dollars! - Me!
- Hold on! - Over here.
Oh, my. He took out a check!
Goodness. That's 1,000 dollars!
- He took out a 1,000-dollar check. - A 1,000-dollar check?
- That's crazy. - Give a round of applause...
to his future uncle-in-law.
I knew it. He's indeed a generous man.
"Future uncle-in-law?"
- He's already part of her family. - Let's see.
We will begin the doljabi in earnest.
All right. Let's begin with a big round of applause!
All right. Let's see which one Jae A will choose.
Okay. Will he choose the microphone?
Let's see.
- He got the cash! - Prince Jae A chose...
the check as expected.
Next, we will play a quiz.
Please actively participate in the quiz.
Great. Let's start right away.
Here's the first question.
How much did Prince Jae A weigh...
when he was born?
- It's 3.4kg! - I got it!
- It's 2.8kg! - Wrong!
It's 3.5kg!
- I got it! - Yes. Mr. Future Uncle-in-Law.
It's 3.48kg.
Correct!
How did I get this right?
I'll give a box of bay salt to his future uncle-in-law.
Gosh.
He's having a blast.
- Great. - Yes, bay salt!
Thank you.
I can see why my son is head over heels for that girl.
Here's the second question.
- He has high standards for women... - What's the animal...
- because he's just like me. - in his conception dream?
- Sir. - Gosh, you startled me.
- I guess you like... - Number one, dragon.
- your son's girlfriend. - Number two, tiger.
I thought no one could be good enough for your boy.
- Number four, eagle. - This is better than living alone.
- Whoever gets it right first... - It's been a long time since...
will get the gift card!
- I last saw him smile that big. - Yes, you.
Number two, tiger?
- That's wrong! - Let's go.
Number 3? What was number 3?
Gosh. What are you guys doing here?
Are you here to have a meal?
No.
We're here...
to perform.
Perfume?
Why did you bring perfume to a barbecue restaurant?
Perform at Sol's nephew's first birthday party.
Has he really gone mad?
Hey, just ignore that.
Performing at birthday parties is beneath us now.
I'll renovate your studio if you perform at the party.
Hey.
He said he'd renovate our studio if we performed.
I'll get you brand-new instruments...
- and equipment. - No way.
He'll get us brand-new instruments and equipment too.
Where is this birthday party...
taking place?
Only the performance to celebrate his birthday remains now.
Hold on.
They will perform here?
This is amazing.
They came to wish Prince Jae A a happy birthday.
Here's Eclipse! Give them a big round of applause.
Four, two, nine.
Start.
Happy birthday, dear our handsome prince
Happy birthday, dear our beautiful prince
Everyone is wishing you a happy birthday
Thank you so much for coming to us
Getting Eclipse to perform at the party was too much.
Their concert ticket is so expensive.
How could you make them sing with the karaoke machine?
I wanted to win some brownie points.
So did you?
Whenever I saw you on TV, I always felt this bond with you.
I guess it was because we were going to be a family.
Mom, come on.
- What? - Gosh.
I haven't done much for my sister.
But I will say this...
on behalf of my father who must be watching over us.
I will be watching you very closely.
If you make my sister cry, I'm going to...
You're taking this too far.
Understood?
Yes, don't worry.
I heard that you just started an acting career.
Hopefully, we'll get a chance to work together.
Brother, I had always been a fan.
Let's work together next time. Okay?
Yes.
Promise me.
He even promised me.
Hey, Jae A is crying. Let's go.
- Okay. Gosh. - Let's hurry.
- Bye. - Goodnight.
- Wait. - Let's go.
Can I get your number at least?
Ma'am.
You can now have a long life with her.
Be happy together.
With a lot of smiles.
Thank you.
Probably?
By the way, why did you suddenly want to get on the ferry?
Just because.
We have a lot of memories on the Han River.
That's true.
It's time.
Well, Sol.
I want to...
"Propose..."
- Strike a pose there. - Propose?
- What? - What?
A pose...
A pose?
Which pose?
A heart?
Yes.
Is it because it's night?
- Are you that dumb? - It didn't come out well.
Are you an idiot?
Why are you laughing?
By the way,
you're not planning to propose here, right?
What?
Do you know what's the most important part of proposing?
Keeping the secret.
- No. - Come on.
Just like in the dramas, did you rent out the entire ferry...
and order fireworks?
Did you ask Dong Seok to push out the three-tier cake...
and In Hyuk to throw flower petals? Are you sure this isn't that?
Dong Seok, come on out.
In Hyuk! Come on out!
Dong Seok!
- In Hyuk! - In Hyuk! Come out!
In Hyuk!
By the way,
you really got it wrong. I feel bad now.
Gosh. I was joking.
Don't look so flustered.
Were you joking?
That was funny.
This one was really funny.
You know, I wanted to talk to you about something.
It will start soon. What do I do?
Yes. I should propose to her before she gets wind of this.
Sol.
- Will you... - I want to make a movie.
What? What did you say?
I want to try out...
becoming a movie director.
- A movie? - Yes.
I'm thinking about entering the short film festival...
that will take place in spring.
I quit my job and tried to finish writing the scenario quickly...
for this, to tell you the truth.
I was excited to watch a movie in a theater...
since it had been a while.
I'm sad we missed it.
- I guess you like movies. - Yes.
I used to watch 2 to 3 movies a day.
I wanted to become a movie director.
Is that so?
I'm worried that I might be too late to try out a new career.
And I don't feel so confident either.
But remember what you told me?
That you were happy when you were a swimmer.
That you couldn't have known that joy without trying it out.
So I want to try it out too.
Regardless of the results,
it might bring me joy.
As long as it makes you happy,
I'm fine with everything.
I'll be super busy again.
We won't be able to meet often.
Then I'll go and see you.
I'll support your dream.
Thank you.
I think I will be very busy for the time being.
Wait a bit.
Of course. I can wait for you as long as you need.
By the way, what were you going to tell me?
- Me? - Yes.
No.
This isn't the right time.
Aren't your ears cold?
I'm fine.
No. It's cold tonight.
It's very cold here.
Go away.
No?
Pull out.
Pull out. Don't come here. Go.
I'm not cold.
Gosh, what?
It feels like Siberia here. You'll catch a cold.
Sun Jae. By the way,
I think I'm hearing explosions or something.
What?
That's my heart exploding!
(Will you marry me?)
What?
Today...
isn't the right time.
Not yet.
(Filming a short movie, "Wish")
Let's go. On standby!
Take 1 for Scene 23.
Ready!
Action!
The weather is amazing. Isn't it?
Earlier, you were...
Director Im.
A coffee truck arrived for you.
A coffee truck?
(Superstar Sun Jae is here to root for Director Im Sol.)
What's all this?
What is this?
You didn't even call ahead. What are you doing here?
I'm here to surprise you with my support.
Actually,
I wanted to use this as an excuse and see you.
Thank you.
Thank you! We'll enjoy the coffee.
- Thank you! - Thank you!
All right. Let's start again with this part...
where you didn't recognize him.
Ready.
- It's raining. - No!
- It's raining. - Cover that.
- The camera! - Cover that up!
Over there!
Hey, I'm still in the editing studio.
It's late. Should I go and pick you up?
What?
(My Fate)
No. I'll order a taxi. It will come quickly.
Don't you have a shoot tomorrow?
Go to sleep now.
Don't come here. Okay?
Okay.
Call me when you're done.
Surprise.
Aren't you cold?
Why did you come here? I told you to go to sleep.
Should I just kidnap you now and run away?
What?
Let's go!
We're here.
("Wish")
(Upload your movie)
(Your movie has been submitted successfully. Thank you.)
Yes!
I'm done!
Im Sol. You finally did it!
Sol, good job.
It's been a while...
since we got to walk like this while holding hands.
You've gotten more handsome while I've been busy.
When I was waiting for my busy girlfriend,
my heart was in so much pain.
Really? Let me see.
I can't show it to you here.
I'll show it to you later.
Gosh, you.
I can't remember the last time we got to spend time like this.
When will they announce the results?
Next month.
I'm sure it will turn out well.
I really wasn't going to have any expectations.
But our heart is a fickle thing. Now that I submitted my work,
I'm sort of hoping I would win something.
I shouldn't, though.
Then...
why don't you make a wish?
Like we did before.
- Shall we? - Yes.
You should close your eyes.
Okay.
What did you wish for?
I...
Sun Jae...
From now on,
I want to spend every waking moment with you.
Will you, Sol?
Won't you give me your answer?
Yes.
I will.
I'll stay by your side for the rest of my life.
- Did you just... - Just now...
(Lovely Runner)
(Thank you for watching Lovely Runner.)