(Byeon Woo Seok)
(CEO)
(10 missed calls from CEO)
(Kim Hye Yoon)
(Lovely Runner)
Breaking news. There has been a shocking incident...
where the actor who started off as a singer, Ryu Sun Jae,
was attacked...
by an unidentified assailant at a hotel in Seoul.
The police are currently in pursuit of the suspect...
who ran away from the scene.
Reporter Kim Eun Ju will give us more details.
The incident took place at a five-star hotel.
So it's difficult for unregistered guests to enter.
The police shared that the suspect stole the master key...
from an employee and broke into the suite Ryu was staying in.
The police found a handkerchief...
- which had traces of anesthetics... - You jerk.
And signs of struggle...
between the suspect and the victim inside the victim's hotel room.
Moreover, based on the DNA analysis of the weapon found at the scene,
the suspect had been imprisoned for murder in 2009...
and was released only a few days ago.
The suspect is identified as Kim, a man in his 40s.
- The police announced that... - Why on earth...
they decided to disclose...
- Why did he hurt Sun Jae? - the suspect's information...
(Restricted Area)
Give me that.
(Operating Center)
I must turn back time.
(Auction for Ryu Sun Jae's watch)
There's nothing online.
Does he still have it?
What if he threw it out?
(Forest Palace)
It's not here. Where is it?
Sol. What are you doing?
Do you know...
- where Sun Jae's watch is? - What?
You know, the electronic watch he used to wear.
The one he used to wear ever since high school.
You remember that, right?
I must find it now.
Why are you asking me about his watch?
Sun Jae was attacked because of you!
Get a grip!
I'm doing this so I can fix everything!
If you want to save Sun Jae, we must find the watch now.
What does that have to do with saving Sun Jae?
I have no time to explain.
Where is the watch?
Is it at his father's house? Where does he live? Please?
Yes. Okay.
I'll look into that.
You can't find that watch!
What?
He lost it a long time ago.
He lost the watch ages ago.
Sun Jae looked for it everywhere to find that too.
But he couldn't find it in the end.
He doesn't have it?
Are you sure?
Yes.
What's with the watch? Why do you want it so badly?
According to a statement of an inmate who was incarcerated...
with the suspect, Kim,
- Sol. - Kim held a grudge...
for a long time against Ryu Sun Jae...
who witnessed his crime and helped the police...
arrest him in May of 2009.
- After investigating the suspect, - What's this all about?
- right after Kim... - I thought the culprit...
- was caught before that. - was released from prison,
- he purchased a black sedan... - How could Sun Jae help them...
- and committed the act... - catch Kim Young Soo in 2009?
- according to the police. - Mom.
- Was I abducted in 2009? - On top of that, Kim already...
- knew that Ryu was... - Yes. It happened not long after...
- at the hotel. - you started college.
Because I came back to the present, there was no report about him.
Then does it mean Kim Young Soo came to me again in 2009?
If Sun Jae witnessed the crime and saved me in 2009...
The police treated it...
as a premeditated crime with a clear intention to kill.
A premeditated crime with a clear intention to kill?
That can't be...
I was afraid that Kim Young Soo...
would go to you after his release.
I was going to tell you to ask for protection.
But I didn't think that he would go to Sun Jae.
What about the thing I asked for?
Yes, sure.
Excuse me.
Yes.
(Investigation Report on Kim Young Soo)
(Statement, Name: Ryu Sun Jae)
(Name: Ryu Sun Jae)
(On my way back from meeting my college friends...)
(May 10, 2009)
It was the night of May 10, 2009.
On my way back home, I saw a backpack.
I spotted a book with Sol's name.
That's when I heard Sol's scream.
I called the police right away,
and I ran toward where the scream came from.
(I called Sol while looking around...)
I called Sol while looking around.
I heard a faint sound of her phone...
ringing in the building that was under construction.
I followed the sound of the ringing phone...
and ran into the building.
Sol!
That's when I saw Sol running out of the building.
- I checked on Sol when she fainted. - Sol.
I saw a man run away then.
- Darn it. - You...
I chased him, and we engaged in a scuffle.
The man was holding something. And that's when he dropped it.
(The man came at me once again and pushed me into...)
Die! Darn it.
The man attacked me when I was on the floor.
- Die! - He started to choke me.
Die!
I extended my arm, grabbed whatever I could,
and hit his face with it.
I guess you feel better now.
You got scared when you saw me after the incident.
By the way, did you really stop contacting him after that incident?
Why are you asking me about his watch?
Sun Jae was attacked because of you!
Sun Jae...
died because of me?
(Investigation Report on Kim Young Soo)
It should have been me.
I should have been the one who got killed.
This...
(Detective Kim)
Hello.
Detective Kim.
I have a question for you.
I saw a picture of items belonging to the victim.
Are the police keeping these items at the station?
No.
We return them after the investigation is over.
Why do you ask?
Nothing.
Did I...
get it back?
Sol. What is it?
What are you looking for?
Mom, are you storing any of my old stuff separately?
What is it? What are you looking for?
I...
Grandma.
I've been keeping it safe.
Mom, did you take Sol's stuff again?
All right. Give it back now.
- Here. - Hold on, Grandma.
I found it.
(Hanguk University Hospital)
How are you feeling? Are you all right?
Sun Jae.
But when I see you, it reminds me of that incident.
It scares me.
So I can't see you anymore.
I'm sorry, Sun Jae.
This all happened because of me.
I'll make sure to fix it this time.
(Imjae Development Center)
Where am I?
- Am I back? - Someone's up there.
- Is she crazy? - What's going on?
- Is she mad? - She must be crazy.
That's dangerous.
- Which school does she go? - Which department is she in?
Hey, be careful!
What?
Why am I up here?
(Yeonseo University would like to welcome Year 2009's freshmen.)
Year 2009?
Yeonseo University?
Sol. Oh, no.
Am I going to die the moment I come back?
I can't die like this.
I must save Sun Jae at least before I die.
Nice catch.
Thank you!
Ryu Sun Jae?
Hey, where are you going?
Thank you!
If you run away alone, it will be more embarrassing.
Hey, wait up.
(Orientation for 2009 Freshmen)
Why did I fall into his arms of everyone's?
Hey.
You didn't even thank Ryu Sun Jae before you ran away.
He saved you from crashing onto the ground.
Right. Why do I do that to him all the time?
By the way, what's Sun Jae doing here?
He's majoring in physical education...
just like Geum.
I thought you knew.
What?
He signed with the agency before our high school graduation,
so he didn't go to college before.
When you are auditioning, don't take him with you.
My focus had been completely off all this time.
I ended up wasting my precious time.
This is a great coincidence.
- Why don't you... - No.
I can't face him...
because I feel so sorry.
Wait. Is this about dumping him before?
No way.
Last year, you suddenly stopped coming to the study room...
and avoided him so visibly. Are you still on that?
Yes. I should be.
Nothing good will come to him if he gets mixed up with me.
Don't get too big-headed.
There are so many beautiful girls.
Why would he want to get mixed up with you who already rejected him?
I wouldn't want anything else.
I'll see you later. I have somewhere to be.
Now? Wait.
Here.
Make sure to bring it tomorrow.
But...
we have our major class coming up next.
Is she ditching the class?
Darn it. She's been diligent lately. Why is she acting like this again?
(March 17, 2009)
(Date of Incident: May 10, 2009)
I need to catch Kim Young Soo before he comes for me.
Then nothing will happen to Sun Jae.
So on September 1, 2008,
you were abducted by a taxi driver in front of your house.
- Correct? - Yes.
But why didn't you report this then?
It's been several months since then. I don't understand...
why it took you this long.
Back then, because of the shock, I had lost my memory.
But my memory came back.
All of a sudden?
Is that even possible?
The culprit who abducted me...
is the culprit...
- of the Juyang Reservoir Incident. - What?
I know who the culprit is. I remembered it.
I know his face, name, and job.
These are...
his car keys.
(Self Defense)
I shared all the information about the culprit with the police.
They'll catch him soon, right?
Yes, they will.
But just in case,
I should protect myself.
Hey, let go of his hand!
Kim Tae Seong?
My ex-girlfriend?
You!
What are you doing here?
Gosh. You pathetic fool.
- Haven't you grown up? - What are you doing?
I told you many times to get your act straight.
You're 20 now.
How could you extort money from a kid? Unbelievable.
Thank you for helping me find my money.
"Thank you?"
Give that to me.
I'm sorry for the misunderstanding.
I wonder how you think of me.
You always treat me like I don't know any better.
I'm just worried about your life.
You were going to throw away your life, you know?
Did you graduate?
That's a funny way of asking to see my graduation picture.
My goodness! You really graduated.
Oh, my.
My dear. Good job.
I'm so proud of you, Kim Tae Seong.
You turned over a new leaf.
What's this?
I see. I know what this is.
What?
You haven't seen me for a while. Do you find me attractive?
- What? - You're doing this on purpose.
So you can make our reencountering moment...
memorable.
Do you want me to turn this into a teaching moment?
Wait.
Why do I get the feeling that...
Sol with the mature ego has come back?
Now that I know that, something seems a bit off.
He's so sharp.
Did he figure it out?
What? What do you mean?
Why are you staring at me like that?
My ex-girlfriend has gotten prettier.
Gosh. You haven't changed one bit.
I bet you say that to every woman you see.
So what have you been up to after the graduation?
Gosh.
Judging by your outfit,
I bet you're drinking every night with your friends.
What about my outfit?
This outfit had the highest sales this season.
Sales?
- Do you run a business? - All right.
Look up Today's Member Kim Tae Seong's clothing website.
(Today's Member Kim Tae Seong's clothing website)
He looks so hip.
Today's Member...
I need to get going now.
If you wanted a memorable reunion, you've succeeded.
See you around.
I'm glad that he's living a good life.
Why did she run away as if she saw a ghost?
What are you mumbling about?
What? Did Im Sol run away when she saw you?
Yes. When we ran into each other before,
she just ignored and avoided me.
But this time, she ran away so quickly.
All right.
Could you tell me how that's supposed to be different?
It was definitely different.
I sensed it in that split second she ran away.
I could tell there was...
some kind of emotion, observing her from behind.
I think her face was slightly red too.
What do you think?
All right. Let me go over this once and for all.
She ignored and avoided you...
because she hated you.
But she quickly ran away from you...
Is it because seeing me stirred up her emotion or something?
It meant she was sick and tired of seeing you.
Darn it.
Move. Don't get on my nerves.
I would have done the same if I were her.
The guy she dumped still couldn't move on with his life.
Seeing how he's attending the same university as her,
she must be appalled.
Don't you even have pride?
No, there's no such thing as pride with me.
What's this?
Hey, now that I taught you a few chords, you wrote a song.
Darn it. Give it to me.
What's up with the lyrics?
"Sonaki?"
Did you write this while thinking about Im Sol?
No.
I just wrote it while watching the rain.
Oh, stop it.
That happened ages ago.
Gosh.
Why are you so annoying especially today?
I don't think you can move on from Im Sol because...
you keep seeing her at school.
"Out of sight, out of mind," you know?
Take a semester off and join our band.
Be our vocalist instead of Dong Seob.
That's a sudden change of subject.
I'll get going.
Hey. Get yourself sorted.
Stop writing pathetic songs like this, you idiot.
It's spring here.
By the time spring is over,
I won't be here, will I?
This is the last chance.
(Nuri-dong, a good place to live)
(The first day of classes!)
Until May 10,
I can't let Sun Jae and Kim Young Soo meet each other.
Knock before you enter!
Knock knock.
Sol.
Sol, can I get your autograph?
My autograph? What are you talking about?
The photo of you hanging over the statue after getting drunk.
It was posted on the school board.
It has created a big buzz.
Hey. You're a star now.
You do have more star potential than I do.
- I give you that. - What? On the school board?
My goodness.
Gosh. Well done.
How are you going to survive four years of college now?
Mind your own business.
Did you return to school?
- Yes. Why? - It's about Sun Jae.
I heard he's majoring in PE. Have you run into him before?
Hey. I started my college years in 2004.
Why would I run into a new student like him?
Right?
Even if you do see him,
don't harass him or try to discipline him.
You're the one who shouldn't act like you know me at school.
Sol. Look at me.
- How do I look? - Lame.
Gosh. That means I look nice.
Okay.
Gosh. How did he win Hyun Ju's heart when he's that pathetic?
I don't like the extendable batons.
How do I use this?
Hey. What about this...
It's burning!
- What's wrong with you? - Nice. I like it.
Sun Jae.
Do you remember what I told you before?
- About what? - About getting a rehab...
in the States.
Did you think about it?
Isn't it a false hope, though?
Hey. Look at this.
Take a seat.
Coach An gave it to me.
Take a look.
("Archer Kim Ga Yeon Chose Jonkins In the US for Stem Cell Treatment")
They are specialized in treating athletes.
A really famous tennis player had retired...
when he was young due to a shoulder injury like yours.
But after getting a rehab there,
he was able to return the next season...
and even won the competition.
They do gene therapy as well as stem cell treatment.
I think there's a chance to recover.
How about taking a semester off and going there right away?
I'll take some time and think about it.
Right. Okay.
Okay. In that case,
think about it.
Take it easy, Son.
Okay.
(Tests in Exercise Science)
(Sonaki)
Do you know what I despised the most?
The rain.
But it rained when I saw you for the first time.
I liked it that day.
Sol.
I like you...
a lot.
I can't reciprocate your feelings.
Hearing this from you makes me feel uncomfortable and pressured.
So...
don't have any feelings for me.
(I didn't want you to be the rain)
(That soaks me wet only momentarily)
(You are a gift from the sky)
I grabbed whatever.
Buy new ones or come home and get them yourself.
How can I go back home when the case hasn't been solved?
You always put your work first.
I'll get going.
Hey, Tae Seong.
I told you to bring my underpants. But what are these?
Those are your underpants.
(Yeonseo University)
What?
(Gold Videos and DVDs)
Sol!
Hey!
You can't be still asleep.
Wake up at once.
You haven't packed, have you?
Gosh.
Wake up and wash up already.
What time is it?
The reported crime has been transferred to Detective Division.
The investigation will continue.
They are investigating it quickly.
It's a relief.
We'll be late.
Do you want to be branded as a troublemaking freshman?
What are you talking about when it's still early in the morning?
"What am I talking about?"
We're going on a field trip to welcome new students.
Did you forget about it?
A field trip?
Hurry and wash up.
Where did you leave the thing I gave you?
- Gosh. What are these? - What are those?
Everyone, take your designated seats.
(Righteous Mass Comm, Spearhead PE)
Back drumming.
Hurry up.
Rock-paper-scissors.
Goodness.
Why does it have to be the same train?
- Do it again. - One more time.
If you don't participate, you lose. Rock-paper-scissors.
Hold on.
Yeonseo University.
Students of Yeonseo University. Attention, please.
Do you know about this story?
There is a myth that has come down in Yeonseo University...
- for ages. - "A myth?"
It says the couple who make out on the first field trip...
for the new students gets married.
- Come on. - Stop joking around.
I'm serious.
The couple that got married this time...
got together after making out on the first field trip.
Also, there are alumni in the School of Management,
who made out on the field trip, got together,
and got married.
But they got divorced after a year and got married to another alumnus.
It turned out, one of them got drunk...
and kissed the other one too on their first field trip.
- What? - Gosh.
I'm not finished.
On the field trip of this major a long time ago,
two male students kissed as a penalty of a drinking game.
Guess what happened?
What happened?
They went overseas to get married after ten years.
Gosh.
No matter what, you'll get married once you make out on this trip.
So, don't make out with anybody because you are drunk.
Control your lips, okay?
We should be careful too.
You don't need to worry about it.
Sun Jae, do you believe that myth is true?
I don't trust such nonsense.
It will be a field of blooming love.
Hey, Sol.
Actually.
Well. How is Geum...
with his girlfriend these days?
I checked his girlfriend's homepage,
and all her photos with him were taken down.
Did they break up?
- Why Im Geum of all people? - What?
There are so many good guys in the world.
Don't say I didn't warn you now.
What are you talking about?
My goodness.
I have no interest in Geum at all.
What are you looking at?
It's spicy.
What are you doing? I swallowed the mouthwash.
Hey. I'm warning you.
- Don't develop feelings for me. - I'm sorry.
Hush.
I just need to hide until we reach the cabin.
- We'll unpack first... - What?
And meet back here.
PE students, we'll gather here after unpacking.
Are we staying in the same cabin?
(New students of 2009 welcome party and field trip)
There's Geum.
He must have come on a different train.
What? What's wrong with his clothes?
- Is he a bum or what? - I know.
You should stop drinking.
I'll drink later, then.
She came.
Why didn't I...
see her on the train, though?
You.
Do you know about Yeonseo University's myth?
- Yes. I know. - Don't you dare...
to try anything for my sister based on the myth.
Watch where your lips go.
You're already removed permanently
from my list of brother-in-law candidates.
If you care about your sister so much,
you should be nice to her at ordinary times.
Why are you talking back to me?
Hey, Hyun Ju. This place is huge.
I'm glad we chose here based on your recommendation.
What? Did you choose this place?
- Yes. - Gosh.
You're driving me crazy.
You hide your lips too.
- Hello, Geum. - Hi, Geum.
- You rolled in your lips. - Yes.
Is she running away because she doesn't want to run into me?
Hey!
I swallowed the mouthwash again.
Gosh. My stomach is upset.
I'm sorry.
Why do you keep holding the mouthwash in your mouth?
By the way, Ms. Underclassman.
Don't tell me you were going to run away.
That's not okay.
Darn it.
(Violent Crimes Unit 1)
Captain.
The victim of an attempted kidnap said her perp is the murderer...
of Juyang Reservoir homicide case, so her case got transferred here.
"An attempted kidnap?"
The victim said she met you...
- on the day of the kidnap. - What?
She had a temporary memory loss back then due to the trauma.
"Im Sol?"
Hey. Are you all right?
Where am I?
In that case, was that day...
She did act strangely on that day for some reason.
I've looked into this guy, Kim Young Soo.
It matches perfectly with what's written in her statement.
I put that key...
into the taxi that he drives, and it matched perfectly.
I got goosebumps.
Can he really be the perp of the Juyang Reservoir's murder?
Where is Kim Young Soo right now?
Since the attempted kidnap, he is in the wind.
He left the taxi company.
He canceled his phone too.
Here.
This is where the victim said the crime scene is.
She said it'd be hard to find...
because its address isn't registered, so she drew a map.
If we find evidence here,
she's spoon-feeding us so that we can catch him.
Hello, everyone!
United Yeonseo!
Righteous Mass Comm!
In the world's best Mass Comm major,
I'm the bob-hair fairy of Yeonseo University.
- I'm Kang... - Kang!
- Soo... - Soo!
- Ji! - Ji!
I'm not in the mood to enjoy the trip.
Hello, everyone!
United Yeonseo!
Righteous Mass Comm!
I'm the talented girl from our major.
- I'm Kim... - Kim!
- Hwa... - Hwa!
- Sol! - Sol!
Nice to meet you.
Let's get out of here.
Where is it?
Okay. Now, let's go inside...
and play games while drinking.
Come in.
What's wrong with her?
Has she passed out from drinking already?
- Come in and set up the place. - Righteous Mass Comm!
- Okay. - Righteous Mass Comm!
New students, we'll mix up the drinks.
The random game that Jin Sang likes.
- Which game is it? - Which game is it?
- Start the game! - Start the game!
I need to get out of here quietly without getting noticed.
I'll do 2 and 3?
The ice cream 31.
I'll do 25, 26.
- I'll do 27, 28. - I'll do 29.
I'll do 30!
- Chug. - Chug.
The alcohol is going in.
Until when do I have to dance?
Drink up.
It's 0, 0, 7...
- Bang! - No!
It's 0, 0, 7, bang!
- Chug. - Chug.
Alcohol is going in.
The black knight!
Here comes the rabbit from the moon.
- Boom, boom. - Boom, boom
- Bunny, Bunny. - Bunny, Bunny.
- Carrot, carrot. - Carrot, carrot.
Alcohol is going in.
- Chug. - Chug.
Until when do I have to dance?
Look at my shoulders. They are dislocated.
Just a little more.
I'm almost there.
I got you.
I thought you blacked out.
Did you pretend you were asleep because you didn't want to drink?
No.
Of course not. That can't be possible.
You're right. That can't be possible.
Darn it.
Okay.
Let's change the vibe.
From now on, whoever loses...
has to drink and do a penalty mission.
Okay. The first penalty mission is...
to go to the PE students' lodging next door...
- Drum roll. - Drum roll.
And dance!
I just cannot lose this.
The game starts now.
Four strawberries.
Strawberry, strawberry.
Two grapes.
Grape, grape.
Four lemons.
Lemon, lemon.
- Eight grapefruits. - Grapefruit, grapefruit,
grapefruit, grapefruit.
Five strawberries.
Strawberry, strawberry.
Three grapefruits.
Grapefruit, grapefruit.
- Eight strawberries. - Strawberry, strawberry,
strawberry, strawberry.
- Seven grapefruits. - Grapefruit, grapefruit,
grapefruit, grapefruit.
One strawberry!
Strawberry, straw...
Yes!
Alcohol is going in.
- Chug. - Chug.
Until when do I have to dance?
Okay. Hello, everyone!
The new student from our major...
will put on a show for you.
Give her a big hand!
Gosh. She's running away.
Sun Jae isn't here. Let's get it over with it quickly.
- Do it 1 more time! - Do it 1 more time!
Gosh. Hey.
You can't stop in the middle of it.
You have to finish your penalty mission.
I told you I was leaving!
How dare you tell me what to do when you're 1 or 2 years older?
If you were born a few years later,
you would have socially buried after getting posted...
on school boards and social media.
Also, penalty drink?
Did anyone do anything to get penalized?
Are you going to take responsibility if someone dies after drinking this?
You young prick doesn't even know how dangerous alcohol is!
Got it?
I'm leaving.
Don't let them drink too much and let them sleep early. Understood?
- Answer me! - Okay.
- Hey. Let's play foot volleyball. - Okay.
Hey. I love playing foot volleyball.
- Let go of me. - You can't beat me.
- Hey. - Be careful.
- I'm confident I'll win. - Hey, listen.
- Come here. - Stop it.
(Watch out for boars while tracking at dawn or night.)
Should we share a cab?
Mom will be...
Guys, I'm sorry.
I have to leave early because I have a TOEIC class.
Nice work today.
Eclipse, peace!
That prick!
We might lose a gig because of him.
And he studies for TOEIC?
The boss said he'd fire us if we can't fill up the venue this month.
What should we do?
Should we make a promotional video?
Darn it.
Hey. Should we enter this?
(Come on out if you can die for singing.)
(Superstar K, The audition to discover stars)
"Superstar K?"
Where is the trail?
Let me see the map.
Right.
This is not a smartphone.
Sun Jae!
What do I do? Sun Jae!
Sun Jae, come to your senses!
Excuse me! Is there anybody out there?
Oh, no. I have no reception.
(Out of service area)
- Oh, my goodness! - Oh, gosh!
Please just go.
Hold me tight.
Okay.
I'm going to untie it.
All right.
Why would they set something like this?
Isn't it illegal?
Here.
If you're going to carry it around to defend yourself,
you should put batteries in it.
Didn't you pass out from the electric shock?
I just fell.
You hit the vital spot with that.
Sorry.
So?
Why did you enter the wild boar habitat at night?
Well,
I was going home as I couldn't get used to the field trip.
You were running away from me.
I saw it.
You've been avoiding me all day.
Do you really have to do this to run away?
There's no walking trail here. Follow me.
Hey.
Do you hate me that much?
Are you doing this because you don't even want to see me?
How can I hate you?
It's because you might die because of me.
It's late.
Let's go.
The person you have reached is unavailable.
- Please leave a message... - It's weird.
- after the tone. - Is Chae Won's phone...
broken?
(Wild Boar Area: Be cautious when hiking at dawn or at night)
Gosh.
What? What's going on?
Why are you coming out of the dark forest?
Hey.
Hey, Ryu.
You didn't put your lips on my sister's...
in the forest did you?
Never mind.
Looking at your long face, it seems you failed miserably.
Gosh, you look capable, but...
It's not something like that.
Hey.
I see why Sol doesn't like you.
- Do you need my advice? - No.
Hey. A woman's heart...
isn't simple like a straight road.
It's like a complex off-road course. If you step on the pedal...
and go straight,
do you know what happens?
You'll just crash.
When you hit on her, step on the pedal.
When you have to step back, you should slow down.
Slow down, speed up.
You should control your speed.
Women go crazy...
because I'm good at it.
This is ridiculous.
Hey. Especially,
I don't cling to them and am cool about it.
That's my style.
When you're dumped or break up with someone,
you should turn away without hesitation.
"What's gotten into him?"
It makes her curious. Got it?
Yes.
Hey, Ryu. Let me borrow your phone.
Will you let me go if I do that?
Give me your phone first.
Thanks.
- Hello? - Chae Won!
My princess, I haven't heard your voice for so long.
I couldn't reach you for the past few days.
I thought your phone was broken.
But it was my phone that was broken.
Geum, my phone isn't broken.
I avoided your calls.
What? You avoided my calls? Why?
I like someone else now.
- I'm sorry. - Someone else?
Who? What are you talking about?
Wait. Don't hang up.
Are you saying you want to break up with me?
Tell me again. Chae Won!
Princess Chae Won!
(2009 Yeonseo University Mass Comm Department Field Trip)
Are you going to start dating Jin Sang today?
He had mouthwash in his mouth all day.
He's determined to tell his feelings to you and kiss you.
What?
I don't like public confession.
Hey. Do you hate me that much?
Are you doing this because you don't even want to see me?
Sol. Why are you drinking alone miserably?
Come here. Drink with us.
No, I'm fine.
Did something happen?
We finished the snack.
Let me bring more.
Chae Won.
Princess Chae Won.
You can't end it like this.
Don't abandon me.
He's so clingy.
Give me your phone now.
Hey, Ryu. I'm in pain.
You smell like alcohol.
Why do you think she doesn't like me anymore?
How can I change a woman's heart?
I wonder.
My heart hurts so much.
It's like I was hit by a bullet.
I can't stay still like this.
I'm going to see Chae Won now.
Right now!
What? Now?
Chae Won!
What?
Where are you going, Geum?
Wild boars might appear in that area!
Where did he go?
Eun Ji!
I'm Jin Sang!
My heart is about to explode because of you!
- Will you go out... - My gosh.
- with me? - Go out.
- My goodness. - You should go out.
- It's embarrassing. - Please go out with me!
- Where are you? - Oh, my.
- Don't make me wait for too long! - How do I look?
You look so pretty.
Come out, Eun Ji!
(2009 Yeonseo University Mass Comm Department Field Trip)
Eun...
Gosh, why isn't she coming out? Something else is about to come out.
My stomach hurts.
Is it because I swallowed the mouthwash a lot?
Eun Ji... This won't do.
Hey.
You're a Physical Education major. We attend the same school.
Can you please help me just once? Please hold the door for me.
What a mess.
Thank you so much.
Please hold the door for me.
- Okay. - Thank you.
So he's the guy.
(Yeonseo University)
Hey, where are you going?
Hey.
I'm here.
- What the heck? - Oh, gosh.
Gosh, it's quiet now.
Sol?
Why is the ground coming up?
Is she drunk?
I would have done the same if I were her.
The guy she dumped...
still couldn't move on with his life.
Seeing how he's attending the same university as her,
she must be appalled.
It's pretty.
Should we just meet up now?
- What? - Just tell me...
that you want to see me.
I'll quit everything and go to you.
Get back to work now.
At that time,
I should've told him that I wanted to see him.
Would nothing have happened then?
Geum!
I'm sure he was going this way. Where is he?
Chae Won.
Geum!
Oh, no. What's this?
Oh, my. Are you okay?
Oh, no.
What do I do?
- Chae Won. - My gosh!
How can your love change?
Do you like that guy that much?
Did you guys break up?
Did she really...
cheat on you?
Don't abandon me,
Chae Won.
Stop calling her.
She dumped you for another guy.
- Why do you keep calling her name? - Chae Won.
I told you to stop calling her.
Do you not have pride?
Princess Chae Won.
You call her Princess even now?
- Princess Chae Won. - Don't call her name!
Don't you dare call her name once again.
Chae Won.
What?
No!
You almost fell.
Why are you here?
You shouldn't have passed out here like this.
Why did you come?
Don't make me worry about you then.
Why did you follow me?
Why do you keep coming?
I was so mean to you.
Why are you worried about me?
Are you a fool?
Are you really a fool?
I said you should think about yourself only.
You should curse me as a bad girl...
and get me out of your mind.
Why did you act like a fool and let something like that happen to you?
"Something like that?"
Please.
Please, Sun Jae.
Okay, fine.
I'm sorry about everything. So...
don't cry. Okay?
Don't.
Just act like you don't know me.
Don't even worry about me.
Whatever I do, whatever happens to me, please...
Please just leave me alone.
(Superstar K)
I'm here.
You came. Did you have fun during the field trip?
I don't know.
Sun Jae.
Was it "Boseulbi" or "Sonaki?" The song you made.
Should we go there with the song?
You said you didn't like it.
Have you let anyone listen to the song?
What? Who?
Whoever it is. Have you let anyone listen to it?
Hey, I listened to the song just a few days ago.
Who would I let someone else hear it?
So you haven't.
That's why I'm saying this. Let's participate in the show...
and let everyone in the country hear it. How about that?
What's this?
Hey.
This darn guy.
- Call 119. - Okay.
My goodness.
There's a fire here. Please come.
There's a deserted house on the right side...
if you cross the bridge and come up...
near the bus stop at Juyang Reservoir.
Please hurry up.
Yes. I'm calling as I want to know how the investigation is going.
We are currently trying to locate Kim Young Soo's whereabouts.
We went to the crime scene you talked about,
but it was already burnt down.
What? It was burnt down?
No. The investigation record didn't mention it.
The evidence should be found there.
There's no way.
Did you not find any evidence?
Not yet.
I think he knows he was reported.
Is he going to find me?
What if he bumps into Sun Jae?
(To Let)
Sun Jae.
I was waiting for you because I have something to check.
I should go somewhere quickly.
How did you...
know the song and sing it?
"The song?"
I've never let anyone hear it except In Hyuk.
How do you know the song?
You are a gift
- From the sky - She's completely drunk.
When you're all alone in this world, I'll protect you
Where did you...
hear the song?
I'll change it this time.
Before I go back, I'll make sure to do that.
Are you going somewhere?
To the future.
To my time.
(Gold Videos and DVDs)
Where are you going?
Well, that's...
Are you going back to your time?
Who are you?
Did you really...
come from the future?
Let's go now. Get on my back.
(Epilogue)
I said get on my back.
(Lovely Runner)
What would you do if someone you like says she came from the future?
What kind of stupid refusal is that?
It's good to see you.
Look at what she's doing. I think she likes Sun Jae.
Sun Jae, would you like to go out with me?
Did you like it?
Don't waste your energy, getting jealous of me for no reason.
Just protect yourself.
Let me ask you one last question.
In all your times, have you ever liked me?
No, I haven't.
I'll leave so that you don't feel uncomfortable.
Don't come.
I said don't come!