Is there something wrong with this guy?
He has been beaten up so badly,
but he's still standing.
Are you done?
I didn't feel anything at all.
Do you want to have a go, too?
This is for my brother!
You're not afraid to die?
Darn it. Beat the girl up, too.
Stop.
That's enough.
Let's go.
That's a lesson for you.
Don't be too arrogant from now on.
Jerk, just wait and see.
Daoming Si.
Daoming Si, are you okay?
How can I be okay?
My hand
and my ribs are almost broken.
Stupid fool!
Why didn't you fight back?
Aren't there just four of them?
Based on your skills,
you could've taken them down easily.
You're really stupid.
If I fight back,
then I would lose.
I won't be able to protect you.
It's easy to deal with them,
but I had to resist it.
I couldn't fight back.
I was only thinking about one thing.
And that is to protect you.
If I die today,
don't be sad.
Don't cry, too.
Daoming Si.
Daoming Si, don't die!
I don't want you to die!
Daoming Si!
Daoming Si.
What are you doing over there?
It's too dangerous to stand there.
Can you help me?
I can't get up.
No.
Stand on your own.
Rely on your own strength to go on.
Don't you hate me?
Then don't beg me.
I hate you?
Who says that I hate you?
Daoming Si, don't do this!
Shancai.
It's great that you're finally awake.
You got me so worried.
Mom.
Where are we?
We're at the hospital.
You were carried here.
You and Daoming Si fainted
at a very remote warehouse.
That's right.
Daoming Si lost consciousness.
What exactly happened?
I was so worried.
How do you feel now?
Does it hurt anywhere?
Do you feel uncomfortable?
Shancai.
Where's Daoming Si?
Is he still alive?
Where is he now?
That's impossible.
It's too late.
Ah Si's gone.
Until the very last moment,
he was calling your name.
I couldn't believe it.
Ah Si really died just like that.
Daoming Si.
How can you die?
If you're dead, how can I apologize?
Even though you're so stupid
and your temper is really bad,
I don't want you to die.
Even though many people want you dead,
I...
Why are you so noisy?
Is this how you should treat your savior?
"I don't want you to die, Daoming Si."
My stomach hurts.
Shancai.
Your facial expression earlier was...
really amazing.
-How infuriating. I want to kill this guy.
-Come back here! Hey!
Do you want to kill me?
My ribs are all broken
and you're even sitting on me.
-Are you crazy?
-Who told you to stoop so low?
-It hurts!
-I'm sorry. It's our fault, okay?
-It's all our fault.
-We're sorry.
Don't be mad.
-It's so funny.
-Calm down.
Not bad, right? Let's go.
Have a good rest here.
Leave everything to us.
Lei, wait.
-If you find them, remember--
-All right.
I know what I should do.
Get some rest.
Let's have a look.
He wrote down how many punches and kicks
he received from each person.
I thought he had gotten more mature.
I don't think so. He's still so vengeful.
What's this?
"Leave Xiaoshun to me. That's all."
Why are you so quiet?
What kind of attitude is that?
Do you think you're so great?
Why should I be so nosy?
I risked my life
and got beaten up so badly
just to save an ungrateful virgin.
You're also a virgin.
How dare you say that.
Shut up.
You always pick fights.
Can't you say nice things
to comfort a patient?
It's because...
What is it?
It's because I had a dream.
I dreamt that you were dead.
I felt so scared.
I wondered if you were really dead.
I thought you wouldn't come and save me
after I said those things to you.
I never thought
that you would come
and save me like a stupid fool.
You were kicked and hit by those scums.
They beat you up so badly.
You even played a prank of me.
I thought you were really dead.
I'm sorry.
Stop rubbing your eyes.
You're already ugly enough.
And haven't I told you before
that even if you go to hell,
I would still go there and pursue you?
Don't struggle pointless anymore.
Stupid fool.
What does "struggle pointless" mean?
You meant, "struggle pointlessly," right?
What an idiot.
You always speak Chinese wrongly.
Are you really Chinese?
I think you should study more.
What are you laughing at?
I think you had that
pineapple-head hairstyle before
because you're too stupid.
That's why all your brain cells
went to your hair.
What's the matter?
Xiaoshun.
Haven't you done enough?
What else do you want?
Shancai, move.
Why are you here?
Don't worry.
I'm not here to do anything to you.
Are you here to apologize then?
No way.
Apologize?
I don't think I did you anything wrong.
Compared to the people
you've beaten up in Yingde University,
your wounds are nothing.
Yours pale in comparison.
How is that person now?
He transferred to a school in the South.
He's still alive.
Are you contented with what you did?
I am.
Even though using Shancai to get to you
wasn't an honorable thing to do,
I was able to teach you a lesson
on behalf of those who lived
under the shadow of your violence.
Even if I'm considered a villain
for doing so, I'm very happy.
You can go then.
You've already said
what you wanted to say.
I suggest you stop doing
these things from now on,
for your own good.
Shancai.
Actually, I came today
to apologize to you.
I wronged you terribly.
Please forgive me.
It's too late to apologize now.
You should leave.
Shancai.
If you're not the girl Daoming Si likes,
I really hope we could
still be friends someday.
The kind that really
understand each other.
I don't think it's possible now, though.
Shancai.
It's really such a pity.
Xiaoshun.
Even though what you did
can be considered as one of the top three
most cruel things
I've encountered in my life,
Daoming Si also did something wrong.
I can actually understand how you feel.
However, at this moment,
I really can't forgive you.
That guy is extraordinarily awkward.
I originally wanted to beat him up,
but now, I'm not mad anymore.
Never mind.
Maybe one day,
when time already healed all the wounds,
we can open our hearts together
and be friends again.
What do you think? Interesting, right?
Let me see.
This is so exaggerated.
How did they turn out this way?
It only took us ten minutes
to handle these guys.
They even cried and yelled for help.
They're so lame. They really suck.
Are you sure they were the ones
who beat you up, Ah Si?
That's right.
And he got beaten up so badly.
Shancai.
You...
Ah Si, who has never lost a fight,
willingly got beaten up.
That's right.
We initially thought
that he might become a convict
with his personality.
We never thought
that he would do that for you.
Though we may not understand it,
the power of love is really great.
I...
I had an examination earlier.
The doctor said I'm fine now.
I'm getting discharged today.
Bye.
Don't run away every time
we talk about this, okay?
Ah Si actually has good qualifications.
He has a few hundreds of millions
worth of assets.
It's a rare opportunity for you.
Consider it carefully, okay?
I don't love money that much.
What's so bad about money?
Think about your family, okay?
He's also very loyal.
He would never find another girl.
He's the best fighter
among the four of us.
That's not considered a good point.
You two should just marry each other.
We're already becoming
so impatient watching you guys.
Also,
when you're in danger,
he will definitely save you
no matter what happens.
I didn't ask him to come and save me.
And...
And what?
And I think Daoming Si is like a dog.
A dog?
You said I'm like a dog?
I'm such an idiot.
How can I say such a strange thing?
Why are you laughing?
A dog.
Knock it off.
He's a male beast
that's full of testosterone.
If he unleashes his savagery,
then I would be in danger.
That's not possible.
He also has a lot of good points.
No matter what you say,
he's so rich.
Besides,
weren't you terribly moved
when he came to save you?
If he doesn't really like you,
Daoming Si wouldn't do that.
I really was very moved.
Daoming Si, whose pride
is higher than Mount Everest,
was humiliated that way because of me.
This has nothing to do with that.
You don't like him,
but you're thinking of dating him.
That's so unconscientious.
Do you think I really like Daoming Si?
Does my heart beat fast
like it does with Huaze Lei?
You're so stupid.
If you don't like him,
then just break up with him.
No.
I can't sell myself out that way.
Just think of it as paying him back.
There are many ways to pay him back.
Should I give myself to him as payment?
How can I do that?
My head is going to explode.
Ah Si.
You're already discharged.
You're here.
Your ribs are connected back together.
Your ability to recover
is like that of a dog.
A dog?
Don't mind us.
Shancai must have meant
that you're as cute as a dog, okay?
That's right, that must be it.
Stop talking about dogs, okay?
Be careful or I'll kill you.
It seems you received
a serious blow this time.
You won't understand
how it feels
when a girl I risked my life to protect
said that I'm like a dog
with that expression.
She said that I'm like a dog.
That stupid girl.
I'm going to bed.
Good night.
Shancai is really stubborn, though.
Girls who emphasize that they're virgins
are especially troublesome
because they have a lot of
unrealistic notions about love.
I think so, too.
Or else, she wouldn't like
autistic people like Lei
to such an extent.
Love is that feeling
in that particular moment.
That's what makes you feel excited.
A feeling in a particular moment?
Is that so?
This is between Ah Si and Shancai.
Why are you involving me?
Didn't the magazine mention it?
That French guy who proposed to Jing
doesn't seem to have any other plans.
What do you plan to do with Jing?
What do you think?
Just wait and see.
God has His own plans.
You're such a strange person, too.
When you write the phrase
"in love" in Chinese,
it looks like "change love" instead.
I remember now.
In Chinese class
when Daoming Si was younger,
he always writes "in love"
as "change love."
There's nothing we can do now.
We can only push that idiot Shancai
to do as we wish bit by bit.
You know,
that red card doesn't seem to be from F4.
Then who is it from?
I never thought there would be
such a fearless person in our school.
How would I know?
Anyway, someone dared to use F4's name
to give Shancai a hard time.
She deserves it.
She was born with such an unlucky face.
She's so annoying.
This proves that we're not
the only ones who hate her.
Other people don't like her, too.
-Of course.
-You two are really such nags.
We're chatting among ourselves.
What does it have to do with you?
Who do you think you are?
You want to protect Shancai? Save it.
Will you die if you don't talk?
Bigmouths.
Who cares, froggy?
Did you call me a frog?
You're the one who's ugly.
You dare to call us ugly?
Look at yourself.
You only follow that poor girl Shancai
around all day.
You're an ugly toad
who lusts after a swan.
No, a dried goose.
Let me tell you.
I'm not afraid of you.
A good man doesn't fight with women.
Stop bullying Shancai.
If you don't, I'm warning you.
I won't let it go. I'm scary when I'm mad.
We want you to get mad. Bring it on.
Let's go. Come on.
I'm so envious of you.
You don't need to see that Shancai
and that big idiot earlier again.
That's right.
I'm going to a jewelry appraisal class.
How nice.
That means you can shop
to your heart's content
in the US.
Of course.
Bring some designer bags
back for me, okay?
That depends on how nice you are to me.
Shancai.
Huaze Lei.
How are you?
How are your wounds?
They're all healed.
You've really suffered this time.
How about Daoming Si?
He was discharged last night.
He's on leave today, though.
His wounds haven't completely healed yet.
-He's out of the hospital?
-Yes.
That's great.
Shancai.
Even if we all grew up with him,
this is the first time
we've seen him like this.
We can tell
that he's really serious about you.
You can also tell, right?
Do you know what I mean?
Lei.
You two look quite happy.
You're bonding behind my back.
-You two--
-You're so lame.
Aren't you on leave today?
I feel weak from sleeping so much
so I went out.
Your wounds are not
completely healed yet, right?
Why are you moving around so much?
Someone said that my ability
to recover is like that of a dog.
I told you that's just a metaphor.
What an amazing metaphor.
Did I ask your opinion, Lei?
All right, I'll go ahead then.
By the way,
I haven't told her what you asked me to.
Just tell her yourself.
I'll go ahead.
-Bye.
What is it?
Do you know what day
the 31st of this month is?
No.
You don't know?
It's my birthday.
Happy birthday then.
They always throw a party for me
on that day each year.
So, you have to bring a gift.
A gift?
Who asks for a gift themselves?
I also don't have money to buy you a gift.
Stop mentioning money all the time, okay?
But that's a fact.
You can come without a gift then.
Just come.
It's your fault this happened to me.
Just treat it like your apology to me.
My mom will be there.
I want to introduce you to her.
Your mom?
My dad can't come because of his work.
Only my mom could come home.
You're introducing me to your mom?
My god.
Daoming Si almost died because of you?
That's like a plot
from a television series.
I'm not made of stone.
Of course, I was moved.
But I'm not really sure
how I feel about Daoming Si.
He always does whatever he wants.
He's so overbearing.
I feel so much pressure because of it.
What I'm most worried about now is that
he said he'll introduce me to his mom
on his birthday at the end of the month.
-Really?
-Yes.
When rich people like them
introduce their girlfriends to their mom,
it must be really formal.
I think it would be
just like an engagement.
"Mother.
This is Miss Shancai,
the girl who I want to spend
the rest of my life with.
-She's nice, right?"
-Xiaoyou, what are you talking about?
We're not even in a relationship.
Spending the rest of our lives together?
You're so cheesy.
Congratulations, Shancai.
You'll become part
of the high society soon.
Cut it out. Stop it.
You know it's not what you think.
What I'm most worried about now
is his birthday gift.
That's right. The gift.
Have you already prepared it?
I really want to lend you some money,
but it's almost the end of the month.
I've almost used up the money
I've earned from this job.
Me, too.
There's only 200 bucks left
from my allowance this month.
I really can't go there
empty-handed, though.
You can make it yourself.
It's the thought that counts.
After your shift,
you can bake some biscuits.
What do you think?
Biscuits?
I burned them all.
Who wants to eat these?
That's all right. You still have two
to three days before the month ends.
I'm sure you can do it.
It's okay. I can help you.
You can do it.
Is it enough?
Yes, these should be enough.
Xiaoyou, do you think these look like him?
Yes, they do.
How many did you make?
One, two, three, four...
Around five or six pieces.
-If we add these...
-Are they enough?
I'm not sure.
That's okay. I'll help you make more.
Thank you.
Why are you all here?
We came to pick you up.
Why are you all dressed that way?
It's the birthday party of Daoming Si,
the heir of the Daoming family.
What are you wearing under that jacket?
My mom's dress when she was younger.
Good thing you thought of
picking her up first
or it would've been so embarrassing.
That's right. Come up with a solution.
What solution?
How would we have time
to get her ready now?
Let's go to Ah Si's house.
Why?
Zhuang must have clothes in her room.
What do you want?
What are you doing?
Hey, what are you planning to do?
Good thing you thought of using
Zhuang's dresses in her room.
Is it okay to use them
without telling her, though?
It's fine, don't worry.
Zhuang likes Shancai, too.
She knows her mom better than we do.
I think she would understand.
Shancai, what do you think of this one?
Mrs. Daoming
seems to really like this brand.
I don't think it suits her.
Shancai would look old in that.
Get your makeup done.
-What do you think of this one?
-Which one?
This one.
I don't think it suits her.
I'm afraid Mrs. Daoming would think
that Shancai is not a decent girl
if she wears that.
Why does the atmosphere feel so strange?
Why is Ximen and the others so nervous?
The Mrs. Daoming they're mentioning
is Daoming Si's mom, right?
Hey, I can just wear my own clothes.
You don't have to go through
so much trouble.
I think this black cocktail dress
looks nice.
Didn't Zhuang had this made
when she was in senior high?
Will it fit Shancai?
Isn't Shancai one size smaller
than Zhuang?
Zhuang had this made
when she was in senior high.
It should fit Shancai then.
Excuse me, wait a moment.
Can I ask
why I should dress up so nicely?
Does this birthday party
have any special meaning?
We haven't really told you.
Ah Si's mom is a very scary person.
That's right.
She's really hard to get along with.
Especially the way she treats girls.
If she finds out Ah Si
brought you there...
Besides,
Ah Si is their family's successor.
Regarding your future...
"Future"?
Your future refers to your married life.
You're the first girl
he has ever brought home.
His mom would surely see you
as his fiancée.
Fiancée?
I'm sorry, I'm going home.
Hey, knock it off.
I'm just attending his birthday party.
If we do this, there would be
a huge misunderstanding.
I'm not going anymore.
This is how it is with children
of business owners.
Our parents sent us to Yingde University
in order to prevent us from meeting
ordinary girls outside the school.
It's the same with our families, too.
If my parents find out that I'm secretly
dating girls who don't go to Yingde,
there would definitely be
a family revolution.
Our marriages have long been set
by our families as business strategies.
Even more so for Ah Si.
He's the only successor
of the Daoming Corporation.
Just imagine how important his future is.
A marriage of convenience?
That's right.
Every one of us is the same.
Why do you think we love
having fun so much?
It's because, in the end,
for our family's image,
we might marry a girl we don't love.
With that thought,
we have to have fun
while we can now, of course.
So,
just pretend to be an heiress
for Ah Si's sake today.
Please.
You know how much Ah Si treasures you.
Though it's destined that you two
won't end up together in this life,
you have to do your best.
Why are you still standing here?
Go inside.
Why took you so long? Did you just arrive?
No, we've been here for a while.
You're dressed quite elegantly today.
Ximen and the others prepared it for me.
Ximen finally did something smart.
Whatever makes you happy.
You look like an heiress today.
A fake heiress.
A fake?
Happy birthday.
Thank you.
Ah Si, happy birthday.
Thanks.
It's so heavy. What is it?
Open it and see.
Why are you being so mysterious?
Hello, Young Master Daoming Si.
I'm a commissioner from Mazda.
Happy birthday.
On behalf of our company,
we're giving you an SUV
as your birthday gift.
The car is right outside.
You can see it when you go out.
Thanks.
Happy birthday.
This should cost at least one million.
How about you?
I...
Happy birthday.
What do you mean happy birthday?
Where's my gift?
I forgot.
You forgot?
You came to my birthday party
and forgot my gift?
I'm sorry. I just forgot.
If apologizing is enough,
what do we need the police for?
Stupid girl.
Never mind. I'll introduce you to my mom.
There's no need.
There are so many people here.
Your mom won't see me.
What are you afraid of? I'm not
introducing you as my fiancee.
-Let's go.
-Idiot. What are you saying?
I don't want to go.
-Just follow me.
-No.
Your mom doesn't know me. Let me go.
Are you kidding me? Let me go.
-Huaze Lei, help.
-Let's go.
No, it's so scary!
Are you okay?
What a huge commotion.
What's the matter?
What exactly happened?
Stand up. Ah Si's mom is here.
Mrs. Daoming, long time no see.
She is...
Meizuo.
It's not your turn to speak.
Miss.
May I ask who you are?
She's Daoming Si's mom.
How terrifying.
How suffocating.
I'm sorry, I...
I'm...
Ah Si.
Is she your friend?
Yes.
Please ask her to leave.
Ah Si.
Did you hear me?
Mom.
She's a girl who's important to me.
Daoming Si, what are you saying?
How can you say that to your mom?
You must have lost your mind.
You said such a thing
in this situation.
Have you ever thought about my position?
My god.
Ah Si.
Did you say that she's important to you?
Do you know what that means?
Yes, I do.
Please wait a moment.
Mrs. Daoming.
She's our classmate in Yingde.
She's our good friend as well.
That's right. She's definitely
not some indecent girl.
Shut up, you two.
Indecent?
I'm not asking you
about those vulgar things.
I just wanted to know if her background
is a match for the Daoming family.
-Sorry.
Miss.
What's your name?
I...
My name is Shancai.
Miss Shancai.
What does your father do?
My father is...
Well...
The chairman of Muye Entertainment
is her father.
That's right.
This group has a golf course,
a forest bath, aromatherapy,
and various natural forest leisure
and entertainment facilities.
They got listed in the stock market
as a public company just recently.
Haven't you heard of them?
Why are they telling lies
that can easily be found out?
Is that so?
Then an heiress
with this kind of background
should at least know how to play
one or two musical instruments.
Which musical instruments do you know?
Can you play the piano?
Then let's ask her to play for us today
in this special occasion.
Mrs. Daoming,
she has matters to attend to,
so I think I would have to...
have to...
Don't be shy.
Play a song for us.
Mrs. Daoming, please don't do this.
If Miss Shancai did not have time
to prepare for this performance
and embarrasses herself,
isn't that too cruel?
A girl who wants to be
the daughter-in-law of the Daoming family
has to get into the social circle
sooner or later.
If she doesn't even have
the guts to do this,
what would she do then?
Please start, Miss Shancai.
Daughter-in-law? Are you kidding?
Even if the sky falls down,
that's not going to happen.
This kind of woman is going
to be my mother-in-law?
Who are you kidding?
What a joke.
A western philosopher once said,
"Women,
your gorgeous diamonds and shiny pearls
give you delusions of being a queen.
But you didn't notice
that there is only
the poison of pretension
and the aroma of arrogance.
The aroma which attracts
and also kills people.
Women,
when you pay homage to fortune,
cheer to fame,
and raise your arms to power,
please don't ask that bird
who used to sing in the past.
It has flown to a place no one knows
because its voice has dried out,
along with the doom of truth,
dignity, and pure souls."
Does the value of a person lie
in whether they can play the piano,
in which family they were born,
or what jewelry they are wearing?
What's so special about
knowing how to play the piano?
Let me tell you.
This is the only song I can play.
So what?
Happy birthday. I'll go now.
Wait.
Ah Si.
Do you have any idea what you're doing?
You don't know how to behave
according to your status.
You even lied and told me
that she's the daughter of a chairman.
You're way out of line.
It's not important to me whether or not
she's the daughter of a chairman.
Shut up!
Stop talking nonsense.
You're our only son.
You're so enamored
with such a low-class girl.
What should I tell your dad?
It was love at first sight for me.
I don't want other girls.
She's the one I like.
This joke has gone too far.
Mrs. Daoming, please don't do this.
We're not...
This is a family matter.
You don't have the right to interfere.
Leave!
Get out immediately.
You want to rebel?
Stop them!
Mrs. Daoming.
Get out of my way.
Shancai.
Your bag.
Stop right there.
I won't allow you to do this.
That's an order!
Thank you.
You were good at playing the piano.
How can you say that?
Your mom wanted me
to play the piano earlier
so that I'll embarrass myself.
Why didn't you say anything?
You also didn't help me out.
So I had to mess with the piano.
When I heard you messing with it,
I was actually quite happy.
Though I know my mom wants
to embarrass you,
I know you have a way
to embarrass my mom more.
Subtitle translation by Coleen Chua