I never expected Shancai
would get a fever.
Ever since she was little,
she rarely catches a cold.
People say that only idiots
and stupid people don't get sick.
Now we have proof
that my daughter is not an idiot.
-This is great.
-What are you talking about?
I heard something though.
They said it's easier for people
who are in love to catch a cold.
-Maybe our daughter is in love!
-In love!
-Congratulations!
Should you be saying that
at a time like this?
I'm sick.
-Oh, that's right.
-You have a fever.
-Get well first.
-That's right.
Here. I made egg porridge.
Feed her slowly.
I'm going to my part-time job.
-Go to work.
-I'm leaving now.
-I'll handle this. Come on.
-I'm leaving.
Hey!
How can you eat
your daughter's egg porridge?
That's because I can't resist the smell.
I'm so hungry, Honey.
We only eat carrots every day.
I'm not a rabbit.
Of course, you're not a rabbit.
-You're almost bald.
-Bald?
Being bald is better than being stupid,
like our neighbor.
You're not stupid.
But the problem is your daughter
is really sick,
yet you're still eating her one
and only nutritious egg porridge.
Don't you have any conscience?
Don't you know we're very poor?
We used all our money
to pay for her tuition and our rent.
You should ride out the storm with us.
Are we so poor that I can't even have
a bite of her porridge?
Of course, you can't.
-If you take a bite, I'll take one too!
-Stop.
-If you eat it, I can eat it too!
-Stop arguing!
Can you two stop arguing? I'm sick.
Do it for me.
-That's right.
-It's all your fault.
-Get out.
-Okay.
-You don't have to take care of her.
-It's all my fault.
-Go to work.
-I'll go to work. I'll do my thing.
He's even stealing porridge.
Shancai.
I've thought about it.
If you feel too much pressure,
you don't have to study
in that elite school anymore.
Really?
Yes.
I've really thought about it.
I think you should just date
that nouveau riche guy
who brought you home, Qinghe.
That would be quicker.
-I want to throw up.
-Maybe we can even save
on tuition for your elite school.
Hey, Shancai.
Do you think that makes sense?
I think it's a good idea.
Are you in a better mood today?
I heard that Shancai is sick.
What?
That Shancai is sick?
Why are you so concerned?
I'm not.
Who says I'm concerned?
I was just wondering why that kind
of person would get sick too.
I'm home.
You! Who are you?
Why are you in my house?
This is our house!
What are you trying to do?
Are you a thief?
A thief came to our house!
Why did you come to our house?
You know him, Shancai?
What are you doing in our house?
Are you trying to pull some tricks here?
Check out his gangster looks.
Look at his pineapple hairstyle
and his lifeless eyes.
You know he's not a good person.
Yes. Dad, Mom, let me tell you.
This person bullied me until I got sick.
Get him out of here now.
Oh, you jerk.
You're bullying our daughter, Shancai.
How dare you!
You have no manners!
Nobody taught you how to respect others?
Do you have a father? What's his name?
I'll call your dad about this.
My father's name is Daoming Cheng.
What?
Your dad's name is embarrassing, right?
-Speak clearly. What's his name?
-We can't hear you!
My father's name is Daoming Cheng.
Daoming Cheng.
Dad, Mom, you're so embarrassing.
Why are you kneeling down?
We're not kneeling. Our legs gave way.
Why did your legs suddenly give way?
He's Daoming Cheng's...
That guy who owns
a telecommunications company.
Two television networks, right?
Three oil factories.
Four semiconductor firms.
One hundred seventy-six
international six-star chain hotels.
And 17,845 supermarket chains
that are open for 24 hours.
That Daoming Cheng?
-That Daoming Cheng?
-Is that right?
-Yes.
But my father is not in Taiwan right now.
So you might not be able
to contact him by phone.
-That's fine.
-Of course, your father is not in Taiwan.
He's so busy. How can he be in Taiwan?
-We're the only ones in Taiwan.
Look. This is Mr. Daoming's son.
-Daoming Cheng's son is in our house.
-Comes to our house.
-How exactly...
-Our house...
Wait, let's...
-Let's think about this.
-Yes.
The way to treat our honored guest...
The way...
The way is not the universal way.
I think we should stop.
Our daughter doesn't look very happy.
Yes, let's...
What should we do then?
Let's make some tea.
Make some tea.
Young Master Daoming Si. Here, have some.
-Have some tea.
-Eat some fruits.
Please enjoy.
Hold this for me first. Here.
Mr. Daoming, this is my business card.
I'm very honored that you came
to our simple home.
Your house may be smaller
than our fish pond but it's quite cozy.
The fishes in your pond are all dead.
Shancai.
Fish pond? You're being too humble.
I think it's your swimming pool.
Swimming pool? Why are you so humble?
Don't just stand. Sit down.
Your legs would get sore
if you just stand. Drink some tea.
Have some fruits.
You're rarely here.
Come on.
Daoming Cheng's son is really different.
Look at that charisma.
And those bright eyes.
He's really the elite among elites.
The best among the best.
Right?
Looking at you, I'd think about
-England's Prince Charles.
-Prince Charles.
Can an elite like you stay and eat dinner
with ordinary citizens like us?
Dad, isn't that too much?
Why are you asking him
to eat at our house?
-Well...
-That's right.
He shouldn't just eat here.
He should spend the night over.
-What do you think?
-Mom, aren't you going overboard?
We're not close with him.
-We'll be close if he spends the night.
Well...
Why is this place so small?
Can anyone live here?
What exactly are you here for?
I heard you're sick so I paid you a visit.
They say only idiots get sick
in summer, okay?
Do you want me to punch you again?
Young Master Daoming Si, I'm sorry.
I didn't discipline my daughter well.
How can I let her hit people randomly?
I'm sorry. She doesn't know how
to respect and deal with people.
Here. Young Master Daoming Si.
I've also prepared dinner.
Here, please have a seat.
Mom, you hit me with a pan?
Yes. What else should I hit you with?
It's very oily.
You're getting a hot oil treatment
at the same time.
Mr. Daoming, please enjoy.
Our dishes are very simple.
I'm not sure if they'll suit your taste.
-What's this?
-Arden Lettuce.
Arden Lettuce.
I think your mother wouldn't cook
this kind of vegetable, right?
The chef is the one who cooks
at our humble home, not my mother.
"Humble home"?
Young Master Daoming Si.
Your mother is the Chairman's wife.
Of course, she wouldn't cook herself.
She must ask the maids to make sure
you get enough nutrition, right?
-That's right.
-No, you've misunderstood.
Mother is not the Chairman's wife,
she's also a Chairman herself.
Because she's always out of the country,
our butler's the one
who manages the maids.
-Butler.
-Who calls his own mom, "Mother"?
Are you stupid?
All right. I'll stop.
Do you need another butler?
Yes.
If the economy becomes bad,
it's going to be hard to find work.
Let's eat.
We can eat? Okay.
Eat slowly.
Eat some more.
Don't be shy.
-It's really a bit bland.
-It's good.
It's delicious.
He's so well-mannered.
He's indeed a high-society heir.
Even simple dishes are good, right?
Thank you for this wonderful dinner.
Though this house is smaller
than our fish pond.
And this table is not even half
of my bathtub.
I'm sure it is.
The dishes are only a tenth
of what they serve at my house
but they're really delicious. Thank you.
-You're done eating?
-Aren't you too shy?
I'm done.
Are you full?
Yes.
-Then...
-Wow.
This guy is so well-mannered.
He's so polite.
Go away.
You dared to do that to a girl?
You deserved it!
Who told you to be with such a tacky guy?
See how I'll deal with you two.
I can't let him fool me.
He's a really bad person.
Young Master Daoming Si,
you're going home?
Shancai, walk him out.
Why did you come to my house?
And you even pretended to be nice.
Pretend? I didn't pretend.
I really haven't tasted
those dishes before.
And they're really delicious.
Your house is so warm.
After my sister left,
I always eat alone at home.
-Every family has its own problem indeed.
-I had fun today.
There are really some things
that money can't buy.
Like a family's warmth.
Are you going to Hawaii?
I don't have any money.
Of course, I'm not going.
That's why I hate poor people.
They can't even afford NTD 50,000.
Never mind. I'll pay for you.
Why do you need to pay for me?
You're crazy.
And I'm going on a three-day cruise
around Taiwan.
Qinghe and I have already made plans.
You're going on a cruise
with nouveau riche?
That's right.
And I'm really looking forward to it.
You'll go to Hawaii.
I'll go around Taiwan.
We won't see each other
for at least a week.
I don't need to see your annoying face!
Goodbye.
Leave now.
Meizuo.
Tell the others that we won't go
to Hawaii anymore.
What?
What did you say?
Isn't it tacky to go
to Hawaii during spring time?
Let the other students go there.
Then where should we go?
Look at penguins in the South Pole
or go to Hokkaido to look at icebergs?
It's a secret.
Should we tell Lei?
Anyone can tell him.
I've already invited Jing anyway.
Will he not come?
Where exactly are we going?
It's the sea.
There are seagulls over there.
This is great!
Shancai, are you happy?
Of course, I am.
Since I entered Yingde,
I had to suppress my emotions
and be prepared to fight.
I have to be ready for war every day.
I wasn't in the mood to have fun.
I'm so happy right now.
Even the humid air feels so nice.
Shancai, look. It's the cruise.
We can go fishing at night.
How do we fish from up there?
We need to tell the captain
when we want to go fishing.
Then we'll ask him
to lower the boat a bit.
Then we can go fishing.
It's just quite dangerous to do that.
Is that true?
Of course, not.
Can't you tell I'm joking?
Your joke is not funny at all.
I'm still thankful
you brought me here, though.
This is great.
Our classmates from Yingde
should already be in Hawaii, right?
I wonder how Huaze Lei is doing.
Is he still being singled out
by Daoming Si?
That's weird. How come my dad
and the others are not here yet?
NORWEGIAN STAR
Why does that person look so familiar?
He looks like Daoming Si.
Daoming Si?
It's so hot.
That's right. Why did we come here?
It's humid and it's hot. How annoying.
Isn't that Shancai?
Why is she here?
Why is it her again?
How annoying.
What are you doing here?
Didn't you go to Hawaii?
Why would I want to go to a place
I've been to 100 times before?
I think it would be quite fun
to go on a boat.
-No way.
-You're kidding.
My dad rented this boat
to go on a pilgrimage around Taiwan.
Your dad just rented this boat.
I bought this boat.
It's mine, okay?
And let me also inform you.
I've already bought another boat
for the people in your hometown
to go on the pilgrimage.
They were so happy,
they forgot you were here.
By the way,
if you're not afraid to ruin our mood,
you can come aboard with us.
Who would want to join you?
Shancai, you two are here.
Let's board together.
There's no need. We won't join you.
Why?
Didn't you come here
to board a boat anyway?
And we'll have a party tonight.
You're welcome to join.
Join us.
Come on.
What? You're leaving me here alone.
People would laugh at me if I go home.
Wait. Please wait for me.
-Why are you still standing there?
-I thought you're leaving me.
How can I do that? Let's go.
NORWEGIAN STAR
It should be somewhere here, right?
It seems to be right ahead.
We're almost there.
Here. Room number 9001.
-The room is so big.
-It's huge.
Why is your room so big?
Then my room must be big too.
I'm going to check my room.
-Bye, see you later.
-Bye.
The sea is so big.
The air feels so nice.
-It really feels nice.
-Yes.
It's better to sit on Hawaii's beach
and watch girls while drinking, right?
Someone said he'll bring us
somewhere more fun than Hawaii.
If I only knew, I'd bring some girls here.
That's why I hate this place.
Lei, are you asleep?
Drink with Ah Si.
This place is already bad.
Isn't it even worse
with you two acting like this?
Let's drink next time.
-What are you doing?
-Nothing.
Shancai.
Jing.
Why don't you sit with us?
It's fine. I'll just walk around
with Qinghe.
Okay.
Don't forget to join the party tonight.
What? I didn't bring
an outfit for that though.
She didn't bring one?
She doesn't have one.
That's right.
It's fine. I'll lend you my clothes.
There's no need.
That would be embarrassing.
It's okay.
It'd be more fun if there are more people.
But...
I'm going fishing
with Qinghe tonight, right?
What?
I see.
Hey, Mrs. Dong.
Shancai? Wait a moment.
Excuse me. I'll just take this call.
-It's fine.
-Hello.
Mom.
Shancai, you have to grab
the opportunity with Qinghe.
Stop saying weird things.
Let me tell you that Qinghe
and I aren't the only ones on the boat.
Our classmates are here too.
Do you want me to grab
the opportunity with all of them?
Then is that Dao guy there?
Yes. So, what?
That's great.
I let you study in Yingde
so that you can become Cinderella.
That big fish is also there today.
-Catch it--
-You're such a nag. I'm hanging up.
I'll let your dad talk to you.
Shancai.
You caught a big fish?
Let me have more allowance, okay?
What kind of parents are you?
My phone!
Cool.
She's got an attitude.
Your hair is so nice.
It's so straight and shiny.
Did Huaze Lei
and Daoming Si make up already?
I don't think so.
Ah Si's personality is more childish.
And he's overbearing sometimes.
We forced Lei to come here.
I hope they can make up here.
Your skin is so nice.
You'll look really pretty with make-up on.
I'll choose a cocktail dress
for you later.
Then I'll get you all glammed up
and surprise all of them.
Jing.
Isn't it inappropriate for me
to dress up like this?
How come? You look beautiful.
Really.
Let's go.
Folks.
Look.
What do you think?
She's beautiful, right?
Is that the poor girl Shancai
who's always in braids?
Jing. Why are you so nice to Shancai?
It's so infuriating.
That's right. What is she doing?
You look cute.
You look nice all dressed up.
Everyone's attention is on me.
I'm just like the princess in fairy tales.
Shancai.
You look really beautiful
dressed like this.
Thank you.
Shancai. May I have the honor
of dancing with you?
I don't know how to dance though.
It's fine. I can teach you.
Thank you.
Shancai, can I dance with you?
This is a dream.
Like that of Cinderella's.
I just hope the bell won't ring
when the clock strikes at midnight.
She's way out of line.
F4 is everyone's dream.
That girl didn't only dance
with Ximen and Meizuo.
Now, she's even dancing with Huaze Lei.
Stop it. I've had enough.
How can we let
that poor girl steal our spotlight?
Baihe, have another drink.
What are you planning?
Everyone, it's 11:59 p.m.
Let's play a special game
for 10 seconds, okay?
It's the exciting kissing game
in the dark.
Anyone can freely kiss
anyone they want in the dark.
Let's start now.
Begin.
-Who pushed me?
-Turn on the lights.
Where's Daoming Si?
What's going on?
What are you doing?
-Where's Daoming Si?
-Turn on the lights.
Where's Ximen?
How come it's you?
I thought it's Daoming Si.
Why did you come over here?
You were the one who grabbed me.
Where's the sea?
Shancai.
I kissed Daoming Si.
I didn't know who pushed me earlier.
Turns out it was you.
Shancai, that girl...
-Did you kiss Daoming Si?
-Shut up!
I don't want to hear it!
-You...
-What are you looking at?
She initiated it.
I kissed a pig!
That was your first kiss, right?
I never thought...
You never kissed anyone before.
And your first time is with me.
You were so daring.
You must be touched, right?
Do you want to set the mood a bit?
-Let's do it one more time.
-Don't come near me!
I'm being punished by God.
It's all because I'm dressed up
in a way I shouldn't be
and forgot who I am.
I was even so excited
to come to such a place.
Cinderella?
A dream?
It's all just wishful thinking.
When the bell rang at midnight,
not only am I not a princess anymore,
I even kissed a pig!
Why am I blushing?
Why are you two suddenly standing
so straight and blushing like tomatoes?
Because they kissed last night.
That's not true, is it?
Daoming Si.
I don't know. She suddenly ran towards me.
I'm really bothered by it.
How tacky.
Her strategy is really despicable.
Taking advantage of the mess,
that girl even made the first move.
That's right. She's so vulgar.
That's not what happened.
Someone tripped me last night.
He happened to be standing in front of me.
You don't have to explain to me.
It doesn't matter to me who you kiss.
You're even trying to reason out?
Lei, don't believe what this girl says.
She's very manipulative.
Where are you going?
I'm really such a fool.
I thought Huaze Lei would come
to my rescue.
That's right.
Shancai.
Open the door.
What do you want? I want to sleep.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
I'll go find you later.
Okay.
Regardless of what happened,
Jing still gave me the Cinderella's dream.
I have to return the dress to her.
And formally thank her.
Hey, Daoming Si!
You dare to bully Shancai.
Let's have a match.
This is what we'll compete for.
Holding our breath.
See who can hold
their breath longer underwater.
Do you dare to do that?
Are you ready?
We'll jump on the count of three.
-One.
-Get ready? Are you a kid?
You're very disappointed, right?
Why?
Because Shancai's not here.
Why do you care about her so much?
You really like her, right?
I realized it
when you had a fight with Daoming Si
that day because of her.
Actually, I'm a little bit jealous.
Because you're no longer the Lei
that only belongs to me.
When you were dancing with her last night,
that's how I felt too.
If you say so.
What else do you want to say?
"I think you two look good together"?
Lei.
Why are you smiling?
You know, you always say one thing
and do another.
You're always so nice
and takes care of everyone.
And you maintain
your heiress image very well.
Even if someone gets hurt
because of your inconsistent acts,
you don't care.
Lei.
I really didn't mean to do that.
Stop playing around with me.
You say I like Shancai.
Then let me tell you.
You're the one I like.
I can't move.
My last ounce of strength left me.
I became as heavy as this boat.
Shancai.
Shancai your face!
Why am I here?
You fainted underwater
in less than three seconds.
Bro, you can't even swim
and you dared to compete with me?
That doesn't count. Let's do it again.
You do it yourself. I'm hungry.
I want to eat something.
Daoming Si, wait for me. Daoming Si!
Daoming Si, I lost to you on that one.
Let's compete for something else.
Are you sure I'll lose to you?
We can arm wrestle or run a race.
Let me find something to eat first, okay?
Stop nagging.
All right. I'm hungry too.
Why is there only wine?
Why there is no food in here?
The kitchen.
Let's go to the kitchen.
Why is there nothing here?
Can't you ask the chef to cook for you?
That's boring.
I want to see
if I can make some food on my own.
By the way, I brought fishing rods.
We can go fishing.
I'm really good at it.
We're so high up. How can we go fishing?
We can take a small boat and go.
Hey.
That's a good idea.
What should we do now?
This was your great idea.
How would I know
that there's no fire in the kitchen?
I got stung.
Why are you complaining
about a wound so small?
Shancai is braver than you.
You're saying this like you know her
really well.
Of course I do.
Shancai and I have been classmates
from primary school to junior high school.
And the Shancai I know
would never let anyone bully her.
And she won't allow her classmates
to be bullied too.
When we were in junior high,
she was bullied because of our classmate.
And those people even got a local gangster
and they beat her up so badly.
She didn't even cry.
That's how she spent her years
in junior high.
I heard it was the same for senior high.
Can you still find that local gangster?
Who knows where they are now?
She's really a cheerful and strong girl.
She's nice to everyone.
That's why she has a lot
of friends around her.
I don't like to drink
the milk from our school meals.
She'll always drink it for me,
even though she gets diarrhea every time.
So you know how important I am to her.
I think she just likes to drink it
because she's poor.
Of course, not.
She's a thoughtful and considerate girl.
Do you like Shancai?
No.
It's a shame though.
That girl likes me now.
You're lying.
Who says I'm lying?
You saw it at the party last night.
She came over to kiss me.
And she even held me really tight.
Her lips were so soft.
You're lying.
How dare you throw ice at me?
You're lying. You're a liar!
Don't run!
Come over here!
-Shut up!
-Get your hands off me!
Don't touch me!
Get lost!
Get your hands off her!
Huaze Lei.
I said get your hands off her.
I'm sorry I said those things earlier.
Because I was just...
It doesn't matter.
I'm not interested
in other people's business.
When your tears are about to fall,
you can do a handstand
to stop them from flowing.
Did you get it?
It's really beautiful though.
You say I like Shancai.
Then let me tell you.
You're the one I like.
Don't run!
-Shancai!
-Don't run!
Shancai, help! Shancai.
Shancai.
Daoming Si keeps chasing me.
Why is Daoming Si chasing you?
We caught a lot of fish, but this guy...
Who are you calling "this guy"?
Cut it out.
Why did you two go fishing?
We're hungry and he didn't
want to ask the chef to cook for us.
So we can only go fishing.
Daoming Si.
You disgusting guy!
You must be thinking about
kissing Shancai again, right?
What? Who do you call a disgusting guy?
Who's disgusting?
-Don't run!
-How nice.
At a night like this,
it's a good thing that I'm not alone
to continue thinking about sad things.
Though that jerk Daoming Si
was the one who barged in here,
it feels a bit different from usual.
Go away! It hurts!
Cut it out!
Stop hurting him!
What are you two idiots doing?
Stop it.
What's the matter, Lei?
What? Don't you mind at all?
Lei.
I really don't mind.
In fact, I'm so happy right now.
This means I'm very important to you.
I forget that Lei's a boy, too.
No.
This is not what I want.
Don't worry.
Sometimes, you need
to let things happen naturally.
No.
I don't want this.
Jing.
I didn't know you're all here.
Get down and grab something to eat.
Ximen, get up.
Meizuo, get up. Hurry up, get down
and grab yourself something to eat.
Qianhui.
Get up.
Hurry up, let's eat.
Ah Si.
Is this some kind of joke?
What are you thinking?
Look at what you're wearing.
Go ahead and eat my sashimi.
I caught the fish myself.
Sashimi.
Oh, my gosh.
There must be something else
you could do, right?
That's why I hate virgins the most.
What? Daoming Si's still a virgin?
You talk too much.
How can I do those things
with a girl I don't like?
You annoying jerks.
Grab a chair and sit with us.
-Okay.
-Yeah.
Give me the chopsticks.
Since we're all here,
I'll give you a riddle, okay?
-What riddle?
-Okay.
-The riddle is "kiss".
-Pass the chopsticks over here.
-"Kiss"?
-Guess a location.
-A location?
-Yeah.
A location for the kiss?
What else?
You'd better be careful with your answer.
Do you already know the answer?
No, I don't.
Has anyone guessed it yet?
I'll tell you the answer now.
The answer is "Jiji" train station.
It's so funny, right?
Because you'll make "Jiji" sounds
when you kiss.
Isn't it funny?
Your joke is so lame.
Subtitle translation by Coleen Chua