["Round and Round" playing on speakers]
[in Korean]
♪ We will go hand in hand ♪
♪ And have fun jumping around ♪
- ♪ Round and round ♪
- [platform clunks]
[woman in English on PA] Ten players.
- [tense music playing]
- [man 1] Here! We need two people!
[players clamoring]
- How many are with you?
- There's four.
- So, that would get us to nine.
- You said you had five?
We're five, that makes ten.
Here, come with us.
Hold on! Hold on! We have five too.
Come with us, hurry!
Come with us! Let's go!
[clamor continues]
We're running out of time.
We need to go, Gi-hun.
[Hyun-ju] We need one more!
Now we have ten!
[Gi-hun] Room 44! The light-green room!
- [Dae-ho] I see it! The light-green one!
- [Gi-hun] Go, 44! Room 44!
[Yong-sik] Right there! Run!
We gotta go, Mom, get in.
Come on, go, go, go.
[timer beeping]
- [timer beeps]
- [latch clacks]
- [dark music plays]
- [clamor continues]
[man 1] Don't shoot.
Don't shoot me, please!
[gunshots]
[player screams]
[man 2] Please don't kill me.
Please don't kill me!
[gunshot]
- [body thuds]
- [Gi-hun breathing shakily]
Every person here owes me their lives!
[Jung-bae]
You almost gave me a heart attack.
[Jung-bae sighs]
You've lived longer
than you were ever meant to,
and now I finally see why.
You're here for a reason.
You were drawn by destiny.
[eerie music playing]
[groaning]
[forklift beeping]
[woman on PA] The following players
have been eliminated:
Player 013, Player 043, Player 049,
Player 054, Player 060, Player 68…
["Round and Round" playing on speakers]
SQUID GAME 2
EPISODE 6
O X
[in Korean]
♪ Round and round ♪
♪ Let's go around in circles and dance ♪
♪ We will clap our hands and sing ♪
♪ La-la-la-la, let's have fun dancing ♪
♪ Ring-a, ring-a, ring-a
Ring-a, ring-a-ring ♪
♪ We will go hand in hand ♪
♪ And have fun jumping around ♪
- ♪ Round and round ♪
- [platform clunks]
- [players gasp]
- [woman in English on PA] Four players.
- [tense music playing]
- [players clamoring]
- No… I thought we were--
- Gyeong-su, you're out!
- [Min-su] Gyeong-su.
- Let's go! Whoo!
- [Nam-gyu] Hell yeah.
- [Min-su] Gyeong-su…
[clamor continues]
[Seon-nyeo] Hold on. No!
- It's okay! You four go!
- [In-ho] I'll leave!
I'll be okay. You guys go. Hurry.
- I need three people!
- [Dae-ho] Are you sure?
- [In-ho] Three!
- We don't have a choice.
- Young-il.
- [In-ho] Anyone have three? I need three!
Whoo!
- [Dae-ho] Young-il's gonna be okay, right?
- [woman on PA] Ten, nine,
eight, seven, six, five,
- four, three…
- Here! Two more!
- [Jung-bae] Gi-hun.
- [woman on PA] …two, one.
- [timer beeps]
- [latch clacks]
[all panting]
Hey, dude, can you see
what happened to Gyeong-su?
- [groans]
- Listen up you shithead.
Don't call me "dude."
We're not friends, got it?
Or next time you'll get the axe.
[Thanos] Hold on, wait!
Where'd you leave Gyeong-su?
Where the hell is he?
- [gunshots outside]
- Holy shit!
[players screaming]
[Thanos] Gyeong-su!
[gunshots continue]
[grunts]
[dark music playing]
It's okay. I don't think they noticed.
[monitor beeps]
[masked manager on radio]
Room 33, eliminated.
[breath trembling] What? What…
[whimpering]
No… Hold on, wait. Wait!
[rapid gunfire]
[latches opening]
[doors open]
[squelching underfoot]
[chilling music playing]
[Min-su breathing heavily]
[Thanos] Hey, Min-su!
Come on, my boy. Come on.
- Mr. Young-il!
- [Jung-bae] Young-il?
[In-ho] Gi-hun!
[Dae-ho] Young-il!
[Jung-bae] Oh, thank God! There you are.
- [In-ho] Whoa.
- I knew you'd make it, man.
It's good to see you.
This guy was something special. [laughs]
I was worried for a second.
Glad you made it.
People say I'm pretty friendly,
so, you know,
- I do all right in these kind of games.
- [other chuckle]
- Oh. How are you feeling, Jun-hee?
- I'm all right, thank you.
We're all really glad to see you.
Hold on, I just realized.
If we have to form
groups of six next round,
then we won't need anyone else.
Why?
- Oh, 'cause the baby?
- [In-ho laughs]
- Ah! That's a good point.
- [all laughing]
[dark music playing]
[Dae-ho] You're right.
But wait, what if it's twins?
- [Jung-bae] Then we'd be seven.
- [laughter]
[woman on PA] Attention, all players.
Please step onto the platform
in the center of the arena.
[Masked Officer] Start the round.
[in Korean]
♪ Round and round ♪
♪ Let's go around in circles and dance ♪
♪ We will clap our hands and sing
La-la-la… ♪
[woman in English on PA] Three players.
- [tense music playing]
- [Young-mi] What do we do?
Let's split up
and each find a third person.
Wait, how do we… How do we do that?
Choose one, dude! Come on!
- They'll play for it.
- What?
- Rock, paper, scissors!
- Let's go together.
[both] Winner stays the loser goes.
Rock, paper, scissors!
[Nam-gyu] Oh!
Shit, Min-su with the scissors!
Min-su, you win!
- Come on, my boy!
- [Nam-gyu] Min-su. Go, go, go!
- You three, go.
- [In-ho] Go!
- Move!
- [Gi-hun] Find a room!
- One more! Anyone!
- One more!
- We need one more!
- We have two!
- Just one more.
- One person!
Over here, we need one!
One person, right here!
[Player 172] Come with us! Hurry!
[Player 220] Do you want us to die?
[Yong-sik] What are you doing? Let go!
That's my mom!
[Yong-sik struggling]
Mom!
[dark music playing]
[breath trembling]
[tense music playing]
- [timer beeps]
- [latch clacks]
- [players screaming, clamoring]
- [gunshots]
[woman on PA] The following players
have been eliminated:
Player 034, Player 038,
Player 104, Player 109,
- Player 291, Player 309, Player 335…
- [forklift beeping]
…Player 345, Player 347…
Are you doing all right?
Oh. Oh, yes. Thank you both.
I would've died
if it weren't for you gentlemen.
Do you know where your son went?
Sorry?
Wasn't he with you?
Ah!
Oh, right. [chuckles]
We got a little separated at the start.
It's stupid, it really is.
We needed one more person,
so I waited while he looked around.
And I guess I got a little mixed up,
you know?
He didn't come get you?
[dark music playing]
How dare you, sir.
He wouldn't leave me, not my son.
He didn't grow up with a lot,
but I know deep down he's a good person.
Even though he got bullied
and knocked around,
he never laid a hand on anyone
or beat other kids up, not once,
so don't you badmouth my son!
Forgive me.
I didn't know what I was talking about.
[sighs]
[doors open]
Hey, welcome back, my friends.
[Nam-gyu] Skrrt!
[players murmuring indistinctly]
- [Young-mi] Miss Geum-Ja!
- [gasps]
[Geum-ja] Oh! Thank goodness.
I'm so glad you're both all right.
- Look at you. You're not hurt, are you?
- [Hyun-ju] No.
Uh, this man saved us.
We didn't think we were gonna find anyone.
And then,
Player 246 rescued the two of us.
Like a knight in shining armor!
Look at you! As handsome as a knight too.
Thank you so much.
Don't thank me.
These two,
they're actually the ones who saved me.
Where's Yong-sik?
- He…
- [Yong-sik] Mom.
[sorrowful music playing]
[breath trembling]
It's okay. I'm alive. I made it.
- [choking up]
- Are you all right? Are you hurt?
Mom…
I'm sorry.
I really didn't…
- [sobbing] Mom, I'm sorry, I--
- No, no. It's okay.
- I'm so sorry. How could I leave you…
- Honey. No, it's okay.
It's okay, we're both here.
- [Yong-sik] How could I do that?
- It's okay.
We're both here, that's what matters.
[Yong-sik weeping] I'm so sorry, Mom.
Mom…
["Round and Round" playing on speakers]
[in Korean]
♪ Round and round ♪
♪ Let's go around in circles and dance ♪
- [platform rumbles]
- [woman in English on PA] Six players.
- [tense music playing]
- Four women and two men, go!
- Wait, which two?
- My mom and I stay together.
I'll go.
- [In-ho] Fine, get moving.
- Move it! Go!
Hey! Two people, over here! Two people.
Over there!
- Shit.
- What the--
- Get the hell out!
- [other yelling]
Here! Quick!
This one is empty! Hurry! Come on!
[woman on PA] Ten,
nine…
- [Young-mi yelps]
- [woman on PA] …eight,
seven, six…
- Wait. Where's Young-mi?
- [Young-mi] Unnie!
- [woman on PA] …four, three…
- Young-mi!
…two, one.
- [timer beeps]
- [latch clacks]
[sobbing] Unnie.
Young-mi! Young-mi!
- Young-mi!
- [whimpering]
Young-mi! Young-mi!
[gunshot]
- Young-mi…
- [body thuds]
- [sinister music playing]
- No.
[screaming] No! Young-mi! Young-mi!
- Oh, no. No! Young-mi!
- Young-mi!
[Geum-ja weeping] No! Yong-sik, she's…
- Not Young-mi, no, she can't be…
- You! It's your fault!
Are you kidding me?
If I hadn't come in,
you would all have died.
It's your fault!
I still had time, I could've saved her!
That's not true. The door was gonna lock!
The second you went out
they would've shot you like they shot her!
Then we'd be down one
and the rest of your team
would've died too!
I saved your lives,
don't you understand that?!
All of you, tell your friend it's true!
Just admit she was gonna die!
It's true.
You wouldn't make it back in here.
Yeah. There wasn't enough time.
[sobbing]
[latch opens]
Thanks, Jun-hee.
Let's not get confused.
All I did was say you were right.
[woman on PA] Attention, players.
The final round will now begin.
["Round and Round" playing on speakers]
[in Korean]
♪ Round and round… ♪
[in English] What number do you think
we're gonna get next?
[In-ho] Two.
- Wait, why?
- [dark music playing]
We're at 126 people,
and there are 50 rooms.
Even if there's two in every room,
then there's still only enough
for 100 of us.
If you don't find one fast,
you're done for.
- [platform rumbles]
- [tense music playing]
[woman on PA] Two players.
[players clamoring]
- [Jung-bae] Gi-hun.
- [Yong-sik] Ready?
[Dae-ho] Come on, Gi-hun.
Let's go!
- [Thanos gurgling]
- [Nam-gyu screams]
[imperceptible]
- [woman screams]
- [man groans]
[woman yelling]
Close it!
Hey! No!
[In-ho] Get in! Get in!
Out.
But we were here before you guys.
- [fist striking]
- [Player 285] Open the fucking door!
I was here first!
- [Jung-bae-grunting]
- [woman on PA] Nine, eight,
seven, six,
five, four,
- three, two…
- [neck snaps]
- …one.
- [timer beeps]
[latch clacks]
- The final round is now over.
- [gunshots]
[panting]
[eerie music playing]
[player whimpering]
[hatch opens]
[hatch closes]
Once we all get back, somebody should
go around and do a head count.
[In-ho] Why?
If we figure out
what the X and O split is,
then we'll know which of the two sides is
gonna have a better shot at the next vote.
Guess we have to hope
more "O"s died than we did.
[drone whirring]
By the way,
what was this contraption called, again?
It's a drone. A drone.
"Drome"? Ain't that something!
When we used to go out,
you always had to
keep checking your binoculars
and climb all those cliffs
just to get a look at an island.
This makes our lives so much easier.
Get us even lower.
They know we're looking for them.
- They might've upped their camouflage.
- Got it.
But still, if you couldn't find this place
after two years of looking,
what makes you think you could do it now?
If we eliminate
everywhere I've already been,
then we can narrow down the search.
We'll find it,
as long as the weather cooperates.
That's right.
We have Captain Ko's boat now too.
And this "drome" thing.
Captain, it's a drone, okay? Not a drome.
Who gives a shit.
My little boy, Min-su!
I'm so happy to see you again, bro.
Yo, Min-su, I was worried about you, dude.
I thought I was running with you.
But when I turned around,
it was this asshole.
It's like I told you, man.
He won't go down easy.
And you saw him, right?
Se-mi was like this,
and I thought he froze up.
And then scissors outta nowhere.
That's when I went,
"Whoa, this boy's crazy."
Yo! Ooh, I fucking got chills, Min-su.
Let's play one more game, okay?
[Nam-gyu] One more, right, bro?
All right, make it quick.
What do you want?
Jun-hee,
once we get out, I'd like to start over.
"Start over"?
How do we do that?
Trust me one last time, okay?
And we'll have our child,
and start a whole new life.
I did a rough estimate, and based on that,
I think each person
will make 300 to 400 million.
That's gotta convince a lot of people.
I think we could win the next vote.
And if we do,
what happens?
So we'd have a lot
if we put our shares together.
I could use that
to pay off a few debts first,
then I'll find something new
to invest the rest in.
No more crypto, no more coins.
Listen, there's this whole crew
of stockbrokers that I know.
Their thing is trading futures
and Inverse ETFs.
Their returns broke 100% just last month.
So you don't need me or our child.
All you need is the cash.
No, Jun-hee, it's not like that.
I just want us to have enough
so the three of us can live a more--
"Enough"?
And exactly how much is that?
Huh?
Pay off your debts
with your own damn money.
'Cause I'm gonna use mine
to raise our child.
[sighs] Jun-hee.
[Thanos rapping] ♪ Min-su, Nam-su
Gyeong-su,Thano-su! ♪ [gurgling]
Yo. Yo. Yo. Check them out.
[Myung-gi] Look at me, I'm serious.
All I wanna do is make a good life…
- What's their deal?
- I guess they're a thing.
[Thanos scoffs] He snagged a girl in here?
Smooth little shit.
[Seon-nyeo]
You shouldn't wallow in heartbreak.
- [mystical music playing]
- There's no point.
You're going to see her again,
sooner than you might think.
You and your friends have all been cursed.
Today I sat and pleaded,
asking the gods of heaven and earth
to help put an end to your existences.
And to let me watch
as each of you perish in this hellhole.
This is where it ends for you.
There's no escaping now.
You're going to die
miserable, excruciating deaths.
One by one, in front of each other's eyes.
[Geum-ja exhales]
What…
[scoffs] She's no shaman.
Well, that lady,
she's just totally insane.
Oh, God.
[spitting]
Come on, you too. [spitting]
Hey, Gi-hun. There are still 55 "O"s here.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah, I counted twice.
What about you? Did you count yourself?
Then there are 56.
Ah, shit.
56 minus 44… That's 12 more.
[sighs] It's gonna be hard
for us to win another vote.
[In-ho] That might sound like a lot,
but if just six of them
change their minds,
it'll be 50/50.
And if somehow we can get seven,
we might even win.
Yeah, but a few of the "X"s could also
change their minds and vote "O" now.
If they pressed "X" last time,
I'm willing to bet
they won't change sides.
Why's that?
When they voted to go home,
they were fine with less money.
Now their share of the prize money's
even higher.
It wouldn't make sense for them
to put their lives at risk
by playing another game.
[Jung-bae]
I'm definitely pressing X this time.
If five other people do the same,
then we have a tied vote.
And if it's six, we win.
Then we should try talking to the "O"s
over on their side,
see if we can change their minds.
- No, it's too dangerous.
- [dark music playing]
Most of those guys want to keep going
till the last game, no matter the cost.
If we try something, they're not
gonna sit back and let it happen.
What do you suggest we do then?
Just keep our mouths shut and pray
everyone over there changes their vote?
And if we lose, what happens?
Then what the hell do we do?
Do we all hold hands and keep playing?
Look, I know how you feel.
I wanna get out of here just like you,
but what we need to do now
is just breathe and focus.
Breathe and focus?
We've gone through this two times
and we're still here.
If we can't change their minds,
then we need to drag them over to our side
and finally finish this!
If we try forcing them now,
it could spark a confrontation
and things might get violent.
Do you really want that to happen?
[Gi-hun sighs]
Gi-hun, he's right.
I'm too scared to do any more of this.
And there's gotta be other people here
who feel that way.
Okay, here's what I think.
If all we need to win
is another five or six people,
then we should just vote like normal.
And I did the math.
The total's over 300 million.
With that much, I think we have
a pretty good shot at winning the vote.
- [doors opening]
- [alarm buzzing]
[masked manager] You have made it through
yet another game in the series.
Congratulations to you all.
Now, if I may have your attention,
I will announce the results
of the third game.
[remote beeps]
Wait, hang on.
Can you go back over that same area?
Yeah.
Look. Beneath the trees.
There's something there.
[Woo-seok] Yeah, what the…
Is it like a hatch? Go a little lower.
[drone pilot]
I can't. Not with those trees there.
Guess we'll have to go by foot.
Hey, everyone, let's move out!
[Jung-bae] 356 million.
Okay, that's good.
That'll make some people
change their minds, I'm sure.
Six more, and we'll have a tie.
With seven we win, right?
[masked manager]
We will once again conduct the vote
in reverse order from highest to lowest.
Player 456, please cast your vote.
To ensure this process
remains fair and democratic,
starting now, disruptive acts of any kind
are strictly prohibited.
We appreciate your cooperation.
[beeps]
[intense music playing]
[beeping]
[masked manager] Player 388.
Now all that we need are six more.
[Gi-hun sighs]
[beeps]
[masked manager] Player 380.
[breathing deeply] Now just five more.
- [masked manager] Player 377.
- Ah, fucking bitch.
[masked soldier] Number 011.
You really should've started playing ball
with us sooner, you know?
Wouldn't have had to scratch up
that pretty face of yours.
Keep up the good work, huh? [snickers]
[door opens]
[breathing heavily]
[beeps]
[masked manager] Player 230.
[intense music playing]
- [beeps]
- Mwah!
"O" Gang for the win! Let's go!
[beeping]
We just need four more.
If we get four more, then we win.
[masked manager] Player 149.
If you pull that stupid shit
this time around,
I swear to god
I'm gonna hang myself right here.
Yeah, I got it.
[beeps]
[masked manager] Player 145.
Min-su. Just one more game.
Yo, he and I had a little chat earlier.
One more game, right, dude?
A billion, and then we leave.
[beeps]
[masked manager] Player 125.
You got this, Min-su. Ready?
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
[intense music playing]
[beeps]
- [Dae-ho and Jung-bae gasping]
- Holy shit!
- We need three more, that's all.
- Just three.
[masked manager] Player 124.
[sighs]
[beeps]
[masked manager] Player 120.
[ominous music playing]
[sighs]
[beeps]
[Dae-ho and Jung-bae gasping]
That's it. Two more. Two more!
- [masked manager] Player 119.
- Here we go. Two more.
Just two more people to go.
[suspenseful music playing]
Looks like it leads
to somewhere underground.
Check it.
[mercenaries scream]
- [explosion]
- [Woo-seok gasps]
[beeps]
[players cheer]
[intense music playing]
[masked manager] Player 015.
[beeps]
[Jung-bae] He switched,
he changed his vote. He pressed "X." Oh!
That's the sixth person.
That means we're tied.
- Okay, okay.
- Just one more and we win.
Are we… are we really going home?
[masked manager] Player 009.
[beeps]
[players cheer]
It's okay. She just voted the same way.
[masked manager] Player 007.
Ma'am, are you sure?
Your son's really gonna vote to go?
I'm telling you, I know my son.
My Yong-sik's a good person,
and he'll do the right thing.
- [beeps]
- [players cheer]
[Dae-ho] He did it! He changed his vote!
We're done! It's over!
Let's get outta here!
That's right, Yong-sik! That's my son!
- [masked manager] Player 006.
- That was it. He was the seventh one.
We're good now. They're both on our side.
We did it!
[dark music playing]
Hey, Gi-hun.
Huh?
I'm worried about Young-il.
Why?
During the game, we were paired together.
- [beeps]
- [players cheer]
That was great.
Nice work, you made the right choice!
- [players cheering]
- We got this! [laughs]
[masked manager] And finally, Player 001.
Please cast your vote.
[intriguing music playing]
[Dae-ho] All right, Young-il.
You got this.
Hey, guys. I guess it's a 50/50 split.
A tie's better than nothing, right?
Right.
[Jung-bae] I don't know, but Young-il…
He scares me a little.
Why?
[Jung-bae] It… it's just that he…
I'm not sure how to bring this up,
but during the game,
when we were in our room together…
- I saw him mur-- [gasps]
- [beeps]
[players cheer]
[players sigh, laugh in relief]
[sighs]
We did it. We're good.
It's a tie, we're okay!
[masked manager] The final player has made
their choice, and the vote is now over.
All right, fine, we wound up with a tie.
So what the hell happens now?
Clause three of the consent form:
Should the initial vote result in a tie,
the players will vote again.
Hold on. When's the next vote?
How long do we have to wait?
To ensure you have enough time
to properly consider your options,
the second vote
will be conducted tomorrow.
Until then, please take this opportunity
to think carefully about your future.
[players murmuring]
[ominous music playing]
[body thuds]
Listen, boys,
don't you think we should return to land?
Isn't this game gonna be over
if we don't find that island
in a few days?
Yeah, but hold on.
Just look at him. He needs a doctor.
How're you doing?
You can push through it, right?
Yes, sir. Can't complain.
The bleeding stopped,
and I stitched him up,
so he should be good.
Okay, but even so,
one of your men just died.
[Kim] Let's keep searching.
He's never gonna rest in peace
until we kill the bastards who did this.
But just think.
If these traps were set up for us already,
then they know where we are
and where we're going.
[Jun-ho sighs]
We use a new radio frequency every day
from now on.
Cell phone use is completely banned.
Is that clear?
- Got it.
- Yes, sir.
Can you radio the other boat?
What were you trying
to tell me about before?
[Jung-bae] Hmm?
You know, about Young-il.
During the game earlier.
- [In-ho] Here, you want some of mine too?
- [Dae-ho] Thanks. I'm okay.
- [Jung-bae sighs]
- Not bad, right? They're decent, for once.
Nothing. It's not him, it's just…
It's all of this.
We gotta get out as soon as we can.
If I stay any longer,
I'll start losing it too.
[Dae-ho] You know, Young-il,
I gotta be honest with you.
I thought for a second there,
you'd vote like the first time.
Ah, I got so anxious when you went up,
I couldn't watch anymore. [chuckles]
'Cause earlier, Jung-bae kept trying
to tell us this weird story--
Hey, come on, eat your food.
Aren't you hungry?
Young-il, thank you, man.
You gave us all another chance.
I just wanted to save my own ass,
don't thank me.
And anyway,
there's enough money in there now.
So I should get out.
While I can.
But when we vote tomorrow,
do we really think we'll win?
I mean, there's no other choice.
Like Gi-hun was saying earlier,
we should try to convince them.
See if we can get
a few of them to change sides,
before they call the next vote.
Do you think we can?
Look at them over there.
You know they've gone
completely crazy with greed.
[sighs] Here's how I see it.
We have the advantage.
We've only had
these gimbap rolls to eat today.
Everyone will be hungry
when they wake up tomorrow.
And when you're hungry,
it makes you feel homesick.
That means everyone will want to leave.
Hey, guys!
Are you really gonna sit over there
eating this dry gimbap?
I just need one person to walk over here
so that tomorrow morning
we can get the heck out of here
- and all go out for Hanwoo beef.
- [Geum-ja laughs]
And what the hell,
I'll cover everyone's meals!
And we'll order naengmyeon too.
Dessert's on me.
Come on, just one of you guys!
- We won't bite!
- [players shouting]
Once you bastards
all kick the bucket in the next game,
we can leave this place
with 800 million each.
With that kind of money,
I'll just head to a Hanwoo ranch
and offer to buy it!
- [laughter]
- Over here!
- That's right! Come on, guys!
- [Jeong-dae] Come with us.
800? Bullshit. You're lying to yourselves.
You guys really believe
you'll survive the next one?
If we don't stop now,
then everyone over there's gonna die!
Okay, so let's stay
and test that theory out.
See which side loses more.
Instead of just running away
like some fucking wussie.
[chuckles] What'd you say? Huh?
What'd you call me?
- Hey, wait.
- Hey, dipshit, say that again.
- Come on.
- [Dae-ho] I'll fuck you up.
- [Jung-bae] Don't threaten civilians.
- Go on.
Look, dumbass, I was a fuckin' Marine!
[players laugh mockingly]
Oh, yeah? Okay, well, if you're a Marine,
then I'm fucking Special Forces,
you lying shit.
You really wanna go there?
If you wanna leave so bad,
why stuff your faces with gimbap, huh?
- It'll be quicker if you starve!
- Greedy motherfuckers.
[Yeong-sam] Oh, yeah?
[players shouting angrily]
[Yeong-sam]
Thought you guys were soldiers.
[shouting continues]
[dark music playing]
[Thanos] Min-su.
I know you're mad at me, dude.
I'm sorry, boy!
You still shouldn't have betrayed us.
That shit really hurt my fuckin' feelings.
- Open the door!
- [grunts] Hey, Min-su.
You said you got scammed
out of your place, right?
- You got nowhere to go out there, bro.
- Min-su, open the door!
[Nam-gyu] So come on, dude.
Just one more game.
And I promise you, man,
we're gonna keep you safe. Hmm?
When we vote tomorrow, you're gonna
press "O," Min-su. Yo, come on!
Whoa, boy. Sit the fuck down.
Look, Min-su.
Before I got here, things were so rough,
I was gonna jump off the Han River Bridge.
Actually, I was there
when this man wearing a suit
gave me a business card.
You must have got one too.
Yeah.
Now, I'm not religious or anything, but…
How should I put this?
It felt like divine intervention.
Like the universe
was giving me a second chance, man.
That's when I decided
I was gonna turn my whole life around,
make my mom proud.
The thing is,
when someone gets in the way of that,
I don't mean to, but I lose my shit!
I'm so fucking angry, man!
[Myung-gi] Leave him alone.
Hey. The fuck you doing? Get lost.
You want him to switch.
Yo, Myung-gi,
who do you think you are, huh?
The National Election Commission?
MG Coin.
You're still on my shitlist.
So why don't you just take a piss
and get the fuck out of here?
"X"s, over here!
These two were just threatening one of us
a second ago!
They're pressuring someone to change sides
so they'll win the vote.
[Player 047] Is that true?
- Hey. What the fuck, man? That's cheating.
- [others murmuring]
Whoa, hey. You immature little dipshits,
who taught you that kinda shit was okay?
Hey! Hey! Listen up, "O" Gang!
These "X"s over here
tried to fucking attack us!
"O"s, come on!
What's that all about?
Why you trying to start shit?
Quiet, the adults are talking.
You "X"s are all wimpy-ass little shits.
Piss your pants and fuck off.
We went already, you dumbass.
Min-su, wait.
MG Coin.
You tripping, dude?
Earth to Myung-gi. Hello?
[Nam-gyu] It's 'cause of that girl, dude.
Remember earlier today,
that bitch we saw talking to him?
You know,
the one we thought he was kind of with?
Ah.
You sly dog. You were trying
to get some action, weren't you?
[Nam-gyu] You know, I started watching her
a little bit more after that.
And I noticed she was walking kinda funny.
[laughs] Her belly was--
Listen, you fucking assholes,
you leave her alone!
What's up?
We must have really hit a nerve.
Oh, for sure, dude.
- MG Coin…
- [Nam-gyu] Something's going on.
if you press "X" one more time,
I swear to fucking God,
I'll cut off
one of your sticky little fingers,
give it to that bitch of yours…
[whispering]
…and then make her my bitch.
She will love it.
- You fucking asshole!
- [players gasp]
[players exclaim]
[shouting angrily]
[intense music playing]
It's all mine!
Your money! Your girl! Your fucking life!
- It's all Thanos's property now!
- [straining]
You fucking son of a goddamn
motherfucking bitch!
- [stabbing]
- [music stops]
[intense music playing]
[closing theme music playing]
Subtitle translation by: Yoonjung Song