(hallyusubs.com)
Don't stall time. Make it quick.
I don't care if it's one or two.
I don't see a baby.
What?
The baby is gone.
See?
There's only one sac left.
What does that mean?
Only one sac left?
Vanishing twin.
It's called fetus in fetu.
One of the twins fails to grow...
and dies in the uterus.
It occurs in 20 to 30 percent...
of twin pregnancies.
And it doesn't affect
the other twin or you.
That's ridiculous.
How is that even possible?
Ms. Oh Yeon Doo.
Enough. I don't want to hear it.
- Stay calm, Ms. Oh.
- Let go of me!
It has nothing to do with me.
That doesn't matter!
Ms. Oh...
(Episode 3)
Dr. Gong.
You have a visitor.
What brings you here?
I'm here to receive treatment.
Treatment? From me?
I'm not in charge of obstetrics.
Get out.
I don't need an obstetrician.
I'm here for the fertility clinic.
I'm infertile, Tae Kyung.
What?
I didn't know
I'd be telling you this way.
Even if we get married,
I can't be pregnant.
If you want,
our marriage can be perfunctory.
Are you saying
you just want to play pretend?
For what?
For everyone's peace of mind.
Why did you make things worse...
by telling Ms. Eun
that you'd cut ties with them?
You could've consulted me first.
About what?
Whether it's perfunctory or not,
I'm not marrying you.
Don't you care about Ms. Lee at all?
- If you're like that...
- I know what I'm doing.
It has nothing to do with you.
While trying to follow you out,
Ms. Lee cut her foot
on a piece of broken glass.
If you keep being like this,
your mother will suffer.
You should think
about what you need to do...
as a son.
I should get going.
What if...
I'm pregnant?
Would things be different?
I want an abortion.
I want it now. Right now.
I can't wait.
The baby is gone.
See?
There's only one sac left.
If you keep being like this,
your mother will suffer.
You should think
about what you need to do...
as a son.
Is your foot all right?
I just needed a Band-Aid.
I didn't have to go to the ER.
I'm fine, so stop worrying about me.
You don't have to buy
things like this.
Just get better
and carry them with you.
Tae Kyung said
he'd cut ties with the family,
but he just did it in a fit of rage.
I'll talk to him.
It's not something
he would've said easily.
Leave him alone for the time being.
What?
What...
What do you think you're doing?
Grandmother had the staff
move Tae Kyung's stuff.
- Mother did?
- Yes.
And you stood and watched?
You should've stopped them!
Come on, Dad.
There's no stopping Grandma.
He left saying he'd cut ties.
He should take his stuff.
What?
I'm sorry, Father, Mother.
Grandmother was insistent
and there was nothing we could do.
Father.
You went shopping too?
You don't mind at all?
What got into you?
Watch your manners.
Are you all right, Mother?
Slam the door harder next time.
Mother. Why are you
making things worse?
What did I do?
When someone moves out,
they take their belongings.
No one's moving out.
Tae Kyung's part of our family.
"Family?"
He calls me by my name...
and doesn't call you "Father"
and he's family?
He was just so angry...
Do you see and care that he's angry,
but you don't care that I am?
Mother, will you please...
Honey.
Mother, he got all agitated...
because of me. I apologize.
I have a tea ceremony tomorrow.
Run a bath then wake me.
Yes, Mother.
- Come with me.
- Mother, you really...
Let's go.
My goodness.
Chun Myung, why is something
always happening in your family?
I think our Chalttuk's stressed out.
Will it be okay?
It'll be fine.
We're not yet sure
you are pregnant, so...
What does that mean?
Do you want us to lose our baby too?
I have no ill will
toward your Chalttuk.
Don't exaggerate.
Honey, Chalttuk,
let's go to our room.
Come along.
It's all done. Now go to bed.
Let's worry about
tomorrow's things tomorrow.
How can she
love her husband so much...
when her son wants to cut ties?
Or is it our money she's after?
Don't forget our wedding anniversary
gathering tomorrow.
Whatever.
Darn you.
In Ok.
Are you protesting? Wake up.
I need some time to think.
Please don't tell Tae Kyung.
In Ok!
My goodness.
Mother, did you see In Ok?
I want to ask you that. Wake her up.
I'll be late for the ceremony.
Honey!
- What's wrong, Father?
- Honey.
What's he doing?
Have you not seen her either?
Who?
Your mom.
You're not making any sense.
Where did she go?
She said she needs time to think.
She asked me
not to tell Tae Kyung either.
What?
My gosh.
Did Mother leave home, then?
She left home?
Try calling her, Father.
Yes, right.
I'm here to take you
to the ceremony.
Why are you all up?
Forget the tea ceremony.
What on earth...
Sir.
Ms. Jang. Something crazy happened.
Mother left home.
What?
The phone is turned off.
Please leave...
Darn it.
Sir. Just a moment.
Let me go, Ms. Jang.
You can't go anywhere
dressed like this.
Ms. Lee hates it
when you look unkempt.
Right.
Calm down, sir.
You'll only make things worse
if you overreact.
You have a breakfast meeting
with the Minister of Startups.
Don't agitate Ms. Eun anymore.
Stick to your work schedule.
I'll do what I can...
to bring Ms. Lee back home.
Be at the gathering later
or I'll turn nasty.
You care about the gathering...
when Mother's out there somewhere?
I do.
People gather every year
to congratulate us on our marriage.
We haven't
made our divorce public yet.
Must I go alone
and humiliate myself?
Why do I even bother?
If you're a no-show,
I won't divorce you.
You might get sick.
Too much water isn't good for you,
Grandmother.
Where do you think she went?
She was a homebody,
so she won't have any friends.
Darn it.
Call the fool immediately.
I'm so bothered.
(Gong Chun Myung)
What's the occasion?
Was this your idea?
Grandmother?
Answer the question.
Did you get your mother
to move out too?
No, Grandmother.
She asked us not to tell Tae Kyung.
What do you mean?
What does Mom not want me to know?
That she ran away from home.
If you hear from her,
tell her I won't let her back.
What are you saying?
You said you would cut ties with us.
Fine.
Why don't we part ways now?
Before I hire a lawyer
to cancel your adoption...
Let's talk later. Bye.
Let go. Give me your phone.
Call him back right now.
Grandmother.
I can't live without you.
Try to calm down, for my sake.
Honey, get her calming medication.
Okay.
- Oh, dear...
- Grandmother. Calm down.
(Mother)
(Edu Mind)
I'm sorry, kids.
My writing's horrible...
and I can't focus.
Let's wrap up for today.
I'll make up for it next time.
- Okay.
- Have a good day.
- Seriously?
I can't believe it.
- No way.
- Stop that.
But it's fascinating.
- Why are you taking photos?
- No way.
I think it belongs to a teacher,
not a student.
It's super annoying though.
Hi, Ms. Oh.
Hey.
There's nothing to see here.
Stop that.
(Looking for the owner)
Don't be so annoying.
- Whose can it be?
- Oh, no.
I know who this belongs to.
Stop that.
Get going, will you?
What kind of an idiot
would play such a dirty prank?
Just wait till I find out
who did this.
You'll be kicked out of
this academy!
Don't you agree, Ms. Oh?
You shouldn't have left the key
to your drawer in plain sight.
It was too easy to find.
How did you know
I had that ultrasound picture?
Have you been
checking my whereabouts?
As if.
You know my wife and I
are expecting our second child.
My wife's OBGYN
is a doctor at the famous...
Gong Obstetrics and Gynecology.
Gong Obstetrics and Gynecology?
That's right.
She saw you asking for an abortion.
I figured she saw wrong...
but I went through your drawer
just in case.
Bingo.
Guess what I found.
I bet your family doesn't know yet.
Your mom once came to me...
with a packed lunch
hoping I'd be nice to you.
She might faint when she finds out.
What is it that you want?
Quit this academy immediately.
Why are you being this mean to me?
I started off as your assistant,
remember?
I got you your cigarettes,
ironed your clothes, helped you
put together your textbook,
and even drove you around
while building my career.
It's why you should've
only crawled up so far.
First, you begged in tears...
for a chance to be my assistant.
But you crawled your way up,
and now
you're threatening my career.
Please give me some time.
I can handle this mess.
How?
This is a conservative facility
where students receive education.
Having a child out of wedlock
could easily ruin your career.
Hand in your resignation letter
by the end of the day...
if you don't want
your reputation to tank.
(Director at Gtoos Education)
If you agree to be on board,
I will use every trade secret
that I know...
to create a curriculum
designed just for you.
She ran away from home.
If you hear from her,
tell her I won't let her back.
Your mother hasn't called, has she?
Don't be alarmed by this,
- but your mom...
- I know.
Grandmother told me.
You know?
Then why are you here
working at the office?
I told you that I was done
with the family.
Sort out
your family affairs yourselves.
They aren't my concern.
"Your" family affairs?
How could you speak that way
about your mother?
Aren't you worried about her?
You'll regret this, you know.
You cold-hearted brat.
(Gong Obstetrics and Gynecology)
Director Han.
I made you wait, didn't I?
Something came up at the academy,
and I couldn't find
the time to call.
It's all right.
Are you on your way though?
I'm afraid not.
We won't be able to meet today,
and we'll have to reschedule.
I'll hear your terms
when we get together.
Sure thing.
I hope you get back to me.
But I don't have any change.
You can't pay for a bowl of udon
with a 100 dollar cashier's check.
Come on.
But you won't accept credit cards,
and I don't have any cash.
You have a cashier's check
but no cash?
Are you kidding me?
I can't take this.
I'm sorry, sir.
Unbelievable.
Don't just stand there.
Get cash from the bank.
But the banks are closed.
Will this cover it?
Just let her go.
It's not like I care who pays.
I'll have a bottle of soju.
You can forget the snacks.
Sure thing.
(tteokbokkisubs.com)
Let me see.
Sir, wait.
Give her the ten dollars back,
and serve us what you have
for this much.
Sure thing.
All right.
I'd like to join you for a drink.
Is that okay?
Sorry?
Go ahead.
There.
It'll burn to have soju
on an empty stomach.
We'll order more if it's not enough.
I'm just an old lady
who ran away from home.
Don't let the udon get mushy.
Eat up.
I'll enjoy, then.
Sure.
The tea ceremony members don't know
what happened to Ms. Lee.
I got someone to go to stores
she frequents, but she wasn't there.
I'm so anxious, I'm going crazy.
Let's call the police, Ms. Jang.
If we call the police
and it gets out,
it won't be good for Ms. Lee either.
I can't stand this.
I should go and see Tae Kyung.
They're already looking for him
at Gong Obstetrics and Gynecology.
If you get worked up,
it'll be harder to convince Ms. Eun.
I'll make sure to find her
and bring her to you.
Wait.
Here.
Isn't this yours?
It must be.
Twins?
They...
were twins.
were twins?
One is gone.
Oh, my.
How did that happen?
You must be upset about
what happened to your baby.
You still shouldn't drink.
It's not because of that.
I'm a teacher at an academy.
Someone blackmailed me
knowing that I was pregnant.
I might have to quit.
Oh, my.
That must feel unfair.
It took me seven years...
to come this far.
I'm so close to achieving my goal.
I did so much to survive.
If I was going to lose one,
why couldn't I just lose both?
Why did one stay?
That baby...
must be trying to survive.
Like you.
I was alone
when I gave birth to my baby.
He's already...
over 30 now.
But now...
he wants to live as strangers.
He must really not like me.
Even if he's your child,
you must resent him.
No.
He didn't do anything wrong.
It's all my fault.
Right. Do you want to see my son?
Here.
He's cute.
He has your eyes and mouth.
He is my baby.
That's when he turned one.
Back then, I was everything to him.
I didn't even notice
when I was tired.
Gosh.
I'll go...
and cool down a bit.
Right. One second.
Gosh.
How could you speak that way
about your mother?
Aren't you worried about her?
Dr. Gong.
Here is Ms. Oh Yeon Doo's chart.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Okay.
Right. Your mother
came by earlier, right?
- What?
- I met her...
in front of the hospital earlier.
She had luggage.
Dr. Gong.
Ms. Lee.
Gosh.
(Ms. Jang)
Yes. It's me.
What's wrong?
Did she drink?
It seems like it.
She can't drink alcohol.
What was she doing?
What if you catch a cold?
Sorry, Tae Kyung.
Don't get angry.
I don't see her bag.
Ms. Lee.
Where did you leave your bag?
At the food cart.
We should warm her up.
I'll take her,
so go back to the food cart
and look for her bag.
Go to my room. Please.
Don't worry.
(My Tae Kyung, June 4, 1991)
Tae Kyung?
You should meet him and face it.
Whatever conclusion you come to.
Enough. I don't want to hear it.
- Stay calm, Ms. Oh.
- Let go of me!
It has nothing to do with me.
That doesn't matter!
What? Mr. Gong.
What brings you here?
What's with him?
Oh, the check lady?
She got drunk and left.
Then she didn't come back.
She was only going to have udon,
but that girl got her to drink.
- Someone got her to drink?
- Yes.
Who was that?
Where is she?
She took the lady's luggage
and left just now.
Her luggage?
Yes.
Where are you?
Gosh. It's so heavy.
What are you doing?
Did you follow me?
Did you drink with her?
Oh, yes.
Do you know her?
She's my mother.
What? Your mother?
Oh, my.
So, this picture is you.
Were you this adorable?
No way.
- Why did you make my mother drink?
- What?
She can't drink alcohol.
Why did you make her drink?
Who made her drink?
You drank too, right, Ms. Oh?
How could you drink
after leaving like that yesterday?
Don't you know anything
about pregnancy?
Whether you had an abortion or not,
you can't be drinking.
Don't you know that?
Why are you always like this?
You just drink when you're upset.
When you're mad at someone,
you scribble on his car.
Does acting up help you feel better?
Do you even know the damages
I had to suffer because of you?
What damages did you suffer?
Forget it.
I don't want to talk to you.
Nothing quite works out...
when you're involved.
I'll just walk away.
That's right! I drank!
I tried, but I couldn't swallow it.
I spit it out like a fool.
Is that so wrong?
To make you think
that I forced her to drink?
Now I understand
why your mother was agonizing.
- What?
- You told her...
that you'd cut ties
with your family.
After breaking her heart like that,
why are you acting
as if you care about her?
Watch what you're saying, Ms. Oh.
It's your mother's fault, after all.
She raised you to be so twisted.
Please tell your mother...
that she's in
for a rough ride ahead.
Gosh, seriously...
What?
You're so indifferent.
No wonder you don't have a friend.
What did you say?
Why? Am I wrong?
You had no one to talk to,
so you asked a stranger
to drink with you.
You have no one around you...
because of the petty life
you've led.
- Darn you.
- Gosh.
Even if I don't have any friends,
I won't make your acquaintance.
Hey, stop right there.
Hey!
Darn it.
Chairman Gong, I took Ms. Lee
to Gong Tae Kyung's room.
Please don't worry.
Now I'm relieved.
Thanks, Ms. Jang.
My pleasure, sir.
Please get some rest tonight...
and visit Ms. Lee later.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Tae Kyung.
Tae Kyung...
She just fell asleep.
She has no fever,
but we need to wait and see.
We need to talk.
It must've been hard
to look for her.
Thanks.
This is surprising.
I didn't think
you wanted to talk to me.
By the way, did something happen?
You look awful.
Nothing.
I think Ms. Lee is
having a hard time.
She wept in her sleep
calling Chairman Gong's name.
When Chairman Gong heard
that I found her,
it sounded like he cried too.
They have a happily married life,
so they can't spend a moment apart.
I told you.
You being like this
will only add to the problem.
I told you...
that I couldn't have a baby.
Remember that?
My offer still stands.
I don't mind paper marriage.
Once we get married,
everyone in the family
will feel at ease.
- It looks so pretty.
- I know.
I'm hooked on pink these days.
Tell me about it. So am I.
Ji Myung, isn't he your brother?
Is he invited
to the wedding anniversary too?
He's not invited.
And he's not my brother anymore.
Come on. Let's not talk about that.
Why not? Are you hiding something?
If you don't stop,
you'll end up fighting.
Aren't you coming?
Do you want to fight me?
Ji Myung.
I guess we're the only friends...
who celebrate
your anniversary for so long.
So you should be nice to us.
I'm tired of celebrating
the wedding anniversary.
You just end up fighting
on a special occasion.
I know.
When I'm with my husband all day,
we have nothing to say.
- Honey.
- What? Oh, right.
Here. This is for you.
You didn't have to do this.
Thanks.
You'll be surprised.
The lingerie is
softer than your skin.
When we lost the spark between us,
we got pregnant because of that.
I got you something too.
Here, Ji Myung.
It's the bath treatment from Europe.
Just by smelling it,
a couple who sleep in separate rooms
will be drawn to each other.
But aren't we the ones
who need stuff like this?
Ji Myung and her husband
fell in love at first sight...
and got married in three months.
And they are still
in the sweet honeymoon phase.
- Right.
- Gosh, I'm so jealous.
So when is Hyun Woo coming?
Is he busy?
Yes.
It's tiring
that the hospital is busy.
- He just texted me he couldn't...
- Hello.
I'm sorry I'm late.
Thank you for marrying me, Ji Myung.
That's so sweet.
All right. Thanks.
- Have a seat, honey.
- Okay.
What took you so long?
That doesn't concern you.
Just give a big smile.
Did you eat a lot?
Yes.
I missed out on so much.
Gosh, look at you.
Done.
You two never change.
You guys are like newlyweds.
We almost got divorced recently.
What? You want me to lose weight?
Men are all alike.
Do you know what my husband said?
He says our kids are lazy
because they take after me.
That almost made me
set my seal on the divorce paper.
What are you guys talking about?
Honestly, I don't understand
those who want to get divorced.
You can just give in a little
and make concessions.
Don't you think so, honey?
Sure.
The only problem with us
is that we're the perfect match.
Let go of me.
What if I refuse?
You two should get a room.
Which is why I got you
one more gift.
A key to the suite.
- What?
- Pardon?
- No.
- It's okay.
- Just take it.
- We're really okay.
- There's no need.
- No, it's okay.
- You two should use it.
- All right.
Let's drink to a toast
and wrap things up.
All right.
To their heated night!
- To their heated night!
- Congratulations.
- Thanks.
(noonaspoiler.site)
- Have a good time.
- See you.
- Thanks.
- Bye.
A vodka martini, please.
Shaken, not stirred, two olives.
A vodka martini.
You ruined my appetite.
I got here first. Get out.
Why should I leave?
You can if you want.
One more.
- More.
Gosh.
- Darn it.
- Gosh.
What? Wipe it for me again.
You pretended to be
so sweet earlier.
What about you?
"I don't get couples that divorce."
"They should try to compromise."
Did you ever compromise with me?
You asked for a divorce first!
Forget it!
Excuse me.
- What...
- Here.
Gong Ji Myung.
Gong Ji Myung!
Your family may be rich,
but you shouldn't...
throw away credit cards.
Hey. Am I an insect?
Am I a virus to you?
I hate you more than I hate bugs.
You're worse than a virus.
That goes for me too.
You disgust me.
I can't stand your breathing.
What?
If you hate me that much,
why did you marry me?
Because I loved you.
I didn't know you were like this.
You know,
I don't like how hypocritical
you are around others,
how you always put work before me,
and how you make all the decisions
yourself as if you're smart!
All sorts of physical contact with you
give me the creeps!
What are you doing?
Gong Ji Myung!
Do you dislike me that much?
Even now?
- That way.
- Okay.
Ta-da!
What's this?
Isn't it pretty?
We went shopping for Soo Kyum...
Let me. I'll tell her.
I liked it as soon as I saw it.
It's meant to be yours.
It looks expensive.
You can wear it to work,
Ms. Star Instructor.
Right. Thanks, everyone.
Auntie, try it on.
Yes, let's see how it looks on you.
Okay, fine.
- Oh, gosh.
- Amazing.
What do you think?
You look amazing, sweetie.
You look awesome.
You look like
a news presenter on TV.
I have a great eye
when it comes to fashion.
You do.
How nice.
Sorry, this is an important call.
Hello, Director.
Sorry to call so late.
I have something to tell you.
It's fine. Go ahead.
I don't think you can work with us.
I'm really sorry.
Okay.
May I ask why?
See for yourself.
Check the student forum.
What?
Oh Yeon Doo is to be a single mom?
What a betrayal.
Doesn't she feel bad
for her students?
Whose lecture should I
subscribe to when she retires?
Shouldn't she compensate us
instead of just a refund?
(Edu Mind, Oh Yeon Doo)
My gosh...
Darn it.
I'm off to work, Mom.
Don't skip breakfast.
(My husband)
My gosh.
Why did you jump?
I didn't jump.
Move.
You're wearing yesterday's outfit.
Were you perhaps with another woman?
What? Unbelievable.
That's what you say after
barging into my office this early?
Get out.
Of course.
You're not one to have affairs.
You love your wife way too much.
Cut the nonsense
and tell me what you want.
Why are you here?
Right.
I found my mom.
She got wasted after a few drinks,
so I took her to my room.
Mother had drinks?
It must've upset you.
Are you all right?
By the way, can I have the material
for the upcoming event?
It's in two days.
Right, of course.
(We support single parents!)
It's an event for single mothers.
When things are hectic,
it's best to bury yourself in work.
Doctor, you have a visitor
in your office.
Ms. Jang told me about your mom.
I'm glad we were able to locate her,
but she still isn't taking my calls.
It's all my fault.
And I apologize, Chairman Gong.
I'm the one who's sorry.
This is all on me.
I wanted to be the fence
that kept you safe,
but all I did was hurt you.
I apologize on behalf of everyone,
Tae Kyung.
Please don't.
Don't force yourself
into an unwanted marriage.
You marrying a decent young lady...
is what your mom and I want for you,
but there's nothing we can do...
if that's not what you want.
However, we can't
let this family fall apart.
I will persuade my own mother,
so all I ask is that
you do the same with yours.
We'll all get together in one place.
If we must be
at each other's throats,
we'll do it in person.
When I call,
bring your mother out with you.
That's all I ask, Tae Kyung.
Here.
Nice. You and your 20-20 vision.
I'll patch up Soo Kyum's sock.
Are you leaving
without having breakfast?
It's the first day of school,
and I need to snag
the front row seat.
You get seated
based on your eyesight,
so how can you sit in the front row?
There's a way to everything.
The store will be vacated
in a few days,
so go to a renovation contractor
with your uncle.
- Got it.
- I want to go as well.
Ms. Oh, meet me in my office.
Come in.
Yeon Doo,
can I borrow your car today?
Uncle and I need to meet
with a renovation contractor.
Sure. Take it.
Thanks.
Dong Wook.
What is it?
What's your thought on me...
quitting my job
as an academy instructor?
Are you out of your mind?
Why would you quit...
when what you dreamed of
is within reach?
Don't you remember
what you went through...
to keep having
a career in this field?
There's no need to yell.
I was only joking.
I won't quit, so you can get going.
(Old School)
Next up is Ms. Kang Bong Nim.
Can you tell me what this is?
As if I wouldn't know.
It's a plane
which I've never been on.
It's a car.
Where on this circle
is it disconnected?
Anyone would know that.
It's disconnected at the top.
Is that a circle and not a square?
Can you tell me what this is?
That darn geezer...
had to pick the number
that symbolizes death.
It's eight. I'm sure of it.
Ms. Kang, you have poor eyesight.
In fact, your vision is the worst.
What now, Principal Jang?
Should I sit up front?
You must be thrilled
to have the best seat.
I should hide in the back row
and have my lunch.
I keep forgetting what I learned...
and should constantly ask questions
from that seat.
That's the best seat
to get to the restroom.
What if I wet myself?
Ladies, I'm sorry.
All that reading...
must've messed with my vision.
Ms. Kang Bong Nim.
(Ms. Kang Bong Nim,
you're on cleaning duty.)
Hold on. Why am I
on cleaning duty today...
when it's not my turn?
Look. You managed to read that.
It seems as though
you can read this.
Hold on.
Can you make out those tiny letters?
You must have 20-20 vision.
Move to the back, Ms. Bong Nim!
Unbelievable.
Ms. Bong Nim,
why did you lie on your eye exam?
I only wanted to get good grades.
Mr. Jang,
I need to get into college.
Are you suggesting
that the others don't want that?
Sorry?
Not everyone can get into college.
Only someone with grades
as good as mine...
You can lie
as long as you get good grades.
Is that what you taught
your children?
Why would you suddenly
bring up my kids?
My children are all sweet...
and never lied while growing up.
Maybe you should learn from them.
At times, even parents
learn from their children.
Anyway, Mr. Jang...
Ms. Kang Bong Nim.
You were wrong to lie,
so you'll be on cleaning duty.
(Teachers' Office)
You geezer.
Why are you always on my case?
Hey, your aunt told you
that her laptop was off limits.
Just a second.
The pink sweater is on sale.
Get out. Come on.
(Reserved for Expectant Mothers)
That baby must be trying to survive.
Like you.
Don't you remember
what you went through...
to keep having
a career in this field?
I see you're just like me.
You may be the principal,
but you sure are annoying.
I'll consider this as your face.
Who are you blaming
when you're the one who farted?
Why you...
Why are you cleaning
when it's not your turn?
Have you forgotten already?
The mother of
an academy star instructor...
lied her butt off.
I know.
But my Yeon Doo
will soon sign a contract...
and make eight figures a year.
- Eight figures?
Will she earn that much?
She'll earn 1,000 dollars
with every breath she takes.
But I'm a known liar,
so don't believe me.
What do you think
of my youngest son?
He's an assistant manager
at a large company.
My nephew's a dentist.
Would you be interested?
How about a lawyer?
I live next door to one,
so why don't I set it up?
Save it.
I wouldn't trade...
a whole truck of them
for Ms. Yeon Doo.
(The Korean Master, Oh Yeon Doo!
Edu Mind)
Ms. Oh, what now?
Ms. Oh.
This isn't what I had in mind when
I gave you the dried bellflower tea.
Do you have any idea how much damage
you've caused us?
Parents are calling nonstop...
asking for a refund
on their children's classes.
I'm sorry, Mr. Park.
This kind of conduct
from an unmarried woman?
I don't even want to speak of it,
so get out of here
before I sue you for damages.
(Edu Mind)
Shouldn't you
get on your knees or something?
Shouldn't you get down and beg,
at least
for your poor mother's sake?
I guess you'll understand
how your mother feels...
once you have a kid like you.
What a good child.
Sir. Do you know...
who made a big deal
out of something...
that could've been
dealt with quietly?
I don't know.
You stole my ultrasound picture...
had shared my private life
without permission.
What are you talking about?
Sir. This is just slander.
Slander? Who slandered who?
Go ahead and look
at the security camera footage...
and track the IP address.
No. Call the police right away.
Ms. Oh!
Are you really going to be this way?
You already caused us
so much trouble.
Why are you harassing the person
who brings in the most revenue?
What? Harass?
Sir. Don't get angry.
How dare you raise your voice?
Don't you have any shame?
Is that how your mom taught you?
Stop talking about my mom!
I'm sorry
for causing the academy trouble,
but is it wrong for a single woman
to get pregnant?
Is what you did not wrong?
Is my pregnancy the only sin here?
Do I have shame?
You used my weakness
to look good to your superiors.
Don't you feel shame about that?
Don't you feel ashamed
to face your students?
I can't work at such a dirty
and cheap place like this.
No. I'm not doing it!
(The Real Has Come!)
It's money!
It could be a conception dream.
A conception dream?
You're such an important daughter
to Mom.
Get rid of it right away.
Kim Jun Ha?
I didn't want to believe it.
This punk.
I'm going to get a divorce.
- Oh, my.
- Grandma!
Do you know Gong Tae Kyung?
Let's get married. You and I.
- What?