THE FOLLOWING EPISODE CONTAINS
DESCRIPTIONS OF CHILD ABUSE
WHICH MAY BE DISTURBING FOR SOME VIEWERS
I think it was around late March,
when I was 16.
After the evening roll call,
around 7:00 or 8:00 p.m.,
the guard would open the gate
with a ring of keys in hand.
BROTHERS' HOME
WOMEN'S PLATOON
He'd say, "So-and-so, step outside."
Mi-gyeong, Mi-suk, or Eun-hui,
for instance.
And when their names were called,
they'd go out.
When they did,
they'd sometimes come back
with cookies and snacks.
We'd all go crazy,
scrambling to split them
and grab our share.
But they were given
in exchange for nonconsensual sex.
We didn't know any better and just waited
for the older girls to return
so we could get some of those snacks
from them.
So around that time,
whenever the intercom rang,
we'd eagerly wait.
And at that point...
I didn't think it would happen to me.
I never thought
it would happen to me, but...
Well...
PARK SUN-I DURING HER INTERNMENT
The commander wanted to see me.
That was when I saw
the bed covered with a blanket.
He sat next to me, put his arm around me,
got friendly, and said,
"Hey there. You need anything?"
He twisted my arms like this.
And put them like this.
Then he grabbed my arms like this.
Just like this.
And he laid me down on the blanket.
Then he...
He gave me some tangerines
to eat when I got back.
I don't even care
that it was my first time.
I'm...
a mother who abandoned her child.
I'm a sinner.
A mother who abandoned her child.
BROTHERS' HOME
I went to the ob-gyn three times.
But I couldn't do it.
I couldn't muster the courage.
And the baby
was already wriggling inside me.
Who was the father?
The commander.
I gave birth at Jinju Medical Center.
On February 4th.
My mom...
put the baby up for adoption.
After what they did
to my body and my life,
I may still be walking,
but they might as well have killed me.
When people pass me,
I'm afraid they'll judge me and think,
"That woman gave birth to a child
and gave the baby up for adoption."
So I can't even bring myself
to talk about it anywhere.
And it's just so painful.
PARK SUN-I WAS HELD
AT THE BROTHERS' HOME FROM 1980 TO 1986.
SHE GAVE BIRTH AT 16 AFTER BEING RAPED.
SHE STILL CARRIES THE GUILT
OF GIVING UP HER CHILD.
THE ECHOES OF SURVIVORS:
INSIDE KOREA'S TRAGEDIES
How many years were you locked up for?
They took me away when I was 11
and didn't let me go until I was 18 or 19.
So it was about eight years.
I was there for a little more
than four years and six months.
I think I was there for about 11 years.
I was taken in when I was 11.
And I got out when I was 18.
My father came for me.
Sir, did you receive any education?
No, I didn't receive any in there.
What is your highest level
of formal education, sir?
None.
We all thought it was okay
not to get an education.
We didn't know any law.
We didn't know about compulsory education,
and we were locked up too.
I didn't go to school
while I was in there.
I just barely learned to read.
I struggle with calculations
when the numbers get too big.
I can't even hope to do
multiplication or division.
The director believed,
"If we give these little punks a break,
they'll try to run."
"Don't let them just sit around.
Put them to work."
A seven-year-old was put to work
doing manual labor.
We hardly ate,
yet they worked us to the bone.
We were on the verge of fainting,
working all day on empty stomachs
in the middle of summer.
We were always hungry.
They hardly fed us anything.
They'd give us meat soup,
but it was just oil floating around.
That stuff was just inedible.
There was hardly anything
you could actually call food.
They gave us barley rice,
but it was barely three spoonfuls' worth.
And the soup tasted like nothing more
than water used to rinse doenjang.
INMATES WAITING FOR SOY SOUP
Most of the side dishes
smelled like they were rotten.
Kimchi tasted like it had already spoiled.
Whenever they went to a farm,
it was always right after the cabbages
had been harvested.
Around then, you'd find leaves
and peels tossed out in the fields.
The farm owner was actually thankful
when someone cleaned it up.
They would collect those leaves,
and the farm owner asked,
"What on earth
do you need all of these for?"
So they told him,
"We have about 30 pigs on our farm."
"We're going to boil these up
for their food."
It's great when all the fish
get auctioned off,
but if they don't and sit for a few days,
the fish starts to spoil.
We'd get a call.
Then we'd bring the blue truck
to go pick up the mackerel.
You can smell it
as soon as you start loading them.
So when I first got there,
they boiled and served spoiled fish,
so I couldn't eat it.
I couldn't eat it.
I just couldn't. It was disgusting.
The director and his family eat here too.
They are frying the fish they bought.
They buy flour, bake bread,
and serve it as snacks
once or twice a day.
"Is 20,000 won a month really enough
to cover the meal I'm eating right now?"
Absolutely not.
PASSENGERS AT THE FINAL STOP
This video shows the exact opposite
of what really happened.
It was their strategy
to promote themselves to the public
by advertising that they served good food,
when, in truth, his meals
were cooked separately from ours.
All income earned by residents working
in the facility is deposited into savings
to support their self-sufficiency
after discharge.
These are the bankbooks
for the residents' savings accounts.
The total savings amount
is around 130 million won.
I didn't receive
a single penny of that money.
As for the money,
I never saw a dime.
So who took all the money?
The director and his family took it all.
Park In-geun started fully exploiting us.
Park In-geun probably pocketed all of it.
PARK IN-GEUN'S KINGDOM
Director Park In-geun and his family
lived in private quarters
on the Brothers' Home property.
EMPLOYEE QUARTERS
The house is huge and spacious.
They had a ton of potted plants too.
It was two stories high
and built like a corridor-style apartment.
On the second floor lived Park In-geun...
PARK DU-SEON
...and the general secretary
of the Brothers' Home.
The pastor, Lim Young-soon,
lived on the first floor.
LIM YOUNG-SOON
PARK IN-GEUN'S BROTHER-IN-LAW
Living next door was Lim Eun-soon,
Park's youngest sister-in-law.
I did all the housework myself.
I looked after the child
and did their housework too.
Park In-geun, the director, liked the...
He liked yukhoe, the raw beef dish.
Yukhoe was always on the table
at every meal.
Whenever I saw
Director Park's son or daughter,
I felt really envious.
If I were his daughter,
I'd get to wear
pretty, comfortable clothes
and eat whatever I wanted.
Seeing that always made me jealous.
Park In-geun's wife
especially wore housedresses.
She'd have her hair up like this,
all nicely blow-dried,
standing next to her husband
in that dress.
His family wasn't much better.
They were scary,
swearing at me and everything.
They totally looked down on me.
You know Park Du-seon, right?
The general secretary of the asylum.
Park In-geun's son.
PARK DU-SEON, PARK IN-GEUN'S SECOND SON
Man, I could never forget that guy.
He made my life hell.
For instance, he'd make me sit
on the ledge by the flowerbed.
He said he'd kill me if I caught it.
Then he threw a real baseball at me.
He threw it at my face
like a crazy bastard.
I'd just take it.
He'd beat a kid until he let it all out.
He kept hitting the kid's head
until it bled.
There was also a pastor
named Lim Young-soon at the church.
LIM YOUNG-SOON, PARK'S BROTHER-IN-LAW
Lim Young-soon was immediately
next in line after Park In-geun.
He was second-in-command.
PARK IN-GEUN, LIM YOUNG-SOON
At the Brothers' Home,
we were forced to attend worship services.
He never hesitated to use brutal violence
and punished the children severely.
And this was actual physical punishment.
Were you ever beaten
by Lim Young-soon too?
He slapped me in the face.
When I was baptized
by Pastor Lim Young-soon,
he'd spit on people if their feet had
a skin disease or athlete's foot.
History will judge them.
And rightly so.
BROTHERS' HOME EXPOSED
Around October or November of '86,
Prosecutor Kim Yong-won,
recently assigned to the Ulsan branch
of the District Office...
YEO JUN-MIN, FORMER SECRETARY GENERAL
OF BROTHERS' HOME CASE TASK FORCE
...went pheasant hunting over the weekend.
And he stumbled upon a bizarre sight.
The villager guiding the pheasant hunt
said those people
were from the Brothers' Home
and added
that they were being prevented
from running away.
So they were taking people in,
forcing them to work,
and not letting them escape?
That seems suspicious.
It all started when the investigation
into the forced labor began.
REPORTER HEO SANG-CHEON
COVERED ON-SITE AT BROTHERS' HOME
During the investigation, they realized
they had stumbled upon something major.
And since I was in Busan,
they said I should check out the scene.
That's where my coverage
of this case began.
BEWARE OF DOG
The first location I visited
was Banjeong Ranch in Ulsan.
BANJEONG RANCH
When I got closer to the scene,
I saw about seven or eight people
lying on the ground.
And their legs,
I mean, their ankles,
were tied up
with what looked like nylon rope.
"Why on earth are they tied up like that?"
I wrote about it right away.
184 RESIDENTS OF BUSAN WELFARE FACILITY
EXPLOITED FOR LAND DEVELOPMENT
DIRECTOR OF CITY-FUNDED WELFARE FACILITY
FORCED 184 RESIDENTS INTO LABOR,
BEAT ONE TO DEATH, AND BURIED THE BODY
Seven defendants, including
the Brothers' Home director Park,
imprisoned residents, forced them to work,
and beat 40-year-old resident
Kim Gyeong-won to death.
After the first report came out,
everyone realized how big this case was.
BUSAN DISTRICT PROSECUTORS' OFFICE
That's when the investigation picked up.
The following day, they visited
the main building of the Brothers' Home.
They brought in police officers
trained in martial arts
to carry out a raid on the facility.
When they entered the director's office,
the first thing they saw
was a large safe mounted on the wall.
Inside the safe,
they found US dollars, Japanese yen,
and other items like bearer bonds.
It was about two billion won in total.
Today, I think it'd be worth
tens of billions of won.
It was absurd
and truly beyond anyone's imagination.
Where would they have gotten
that money from?
He embezzled it from the residents.
How many people
would you say were kept in there?
As of 1986, there were about 3,200 people.
DETAINEE STATUS
At its peak,
up to 4,300 people were held there.
PARK MIN-SEONG
FORMER BUSAN CITY COUNCIL MEMBER
Considering the facility operated
from 1975 to 1987...
we estimate it held
about 38,000 people in total.
TOTAL NUMBER OF DETAINEES
38,000
It was probably for money.
Their funding was based on
the number of people they held.
The more people they brought in,
the more government subsidies they got.
The more, the better.
They wanted as many as possible.
I believe they received
up to two billion won...
1.7 BILLION IN '85
...in subsidies from the Korean government.
2.1 BILLION IN '86
They refused to cooperate with the police...
...Orders of Merit and Medals of Honor.
The Brothers' Home
must be shut down immediately.
He was arrested.
Park In-geun was arrested
in December of '86.
I thought, "Wow, finally,
the Brothers' Home is being shut down."
"That motherfucker Park In-geun.
He'd be put away for good, wouldn't he?"
The Ulsan branch of Busan Office
requested a 15-year prison sentence
and a fine of 681.78 million won
for the defendant, Director Park In-geun.
Prosecutors stated
they were seeking a heavy sentence,
as Park's embezzlement
of government subsidies was unacceptable
in a welfare-based society.
JUNE 30, 1987
BROTHERS' HOME SHUTS DOWN
I was released
when the Brothers' Home shut down.
My family was ruined.
We were struggling badly.
They'd been traveling all over the country
looking for us instead of working
and ended up spending all their money.
My mom said she tried to find me
by searching every single orphanage
across Korea.
As for my father,
he died of illness
after I was gone.
After that, the family fell into decline.
The entire family was shattered.
Things only got harder after I got out.
It was hard
because I couldn't live a normal life.
There was nothing... I could do.
Nothing at all.
The hostess bar was the only place
that welcomed me.
Because I was young.
It was humiliating,
and I didn't want to work there.
But I had no choice.
Getting out didn't end the misery.
I went to prison too.
I lived like a thug for a bit,
eventually ending up in Busan prison.
I tried to take my own life
three or four times at home.
For me, the pain of living
was too much to bear.
I thought it'd be better to just die
and not have to exist anymore.
I found out my little brother went through
the same things I did in there.
He attempted suicide a few times too.
He slit his wrist.
Eventually, on October 9, 2009,
I got a call from my nephew.
He was crying, saying,
"Uncle, Dad's trying to kill himself."
CHOI JAE-U
I felt deeply guilty.
I just...
miss my brother so much.
BROTHERS' HOME SHUTS DOWN
ENCOUNTER WITH PARK IN-GEUN
I think it was around '99.
I just happened to be coming out
of the bathhouse after a bath
when a very familiar face
caught my eye.
I walked toward him slowly
to get a better look...
and it was Park In-geun.
"That son of a bitch is alive?"
I got goosebumps all over at that moment.
I said to myself,
"Isn't that motherfucker Park In-geun?"
I opened my trunk,
grabbed the baseball bat...
and yelled,
"You son of a bitch! Park In-geun!"
as I ran toward him.
The bastard freaked out
as soon as he saw me,
got into his Volvo, and locked the doors.
I started hitting the car with the bat
while shouting,
"Open the door, you son of a bitch!"
But he was already in the car,
so he took off.
I thought, "I need to kill him."
"I'm going to kill that guy."
I thought he'd been sentenced
to life in prison.
I thought he'd be there for good.
He was sentenced to just two years
and six months in prison.
No further investigation was conducted
into the harm or human rights violations
suffered by the victims.
The investigation only focused
on Park In-geun's corruption
and embezzlement.
But they never carried out
a proper investigation.
The prosecution openly pressured
investigators to halt the investigation.
Despite uncovering nearly 1.1 billion won
in embezzlement by Director Park,
there was persistent pressure
to understate the amount.
Apparently, he was like an emperor there.
In there, he could do whatever he wanted
with the money he had.
Even in the detention center,
he still went to bathhouses or cafés.
PARK FREQUENTLY LEAVING THE PREMISES
DURING HIS TIME IN DETENTION
He was supposed to be behind bars,
but he came and went freely.
A WELFARE FACILITY DIRECTOR
ENJOYS OUTINGS WHILE IN DETENTION
Mayor Kim Ju-ho started a campaign
to secure his release.
CHUN DOO-HWAN, PRESIDENT
KIM JU-HO, MAYOR OF BUSAN
He held my hand
and said he didn't want this made public.
I assumed he was someone remarkable.
I thought the mayor of Busan
was the most powerful person in Busan.
So this guy was above the mayor.
AFTER 7 TRIALS, PARK GETS
2 YEARS AND 6 MONTHS IN PRISON
FOR EMBEZZLEMENT
AND FOREIGN EXCHANGE VIOLATIONS
Park In-geun, the director, died in 2016.
He died in a nursing home.
Back then, I thought,
"Couldn't he
at least have apologized
before he died?"
"That's the least you could do,
you piece of shit."
I'd have rather been the one
to kill Park In-geun back then.
I was in my mid-twenties then,
so I'd have been released by now.
A monster like him was going around
spending money like water.
AFTER HIS RELEASE, PARK IN-GEUN RAN
VARIOUS FOR-PROFIT AND WELFARE BUSINESSES
I heard that until the day he died,
he said,
"I did nothing wrong."
NEWSTAPA
MARCH 6, 2013
Hello. Are you Director Park In-geun?
Who are you with?
- I'm with Newstapa.
- Don't you see him right now?
Hey, what if he goes into shock
because of you, huh?
PARK IN-GEUN'S SON
What if he goes into shock?
You gonna take responsibility
if he collapses?
What have I ever done wrong, huh?
It's been over 20 years, you bastard.
Call your supervisor now.
Hey, tell me something.
Doesn't my father have any rights?
Doesn't he have any basic human rights?
Tell me. Does he not have any rights?
Please calm down.
JO SEONG-HYEON
DIRECTOR OF THE ECHOES OF SURVIVORS
The interview you just saw was
the last time Park In-geun was on tape.
Here's one thing we should remember.
From the day he was released
to the day he died,
Park In-geun never once apologized
to the Brothers' Home victims.
Does his family still think the same way?
We went to great lengths
to finally get hold
of a member of Park In-geun's family.
PARK CHEON-GWANG, PARK'S YOUNGEST SON
CHAIRMAN OF THE BROTHERS' HOME FOUNDATION
Are you nervous?
Yes, very much so.
I know it wasn't easy for you
to agree to this interview.
What were you most worried about?
My biggest worry
would be my family.
What I worry about most
is the possibility
that my wife and children
might be threatened or put in danger.
Who do you think would harm your family?
The people
who would be upset with me
revealing the truth.
Especially those in the government,
the city of Busan,
and the police.
I don't think
they'd be very happy with this.
Given everything,
what made you decide to do this interview?
The reason I wanted to come
and speak with you
is to tell you
that Director Park In-geun
of Brothers' Home wasn't the only one
responsible for everything that happened.
I think my father was about 30% to blame
and the government about 70%.
That's what I believe.
PARK IN-GEUN
At the time, my father said
it was a direct order from the government,
issued by the president.
As far as I know,
President Chun Doo-hwan
even presented my father with a medal
and offered significant support.
Near Hwangnyeongsan Mountain in Busan,
there used to be
a presidential villa.
THE VILLA OF PRESIDENT CHUN DOO-HWAN
We went all the way there,
and I waited in the car
while my father went inside
to speak with the president.
He even got a watch from the president.
Once, while he was driving,
he was stopped by the police
for running a red light.
But once they saw the watch
from the president, they just let him go.
They gave him a medal
and made him do the work, but later,
when the president found him inconvenient,
he made my father take the fall.
Then why give him the medal?
It's pretty absurd, isn't it?
Seoul has been chosen
to host the '88 Olympics.
As citizens of the Olympic host nation
and as citizens
of a country emerging as a global player,
we must earn the trust and respect
of people around the world.
LET'S PURIFY OUR SURROUNDINGS
TO BUILD A BRIGHTER SOCIETY
After Seoul was confirmed
as the host of the '88 Olympics,
there was a push to clean up the streets.
To show foreigners that Korea
is a clean and developed country.
The poor, beggars, and street gum vendors.
They didn't want people like that
to be seen.
MINISTRY OF HOME AFFAIRS DIRECTIVE NO. 410
They carried out a crackdown on vagrants
under Directive No. 410,
issued by the Ministry of Home Affairs.
DEFINITION OF A VAGRANT
I see it as a kind of human cleanup,
meant to remove citizens,
including the innocent and vulnerable,
from the streets.
Back then,
everyone loved Director Park In-geun.
VAGRANTS BEING SENT TO BROTHERS' HOME
Just one call was enough
to take care of them.
The program was a major success
in Busan at the time.
No other country
does it better than we do.
There's not a single beggar
on the streets.
Do you see any beggars in Korea?
Take a look. We have none.
There's an uproar over a single death
at the facility in Busan,
but in a developed country like the US,
that's barely an issue.
Not even an issue.
They found the record books documenting
when the police handed people over
to Brothers' Home.
The names of police officers,
civil servants,
and those who were captured were on them.
BROTHERS' HOME INTAKE FORM
They recorded when, where,
and how those people were captured.
Nearly 80% of them
were taken in by the police.
TOTAL DETAINEES IN '86: 3,975
REFERRED BY THE POLICE: 3,117
RATE OF DETAINEES REFERRED BY POLICE
1985: APPROXIMATELY 95%
1986: APPROXIMATELY 93%
What do the police do?
Even now,
the people I hate most are the police.
I want to kill him.
How could a police officer say
they'd take me home,
then take me to Brothers' Home instead?
I want to see his face one more time
if he's still alive.
MOON JEONG-SU, FORMER ASSEMBLY MEMBER
NEW KOREA DEMOCRATIC PARTY
Bringing an ordinary public order offender
to the station
only added a mere two points
to an officer's performance score.
However, turning in a beggar or vagrant
to the Brothers' Home...
PERFORMANCE SCORE
...earned them five points.
DETAINMENT, 2-3 POINTS
ADMISSION TO BROTHERS' HOME, 5 POINTS
One of the things
that motivated the police officers
to be more vigilant and active
was the bribes they received.
Whenever officers handed people over
to Brothers' Home,
the staff there slipped them some money.
At the time, police officers
frequently visited my father's office.
He sometimes handed them cash.
There was this team leader
at the Geumjeong police station.
I think my father gave him
around five million won as well.
Put simply, it was a bribe.
Were there any officers
who refused to take bribes?
I don't think I've seen any.
WHO IS BROTHERS' HOME DIRECTOR PARK,
A MEDALED MEMBER OF THE PUAC?
DIRECTOR OF BROTHERS' HOME
EMBEZZLES 1.1 BILLION WON
WHY HASN'T THE BROTHERS' HOME CORRUPTION
BEEN BROUGHT TO LIGHT?
What happened to your family
after your father was arrested
and Brothers' Home was closed?
After his release
following his arrest in '86,
my father decided
that we would immigrate to Australia
in 1990.
Our family's total assets
were once appraised at 36 billion won.
That was in 2011.
We owned a property in Australia
called the Milperra Sports Centre.
In Australia, they currently hold assets
worth about 14 billion won.
I believe his third daughter
and her husband
currently own the golf course
and sports center.
PARK'S THIRD DAUGHTER AND HER HUSBAND
CURRENT OWNERS OF THE GOLF COURSE
After planning our immigration
to Australia,
my father secured the funds...
EMPLOYEE OF VAGRANT FACILITY
IN WASHINGTON, UNITED STATES
...to buy the business in Milperra.
Even when Min Gyeong-u,
my third brother-in-law, ran it...
AUSTRALIA BUSINESS REPORTS
BROTHERS' HOME FOUNDATION
...he used to give my father daily updates
on revenue and expenses.
It clearly shows
that my father was the real owner.
The assets he siphoned off to Australia
were the assets of Brothers' Home.
To put it simply,
it's the proceeds of crime.
"This is what I inherited from my father."
"I have nothing to do with my father,
so I'll make good use of this money."
Do you find that acceptable?
His kids are living large now,
but it's blood-stained money.
"It was in the past,
but it was still wrong."
If they had just said that,
it would've been enough to ease our pain.
Now that Park In-geun is dead,
his kids should at least come out
and ask for forgiveness.
Who else are we supposed to get
an apology from?
Did we deserve this? We did nothing wrong.
Please, just apologize
so I can go on living.
I really don't want to live like this.
I came all the way from Busan
to Sydney, Australia.
It's been nearly 40 years
since I last saw Park In-geun's family.
NEW SOUTH WALES
AUSTRALIA
This is the driving range
and sports center
run by Park In-geun's daughter.
This is where their home is, right here.
Seriously.
I mean,
I can't believe
they're living such a happy life.
That boat's got to be worth
several hundred million won.
This property is currently valued
at over ten billion won.
"Are you happy living it up
with the money your father made
from killing people?"
"Are you people
willing to acknowledge it
and apologize at all?"
That's what I want to ask them.
Have you ever met Park In-geun?
LEE GI-BEOM, KOREAN-AUSTRALIAN
ACQUAINTANCE OF PARK IN-GEUN
Yes, we've met several times.
Back then,
there were a lot of thugs in Korea.
He himself said that he was good
at managing people like that.
What kind of place
did Park In-geun say Brothers' Home was?
A place of good deeds.
They are extremely wealthy.
It seems like the family was constantly
going back and forth to Korea,
engaging in things like that.
And every time Park Je-hui came back,
she always had new jewelry.
They're a happy family,
thanks to their wealth.
Wait, we should go that way.
Hello, I'm Jo Seong-hyeon,
a producer at MBC.
IN-LAW OF PARK IN-GEUN
- I'm from MBC in Korea.
- Okay.
Are Ms. Park Je-hui
and Mr. Min Gyeong-u at home?
They're in Korea now.
- Are you his father?
- Yes.
- I know what you're here to say.
- Right.
- But stop doing that. You see...
- Yes?
Why do you keep harassing people?
Sir, let me tell you this.
I'm a survivor of the Brothers' Home,
and while I was in there--
- That has nothing to do with me.
- No, please wait.
- Please hear me out.
- I'm not talking to you.
We're here because Ms. Park Je-hui
is Park In-geun's--
- No, just go.
- She's his daughter, right?
Just leave.
But, sir, do you at least admit
that this land, this golf course,
was purchased with Park In-geun's money?
No, that's not right.
You can request an investigation.
Don't we have rights as well?
What wrong have
Park Je-hui and Min Gyeong-u done?
I'm suing you, I swear.
There's a lawyer here too, okay?
Park Je-hui's daughter is also on her way
to becoming a lawyer.
You can't do this.
Do you know how painful this is?
I'm not just in pain.
I'm struggling to live.
Well, I have no reason to talk to you.
And, mister...
You say you're with a TV network?
But I'm the victim of--
- You're taking it too far.
- Sir.
What does it matter now
what Park In-geun did with his money?
It does matter, sir.
Even the Australian government--
HOME OF LIM YOUNG-SOON
FORMER BROTHERS' HOME PASTOR
Hello, is Pastor Lim Young-soon here?
No, he's not here.
- We know he is inside.
- He's not.
- Isn't this Pastor Lim Young-soon's home?
- No. It's not.
- It's not?
- No.
It isn't?
So Pastor Lim Young-soon
doesn't live here?
No, he doesn't.
That makes no sense. Let's have a look.
- Hello.
- Excuse me.
Could you take a quick look at this?
We checked with your next-door neighbor
and the register
and confirmed that he lives in this house.
- I see.
- Who is this person?
Isn't he your father?
Why are you here?
We had questions for your father,
so we tried to get in touch with him
from Korea as well.
You can't come in here.
- Okay, we won't go inside.
- You see, I...
I really wanted to meet
Pastor Lim Young-soon.
I was in the Brothers' Home
when I was young.
Can you tell me who this guy is?
It doesn't matter.
I have some unrelated questions
I'd like to ask.
Why did you say
Pastor Lim didn't live here?
- I don't care.
- That's none of your business.
- What's your name?
- No, hold on.
Then where is he? We want to talk to him.
It's none of your business!
You find him, if you want to find him.
It's none of our business.
Do you think
that he does not have any responsibility--
What has he done, sorry? What has he done?
- He is the victim.
- For what?
Why is he the victim?
I am a survivor of their abuse.
My brother died there,
and I was imprisoned
for five years as well.
Look at this. See this?
I was beaten so badly,
I lost all my teeth.
You don't have to say anything.
I was beaten when I was a kid.
I was beaten as a kid--
Bye. We've asked you guys
to leave our property.
Excuse me.
Come on.
Let's go.
Wow, seriously.
This is infuriating.
I was telling them
about the abuse I endured.
I even took out my dentures to show them.
As human beings,
they should at least hear me out,
understand why it happened,
and know exactly what happened.
Who can I even talk to about the sorrow
of my brother's wrongful death
and the pain I've suffered my whole life?
That's what makes me feel
so devastated and resentful.
Goddamn it.
Damn it.
We can't enter that house anymore.
- We'll just stay like this.
- Yes, let's wait.
Excuse me.
PARK IN-GEUN'S NIECE
PARK IN-GEUN'S NEPHEW-IN-LAW
Can't we just talk for a moment?
Please?
Excuse me.
Can't we just talk briefly?
Can't we?
She's smiling.
She smiled as she passed me.
Unbelievable.
I was saying, "Excuse me,"
and she looked at me while smiling.
Seeing her drive away smiling
sent a chill down my spine.
I got goosebumps all over my body.
This is driving me nuts.
BUSAN
I'm going to show you a picture.
Please tell me who this is.
I got it.
Who is this?
He's my second-oldest brother.
His name is Park Du-seon.
- Excuse me.
- Yes?
Is Mr. Park Du-seon here?
Who are you?
I'm Jo Seong-hyeon, a producer at MBC.
There's no one here by that name.
- You're at the wrong place.
- Sorry?
- No, I'm not him.
I'm not him.
I don't know who Park Du-seon is.
He's not here.
- He's not?
- No.
Who's Park In-geun?
Mr. Park In-geun,
the director of Brothers' Home.
- Where is this Brothers' Home?
- Jurye-dong.
Unbelievable.
- But weren't you the general secretary?
- No, I wasn't.
Sir, the victims
just want to hear an apology.
This person was partially paralyzed
while in the mental health facility.
Don't you think these people are victims?
I don't think so.
They have nothing to do with me,
so just go.
- Those people aren't victims?
- No.
Why do you say they aren't?
Why are they victims?
What are you bothering me for?
They just want an apology.
Do you have no intention of apologizing?
Sir?
- They just want to hear an apology.
- What apology?
Can't you just take a look at this
with me?
Please?
Let's go.
I already have a passenger.
Sorry.
Sir, don't be like this.
- This business won't last either.
- Seriously...
But these people's lives have been ruined.
What do they have to do with me?
My life was ruined too.
Why was your life ruined?
The government acknowledged what happened.
Over 600 people died.
Sir.
Over 600 people died in the institution
you and your father ran.
You won't refute any of this?
- No.
- You're not refuting it?
Sir.
Sir!
All those vengeful souls.
Aren't they afraid?
If you so much as hurt someone,
you'd normally feel guilty about it.
His entire family
took those people and exploited them
to make money, using them as tools.
Why do you think
he said he wasn't Park Du-seon?
Mr. Jo, I'm sorry,
can we resume in five minutes
after I smoke a cigarette?
- Sure.
- That question makes me feel suffocated.
Go ahead.
Thank you. Sorry about that.
I really don't understand it either.
I don't understand
why they told such blatant lies
when the truth could be easily revealed.
In my view, Brothers' Home
was the perpetrator.
But I believe
the Korean government
is most responsible for what happened,
as they gave the orders.
Instead of just me,
the son of Director Park In-geun,
stepping up,
the government should also say,
"Yes, these things were wrong back then."
They should own up to it
and offer sincere apologies.
That's what I think.
Once again,
I would like to extend...
my apologies
to the victims and their families
who suffered during their time...
at Brothers' Home,
and for all the pain
they've endured since.
From my perspective,
this is not a genuine apology.
A true, genuine apology
should include specific measures
he will take
to make amends.
This is nothing but...
All I'm hearing are excuses,
blaming the police,
the government, and the city of Busan.
THE BROTHERS' HOME INCIDENT
IS A HUMAN RIGHTS ABUSE
THAT OCCURRED FROM 1975 TO 1987
UNDER THE PROTECTION
OF A MILITARY DICTATORSHIP
38,000 PEOPLE WERE DETAINED,
WITH 657 OFFICIAL DEATHS.
PARK IN-GEUN,
KNOWN AS THE KING OF BROTHERS' HOME,
DIED IN A NURSING HOME IN 2016
PARK CHEON-GWANG WAS THE FIRST
IN HIS FAMILY
TO APOLOGIZE FOR THE INCIDENT
PASTOR LIM YOUNG-SOON
DID NOT EXERCISE HIS RIGHT OF REPLY
EVEN TODAY, BROTHERS' HOME VICTIMS
CONTINUE TO DIE FROM SUICIDE AND ILLNESS
IN 2024, THE KOREAN GOVERNMENT
APPEALED THE RULING
REGARDING COMPENSATION
FOR THE BROTHERS' HOME VICTIMS
AS OF 2025, 38 YEARS
AFTER BROTHERS' HOME SHUT DOWN,
THE POLICE HAVE YET TO APOLOGIZE
FOR THE INCIDENT
ALL INTERVIEWS USE REAL TESTIMONIES
SOME HAVE BEEN REENACTED BY ACTORS
TO PROTECT THE SUBJECT'S IDENTITY
Subtitle translation by: Sung In Jang