THE FOLLOWING EPISODE CONTAINS
DESCRIPTIONS OF A MAJOR DISASTER SCENE
WHICH MAY BE DISTURBING FOR SOME VIEWERS
I got a call around six o'clock.
"Professor, it's an emergency."
KIM SE-GYEONG
FORMER HEAD OF EMERGENCY DEPT.
AT GANGNAM ST. MARY'S HOSPITAL
"The Sampoong Department Store collapsed.
Patients are pouring in."
It was just like a scene
from a zombie movie.
People were swarming in,
bleeding, crying, and screaming.
Don't come in!
Patients came in with hemorrhagic shock,
cardiac arrest, burst intestines...
There were people with severed limbs.
Blood covered the entire floor,
from the corridor to the treatment room.
If someone were missing a leg,
we'd contact people at the scene...
CHO YUN-MI, FORMER NURSE
AT GANGNAM ST. MARY'S HOSPITAL
...and ask if anyone could look for a leg
that might be lying nearby.
Around a thousand patients
arrived at the ER
at Gangnam St. Mary's Hospital that day.
Dear me. What am I going to do?
Goodness me.
How can this happen?
LEE SEON-MIN
SAMPOONG COLLAPSE SURVIVOR
What I experienced back then
was absolute hell.
As a survivor, I've never once thought,
"I'm so glad I survived."
My family probably did
because they are my loved ones,
so if I had died back then,
they would have been in a lot of pain.
But as the person who went through it,
I wasn't all that happy about it.
Do you believe
you've lived well for those who died,
just as everyone wished?
I don't think so.
For about...
YOO JI-HWAN
SAMPOONG COLLAPSE SURVIVOR
...a year?
For about a year or a little longer,
I think I just let go of everything.
My mind wasn't all there.
I didn't want to live...
but I didn't want
to take my own life either.
I think that's how I felt back then.
So...
So back then...
THE ECHOES OF SURVIVORS:
INSIDE KOREA'S TRAGEDIES
JIN OK-JA
MOTHER OF SAMPOONG VICTIM JUNG CHANG-SUK
I think we went to karaoke
a few months before the accident in 1995.
Even after all this time,
her voice is still with me.
THE LATE JUNG CHANG-SUK
My daughter's name was Jung Chang-suk.
She lost her life
in the Sampoong Department Store collapse.
THE BABY STORE WHERE JUNG CHANG-SUK WORKED
I keep imagining her crying out for me
before she died.
SON SANG-CHEOL
BROTHER OF SAMPOONG VICTIM SON EUN-JU
People say
time heals the pain of losing loved ones.
You hope next year will be better.
But it's exactly the same.
You think, "Maybe the year after that?"
It's still exactly the same.
So
I think...
that was the hardest time of my life.
Even to this day.
JUNE 29, 2024
29TH ANNIVERSARY OF THE SAMPOONG TRAGEDY
It feels like just yesterday
I was trapped in that nightmare.
Thirty long years went by.
KIM DEOK-HWA, SON YEONG-SU
PARENTS OF SAMPOONG VICTIM SON GYEONG-A
But even now, she's still in my heart.
I always miss her,
long to see her, and feel deeply sorry.
I never knew the three syllables
of her name could carry so much sadness.
Even just thinking of her name
makes my heart ache.
SON GYEONG-A
She was my eldest daughter.
THE LATE SON GYEONG-A
You know, my daughter
was incredibly kind and gentle.
When I got to the scene,
it was more overwhelming
than I could have ever imagined.
It was on fire for days,
and it rained every day.
PRAYER VIGIL FOR VICTIMS OF THE COLLAPSE
So I...
A prayer room was set up there.
SO DO NOT FEAR, FOR I AM YOUR GOD
I WILL HELP AND UPHOLD YOU
So I prayed there, but at some point,
it started to feel selfish to be praying.
Because if she were alive under the ruins,
she'd be in so much pain.
So I started thinking
that if she was going to pass anyway...
I hoped she'd died in the fire
and turned to ashes
so she could finally rest.
SEOUL NATIONAL UNIVERSITY OF EDUCATION GYM
WAITING AREA FOR FAMILIES
OF MISSING PERSONS
They'd call the missing person's family
to confirm the body that was found.
When people saw
someone pack their things to leave...
...they would say, "Congratulations."
LIST OF THE DECEASED
KIM MUN-SU
BROTHER OF SAMPOONG VICTIM KIM HAK-SU
Those who were leaving first would say,
"Sorry for leaving first."
So people who had just found
their children's bodies
were congratulated on the way out,
and everyone sincerely meant it.
"SORRY FOR LEAVING FIRST"
"CONGRATULATIONS"
He was found in the basement,
and there was no skin left on his face.
He was nearly a skeleton.
What I saw at that moment
wasn't a skeleton
but my kind little brother.
I felt gratitude
and
a sense of guilt.
I guess
it was a mixed feeling
of anger and regret.
THE LATE KIM HAK-SU
So I held him in my arms...
before I knew it.
5 DAYS SINCE SAMPOONG COLLAPSE
RAINY SEASON
Heavier rain is expected
this rainy season than last year's,
so thorough preparation
for rain damage is advised.
The Korea Meteorological Administration
expects heavy rainfall this year...
I had no idea
how much time had passed, but suddenly,
I heard the sound of water.
I wondered if I could drink it,
so I put my mouth under it...
but it tasted like rusty water.
To be honest, at the time,
I think I was fighting on my own.
"I might starve to death."
"I could be crushed to death."
When I felt okay,
I thought, "I can survive this."
Other times,
"I'm going to die."
No one could have survived.
With all that water spraying
and the excavator digging,
even a survivor would die.
The news reported ongoing rescue efforts,
but it was strange because I saw
nothing happening at the scene.
Stop pushing!
Why are you telling us to stop pushing?
Don't be rough with him!
What the hell did you say?
Let go! Just kill me, you assholes!
- Sir, please calm down.
- I said just kill me!
Bring me my daughter!
You can't even rescue anyone, huh?
You people arrived two hours
after the media.
We were here before you!
What the hell is this crap?
Seriously,
it was... I mean...
I was just devastated.
JUNG GAK-HYEON, FORMER RESCUE TEAM
SEOCHO FIRE STATION
It was so heart-wrenching
that I remember it to this day.
As the search for survivors progressed,
we also began recovering bodies.
We found a mother's body
and began recovering it.
Then we found something else.
The body of a small child beneath hers.
It must have been
around two or three years old.
She was leaning forward,
protecting the child beneath her belly.
So the child was somewhat shielded
from all the concrete.
As for the mother... I mean,
she was crushed so badly
that it was hard to even identify her.
But thanks to the mother,
the child's body was somewhat intact.
10 DAYS SINCE SAMPOONG COLLAPSE
All right. Lift the legs.
Wrap it up.
Lift it up more.
Wrap it with this.
Move. Pouring water will make it stink.
- Yeah. That's fine.
- It's fine. Just wrap 'em up!
- Wrap the body up.
- Cover it.
- Come on, let go.
- We're done moving them.
- It's fine.
- Okay.
Cover it now.
Lift it up.
Lift it higher!
I had never seen bodies decay like that.
They had gotten so mushy,
you couldn't even recognize them.
We put them in the body bags we'd brought,
using only rubber gloves as our tools.
We'd put those on, gathered the remains,
and put them in the bag.
Honestly, I was scared.
It was truly horrifying work.
DECEASED INFORMATION
After a week, and then ten days,
more victims' bodies were discovered.
The count rose to 100, then 200, then 300.
The numbers just kept climbing.
I thought,
"This could reach into the thousands."
DEATH TOLL
We were recovering only the deceased,
no survivors.
And that definitely discouraged everyone.
No matter how hard we tried,
we found zero survivors.
But then...
ALIVE
Take one step back.
The unit commander suddenly radioed
that they couldn't see anyone
but did hear a voice.
GYEONG GWANG-SUK, FORMER RESCUE TEAM
DOBONG FIRE STATION
I was told to move
to the first basement level right away.
Someone was in there.
Can you hear me?
I said, "Can you hear me?"
and they said they could.
I asked what their name was,
and the survivor answered very clearly.
I rushed over to the central command
and informed them.
"We got a survivor."
"Male. Choi Myeong-seok."
He's coming out. Keep quiet.
- A bit more.
- Don't go in.
Please quiet down.
Get him up!
- Don't do that!
- Get him up.
11 DAYS SINCE SAMPOONG COLLAPSE
CHOI MYEONG-SEOK IS RESCUED
Grab the handle.
This morning,
a survivor was miraculously rescued
from the wreckage
of the Sampoong Department Store.
Twenty-year-old Choi Myeong-seok
was working part-time
at a store in the basement
when the building collapsed.
At 6:30 a.m. today,
after being trapped for 11 days,
he was found by the rescue team
and freed from the fear of death
following an hour and 40 minutes
of rescue efforts.
You survived miraculously.
Do you think there might be
other survivors like you?
I think there are.
Why do you think that?
It's just a feeling I have.
I'M GRATEFUL FOR EVERYONE'S CONCERN
CHOI MYEONG-SEOK
"Hang on."
"If this gentleman survived
and managed to pull through,
there might be more survivors.
Another Choi Myeong-seok."
After Choi Myeong-seok was rescued,
whenever we found
even the tiniest opening,
we called out to see if anyone was inside,
hoping for more survivors.
That's when I heard people.
I could hear them talking on the radio.
I began hearing it from a distance.
Then someone asked
if anyone was there.
Like, "Is anybody in there?"
So I responded,
but they didn't hear me.
So...
I think that's when I knocked
on the wall or something.
I was trying to make some sort of noise.
And they were saying,
"There's someone in here."
Let's go in this way.
And suddenly, I saw a hole near my feet.
I saw the foot move!
That's when they asked for my information.
I said, "My name's Yoo Ji-hwan,
I'm 18,
and I live in Suyu-ri."
RESCUE IN PROGRESS
FOR SURVIVOR YOO JI-HWAN
We've confirmed the identity
as 19-year-old Yoo Ji-hwan.
Ms. Yoo Ji-hwan, 19 years old.
The person you are seeing on the screen
is Ms. Yoo Ji-hwan.
Due to the high risk of injury
to Ms. Yoo Ji-hwan,
rescuers are manually securing space,
centimeter by centimeter.
It was so chaotic outside.
I could hear their entire exchange
over the radio.
They were saying
it would be difficult to rescue me.
So I asked him.
I said, "Mister, will I live?"
And what did he say?
That I will.
To wait a little longer for the rescue.
Honestly, at that moment, I thought,
"Even if I die, I can rest easy now,"
since they knew who I was.
Hey! Get her up!
I had held on this long,
so I felt like it was enough.
Ms. Yoo Ji-hwan
is now slowly being brought out
to the place of light,
back into the world of the living.
You are watching Ms. Yoo Ji-hwan's rescue.
Ms. Yoo Ji-hwan was miraculously rescued
from the narrow space
where she was trapped
and is now being carried to the ambulance
by the rescue team.
Ms. Yoo Ji-hwan was miraculously rescued...
No pictures!
...285 hours after the accident.
I was found on July 11,
meaning I was rescued
on the 13th day after the incident.
13 DAYS SINCE SAMPOONG COLLAPSE
YOO JI-HWAN IS RESCUED
YOO JI-HWAN, AN 18-YEAR-OLD MIRACLE
ANOTHER MIRACLE
MS. YOO JI-HWAN'S SURVIVAL
IT FELT LIKE I DOZED OFF FOR A WEEK
- Please tell us how you feel.
- Thrilled.
CHEON SEOK-GI, RESCUE TEAM LEADER
YEONGDEUNGPO FIRE STATION
This is why we do this,
and it makes us proud.
Let's go, Yeongdeungpo!
She was conscious when she...
The applause.
The way the public celebrated
and applauded us
truly gave us a boost of strength.
We were completely worn out,
but that really gave us strength.
Now, the parents...
Director.
If we could just get her name...
You must have been
really hungry and thirsty.
How did you cope?
I screamed.
She says she screamed.
Did you try drinking your own urine
when you got thirsty?
Try it yourself. It's impossible.
Was it impossible?
Good evening, everyone.
Another miracle occurred
at the site of the collapse.
Today, 17 days
after the Sampoong collapse,
Ms. Park Seung-hyeon, the third survivor
and just 19 years old...
MIRACULOUSLY RESCUED AFTER 17 DAYS
...returned to us safe and sound.
The meeting between the two girls,
whose survival gave us immeasurable joy,
was an emotional moment unlike any other.
I was in the children's wear section.
- Do you know who this is?
- Yes, I do.
Yes, I think so.
When were you rescued?
That filled me with immense hope.
These kids actually made it out alive.
We got a call at home.
It was a call for my father.
They told us they had found her,
so I thought that meant she was alive...
WE FOUND HER
...but...
She was listed as unidentified.
Because her remains
couldn't be recognized.
But her hand was still intact.
I think she was flattened like this...
by the concrete slab,
like a pancake.
There were reports that another survivor
besides Park Seung-hyeon had been found,
but upon verification,
no additional survivor was found.
Contrary to our hopes,
no other survivors were found.
Almost none of the other girls I was with
at the time managed to survive.
I also sometimes wonder
how I managed to get out of there alive.
I also thought about it a lot
after I got out.
"What happened?"
"How does something like this happen?"
GROSS NEGLIGENCE
Did a building that stood solidly
for five years just collapse?
No, the building didn't just stand firm
for five years and then suddenly collapse.
Structural deformation accumulated
over those five years.
That building was bound to collapse.
I talked to him on the phone
two days before the incident,
and he mentioned
hearing a noise in the ceiling.
There were partial power outages.
He told me several times
that the department store might collapse.
The key evidence
was a column we found
at the Nanjido Landfill.
According to structural calculations,
the columns should have been
80 cm in diameter,
but the columns we found at the scene
were only 60 cm in diameter.
ACTUAL DIAMETER: 60 CM
DIAMETER ON THE PLANS: 80 CM
And the columns were supposed to be
reinforced with 16 rods of rebar,
but as you can see here,
there are only eight.
It's about half.
REBARS ON THE PLANS: 16
ACTUAL NUMBER OF REBARS: 8
As a luxury department store,
they wanted it to look open and spacious.
Certain structures require support frames,
but they wanted them removed.
Repeated requests to remove certain parts
shaped the final product.
And when the building was rezoned,
they didn't change much in Building B,
but they made a lot of alterations
to Building A.
We specialize in making
these building frameworks.
Things like columns,
retaining walls, and slabs.
Looking into the cause,
I actually counted the rebar strands.
I counted every one of them precisely.
Even after 30 years, I still can't forget.
I wondered what kind of insane people
would do something like this.
I was absolutely speechless
that they had skipped rebar like this.
It was faulty construction for sure.
We gathered statements
from both the store staff who escaped
and people involved in the construction.
They told us about the emergency meeting
and where it was held.
4 HOURS BEFORE COLLAPSE
EXEC. MEETING 4 HOURS BEFORE COLLAPSE
They obviously held a meeting,
aware of the signs
that the building was about to collapse.
There was a big whiteboard in that room.
They had marked areas on it
that showed signs of collapse,
where pieces of concrete had fallen.
They wrote "Stay open or close?"
and marked O's and X's.
STAY OPEN
CLOSE
If the owners had even the slightest idea
that the building was showing
signs of collapse...
STAY OPEN
it would be gross negligence.
MEETING DECISION
KEEP CONFIDENTIAL AND CONTINUE OPERATIONS
REPAIR AFTER CLOSING TODAY
That's as bad
as deliberately committing murder.
RISK OF COLLAPSE WAS KNOWN
If they had just closed early,
they could have saved all those lives...
SCREAMS FOR HELP IN LIVING HELL
and avoided the financial loss as well.
One person's poor judgment
amplified the damage.
FREQUENT EXTENSIONS
CAUSED STRUCTURAL FATIGUE
SEOUL SEOCHO POLICE STATION
Come on.
"What did I do wrong
for you to come and arrest me?"
THE LATE LEE JUN
CHAIRMAN OF THE SAMPOONG DEPARTMENT STORE
AT THE TIME
MAJOR CRIMES UNIT 3
Why did you bring him here?
I thought he was being questioned.
Your employees told us
that serious signs of collapse began
about ten days ago.
- There is a CEO.
- Right.
The CEO is in charge.
And I only attend meetings
once a week as the chairman.
But the technical director says
he pointed out the risks
during the meeting.
Look here.
If a building collapses,
it's not only the customers who get hurt.
It would also damage
the company's property.
We'll wrap up after that.
Please say a few words.
He never even lowered his head.
Totally stiff-necked.
His arrogance was beyond words.
I felt the urge
to punch him and say,
"Have you lost your mind, old man?"
CIVIL SERVANTS AIDED AND ABETTED
COLLUSION BETWEEN SAMPOONG
AND CIVIL SERVANTS
DID NOT MEET STANDARDS
ILLEGAL EXTENSIONS, FALSIFIED DOCUMENTS
There is no way
civil servants weren't involved in this.
The Sampoong Department Store management
colluded with relevant officials
from the Seocho-gu Office,
which had jurisdiction over the store,
involving connections and bribery.
CIVIL SERVANTS GO INTO HIDING
The civil servants in supervision
are always the first to disappear
whenever major incidents take place.
This incident was no exception.
All nine civil servants involved
from the Seocho-gu Office fled
after the incident.
First thing in the morning,
we went there to look for those
involved in the case,
but it was as if the building
was abandoned.
No one had come in that day.
My detectives came back and said,
"They all ran off."
So we were unable to obtain statements
from any of the civil servants.
They went into hiding.
The civil servants who fled
after the Sampoong collapse
are now wanted by police.
Lee Seung-gu served
as director of urban redevelopment
at the Seocho-gu Office
from March 1989 to July 1990.
He is suspected of illegally issuing
rezoning and interim use permits
in exchange for a total bribe
of ten million won over two occasions.
They are skillfully evading capture,
but unlike other cases,
public tips have been lacking,
making it hard to catch the suspects.
I think it was all about money.
Lee Jun, the chairman,
acted that way because of money.
The civil servants who took bribes
did so for the money.
Same goes for the person
who issued the permit.
Would they have done that
if it weren't for money?
For these people,
money was far more important than people.
I mean, where does greed even end?
MONEY OVER PEOPLE
We're seeing many shameless looters
posing as volunteers at the collapse site.
When I first heard
that they had arrested a looter
at the scene,
I couldn't believe it.
The Sampoong Department Store
sold many expensive items,
and some people openly admitted
that they thought they could steal
cash or checks if they went to the scene.
- Go on.
- Just wait.
Go slowly.
Wait. Slow down.
Slow down.
We cracked down
on almost 800 cases of looting.
Get a move on, punk.
Sit on the chair.
On the chair. Hey, you!
I saw a lady there.
Looking back, she was carrying
a bunch of fur coats.
I mean,
I didn't think much of it at the time,
but in hindsight, she was stealing them.
I thought they weren't even human.
I want to ask them if they're happy.
With the money they stole, I mean.
ONE MONTH AFTER SAMPOONG COLLAPSE
It's been a month since
the Sampoong Department Store collapsed.
Now that 34,000 tons of debris
have been cleared,
they are working
to recover the merchandise.
By the 25th day,
all rescue efforts had effectively ended.
But then,
all of a sudden,
the families of the victims
whose bodies hadn't been recovered
lay down in front of the rescue teams
as they tried to leave.
They said, "No."
I'm gonna kill them.
Those sons of bitches,
telling the volunteers to leave.
If the rescuers were leaving,
it meant they wouldn't be doing
any more work at the scene.
So they were asking
how they would ever find their loved one.
The families of the missing victims knew
the debris had been dumped
at the Nanjido Landfill.
So they went to the Nanjido Landfill
and searched for the belongings
of their family member.
But did they just find their belongings?
No.
No one thought
there could be bodies or remains there.
They were so focused
on clearing the scene quickly
that they loaded everything
onto the trucks and dumped it there.
Those huge trucks dumped everything
at the Nanjido Landfill.
So the mothers went there
hoping to find traces of their children.
People went there, day after day,
to search for anything they could find.
NANJIDO LANDFILL
We took turns going there every day.
Every time they dumped debris.
We dug around the piles with a hoe,
hoping we'd find something.
We cleared the rocks
to look for bone fragments.
We took hoes and similar tools,
knocked the rocks aside,
and looked for anything
that might be bone fragments.
Some people found only a hand,
while others found only a foot.
Someone found only a finger
and held a funeral with it.
One of the bones we found
belonged to our daughter.
Nothing we could recognize her by.
They ran DNA tests
using my blood and the two kids'.
They told us the bone was hers,
so we accepted it.
- We couldn't tell.
- It was hard to believe the test.
Now that I think about it,
I believe it was her arm.
It was just like a cut of meat
at the butcher's.
There were no fingers, no toes. Nothing.
It was just...
like a piece of meat.
Did you not find
a single part of her body?
I found nothing.
My daughter was one of the missing.
One of the 31 who weren't found.
There was nothing.
I saw nothing.
NANJIDO NOEUL PARK
Later on, I began to envy
those who found a body.
I thought she must have really hated me,
keeping me from seeing her body
or even a trace of her.
That I must have been a bad mother.
937 INJURED
502 DECEASED
31 BODIES NOT FOUND
THE COST OF SURVIVAL
- The Sampoong Department Store.
- Yes.
The three survivors,
Mr. Choi Myeong-seok, Ms. Yoo Ji-hwan,
and Ms. Park Seung-hyeon
are joining us today.
I'd never been through anything like that.
THE SAMPOONG MIRACLE TRIO
Being interviewed, appearing on TV...
YOO JI-HWAN
SPECIAL GUESTS!
YOO JI-HWAN, PARK SEUNG-HYEON
At first, I didn't see anything wrong.
I guess I was just going with the flow
back then.
I saw it as a way to repay the public
for their support and care.
But...
at some point,
it started to feel like a burden.
The three of you should always remember
that you're living for everyone
who was there.
You must strive
to be your best selves and succeed.
The two, I mean the three of you,
will go down in history.
- Right.
- Things will go well from now on.
You'll never see another bad day.
The rest of us
will watch you live your lives
and be inspired by you.
I was simply a victim
of an unexpected incident.
I'm just an ordinary person
who somehow managed to hold out
and make her way out of there.
But I became someone
who wasn't allowed to make any mistakes.
Everyone asked
how much compensation I got.
"Hey, you won the lottery."
They told me I won the lottery.
LOTTO
SPORTS TOTO
And what else did they say?
"You're set for life."
In accidents like this, compensation
is the first thing people bring up.
Compensation.
They put money before life, saying,
"We'll compensate you well."
"Is this all about money?"
Those words crush us completely.
Money is meaningless. I mean,
if God offered
to bring my brother back to life
for ten times the compensation I got,
I would ask for him back immediately,
even if it meant I'd be in debt
for the rest of my life.
I mean,
who would trade a life for money?
Thank you.
Why did you agree to the interview?
At first, I had no intention of doing it.
Well, it's been so long already,
and bringing it up again
to think about that situation
isn't really something I want to do.
My appearance here as a survivor
might hurt the families of victims
who didn't make it,
reminding them of their own children.
You see,
looking back on the incident
is extremely difficult.
But I agreed to do this interview because...
Because if we don't,
everyone in Korea will just forget.
They always do.
Please help spread this,
even if it's a hassle.
Some people might say,
"After the Sampoong Department Store
collapsed, killing all those people,
could it happen again?"
But...
Yesterday afternoon,
the exterior wall of a building collapsed
at an apartment complex construction site
in Gwangju.
When the apartment building
in Gwangju collapsed...
and I saw the pictures on TV,
it looked just like the Sampoong collapse.
That was just last year.
That's the "Boneless Apartment" incident
from last year.
Upon investigating all apartments
commissioned by LH,
it was found
that 15 other complexes lacked rebar.
They forgot what happened 30 years ago.
They completely forgot.
It's enough to drive you mad.
THE SAMPOONG DEPARTMENT STORE
WAS FULLY DEMOLISHED ON JANUARY 30, 1999
RESIDENTS OPPOSED TO A MEMORIAL PARK
OVER PROPERTY VALUE FEARS
OF ALL THE PERPETRATORS,
INCLUDING CIVIL SERVANTS,
LEE JUN RECEIVED THE LONGEST SENTENCE
OF 7 YEARS AND 6 MONTHS IN PRISON
THE SAMPOONG SITE NOW HOLDS
A HIGH-RISE MIXED-USE BUILDING,
NOT A MEMORIAL
I don't think the Sampoong tragedy
has ever truly ended in Korean society.
I believe it keeps repeating
in different forms,
in different places,
and under different names.
JINDO, APRIL 2014
It was the same with the Sewol ferry.
They overloaded the ferry for money,
out of greed.
And the civil servants allowed it again.
And the flooding of the Osong underpass.
OSONG, JULY 2023
We are constantly met with incidents
that keep reminding us
of the Sampoong Department Store.
MUAN, DECEMBER 2024
We should never forget those disasters.
And to those who lost their child...
Do you think
this is really in the past for them?
Do you think you could die at any moment?
Yes.
I do think so.
Nothing would be surprising at any time,
especially here in South Korea.
OVER THE PAST 45 YEARS,
58 SUCH TRAGEDIES HAVE OCCURRED IN KOREA
WE ARE ALL SURVIVORS
Subtitle translation by: Sung In Jang