[Love of Petals]
[Episode 6]
Mr. Lyu, I'd like to become
sworn brothers with you.
What do you think?
Mr. Sun, you're an upright man.
It would be my honor to become sworn brothers
with you.
Wonderful.
That's great.
From today on,
we are sworn brothers.
Let's share joys
and hardships together.
Count me in.
Let's share joys and hardships together.
Let's have a few more drinks to celebrate today.
We're out of wine.
I want more.
There's none left. I'll go get another jug.
Master,
I thought you didn't want to meddle in the mortal world affairs.
Why did you become sworn brothers with Pingkang?
By becoming sworn brothers with Sun Pingkang,
I'll have a reason
to legitimately stay at the Sun's Mansion.
And
find a way to retrieve the Flower Spirit.
Master,
you can teach me immortal cultivation
from now on.
You can be my legitimate master
-and teach me immortal magic.
-Her dream is full of Sun Pingkang now
because Sun Pingkang is in trouble now.
If you solve her problem
and guide her to recall her past,
then I'll have my chance.
I will definitely succeed in my cultivation!
Then you must practice diligently.
Don't disappoint me.
I will heed your teachings, Master.
Master, let's have another drink.
Where's the wine?
So,
to find out whether her past
is reated to the Flower Spirit,
you need to get her drunk.
After you get her drunk,
leave the rest to me.
But remember,
she has to be completely drunk.
Pingkang went to get more wine.
Why hasn't he come back?
Actually,
I have...
Let's drink this one.
I'd like
to propose a toast to you.
Come on.
Cheers!
I'll drink.
Father said we need to revive
999 flowers and plants.
Only then will the Flowers Immortal Lord come.
I didn't expect you
to arrive early.
Gu Qingcheng.
You're drunk?
I'm not drunk.
Then tell me,
besides seeing that Immortal Lord in your dreams,
what other
magical things have you encountered?
Meeting you,
is that
the most magical thing?
Same old story.
Think carefully.
Have you seen anything or
anyone strange?
Anything strange...
Anyone strange...
Strange...
Let's drink.
Unreliable Ye You.
I'll teach you a few sword moves.
Watch carefully.
Master, this move is really beautiful.
Don't just focus on the beauty of the moves.
Feel every move
with your heart.
♫A flower blooms, a thought arises♫
Yes, Master.
I'll remember that.
♫A thought descends into the dust of fate♫
♫Fate stirs, whose gaze lingers with longing?♫
♫Stirring dreams of joy deep within the heart♫
♫Light, still lingering♫
♫For the days and nights are too brief♫
♫Before we share the rain's refrain♫
♫A falling star, two eyes embrace♫
Gu Qingcheng.
♫In this world, blossoms fall like dreams, countless as the stars♫
♫Yet no radiant light compares to the grace of your gaze♫
Come here.
♫Through storm and snow, love carves its trace♫
Master.
♫Reluctantly, I take one last lingering look♫
♫I vow to stay, through time and tide♫
♫Like morning dew, unswayed, untried♫
♫A single tear, a thousand words♫
Why are you turning it off?
I told you to look into her dreams for clues about the Flower Spirit.
What exactly did you see?
I can't control what she dreams about.
Besides,
you two just now
sharing an umbrella in the rain,
dancing with swords in the peach grove,
locking eyes in the flower field.
Young girls nowadays love this kind of thing, huh?
What? What's wrong?
Can you shut up?
Yes.
But my silence won't change anything.
This girl's mind is full of you now.
Can you really bear to take the Flower Spirit from her?
Of course.
Well, if you really want to take it,
I have a more direct method.
It's just that you might need to
sacrifice yourself a bit.
Keep your silly ideas to yourself.
It's not silly. It'll work.
Just consider it, will you?
What's with those expressions?
Can't stand to see it.
Go away.
What's that?
Master.
I went to the back mountain and collected fresh dew.
Master,
here's the fresh dew I collected.
Master.
Where did he go?
He's not outside,
nor inside.
Gu Qingcheng.
I heard you're about to
marry Pingkang.
Ma'am,
don't listen to their nonsense.
The Lord himself told me
and asked me to arrange your wedding.
But
if you want to be the daughter-in-law of the Sun family,
you still have a lot to learn from me.
You'll need my help and support in the future.
It seems the marriage with Pingkang
can't be delayed any longer.
Ye You didn't find anything useful from her dream,
but a bunch of frivolous thoughts.
I can't trust his silly ideas anymore.
I need to think of my own way.
I haven't had time to properly decorate the flower nursery lately.
When you're done,
you must help me take good care of the flower nursery.
Master, why are you here?
Master, why... why did you just show up like that?
Why are you here?
No, Master, I should be asking you.
Why did you suddenly appear here?
What exactly are you doing?
Why aren't you dressed?
I was taking a bath. You're peeking at me.
This is my room!
Who's in your...
But this is clearly my room!
I'm not even married yet!
How could you do this to me?
Stop shouting!
Why do I always end up in front of
Gu Qingcheng for no reason?
Why is it exactly?
Master, what are you doing?
Master.
What are you up to?
Could it be
that my Flower Spirit is connected to her bloodline?
So whenever she bleeds,
I get summoned over.
Turn around.
Gu Qingcheng.
I have a gift for you.
What's this?
Try it on.
Master, why are you
suddenly giving me a gift?
This bracelet
can protect your hands from harm.
You're a gardener.
You need to take good care of your hands.
Master,
how did you know that a gardener's hands
are always hurt and full of cuts?
So you won't cut yourself again
and summon me for no reason.
It's beautiful. Thank you, Master.
Master,
I've decided to gather my courage and do one thing tomorrow.
Master, do you think I'll succeed?
I will, right?
Will I?
No matter what it takes,
I have to succeed.
Father,
there's something
I hope you'll grant me.
Tell me whatever you need.
I'll
agree to anything.
What are you doing?
Father,
I hope
you'll agree
to cancel my engagement to Pingkang.
Are you here to speak for Pingkang?
No,
I'm here for myself.
Do you not like it here?
No, Father,
I like it here very much.
I grew up in the Sun's Mansion since I was little.
This place is already
a home to me.
Father and Mother love me,
and Pingkang takes good care of me.
It's just that, Father,
I see Pingkang
as a sibling,
not a lover.
Father,
can you understand?
Pingkang.
Qingcheng.
What brings you here?
Mother asked the kitchen
to make your favorite sweet soup.
Try some.
What's wrong?
Why do you look so worried?
Is something bothering you?
Pingkang,
I came here today
because I have something to share with you.
Father...
has agreed to cancel our engagement.
W-what?
Father has agreed to cancel our engagement!
Father.
Pingkang will surely find
someone he truly loves.
Since neither of you
wants this marriage,
let's officially cancel it.
From now on,
you're no longer my daughter-in-law,
but
the young lady of our Sun family.
Qingcheng,
you're determined to participate in the Floral Competition
and win the championship.
I support you.
Go ahead and do it without worries.
Father.
You're always the one with the solutions.
From now on, we're no longer
bound by this engagement.
We're truly siblings now.
To siblings.
My painting.
I just knocked on the door several times
but you didn't answer.
So you were
painting...
It's not what you think.
I've been free recently,
and a client happened to ask for my help.
I thought I could earn a little money.
However,
the client requested
that I must not let anyone else see it.
I won't say a word.
Don't worry. Go on.
Remember to drink the sweet soup.
Your soup.
Both bowls are yours.
So your brilliant plan is
to have me stand here like a wooden statue?
How could you be a wooden statue?
In Miss Gu's eyes,
you are the most beautiful peony in the world.
This is the last time I trust you.
If it fails,
I'll pluck out your immortal root.
Here she comes.
Master, you look quite different today.
You look quite
different too.
Very happy?
Father
has agreed to annul
my marriage to Pingkang.
Breaking off the engagement?
Could it be because of me?
It's unexpected
you'd propose to break off the engagement.
Why?
This marriage
was arranged by our parents in the first place.
I didn't like it, but I didn't have the courage to speak up.
This time I mustered up a lot of courage to bring it up.
It wasn't
as hard as I imagined.
Was it?
Your courage is commendable.
To reward your bravery,
I'll
give you a gift.
Master, you have another gift for me?
What's this?
This is...
One-of-a-kind in the world—
the Truth Powder.
Pearl powder?
Yes, pearl powder.
Pearl powder is best for beauty and skin care.
You've been so tired taking care of me lately.
You really need it.
Find a good chance
to make Miss Gu inhale
this powder.
She'll open up to you and tell you
everything about her life.
At that time, getting the Flower Spirit
will be so easy.
How about
you come closer and take a sniff?
You're so indecisive.
Just blow it
onto her face.
Master,
both you and this powder
are a bit strange today.
The finest pearl powder.
Donkey.
How could there be a donkey in the Sun's Mansion?
Bad news, My Lady!
My Lady, bad news!
What's wrong?
It's the Young Master. The Young Master...
What happened to him?
Well...
You... I...
Zisu, are you alright?
It's not me. I didn't mean to--
What did you say about Pingkang just now?
He... he went to Tianxiang House.
Why would he go to Tianxiang House?
Pingkang isn't into women or alcohol.
There must be something wrong.
Let's go take a look.
Master, wait for me.
What...
Sir, you look unfamiliar.
When did you come in?
Oh no.
Its side effect is talking while hugging people.
Wait, wait, young lady.
Calm down, please calm down.
Get... get down!
Sir, I'm very calm.
Calm down.
Why is your grip so strong?
Help!
Sir, you've already had your third pot today.
Hurry up, bring another pot.
Please wait a moment, sir.
The Xiaoyao wine will be served soon.
Mr. Han, are you satisfied with the food and wine?
Master, the people in here are acting strange.
Why did Pingkang come here?
Has he forgotten about Si Shulun
who died mysteriously at Tianxiang House?
This is not a good place at all.
Don't worry, he won't recognize us.
I've temporarily cast a forgetting spell on him.
I suppose it's the first
time of you visiting here.
Would you like to drink or watch the dance?
We're just looking around.
Just looking around?
Bring me two pots of
your best wine.
We're here to drink... to drink.
You've come to the right place.
We have every kind of wine.
Which one would you like?
For my wife and I,
which one do you recommend?
There are private rooms upstairs.
Please.
This way, please.
If I catch Pingkang,
I'll teach him a lesson.
My dear.
This way, please.
Please, come in.
Master.
Please enjoy your meal.
Master,
shouldn't we
quickly go find Pingkang?
My dear,
now that we're here,
let's enjoy ourselves.
Please.
My dear.
Wuyuzi, what are you peeking at?
Last time I was beaten so badly by that Jade-Eyed Fox.
I don't want any more trouble.
Master,
I can't drink anymore. My alcohol tolerance is low.
We're being watched.
What?
What should we do?
Wuyuzi.
I think they're just here for some drinks and entertainment.
I have to make sure.
We have to...
Is this the only way, Master?
Alright, alright.
We've seen all kinds of customers.
Let me take another...
Let's go.
We shouldn't stay here long.
Once we find Sun Pingkang,
let's leave quickly.
Why are you still sitting there?
Stay close to me.
Oh no.
Gu Qingcheng.
Gu Qingcheng!
This can't be.
You're back.
You haven't finished today's lessons yet.
You went out to play again.
Mother.
Look.
Why are you crying?
Did those little monsters
from Shouyang Mountain
bully you again?
I'll go and demand justice for you.
What exactly happened
on the night of lunar March 7th?
Why did you and Father
disappear overnight?
It's alright.
I'll tell you later.
Once someone enters Master's Illusory Realm,
it's not easy to get out.
But that Lyu Gengyun has powerful magic.
Can this Illusory Realm alone
really trap him?
Then let him see
something he desires but can never have.
When he's consumed by desire,
that's when we'll strike.
Qiansi,
hold back Sun Pingkang and that girl.
Make sure they don't meet up.
Understood.
Strange.
Shouldn't the Tianxiang House be bustling?
Why is there not a single person here today?
That girl only said
to deliver this painting to the entrance of Tianxiang House,
but didn't specify the exact location.
Where should I look for her?
Mr. Sun.
Miss,
here's the painting you asked.
I have finished it
and brought it here for you.
Thank you, Mr. Sun.
Why don't you come in and sit a while?
I'll treat you to
the best wine in our Tianxiang House.
Come on, Mr. Sun.
No, no.
I
have urgent matters at home.
I'll
take my leave now.
Sir, won't you come in for a drink?
I'll... I'll come another day.
Where are you going, sir?
Are you done with your act?
How dare you offend my mother!
I didn't expect you to see through it.
I'll kill you!
Master, help!