[Love of Petals]
[Episode 20]
Don't worry.
I won't let your sacrifice be in vain.
One day,
I will go to Lotus Island
and use the lotus
to reconstruct your physical body.
Moreover,
I will promote you
as the candidate
for the next Flower God.
I'll follow your arrangements.
[Remove the diseases; Long-term use lightens the body, boosts energy, and extends life.]
[Tiandong, bitter taste, neutral nature, mainly treats sudden rheumatism and paralysis, strengthens the bone marrow, kills three types of parasites.]
For your own selfish desires,
you didn't even spare your own follower.
Those who achieve great things don't sweat the small stuff.
To sacrifice for me
is also his honor.
Since the matter has been clarified,
steward,
write the truth in an official announcement and post it
to clear Gu Qingcheng's
name.
Yes.
Gu Qingcheng,
since you were wrongly accused,
the champion of this Floral Competition
naturally belongs to you.
In this brocade box
is a supreme elixir.
After you take it,
you can directly reach Mystic Branch Stage.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Master.
[Qingcheng Flower Nursery]
Your Excellency.
Are you waiting for someone?
It's my fault for not managing my subordinates strictly.
Regarding the incident with Tiandong,
I formally apologize to you.
I hope this doesn't become
a barrier between us.
Qingcheng,
will you forgive me?
This matter had nothing to do with you in the first place.
You don't need my forgiveness.
It's just that...
Tiandong has already become a celestial attendant,
yet he still harbors evil thoughts out of jealousy.
It seems that immortals and mortals are not so different.
When facing inner desires,
they are equally susceptible to worldly temptations.
You shouldn't biased against the Heavenly Realm
because of one person.
Qingcheng,
you've been caught up in trivial matters lately,
and haven't come to practice the Buhua Stone with me.
Today,
I'll help you catch up on
everything you've missed.
I know
you're not aiming for immortality,
but the Buhua Stone
is only for saving people,
not for achieving immortality.
Your Excellency,
could you tell me honestly,
how long does it take to achieve the Buhua Stone?
It depends on one's innate talent.
With your aptitude,
it certainly won't take too long.
But I've read in ancient texts
that the last person who succeeded
took over ten thousand years.
Qingcheng,
you no longer trust me?
It's not that.
As long as there's enough time,
I won't give up
even the slightest hope.
[Qingcheng Flower Nursery]
But now,
Master has broken through the Red Spider Lily barrier
and lost its protection.
He may lose control of his demonic nature and be in danger at any time.
I...
I'm afraid I can't wait.
So let's forget about it.
So it's indeed because of
Lyu Gengyun that you're giving up your path to immortality.
Gu Qingcheng,
you've already obtained the elixir
and can directly reach Mystic Branch Stage.
Giving up like this
is really not worth it.
I didn't take the elixir Princess Ning gave me.
What?
For the remaining days,
I don't want to think about anything else.
I just want to be with Master,
travel across the beautiful landscapes,
see all the famous mountains and rivers,
and accompany him
through his last days.
Your Excellency,
if there's nothing else,
I'll take my leave now.
[Qingcheng Flower Nursery]
Master!
Look at the flowers I just picked.
Lyu Gengyun,
you, half-demon, half-immortal,
could easily steal the show
in the Celestial Court.
Now that you've luckily survived
and easily snatch away the person I've set my eyes on.
Why on earth?
Qingcheng gave up her promising immortal path for Lyu Gengyun.
Senior sister gave up
the prestigious position of Flower Goddess for Bai Yu.
Why can they always get what they want,
while I
am always the one being abandoned?
The stems are still moist.
There's still hope.
No, wait.
This flower grows in such a dry stone wall.
It can't take too much water.
Son,
did your parents teach you
how to nurture plants?
My parents died when I was born.
No one taught me.
I figured
all these things out by myself.
You have quite a talent
[Primordial Lord]
for nurturing plants,
and you have no one to rely on.
Would you like to go to heaven with me
and be my flower attendant?
[Young Yuxiao]
Heaven?
I am the immortal in charge of
all the flowers and plants in the world.
They all call me...
-Immortal?
-Primordial Lord.
I'd like to.
My Tian'er!
Where are you?
Didn't we agree that
it's dangerous on the mountain
[Yuxiao's Grandma]
and you wouldn't go pick herbs for me?
My bad.
Hearing that you have no parents,
I thought you were alone and helpless.
I didn't expect
that you live with your grandma.
I can't separate you from your family.
As for immortal cultivation,
let's wait until the right opportunity comes.
Grandma,
I failed to get the medicine for you today.
Grandma!
Grandma.
I'm sorry, Grandma.
I was wrong.
Grandma.
Grandma!
Primordial Lord!
I have no more attachments in this world.
Please take me to heaven!
Are you sure about this?
Yes.
I've made up my mind.
From now on,
you are my disciple.
Lyu Gengyun,
I will make Qingcheng
see your ugliest face.
I will make everyone turn against you.
I will completely
destroy you.
It's you.
Why are you here
in the middle of the night?
The night is dark and the wind is strong.
The cold moon is heartless.
All lovers in this world
should sacrifice themselves to the moon.
Lyu Gengyun,
Gu Qingcheng is now in danger.
How can you stand by and do nothing?
Gu Qingcheng's life
is in your hands.
She's possessed by demons.
If it weren't for the Demon King...
Master, save me!
she'll definitely not survive.
Master, please save me!
Master.
Master, come and save me!
[Peace and Clarity]
[Qingcheng Flower Nursery]
Qingcheng,
rest in peace.
Ye You, watch your mouth.
I...
Have a safe trip.
Take good care of yourself.
We'll all miss you.
Please take care of
the Qingcheng Flower Nursery.
Don't worry,
we'll take good care of it.
Come back soon.
Oh, by the way,
I made some pastries the day before yesterday.
Take them to eat on the way.
That's thoughtful of you.
Let Hong accompany you on the way.
Hong?
Hong seems to like you more.
[Qingcheng Flower Nursery]
Maybe it should stay here with you.
Why isn't Master ready yet?
Qingcheng!
Pingkang.
Qingcheng,
something's happened at the Sun's Mansion.
Why are they so cold?
They're still breathing,
but very faintly.
How could this happen?
What should we do, Pingkang?
Gu Qingcheng.
[Peace and Clarity]
Where are you?
Gu Qingcheng.
Qingcheng!
-Wushuang!
Wushuang.
Don't go over there.
Master has lost his mind!
Qingcheng!
Master.
Where is Qingcheng?
I am Qingcheng.
I am Gu Qingcheng.
Master.
It's me.
Qingcheng.
Master!
Master.
Mr. Lyu.
Master, wake up.
Wake up, Master!
This is impossible.
Gu Qingcheng actually broke the inner demon I planted.
Doctor,
how is he doing?
This disease is extremely rare.
I've only seen similar symptoms
in a medical book.
Let me check back home.
But the chances of saving him are slim.
Qingcheng.
Master.
Easy.
Qingcheng.
You're awake.
How could I harm people at the Sun's Mansion?
I just went to find you
and heard your cry for help.
I didn't hurt them.
I know.
I believe you.
I'm sorry. I...
I hurt you again.
You didn't hurt me.
It's me.
It's alright.
Does it hurt?
I'm sorry.
Don't worry, Master.
Everything will be alright.
[Peace and Clarity]
Father.
Here.
Slowly.
Qingcheng.
Father.
Doctor.
All the best doctors in Pingcheng
have all examined him,
but none have any solutions.
I'm afraid...
Have some water, Pingkang.
I feel like this is
aimed at me and Master.
Master is now bedridden and unable to act,
but we have to find a solution.
Why don't
I go and ask Immortal Yuxiao for help?
Maybe he will have a solution.
I suppose that's all we can do now.
This illness is strange.
I'm afraid it's not a mortal disease.
Could it be...
that Mr. Lyu
lost control of his demonic nature
and that's why
he fed on people's life force?
It can't be.
Master would never do such a thing.
I also believe Mr. Lyu
wouldn't do something like this.
But
once his demonic nature takes over,
he'll gradually lose his sanity.
Maybe he didn't mean to.
But...
He...
Pingkang,
I believe him.
What should we do now?
There's a flower called the Soul-Calling Flower.
It not only can replenish one's essence blood,
but also can sustain life.
Although it's in the back mountain,
it's extremely difficult to find.
I'll go and try to find it.
Qingcheng,
let me go instead.
You stay here
to take care of the Sun's Mansion
and Mr. Lyu.
In case
he loses control again.
only you
can calm him down.
Pingkang,
now everyone in the Sun's Mansion
has been infected with this strange disease.
Why are you the only one unaffected?
I don't know.
Let's not talk about this now.
Saving people is the priority.
I'll go find the Soul-Calling Flower.
I'll go with you.
It'll be safer this way.
Okay.
Is there any?
No.
Be careful.
Thank you.
The Soul-Calling Flowers on the mountain
have been destroyed by someone already.
Could it be that someone is targeting your family?
Our family has always been kind to others.
We've never made enemies with anyone.
Who would want to harm us?
It's alright.
There must be new
Soul-Calling Flowers somewhere on the mountain.
Let's keep looking.
Soul-Calling Flower.
Here.
This is the last Soul-Calling Flower.
Give it to me.
Another old acquaintance.
Wushuang!
It's you.
You're the one trying to harm our family, aren't you?
Those who stand in my way shall die.
Blame
your own bad luck.
Take it out
on me!
Wushuang.
Are you alright?
Wushuang!
I'm sorry.
I failed to protect the Soul-Calling Flower.
Wushuang.
♫How can we predict the separation and reunion?♫
Let's hold on a little longer.
I... I'll take you back to Qingcheng Flower Nursery.
They'll surely find a way to save you.
♫I'm obsessed with you in every life♫
Wushuang.
Wushuang!
♫Can you recall the traces of our bond?♫
♫How do you see through the means of fate?♫
I remember
♫The mortal world is our chess board and we have some regrets♫
this is how you held me
♫Longings are blooming all over the lake again♫
the first time
when you took me out of the cage.
♫Time can solve all problems♫
♫But it just stands by♫
Miss.
♫I'm willing to use all my courage♫
♫For the happiness of the next life♫
I know
you've always been good to me.
♫For you♫
Confucius said,
♫I'm willing to keep searching with joy and sorrow♫
"Born and grown,
peerless in beauty."
How about I call you Wushuang (as in peerless)?
♫With you♫
♫It's never too late as long as we are together♫
Wushuang's wish
is my wish.
If there's an afterlife,
♫In dreams, fleeting as flowers, may we turn and look back♫
♫Spring returns, and our reunion shining bright at last♫
I'll give you...
♫A path home, paved with petals so grand♫
♫I know you're waiting on the other end♫
♫Just as I have wished♫
Wushuang.
Wushuang!
Wushuang, look at me.
Look at me, Wushuang!
Wushuang, look at me! Wushuang!
Wushuang!
♫Just as I have wished♫
The poem says that
♫For you♫
red beans are the most symbolic of longing.
♫I'm willing to keep searching with joy and sorrow♫
It must be a precious gift.
I picked these in the Misty Forest.
♫With you♫
For you.
♫It's never too late as long as we are together♫
Red beans grow in the southern land.
How many branches will sprout in spring?
♫In dreams, fleeting as flowers, may we turn and look back♫
May you pick more of them.
Because these beans are symbols of longing.
♫Spring returns, and our reunion shining bright at last♫
♫A path home, paved with petals so grand♫
♫I know you're waiting on the other end♫
♫In dreams, fleeting as flowers, may we turn and look back♫
Wushuang!
♫Spring returns, and our reunion shining bright at last♫
♫A path home, paved with petals so grand♫
[Longing Beans, From the Tang Dynasty]
[Red beans are symbols of longing; Every inch of longing turns to ash.]
[In the southern land, a few branches sprout in spring; Pick some to send your longing.]