[Love of Petals]
[Episode 2]
[Sun's Mansion]
[Master Sun, Sun's Mansion]
[Eldest Madam, Sun's Mansion]
The weather is so hot that I'm getting dizzy.
How about
I ask someone to bring some ice here
to help you get cool, Dear?
Don't bother.
I'll go lie down in my room for a while first.
My Lord!
My Lady!
My Lord! My Lady!
Great news! Great news!
Young Master has passed the local examination
and become a scholar!
Heaven truly rewards those who persevere.
The Sun Family's ancestors have blessed us.
Pingkang has finally passed the exam and become a scholar.
That's great.
Pingkang will come back tomorrow.
Everyone, get busy and prepare for it!
-Yes!
-Yes, My Lady!
Good, good, good.
We should start preparing for it.
When Pingkang comes back this time,
we can arrange his marriage with Qingcheng
at the same time.
It's a double celebration!
It's all up to you, Dear.
Good, good, good.
That's great!
[Sun's Mansion]
Congratulations!
Thanks for your congratulations!
Thank you!
I want it, too! I want it, too!
Here's some for you.
Thank you so much! Thank you!
Thank you, everyone!
Thank you all for your support!
When our Young Master and Young Lady get married,
we'll give out red envelopes to everyone again!
[Sun Pingkang, Young Master of Sun's Mansion]
Thank you.
[Si Shulun, Young Master of Si's Mansion]
When he was studying in the private school,
he was just Young Master Si's errand boy.
Exactly.
Who would have thought that he'd be so lucky?
Where's the justice in that?
Everyone here can get a share of it.
Thanks for your congratulations!
[Sun's Mansion]
There's plenty for everyone!
Young Master!
This distinguished scholar can't even dismount from his horse.
He's just a low-ranking scholar.
What's there to congratulate him on?
He doesn't even know how to dismount.
He's truly a laughingstock.
Mr. Si.
You and I were once classmates.
Our conflicts in the academy
shouldn't be brought here.
Your behavior
is truly disrespectful.
Now that you're back home, you're really different.
You even dare
to lecture me now.
Do you remember the times when we were at the academy?
Back then,
you didn't even dare
to let out a fart.
What's that?
What is this?
It's natural high-quality fertilizer.
Let me pour some on you all
so that you can be smarter.
You...
Who is this?
You bastard!
How dare you pour such filthy stuff
in front of me!
In terms of filth, no one can be compared with you.
You're just jealous of those who are better than you.
That's ridiculous!
Why
would I be jealous of him?
He's just a low-ranking scholar.
It's questionable
whether he has any real talent.
Pingkang's scholar title was granted by the imperial court.
By questioning him now,
you're also questioning the imperial court.
You...
Guards!
As this person tried to slander the imperial court
and bring bad luck to this joyous day,
help me drive him away!
Who are you?
Hurry up!
Don't touch me!
Stay away from me!
Sun Pingkang!
You're a coward!
You're only capable of hiding behind a woman!
You...
Qingcheng.
You're only capable of hiding behind a woman!
That's not real talent at all.
It's a joyous day, so let's just go back quickly.
Don't make our parents worry.
Don't touch me!
Pingkang.
Let's go back.
Then I'll do as you said.
Do you dare to touch me?
Sun Pingkang!
My Lady!
Don't run away!
Just wait and see!
Sun Pingkang!
Calm down, calm down, Mr. Si.
I'm so angry!
[Lai, Servant of Si's Mansion]
What a disgrace!
It's not worth getting angry at them.
What kind of people are they?
Young Master.
Look.
Sun Pingkang's jade pendant was left here.
[Sun's Mansion]
It's been a long time since we last met.
You've lost quite a bit of weight.
Look at you.
I haven't lost that much weight.
Greet your father now.
Good, good, good.
Father.
I've made you worry.
Good, good, good.
Dear,
Pingkang has become so successful.
It's truly a blessing from our Sun Family's ancestors.
My efforts of burning incense and praying
all day for divine protection
have not been wasted.
You really know how to take credit for yourself.
Pingkang's achievements today
are all due to his own diligent studies in harsh conditions
through his own efforts.
Alright, alright, alright.
Everyone, please sit down.
Please sit down.
Come on. Let's sit down. Hurry up.
Now that Pingkang has become a scholar,
I think these two children's marriage
can be put on the agenda.
Dear,
it's okay to let Qingcheng
marry him.
However, in the future,
if Pingkang
becomes the Number One Scholar,
then his marriage
will be decided by the emperor.
Guess what?
I won't guess.
Then I'll just tell you directly.
I'm not interested in knowing it.
I'm going to tell you anyway.
Your easily-obtained disciple
is really like a punching bag in Sun's Mansion.
We thought that since Sun Pingkang became a scholar
and returned home in glory,
their marriage would be settled.
Then she would live a good life, wouldn't she?
But in the end,
the Sun Family
thinks that Sun Pingkang will have a bright future,
so they no longer think that Miss Gu is good enough.
They won't let her be his principal wife.
They want to make her a concubine instead.
Don't you think this is...
Hey.
I'm telling you
your disciple is going to be someone's concubine!
You
have no sympathy at all.
After the marriage,
will the Flower Spirit become theirs?
When Qingcheng marries into the Sun Family,
it has to be a proper and formal marriage.
Only Qingcheng can be
Pingkang's sole principal wife.
Back then,
when Gu entrusted Qingcheng to me,
I promised him that
I would never mistreat Qingcheng.
You and Pingkang grew up together,
and you know each other well.
The daughter-in-law of the Sun Family
will be you only.
Father.
Dear.
In the future,
it's Qingcheng and Pingkang who will live together.
Why don't we ask
about Pingkang's thoughts?
Pingkang,
what do you think?
please speak your mind.
What's wrong?
Father.
Mother.
I'm sorry, but I cannot obey your wishes.
Whether I had passed the imperial examination or not,
I will not marry Qingcheng.
Sun Pingkang.
Do you realize what you're saying?
I think becoming a scholar
has made you so insolent.
How dare you be so disobedient!
If he doesn't want to marry her,
then it means he doesn't like her.
Dear,
please don't be angry.
Pingkang is an adult now.
Perhaps
he has a girl whom he fancies.
Tell me
whether there's someone outside
whom you have a crush on.
Not yet.
If there isn't,
then why can't you marry Qingcheng?
I think
marriage is different from studies.
It shouldn't be facilitated by parental orders
or matchmakers' words.
Qingcheng and I
are like siblings.
But she is not the one I want to spend my life with.
Shut up!
I think you've lost your mind.
Go kneel in the Buddha hall now!
Dear.
You're not allowed to get up
until you think it through.
Pingkang.
Yes, Father.
Don't be angry.
The dew collected by this little disciple
is actually quite good.
Let's continue to talk about the story.
The Sun Family wanted to take Gu Qingcheng as a concubine.
However, Sun Pingkang publicly refused the marriage.
Now this handsome audience member might want to ask...
Sun Pingkang and Gu Qingcheng
have been close since childhood.
Why did he publicly refuse to marry her?
Has he
fallen in love with someone else,
or is there more to the story?
To find out what happened next,
I'll go gather more information.
I'm leaving!
I still need to retrieve the Flower Spirit as soon as possible.
Pingkang.
You've been kneeling for a day and a night
without eating anything.
I've brought some snacks that our mother made.
Taste one of them now.
Eat.
Is it delicious?
Qingcheng.
I'm sorry.
In front of so many people,
I embarrassed you.
I'm not an outsider, so you don't have to say sorry.
Aren't we family?
Pingkang,
you know I don't mind at all.
As for our father,
he seems tough while talking, but he has a soft heart.
I've already talked it over with our mother.
From tomorrow onwards, you won't have to kneel as punishment anymore.
I know that
you've always
longed for freedom the most.
However,
you can't let go of our parents' expectations
and the constraints of this arranged marriage.
Using this debt of gratitude
to trap you in the Sun Family for the rest of your life
is too unfair to you.
So you did all these things today
for my sake?
You silly girl,
why are you looking at me like that?
It's just kneeling as punishment.
I thought
I'd be flogged as punishment.
It hurts.
Have another bite.
You should eat more.
It was not easy for our mother to cook this time.
Is it delicious?
Yes, it is.
By knowing both your enemy and yourself well,
you can always win in battles.
To retrieve the Flower Spirit,
I still need to figure out who she really is.
Master.
What brings you here?
It's windy outside.
I'm here to seek shelter from the cold.
I understand.
What does she understand?
Master.
Wrap this around you.
Don't catch a cold.
You don't feel cold now, huh?
Sit down.
Okay.
Chat with me for a while.
What would you like to talk about, Master?
Let's talk about you.
Me?
When you were a kid,
did you have any special experiences?
Special experiences?
I mean those unusual experiences,
which you think might be related to the practice of immortal magic.
If she is just an ordinary mortal,
why was my Flower Spirit absorbed into her body?
I remember it now!
I've seen an Immortal Lord before.
An Immortal Lord?
Where?
It was on a
very high mountain.
On that day,
my father taught me to identify flowers and herbs.
At the top of the mountain,
amidst the clouds and mist,
there seemed to be a strange phenomenon.
What kind of phenomenon?
The floating clouds and mist
suddenly turned into seven colors.
At this moment,
an immortal in a white outfit
appeared
among the flowers.
When he arrived, the flowers bloomed,
and a strong fragrance filled the air.
On which mountain did you encounter him?
On...
the mountain in my dream.
The Flowers Immortal Lord in my dream said that
I had great potential for wisdom
and the temperament of an immortal,
so I could definitely become an immortal through cultivation.
I couldn't see his face clearly in my dream,
but Master,
when you first appeared,
I knew it was...
you.
[Tianxiang House]
Waiter, we're out of wine!
Coming, coming!
Don't worry.
I'll go get it for you right away, okay?
Hurry up!
Please be patient.
Master,
since Lyu Gengyun woke up,
he has been hiding in Sun's Mansion.
He gets along so well with Miss Gu.
[Qiansi, Millennia-Old Snake Demon]
He has even
taken her as his disciple.
[Jade-Eyed Fox, Millennia-Old Fox Demon]
He's actually not playing by the rules.
In my opinion,
he has no fighting spirit now.
And he's all alone.
Why don't we attack him
while he's unprepared?
He is the son of the Demon King.
Even that person fears him to some extent.
What should we do then?
Keep an eye on him.
If anything happens,
report it to me.
Yes.
Master.
That half-demon who caused trouble in the Heavenly Realm is awake,
but he's keeping such a low profile.
While he's staying in Sun's Mansion,
I wonder what he's up to.
But I'm afraid Sun's Mansion
is about to face some turbulence.
[Sun's Mansion]
Straighten that out.
The authorities are investigating a case!
My Lord.
My Lord, this...
Why have you all come to Sun's Mansion
with weapons?
Scholar Sun Pingkang
is suspected of intentionally hurting his classmate
and causing the death of his servant, Lai.
We are here under orders to arrest the suspect.
There must be some mistakes.
My son is just a fragile scholar.
He couldn't possibly commit murder.
Here's the arrest warrant.
That's impossible.
You must have misunderstood.
My son
has never even stepped on an ant since he was a kid.
How could he possibly kill someone?
You must have made a mistake.
Dear, this...
I think you can recognize this object, huh?
Sun Pingkang's jade pendant was found on the victim.
Whether he's innocent or not,
the court will make its own judgment.
Those who try to stop us
will all be considered as his accomplices.
Sir,
I think there might be
some misunderstanding here.
Dear.
Do you all want to go to prison?
Search the house!
Yes!
Pingkang!
Qingcheng?
Let's leave here now.
What happened?
Stop asking about it.
Let's leave here...
Where are you going?
So you're Sun Pingkang?
Yes, I am.
Someone has accused you of murdering Si Shulun's servant, Lai.
Come with us now for interrogation.
Master.
Lai?
How would I kill Lai?
Master.
Arrest him!
No.
What... What are you doing?
Officers.
What are you doing?
Let go of me!
Qingcheng!
No...
[Sun's Mansion]
Besides dreaming about an Immortal Lord,
haven't you had any other special experiences?
I'll take this, too.
Pingkang will overthink things in prison.
This outfit...
I'm asking you a question.
Did you hear me or not?
Why couldn't they see you just now?
Because you are my disciple.
Only you can see me.
Pingkang is in great trouble now.
I don't have time to chat idly with you here.
Although you two are not officially married,
you care for him so much.
It's no different from being his wife.
Master!
You have no relation with Pingkang.
I can understand if you don't want to help,
but don't waste my time here while I'm trying to find a solution.
And don't say such cold-hearted words.
How dare you be angry?
I'm even angrier.
[Sun's Mansion]
Why don't you elaborate on it?
What exactly did that girl do to you?
Not only did she talk back,
but she also talked nonsense to fool me.
However, she seems to care about
Sun Pingkang very much.
That's quite normal.
They are humans
and are different from us.
Humans
value relationships greatly.
But relationships
can be simple sometimes
and complex sometimes.
You
won't get it.
Well, we've never
dealt with the government before.
What should we do now?
How much more suffering will Pingkang have to endure in prison?
There must be a way.
Dear.
Please think of a way to save Pingkang now.
I'm thinking. I'm thinking.
Why don't we ask Qingcheng for help?
That girl has always been clever and mischievous since she was a kid.
She's full of novel ideas.
Let's just ask Qingcheng for help.
Let's ask her for help.
Qingcheng can surely solve the problem.
Stop yelling.
I'll find a solution.
[Pingcheng County Government Office]
Let's make it quick.
Mr. Jailer,
this is a treasure I've kept for many years.
Please accept my gift.
Why are you giving...
a gift to me?
I'll guard the door for you.
Take your time to have a chat.
Qingcheng.
Pingkang.
Are you okay?
Have you been eating and sleeping well?
Have they tortured you?
I'm fine.
How are our parents?
They're fine.
Here's something.
Take it now.
You might need it inside.
How come all of these are flower seeds?
I just want to know why my Flower Spirit
entered her body
and how I can get it back.
It must be related to her past experiences.
But I really don't know
what she's really thinking in her mind.
That's easy.
I'll take a look inside her mind.
Hit him hard for me!
Stop it!
Pingkang!
Did you see it?
I...
saw... saw it.
What did you see?
Sun Pingkang.
Besides Sun Pingkang,
was there nothing else?
It was all about Sun Pingkang.
But he was being whipped hard.
Aren't you able to create dreams?
Then just create a dream that has nothing to do with Sun Pingkang.
Well, I could create dreams 500 years ago.
But during these 500 years,
I've been infusing you with spiritual power every day.
And when I woke up, I got beaten by you again.
Now I can only
peek into dreams.
Come back, come back, come back.
I haven't finished speaking yet.
Speak.
At night, a person tends to dream about
what he thinks during the day.
Now in her dreams, it's all about Sun Pingkang,
because Sun Pingkang is in trouble.
If you solve this problem for her
and then guide her
to recall the past,
then I'll have a chance to do it, won't I?
Pingkang.
What exactly happened?
You need to tell me everything in detail.
Only in this way can I figure out how to help you.
Pingkang.
After kneeling in the Buddha hall that day,
my legs were sore,
so I bought some herbal plasters at the street.
I accidentally bumped into Si Shulun's servant,
Lai.
I'm sorry.
I...
You think a simple apology is enough?
As Young Master Si, how can I endure
such a disgrace just like that?
What do you want then?
You passed the exam and became a scholar.
Don't touch me!
Why can't I touch you?
Let go of me!
Let go of me now!
Look what you've done.
You've ruined all my top-quality medicinal herbs!
Obviously, you...
What do you mean by "obviously?"
These are top-quality firefly mushrooms.
My father specially brought them for me from the capital.
Ordinary people don't even have the chance to see them.
Tell me.
Compensate me!
You...
Fine.
I'll compensate you.
I knew very well that Si Shulun was difficult to deal with,
and I didn't want to get entangled with him,
so I secretly took the firefly mushroom from home
to settle this matter.
From now on,
your young master and I are even.
I found and got this firefly mushroom by chance.
It's just a tonic.
It's not a poison.
Si Shulun and I have had a grudge for a long time.
This time,
he definitely won't let me off easily.
Qingcheng.
Go back now.
Don't get implicated in this trouble.
Pingkang, what are you talking about? We're a family.
What do you mean by getting implicated in this trouble?
What's wrong?
Nothing, Pingkang. Nothing.
Don't worry too much.
What's Gu Qingcheng up to?
This time,
I'm afraid my fate is settled.
Pingkang.
Pingkang, don't say such things anymore.
I absolutely won't let you suffer an unjust accusation.
Gu Qingcheng.
Why are you ignoring me?
Pingkang,
while you're in prison,
be nice to the chief jailer and other jailers.
Eat well and sleep well.
If you need more of those things,
I'll bring them for you next time.
You have to take good care of yourself.
Got it?
There's still time for a heart-to-heart conversation?
Go home now.
It's almost dawn.
What are you looking at?
Nothing.
It's nothing.
Just make sure to take good care of yourself.
Gu Qingcheng.
Gu Qingcheng!
Are you still going to investigate this case or not?
Master,
do you mean that you'll help me?
Sun Pingkang's life or death is none of my business.
But since you are my disciple,
I surely don't want to see that
you're always distracted by this matter.
It'll hinder your cultivation of immortal magic.
I knew that
you wouldn't just stand by without saving him.
After all,
you're the virtuous Flowers Immortal Lord.
Master,
this situation is a bit tricky now.
According to them,
the servant, Lai, died from eating a firefly mushroom.
But this firefly mushroom
was indeed given by Pingkang.
If Si Shulun keeps harping on this point,
it'll be very difficult to handle this matter.
We haven't even investigated it yet,
and you're already giving up?
I'm not giving up.
Officer.
This small gift is just a token of my respect.
I hope you'll accept it.
Please accept it.
Master Sun, please don't make me get into trouble.
Master Sun, please go back home.
Our Lord has already given instructions on this matter.
We'll definitely investigate it thoroughly.
Officer.
Here you are.
Please
be a bit more accommodating.
Thank you, thank you.
Master Sun.
Please just go back home.
You...
Since you're so concerned,
why don't you go comfort him?
My father has always been proud
and has been respected by people all his life.
Now because of Pingkang's matter,
he has to humbly beg others.
He certainly wouldn't want his juniors to see this.
Alright.
Let's go check on Lai.
Sir, why are you in such high spirits today?
I've finally dealt with Sun Pingkang.
Oh, what a pleasant thing!
Is it delicious?
Come on.
You're going to drain me soon.
Do you know that?
[Morgue]
Why did you hit me?
What?
You're still denying it, huh?
I didn't hit...
You'll be the stand sentry.
I'll sleep.
I caught you, didn't I?
My hands are right here.
Why is there a scent of a fox demon?
How come there is frost?
Firefly mushrooms are extremely Yang substances.
Even if he had been poisoned with it,
there shouldn't be any frost.
Perhaps it's because of
food incompatibility.
I remember that when I was a kid,
I once read about it in my father's ancient books.
For such extremely Yang substances as firefly mushrooms,
they can never be combined with a certain herb.
It would produce an extremely cold and deadly poison.
This herb is...
Water hemlock!
So,
Lai's death wasn't caused by
firefly mushrooms.
It was the person who gave him water hemlock.
It was...
Si Shulun?