Shit.
Ispilio?
Akui, bring the distortable sword and give an old wood sword.
Hurry up and do it!
All right, I'llnow do my best to support this achiever!
Fighting!
I信 my sister is the one who will betray us!
I want to grab something, so I want to hold it strongly
The heat is not changing, it's hot, it's hot, the moon is moving
I'm in a long road, where am I now?
Where is the goal? Is that really true?
The moment I look at a different scenery than yesterday
I can't say it well, but I can see through the power that I'm moving forward
While reaching the light of the future, I'm living in a flower that I can't stop
Even if I get close, even if I get close, I won't be able to chase my dream
I want to grab something, so I want to hold it strongly
The heat is not changing, it's hot, it's hot, the moon is moving
The power of God
The daughter of the current village?
It's true that the place where the slaughterhouse is
The gate is broken! Come here!
Masuo! Akida!
The gate was opened because the slaughterhouse was open!
The evil spirit has entered!
Don't move! We'll stop them!
Master!
Leave the back to us
You'll be able to live from here
The power of the current village and the power of the Bejii
I can't stop them from being evil
I have to make sure I don't succeed
I don't know how to use the power of God I saved
But I'll use it to protect the Ragnarok Village
The gate was opened?
Yes
It's bad, it's going to be taken to the
I saved you, thank you
The rest is the new seat
If you don't mind, I'll do it here too
You guys are the new seats?
I just painted the door on my face, but they're all shaking
Let's go!
Close the door at the moment!
Don't let them in any more!
Keep them up!
Alright, we'll die here
They're going to get caught!
We can't let them in!
Report! The evil spirit army is gathering in front of the gate!
What?
We'll protect this place
Please leave the Lord God to us
You're going to make me a fool?
Lord Toshigami and Lord God are one body
If Lord God is not around, the villagers can do it
What do you say?
Let's take care of the dance
If they see us, we'll be in trouble
Please do us a favor
Hurry up!
The red guys are coming up like this!
Transformers!
The people of the Lagumura are the soldiers here
And the people
They're all the same, the innocent ones
I beg you, please take care of the Lord God
We can't let them in
What are you saying?
I'll stay here
I'll leave the rest of the evil spirit behind
Don't worry, if you're going to die, I'll let you escape
You're going to be destroyed!
Bring the Marutas!
You're going to die!
They're coming!
Lord Abethin, you're doing great!
That's the true power of the Lord
I'll make you a fool!
You're going to die!
I'll take your life!
Father, I'm just about to die
You shouldn't be so rude
I'm fine, this is my will
Akari, you can leave
You're going to die
I'm going to die here, just like the King of the Kingdom
I'm a traitor
I'm sure I can fight
This is Usel's spear
Usel's master is a woman
He risked his life to protect the people
I'm going to fight too
Lord Orphan is here!
Lord Orphan?
Lord Orphan, did the disease heal?
Yes, it did
We have two swordsmen
Then let's use the evil
You're going to die!
He's still alive
You're the one who's going to die!
Lord Orphan!
I'll protect the Ragnarra!
Jyothen!
You're not afraid of the evil?
It's hard, I'm going to die
Lord Jyothen is fighting like that
Hurry
I'm done, too
Go on with Lord Jyothen and Lord Orphan!
Lord Orphan
Let go of me!
I can't do it yet
I'm going to protect you, even if you're going to die
Jyothen, I'm not afraid of women
I'm not afraid of women
What's wrong?
Let go of me!
I'm going to die!
There's no one to protect you
What happened?
Please, Lord Tachigami
What the hell is this?
It's coming closer
Kai, are you back?
Take this!
Yes, sir!
Sorry, but I won't let you guys get in the castle!
What the hell is this?
How could you do this to me?
What's that?
Is that really Kai?
How much power can you use to fight?
How many new stones can you use to defeat him?
Then, it's like the real treasure
The power of God!
The power of God?
Zulin, we may have been able to defeat the lack of power
The Lord Kaun was runs away
Their abilities improved
What an insane world
Don't kill me.
I fought well, didn't I, Akui?
Yes. Thanks to you, the village was protected.
The one who saved the village was the one who was holding a hole in the fence.
Oh, you're still on your face?
You were also drawing a pattern on your face?
Even with this, I can fool them.
If you can fight like that, you don't need that kind of material.
No, that's not true.
Kai, what happened to Lady Narda?
After the old lady died in Edamura, she was killed after she was killed in Makaku.
What?
The enemy was a three-armed cargo carrier, and I was also a total enemy of protecting myself.
Even without the cargo carrier, she was so strong that she could show her true colors.
But that person didn't take any of them.
It was a great battle.
I couldn't even take care of them properly.
I'll send the army to the field later.
Kai, Lili-san...
Your sister isn't home.
Elsa? I thought she was just trying to make things worse.
We can't go back without sending her to the field.
I saw a village girl being brought back to the village by the vassal who ran away from there.
Is that a fact?
Yes, that's true.
Kai!
Hey! What are you going to do?
I'll chase her and take her back!
What about the vassal and the other party?
How can he go after her?
What?
What's wrong?
It's safe to come this far.
How far is the hut?
Is it around 1000 yards?
It's still a long way to go.
I'm not saying I'll give you a lot of love for a strange girl.
What happened?
Are you stupid?
No, I'm more...
Aragur, something's...
Come here.
My tribe is the kingdom of Chuana, Kizaku!
Stop it!
You're a coward!
Get out of my way!
What are you afraid of?
What?
Wait, Uba!
Yes, Your Highness!
Don't go, Bun-kan!
Are you going to leave me behind?
Elsa!
My wife!
You...
Kai...
Wait!
Wait, I'll save you!
With my magic...
I'll make you live a life of your own!
Why?
Why won't you listen?
You're too ill to catch up with me.
What should I do?
Die, you bastard!
I'll kill you!
Did you kill Elsa?
The light you saw earlier...
Are you a village person?
It's your fault, Elsa.
It's not my fault!
Your fault is that girl's death!
What?
Your strong power has made Uma angry!
Even so, it's not your fault!
Is that so?
You're not even going to run away from me!
It's my fault...
It's not my fault to betray you!
You're the one who killed that girl!
No!
Huh?
The treasure of Raghumura should be Miha's.
I don't know who it is, but I'm sorry for raising your hand on the suicide death that caused you to die!
That's not the case yet!
The one who has the power of God...
I'll kill you, you bastard!
I see.
In a village like yours, you'll be able to drown in your power and suffer the death of many more people!
I see. If this is what you want...
I'll kill you, you bastard!
Elsa! Elsa, can you hear me?
Kai...
I'm sorry...
No!
We'll be together forever!
If we drink this, we'll be healthy!
Kai...
We'll be together forever...
If we drink the water of the new stone, we'll be strong and have a strong spirit.
And we'll be able to heal the water of the treasure!
Kai...
Huh?
Thank you...
Elsa!
I don't know what happened, but I'm the only one who can rely on you.
Did you give this girl a new stone?
Yes, that's right.
You've done something bad.
Why? You've given her a new stone to heal her wound.
There's a problem with the name of the same person.
If you give her a new stone at the same time, she'll be in a very strong and poisonous situation.
If she's the worst, she'll die.
Elsa's going to die?
No way! She's not going to save us!
It's not like she's not going to save us.
But I hope we can make it.
Please! Do whatever you want!
I'm sure of it.
Leave the rest to us.
First, we'll get rid of the water we've eaten.
You two, please trust this person.
If I had to chase Elsa, I wouldn't have to do this.
Is my power just to make her die?
How am I supposed to use this power?
Makaku!
You're here at this point!
Are you going to attack my body this time?
I'm not going to attack you!
I'm sorry for your misdeeds.
What?
I'm going to kill you, the wolf that's been killed.
The wolf that's been killed?
I'm going to wait for you to wake up.
Please, give me a five-star ring.
What?
Then, what about this world?
We'll disappear, and we'll be like this, too.
We're not really serious, but...
The blue moon is just a little bit,
but people realize that loneliness is the only thing that exists in the night sky.
I don't want to talk about my life without doing it.
I'm just a little bit of a fool,
but if I lose you, I'll be myself,
and I won't lose to you.
I'll be myself, who won't lose to you.
Will you forgive me?
The wolf that's been killed?
I can only do that.