Ahn Ja-young.
Yes?
I'm the same.
What do you mean?
I'm the same as any other dude out there.
I like you.
Ahn Ja-young.
Ja-young.
Ja-young!
Oh, hey.
-Have you eaten?
-Yes.
Let's go.
Hello.
Are you heading to work now?
Yes.
I'll get going, then. Have a nice day.
Did something happen?
No.
What's up with him?
Officer Ahn.
Officer Ahn!
Yes, sir.
Is something wrong?
No. Why do you ask?
Do you want to go
to the peach farm with me?
Why are you going there?
Don't you want coffee?
Right.
I'm okay.
I don't feel like it right now.
That's odd.
You drink like five cups a day.
-You go ahead.
-Okay, I'll be back.
What's he doing here?
I thought I'd make a delivery
for a change.
SANDEUL POLICE STATION
I like you, Ahn Ja-young.
What are you doing?
I'm confessing.
What?
It's become too much to keep bottled up.
Look. I…
Just like that.
Keep thinking about it.
I just wanted you to think about it.
For now, that's enough for me.
You don't have to get all serious.
I've been around you for your whole life.
Try to look at me
from a different perspective.
Let's start with that.
Don't look at me like that.
I just wanted to let it all out.
It felt unfair to suffer alone.
Aren't you scared?
Of what?
What if we can't even stay friends?
I'm not scared.
Do you think our relationship can
be defined as simply friends or lovers?
I guess not.
Exactly.
To me, you're a friend, but also a woman.
Sometimes you're a little sister,
and sometimes a big sister.
I could even think of you
as an aunt, cousin, and mom.
It would be great
if you were my "special someone."
But even if that doesn't happen,
you're still my friend,
my neighbor, and my family.
So there's no way
we'll stop seeing each other.
The awkward, uncomfortable phase will be
just a short moment compared
to all the time we spent together.
And it'll eventually pass.
We have plenty of time, Ja-young.
Take your time.
I mean, aren't I pretty attractive?
It's hard to come by
someone this handsome.
I'll get going.
See you later.
Thanks.
Let's just keep being the usual us.
Have you watched our videos lately?
No, I go straight to bed
and pass out after work.
And what do you mean, "our"?
I only helped you out twice.
Hey, do you know how empty I feel
because of those two times?
Do you?
I do my best to explain
and make them laugh,
only to see them ask
when you're coming back.
Hey.
Let's be honest.
You know I'm pretty good-looking myself.
But because of you,
my self-esteem hit rock bottom.
Just tell them I'm not coming back.
What, are you planning
to just settle down over there?
You must be enjoying this.
Hey, what's bothering you this time?
Is that nosy police officer
being all nosy again?
It's not that.
And why are you suddenly bringing that up?
Man, you must really hate her.
Hey.
I get that you are annoyed
that you have to keep seeing her,
but just hang in there.
You're coming back to Seoul soon anyway.
Just stick to the basics.
You're good at drawing boundaries.
I am. There's no need to cause
any misunderstanding…
Misunderstanding?
Hello?
I'm at the barn now.
I'll talk to you later.
SANDEUL POLICE STATION
SANDEUL VILLAGE CULTURE GARDEN
When did it start having diarrhea?
About four days ago.
You should give the mother cow less feed,
and you need to clean up
the floor of the barn.
And to keep the calf's temperature up,
lay down some rice straw…
Ta-da!
I went all the way to the peach farm
to get this for you, Little Doctor.
Drink up while it's cold.
Thank you.
Oh, right. Officer Ahn just stopped by.
She wanted to borrow a cage,
so I let her. Is that okay?
Sure.
In that case,
would you come with me?
You think you should go with Mr. Lee.
I'm fully booked tomorrow.
I didn't think it through.
I wouldn't want to cause
any misunderstanding.
Was she alone?
She wasn't with Mr. Lee or anyone else?
She came alone.
She said she was using her lunchtime
to go to the mountains behind the village.
Apparently, Boksil had puppies there.
Gosh, it's hot. Let's get back inside.
Did she say anything else by any chance?
Was she looking for me at all?
She wasn't.
Oh, she saw the director's bicycle
and fiddled with it a little.
She said something was loose
and about to fall out.
You see, she's Huidong's MacGyver.
Whatever the problem was,
I'm sure she fixed it.
Why did she leave her bicycle here?
You're right. Maybe because of the cage.
My, the weather really is beautiful today.
It makes me want to drink
some cold bean soup.
Let's have bean soup noodles for lunch…
What's Officer Ahn's number?
Yes, I'm rescuing animals.
I'm just doing my job.
Hey.
What happened to you?
Why are you here on your own?
Hey, you came.
Hey, where did you find this one?
I looked all over and couldn't find it.
What a relief. Let's get you in the cage.
There you go.
Okay, let's get in there.
Why are you doing this by yourself?
You should've brought someone.
Well, everyone was busy.
And I thought I could handle
three little puppies on my own.
But I was overconfident.
They were quicker than I'd thought.
I guess all your help has gone unnoticed.
No one's helping you on a day like this.
I didn't bother asking for help,
but there are plenty who would be willing.
Don't touch the wound.
It might get infected.
But seriously, where did you find it?
It must have been hard
to find it in the bushes.
It was pretty easy to find.
And it went into the cage by itself.
What was that about?
All right, let's go.
The baby is over here, guys. It's okay.
I spoke to Aunt Gang-hwa,
and she told me to bring the puppies over.
We could put them up for adoption later,
but Boksil is still a bit on edge,
recovering from delivery.
So she doesn't think
we should separate them.
We'll run some quick tests at the hospital
and bring them to her.
Okay.
You left your bicycle at the hospital.
Did you walk all the way here?
I ran into the village head
and got a ride on his truck.
A truck is faster than a bicycle.
It's a rescue operation after all.
HIS PEACH FARM
Would you like some coffee?
No, I'm good.
I ran the tests.
Luckily, they are all healthy.
They just need to get vaccinated
on schedule.
I guess I could just give them
the first vaccination.
Only the first one?
Right. You have to get back to Seoul.
Anyway, this is great.
Boksil, your babies are all healthy.
I'll let Aunt Gang-hwa know.
Hey, you found each other.
Oh, my gosh. There you are.
Aren't they so cute?
Nurungji and Boksil's babies.
Oh, my. When did you two make all these?
My goodness, you look just like your dad.
Well, I'll be going now.
Yes, you should.
It looks like it's going to rain soon.
-Have a good one.
-You too.
Wait. I…
Never mind.
Let's go, Boksil.
My gosh, you're so cute.
Let's go.
HAN DEOK-JIN VETERINARY HOSPITAL
Good girl.
My job being what it is,
I couldn't just ignore it.
I'm fine.
Occupational habits die hard, don't they?
I'm not actually that nosy by nature.
I just have a lot of things to do
as a police officer.
So I think you should see it
as dedication to my duty
rather than an act of
being nosy or attention-seeking.
You know what I mean?
You must have gotten
a new pair of contacts.
I was going to refer you to someone
if you hadn't.
There's this optician I'm quite close to.
-If you go to him--
-I know.
I know that you're trying
to take care of me in various ways
out of dedication to your job.
I'm staying in this village at the moment
after all.
I'm saying that I am grateful.
As a temporary resident.
I already got new contacts,
but thank you for your concern.
Are you mad at me about something?
Of course not.
Are you sure?
You're not mad at me
for making your bike fall into the paddy?
Just how old do you think I am?
Thirteen?
Thank you for the treatment.
I better come here again
when I get hurt next time.
You're not too bad.
Bye, then.
HAN DEOK-JIN VETERINARY HOSPITAL
Yes, okay.
The 13th?
It's going to be difficult.
How about the 21st?
Yes.
The 21st is okay.
Yes, okay.
Bye.
THE DAY DIRECTOR HAN IS COMING BACK
-The summer sure feels long, doesn't it?
-It does.
It may feel like you're in exile,
but time will fly
if you keep yourself busy.
Oh, no. The ice is all melted.
I told you to drink while it was cold.
CALLING…
LEE SANG-HYEON
Hello.
It's your cute mascot and the director
of Doctor Choi Animal Hospital,
Choi Yun-hyeong.
It's nice to meet you all.
Today, we'll talk about disc disorders,
some of the oldest
chronic illnesses for puppies.
WHEN IS DOCTOR HAN JI-YUL APPEARING?
WHERE IS OUR DOCTOR HAN?
Man, I hope it doesn't rain too much.
MISSED CALL
JA-YOUNG
What's wrong, Seon-dong?
The dog ate some chocolate last night.
I'll drop him off and go to the hospital.
Let's talk there.
Doctor, please fix my Ttoli.
-Okay.
-Let's go, Seon-dong.
Hey.
Is Ttoli okay?
He threw up everything,
so there was nothing left in his stomach.
He'll be all right after some IV fluids.
And please tell Seon-dong
never to feed him things like chocolate.
My goodness. He must be worried sick.
Is he at school right now?
He was so worried,
he was jumping up and down.
Thanks for helping out
so early in the morning.
How about Ja-young? Is she okay?
I heard she's at
the Eastern medicine clinic.
I heard she's getting acupuncture
and physical therapy,
but I don't know how she is.
I should go check on her.
Can we have a word, doctor?
She called this morning.
She said she'd fallen pretty hard
and couldn't take Seon-dong to school.
The dog was foaming at the mouth
and nearly dying,
so Seon-dong was shocked
and called Ja-young.
Since the boy was crying,
Ja-young ran out in a hurry
and forgot that the bicycle was broken.
Broken bicycle?
When yours fell into the rice paddy,
a part must have fallen out.
Ja-young probably used
a part from her bicycle to fix yours.
I guess you didn't know.
That's how she is.
You know something?
I've been checking the calendar
every day lately.
I'm counting down the days
until you return to Seoul.
Ja-young cares about everything
in this village.
She loves this village
as much as she loves herself.
And I hate that you're
within the boundaries of this village
that she loves so much.
Why? Because you'll be gone soon.
It means that you won't
take responsibility for anything,
and I don't want to see Ja-young
get hurt over something like that again.
It looks like the part you really hate is
how much Officer Ahn cares about me,
and that's what you're mad about.
Am I right?
That's not the point.
You'll be gone soon.
That's the part I'm emphasizing.
If you'll be gone soon,
don't give her the wrong idea.
What brings you here?
What are you doing?
Oh, I was told I had to keep them in
like this for a while, so…
And what are you doing here?
They're from Ms. Jang.
I see.
Thank you.
Are you not hurt enough?
I'm sorry?
Why are you doing that
when you're the patient?
Is there no one else
that can cut those things?
-Well, I just--
-Are you a robot? Do you have superpowers?
If you're injured, you should
lie down and rest so you can heal.
Don't you know this is self-abuse?
It's not healthy to seek
reaffirmation of your self-worth
from constantly helping others.
Do you need people to thank you
that badly?
Why would you sacrifice yourself
for something so stupid?
Look, Mr. Han Ji-yul.
So why did you have to fix my bicycle
in the first place
and end up getting hurt?
Why did you do something I never asked
and make me feel indebted?
It makes me feel so uncomfortable.
You're right.
"Thank you, I appreciate it."
That's what l live for.
So what? What's wrong with that?
If I could be appreciated like that,
who cares if I hurt myself a little?
HAN DEOK-JIN VETERINARY HOSPITAL
Doctor Han.
SANDEUL POLICE STATION
Jeez.
Oh, hey.
Why did you come in?
I told you I'd give you sick leave.
It's not like I can't walk.
How are you going to go on patrols
with a limp like that?
You'll make the residents feel uneasy.
Jeong-sik and Geun-mo will
go on the patrols, so go home.
This kind of injury only improves
with lying down and resting.
Then let me do some office work.
I have to do something right now.
-Hey, Geun-mo.
-Hey, go rest. Let's go.
Please, Chief.
Hey, I'm really fine.
Take care of yourself
so I can work you for a long time. Gosh.
Go start the car already.
It's cold.
Which idiot forgot to roll up the window?
It was actually you, Chief.
You said it was too hot.
Get in.
All right.
-Hey, Geun-mo.
-Yes, sir.
After dropping her off,
go check in on Pyeong-sik's.
It's a disaster there when it rains.
Yes, sir.
I don't know what's going on with you,
but working won't make you
feel any better.
Go get some sleep and shake it off, okay?
-Okay.
-Go.
Yes, sir.
I like the sound of the rain.
I'll drop you off after the rounds then.
Get some shut-eye.
Okay.
Sang-hyeon told me,
but I wanted to see with my own eyes.
-He's really okay now, right?
-Yes.
He's done with the fluids,
so you could take him home.
But it's raining too much, isn't it?
Right, and I have to stop
by the school supply shop.
-Can I pick him up tomorrow after school?
-Of course.
Then please look after my Ttoli
for one more day.
Okay.
By the way, Doctor,
did Ja-young do something wrong?
What?
She said hi yesterday morning,
and you just walked off.
I said hi back.
But your face didn't say hi.
Admit it. You're mad at her, right?
No way. Not at all.
I really am not mad at her.
Even if you're mad at her,
can't you just give her a break?
I mean, that's…
Ja-young is a really nice person.
She's as nice as my grandma.
She might have done something
to make you angry,
but she always means well.
Could you please stop being mad at her?
Ja-young didn't do anything wrong.
-If anything, I did something wrong.
-Really?
What did you do wrong?
I got mad at her,
-when I should have been thanking her.
-Why?
That's what I'm asking myself.
I was so stupid.
Gosh, I envy her.
She has so many people who care about her.
-You want some hot chocolate?
-Yes.
Okay.
Doctor!
Hey, Seon-dong.
Tell her you're sorry.
Were you worried about me?
I'm totally fine, so don't worry.
I'll be heading back home
after I visit Mr. Pyeong-sik's place.
By the way, where are you?
Hello?
Officer Ahn.
My gosh, what a scary downpour.
SANDEUL POLICE STATION
Yes, this is Sandeul precinct--
Sergeant Yoon.
Officer Ahn.
Officer Ahn!
Wake up!
Officer Ahn, wake up!
Come on.
Officer Ahn! Wake up, please!
Hey! Open the door, kid!
I took pity on you
because you have no parents.
Why do you always take Huidong's side?
That's enough!
What can I do for you?
Do you want a cooler full of beer?
Jeez, you punk.
You miss them, don't you?
Your mom and dad.
You were so adorable
playing together in secret.
I'm sorry I didn't recognize you
right away.
I wonder where he went.
Subtitle translation by: Daniel Shin