Do you just hate your house?
Seon-dong's summer break starts today,
so I ended up coming a bit early.
I know you're glad to see me.
Is something bothering you these days?
I guess something is.
But I don't know what.
The village is the same every day.
What could it be?
Could it be the vet?
What?
What are you talking about? It is not!
Right. I'm sure it's not.
Could it be Sang-hyeon then?
I'm sure that's not it either.
Then what could be
bothering our Officer Ahn?
I have no clue.
Little Doctor.
-Excuse--
-Hello.
Oh, my goodness.
What brings you little munchkins here?
She says that Judy isn't eating.
And she has diarrhea.
-Judy?
-It's this one.
May I take a look?
Judy isn't one year old yet, right?
She's three months old.
She's too skinny.
When did she start having diarrhea?
Two days ago.
Is my Judy going to die?
What?
My mom keeps telling me
that she'll buy me a new rabbit.
I don't need a rabbit
other than Judy, doctor.
I have a lot of allowance money saved up.
Please save my Judy.
Let me see what's wrong with her first,
then I'll do my best to help her.
So stop crying now. Come on.
Yes, stop crying.
While the doctor checks on Judy,
you two go get yourselves some popsicles.
Seon-dong. Take good care of her, okay?
I'm better at taking care of people.
Anyway, thank you.
Sure.
Why aren't you going with her?
Thank you.
Sure.
Did they fight?
We should check
for infections first, right?
What are you doing?
It's been a while
since I treated such a small animal.
In Seoul, I only treated animals
that I could hold in my hands.
The small humans outside are also waiting.
So hurry up, please.
I will.
Please hold her.
Sorry for the wait.
No, just stay seated.
Fortunately, Judy doesn't have
any parasites or other problems,
but she's very dehydrated,
so I'll give her fluids.
I'll have to keep her here for a while
to monitor her condition afterward.
-Could you come back later?
-Yes.
I don't care how long it takes.
But my Judy really is
going to be okay, right?
Of course.
Did you feed her any fruit by any chance?
I fed her some pear that I was eating.
She's still a young rabbit,
so she can get sick
from eating something juicy.
From now on, give her
dry grass or rabbit food only.
-Can you do that?
-Yes.
See? I told you she'd be okay.
I'll call you when she's ready.
Are you going home?
No.
Ga-on's house is close by.
I can hang out there.
He's very smart and meticulous.
He remembers everything,
like where we've gone and what we've done.
Is that so?
That's amazing.
I'll be back later then.
Thank you.
No problem. See you.
Did you two fight?
Doctor.
Why am I so dumb?
Do you know what a manito is?
I know, isn't it like a Secret Santa?
We do that every year at school,
and in first grade, Hui-won was my manito.
-Right.
-I was talking with friends
about things we'd exchanged,
and Hui-won asked,
"My gift was the best, right?"
And I was stupid enough to say,
"What was the gift?"
I'm such a fool!
Meanwhile, Kim Ga-on even remembers
the color of the raffle ticket he drew.
But honestly, the book she gave me was
really boring.
So it was a book.
But it was a gift from the girl I like.
I should have remembered it.
I know I'm in the wrong.
Gosh, I can't believe I forgot.
-You like her?
-Yes.
Sang-hyeon told me that
if I'm constantly curious
and worried about her, I must like her.
How can I get her to forgive me, doctor?
She said her rabbit was sick,
so I told her that I was close with you
and convinced her to come here.
But the more I talk to her,
the worse things get.
Here's an idea.
How about just not talking to her
for a while?
Give her some time.
Some angry feelings go away
after you think about them on your own.
The things you say to appease her
might be making things worse.
I think you're right.
She glares at me
every time I say something.
So if I don't,
at least she won't glare at me.
I'll try doing that.
Okay. Good luck.
-Thank you, doctor.
-Sure.
I'll get going too.
I can't leave her alone with Ga-on
for too long.
He's handsome.
Okay.
Wait.
-This morning, I didn't see…
-See what?
You.
I didn't see you, so I was worried
that you were late for school.
Summer break started today,
so there's no school.
You were worried about me?
You're much nicer than I thought.
Have you been…
well?
OFFICER AHN
Doctor, there's a cow that's been in labor
for a whole day without giving birth.
Okay.
So it's been decided?
Oh, no. Aunt Se-ryeon must be so upset.
Then we shouldn't talk about
Majeong for a while.
Okay.
Thank you, Aunt Gyeong-ok.
What is it now?
The National Singing Contest.
It's going to be held in Majeong.
Oh, no.
I can almost hear Jang Se-ryeon fuming.
So we have to go all the way to Majeong
to watch it?
If you go there to watch,
you'll be signing your own death warrant.
Why? Can't I go and watch?
Am I not allowed to go?
Gosh, I'm so mad!
It's so annoying! It's infuriating!
I'm not watching that show again
from this moment on!
Those TV station people
seriously lack judgment!
Park Mal-geum's soles must be all worn out
from dancing in celebration all day.
If we lose
the specialization funds to them too,
I'm going to move out of Huidong.
It'd be so humiliating
whenever I run into that bitch.
I won't live here!
Why would you leave? What about us?
-Should I poison her food?
-What?
Let's stay within the bounds
of the law, okay?
Let's focus on getting the funds.
If we have non-stop meetings
with the Young Men's Association,
we should find some kind of solution.
What?
So what happened
when you did as the doctor said?
She's not glaring at me anymore,
but she doesn't look at me at all now.
It's like I'm totally invisible.
Seriously.
Kim Seon-dong.
Have I taught you nothing?
You obviously know why Hui-won is upset.
Then just say,
"It's been a long time, so I forgot."
"I'm sorry for not remembering."
That's what you should do.
Why would you listen to that nonsense?
Why are you getting upset too?
No, I'm not upset.
It's just frustrating, that's all.
It's not like you don't know
why she's angry.
If you know why, you should just be honest
and tell her you're sorry.
So why choose the more difficult path?
I told her I was sorry at school
and on the way to the hospital.
But she was like, "Whatever. bite me."
Her rabbit was sick,
so she was probably
too upset to accept your apologies.
And if she's upset because of you
and you don't do anything about it,
won't she get even more upset?
"I am still sorry about what I did.
I want to stay friends with you."
You have to show her how you really feel.
Love is not easy.
Okay, I'll try that.
That's a good boy.
Yes, that's the Kim Seon-dong I know.
HAN DEOK-JIN VETERINARY HOSPITAL
Doctor.
You and Ja-young ruined everything!
Seon-dong.
You said you liked hot chocolate, right?
Here.
So what happened
when you did as Ja-young told you?
She asked if I had a split personality
and why I kept changing my attitude.
She said she wouldn't
hang out with me anymore.
What did you do?
You should have waited like I told you.
When I didn't say anything to her,
she also didn't say anything to me.
When I listened to Ja-young,
her words made sense.
So I told her I was sorry over ten times,
and she asked if I was mocking her.
When I said you should wait,
I literally meant you should take some…
Did Ja-young really tell you to say sorry
until she accepts your apology?
She said that doing nothing would
just make things worse.
And that what you said was nonsense.
I mean, what are you…
It happened a year ago.
It's understandable that you forgot.
Plus, it's not like you completely forgot.
You just couldn't remember.
Why would you be sorry?
Why are you getting upset, doctor?
I'm not getting upset.
I'm just taking your side.
From your perspective.
Seon-dong.
Let's try my idea again.
And let's be firm.
You've apologized enough.
"I sincerely apologized,
but you still won't hang out with me.
So okay. It saddens me,
but we'll do as you say."
That's your stance.
You won't have to see her anyway
since it's summer break.
What if she doesn't contact me
until the summer break is over?
In my experience, if you're out of sight,
she's bound to be concerned.
But you have to be patient, okay?
Don't say anything else to her.
You said you had a girlfriend, right?
Well, I…
I guess I should listen to the person
with experience.
Ja-young has never even had a boyfriend.
Really?
I'm going to go now.
Thanks for the hot chocolate.
-Let's do this.
HUIDONG STONEWALL TRAIL
It's done.
Hello.
I…
I didn't get a chance
to say this yesterday,
but thank you for helping me
after the accident.
I should have thanked you sooner,
but I missed the timing.
Sure.
But some things still need to be said,
even if the timing isn't right.
Especially with things like
"thank you" or "sorry."
And some things don't need to be said.
Like when you just said, "Thank you."
I didn't have to hear it to know.
I'd like to say it regardless.
Thank you.
Yesterday, I was…
Visiting the barn?
Yes.
Why didn't you come yesterday?
I had a lot of beer ready.
I mean, it was raining and everything.
So there was no other reason?
No, nothing like that.
I just passed out at home.
Let's put them up.
I replaced all the bulbs.
Sure. Let's.
I'll be on my way then.
Tell me.
Tell you what?
You know what I'm talking about.
He remembered.
The guy from Seoul.
At last.
At last what?
You were fussing
about being secret friends.
Why are you so lukewarm
when you both remember now?
I know, right?
I thought there would be
a lot to talk about.
But strangely, there wasn't.
It just became awkward.
It's all in the past now.
It's kind of unnecessary.
I won't ever see him again
once he goes back.
There's no point now,
Why bother?
You're right.
You were just kids back then.
Why bother?
I'm going to Seoul to meet a client.
Let me know if you need something.
I'll get it.
It's not like you're going overseas.
I'm just worried.
What are you worried about? I'm not a kid.
All right, then.
Be good while I'm away.
Hey!
Doctor, I'm stepping out for a second.
Okay, see you later.
What is it?
Is everything okay?
Of course. Everything's fine.
Then why do you sound so down?
Is that Officer Ahn still bothering you?
Has this happened to you?
You meet a stranger,
but they turn out to be someone you knew.
What does that even mean?
Are you saying you knew her
but you didn't recognize her?
I guess.
And she recognized you?
I guess that could happen with you
since you're so indifferent about others.
But I have a sharp eye,
so I'd definitely recognize someone.
You know, she must not have
such great memories of you.
She's been pretending
she doesn't know you.
No, there's no way…
Could there be?
Anyway, what about it?
Does she look different
now that you recognize them?
Aren't people usually like that?
Once you realize
that they aren't a total stranger,
they look more…
You know, more…
-They look better?
-That's right.
Wait, what?
I didn't mean in a romantic way.
Just as a person to another.
Don't people generally think better
of people they know?
That's what I mean.
You think better of Officer Ahn now?
-What?
-Unbelievable.
So she knew you all this time, right?
And she acted like she didn't?
Seriously.
You must have been an absolute jerk.
So how do you know her?
When I was a kid…
When we were kids, we played together.
I see.
Now, this is the most important part.
Is she pretty?
Doctor.
Welcome back. Where's Seon-dong?
He won't even answer his phone.
What's wrong with him?
I'll disappear as you wish.
Don't look for me. Goodbye.
SANDEUL POLICE STATION
-Do you happen to know…
-My goodness.
…any place Seon-dong might go to
besides his home?
-What?
-Who?
Why all of a sudden?
He texted Hui-won
telling her not to look for him
and disappeared.
I just checked his home,
and he's not there yet.
He's not answering
my calls or his grandmother's.
Hopefully he's just
hanging out somewhere, but…
What is going on here?
Did you look everywhere?
-Yes.
-Jeez, this kid…
-It's quite late.
-He's not answering?
No.
My goodness.
Yes, ma'am.
Yes, I just heard.
It's probably nothing.
I'll find him quickly and take him home,
so don't worry too much.
Okay.
Maybe he's just playing somewhere.
He was depressed all day.
He was having problems with a friend.
But even then,
he's not the type to act like this.
He said not to look for him.
He must have run away from home.
Should I broadcast it?
-Sure.
-Yes, sir.
Let's go look for him.
How far could he have gone?
Is there anything you know?
That's…
Huidong residents,
Huidong Elementary School second-grader
Kim Seon-dong has not returned home yet.
His grandmother is worried sick.
If you see Kim Seon-dong,
please call me or the police station.
Seon-dong!
If you're out playing,
hurry up and go home, okay?
I repeat.
Seon-dong!
If you see Seon-dong…
How could you give him advice like that?
It's obviously a misunderstanding.
I didn't tell him to run away from home.
He's just nine.
Of course he wouldn't understand!
Staying out of her sight?
How did you think he'd interpret that?
Now he's done this.
Yes, I guess you have a point.
I agree that I'm partially responsible.
I meant that he should keep some distance
from Hui-won, but not like this.
Frankly, I only told him that
because he said following your advice
ruined everything.
Because she wouldn't accept his apologies.
Feelings are bound to get hurt
if you don't talk it out.
They might say some harsh things,
but it's better to apologize and make up.
You think it's better to wait it out
until the other person gets tired?
But the timing matters.
If the other person isn't
ready to accept it,
you can't just keep saying
what you need to say.
"I am very uncomfortable,
so accept my apology already."
That's just unreasonable.
How could you process it like that?
You have to say you're sorry
for them to know and understand.
A girl he likes is angry because of him,
and you told him to do nothing
because he's apologized enough?
I mean, that's just so like you.
Seon-dong!
I mean,
he said he was sorry.
He's done all he could
and it still wasn't enough.
Wouldn't it be better
to at least make her worry about him?
Sure, you did a terrific job
teaching an innocent kid
how to play hard-to-get.
Can you even call it proper love
if you're keeping distance
and being calculative?
I don't know how you do relationships,
but I wouldn't teach anyone to do that.
Hold on. What about you?
You sure sound like an expert.
How are you doing in that department?
"Proper love." Give me a break.
You've never been in a relationship.
What did you say?
I'd rather not date anyone
than do it your way.
Have you been in a relationship with me?
You don't know anything.
I mean,
what I'm saying is…
Yes, Chief.
Really? Yes, I know where that is.
I'll be there right away.
Did they find him?
He's been on the bus
that circles the village.
He wouldn't get off,
so the driver called the police.
Let's go to town first.
Okay.
The apology should have been
more sincere, right?
I'm talking about Seon-dong and Hui-won.
Seon-dong should have apologized
more sincerely,
but I don't think Hui-won said
she wouldn't hang out with Seon-dong
because she really hated him.
She kept snapping at him,
but I'm sure she eventually realized
how sorry he was.
Don't you agree?
The thing is,
your coaching wasn't exactly
great advice for a nine-year-old,
but it may not be all wrong.
Nothing's more concerning
than to have someone disappear.
Were you concerned too?
Officer Ahn?
Yes.
Of course.
A child went missing.
I'm not talking about…
Never mind.
Seon-dong.
Kim Seon-dong.
Ja-young.
You brat. What are you doing out here?
Were you planning on not going home?
Doctor.
Hui-won's not angry anymore.
She says you can contact her.
Really?
Doctor, you're awesome!
You little punk!
Ja-young.
Don't ever do this again.
Have you been…
well?
We parted so suddenly,
that I thought I'd have a lot to say
when we met again.
But I forget.
Say something.
But then again,
I did all the talking back then.
How long have you known?
You wrote me your name when you left.
On that book.
Also, you're Director Han's only grandson.
So I was the only one
who completely forgot.
It has been a long time.
You weren't exactly here
on a good occasion.
And it's not like I couldn't stop
thinking about you all this time.
I'd forgotten, but I remembered
when I saw your face and heard your name.
This village is still the same, isn't it?
Nothing's changed.
This place is also the same.
I think a lot has changed.
With you, Officer Ahn.
Since I've grown old?
It looks like it's going to rain.
Let's talk later. You should get home.
What?
Why are you still here?
Did Seon-dong get home safely?
Yes. His grandma slapped
his back a little, though.
Thanks to you,
I learned a new technique as well.
I'm going to try it
when a relationship doesn't go well.
Keeping distance.
I was just joking.
Anyway, have a good night.
Wait.
You were…
the only good memory from that year.
I'm sorry I forgot.
Ahn Ja-young.
I'm not the type to enjoy
spontaneous events, okay?
It's so good.
Despite all that, I don't hate it.
What do you think is up with her?
Ji-yul!
Anyway, who is she?
A woman.
A young and pretty woman.
Our bed-and-breakfast guest was
our vet's guest?
Your girlfriend must have missed you a lot
to come all the way here.
So who is that Officer Ahn?
Besides, she is your first love.
Subtitle translation by: Daniel Shin