♪You're the unattainable star♪
♪I'm the tiniest dust in the world♪
♪With all the sincerity I can muster♪
♪For your kiss after the tears♪
♪Through the storm♪
♪I'd like to travel with you♪
[Beauty Strategy Season 1]
[Adapted from The Spirit Queen
by TUTU on Kuaikan Comic]
[Episode 17]
[Who Killed His Mother?]
Unexpectedly,
to save my life,
you would rather expose yourself.
The next time we meet,
I'll be coming to marry you.
What kind of wedding do you want?
I heard
the wedding of common people
of your clan is interesting.
The bride has a red veil on her head.
They'll eat and drink at night.
You care so much for me.
I won't disappoint you.
What?
Mu Xuanjue has survived?
Who could save him?
This is really weird.
No imperial physician
went to check on him.
Go investigate
every single one around him.
Yes.
Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, you're awake.
I'm all right now.
Did anyone else see
what happened last night?
No.
But Her Majesty's men just came.
I guess they want to figure out
how you came back to life, Your Majesty.
I've recovered without any treatment.
It's really hard to explain.
Your Majesty,
I know Consort Ling
is meritorious for saving you.
But please focus on the big picture.
With Her Majesty's power,
she will figure out who Consort Ling is
sooner or later.
By then, you can hardly
distance yourself from her.
Why was I so impulsive last night?
Do I have true feelings for Mu Xuanjue?
You want me to sell her out
to calm Her Majesty?
Your Majesty,
being soft-hearted will
cause you to lose everything.
This is what you said.
We've been hibernating
to fight back against Her Majesty.
We can't give up for a mere consort.
Say no more.
I have my plan.
She's still useful to me.
Your Majesty, please don't forget
that Princess Shuoye killed your mother.
You've been using and torturing her
just for revenge.
Lingzhi, hear me out.
Why?
Why did you say I killed your mother?
I didn't even know her.
How could I possibly kill her?
It happened six years ago
during the war.
Six years ago?
I don't remember anything.
Did I really kill your mother?
Did you see it with your own eyes?
Yes.
I saw it with my eyes.
Lingzhi.
Don't touch me!
You've long figured out who I am, right?
Only I was kept in the dark
and deceived by your insincerity!
Lingzhi.
Right.
I knew who you were.
I was planning to take revenge.
But I...
You want revenge?
You can kill me now.
I'll pay with my own life.
♪If love had never♪
♪Broken into my heart♪
♪When I looked back, I'd miss♪
♪Who I met at first sight♪
♪I kept dreaming about you♪
No.
I won't let you die.
♪I'd forget♪
♪All the miserable old memories♪
How come I killed his mother?
How come?
♪Expecting to get wet
in the snow when I'm old♪
Who am I to him?
♪I'll turn around for my next life♪
Is it that...?
♪If I'm lucky enough
to grow old with you♪
What happened in the past...
and all his feelings for me are fake?
♪My heart calls for you♪
♪But I had to sleep alone♪
♪I'd forget♪
♪All the miserable old memories♪
♪Expecting to get wet
in the snow when I'm old♪
♪I'll turn around for my next life♪
♪If I'm lucky enough
to grow old with you♪
♪How much will destiny
keep its promise?♪
Your Grace,
Her Majesty is summoning you.
Come with us, please.
Your Majesty,
Consort Huan's maid Shana
is here to see you.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
What are you doing here?
I want to plead for Consort Huan.
You're a mere maid.
You are in no position to plead for her.
I'd like to exchange a secret
for Her Grace's life.
Your Majesty,
if you can spare Her Grace's life,
I will tell you
the truth of your mother's death.
I eavesdropped on this secret
in the palace of the Phantom clan.
Even Consort Huan doesn't know about it.
Your Majesty,
Her Majesty is summoning you.
Greetings, Mother.
How do you feel now?
Thanks to your blessing, Mother.
I was wearing a soft armor
so Consort Huan only pierced my flesh
instead of my heart.
Don't worry, Mother.
Is that true?
The night you were injured,
was Consort Ling keeping you company?
Your Majesty,
I know some simple medical skills.
I then took care of His Majesty
when he was asleep.
Simple medical skills?
I didn't know
you who was once a slave
could cure people.
Before I came to the palace,
I once
was a quack doctor's apprentice.
I wonder how much more
you're going to surprise me.
Consort Ling is meritorious
to protect me.
But Mother, you're so indifferent.
Does my survival
upset you?
I think you're shocked
by Consort Huan's assassination.
You seem to forget
you should kneel to me
when you meet me alone.
His Majesty hasn't fully recovered
and it's inconvenient
for him to kneel now.
Your Majesty, please forgive him.
How about I kneel
on behalf of His Majesty?
You're in no position to talk here!
Mu Xuanjue,
I'm the Royal Empress Dowager,
after all.
Don't forget
who made you the Emperor.
When the Human army
broke into the Spirit Shrine,
the Royal Empress Dowager
threatened our clan to send an assassin
with the extinction of our clan.
Disguised as Princess Shuoye
with our forbidden spell,
he killed your mother
and framed the Spirit clan.
The one behind this tragedy
is Her Majesty.
I'm wrong.
I won't forget how you've raised me.
I'll always keep it in mind
and never forget it.
Please forgive me, Your Majesty.
Reflect on yourself.
If you dare to contradict me again,
you'll have to bear the consequences.
Mother,
I've found out the real murderer
who killed you.
When I can tell everyone
what she has done,
I will kill her
and avenge you.
Sorry.
Your Majesty, don't say this.
Just now, you helped me out.
I'm really grateful.
Wait a minute.
Go somewhere with me.
I'll explain everything to you.
Are you saying
that the one who killed your mother
wasn't me,
but Her Majesty?
Before, I was deceived by the illusion
and got you wrong.
Can you forgive me?
Yes, of course.
We've been through this much.
I'll continue to assist you
as your consort.
Will you only
be my subordinate?
Your Grace, His Majesty
wants to see you.
It's so late.
What does His Majesty want me for?
His Majesty is waiting for you
in the Chenning Palace.
Please get changed and go immediately.
♪Winter snow gently falls into the yard♪
[Chenning Palace]
♪There is no mercy in the palace♪
[Xi]
[*It's always used in Chinese weddings]
♪The further, the harder.
How brave do I have to be to reappear?♪
♪Is the murmuring memory
a dream or a fantasy?♪
♪Butterflies can fly
over the mountains for love♪
♪And die before the flowers♪
♪You're far away and you're right here♪
♪The game we play is destiny♪
♪I fancy myself by your side♪
♪If you agree to meet me,
I'll have nothing to regret♪
♪You're the unattainable star♪
♪I'm the tiniest dust in the world♪
♪With love and hate,
we look into each other's eyes♪
♪As the wind blows, the petals dance♪
♪You're the unattainable star♪
♪I'm the tiniest dust in the world♪
♪With all the sincerity I can muster
For your kiss after the tears♪
♪Through the storm,
I'd like to travel with you♪
♪Butterflies can fly
over the mountains for love♪
♪And die before the flowers♪