Is everything you said in court true?
Have you been lying this whole time?
Who is the person who
promised you your future?
Did these drug parties happen often?
Who forced you to make
a false testimony?
Are you admitting to regular drug use?
We need to move. Please move.
Why are you doing this now?
The thing that secures my future
is not someone powerful
but fans who believe in me.
I had forgotten that.
When I realized that, I came to my senses.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry that I have
nothing more to say.
Is this fan a man?
- Yes.
- What is your relationship to him?
I am his fan as well.
I'm sorry. I'll explain everything after
the investigation is over.
Is he also a celebrity?
Is he a sunbae actor?
- Did someone suggest a sponsorship?
- Park Hae Na!
Bravo!
- Bravo, bravo!
- Applause!
It's not like I won a gold medal.
What's up with you guys?
I feel like ten years' worth of
constipation was just released.
My friends in the administrative
and executive departments
kept saying we were making the trial drag,
and asked me what was wrong with you.
That you lost it because it's an actress.
There was much talk.
Isn't it true we become either
proud or ashamed
of our work depending on
whom we're dealing with?
Was this the last trial you
absolutely had to work on?
Yes.
All right.
You made a difficult decision.
Not really.
Of course.
I know it must not have
been easy for you.
I always...
go by the law and my
conscience. For justice...
That's enough.
You're resigning; you don't
need to bring up justice.
- Resign?
- You just had to hand it to me.
You came in on a Sunday and
so tenderly put it on my desk.
I know I kept telling you to resign, but now
that you did, I feel strange.
I put this robe on you and now
it feels like I'm kicking you out.
I approved and submitted it, so it
will be processed in a week.
I...
resigned?
I will stake my life on defending you
to the disciplinary committee.
We shouldn't mar the records
of a departed family.
I know, I know. I know
how you feel of course.
I know it's not easy to quit being a judge.
Who wouldn't have regrets?
Don't worry about the other matters.
Let's just wrap up the rulings you have left.
Go take a trip and prepare to
start your career as an attorney.
I might not be a big help, but
I'll help in any way I can.
So Eun,
- a moment, please.
- Yes.
Yes?
- Should we run away instead of working?
- What?
- Where?
- Lunch.
It's only eleven.
You never skipped class
in school, did you?
No, I didn't.
I've never not skipped class.
Let's go.
What is this?
I wanted to get you
something nice somewhere.
I've wanted to do something like this.
To get some sunshine,
people-watching, and
have a conversation,
while feeling relaxed.
You can do this any time.
You could do it every lunch hour.
Not like that.
I actually wanted to relax.
I've never really done that.
My sister was a junior in
college when it happened.
I was a freshman.
After she disappeared,
I transferred to study law,
to get the bastard in court again
and to let my sister come out of hiding.
So...
I have not had time to relax.
I had to study all the time.
It would've been easier to be a killer.
Right.
Every day felt impossible.
But...
today feels different, thanks to you.
Just wait a bit more.
All your wishes will come true.
You'll find your sister
and he'll be punished.
When you are not hurting anymore,
this will break.
It will happen, right?
No matter what.
But instead,
you need to become a judge,
even if it takes time.
In this world, the judge is king.
I want to as well.
You'll have moved to the
collegiate division by then,
and I'll fight to follow you
and be a fellow judge.
Your Honor, it's certain
you will give me all the work.
I will stay late every day
and you will...
ask me why I work so hard,
say I shouldn't work so hard
for my measly salary.
You'll drag me out to eat and
drink late into the night.
My sister...
will call me to ask when I'm getting home.
Why right now?
For what reason?
Why are you so pretty?
If you say that kind of stuff
all of a sudden...
Could you repeat that?
No.
Why not?
You should've been listening the first time.
Let's go.
Yes. We need to work.
No. We're going to play.
What about work?
Let's play just one last time.
So Eun, So Eun! It's okay. Stand up.
I'm taking this off.
It's okay.
- Trainee Song.
- Yes?
I didn't get scolded much,
and the judge is feeling fine.
And I'm always on your side.
Oh, you gave this to me last time.
Here.
- You have a piece of hair.
- What?
Me, too.
The idol star Park, who has been
under investigation for drug use,
has outed the heirs of a
conglomerate and a hospital
and a son of a prominent political
figure thereby shocking us all.
She has exposed the so-called
"high-class drug parties."
For the first time, a judge made allegations
in the middle of a trial.
Yes, Press Director.
Yes.
What is this?
Open it.
They're gift certificates.
It's from the department head.
Text him and thank him.
Is it a retirement bonus?
- I'll see you on the news.
- Why are you all doing this to me?
The message boards are
blowing up about you leaving.
"Did you fire her because
she delivered real news?"
"I' will petition it before the president."
People called to complain,
so the president's cell and office
phones were ringing all day.
Who are these people online?
Why are they so diligent?
Is that why?
Don't get me wrong. You're not coming back
because of a few online messages.
You're the number one search term,
so we're using you again.
Yes.
Do you even know what
you're agreeing to?
The viewers are saying they want
to see you, not the news.
You make us money, so
we are reinstating you.
That's the main reason.
You want me to make
a lot of money, right?
If you don't, be ready to disrobe.
(Means quit the job figuratively)
Hey.
That wasn't sexual harassment.
I, when I said disrobe...
I meant it symbolically, to the
organization you belong to...
Do I need to keep explaining?
I'll go and earn money.
Wow...
Ohdaeyang, the number one
legal firm in South Korea.
Its top lawyer, Oh Sang Cheol
over there, and his team.
I really liked you, Hyung.
What is this?
I said, what is this!
Did I...
disappoint you guys in some way?
Did I not treat you well?
Hey, you.
Listen carefully.
I won't be investigated.
No, I cannot be.
I will put in all I have
and make sure you waste time
in the middle of nowhere
until you quit.
Mr. President, you too.
You have nothing to say, do you?
My inadequate son made a mistake.
- Let's talk privately.
- I don't need it!
Don't even think about working
with Oh Sung again.
That's between the chairman
and me, Managing Director.
Oh, so you're close with my father?
Do you think my father will be alive forever?
You have no guarantee of
becoming the chairman.
If you don't treat this case with caution,
don't you think your brother,
Lee Ho Jun, will leap forward?
Wow...
The drugs were paid for
with a check under Choi Min Guk's name.
It appears that he committed
the actual crime.
Do you have a right to be sitting here?
Get out.
Please excuse us for a moment, prosecutor.
Geez. S***.
Sunbae, it looks like you will
work regionally and retire.
You have to at least stick the sword in
to have power if you start
an attorney's office.
You mother******.
A lawyer mocking a prosecutor?
What's a prosecutor anyway?
- What?
- What's a prosecutor?
You must be insane.
What is a prosecutor anyway, Sunbae?
Power.
You might be mocked for kissing the government's a**
and backing conglomerates, but in the end
prosecutors have the power to kill an
administration and take down a conglomerate.
Get yourself together.
Sunbae, you own this nation.
Are you comforting me or encouraging me?
Are you kidding me?
No matter how big a conglomerate,
they're just businessmen to me.
I got slapped by lowly businessmen.
Would I be kidding your right now?
What gives you such confidence?
Drop Oh Sung and align
yourself with Han Young.
You have a hookup?
I will make a spot for you.
So Sunbae, you must handle this case.
To go mainstream, or to leave my
post in some country town.
You want me to gamble.
Is that it?
You have a great deck.
You cannot lose.
I was not able to put in too much.
Aigoo, how small.
Things are a bit difficult over
there these days, huh?
It's because I'm still a trainee.
You might make a little now, but when
you are a judge or prosecutor
and earning a lot,
you will feel so satisfied.
So take this for the road,
and treat yourself to some ice cream.
No, please, take it.
You dropped my case in return for
finding your sister. It's a done deal.
Why are you shoving this in my face
when it's been settled?
Just think of it as a small gesture.
Small gestures become
big fortunes later!
I've been trying to teach you that a threat
works better than a request in this world.
Here.
Okay, fine.
Mr. Sa.
You know your deadline with
me is approaching, right?
If you don't keep your word this time,
I will sue you again for fraud.
Aigoo.
I have already drafted the paperwork.
I just need to submit it.
Legally, once a case is dropped,
it cannot be resubmitted.
Once gone, no more;
that's the golden rule.
Try threatening me when
it's actually effective!
You're looking for my sister, right?
You need to have faith
to have immortal life.
Please keep your promise.
If you find your sister, are you going
to try him in court again?
I am going to submit an appeal
and go all the way.
Miss judge-in-training,
you've never been tried, huh?
No.
Why?
The world is like that.
More important thing than
the guilty being punished
is that the innocent is shielded from pain.
Aigoo, welcome.
For two?
We're here for you, Your Honor.
We collected the black box.
Would you like to check?
Aigoo, not necessary.
We trust people easily.
One must have faith to attain immortal life.
I enjoyed watching the trial and the news.
The word is as out as it can be already.
We have already pretty much
won the bidding.
Thank you with all my heart, Your Honor.
I should give this to you when
the guilty verdict is confirmed, but...
you really hurt their image with
the upper-class drug party stuff.
So, it's all but pretty much confirmed.
I'm so happy to have a great
relationship with you, Your Honor.
I really...
did all that only thinking about this.
Do you have any idea what the
last month was like for me?
How could I comprehend
your deep thoughts
and hard work?
You could not.
Is this a billion won?
Yes.
If you give me your key,
I'll put it in your car.
No.
Let me revel in this moment.
A billion won.
A billion won in cash.
Being a judge is great.
Money! One billion won!
You're all dead to me!
I earned a billion won!
[ From Park Jae Hyung ]
Your Honor.
I know you put in hard work
for justice, day and night.
I sincerely respect your efforts.
I am Park Jae Hyung, the younger brother
of appellant Park Ji Ho.
My brother has a developmental disability.
He has a low IQ
and cannot make eye contact with others,
but he is a good son who does
whatever his mother says.
Mom,
the fridge is packed.
Put, put it here?
Or here? Here?
Here? Oh, here!
Like this?
Mom, are you sick?
You're always sick.
The side dishes.
Are they from Woo Jung?
I need to die so you two
can live together.
How is school?
The teachers are nice
and I'm learning technical skills.
They call me a technician.
Mom, Mom, I don't need money.
Mom... hospital...
You should buy medicine.
Jae Ho...
have a happy life
with your brother
and Woo Jung.
Mom?
Because I'm...
so tired,
I want to sleep.
If I don't answer because I'm sleeping,
don't wake me up
and go to school.
I'm...
cold.
Put the blanket on me.
You're cold.
Cover my face, too
since I'm cold.
Please...
and press down.
Like this?
She's cold. My mom is cold.
More?
How long do I need to do it for?
Mom. Are you still cold?
Are you cold?
Mom.
Are you asleep?
Are you asleep, Mom?
I...
am engaged to be married to
the appellant Park Jae Ho.
My name is Bang Woo Jung.
My fiancé is
accused of murdering his own family.
Everything on here
is true, right?
Yes.
Why did you kill your mother?
Because of money.
Mom, hospital, under her blanket.
because of money.
Good job.
From now on,
no matter who asks, just answer that way.
Then...
the judge will send you home.
Got it?
The judge...
hates people who keep flip-flopping.
You know?
Then...
you'll never go home.
The criminal intent of Park,
under investigation
for murdering a family member,
has been revealed.
According to the prosecution, Park
murdered his mother after an argument
over her refusal to give him money.
The amount was only 200,000 won.
Defendant Park Jae Ho was his mother's,
Lee Young Soon's, caretaker.
He said things like, "I was tired."
"I wish she would die already."
He often revealed his discomfort.
He fed rotten food to his mother,
who could not move.
He attempted to worsen her condition.
When his plan didn't unfold,
he finally murdered her.
The defendant is not such
a cold-hearted murderer!
Not everything that has been
reported in the media is true.
Watch what you say.
I don't rule by public opinion.
The defendant has a
developmental disability.
This was not an intentional crime.
Please accept the diagnosis from
a psychologist as evidence.
The defendant is learning technical
skills at a trade school.
He has already
earned a certificate for the third degree.
I cannot accept the opinion that
he is disabled enough to be
unaware of his homicidal act.
That's enough for arguments
on either side.
Is everything on the report true?
Do you have an opinion?
What?
Yes.
Prosecution, please
recommend a sentence.
For the defendant...
I recommend the legal maximum.
The death penalty.
Your Honor.
Please find the truth within the lies.
I beg of you.
Please be lenient toward Park Jae Ho,
who is about to be my husband.
I beg you with all my heart.
From Bang Woo Jung.
You want to use my trial to
cover up a drug party
some rich kids had?
There's something to this, right?
They're trying to cover
up something, right?
How would a judge know?
I'm not asking you to rule either way.
Just so the mood doesn't go sour...
you can wrap up the trial quickly.