I've never seen this much money
before in my life.
This is crazy.
Where should I spend this?
Wherever you want.
Can I do anything with it?
This much money?
It's not that much, thinking
about your future, Your Honor.
Then I'll be extravagant.
First, I'm buying clothes.
Shoes.
An imported car.
A trip abroad.
Entertainment. No.
I need to buy some land.
If I take this much out to buy land...
then nothing's left.
A billion won isn't that much after all.
So little.
Did I upset you somehow?
No.
I like how you think.
Money buys everything.
So honest and earnest.
They say it's dirty to like money,
but I don't agree.
So why are you acting like...
It's just that
I hate you guys.
If you tell me what I did wrong,
I will fix the misunderstanding.
There's someone I really like right now.
Is there someone you like, ahjussi?
I am married.
Having a family is good.
Try not to like anyone.
Do not like your wife.
Or your son or daughter.
Don't like anyone.
Ever.
A bad guy
does not have the right to like someone.
Your Honor!
What was that?
Long time no see, Your Honor.
Park Jae Hyung?
Yes.
- Are you here to kidnap me again?
- Yes.
You got the wrong person.
I...
His twin brother must be somewhere.
He's not.
I've looked around here for hours.
Hurry up.
This kind of thing is my specialty.
What's it like to be on the
other side of judgment?
Let's share our names first.
You're that kind of guy.
No matter how much I cried and shouted,
you didn't know who I was.
I'm Bang Woo Jung,
Jae Ho's fiancé.
Nice to meet you.
Bang Woo Jung?
I...
am Judge Han Soo Ho's brother,
Han Kang Ho.
What?
You don't know this, but
we're twins.
My brother is a judge, and I am me.
I know you are twins.
We followed you out of court.
Is everyone who comes
out of court a judge?
Do you want to live that badly?
My work is done.
It's not me.
Apologize to Jae Ho.
Apologize and
die.
My f***ing brother did it!
The whole world wanted Jae Ho dead.
But the judge should have said no.
[ This is Judge Han Soo Ho. Let's talk. ]
You are the law.
You should not have.
I'm Han Kang Ho.
I'm not Han Soo Ho!
Wait!
Hello?
Who are you?
Seoul Central Court Criminal Division
Judge Han Soo Ho.
I'd like to meet up.
With Bang Woo Jung, too.
You pick the time and place.
I'll call you back. Wait.
What? Who was that?
Judge Han Soo Ho.
What are you going to do?
I need to get him.
Kill one or kill both.
I heard about the case.
Are you going to kill Soo Ho?
After you kill him, what will you do?
What are you going to do with me?
You can kill Soo Ho, but
I'm an innocent citizen.
I...
Hey!
If you do this kind of thing, later...
The call is not going through.
After the beep...
Your Honor, what's up?
Okay! I'm glad you caught him!
Look, that's Han Soo Ho!
Ask him if that's true or not!
Untie this and let's talk.
Don't get it twisted.
We didn't meet you to talk.
Who is Han Soo Ho? Be clear.
I am Han Soo Ho.
That's right! A judge does not lie!
If you want to prove it further,
take off his shirt.
On his right arm.
Hey, hey, hey!
Judges usually do not get tattoos.
Don't think about it too hard.
Let's kill Han Soo Ho first
and deal with the rest later.
Apologize to Jae Ho first.
Then you'll die.
It's true that Park Jae Ho killed his mother.
Whether he had a low IQ,
whatever his intent was,
the act of killing another human being
does not change.
I chose a sentence that is
fitting for that act.
You're lying!
The criminal intent shown
in the media was not the problem.
I just went by the law according to the act.
Do you know my brother?
What do you know?
How is someone like you the law?
Huh?
Hey!
Send me home!
I had nothing to do with it!
How can you say that when
your brother is about to die?
If it weren't for that bastard,
I wouldn't be here.
If it's hard to kill him, let me know. I'll help.
Shut up and stay still
before I kill you first.
Is that your apology?
An unfortunate upbringing.
A developmental disability.
Taking those into consideration,
I could have sentenced about ten years.
But...
I wanted to end the trial quickly...
and there were some agreements.
Who agrees with whom
about such a thing?
A year...
or ten. You should have
figured out the truth.
How could you rule like that?
It's my fault.
But...
it does not change the fact
that he killed his mother.
Jae Ho...
listens to everyone he likes.
He said his mother asked him to.
He has no idea what life or death is.
Did you research the visitation logs?
Has it occurred to you that
he might have died
because you told him to?
I messed up the trial.
You messed up your words.
We are accomplices.
If this is really for Park Jae Ho,
get a retrial.
I did nothing wrong.
This is all...
your fault!
Let's stop right there!
You call yourself a judge?
I am going to tell mom about
everything that happened today.
She always says you are the best,
but I am so curious what
her reaction will be.
It's okay.
Park Jae Ho's case was
pushed to the forefront
to cover up a drug case involving
the sons of powerful families.
He knew that, and still
that so-called judge sentenced
the death penalty.
If you really want revenge, appeal
and put that guy on the stand.
Make him say he was wrong
on the witness stand.
Make him repent.
And if he doesn't,
still forgive him.
Even if I die,
our mom will live.
But if Hyung dies, our mom will die.
Our mom...
only cares about Hyung.
We lost everything
and you want everything.
I have nothing anyway.
No money, no family.
Our mom...
removed me from the family
register when I was young.
I have five criminal records.
She says that my coming
home is embarrassing.
I can't know
what you two are feeling.
And even if you cannot forgive
my stupid hyung,
please don't kill him.
I beg you.
Did you use me as bait?
They kidnap me, you show
up and act all smart?
You volunteered to be bait.
Wow. You're so-called hyung.
That is so you. You really are Han Soo Ho.
Extremely annoying.
I don't care if you die, so
watch your own neck.
I know I don't deserve to be a judge.
A few days ago,
I resigned.
He's a great lawyer.
If you contact him, he'll help with the retrial.
I will be a witness.
Come see me anytime.
If you want to kill me,
you can.
♫ The memories that await me there ♫
♫ Like a dream, the
loneliness digs into me ♫
♫ I miss you, in my heart,
I can't pacify these emotions ♫
♫ It leads you back to me ♫
- Hey, it's me.
- Are you alive?
I'm going to go in tomorrow and pack up.
Don't you dare come near the court.
I have a trial tomorrow. I'm really busy.
Don't you dare come in.
How are you going to run a trial?
It's the last ruling my trainee
wrote, so I have to read it.
She's miles better than me
and miles better than you, bastard.
I'm hanging up.
Crazy bastard.
You know each other by
face and name, right?
I apologize for fighting
Han Young unintentionally.
We are always following Ohdaeyang's power.
So old-fashioned.
I heard that these days, you should get to the
point first and save the small talk for later.
Why don't you discuss how much you'll
pay me for this blind date?
The bidding on the government
land looks promising, yes?
We are hoping for a smart
decision by the government.
If O Sung loses the bid,
according to the process,
we will file an administrative lawsuit.
There are no problems with the process.
The announcement should have been confirmed
before the final deadline, fourteen days ago,
but it was changed thirteen days ago
in case O Sung loses, to use as retaliation.
You're here to make waves.
Is this Ohdaeyang's doing?
This is an 11 trillion won project.
We are not willing to hand it
off to Han Young.
What do you want?
Let's join forces.
Would your father let that happen?
My father will be arrested
along with Lee Ho Sung.
In the olden days, grownups were scary.
But these days, young people are scarier.
What are your terms?
An ongoing partnership.
If not, we have no reason to abandon O Sung.
The call is not going through.
After the beep...
- The judge isn't answering his phone, right?
- No.
What's going on?
It's unlike him.
Is he sick, or did he get into an accident?
That can't be, right?
Maybe you should go to his house.
If we had a trial or something, I would.
But I feel strange going when
there's no urgent matter.
If you give me the address, I'll go.
That's personal information, so I can't.
Did he get drunk?
Yes.
Aigoo, hello! Section Leader, I'm here.
Hey, what's going on today? What's this?
I'm here to collect paperwork.
Please give me all of these.
Besides tomorrow's case, that should be all.
What's this?
Why all these cases?
The judge resigned.
Our judge did?
What?
You didn't know?
Anyway, please just bring them over.
Get the judge's signature on that
and send it to administration.
♫ I lost myself ♫
♫ Through the thick fog,
I am falling apart ♫
♫ Like a fading star ♫
♫ In the empty night sky, I'm alone ♫
♫ Oh baby, please tell me ♫
♫ That tomorrow is coming ♫
[ Song So Eun ]
♫ I'm walking in the
endless darkness ♫
♫ I'm headed to you at
the end of the road ♫
The phone is turned off.
After the beep...
♫ In my heart ♫
Are you sick?
You're not in an accident, right?
Call me.
♫ Shine on me ♫
Wow, you must be elated, Section Leader.
You won't have any work for a while,
so you can go home on time.
- I'll be off, then. Good luck.
- Good luck.
Could you help me?
Thank you.
- Bye.
- Sure.
How can the judge do this?
He should have told us.
He always said he was going to quit.
There must have been a reason.
Since he resigned, is he not coming in?
I don't know. Why are you asking me?
- Then whom do I ask?
- I don't know. Not me.
♫ I close my eyes until the
night goes white ♫
♫ I am headed to you ♫
♫ After I've been hurt so much ♫
♫ In my life ♫
♫ Embrace me with your warmth ♫
♫ Shine on me ♫
[ Mom ]
Hello?
Mom?
Come home this weekend
with your brother.
I'm busy.
Speak to your brother and
come down together.
I can't see you two like that anymore.
You said I should never see you again.
What changed your mind?
I have something to tell you. Come
together this weekend. No matter what.
If not, I'm coming up there.
My sons are coming.
You have the good stuff you hide away
in the fridge, right? I'll take that.
Geez, they hit the back of my head.
So Eun, it's me.
I'm okay.
Where are you? Are you off work already?
So Eun, it's me!
I'm sorry.
You were worried, right?
No.
I fell down on my way home.
I kind of cracked the back of my head.
So I have a big headache.
I meant to go to sleep, and passed out...
I'm so sorry I didn't call.
I mean...
Did you get hurt badly?
A little.
You told me you would let
me know if you got hurt.
Is something wrong?
Someone from the administration came.
He took all the records except
the one for the trial tomorrow.
Why?
Why did they take my stuff?
Because Your Honor, you resigned.
- I meant to tell you.
- When?
Before or after you resigned?
I'm sorry I didn't tell you before.
You said you would stay with
me until I finished.
I'm sorry.
Although I have fewer than
ten days of training,
it seems you're quitting.
See you tomorrow.
I came to see your face.
I thought you might be worried.
I worried all day.
Why am I so worried about you?
I was worried about myself
since I couldn't do anything but worry.
Hey, let it go.
After you're done training,
I'll come by with flowers.
I'll get the biggest bouquet.
You're not my mentor judge anymore.
Yes.
We don't have a work relationship.
I have nothing to report to you.
Yes.
You're not my superior anymore, either.
I've never thought of us that way.
Anyway...
we're no longer trainee and judge.
I'm leaving.
See you tomorrow.
Stay over.
♫ Story, my story ♫
♫ Your shouts can't heal my wounds ♫
♫ I don't want to be without you ♫
♫ I remember the times we had together ♫
♫ Story, my story ♫
♫ No matter how much I shout... ♫