Honorable Chairman
and members of the
Disciplinary Committee, hello.
My name is Song So Eun, a judicial
trainee under the mentorship
of Judge Han Soo Ho of the criminal branch.
I heard Judge Han was summoned
to this disciplinary hearing.
Judge Han I know is a warmer
judge than anyone I know.
If a judge, through interpretation,
fills in the gaps of the law
Han Soo Ho goes one step further to
fill the pain of those going through the trial
and endeavors to heal them.
The Judge Han Soo Ho I saw was
more passionate than anyone else.
He even takes off his robe
and runs to the crime scene
to check the authenticity of the petition.
The Han Soo Ho I saw is more
humble than anyone I know.
After every trial, he bows to the audience.
He might be on a high legal pedestal,
but he lowers himself to show
that laws are not above people.
And the Judge Han Soo Ho I saw...
is a good person.
Okay.
I'm out of here.
Goodbye,
Han Soo Ho, you bastard.
I'm leaving.
Dang it.
Why is my mom here?
Soo Ho.
Why are you at your hyung's house?
Where is Soo Ho?
Soo Ho! Soo Ho!
Soo Ho isn't here.
He's on a business trip.
- Where?
- How would I know?
Why are you in Seoul?
Today's the ancestral rite for
your grandfather in Bangbaedong.
But I can't reach your older brother's phone.
I keep calling, but it says
I have the wrong number.
I'm so worried, I can't just stay still.
He must have changed his number.
He'll tell you later.
What are you doing in his house?
I was going to stay a night,
but I'm leaving since he's not here.
What's this bag?
- Are you stealing something?
- No!
Let me see what you swiped from him.
Don't!
- Let me see it.
- Seriously?
What is this, stop and frisk?
Are you the police?
These clothes are your brother's, right?
Stay the night, all right?
I'll be home in a few days.
Why are you running away?
Where are you going?
Mom,
if I open a nice restaurant,
do you want to run it with me?
I'll be the chef, and you can be the manager.
I'll pay you a lot.
You're in trouble again, right?
Bring a resume and a cover letter
and your salary requirement.
Where are you going this late, Kang Ho?
Mom's here, stay the night!
Hey! Han Kang Ho!
I don't have your number, so I'm
going home without calling you.
From Song So Eun.
Hello?
Oppa?
You're not busy?
How come you're here during work hours?
You don't have a trial?
No.
You're resigning?
Really?
How much did you get?
You really did get paid.
I'm going to pay it back.
That's weak for a judge's explanation.
Sounds like a politician's go-to comment.
"It wasn't a bribe. It was a loan.
I'll be paying it back."
I told them I'd be paying it back.
I was going to.
The golf ball incident is about to blow up
as a bribery scandal of the judicial branch.
There is a bribery list circulating
amongst reporters.
Your name is on it.
Eun.
If it's reported, I have to say your name on air.
What am I going to do?
When I first met you, I thought...
A woman like me should
at least date a judge.
But...
while I was dating you, my pride
was severely hurt.
The door was shut so hard.
I want to go in, but you won't open it.
How great could you be?
I wanted to go inside and mess things up.
But once I finally entered,
I saw nothing.
You're an empty person.
I should have left you then, but I couldn't.
I wanted to fill you.
I know.
No.
You don't know
what it feels like to completely
fill another person,
what it feels like to mean
something to someone else.
If you feel the same way,
pay that money back.
I will.
Ask me again after you pay them back
If you deserve to be a boyfriend or a judge.
I'll give you my answer then.
I have to run.
I have a meeting.
And...
don't be mad if I utter your name.
I summarized the main points
of the Lee Soon Cheol case.
But the more I think about it,
the more unfair it seems.
I'm sorry about yesterday.
Something came up, and I couldn't call.
You waited long, right?
It's okay. I just worked and went home.
But...
Is your phone not working?
I have a separate phone.
My real number...
Oh, you do?
Can I have it?
Later.
Let's have dinner tonight.
Not soju or beer, but a grand meal.
You're not going to run away again?
No reason to anymore.
It's all over.
What is?
Oh, sorry.
[ President Sa ]
Hello, Mr. Sa.
What?
One second, one second.
Yes.
Yes, I'm writing it down. One second.
Oh, yes.
Kim...
Yes.
Yes, thank you.
Your Honor, can I...
Can I leave early today?
Did something happen?
Um...
I...
No. It's nothing, but...
So Eun!
I'm sorry.
I have to leave early, thank you.
Aigoo, I'm the best at
finding missing people.
The person who sold an
I.D. card to someone
who looks like your sister
finally contacted me.
[ Gimpo, Hwangung Mi's Club, Strawberry ]
In downtown Gimpo,
there's a club called Hwangung Mi's.
It's a nightclub.
Strawberry. She's going
by the name Strawberry.
She's registered as a foreigner from Harbin.
That's what they said.
[ Gimpo, Hwangung Mi's Club, Strawberry ]
I heard the gist from the girls.
- You're looking for your sister?
- Yes.
Her real name is Song Ji Yeon.
She's working here as a
foreigner from Harbin, I heard.
Daughters who left home.
Runaway sisters.
In this world,
that's a tale as old as time.
I don't need a sob story.
Go home.
I heard she goes by Strawberry.
An employee said she does work here.
- Please just call her.
- I...
have a responsibility to protect my girls.
How bad was it
that they left their families
to work here? No,
do you think they want
their families to know they work here?
Call her, please.
If you want money, I'll give you any amount.
I make a lot of money, lady.
Leave while I'm asking nicely.
Please, I'm begging you.
I...
have been looking for her for seven years.
You don't understand.
I hear many stories like that, I said.
I work in the courthouse.
If I need to,
I can take every legal measure possible.
Get out!
Let me go, I said!
Let go!
Rude b****, you want to talk about law?
Come here!
No, no, please!
You think I don't know any
judges and prosecutors?
Come here!
- Damn it!
- Hey!
- Who are you?
- Me? I'm a thug.
Bastard!
Are you okay?
How did you get here?
Send Strawberry to room number five.
Get them out!
Get her over here now.
She'll be right here.
When you leave
I'll walk you out, Your Honor.
You shouldn't come to
a place like this alone.
Thank you.
Drink.
I...
can be alone now.
Okay.
I'll wait for you at the entrance.
My real number.
Call me if anything happens.
You are looking for me?
I'm...
from Harbin.
You have...
news of my family?
I came to Korea alone.
My family was supposed to follow,
but I have no news of them.
My sister...
was sexually assaulted.
I thought he would obviously
be punished. But...
as the trial progressed, things got stranger.
They portrayed my sister as
a vixen who tried to seduce
a med student, failed and tried
to get settlement money.
She tried to kill herself, failed, and left home.
My parents emigrated abroad.
That happened to my family.
But do you know what punishment he got?
A 1.5 million won fine.
He had a team of six lawyers.
Must be from a wealthy family.
Yes.
The son of the famous
CEO of the Choi Hospital,
Choi Min Gook.
You have too much pride.
Dr. Choi Min Gook, the heir
to the Choi Hospital?
He's famous.
Now he's a humanitarian
who volunteers all the time.
Everyone is living well,
but where's my sister and what's she doing?
I tried to forget it all,
but I can't forget.
It feels so vivid.
I've been looking for seven years.
I'll find her someday.
I'll see her again someday.
Do you get it now?
How cruel the word "someday" can be.
When I was waiting for my sister by myself,
I prayed that it would be her.
And also wished it wouldn't be her.
Stop drinking.
♫ I've lost myself ♫
♫ in a thick fog ♫
Should we take a walk?
I'm sorry to show an ugly side of me.
But how did you find me?
♫  In the night sky ♫
Actually, I...
was going to quit today.
Stop joking.
Really.
You promised me.
A guy like me, promise?
I wanted to have dinner
with you one last time,
like the Last Supper.
It's good we didn't, then.
Sure.
It's good.
♫ In my heart with so much pain ♫
♫ with your warm light ♫
I'll be in tomorrow.
We need to fight on again.
♫ Shine on me ♫
♫ I close my eyes ♫
Let's go.
♫ Until the night turns white ♫
♫ I'm coming to you in the pouring rain ♫
♫ Shine on me ♫
How much did he put down?
He must have told you.
I don't know. I only heard he's bringing it.
So why did you call us here?
Hey, from Soo Ho's point of
view, we need to clear the air.
Everyone's awkward right now.
Is he going to request a couple
billion won or something?
He knows the rules of this world.
I'm guessing under 1.5 or 2 billion.
You never know.
People who grow up poor
have a beggar complex.
Friends!
Have you had breakfast?
Why aren't you eating?
What are you doing? Since
when do we eat stuff like this?
Why? It's delicious.
You brought the check, right?
Of course I did.
With this, I'll really get the amount I wrote?
Of course.
Cash or transfer?
However you want.
- Bastard.
- Geez.
That's not for the recipient to
decide. The giver is the king.
How much did you put?
Don't be surprised.
I knew you'd be surprised.
Hey, Han Soo Ho!
[ 23,000 won ]
23,000 won? Is that right?
Yeah.
Soondae, spicy rice cakes,
two tempura. 23,000 won.
It was 25,000, but I asked for
2,000 off to not burden you.
If you don't have cash, transfer please!
Are you joking right now?
Isn't it a joke to hand a judge a blank check?
Hey!
Who do you think you are?
Why are you doing this?
Because...
I don't like you guys.
What, a sense of justice or something?
Justice? That's been long out of style.
I don't know anything like that.
I'll say it again.
You.
I really don't like you guys.
You guys are so annoying.
I have to win.
I want to hang out, but I have to
run to my disciplinary hearing.
You guys can clean this up, right? Later.
I'm a fan.
See you in court.
So pretty.
Move it!
What's going on?
I'm not getting executed.
I'm going to win and come back.
The afternoon trials...
I've postponed them.
Section Leader Jo, you're the best!
Off to my hearing!
Your Honor, wait!
Yes, what's up?
Your tie.
What about my tie?
You're being called in for
not maintaining your dignity.
You should maintain your dignity.
I'll be back.
Want to come with me?
Just to the waiting room.
Yes.
Let's go.
♫ We might be giving each
other pain, living just like now ♫
♫  Burying your sadness in
a grave, saying I'm okay ♫
♫ Someday, to me, to you ♫
♫ the morning will come back... ♫