Dad, I remember everything now.
I'm sorry, son.
Can I...
Can I hug you?
EP.10: Yes means yes
How was it?
I apologized to my dad.
I told him how I felt.
How I was hurt when he
didn't care about me at all.
And how I was jealous of Auntie
Fay and Fa who received his love.
I also promised him that I'd be a good son.
He even cried too.
This is the first time
I saw his emotional side.
And he told me that he loves me.
But I couldn't say that I love him.
I was tongue-tied.
It's okay.
Like I said, you can take it slow.
Because from now on, you and
Uncle Mait can spend more time together.
I'm more scared that you
won't have time for me.
You know fear too?
Fiat.
How was the talk with Mait?
Am I disturbing you?
I wanna talk to you and Fa, Auntie Fay.
Nong Fa, P' Fiat has
something to say to you.
But I have nothing to say to him.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry that I made your mommy cry
and hurt Daddy's feelings.
And I'm sorry...
...that I've never been
a good brother to you.
Will you give this brother a chance?
Now what do you do? Hmm?
But P' Fiat hurt Mommy.
P' Fiat already said sorry to Mommy.
And Mommy did P' Fiat wrong too.
You won't forgive Mommy for this?
No, I'm not angry with Mommy.
Then what do you need to do?
You won't bully Mommy anymore, right?
I promise.
Then let's make up, P' Fiat.
My sister's super adorable, isn't she?
We even made a pinky promise.
Had I known it, I would've
treated her better in the first place.
The important thing is that you're happy.
I'm over the moon right now.
I got to talk to my dad,
Auntie Fay, and my sister.
And got to see my mom too.
I'm relieved.
And what about me?
You're sulking? Well?
How could I not?
You always dismissed me.
Come on, I thought it wasn't
something to worry about.
But it was something big
in your boyfriend's eyes.
Leo.
Let me apologize then.
How can I make it up to you?
Are you seducing me?
Did I succeed?
What are you rushing for?
To punish you.
Hold on a sec.
Hey, I'm gonna fall!
Falling is the last thing
you need to worry about.
Hey, Leo!
I can't guarantee
that I'll be gentle.
Who wants you to be gentle?
You're such a tease today.
'Cause I'm gonna get it today.
Today or tomorrow,
I won't let you leave the bed.
Bring it on.
I can't do it anymore.
I thought you wanted to seduce me.
During these past few days, we only
stayed on bed, used the bathroom , and ate.
This is too much even for me.
But you told me.
To bring it on.
It's true I said that,
but this is too much.
You don't like it?
Are you hurt anywhere?
No.
It's not bad to do this once in a wihle.
So can you go to class tomorrow?
Nam said the professors had asked for you.
I've got to go even if I can't.
I've been missing
classes for two weeks.
I won't graduate if I keep this up.
You don't have to practice tomorrow.
Even if I want to,
I won't be able to do it.
Don't worry, I'm confident
that we'll win the next game.
You can browse MMY
Gift Shop's catalogue at...
Hi, I'd like to buy some dolls.
Which ones would you like?
Hello, I want to buy the ones
in the pictures I sent you.
Yes, all of them.
Don't miss a single one of them.
Oh, and send them to
the address I gave you.
Yes, okay.
P' Pob, are you
writing your thesis?
No, why?
Then I'll take you out for lunch.
My mom misses you.
Do I need to prepare myself?
Don't, just be yourself is enough.
Mom likes it, so do I.
Hmm?
Are you shy?
Why are you quiet?
That's nice, I thought I was
the only one who felt shy.
If you wanna do something for me,
just call yourself Pob...
...and I'll fall at your feet.
See you soon.
Okay, hurry up and come pick me up.
I lost.
I've lost since I first
met him until now.
I've lost so much that I almost
become a sucker for Pobphan.
Pob, bring me another plate.
- This one?
- Yes, put it here.
Looking for Leon?
No.
Yes.
He's gone shopping for me
and will be back soon.
Hand me the ladle.
Take the spoon.
Since you're here, help
me taste my cooking.
I haven't cooked in ages.
Don't know if I've become rusty at this.
Guess my skills have regressed.
- Here, can you hold it?
- Okay, Auntie.
Delicious.
And next time, don't call
me Auntie. Call me Mom.
Leon's feelings are so obvious.
But I'm not worthy to be with Leon.
How do you measure your worth?
In the end, it's up to the couple
whether they're happy or sad.
Us parents can only be bystanders.
If my father were alive, he would
have gotten along well with you.
Wow.
Then your father must've
been a really great man.
Right!
There's an annual banquet coming up soon.
Has Leon invited you?
You must come!
You don't need to
worry about your outfit.
My two sons aren't
interested in fashion at all.
They only wear dull suits,
so Fiat's my only hope.
If you join in too,
it's going to be so much fun.
Oh, I should tell Dad you're
going to attend this year.
Ah!
I should take this opportunity
to introduce my sons' boyfriends.
Wait for me here.
Is Mom serious about the banquet?
What are you worried about, P' Pob?
It's just a party.
But if you don't wanna go,
I'll tell Mom for you.
She's just excited to dress you up.
But let me tell you, getting
dressed up by her isn't fun at all.
Then can I not go?
Umm...
If you beg me, I might
help you talk to Mom.
But if you don't wanna do it, then...
Leon.
Can I not go?
Please?
Damn.
Your 'Please?' almost
gave me a heart attack.
Serves you right.
What, Leon?
Huh? Hey! What?
Leon, what are you doing?
What are these?
I know you've been
feeling lonely without Pobjer.
I love it when you call me often.
But I don't like your gloomy voice.
Does this make you feel better?
When you disappeared in the evening...
Oh.
I went to pick up the dolls
and placed them in your room.
And asked Mom to buy me time.
Shouldn't have given you my keycard.
You don't like them?
They're going to be covered with dust.
And there're too many.
I'm sorry.
It doesn't mean I don't like them.
Thank you for doing this for me.
If you're unhappy,
Pobjer will be unhappy.
You've got to smile a lot,
so that Pobjer and I will be happy.
What does it have to do with you?
Of course it does.
Because my head's full of you.
Thank you so much.
But just this one's enough.
This doll can represent
both Pobjer and you.
You stole a kiss from me?
This is what you call stealing a kiss.
You're cheating.
You don't like it?
Says who?
Are you seeing what I'm seeing, Tho?
What's gotten into Leo?
The backboard almost breaks
because he wouldn't stop shooting.
I bet he's on dope.
What did you do to him?
- Did it.
- Did it?
Did the deed?
What are you on about?
He said he did it.
What? Making a pledge?
Don't tell me...
We did it.
For three days and three nights.
I'm gonna go see Leo.
- Horny bastards.
- So annoying.
Hey, do you think there's
gonna be a fourth day?
Bet your ass there'll be.
I bet Fiat made a grand entrance
when he came home this time.
Why?
Because he came back with a bang.
I'mma kick you.
But trust me.
- What?
- They'll do it again today.
- Believe me.
- The fourth round?
What did you say to them?
Nothing.
Believe me, it's really nothing.
By the way, why were you
so energetic today? Hmm?
All the girls were
screaming their lungs out.
You know the reason.
Because of me?
Then...
If you behave...
...I'll let you do it again.
What if I...
...act up?
I'll still let you do it, but less.
I think Leo's team will
see us in the final this year.
Need something?
I want to apologize.
I was too impulsive that day.
I'm sorry I slapped you.
So you wanna keep it
casual with me this time?
Can't I?
Maybe yes or maybe no.
Don't tell me it's because
of that dull-face senior?
Wait, Leon!
Still angry with me?
I'm not angry.
I met P' Pob because of you.
Oh, and another thing.
Next time, don't look
for me for a hook-up.
Because I'm serious about P' Pob.
Are you angry?
I swear there's nothing
between me and Nina.
Ever since I met you,
I've stopped fooling around.
I'm not angry.
Then why did you run away?
Please believe that
there's nothing going on.
I even stopped partying,
fooling around, and everything.
I said I'm not angry.
Then why...
I'm jealous.
P' Pob, wait for me!
Leon.
Leon, wake up.
It's getting late.
What are you playing at?
I'm not playing.
You said you were
doing an assignment.
So I waited until you finish
so that we could chat.
It's late, you're not going home?
No.
I'll stay here until we're
clear about your jealousy.
It's just jealousy.
No big deal.
But it's a big deal for me.
This is the first time you're jealous.
What? I can't get jealous?
Of course you can.
You can do everything.
Then...
I'm jealous.
I think I'd better go.
If I stay any longer,
you'll be in danger.
You said your head was full of me.
What do you mean by this?
Don't tell me
I haven't said I love you?
Well...
I admit that I liked you
since the first time I saw you.
I don't know when I fell in love with you.
Maybe when you were kind to me.
Or when you were with Pobjer.
I really don't know.
But the next thing I know...
..all I think about is you.
If this is love, then I love you.
Please don't be so cute.
Now I don't wanna leave.
Then stay.
Can I?
Don't ask again.
Thank you for waiting.
P' Pob, look at me.
I'm embarrassed.
Why are you embarrassed?
I belong to you.
Look at me.
It's obvious that you're very experienced.
But from now on, I'll use
what I've learned with you only.
What's on your mind?
Hmm?
You're frowning.
Don't tease me now.
My brother's been quiet lately,
so I'm teasing you instead of him.
Stop talking about him
or he'll show up.
I'm thinking about the tournament.
If we keep winning the games...
- ...then we'll face...
- King.
Yeah.
I don't know what tricks
he has up his sleeves.
But I won't fall for it this time.
But he's terrifying.
I know.
But I'm going to beat him this time.
Okay.
What's up?
My brother wants to talk to you.
Leon, I've put you on speakerphone.
Hello, what do you want?
Nothing much, P' Fiat.
I'm just calling to say that my
boyfriend's way cuter than you.
The hell are you playing at?
Nothing.
I love, respect, and worship P' Leo.
But I must say that my boyfriend
is way better than P' Leo's.
So you're just calling to piss me off?
Can't face the truth?
P' Pob's prettier, cuter, and nicer.
You can't compare to him.
Go fuck yourself, you little shit!
Take it away.
The hell he's playing at?
Leo, have I told you
that I hate your brother?
Why did he call me?
You said it often
that I'm used to it.
But I still think that
you're cuter than P' Pob.
I dare you to think I'm not cute.
What?
P' Pob, you weren't sleeping?
You were loud.
- And talking nonsense.
- I was showing off my boyfriend.
Whose boyfriend are you? So cute!
But you didn't have to tell anyone.
I only told my brother.
Actually, I wanna tell my family
how serious I am with you.
I'm sleepy.
Then let's sleep.
I'm sleepy too.
Didn't you sleep a lot already?
It's because I suddenly feel sleepy
when I hug your warm body.
Come on, P' Pob.
Don't chase me away.
Please let me stay the night.
Please.
Pretty please.
Pleaseeee.
I know you planned this.
Hello, P' Leo.
Need something?
I can't greet you if I don't
have business with you?
I've heard your parents
are staying in Thailand right now.
My family wants to visit them.
You can tell your father
to contact my father.
Can't you tell your father for me, P' Leo?
I can't, I've moved out.
Oh, my family's invited
to this year's banquet.
It's expected, since your
father and mine are close.
Oh, my father really wants to meet you.
And why is that?
I told him that you're good
at studying and sports.
It's been a while since he's seen
you, so he wants to meet you.
He can see me at the banquet.
Please excuse me, I'm
meeting up with my friends.
Okay.
[Games Schedule]
- Aek.
- Hey, Fiat.
Why are you at Pol. Sci. buliding?
Huh, can't I come?
My boyfriend studies in this building.
That's not what I meant.
But every time class ends,
Leo always runs off to you.
So I rarely see you come here.
But my twin often see
Leo at your building.
So have you seen Leo?
I called him, but he didn't pick up.
Oh, some juniors called him over
to discuss Bye Nior party.
The girls still can't
decide this year's theme.
Last I've heard, they wanna see
Leo dress up as Count Dracula.
Dream on, I won't let them see.
Possessive, aren't you?
If you're looking for Leo,
the girls dragged him there.
Okay, thanks.
♪ There’s only you in my heart ♪
♪ I assure you there’s no one else ♪
♪ Just have faith in me ♪
♪ Baby, please don’t say no to me ♪
♪ Don’t say it again ♪
♪ If sometimes I’m too scared to say ♪
♪ And it keeps you in the dark ♪
♪ I just want to ask you one thing ♪
♪ Please believe that
our hearts are close ♪
- Hello.
- Bro, help!
Science students
are gonna beat me!
Huh? What did you say?
Are you deaf?
They're gonna beat me!
It's you, Nam.
You pissed them off!
You used cheesy pick-up
lines with their women.
Aek, come help us ASAP.
We're running around like dogs now.
Where are you guys?
Fine, I'll be right there.