What did you say?
I've looked into the incident
this little shit told me about.
King and Punn team up
to screw with your heads.
You were drugged
the day Leo met you at the bar.
Damn, that's why you kept barfing
when you stayed at my place.
Now that you know it,
what are you gonna do?
If he doesn't wanna see
me anymore, I'll back down.
But if he still does,
I'm gonna get my man back.
That's what I'm talking about!
We're here for this reason.
Tonight, we'll be your bodyguards.
EP.12: When our hearts are close
Fiat.
Who do you think he'll choose?
Fiat, wait.
P' Leo, where are you going?
Your role ends here.
And I think we need to talk.
Move.
We won't stand in your way.
We just wanna say...
Don't let him go this time.
Your favorite son
sure draws attention.
As expected of Fiat.
That's the boy I raised
with my own hands.
You seem proud of yourself.
Of course.
Seeing the star of
the party chase after him...
...now we know who's the real winner.
Then why don't we hold an event
to announce their relationship?
You know me so well.
You're the best.
How could I not know?
Thutanukul men are all alike.
We want to indulge the people we love.
Thank you.
Fiat.
Why are you crying?
Do you know?
When I challenged that woman,
I wasn't confident at all...
...that you'd choose me or follow me.
I kept thinking that
you wouldn't choose me.
What would I do if that happened?
You know that you're the
most important person in my life.
I was unsure.
Ever since you said you couldn't
bare to look at me, I've been at a loss.
Fiat.
I don't even know if I should be here.
You said you didn't wanna see my face.
So we should go back to being friends.
But Leo, I couldn't stand it.
Couldn't stand to see you
leave with someone else.
I love you, I really do.
I promise you'll be
the only one for me.
There'll be no one else.
Don't leave me.
I really can't stand the thought
of being just friends with you.
I'm sorry.
I can't stand to be
just friends with you too.
I told my brother.
That I'm willing to be your friend or
anything, as long as I can be by your side.
But it's not what I want at all.
I don't want to see you smile at anyone.
Don't want to see you kiss anyone.
Don't want you to love anyone but me.
♪ Every time we meet each other’s gaze ♪
I'm the one who can't stand
to be just friends with you.
♪ My heart never fails to skip a beat ♪
But didn't you say you
couldn't bear to look at my face?
Because I was afraid I'd hurt you.
You've never hurt me.
You don't know how
possessive I am of you.
You don't know that
when you're with someone else...
...I want to pull you away.
I want to lock you up,
preventing you from seeing anyone.
You don't know there's a demon in my
heart that could harm you at any time.
I don't want to hurt you
like your mom did.
I can barely hold myself back anymore.
I've kept thinking...
...that I want you to be only mine.
You can do it.
You can lock me up.
Tie me up.
You can do that.
Because my heart
has long been yours.
♪ Ever since I met
and fell in love with you ♪
♪ We’ve been through a lot
of thick and thin together ♪
♪ It makes me realize ♪
♪ That nobody deserves you more than me ♪
We love each other, right?
Yes.
We love each other.
♪ There’s only you in my heart ♪
♪ I assure you there’s no one else ♪
♪ Just have faith in me ♪
♪ Baby, please don’t say no to me ♪
So close.
♪ Don’t say it again ♪
♪ If sometimes I’m too scared to say ♪
Yeah.
♪ And it keeps you in the dark ♪
Our hearts are close now.
♪ I just want to ask you one thing ♪
♪ Please believe that
our hearts are close ♪
Let go of me.
You think you can do anything
just because you're P' Leo's friends?
What did we do?
We didn't anything.
More like, what did you do?
What do you mean, P' An?
I didn't do anything.
Aek, what do you think?
Do you know a guy named King?
No.
Really?
But you met him at your aunt's
new brand launch three months ago.
You were even pictured together.
And I've heard you've gotten
close and often met with him.
Yeah, surprisingly often.
And what's that got
to do with you guys?
We wouldn't have cared
if you hadn't messed with our friends.
That's why I'm asking,
what did I do?
Finally! I got it.
I think you aren't just on friendly terms,
but physically intimate.
With the hugging, kissing,
groping, and all that.
And in a public place of all places.
Seriously, weren't you
afraid of being seen?
If you still don't know what you did...
...then we also don't know
what's gonna happen after this.
I'll have it back.
You're messing with the wrong man.
Wanna harm my friend?
If the whole campus knew about
Fiat's love confession last time...
...this time, I'll let every
university know who Nong Punn is.
What's the matter?
Aren't you gonna take me to Mom?
Why are you almost naked?
You're crazy, I'm fully clothed.
Does it have to be this revealing?
Why? You don't like it?
Mom bought it for me.
It's so revealing that
I can even put my hand inside.
There're people here!
So?
Fine, that's enough! I got it!
You said I could be possessive.
So, can I punish you?
Yes.
Then let's go see Mom
after I burn this outfit.
What a jealous man.
Yeah, I'm jealous.
Prepare to endure my jealousy.
My brother's the best.
I miss P' Pob.
Looks like someone's
been reading my mind.
Yes, P' Pob.
Yes? Where are you?
Yes, okay. I'll be down now.
P' Pob, how did you get here?
You should have...
Are you busy, Leon?
Do you have a moment?
Are you crying?
I have something to tell you.
Do you remember what I told you?
That my dream is to help
underprivileged children?
Yes, you looked so happy
when you told me about it.
Before I met Pobjer.
I applied for field work
at an underdeveloped area.
But I didn't keep track of the result.
I got an email.
I got the job.
This field job is located
in Thailand, right?
No, not in Thailand.
When are you leaving?
Next week.
Why so sudden?
They urgently need people.
Citizens are emigrating due to
escalating economic problems.
The children are
starving and homeless.
And...
They want someone
who's ready to work.
Well...
I submitted my thesis
and talked to the professor.
I'm considered a graduate now.
And I won't stay for
the graduation ceremony.
You're only telling me now
after you've dealt with everything?
I'm sorry.
So what do you want me to do?
Congratulate you for getting a job?
Congratulate you
for fulfilling your dream?
And congratulate myself
for getting dumped?
♪ The things I’ve never said ♪
♪ It doesn’t mean I don’t feel them ♪
Yes.
I want you to be happy for me.
But I don't want to leave you.
Then let me come with you.
- No.
- Why?
If I do that, you're
going to hate me one day.
♪ I want you to know everything
I keep inside my heart ♪
♪ And if you put yourself in my shoes ♪
♪ You will understand ♪
You said you love me the way I am.
I also love you who has a dream.
Your dream is to settle down.
But my dream is to help people in need.
If I shatter your dream...
...you're going to hate me some day.
I can't bear to let it happen.
♪ Try being me who,
whenever seeing your tears ♪
So you choose to break up with me?
♪ Have to hold back my own
until you look away ♪
♪ And then break down ♪
♪ You will see that the one beside you… ♪
If that's the case,
are you going to stop me?
♪ …is willing to be yours
and won’t go away ♪
♪ I will be right here ♪
♪ Never disappear ♪
You're so unfair.
You know that I'll
never crush your dream.
Yes.
And I'll never crush yours.
Do you know?
You're the cutest person in the world.
And the trickiest one too.
You just tell me you love me.
On the day you're
breaking up with me.
You're the trickiest man ever.
I'm sorry, I really am.
I'm sorry, Leon.
I'm sorry.
Don't take it off.
You love it when I wear this outfit?
Yeah, so don't take it off.
Can I at least take off the suit?
Beautiful.
No, I'm handsome.
No.
Everything about you is beautiful.
And you're the most handsome man ever.
I heard from Mom.
What did she tell you?
She said she saw you and
P' Pob hugging and crying.
So she guessed something happened.
Do you have anything
to tell your brother?
You know that I need you, P' Leo.
And I'll always do anything for you.
You once said you cared about P' Fiat
so much that you'd do anything for him.
I used to wonder why
my brother was so stupid.
If you love someone, then
you should make them yours.
But now.
I realized.
Because we love them so much.
Care about them so much.
That we can't be selfish
and force them to stay.
P' Pob doesn't wanna crush my dream.
And I don't wanna shatter his.
I like...
I love P' Pob the way he is.
I don't wanna turn him
into someone I want him to be.
Do you know how long I've loved Fiat?
Your whole life.
And how long had I waited for him?
Yes, I can wait.
Even if it takes my whole life.
What about you?
It may not be today or tomorrow.
But if you still love him,
the right time for you will come.
It's up to you whether
you can wait for him or not.
But I don't know when he'll be back.
Then make the most of
the time you have left.
Keep him in your memory.
Engrave it here.
I understand that you can't
take it if you can't be by his side.
But you won't be able to take it even more
if you become the one who hurts him.
Even if it's the last time...
...make him happy.
The men in our family are so silly.
We just put their happiness...
...before our own.
Thank you, P' Leo.
I'm so curious about the locker
room's atmosphere right now.
I bet it's hyped up.
Since King knows that
we've dealt with Nong Punn.
How's it, bro?
It's all my friend's doing.
So let's consider all is forgiven.
Hold on, I was the one
who did everything.
You guys only edited and posted the clip.
And with such important matter,
you went to An instead of me.
By the time I figured out who
Nong Punn was scheming with...
...Leo and Fiat almost broke up.
I'm heartbroken, our good
deeds aren't appreciated.
Right, Nam?
Yeah, I really put my mind to it,
but your twin chews me out.
He doesn't appreciate me at all.
Should I jump off
a building to kill myself?
Good idea, one less waste of space.
It's okay, man.
What do you think?
I'm sure we're gonna
enjoy this match.
You look a little upset today.
What are you doing here?
To say hello to our rival.
I think you look familiar.
He looks like the guy in
the clip with your junior.
Oh, do you know a girl named Punn?
The one with the scandalous clip.
Yeah.
So what?
It's none of your business
what I did with her.
You're right.
But did I tell you?
My friend got a clip where you
tampered with the water bottle.
I think we should tell the referees.
Let's wait after we win
the championship.
Because we're going to
play fair and square today.
Yeah, fair and square. Right?
We should go get ready.
Let's go.
Motherfuckers!
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
I'm ready to crush them.
I'm really fine.
We're going to win.
And if we win...
...I've got a reward for you.
Then...
I must win.
I'm going to win today.
Dream on.
Time's almost up!
Ah, I'm going crazy!
The tension's killing me!
Damn, we're gonna win
if he can make this shot.
They can't square our score.
You must make the shot, Leo.
The best way to get revenge on you...
...isn't using dirty tricks like you do.
It's winning the game fair and square.
You'll never defeat us.
Hey, look!
They're kissing!
Now everyone knows that
I'm yours and you're mine.
Like my reward?
Absolutely.
I love you.
I love you too.
Where are you checking in, P' Pob?
Up ahead.
Send me here is enough.
Take good care of yourself
when you're there.
Don't work until
you lose track of time.
Okay.
When you put your mind to something,
you tend to forget about yourself.
You can't do that anymore.
Because I can't take care of you anymore.
P' Pob.
Can we not break up?
We can't.
I can't hold you back.
I don't know when I'll be back.
I can't be selfish.
I stand by my word.
You really are a tricky person.
When I express my worries,
you only mumble in response.
But when it's about our breakup,
you give a clear-cut answer.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I understand.
Am I your Mr. Right?
Yes.
You're my Mr. Right.
But it's not the right
time for us, right?
It's just that our time doesn't match.
I love you.
I love you too.
Take care.
Pob...
No.
I have to go now.
What's this?
Oh, Kitty Boy.
Pob, my name is Pob.
I'm pursuing you.
And I'm...
...gonna be your boyfriend.
This is what you call
stealing a kiss.
Next time, just tell him we're dating.
Sometimes, love plays tricks on us.
The one we love stands before us,
yet they are too far to reach.
Sometimes, we need to let go
because it's not the right time.
Sometimes, we are forced to choose...
But when the right time
and right one come.
Will you be my boyfriend?
Okay.
I'll be your boyfriend.
Love will tell us that we don't
need to run away anymore.
I'm proud of you today.
If it feels right, don't deny
the love in your heart.
Who are you looking for?
The guys who roll the ball.
And the guys who carry
the lights and stall the janitor.
Oh, and the guy who
films the clip too.
They're not here.
There's only me today.
Says who? There's me too.
Yes, there are you and me.
There's us.
Let me say it first.
I wanna apologize for all those times.
I made mistakes.
I screwed up.
I hurt you.
I did spiteful things which hurt everyone.
Now that when we're dating,
I still screwed up.
I don't know if there'll be a day when
I become a perfect boyfriend for you.
But I'll be me...
...who loves you with all my heart.
My turn.
In my whole life.
There's a boy who's
always been by my side.
I promised to take care of him.
To protect him.
To stay by his side.
But I...
...made him cry over and over again.
I'm sorry.
For being a coward.
I don't know what I
should do in a relationship.
I'll probably never be
a perfect boyfriend.
But there's one thing
I'm better than anyone.
It's loving you with all my heart.
Whether in the past,
the present, or the future.
I'll be by your side forever.
I'll also be by your side forever.
Yeah.
I won't let you reject me again.
And I won't reject your love.
[Be My Boyfriend]
I was kidding when I said
I wanted a piggyback.
It's okay, I can carry you.
This is bad, you're
spoiling me too much.
I'll keep spoiling you until
you can't live without me.
Fiat already can't live without Leo.
What did you say?
What? Is it wrong
for me to sweet-talk?
No.
But if you're too sweet,
my heart won't be able to take it.
Then you'd better get used to it.
I told you, I'll never ever let you go.
♪ We will turn this love, our love… ♪
♪ …into precious memories ♪
Then...
♪ So that when we look back ♪
I won't let you sleep tonight.
Who sleeps on a day like this?
♪ We’ll think of each other ♪
♪ No matter when,
we’ll think of each other ♪
[The End]