Silence Wang - "An Alluring Smile"
♫ I always casually tell you my wishes ♫
♫ And give you looks that a thousand words wouldn’t be able to describe ♫
♫ In this world, there will always be people who are busy looking for treasure ♫
♫ But they mistake the blazing sun for it ♫
♫ And miss out on the manifestations of life ♫
♫ On the long bridge of this ancient city ♫
♫ There is a sea of people and cars going on their way ♫
♫ Your smile is like a ray of light ♫
♫ That suddenly lights me up ♫
♫ (Your smile is like a ray of light. That suddenly lights me up) ♫
♫ The wind blows gently; summer is not yet over ♫
♫ Bikes ring on the greenway ♫
♫ So this is what love looks like ♫
♫ Just admit that you were allured by my smile and couldn’t forget me after you first saw me ♫
♫ Saying that love is deep like the sea… you flatter me ♫
♫ The most romantic thing is to just watch the sunset with you shoulder to shoulder ♫
♫ That’s the direction my heart goes in ♫
♫ (Watching the sunset with you shoulder to shoulder. That’s the direction my heart goes in) ♫
♫ I want to travel to all four corners (of the earth) with you to enjoy the views in all kinds of weather ♫
♫ I want to write the remaining chapters of life with you ♫
♫ Sharing the laughs and tears with you freely no matter the circumstances ♫
♫ Our story won’t end ♫
[Love O2O]
[Episode 25]
Hello? Weiwei, what's wrong?
Nothing. Then I'll hang up first.
Hello?
Let's take off work early today.
We will move your stuff to my apartment and move my stuff to my parents' place later.
I can do it on my own.
Are you sure?
Absolutely.
They are indeed living together.
Luwei Weiwei, we meet again.
Zhenshui Wuxiang?
That's my gaming username. My real name is Zhen Shaoxiang.
You can call me "Shaoxiang."
Where are you going? Let me give you a lift.
No need. I can go on my own.
Don't be shy. Although we had some misunderstandings when we were in the game,
we are still considered acquaintances. Right?
It has nothing to do with the game. I don't wish to give you any hassle.
Thank you.
Fine. I won't force you then.
By the way, what's your real name?
If we meet again, I can't still call you Luwei Weiwei. Right?
That's so awkward.
I think we probably won't meet again.
I think we will.
Actually, Zhao Erxi told me what your real name is.
If not, how would I know that you were living here?
Did she tell you that my family name is Lu?
So, your family name is Lu.
Of course.
What are you laughing at?
Let me give you a lift. It will take a long time for you to walk.
No need. I'm going to my boyfriend's place.
I fear it's not convenient for you to give me a lift there.
Your boyfriend? Xiao Nai?
A while ago, he came to my company to seek funding,
but it's an unseasoned team made up of students after all.
If I remember correctly,
your company is Zhen Yi Technology. Right?
Mr. Zhen,
if we are discussing from the perspective of a company, Zhi Yi Technology and Zhen Yi Technology
are both competing for the development rights of "A New Chinese Ghost Story."
This means both companies are on equal footing.
In terms of individual standpoint,
my boyfriend is the main programmer and decision maker at Zhi Yi Technology.
I wonder what Mr. Zhen's position in Zhen Yi Technology is.
On behalf of my boyfriend,
I thank you for not investing in them back then.
She has the same temperament as when she's in the game. How Interesting!
I cleared half of my wardrobe for you.
Hang up your stuff as you please.
I will wait for you to pack first before I unpack.
Are you really letting me have your apartment?
I don't have any confidence in my self-control.
Fortunately, I can still go to my parents' place.
If not, I would have to sleep on the floor in the office.
Help me with the clean-up.
I'm going to get a mop.
Okay, thanks. I know.
The maintenance guy will be here tomorrow.
Fortunately, this chest is fine.
Or else, Professor Xiao would be hugging this and crying for three days.
I think with the way you talk about your father,
Professor Xiao will cry for three days.
What will you do with this then?
Pack it and keep it at my place.
These are manuscripts. Find a bag to keep them in.
Don't worry. Your paintings of Wu Guanzhong are fine.
Xu Beihong's are fine, too.
I have packed them.
I will keep them at my apartment off campus for the time being.
Okay.
Where should we place these?
There aren't any suitable places.
Leave them in the wardrobe first.
You said that you weren't staying at your parents' place, you
would have to sleep on the floor in the office.
So, where are you staying tonight?
I don't mind sleeping on the floor in the office,
but these paintings have been collected by my parents for many years.
Nothing must happen to them.
If you are here alone, I will worry.
And so?
I will stay here and keep watch over them.
It seems as if I just saw us several decades into the future.
♫ Rain drips on my jacket ♫
It's not bad.
♫ Longing (for you) soaks the corners of my clothes ♫
♫ The signal you gave me, a smile ♫
♫ Came at just the right time ♫
♫ As I pass by you, the tips of your hair ♫
♫ Are like grass blown by the spring wind ♫
♫ Romance is fermenting ♫
♫ For you, I’m willing to ♫
♫ Chase away all the troubles ♫
♫ I want to take you to the ends of the earth ♫
♫ I want to listen to your heartbeat ♫
Reporting. Coffee has been eating and pooping normally.
♫ I want to give you a hug and make the whole world know♫
Just a little lethargic and staring out of the window all the time.
She probably misses you.
Hehehe, I have succeeded in winning over Coffee's heart.
We are bosom friends now.
Coffee's silent line is "If you don't show respect to Sister Erxi,
then you are not showing me respect."
"I will dismiss you with my gas."
Are you still angry with me?
It was my fault before.
I will wait for you at the same old place in the game.
I will let you kill me a hundred times. Won't this do?
Are you still angry with me?
It was my fault before.
I will wait for you at the same old place in the game.
I will let you kill me a hundred times. Won't this do?
Coffee, Coffee.
Your poop scooper is really ditching us.
Women are such a hassle.
That's right.
I haven't settled the score with someone. I almost forgot.
Yiran, about the video in my cellphone,
did you delete it?
I didn't. What's wrong?
This is strange. Why did the video in my cellphone suddenly go missing?
By the way, what was Xiao Nai's reaction after he saw it?
- I don't know either.
- You don't?
That's right. He asked me where the video was shot
and when it was shot. So I told him everything.
He wanted me to delete the video in my cellphone.
That's it?
Yes, that's it.
What's Xiao Nai's reaction then?
Did he see Bei Weiwei's true colors?
This is not right. All the copies of the video are gone from our cellphones.
It's fine since he saw it. He should understand.
Perhaps, they are having a row about breaking up.
Why did Cao Guang call me?
Hello, Cao Guang. What's up?
You and Meng Yiran meet me at the south gate of the school tomorrow at 10:00 a.m. I have to talk to you about something.
What's with your attitude? You think you can order us to go. Who do you think you are?
You secretly filmed me and distributed the video
to slander a student. Who do you think you are?
If I don't see you tomorrow, you will live with the consequence yourself.
You!
Hello? Hello?
Yiran, what should we do?
I heard Cao Guang's family is quite powerful.
Is he going to settle a score with us?
It was wrong of you to secretly film him
but your intention wasn't bad.
If he's a reasonable person,
he probably wouldn't give you a hard time.
How did Cao Guang know that I shot the video?
Did Xiao Nai tell him?
That's right. Why didn't I think of this?
Xiao Nai must have been looking for confirmation from Cao Guang.
Na Na, he believed me.
There is this mounting evidence. How could he not believe it?
I wonder what love potion Bei Weiwei made him take.
It took me so long to think of this. I'm so stupid.
Is Cao Guang looking for us because he found it embarrassing?
He was dumped by her and his love rival even went to see him.
He must have been totally humiliated.
Probably so.
Everything's fine. When he's here,
just apologize and everything should be fine.
Cao Guang, you asked us here,
but you are late yourself.
We waited a long time for you under the harsh sun.
Aren't you too cruel?
You probably know that I'm here to settle the score with you.
Stop talking to me in this manner.
This is how I usually talk.
It was my fault for secretly filming you
but I didn't do it on purpose.
I just happened to film it.
Fine, I will apologize to you. Okay?
As a person of respect and stature, please forgive me.
Cao Guang, Na Na's action was wrong
but her intention was good.
She didn't want you and Xiao Nai to be deceived.
Meng Yiran, you like Xiao Nai, right?
You are trying to snatch Xiao Nai from Bei Weiwei.
It has nothing to do with whether I like him or not.
I merely didn't want you and schoolmates to be deceived.
Stop trying to give these dignified justifications.
You clearly know why you did it.
Also, no matter how hard you work,
Xiao Nai won't think highly of stupid people like you.
How could you talk to girls this way?
You should be grateful that you are girls.
If not, do you think I would let you off that easily?
Na Na, this matter ends here.
I won't pursue it any further.
I'm warning you. Watch your mouths.
If I hear any more negative rumors about Bei Weiwei,
whether the source is from you or not, I will hold you responsible.
In the end, it's still about Bei Weiwei.
I didn't expect a talented scholar like you
would turn out to be a sex-crazed silly fool.
Just because of a two-timing girl, you went all out to protect her!
Didn't you hear what I just said?
You were the one who said two-timing.
I didn't say that.
I got the wrong person!
Got the wrong person?
Wasn't it Bei Weiwei?
Who was it then?
No matter who it was, it doesn't concern you!
Remember this. Watch what you say.
Otherwise, don't fault me for not being nice to you.
You!
Let me wish you good luck.
Also, in the future, you can go after guys,
but by using this kind of despicable tactic repeatedly, aren't you becoming too unseemly?
Don't you need to go to work in the afternoon, either?
The progress for the game is going well. So, there's no need to work overtime.
Are you trying to kick me out?
How could I? I was afraid that by walking around, I would disturb your work.
Bring your laptop
and sit next to me for a while.
I didn't expect to meet again today.
Luwei, do you still remember this place?
When we fought that boss together after we first became a couple,
it seemed to be this place.
We didn't have enough people then and could have been eliminated.
In the end, thanks to your strike, you saved the whole team.
Every time when we entered a dungeon, you were always in front.
You have never needed anyone to take care of you.
I really miss those times when we fought together.
Thinking about it now, only with you, we
were the couple with the best tacit understanding.
If it wasn't in the game,
I couldn't say these words face-to-face.
Weiwei, are you there?
Are you disconnected?
Luwei Weiwei, in the past, I was ignorant.
After going in a circle, I finally understood
what kind of person is most suitable for me.
Every person makes mistakes. I have made many mistakes.
If it was possible, I really would hope that all these things didn't happen
but it's probably not too late now.
Give me another chance to start over.
Answer me, okay?
I'm Yixiao Naihe.
What's going on?
Reminiscing about the past.
I think Zhenshui Wuxiang must be very angry with you.
Did you bump into him yesterday?
That's right. I wonder how he tricked Erxi into giving him the address.
He waited at the entrance for me and even lied that he knew my name.
I know Erxi.
No matter how angry she is, she will never betray me.
So I tricked him into exposing himself.
Why didn't you tell me?
It was too easy to handle and I forgot about it.
The missus indeed has been getting confessions growing up.
Remember to brief me in the future.
For the sake of equality, you must do the same.
It's true that it's easy to forget. Never mind.
Why do I feel that I'm that kind of legendary
femme fatale? I always run into lousy romances.
Fortunately, I got you.
So, Yixiao Naihe is Xiao Nai.
Main programmer and decision maker of Zhi Yi Technology?
So you think you are that great?
In my eyes, you are nothing!
Did you read the documents I gave you last time?
You should know that if we use these documents to sue your friend,
your friend's future will be destroyed.
I fear he may be imprisoned, too.
What do you want?
As long as you work with us
and obtain what we want,
we won't sue you.
You are thinking too highly of me.
All of Xiao Nai's critical codes
have been encrypted with a 128-bit key.
With my ability, I can't break the code.
If there is any other information about him,
we will happily accept it, too.
How can you guarantee that Zhen Yi won't sue?
Other than this, you don't have any other choice.
Okay.
But even if you know,
you have a slim chance of winning.
People make things happen.
What's the situation with Zhi Yi?
That person said there's currently a fatal flaw with the game.
The game consumes a lot of memory during the execution of the game,
but Xiao Nai is working on a tool to optimize it.
As soon as its development is finished, it can be applied to the game
and reduce the usage of memory tremendously.
Can he succeed?
They seem to be quite confident.
They said it will be completed by September 15.
Then, we must not let them succeed.
But our guy is not in a key position.
He may not be able to sabotage it.
It's impossible on the side of Zhi Yi Technology.
Then, what if the demo date at Feng Teng Technologies is moved forward?
That's right. In any case, we have completed our demo.
I will give it a try, President Zhen.
Manager Zhen.
Dad, is the company competing for the development rights for "A New Chinese Ghost Story?"
Go back to work.
Today is the weekend.
Young Master Zhen, why are you in the mood to come into the office today?
Dad, I'm serious.
Is the company competing for the development rights for "A New Chinese Ghost Story?"
How long have you been with the company?
And you only think about this issue now?
I want to ask you. When will you really settle down,
and truly pay attention to the company for me?
Now's the time.
Dad, I want to join this project.
I guarantee we can outdo Zhi Yi Technology
and obtain the development rights for this game.
You? Just don't make troubles for me.
Dad, why are you like this?
I'm a player of the elite level in "A Chinese Ghost Story."
Moreover, who in this company knows the game better than I do?
I must take part in this project.
I will definitely beat Xiao Nai to a pulp!
Are you being serious?
I can't be more serious than this, Dad.
Okay.
My son has finally grown up.
The company spent so much money to hire you
and you only did this?
Manager, do you feel that we should make some improvements?
Have you guys played the "A Chinese Ghost Story" game?
- Yes.
- How long have you been playing?
A little more than a year.
A year or so? How did you play?
Did you just wander around in the game for a while every day and then leave?
As a veteran player of "A Chinese Ghost Player," let me tell you,
your demo doesn't appeal to me at all.
Let's not even mention the many players out there.
The appearance of the characters is mediocre. The character's skills are indistinct.
The scenery is way too crude.
Creativity? I didn't even see it.
Manager, are you saying that...
I have been playing this game for many years.
I have my own thoughts and ideas.
Just revise according to what I say.
Manager, we only have a mere month more before the bid.
If we make the modifications now, I fear we will not make it on time.
I don't want to hear this phrase, "We will not make it on time."
Your overtime will pay five times your regular rate. If there isn't enough manpower,
recruit people now.
All of our players are very young.
Is this a drawing of a ghost?
Young Master is an expert hiding behind the scenes.
Young Master's demeanor now is showing strong resemblance with you, President Zhen.
President Zhen, you have taught him well.
Young Master will accomplish great feats in the future.
What's the status of that task?
There was a great opportunity, and we took advantage of it. No one will be able to tell.
Well done.
But Young Master's plan may not be implemented on time.
He will have plenty of opportunities to demonstrate his potential. Once we get this project,
he will have all the time he wants for development.
But... regarding our plan,
don't tell him. I'm afraid it might affect his feelings.
Yes, I understand.
Okay.
Why isn't Third Brother back yet?
Hey, Third Brother is getting food for me and he's not back yet. I'm starving.
Do you have anything to eat?
- In my drawer, there are things which squirrels love to eat. Help yourself. (Note: referring to snack logo of a squirrel)
- Thank you.
[Home Purchase Contract]
What are you doing?
What is this?
Home Purchase Contract? There are even two.
And paid off in one lump sum.
What are you doing?
What is this?
It's mine. Give it back to me.
Everyone, come and look at this scheming boy!
Hao Mei has something to tell everyone.
What is this?
There are even two sets.
It's two sets.
Scheming boy.
Why didn't you tell me when you went to rob a bank?
That's right, Brother Hao. How much balance do you still have left from your lottery winnings?
Why don't you buy houses for everyone here?
Brother Mei, you're a real estate mogul, yet you've been hiding among us proletarians for all this time.
What for?
Brothers, this is a harmonious society.
We should talk in a civilized manner.
You must not get violent!
K.O., help me!
Come out.
K.O., we are from the same rank.
You shouldn't be an enemy of the people.
What are they doing? Are they bullying Mr. Beauty?
Let's take a look.
Get him out from there. Come here.
Darn Beauty!
Hao Mei, how can you forsake us?
When we were in school, why did a mogul like you borrow money from a poor student like me?
Each time you borrowed so much! Have you paid any of it back?
Do you think I wanted to do that? I was poor then.
Thinking about when I applied for Tsinghua University behind my father's back,
I only got ¥600 per month.
Had I known Beijing had Third Brother and sandstorms, I never would have come here!
Who cares whether you would come or not? Catch him!
- Catch him!
- I will treat you guys to a meal!
Senior Hao Mei really thinks so highly of you. He even put you in the same category as sandstorms.
Give this to Yugong. Also, tell Hao Mei casually that I'll remember this.
[Notification of New Demo Meeting Time]
Buddies, I found a great hotpot place nearby.
Its food is really tasty and the price inexpensive, too.
I spit on it. Eating this kind of inexpensive hotpot
is an insult to our Brother Mei's two homes.
- That's right.
- We should go for the most expensive food.
The most expensive one.
Junior Sister Weiwei,
what would you like to eat?
It's fine as long as it's expensive.
You... not one of you is a decent person.
Let's go for seafood then. Seafood is the most expensive. It's several thousands when you order a regular meal.
It completely suits the stature of our Mogul Brother.
It's seafood then. How about the seafood night stall?
You guys think in such lowly terms.
What is considered high end?
Is a seafood stall good enough? Isn't that right, Brother Mei?
- It's not.
- That's right.
Yes.
Third Brother, you have been to many places.
Choose one and let's go with Brother Mei.
Meet in the conference room in five minutes.
Yang Yang - "Just One Smile Is Very Alluring"
♫ Rain drips on my jacket ♫
♫ Longing (for you) soaks the corners of my clothes ♫
♫ The signal you gave me, a smile ♫
♫ Came at just the right time ♫
♫ As I pass by you, the tips of your hair ♫
♫ Are like grass blown by the spring wind ♫
♫ Romance is fermenting. For you, I’m willing to ♫
♫ Chase away all the troubles ♫
♫ I want to take you to the ends of the earth ♫
♫ I want to listen to your heartbeat ♫
♫ I want to give you a hug ♫
♫ And make the whole world know ♫
♫ Only after meeting you did I realize how important you are to me ♫
♫ No one else can feel your sweetest smile ♫
♫ I don’t need to look for anyone else ♫
♫ Because I’ve already found (you) ♫
♫ Our fate just happens to not let anyone else disturb us ♫
♫ Only we know how beautiful our love is ♫
♫ I want to be around you every minute and every second ♫
♫ You are so important to me ♫
♫ As I pass by you, the tips of your hair ♫
♫ Are like grass blown by the spring wind ♫
♫ Romance is fermenting. For you, I’m willing to ♫
♫ Chase away all the troubles ♫
♫ I want to take you to the ends of the earth ♫
♫ I want to listen to your heartbeat ♫
♫ I want to give you a hug ♫
♫ And make the whole world know ♫
♫ Only after meeting you did I realize how important you are to me ♫
♫ No one else can feel your sweetest smile ♫
♫ I don’t need to look for anyone else ♫
♫ Because I’ve already found (you) ♫
♫ Our fate just happens to not let anyone else disturb us ♫
♫ Only we know how beautiful our love is ♫
♫ I want to be around you every minute and every second ♫
♫ You are so important to me ♫