[Kang In Soo]
[Lee Sang]
[Soo Bin]
[Baek Seo Bin]
[Park Jung Hoo]
[Wish You: Your Melody From My Heart]
Timing and Subtitles by the 🌟Wish Upon a Star Team🌟 @Viki.com
No. This part right now.
♫  Today's weather is nice, as well  ♫
♫  Take light steps with my feelings in it  ♫
♫  At this moment, right now  ♫
♫  A sweet melody is ringing  ♫
♫  It's strange. When I'm with you,
I feel like something good will happen  ♫
♫  I feel renewed every time I look at you. What about you?  ♫
♫  Let's go far away. Just stay two of us, all day  ♫
♫ This feeling that everything will be perfect ♫
Hurry and open your mouth. I'll feed you.
This is a really good restaurant. Is it good?
It's crazy, it's crazy.
Why are you so surprised after you were fed by him?
You're here? I called him because I'm in a good mood.
What? You already started without me?
I heard you got fired. So I was going to take you under my wing again, but you guys are having the time of your lives.
I'll pour it for you.
Because we're all the same age, we can speak informally. Right?
Because you're close, he's making me feel more comfortable.
Anyway, let's celebrate us all getting together.
For Kang In Soo's successful debut.
For Kang In Soo's successful debut!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
- Hey, Sang Yi.
- I'm Min Sung.
- Min Sung.
- What?
My mood is the best today.
Watch out for the car!
Sang Yi is a good musician, too.
- Min Sung.
- What?
- We should have another drink.
- Ah, stop it.
Sang Yi you should have another drink, too.
Hey! This is hard. Grab him.
Hey! Lay him down here.
Why did he drink so much?
Actually, something happened with In Soo today.
You know what?
I've known In Soo for a long time... Anyway,
I've never seen him this drunk before.
But seeing him like this, for some reason, I'm relieved.
And I feel better because it's you, Sang Yi.
I heard about them picking up In Soo. If it was you instead of that female agent...
I think, he would have been really happy. Having his true worth recognized.
Because I pity him, I always nagged him because I felt he was not reaching his potential.
In Soo is pitiful? What do you mean by that?
I don't know the details either. But In Soo's parents
seem to be important people. They dislike that he's a singer.
So I think they're interfering. But because he's always joking around and is a happy guy,
also, because he doesn't show his feeling that much, I just assume what's going on as well.
I'll get going.
♫ When you didn't know me, I was praying ♫
♫  May your eyes always reach me  ♫
♫  As much as I try to get close to you, the farther away you go  ♫
♫  You wouldn't know how I feel  ♫
♫  You know about it, but I wonder why you're like that.
Maybe you're not used to it  ♫
♫  I like everything about you  ♫
♫  I want to be the one who can see you when I want
and can be with you when you need me  ♫
♫  I want to be that precious person to you  ♫
♫  You're perfect as you are   ♫
♫  Open your heart a little more and come closer to me  ♫
♫  I want you to come closer to me  ♫
Why would you want to leave your house and come here?
I was curious. I wanted to come once.
Anyway, you're a weirdo.
What about you?
You are a weirdo as well!
This is different than what I thought.
It's humble, but it has everything I need.
No, because it's cozy.
For some reason, just looking at you, I thought it would be a lot bleaker.
With nothing but a mattress on the bed.
What do you think I am?
Am I homeless?
I wanted to come here once. The space you live in.
Why?
I'm not sure.
Just because.
Let's go out. There's a place I want to show you.
♫ If it all comes crashing down, we'll be just fine ♫
♫ When the day and night collide, we'll stand and fight ♫
The scenery is fantastic.
It's nice, right?
It's where I used to work part-time.
Sometimes I would come up here for a drink.
You don't need drinking and snacks.
I'm flattered.
That you wanted to show me a place like this.
What are you saying?
I can sleep here, right?
♫ When the storm is raging on, we... ♫
Yeah, as long as you're not uncomfortable.
You'll be more uncomfortable. Because of me.
What are you saying?
Why are you getting so close to me?
My mood is the best today.
I felt like I was walking in place,
with no end in sight.
♫ There's something about it, made us believe ♫
♫ that everyone's standing always in the ocean, and we are the only ones... ♫
The fact that it will be officially released,
why can't I believe it?
Actually, I don't know.
I'm still nervous.
♫ Trying to get up the courage ♫
Is it going to end well?
♫ Trying to jump overboard ♫
What's wrong with you? You're self-confident Kang In Soo.
Then, what about self-confident Yoon Sang Yi?
Are you scared?
Naturally! I'm scared!
On a day like this, shouldn't we invite Min Sung, too?
If if it's officially released,
then we'll do it then.
Today's only the two of us.
♫ If it all comes down to us, we'll be all right ♫
The two of us?
Cheers.
Yoon Sang Yi.
Because of you, I was really happy.
Don't say, "was happy," say, "be happy."
Let's be happy Kang In Soo. In the future, too.
♫ What we're afraid of is all that we're made of, and somewhere inside...  ♫
Let's be happy.
♫ Let's find it out for each other ♫
Thanks to you, I was able to move forward little by little.
♫ Let's reach inside deep down ♫
What are you saying? That's so cheesy.
♫ ... pull up all that the other ♫
Thank you, Yoon Sang Yi.
Timing and Subtitles by the 🌟Wish Upon a Star Team🌟 @Viki.com
♫ With heavy breathing ♫
♫ I'm running toward you ♫