PARK JU HYUN
PARK YONG WOO
KANG HOON
HUNTER WITH A SCALPEL
PLACES, COMPANIES, FIGURES, ORGANIZATIONS,
BACKGROUND, SETTING, CASE, ETC. ARE FICTIONAL ONLY
CHILDREN AND ANIMAL ACTORS UNDER THE
SUPERVISION OF GUARDIANS AND EXPERTS
What's this?
Eun-seo, why don't you
sleep? and is it outside?
Father.
Something like this shouldn't happen.
HUNTER WITH A SCALPEL
EMERGENCY MEDICAL CENTER
EPISODE 13
There is a stab wound in the left
abdomen patients and severe bleeding.
How is the condition?
In the ambulance can only maintain
blood pressure by administering volume.
- You can just come in, right? - Yes, can.
- Have you called another doctor? - Yes.
- Where is the patient's guardian?
- Yes, it is me!
What happened?
Yes, female patients experience
beatings and his fingers were cut off.
The male patient was stabbed twice.
We brought him here right
away. Will they be okay?
We have to see it.
I don't know much about the condition of the female patient,
but the condition of the male patient is difficult to ascertain.
What happened? What does it
mean? Chairman Jung is a victim?
Then who is the perpetrator?
Escape while holding hostages small
children who were at the location.
Off again?
Did you just say "again"?
Why use informal language?
That's right, right?
You've failed to catch me twice.
Perpetrators because they acted alone.
Acting alone?
This jerk is really annoying.
What were you doing at that time?
- What do you know about the situation...
- Stop.
You just stay at home!
- Why are you still... - Good grief!
It's only natural.
Unlucky.
Chairman Jung is like that...
was Choi Min-guk's doing.
When Chairman Jung and Senior Jeon
proposes Choi Min-guk's examination...
what did you say then?
If only you had allowed
that time we move together...
he won't be like that.
Unlucky.
Why can't you be contacted?
You received a message
from Chairman Jung or not?
That's enough.
You still have scribbled documents while
investigating the Blue Tong case, right?
Send it all to me.
Photos, memos, everything.
We can't get on the boat?
Se-eun.
This is because of Brother.
We missed the boat because of you.
I told you Dad was late,
but brother said it hurts...
Look at this.
This is also because of
Brother pulling me hard.
Do you know your brother? bring that spray?
It seems like Dad told
me to you carry the stuff.
Right?
OPERATING TIME 47 MINUTES
He dared to stab a detective?
This can't be allowed to continue
any longer and let's catch him.
Please return our team immediately
and we have to catch him.
So, I mean...
What about the evidence? he
is the perpetrator of our case?
Still nothing.
Because until now, Seo Se-hyun still has
the status of the original perpetrator...
what if we catch him...
as an identity forger or
attempted murder, Chairman Hong?
This will be very troublesome...
if the victim of the case The fifth
was accused of kidnapping the suspect.
Can't.
We have to check on Choi Min-guk.
As an accomplice of the perpetrator.
Haven't we said it many times?
Choi Min-guk is weird!
What are you doing?
So, do you think it is a good idea to
put the body of the victim he killed...
in the bathroom of
his own house is it normal?
Yes?
Even the most psychopathic person
burying his victims in the ground!
Jong-su, you...
Don't you take care of them? Do you?
Know they do independent investigations?
Don't know.
Your boss doesn't know?
Isn't this happening because of the children?
Who was suspended for acting without permission?
And you're chasing the same person has
nothing to do with the direction of this case!
If you really want to rebel, at
least take a little responsibility.
But what is this?
Anyway, we investigate
this case separately.
Let go of Choi Min-guk's hand first.
Chairman Hong.
Since Seo Se-hyun has been caught, interrogate
him first when he regains consciousness.
Our team members!
Stabbed by that bastard.
This situation was enough to make
him suspected of being his accomplice.
Who says you can't catch it?
We got a report serial killer case.
Show that we is focusing on that case.
Choi Min-guk is handled by the
department crime also seems better.
Looks good?
Do you know what the
most make me regret now?
When Chairman Hong
talking about the gang...
I forbid them if I
dare dig up that cold case!
Because we are sure treated like this!
Cold case?
What nonsense is this?
Mr. Head of Office, you have to see this.
Please turn it on.
Isn't that Choi Min-guk?
Correct.
It's Choi Min-guk.
But in the case of the Blue Harbor
Barrel Cheongun 1999, he is Go Doo-sam.
Oh my gosh, why? the
problem becomes like this?
What does it mean that
Doctor Seo was kidnapped?
Doesn't that mean there
are other perpetrators?
You don't need to worry.
Doctor Seo is not the culprit either...
he has dropped the good
name of the Forensic Agency.
But, since he has been arrested
police and will start investigating...
we also have to prepare.
Even though we have passed
through a period of crisis.
This is really giving me a headache.
What does it mean?
Nothing has changed, Doctor Cheon.
Therefore, do not interfere
and shut your mouth.
Doctor Seo is still proven to have falsified
evidence Nam Seung-hyup's case to The Tailor.
Isn't he not involved?
With the Nam Seung-hyup case?
What?
I know you're thinking about it because
have been working with him for a long time.
Doctor Seo keeps asking for
retests Nam Seung-hyup case sample.
- But that day you... - What?
Who signed the report Nam
Seung-hyup's autopsy results?
Who changed the evidence
in the Yongcheon case?
These are the cases I have handled together
Doctor Seo for the past three years.
INTRODUCTION OF THE
INCIDENT MAKGEOLLI CYANIDE
I have checked and double check everything.
Everything is clean.
Doctor Cheon.
So far Doctor Seo has never
tried falsifying or hiding results.
He must have a reason
regarding the Yongcheon case.
Therefore, we also have
to step in and help...
Wake up!
He is a murderer.
We must side with those
who deserve to be defended.
What is this nonsense?
Come on, run!
Se-eun!
I have to know where he was taken.
SEO SE-HYUN THE PERPETRATOR OF
MURDER CASE, FAKE AUTOPSY REPORT?!
Why is there no news?
Sit properly.
Do that until you
understand what you did wrong.
Understand?
Look carefully don't
until something is missed.
Yes I understand.
How much longer?
Still a long time.
We only search via facial recognition.
We should check at least 800
thousand men over 50 years old.
This will just be a waste of
time if there is no comparison.
Ensuring his identity is a priority
us. Please do it as soon as possible.
Yes.
Chairman Hong.
Laundry searches and Choi
Min-guk's house is finished.
We got nothing because it has been cleaned.
But we found something
strange on Seo Se-hyun's route.
After putting a book on the
shelf, he immediately left.
Why did he look for the camera first?
The thing he hid also a little strange.
When is the date of this CCTV?
Just before the incident occurred
attempted murder at the laundry.
He hides things here before
going to see Choi Min-guk?
He put all the other evidence
in his house except this one...
and like to be seen?
YOON SE EUN
Se-eun.
Come to Father.
Se-eun!
Se-eun.
Se-eun, come here!
Se-eun, what's wrong with you?
You can't get away from me.
Se-eun, hurry!
Se-eun.
Father will forgive you.
Se-eun!
Miss Seo, are you awake?
The operation is complete.
Is there anything uncomfortable?
Chairman Jung...
Yes?
What about people? brought with me?
Even though it has passed a critical
period, the wound is very deep.
We have to monitor his recovery condition.
That means, Cho Min-guk...
pretending to be a laundry
owner to get around Yoncheon City?
That's right.
But what is more surprising is...
he deliberately limped to deceive other
people so as not to be considered suspects.
He is absolutely amazing.
Damn, what do you mean he's amazing?
He's a psychopathic killer.
Wait a minute.
The address is correct here.
- Here? - Yes.
How about now?
It seems like there's nothing we can get.
Because it's been more than 20 years.
I will try to meet the residents.
Yes, let's try asking.
Wait a moment.
Pack!
Sorry to interrupt, but we have a question.
How about this?
That day...
When I said can't believe you...
Excuse me.
I am better?
Yes.
You already know you are
wanted publicly as a suspect?
Yes.
As there is a lot of direct
evidence found in your home...
we have absolutely nothing
another obstacle to accusing you.
It is just...
There is something bothering me.
We need your explanation regarding
this your relationship with Choi Min-guk.
Has Chairman Jung regained consciousness?
Answer my question.
Please introduce me to him.
I ask again.
What is your relationship
with Choi Min-guk?
YOON SE EUN
So what is this?
We found it today on your route.
YOON SE EUN
Yoon Se-eun.
What is your real name?
The guy said it was around here.
FORGET-ME-NOT FLOWERS
Right there.
I know Jung-mi very well.
Right next to here there is
a drinking shop owned by him.
He struggled to live alone with
his daughter by doing business...
but she met the wrong man.
What's wrong with him?
We are finding out about Go Doo-sam...
who is Lee Jung-mi's husband.
This person.
He's not the one.
What?
Then who is he?
His name is...
Wait a minute, if I'm not
mistaken His surname is Yoon.
Yoon Jo Kyun!
I don't forget the name
the man is a jerk apparently.
Gosh, we didn't know that either.
We know he is Lee Jung-mi's husband.
Yes, please identify.
Yes, man.
Yoon Jo Kyun.
That's because before meeting Go Doo-sam...
they live together with
the status of a secret marriage.
They lived together for quite a long
time their respective biological daughters.
That is how it is.
So?
The man made Jung-mi
life is very miserable...
like a parasite.
That's why Jung-mi recorded it
first. her marriage to Go Doo-sam...
who often helps out at the shop.
To get away from that bastard Yoon.
Well then, the news is very good. It's
a big deal in this neighborhood, right?
A mother goes to throw her daughter
away to run away with another man.
Of course Jung-mi was insulted like that.
They ran away at night just the two of us.
Is that true? When did that happen?
Let me remember. 1998 or 1999?
I don't remember clearly.
But, that's still the
case the mystery now is...
he is not the one who
will throw away his own child.
I don't know what made
him so sick of that guy.
By the way...
Is that damn Yoon causing trouble
now? by claiming to be Go Doo-sam?
- Chang Jin. - Yes?
Why?
IDENTITY CONFIRMATION
DOCUMENT NAME: YOON JO-KYUN
Geez.
Even though Eun-seo is
very beautiful and kind.
He also takes good care of it The
boy's daughter is like his own sister.
You stare at the CCTV camera for a
long time before hiding this book.
Why?
Do you remember Go Eun-seo?
He has no history since 2004, the
same year you entered the orphanage.
Then in 2006...
she reportedly died
along with her mother.
Go Eun-seo's father is Go Doo-sam.
You know the Blue Tong
case Cheongun Port, right?
He is a suspect in the case, but
also the same person as Choi Min-guk.
This photo was taken in Haryong
place Go Doo-sam is or rather...
in Choi Min-guk's yard.
Then in this place, we found your
and Choi Min-guk's footprints...
which we just assumed come there.
You still deny not knowing him?
Seo Se Hyun.
Refusing to testify like this now...
there is absolutely no benefit.
We don't know what your relationship is
with Choi Min-guk or why he kidnapped you...
you have to tell the truth so
that we can can investigate properly.
We have no evidence that Choi
Min-guk is the perpetrator.
Do you want to cover it yourself?
Doctor Seo.
I will say everything.
But...
Please hold a press conference.
Your bleeding is severe.
Do not talk.
Help...
Someone help us!
Here...
Please call 119!
Please call 119...
Help...
Seo Se-hyun, the Agency's renowned forensic
doctor The National Forensics recently...
named as the main suspect
Yongcheon serial murder case...
volunteer to do Press conference.
Through this press conference,
attention will focus on developments on...
possible confession from Seo Se-hyun
or the emergence of other suspects...
and is it Seo Se-hyun who
also is the doctor in charge...
the autopsy process of the late Nam's
case Seung-hyup related to drug delivery...
A little to the left.
Okay.
Go back a little.
CASE PRESS CONFERENCE
YONGCHEON CITY SERIAL MURDERS
Chairman Hong.
Is this going to be okay?
It would be a sensation
if he say something strange.
Do you have a reason why? have
to speak at a press conference?
A famous person like you asks
something impossible like this...
That person will move...
if you see me.
What do you mean?
I will be the bait.
Please.
- Good work. - Thank You.
The speaker has arrived.
AUTOPSY PRESS CONFERENCE
SUSPECT SEO SE-HYEON
BY THE NATIONAL FORENSIC
AGENCY REQUESTED VOLUNTARILY
I'm Seo Se-hyun, the head of the
forensics team. Seoul Forensic Laboratory.
I am a strong suspect
Yongcheon serial murder case...
as well as people who know the original
perpetrator of six mutilation cases...
which has been happening since
1999 until 2004 and remains a mystery.
I am a daughter...
from Yoon Jo-kyun.