[English subtitles are available]
[Strange Tales of Tang Dynasty II To the West]
[Episode 3]
[Chongwen Hall]
Let me down.
Let me down!
Lu Lingfeng!
Your Highness.
Let me down.
I want to pay my respects to Your Highness.
Forget about these formalities.
Send General Lu
to the study.
Yes.
Guo Zhuang.
I'm not familiar with him,
but since he was once an Imperial Guard
and followed Lu Tong,
he's a meritorious minister
who helped me eliminate Queen Wei's party.
To think it'd end up like this.
Guo Zhuang was killed
because I fell
into a thief's trap.
Please punish me, Your Highness.
Get up.
You're seriously injured.
You must've done your best.
That's not a crime.
Lu Lingfeng.
Do you know that these days,
His Highness couldn't sleep or eat
because of you?
Don't tell him that.
I didn't eat because I have no appetite.
This Ghost Market...
I'm willing to lead the elites
to subdue Ghost Market.
Then there won't be
a place outside the law in Chang'an.
The Mara doesn't just kill
and take livers in Ghost Market.
I heard that
there are many who rely on Ghost Market
to make a living.
Though many are refugees,
they are still the people of Tang after all.
The court should find a way
to manage it
and take care of it.
Your Highness is broad-minded,
serving the country and the people.
What are you doing now?
Your Highness, please give the order
to get rid of the Mara's Defeat mural in Chengfo Temple.
This...
A few days ago,
Kong Mao's father
took people to Chengfo Temple.
They failed to remove the mural
and even got scolded by
people from the Princess' Palace
and had his salary confiscated.
Administrator Du Ming of Yongzhou
was ordered to send troops to Chengfo Temple
to protect the mural.
I received an invitation
from my aunt to unveil
the greatest
mural of Tang with her
on Mingyin Festival.
Tell me. How can we remove the mural?
It must be removed.
Did you...
really meet Mara
who came out of the mural in Ghost Market?
Regardless whether
Mara broke out of the mural,
they must be related.
Remove the mural
for peace in Chang'an.
You're badly injured.
Let me send you back
to rest.
Your Highness, please give the order to remove the mural.
Lu Lingfeng!
You're putting
His Highness in a difficult spot.
[Supreme Court]
Guards!
Let me ask you.
Who was here?
Who took away my investigation journal?
Mr. Su.
What Mr. Su?
I'm Su Wuming.
Senior.
Junior.
People say
if you survive a great disaster, you will be blessed.
You must pull yourself together as soon as possible.
Senior.
Why are you back in the capital?
I'm the new
Deputy President of the Supreme Court.
Acting Deputy President.
Su Wuming!
You young one.
You run faster than me.
Lu Lingfeng.
I just put lesser incense
and you woke up!
Let me tell you.
My treatment for you this time
is very special.
It's mainly
to restore your vitality.
You're a martial artist.
If you don't
fully recover this time,
you can't even beat others in fighting.
Fei!
Why did you lie to me
about Guo Zhuang?
Well...
Let go.
Let go!
Fei saved your life.
Why are you blaming him?
Exactly.
Give me the investigation journal.
I need to solve this case as soon as possible.
Enough.
Focus on recuperating now
instead of
investigating.
Give me ten days.
Well...
Eight days will do too.
As long as you listen to me,
I guarantee your health will be as good as before.
Shut up!
Get out.
I won't...
Fei's right.
Right now,
your recuperation is key.
Because of this case,
I was transferred back to the capital.
To be promoted to
Deputy President,
I must earn merits
with this case.
How about
you give this case to me?
Mr. Lu, please help me.
Give me the investigation journal.
Hurry up and send it to me.
You two became major officials
all of a sudden.
Why are you
even rivals?
We haven't seen each other for months.
You didn't even prepare a jar of wine
and two chickens for me.
Princess.
Where are you going?
Lu Lingfeng had been missing for days.
I heard it was a close call.
I'll go check on him.
No way.
Lu Lingfeng went straight to Eastern Palace last night.
I heard the Crown Prince welcomed him in the rain.
He is the trusted subordinate of Eastern Palace.
So what?
Lu Lingfeng's disappearance
might've been Eastern Palace's plan.
Now that you and Crown Prince are at odds,
there will be a war sooner or later.
I've received the report.
They are planning
to attack you.
Aren't you allowing them to do so
by going to the Supreme Court now?
Enough.
I don't want to listen to you.
Then...
you need to be protected by guards and horses.
No need.
Princess!
Didn't you transfer me here
to plot something big?
Always be careful.
You taught me that.
Fine.
I'll have some tea.
Help me prepare quickly.
Princess.
I'll say one more thing.
Lu Lingfeng
didn't solve the case well.
Why don't you take this chance
to cut off the wings of the Eastern Palace
and kill him to prevent future troubles?
It hurts so much.
You...
Slap yourself
until I come back.
[Supreme Court]
Greetings, Your Highness.
Where is Lu Lingfeng?
I-I don't know.
Su Wuming.
He's badly injured.
Shouldn't you be by his side?
I...
Your Highness.
Mr. Lu is seriously injured,
but he should be fine.
An hour ago,
I saw him with his armor and spear
riding a horse.
I really admire
his majestic aura.
Where can he go when he's seriously injured?
Princess.
I think I know
where he went.
[Chengfo Temple]
You can't enter the temple with a spear.
Step aside.
Soldiers of Yongzhou Government
are ordered to guard Chengfo Temple.
No one is allowed to enter with weapons.
Please step back.
Get out of the way!
I, Lu Lingfeng, will remove the mural
to suppress the demon.
If it's a crime,
I'll take the responsibility.
It has nothing to do with you.
Move back!
Try to stop me
and meet my spear.
Qin Xiaobai?
Move!
Lu Lingfeng.
Why do you want to
destroy my Mara's Defeat?
If you weren't arrogant
and claimed Mara would break out of the mural,
Chang'an's people
wouldn't be in panic.
If you don't move,
I'll kill you
with my spear.
I, Qin Xiaobai,
haven't made the finishing touch.
It's agonizing.
I just want to die.
Come on.
You're from the Lu family of Fanyang
and the former general of the Imperial Guards.
For Chang'an black tea and Sky-scraping Tower,
you were involved.
You can be considered a big shot.
I can make do with you being
my executioner.
Come on.
It’s my destiny
to die in front of the mural.
Fine.
In that case,
I'll grant your wish.
Stop!
Lu Lingfeng.
Don't you know
murder is a capital crime?
If I can destroy the mural,
what's with a death?
Lu Lingfeng.
Great.
You're back.
Are you hurt badly?
What are you doing?
Qin Xiaobai was hired by me.
Why do you want to kill him?
There is law in Tang.
If you stab him,
even I can't save you.
He's timid.
Lu Lingfeng.
Is your valiant body a decoration?
Come on.
With your spear,
stab my throat
and let my blood
splash on this mural,
and I'll be remembered forever.
Qin Xiaobai.
You’re famous.
How dare you drink so much?
How inappropriate!
Guards!
Take him out!
Princess.
Princess!
Please let Lu Lingfeng kill me!
Shut his mouth.
I don't want to listen to his nonsense.
Lu Lingfeng.
Pay your respects.
I'm Lu Lingfeng, Deputy President of the Supreme Court.
Greetings, Your Highness.
I’ll wait outside.
Tell me where you are hurt.
I was so worried these days.
I thought
I'd never see my son again.
Your Highness.
I...
am injured,
but I've been treated.
I'm fine.
The walls have ears.
You're so thoughtful.
I must destroy this mural.
Please move out of the hall
in case you get hurt.
Destroy the mural?
Why?
Qin Xiaobai is a drunkard.
Although he is unrestrained,
his painting skills are unparalleled.
Mara's Defeat is missing its finishing touch,
but it's already
reminiscent of a legendary masterpiece.
Since Qin Xiaobai drew the mural,
it's my first time here.
Look.
The painted demon
is so lifelike.
That's why
I must destroy this mural.
This is just a painting.
Do you really believe
Mara will break out of the mural?
I don't believe it.
Do you believe
someone used this mural
to kill people
and disrupt the capital?
Apart from Imperial College's professor Kong Mao,
Hot Springs Overseer He Chi,
Chief Musician Sun Wang,
and my subordinate Guo Zhuang
were also killed by him
and their livers were dug out.
Is there really a demon
using this painting to kill people?
Do you have evidence?
I...
I saw it in Ghost Market that day.
Mara looks just like the demon
in this mural.
What does that prove?
Lu Lingfeng.
As the deputy president of the Supreme Court,
I won't punish you
for failing to catch Mara.
Why pick trouble with this mural?
The demons in the dark
are misleading people.
Removing the mural
will quell the demons' ill intentions
to pacify the people.
Do you know
I ordered for this mural to pray for
Heavenly Empress' blessings?
I know.
Heavenly Empress is my birth mother.
Who is she to you?
On the first day of October, Mingyin Festival,
I wanted to bring you
to chant sutras with me
and consecrate the mural.
Do you know what I mean?
But you want to destroy it.
Lu Lingfeng.
Is someone
scared to death
by the meaning of this mural?
What you did today
must be the Crown Prince's order
to use it to their advantage.
It's unrelated with Crown Prince.
I just don't want the murderer
to use this painting again.
After I destroy the mural,
I'll turn myself in to you.
I have no regrets even if I die.
The Eastern Palace is so clever.
He's using you to deal with me.
Your Highness.
You misunderstood.
I don't want to hear you
explain for Crown Prince.
My heart aches.
Ji'er.
I've wronged you before.
Today,
even if you stab me here.
I won't blame you.
Lest the Eastern Palace plot
to initiate war
and destroy Chang'an
with blades and swords.
Do it.
Today is a rare opportunity.
Killing me would
earn you great merit with them.
Please stop.
You have my blood.
You can't do it.
In that case,
let Su Wuming
handle this case.
My son needs to recuperate.
Don't make me
worry about you.
Lu Lingfeng!
Ms. Xijun.
It's been a few months.
Why do you cry so much now?
He's badly injured
but doesn't want to be treated.
What's the use of pounding these medicines?
Just do as I say.
I'm sure it'll be of use later.
I'm sure.
Destroying the mural,
the demon will have nothing to rely on.
Then he will show his true form.
Mr. Lu's move
seems reckless,
but it's a good idea.
Unfortunately,
I failed.
No.
Doesn't the princess protecting the mural
further confirm
your previous deduction?
My deduction?
How do you know about that?
Although Kong Mao and He Chi
are not high-ranking officials,
they were all promoted by the Crown Prince recently.
They died one after another.
It was not a coincidence.
They should be sacrifices
in the court disputes.
This was indeed what I used to think.
But Sun Wang wasn't promoted by Crown Prince
but Princess.
Have you found out
that Sun Wang drank at Cloud Tower
before he died?
Of course.
Sun Wang even
had an argument with Qin Xiaobai.
Qin Xiaobai outrageously said
that Mara could break out of the mural.
So you followed
along this clue.
Isn't that right?
Yes.
But did you notice that
on that day,
among his colleagues from the Court of Imperial Sacrifices
that Sun Wang drank with,
there's a man
named Xu Zhiyun.
He was recently promoted by His Highness,
just like Kong Mao and He Chi.
Ridiculous!
Chief Musician.
[Xu Zhiyun, Minister of Rites, Court of Imperial Sacrifices]
You once paid a visit to Chengfo Temple
to see the murals too, didn't you?
We've got the Master here today.
Come and propose a toast.
So the one Mara wanted to kill
in the first place was Xu Zhiyun,
not Sun Wang.
This is just one of the possibilities.
Killing these three minor officials
has been enough to intimidate those
who want to lean on His Highness.
I'll go find Xu Zhiyun
and ask him not to go out.
I've already done that.
I also asked someone to stay there and protect him.
I feel so woozy.
Fed.
What kind of incense is this?
Of course it's good stuff.
This incense wasn't for you.
You should thank him.
Me?
I feel dizzy too.
This incense...
Master.
Are you going to sleep?
Do you think I can sleep?
Think about it. I, Xu Zhiyun,
am valued by the reigning Crown Prince
and got transferred to the Court of Imperial Sacrifices as the Minister of Rites.
I was riding high.
Given how great my life is,
I should be having drinks
and enjoying shindigs now.
But that Su Wuming, he...
Recently, there have been many killings
of officials in the capital.
Mr. Xu.
I heard about it.
I'm not afraid.
It's brave of you, Mr. Xu.
But if you trust my predictions,
I’m afraid
it's your turn next.
You...
What kind of nonsense was that?
I can't even get out of my house.
What an anticlimax.
This pot of treasure
has been boiled to the final stage.
Why haven't you brought me
what I want?
Please spare my life, My Lord.
It's just Xu Zhiyun
seemed to be on guard
and didn't dare to go out at all.
Are you looking for an excuse?
I dare not.
I'm incompetent, My Lord.
But it's actually
not that difficult to get a liver.
The prisoners in the Ministry of Justice Prison,
the beggars on the streets,
and the dying men in the Ghost Market...
Bastard!
Why don't you just go find a tomb robber
and buy a dead man's liver?
I dare not, My Lord.
The treasure I'm making
will still shine in a thousand years.
Or, it's safe to say that
only by using my treasure
can I leave
an indelible masterpiece for this world.
How can we
cut corners on the paint
and tolerate shoddy material?
I understand, My Lord.
You must get it within two days.
Otherwise,
you may want to worry about your life.
Yes.
The finishing touch
Mara's Defeat of Chengfo Temple is waiting for
is this treasure.
What took you so long, loser?
Pour me some wine.
Yes.
Yes, Senior.
Please enjoy, Senior.
Go away.
Leave me alone.
Se... Senior.
The moonlight is bright tonight.
Why don't you do the finishing touch
under this moonlight?
Three days ago,
when Her Highness came to Chengfo Temple,
she made a threat that
if you couldn't get the job done
before Mingyin Festival, she...
She'd kill me?
She didn't say it that way.
I, Qin Xiaobai,
have drawn all the murals,
loved all the women,
and had all the wine
that I wanted.
I have no regrets.
Anyone can
take my life anytime.
But... But the criticism of you
from the art world of Chang'an
will be passed down to future generations.
How many decent painters are there in Chang'an?
How are they qualified to talk about me?
To... Tonight,
Dan Zhu who paints murals at Guangde Temple
invited a few fellows
to have a drink at Dong's Restaurant.
They said at dinner that
you've not only lost your touch, Senior,
but...
But also exhausted your talent.
Senior, you can hit me if you want.
It wasn't me who said that.
I just heard it.
If I knew how to use a knife,
I would have rushed in
and killed those jerks
who were slandering you, Senior.
Let them
say whatever they want.
Senior.
You've been delaying the finishing touch.
You must have no inspiration.
I actually have an idea.
What, Senior?
You've also heard of Flying Light?
This thing appeared in Dongdu a few years ago.
I heard
the murals that use this as the finishing touch
are the most attractive to pilgrims.
Its eyes shine extraordinarily brightly,
and they even
move as
the viewers move.
Now,
just over a month ago,
the best Flying Light appeared in Chang'an.
Many people only have average painting skills,
but with this Flying Light,
they received lots of offers of mural painting
and made loads of money.
Although I haven't bought it yet,
I believe
nothing is impossible for a willing heart.
I will definitely
buy the Flying Light for you, Senior.
A few years ago,
in Dongdu?
You are so ignorant.
That demon has been around
for hundreds of years.
Hundreds of years?
Zu.
You lowly slave.
The reason why I redeemed you
is that I wanted you to stay by my side
and learn the Way of Danqing.
Not only do you rest on your laurels,
you also came up with such an idea.
Would I, Qin Xiaobai, go this low?
Get out!
Qin Xiaobai spent every day
thinking about the finishing touch for the mural.
I peeped from outside the window
and saw him crying a lot.
To be honest,
even I wish he could start soon
and stop torturing himself.
In that case,
there's nothing suspicious.
Indeed.
But
his junior, Zu,
has been wandering around.
He has been to
almost every painting shop in both West Market and East Market.
So a painter went to some painting shops.
What's the big deal?
If he was just buying some ordinary paints,
it wouldn't have been a big deal.
But he went to
Shenzhu Painting Shop in East Market alone
three times a day,
and got kicked out in the end.
[Shenzhu Painting Shop]
It seems that he broke
their rules.
He wanted to buy
some valuable paint
without making a reservation in advance.
Shenzhu Painting Shop?
What a coincidence.
Bi Chengye also went there every day.
The owner of Cloud Tower
visited a painting shop every day?
That's right.
I asked around.
Shenzhu Painting Shop's owner
is Bi Chengye.
The so-called shopkeeper
is actually just a accountant.
That's quite
interesting.
[Peaceful Wind]
Fed is taking care of Lu Lingfeng.
He should be fine.
I'll show you around the painting shops.
Cheer up.
Please.
[Shenzhu Painting Shop]
Sir.
I'm really sorry.
It's okay.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I don't know why my legs got weak.
Thank you for your help, Sir.
Thief!
You beautiful thief!
Give my treasure back!
Beautiful thief?
Is that a compliment or an insult?
Give it back.
What's your name?
Why should I tell you?
I've got
my eyes on you.
My name is Dan Zhu.
I'm a painter.
I do murals at Guangde Temple.
You can come see me there anytime.
He said this is called Flying Light.
A small bottle of it is worth 3 golden cakes,
and you have to make a reservation 5 days in advance.
But he wouldn't tell us
what the use of it is.
Dan Zhu?
I've heard of this painter.
She's quite famous.
This was bought from the painting shop.
You must have seen Xijun, right?
I actually haven't.
We can only ask him.
Are you here to take me as your master?
I'm not in the mood anymore.
Please leave here
and leave me alone.
Master.
My sworn brother is here
to pick your brain today.
You're an official.
All you have to do is social climbing.
You know nothing about painting.
What do you have to ask me?
You...
Mr. Qin.
I have something to show you.
Mr. Qin, please take a look.
This thing's called Flying Light,
right?
Why did you
bring this to me?
What an eyesore!
Don't do that.
It wasn't easy to get.
If you don't want to see it,
I... I'll put it away.
But Mr. Qin.
Why do you hate
this Flying Light so much?
Rumor has it that
after the Mara escaped the wall and did evil,
this mysterious paint suddenly appeared.
I suspect there are connections between the two events.
Please tell me everything you know, Mr. Qin.
The Flying Light
is the Mara.
This thing came into being
before late Wei.
It was originally named Flying Light
because it was no ordinary paint.
Its main ingredients are
Azurite and Silverfish.
In addition,
there are many other mixed ingredients in it.
There are different rumors about it.
But this evil being
has long been judged
as a taboo item.
You are a government official.
How could you not know?
I... I really didn’t know that.
It is said that
the painting finished by Flying Light
can be incredibly lifelike.
Now,
various temples are competing in murals.
Many painters
spend a lot of money
on this taboo item
to boost their status.
Shameless.
Do you know
why I, Qin Xiaobai,
still haven't done the finishing touch?
It's because I want to do my finishing touch
better than Flying Light with ordinary paints.
Only in this way
can I live up to
the title of the Best Painter of Tang.
Thank you, Mr. Qin, for enlightening us.
After hearing what you said,
I sincerely admire you.
I believe
you can successfully add the finishing touch
and complete this great work.
At that time,
if you don't mind,
I, Pei Xijun,
would like
to be your apprentice.
Should we confiscate
Shenzhu Painting Shop right away?
Don't alert them.
We should start by investigating the raw materials.
Although Azurite is rare,
[Great Buddha Hall]
Chang'an is such a big city.
I believe we can buy it somewhere.
What is this Silverfish?
A Silverfish is a bookworm.
It's the silver white shiny thing
in the powder.
I, Su Wuming,
have been studying for most of my life, but I didn't think of that.
Bookworms?
They're so hard to find.
It takes a lot of bookworms to make Flying Light.
Where can we get them?
Bookstores.
There are only limited number of books
in bookstores.
Besides, most of them are new books.
Brother.
The Palace Library.
Right.
There are more than tens of thousands of books there.
Besides, they're mainly ancient books.
They must have the most bookworms.
[Palace Library]
Su Wuming.
Do you know the skill of divination?
I'm not that capable, Directorate.
Then how do you know that someone in the Palace Library
has been secretly catching bookworms?
Liang Zhi.
What are you doing?
[Liang Zhi from Palace Library]
I was looking for the works of Wei
when I found that
the books are too old.
They're full of bookworms.
I was worried that the books might be damaged,
so I came to catch them.
All the books here are ancient books,
so there are many bookworms in them. What's the big deal?
Do you think you can catch them all?
Go back to proofreading.
Yes.
After that,
I saw him catching bookworms
more than once.
What?
Is it related to your case?
Directorate.
Can you take me to see him?
Where is Liang Zhi?
Directorate.
He isn't here yet.
It's already this hour.
Why is he still not here?
Where does he live?
He doesn't have a house in Chang'an.
He usually stays
at the Xuandu Temple.
But
he's been going to
Cloud Tower in Pingkang Fang a lot lately.
Cloud Tower?
Come on, have a drink.
Come on, have another one.
In the future,
I'll marry
both of you.
Mr. Liang.
-Come on.
-Are you Liang Zhi?
Beauty.
Why haven't I seen you before?
What was Mr. Bi thinking?
There's such a beautiful courtesan here,
but didn't tell me.
[The Supreme Court]
I only caught
some bookworms.
So there's no need to be scared.
Let me ask you.
How many people in the Palace Library
are there who catch bookworms
like you do?
Including the Collators and Proofreaders,
there are more than 10.
So who initiated it?
I did.
I'd also collect
all the bookworms they caught.
And who do you hand them to?
Commander Hu.
He claimed to be the former Military Commander of Zhexi.
His surname is Hu.
He has a big mustache
and likes to laugh out loud.
He gives off a weird vibe.
In the future,
I'll marry both of you.
Stop bragging.
Give me the money you owe me
from the last two times.
What's the rush?
I am
a ninth-rank Collator.
How can I possibly owe you money?
Go to hell.
We have
many fourth-rank and fifth-rank officials
coming here every day.
Everyone knows you're poor.
Listen.
You must pay off
all your debts today.
Otherwise, don't blame me for being rude.
I'll pay for his drinks.
I was only appointed at the beginning of this year.
My monthly salary is not enough
to cover my house rent and life expenses in Chang'an.
Commander Hu told me that
Silverfish is valuable.
I thought,
how much could it possibly worth?
But I didn't expect that
although I only caught a small bottle of bookworms,
Commander Hu
really paid me a lot of money.
So you instigated your colleagues
to catch bookworms with you?
You collect them at a low price,
and then sell at a high price?
I... I just wanted to make more money.
Where do you
trade every time?
At Cloud Tower.
Look. I have it with me.
That's why
I didn't go to the Palace Library today.
But instead of Commander Hu,
that woman was the one who showed up.
Oh no.