[English subtitles are available]
[Strange Tales of Tang Dynasty II To the West]
[Episode 13]
Which way should we go?
Let the horses rest for a while.
Fed
left in the middle of the night.
He said he would be the vanguard.
I wonder which way
he went first.
Chicken Fed
is just the vanguard who scouts for alcohol.
No matter where he gets drunk,
in a few days,
he'll catch up with us.
That must be because he's out of money.
[Longyou-Hexi Map]
It's about ten miles
from the last stage station.
How come there's no stage station in sight?
Sir.
May I ask
if there's a stage station ahead?
Maybe it's because he's old.
He's hard of hearing.
Sir.
It's freezing.
You're wearing thin clothes.
How about giving you an item of clothing?
Bring it to me.
Are you
giving him clothes or not?
Yes, I am.
Sir.
May I ask
if there's a place to rest from where you came?
No.
Then is there a village?
Then where did you come from?
What's it to you?
Old man.
How rude of you.
Don't stop me.
Let me teach him a lesson.
Forget it.
He's old.
The world is vast.
Jianghu is a mixed bag.
Although this man is old,
he may not have a good heart.
We kindly gave you clothes,
but you responded coldly.
You even refused to give us directions when we asked you.
It makes no sense.
I said,
"No."
You...
If we take the main road,
the next stage station
will be dozens of miles from here.
Taking the path is a bit quicker.
But I don't know if the path
is easy to go.
No, it isn't.
There're snow pits ahead.
The weather is cold, and the path is slippery.
It's likely that you'll fall and die.
You...
Yingtao.
Put it down.
Put it away.
Yingtao.
No offence.
Your temper...
[Turn a Robber into a Buddha]
Guess
what these words are.
Become a Buddha on the Spot?
See the Nature and Become a Buddha?
Let's take the path.
There should be a temple ahead.
[Mo's Inn in a Snowstorm]
We just saw
a large area of wild green onions and chives.
Why did it begin to snow so heavily
all of a sudden?
Didn't the old man
riding the donkey say
that there're snow pits?
But it's early winter now.
The journey to the west is quite cold.
If we pass the frontier,
snow in August
won't be strange either.
Su Wuming.
Where is the temple
you mentioned?
It should be right ahead.
Brother.
There's no temple.
But there's an inn.
Mo's Inn?
Let's go
and have a look.
Wait.
Let's walk a bit further
and stay at an official stage station.
But it's dozens of miles away.
But this place
looks really weird.
[Mo's Inn]
Generally speaking,
private inns
should be built on a roadside
to attract passing travelers.
But look at this inn.
It's built
deep in a remote area.
This inn isn't only weird.
It may also have some history.
I don't know if it has a history.
But I'm
really hungry.
Lu Lingfeng.
Why did you become so cautious
all of a sudden?
I'm going to Yunding to take office.
You're going west with me.
With responsibility on my shoulders,
I don't want any mistakes.
Let's walk a bit further
and find an official stage station.
It's no use for you two to look at me.
We all have to listen to Sheriff Lu.
Stop right there!
You can't leave!
You ate two chickens
but only paid for one.
You can't go.
Chicken Fed.
Lu Lingfeng.
Whether to stay or not isn't up to you now.
Let's go.
Let me ask you.
How many legs does a chicken have?
Two.
Say it with confidence.
[The Old Waiter of the Mo's Inn]
Two.
Right. Definitely two.
Then how many legs do two chickens have?
Four... Four legs.
That's correct.
When I ate chicken,
I only ate two legs.
If I can't pay for one chicken,
how much more should I pay?
It can't be just two legs.
You're cheating.
I... I...
You... What are you going to do?
What am I going to do?
I'm beating you to death!
How dare you run! I...
What are you doing?
[Lady of Mo's Inn]
Why are you slacking again?
He cheated!
Who cheated?
Landlady.
If you don't believe me,
you can count the chicken bones
I ate
and see how many legs there were.
You go back inside first.
Landlady, you're more sensible.
Why don't you leave after taking advantage?
Aren't you afraid that I'll get angry
and stew you together with chickens?
I do have two legs.
But I don't have wings.
Besides,
does the pot in your inn
big enough to stew me?
Get lost.
I forgive you.
♫If you ask what the happiest thing in the world is♫
♫It's to eat and drink as I please♫
You...
You finally said
your life ambition.
You also took the path?
There's a big slope on the path.
Judging from your appearance,
I guess you didn't fall.
Uncle Fed.
Who hit you?
Is it the waiter just now?
Let me teach him a lesson for you.
No need. No need.
Didn't I just say
that there's a big slope?
The snow was heavy, and the road was slippery.
My horse and I slipped and fell.
The horse fell into a deep ditch.
It took me a long time
to climb up.
Then it became like this.
Brother is
well-traveled and knowledgeable.
Seeing the snow was heavy,
he asked us to dismount and lead the horses.
The deep ditch you mentioned
may be caused by ground fissures.
Some of the deep ditches in the mountains
are hundreds of meters deep.
It's good that you're fine.
I'm very hard to kill.
God doesn't want me.
Let's go back
and take the main road.
Let's go.
You're full.
But we're still hungry.
Fed.
Why are you in such a hurry
to leave?
Their inn is strange.
I can't say what's strange about it.
It's just strange.
The Mo's Inn looks
quite new.
It doesn't seem like an old haunted inn.
Besides, the snow is too heavy.
Why don't we stay here?
But this place...
What?
You don't dare to stay
at this remote inn?
If Liu Shiba knew it,
he would definitely laugh at us.
Who is Liu Shiba?
I remember now.
You told me before
about the Gantang Post.
This place
is even weirder than the Gantang Post.
I...
You're really staying here?
It's weird.
I'm not in a hurry to take office in Yunding.
Encounter something weird on the way and get to the bottom of it.
Isn't it a joy?
Su Wuming, so you're
doing this for fun?
You're even less serious than me.
Let's go.
Landlady.
The five of us would like to stay at the inn.
[Good Fortune Throughout the Year]
My Mo's Inn
isn't a place where ordinary people can stay.
If you want to go in and rest,
each one of you
needs to show your unique skills.
What kind of rule is it?
It's my inn.
I made the rule.
Fed.
What unique skill did you show just now?
There was no such rule just now.
He's right.
The rule
was just made.
What?
You don't even want to make money?
There're already guests at my inn.
You're quite a few.
If you all stay
and the heavy snow continues for a few more days,
the food at my inn
may not be enough.
Then I'll have to go to
the town dozens of miles away to buy it.
The weather is so cold.
I don't want to bother.
Then let's just keep going.
Keep going. Keep going.
I must stay
at this inn.
We'll show you our unique skills.
Yingtao.
Nice sleeve arrows!
With this unique skill,
may she stay?
You may go in.
I need some time.
Then I'll go first.
May I stay?
Of course.
I'm ready.
I wonder if it's okay.
What a marvelous drawing!
Please go in.
Do you two have problems?
How about
I examine you?
How dare you!
No.
I mean
if you have a long illness,
I can really treat you.
Don't be ungrateful.
Who wants to stay at your inn?
You old fraud.
I made this rule
to keep you from entering the inn again.
Get out!
If I still have some skills,
[Good Fortune Throughout the Year]
can I bring him in too?
Then
it depends on how capable you are.
Then I'll tell
the history of this place.
During the Six Dynasties period,
the great monk Master Moshi
built a temple
between Hanzhou and Chang'an.
During construction, he was threatened by the thieves who dug for gold and silver.
Master was unmoved
and remained focused.
Not only did he built the Vajra Temple,
he also translated many scriptures
that have been handed down from generation to generation.
And eventually,
he reformed those robbers.
I think this should be
the site of the Vajra Temple.
You're just guessing, aren't you?
No, I'm not.
In this season,
there still are green onions and chives
growing on the hillside outside.
In the heavy snow,
they still remain lush and green.
It can be said to be a marvel.
It's a sign that there're gold and silver under the mountain.
Just as the saying goes, if there're green onions on the mountain, there's silver under it;
If there're chives on the mountain, there's gold under it.
Moreover, in the ancient book
"Record of the Six Dynasties Lost Works" from the Sui Dynasty,
it was recorded
that there were green onions and chives
growing around the Vajra Temple.
I also saw a stone lantern
of the Six Dynasties
on the hillside a few miles away.
Although the inscription is blurred,
I think
the words should be "Turn a Robber into a Buddha."
Also,
this place is located
right between Hanzhou and Chang'an.
Everything fits.
Therefore, I deduce
that this is
the site of the Vajra Temple.
What I said
is unique skills.
You only talked.
What?
Doesn't this count?
But if I don't let you in,
you'll definitely say I don't keep my word.
Fine.
Then I'll cut you some slack
and let you in.
But he
can only stay at the woodshed.
Why?
Because you ate the chicken and didn't pay for it.
Lu Lingfeng.
She's disrespectful
to your savior.
Drink more alcohol.
Once you're warm,
you won't feel cold
staying at the woodshed.
Lu Lingfeng.
Which side are you on?
I think Lu Lingfeng is right.
If you stay at the woodshed alone,
you can drink as much as you want.
No one will say you drink too much.
Isn't that great?
I'm not staying at the woodshed.
I want to stay at the superior room.
One scholar.
Two merchants.
One of them is Sogdian.
He does either spice business
or jewelry business.
As for the other one...
He's either a hero
or an assassin.
Stop looking.
They're all here to take shelter from the heavy snow.
Follow me.
How is it?
The superior room is nice, isn't it?
I have to tell you first.
It's not cheap.
It's understandable that it's a bit expensive.
After all, the heavy snow blocked the mountain.
We're in the middle of nowhere.
500 coins per person for each of the four of you.
150 coins for the one staying at the woodshed.
500 coins for the four horses.
1,000 coins for your food and drink.
The total is
3,650 coins.
This...
So expensive?
That's the price.
If you're not staying, leave now.
Mr. Lu.
We can't be taken advantage of
and be tricked.
Let's go.
Wait.
Xijun.
She's charging an unreasonable price.
We're not staying.
Landlady.
Your price is too high.
If it weren't for the strong winds and heavy snow,
we definitely wouldn't let you succeed.
Here are five silver ingots.
Give me the change tomorrow morning.
But we want two superior rooms.
The food must be good.
And the alcohol must be enough.
Okay.
The superior room next door is also for you.
How to arrange rooms
is up to you.
But he
must stay at the woodshed.
You...
You know that this is a clip joint.
Why do you insist on staying here?
Lu Lingfeng.
He's doing it for fun.
What are you doing this for?
You've been delayed in Shiyang
for more than ten days.
Aren't you in a hurry to take office
in Yunding?
And you, Xijun.
Five people and four horses.
She charged too much money.
You just paid her?
It's indeed too expensive.
Chicken Fed.
Didn't you see?
They
think there's something wrong with this inn
and want to find out.
They said earlier that they were leaving, but that wasn't their true intention.
Xijun, you also learnt smokescreens.
What you did just now was to avoid
arousing the suspicion
of that landlady?
Exactly.
If this is really a clip joint,
those people downstairs
should all be on the same side.
Otherwise, with just the landlady
and that old waiter,
she wouldn't have dared to let us
stay here together.
-That old waiter...
You go first.
Just now, I intentionally
weighed the weapon he used in my hand.
It's a little heavy.
It's just a stick.
But when he used it...
I once patrolled the frontier with my master.
The posture he used when he moved
looks quite familiar.
What are you talking about?
Wait.
Nothing's wrong.
You can drink it now.
What did you put in just now?
Yong'an Pill.
It can test for not only poison
but also roofies.
If something is put in the water,
when Yong'an Pill is added,
bubbles will appear.
Yingtao.
Impressive.
It's just a petty trick.
Petty tricks can sometimes be of great use.
This kind of inn built in the remote area
usually has wing-rooms on both sides of the courtyard
and a main room in the middle.
How come there's an ancestral hall?
And it's so ancient too.
It's not only ancient.
The construction method of this ancestral hall
is also completely different from the other buildings.
As soon as I entered the courtyard,
I found that this ancestral hall
must have some history.
It seems familiar to me,
but I can't remember
where I've seen it before.
On my way here,
I encountered a snow pit.
That was too dangerous.
Many horses and goods
fell into it.
When I looked down,
there were many corpses
in it.
Luckily,
someone next to me pulled me up.
That's why I'm fine.
Landlady.
I'm coming.
Another one came.
I'd like to see
what unique skill he has.
I'm Hermit Jiang.
It's been snowing heavily.
I'd like to stay here.
Landlady,
please do me a favor.
Then please go in.
Why can he go in
without showing his unique skill?
I own this inn.
The rules are made by me.
What's it to you?
If the heavy snow continues for a few more days,
the food at my inn
may not be enough.
Then I'll have to go to the town
dozens of miles away to buy it.
The weather is so cold.
I don't want to bother.
Who said that?
For this distinguished guest,
I'm willing to bother.
Step aside.
No!
Hermit.
This inn isn't a place where ordinary people
can stay.
If you want to rest here,
you must show your unique skill.
You...
You what?
If you want to use your good looks
to make this landlady change the rule,
then please go in.
After all, it's her who owns the inn
and makes the rules.
It's inappropriate for me to say more.
Ignore this old drunkard
who wants free food and drink.
Please go in.
Unique skills, right?
Don't mind
if I do.
You really have a unique skill?
Guys, come and see!
There's a unique skill!
Come out quickly and see it!
-Let's go.
-Hurry up!
Let's go and see.
Okay.
Let's go.
Let's take a look.
[Swordsman]
I just performed an illusion
to climb a lofty mountain
of the Eastern Jin Dynasty.
My feet were sore.
While I was resting,
I saw someone coming with a goose cage on his back.
I wanted to borrow the goose cage to rest.
But then I thought I still needed to stay here,
so I came back.
A scholar from Yangxian?
In that case,
we don't need to bother
Landlady tonight.
Let's ask Hermit Jiang
to make some fine alcohol and delicacies
for us to enjoy.
It would be best
if you could make a beauty
to drink
with my friend.
Good. Good.
Although I learnt some illusion skills,
I can't make
fine alcohol and delicacies.
I
can't make a person either.
He got our hopes up for nothing.
This...
In front of so many scholars,
I showed off my skill.
Please don't mind.
Xijun.
Which book is this?
I've never read it before.
It's a mystery tale.
I'll tell you this later.
Hermit.
Don't stand in the snow.
Come in.
Thank you, Landlady.
Please.
You've been
running this inn for seven or eight years, right?
I mean
you should have some vintage alcohol in stock.
Of course.
Good eye.
I've been running this inn for about ten years.
Of course I have vintage alcohol.
Serve dishes.
I'm in no rush to eat dishes.
Alcohol.
The sooner, the better.
I'd like to get warm.
Okay.
Hurry up and serve our alcohol too.
Serve it together with the dishes.
Also, when serving the chicken,
count how many legs it has.
Don't accuse me of not paying the bill later.
Why are you two looking at me?
Mr. Jiang.
I saw your impressive illusion skill just now.
You even showed us
the essence of scholars in Yangxian.
It was truly amazing.
Since we met at this remote inn
on this snowy night,
would you like to join us for a drink?
Well said.
[Lan Juzi]
Fate brought us together.
Come.
I'll join you for a drink too.
It's good to drink together.
[Jia Buli]
I just finished my alcohol over there.
Mi.
Come quickly.
Let's sit
and drink together.
Put your bag down.
Who would steal it from you?
No, I can't.
This bag of stuff
is worth more than ten years of salaries you'll receive as an imperial scholar
after you pass the imperial examination.
I can't put it down.
Stop bragging.
Right.
I was just bragging.
Look.
You're being taken advantage of.
In the future, in places like this,
you can't pretend to be rich.
You...
Thanks for your kindness.
Your reserve
cost him a lot of money.
Don't worry.
This man has graces.
He's obviously
a rich man.
That man over there.
Aren't you coming?
Guys.
Please.
[Good Fortune Throughout the Year]
As I stay awake until midnight,
I get up from the bed and play the lute.
Through the curtains comes the bright moonlight;
The gentle breeze is blowing at my suit.
In the wilderness shrieks the solitary swan;
In the northern woods screams the circling bird.
What do I see while I pace up and down?
Alone I'm sad for what I saw and heard.
It's snowing heavily.
The bright moon is nowhere to be seen.
Ruan Sizong's poem "Meditations"
isn't suitable, is it?
Indeed, it's not suitable.
But I like this poem.
It's because it hasn't been given
more implications.
The only thing it expresses
is sadness.
Just sadness.
Why are you suddenly so sad?
The scene just evoked my emotions.
Facing the heavy snow,
which poem would you like to use
to express your feelings?
I only think of one line.
The rivers and mountains are vast;
They're actually thousands of miles wide.
Thousands of miles wide.
After all, you were once the General of the Imperial Guards.
Just like my master's
expectations of you back then.
Who's inside?
Come out!
What's going on?
What happened?
Why are you yelling?
There's no one inside.
I clearly heard some noise.
If there was no one inside,
could it be a ghost?
Nonsense.
There's only a god in the ancestral hall.
A god?
Can you let us take a look?
It's late.
If we disturb the god,
aren't you afraid that it may
take one of your lives tonight?
Are those who take people's lives still gods?
Please do us a favor.
Alright, then.
Open the door.
This is a god?
What god is it?
I don't know either.
But it's very efficacious.
When it receives incense,
everything's fine in the inn.
But if we don't give it offerings,
ghosts will haunt the place at night.
It's such a strange god.
I've never seen it before.
Mi.
Do... Do you know this god?
Even if he knows the god,
the god doesn't know him.
Stop kowtowing.
It's... It's so scary.
Exactly.
Worshiping the wrong god will bring trouble.
Go away.
Don't disturb me while I'm worshiping the god.
Every time after worshiping the god,
I have to dust off the god.
It's so cold here.
Let's go back.
Seeing this god today,
I feel it's very mighty.
I want to serve here all night
in order to be blessed with safety in the future.
No.
Get him a blanket.
Hermit.
A toast to you.
Cheers.
Landlady.
There're so many people here.
You don't toast us.
Why do you only toast him?
I toast whomever I want.
It's none of your business.
Get lost.
How rude of you!
Not only did you not toast us,
you also cursed me.
When you cursed me before,
I did nothing.
Now I have so many friends
here.
We're staying at your superior rooms
and having your food and drink.
You've already earned our silver ingots.
You...
You still cursed me.
I'm old.
Should I be cursed by you?
You're taking advantage of your old age, right?
Fine.
After I toast Hermit,
I'll toast you.
Hermit.
Landlady, thanks again.
It's your turn.
Drinking alone is boring.
Why don't we play something exciting?
How?
How about the Tokhara Knife?
This... This...
This thing is too dangerous. I won't play.
You don't dare to play?
It's not that I don't dare to play.
I still want to drink for a hundred years.
Then
it's not me who don't toast you.
It's you who're not worth being toasted.
Fed.
Enough.
Drink.
Here.
The blade of this dagger
is usually retracted in the handle.
There're nine gems around this circle.
Only when one of them is pressed
will the blade come out.
The rule of the game is
that two people participate.
One person turns the button
and hands it to the other person.
The other person places the knife in front of his chest
and presses the button on the tail.
If the blade doesn't come out,
the one who turns the button
will toast him with a bowl of alcohol.
If the blade comes out,
then everyone here
will toast him a bowl of alcohol.
When you showed your unique skill,
you looked quite valiant.
Let's play it.
I've heard about
the Tokhara Knife before.
It was once popular in the Western Region
but was banned early in our country.
I'll never participate.
So you're just a good-looking but useless man.
You...
Forget it.
Swordsman.
You look scary with this sword.
You pretend not to hear me at this moment.
I didn't expect that on this snowy night,
no one in the Mo's Inn
has guts.
I'll play it.
But I want to add a bet.
The gold coin you just got.
Okay.
If I lose,
I'll give him the gold coin.
Mistress.
It's dangerous.
Don't do it.
How dare you try to control me?
Mistress.
Put down the gold coin and get lost.
The gold coin is right there.
What's your bet?
Me?
If I lose,
I'll stay and be your man.
I'm much better than your disobedient
old waiter, right?
After all,
I can read poems for you in front of flowers.
I'm very gentle.
If you lose,
you'll die.
Go and be a gentle ghost.
Then...
Then I need to reconsider it.
No way!
You already gave your word.
The bet is set.
No...
Please.
If you win, you'll get the gold coin.
If you lose, you'll get the beauty.
What I want to say is
that if you don't die,
you'll win both.
Honey.
A toast to you.
It's your turn.
Spin it.
Honey.
Please.