[English subtitles are available]
[Strange Tales of Tang Dynasty II To the West]
[Episode 12]
Ma Huai.
In that case,
you're a nice person.
But you strangled Lou Qingtai.
This is a capital offense.
By the way, Ma Huai,
I remember you said
the first time you left the burial goods store...
That's exactly what the situation was.
When you went to stole from the burial goods store,
you also crossed the backyard, right?
Steal?
Backyard?
What are you talking about?
The scribe recorded it clearly
that when you were interrogated last time, you said...
I was on duty last night.
I left the government office at 9:30 p.m.
I arrived at the burial goods store at 9:45 p.m. at most.
I said a few words and left.
Right.
But I asked your friend
who was on duty with you that day.
Yes.
It was Officer Niu that day.
No, Niu Daming.
He was on duty.
Magistrate is so easy-going.
He invited a coroner to drink alcohol.
It's going to rain.
It should be fine today.
Keep an eye out.
I'm very sleepy.
I'm going to find a place to sleep.
Yes.
You didn't go to sleep.
Instead, you went to the burial goods store
while Dugu Yang was away.
Nonsense!
What proof do you have?
Your shoes are quite new.
The old ones are at your house.
You didn't have time to wash them, right?
I found these at your house.
If you hadn't gone to the backyard of the burial goods store
on the rainy night,
how could the shoes be covered
with so much clay
exclusively used for making clay figurines?
No, I didn't.
I had no reason to go to the burial goods store.
For the Dugu Xin Multifaceted Seal.
When I captured you, you said...
That seal has killed several people.
But no one has ever seen it.
I think
it's a lie
that Dugu Yang
told to his wife.
There is no such thing in the world at all.
I didn't expect
that I would also be tricked
after working in the government office for many years.
You were tricked by Dugu Yang
when you were following Chuntiao, right?
[Lingdu]
Dong Haogu is nothing.
His entire Treasure Pavilion
isn't worth my seal.
The poor coroner has such a treasure?
Even though I went there, I didn't kill anyone.
Did I ever say you killed someone?
When you were imprisoned,
you didn't see
Lou Qingtai's body.
I just deliberately said
that Lou Qingtai has died.
But you weren't surprised at all.
You're
the person who killed Lou Qingtai.
Niu Daming.
Look.
What is this?
This is what I drew
based on what Qingniao said.
Niu Daming.
That day, Qingniao went to look for his brother
in the rain.
But she found you coming out of the backyard.
She was so scared that she ran back home in a hurry.
That's why she missed the chance
to find his brother.
She...
She's slandering me.
Torture him!
Magistrate Dugu, stop hesitating.
Without torture,
this thief won't confess.
Xu.
You also hit me when I'm down?
Assistant Xu is right.
I can give you some advice
on what kind of torture
to use.
Tell the truth!
After I sneaked into the burial goods store,
I searched everywhere.
But I couldn't find that seal.
Suddenly, I heard some noise outside the window.
Who's there?
Officer Niu.
You're here to steal?
Lou Qingtai?
I can keep the secret for you.
But you...
You have to give me justice.
Behead Ma Huai who poisoned my father
and Dugu Yang
who performed a fake autopsy.
I won't tell anyone
about you being a thief.
Okay.
Only the dead
won't tell anyone anything.
Qingniao.
Lu Lingfeng, impressive!
Now,
you're much better
than when you were in Nanzhou.
Su Wuming.
You're good at teaching him
on behalf of your master.
In the court,
don't say anything unrelated to the case.
This...
General Lu.
Please get it straight for me.
On that rainy night,
what happened
in the Lingdu Burial Goods Store?
Fine.
I'll begin now.
That night,
Dugu Yang went to the government office
to drink with Magistrate.
Chunshan used the chance to sneak into the burial goods store.
Chunshan found some copper coins
but was scared away
by the noise in the backyard.
It was Ma Huai who came to deliver clay.
Chunshan escaped.
In the backyard,
Ma Huai and Lou Qingtai
had a conflict.
You can't slander Coroner Dugu!
I...
The rain poured down.
Ma Huai left.
Then,
Niu Daming sneaked in
but met Lou Qingtai.
He killed Lou Qingtai.
But Ma Huai was worried
that Lou Qingtai would harm Dugu Yang.
When he returned,
he found Lou Qingtai's body.
He thought he was the murderer.
In a panic,
he used the clay figurine to hide the body.
Next,
Dugu Yang returned to the burial goods store
and encountered the tomb robber, Lu Er.
[Lingdu Burial Goods Store]
Who is it?
An old friend.
I don't know you.
But I know you.
We both deal with dead people.
Can't I be called as your old friend?
You're a tomb robber?
After that,
you
returned to the burial goods store again.
In order to save your life,
Dugu Yang killed Lu Er.
He did this, not me.
Then, you lost your gambling tool
in the fight with Lu Er,
which exposed your whereabouts.
I know your family was rich before.
It's gambling that made you poor.
If it weren't for Dugu Yang's help,
you would have starved to death.
You're ungrateful
and even tried to blackmail him.
You're
such a rat.
You...
Mother.
Calm down.
Sit down.
Sit down and listen to him.
He's analyzing the case now.
What he said may not be true.
It may not be true.
Mother.
Lu Lingfeng.
Go on.
Then,
Dugu Yang gave a silver ingot to Chunshan
and asked him to leave Shiyang.
After that, he hid the body with the clay figurine.
At this time,
you came to the burial goods store again,
probably regretting not handling
Lou Qingtai's body better.
You tried to test
whether Dugu Yang had found it out.
Why are you still here so late?
Aren't you afraid
that your wife will sleep with someone else?
Okay.
You're right again.
After Niu Daming left,
you, Boss Dong,
came to talk business.
I left home at 9:45 p.m.
It took at most seven minutes and 30 seconds to get to the burial goods store.
Dugu Yang promised
to sell the Dugu Xin Multifaceted Seal to me.
I went home happily
to get the money.
When I came back,
he already died.
I, Dong Haogu, am telling the truth.
Niu Daming.
The third time you sneaked into the burial goods store,
you killed Dugu Yang.
Was it for Chuntiao
or that seal?
I...
No, I didn't.
Here you are.
We also have the night watchman, Uncle Zhong, as the witness.
You still want to deny it?
Uncle Zhong was talking nonsense.
Indeed, I went back to the burial goods store again.
I also thought about killing Dugu Yang.
But...
But Dugu Yang wasn't there.
Lou Qingtai's body
also disappeared.
Nonsense.
There were many paper people and paper horses there.
Even if, as you said,
Dugu Yang wasn't in the store at that time,
how could he not put out the candles?
This...
I don't know.
You wanted to get the seal
and lusted for Chuntiao because of her beauty.
After killing Dugu Yang,
you put the murder weapon in the hand of the clay figurine.
There was no sheriff in Shiyang County before.
Once there were murder cases,
they would be given to you to deal with.
You wanted
to cover up the case by saying
that the clay figurine killed people.
Unfortunately,
the newly appointed Magistrate Dugu
investigated the case personally.
His old friend also came a long way
to help him.
You failed.
Killing one people
costs my head.
Killing two people also costs my head.
Why would I deny it?
Magistrate Dugu. Assistant Xu.
That's all I can think of.
Whether Niu Daming will confess
depends on your methods.
As a person from the government office,
Niu Daming,
you're greedy and lustful.
You killed two people overnight.
Guards! Drag him out!
Beat him!
Beat him until his skin splits open! Beat him...
Beat him until he confesses!
Yes.
Wait.
Magistrate Dugu.
Why don't you invite Uncle Zhong here
and ask him to confront Niu Daming
on the spot?
If the scribe's record is correct,
Uncle Zhong
has already testified against Niu Daming in court last time.
Did you forget about it
because of your injury?
I didn't forget.
But this thing matters.
It would be safer to invite him here
to confront Niu Daming
on the spot.
Magistrate Dugu.
Bring the witness, Uncle Zhong.
Uncle Zhong.
It's him.
It's him who killed Coroner Dugu.
No.
Uncle Zhong.
Niu Daming has already confessed.
The murderer will pay with his life.
You've had your revenge.
Really?
Uncle Zhong.
You have a vendetta against Niu Daming?
I...
No.
He...
He's the murderer.
Committing perjury in court
is a serious offense, Uncle Zhong.
I...
I'm not afraid of death,
as long as I can see Niu Daming
be beheaded with my own eyes.
Zhong.
What grudge do you have against me?
That day,
you testified against Niu Daming.
That night, Magistrate Dugu and I
went to the burial goods store again.
He's the one who lied.
It was clear that night.
The moon was big and bright.
But I didn't see
where the body was.
But where you were was...
Uncle Zhong.
Why did you lie?
I... I... I...
I just
want to avenge my younger brother's death.
Last year, there was a thief in Shiyang City.
A few days later,
my brother's body
was hung on the city tower
in public.
Uncle Xun?
Uncle Xun was your younger brother?
But you didn't have the same surname.
We were both night watchmen.
We already became brothers with different surnames.
Just because my brother loved drinking,
he lost his job as a night watchman.
You couldn't catch the thief,
so you made my brother a scapegoat.
Do you admit it?
I...
I still remember the theft case
last year.
Niu Daming.
You even asked the government office
for a reward of 3,000 coins.
Yes.
So what?
There was no thief.
They were all stolen by me.
Didn't he already take them away?
Bring the stolen things here.
But who killed my son?
Madam, don't worry.
The answer
should be hidden in Uncle Zhong's heart.
Coroner Dugu.
I'm sorry.
You asked me to testify against Dong Haogu.
I...
But I was selfish.
Testify against me?
What do you mean?
Shut up!
If you hadn't wanted
to take the Dugu Xin Multifaceted Seal for yourself,
the serial murder
wouldn't have happened.
Uncle Zhong.
Please tell the truth.
Okay.
I'll tell you.
After my brother died,
Dugu Yang
was my only friend.
That day,
I passed by the burial goods store again
and wanted to ask for some water.
Niu Daming was foul-mouthed.
He also said Chuntiao and Dong Haogu
slept together
and got caught in bed by him.
That's not true!
Niu Daming, you're shameless!
Niu!
You...
Stop!
I do like Chuntiao,
but I'm not as dirty as you!
I made it up. So what?
If Dugu Yang had been fooled
and killed you,
Chuntiao
would be mine.
Dugu Yang was really fooled.
Unfortunately,
coroners can't kill people.
Coroners cannot kill people.
Coroners can't kill people.
Coroners are only responsible for autopsies.
We can't kill anyone.
Whatever the reason,
people who break this rule
should
commit suicide on the same day.
This is a rule of this industry.
In order to save Chunshan,
Dugu Yang killed Lu Er
in an emergency.
He knew Lu Er was a tomb robber.
If he had reported the crime in time,
he could have been exempted from the death penalty.
But in Dugu Yang's heart,
it was hard for him to break the rule
of coroners.
He hid the body with the clay figurine
and asked Chunshan to leave Shiyang.
He tried to cover it up,
but...
Dugu Yang, who killed Lu Er,
was forced into a desperate situation
by the rule of coroners.
In a trance,
he was stimulated by the dirty words
made up by Niu Daming.
I've
never met Coroner Dugu,
but at this moment,
I can feel the pain
in his heart.
At this moment,
Dong Haogu came to buy the seal.
You came at a bad time.
Convert all the money into silver ingots.
Bring them to me
by 1 o'clock tonight.
You want it tonight?
Forget it if you have no money.
No. Wait for me.
I'll go get them.
At this moment, Dugu Yang
was in a trance.
But he had to do one thing.
One thing
which was very important to him.
So when he left
the burial goods store,
he didn't put out the candles.
And when Niu Daming
came to the burial goods store for the third time,
he found that there was no one
in the store.
Su Wuming.
What on earth
did Dugu Yang do?
Madam.
When Dugu Yang brought Lou Lide's body
home,
what time was it?
Around
11 p.m.
Everything fits.
Although Dugu Yang decided to die,
Lou Qingtai kept badgering him.
He was also worried that he had misjudged the truth
about the death of Lou Qingtai's father.
So he decided to carry the body home
and asked his mother Cao Hui to re-examine it.
So my son
said that night...
Mom, it's great to have you
re-examine it.
Mother.
I've been a coroner all my life.
I've never made a mistake.
I've lived up to
the skills you taught me.
Mother.
My greatest blessing
is that I can be your son.
Son,
did you kill yourself?
Yes.
Brother.
Before 1 a.m.,
I passed by the burial goods store again.
Seeing the candles were still lit,
I went
to talk with him.
You're here.
I've been waiting for you.
You don't look well.
Shouldn't you rest early?
Why don't you
go home and sleep tonight?
This place
has much Yin energy.
It's not this place that has much Yin energy.
It's me who has much Yin energy.
Uncle Zhong.
Could you do me a favor?
Coroner,
why are you suddenly so polite?
Tell me if you need anything.
Uncle Zhong.
Please accept
my bow.
Coroner, you...
He wanted to kill himself.
He asked me to put the sword
in the hand of the clay figurine,
wait outside the burial goods store,
and testify against the person
who came to the burial goods store
around 1 a.m.
I asked
why.
But...
Why?
Coroner.
Deaths of coroners
are insignificant.
Why?
Please agree to my request.
Brother.
Coroner has already died.
Even the best doctor couldn't save him.
I could only follow his instructions
and put the sword
in the hand of the clay figurine.
I know everything.
I thought it wasn't Dong Haogu
who caused Dugu Yang's death.
It's Niu Daming!
I had the same enemy as Coroner.
So I took the liberty of testifying against him.
Mother.
Niu Daming, according to the rules,
coroners don't go to execution grounds.
But when you're beheaded,
I, Cao Hui, the female coroner of Tang,
will personally perform an autopsy for you.
I want to see
if you have a heart.
Mother!
-Don't panic.
-Mother.
Put her down.
I'll give her acupuncture.
Su Wuming.
Su Wuming!
Are you Coroner Dugu?
No.
I remember
you seemed to be dead.
Dugu.
Do you
have any regrets?
Dugu Yang!
It's been ten days.
Your wound is almost healed.
Why do you still have nightmares?
It's all because you played tough.
You went to the trial as soon as you woke up.
The poison took effect again.
You almost died.
You even stole
the limelight from General Lu.
No way!
Why were you avoiding me?
Do you think that I, a woman from Jianghu,
am not worthy of you?
No.
I'd never been hurt
so badly.
I already gave you half of my life.
Su Wuming.
As for the remaining half,
if you don't want it, just tell me.
No, I...
Did you chase me away because you knew
you would encounter assassins?
You didn't want me to follow you
because you didn't want to get me in trouble.
No...
I guess
that he should be awake.
Look. Look.
He woke up.
Fei. Xijun.
Didn't I tell you before...
She...
You said you didn't want to see Yingtao.
But we couldn't stop her.
Right.
You did something wrong to her.
Just apologize.
You're a man.
A man of integrity.
Is it so difficult
to say sorry?
Do you think you could chase Yingtao away again
if you refused to see her
this time?
It's like
you don't explain to Lu Lingfeng.
Doesn't he know
you're doing it for his own good?
Yingtao.
Please accept my bow.
Don't just bow.
Say what you should say.
I'm not good at saying nice words.
You're not good at saying nice words?
If you were not good at saying nice words,
we would all be mutes.
I seemed to dream
of Dugu Yang just now.
He asked me to go to the burial goods store
again
and find something for him.
Come back.
Is it money?
Lu Lingfeng has already found it.
You don't need to go.
[Highly Skilled]
We've reported the case
to the Yongzhou Government.
These five silver ingots
were obtained by Dugu Yang from his teaching.
Now, they're returned to his family.
That's all?
There were six silver ingots.
But Dugu Yang
gave one to Chunshan.
There're five silver ingots left.
They're all here.
I'm not talking about the silver ingots.
Didn't he leave me
anything else,
even if it's just a few words?
[A Letter of Divorce to Chuntiao by Dugu Yang]
A letter of divorce?
General Lu said
you can pretend it doesn't exist.
It's said that once people are married, their feelings will be deep.
I was so lucky to meet you.
Riding the same boat needs ten years of cultivation.
Sharing a bed and dreaming together need the fate of three lifetimes.
I wanted to hold your hands under flowers,
cook with you,
be a loving couple with you,
and make others envy us.
But I was born into a family of coroners.
I'm always looked down upon.
I'm not outgoing either.
It's hard for me to make you happy.
I have skills,
but I make clay figurines to make a living,
stop thieves from the tomb,
and am not valued by the world.
Seven years have passed, and discord has appeared.
The resentment is hard to resolve and has become deep.
I wanted to change my temperament,
but it's hard.
I wanted to left my job as a coroner,
but I fell for it over time.
While I look old, you look beautiful.
I can't delay you
for this reason.
Today, I let you go, which makes both of us happy.
May you find a good husband.
Raise children with a smile on your face.
The family members will be happy, and I won't have regrets.
In order to leave a proof, I, Du Guyang, who's from Shiyang County of Yongzhou,
wrote this with respect.
Dugu Yang.
This isn't a letter of divorce.
Clearly, the whole letter is full of wistfulness.
It seems
that I, your wife,
am not that bad.
My Dugu was so good at writing.
If he hadn't born into a family of coroners,
he would have passed the imperial examination and become an imperial officer.
Forget about that.
Being an imperial officer
is a dream of all scholars,
but there has to be someone
being a coroner.
Mr. Su. Physician Fei.
Ladies.
You came just in time.
We have a big event today.
Please witness it.
I, Cao Hui, the female coroner of Tang,
will teach skills on behalf of my son Dugu Yang.
Who is kneeling?
The wife of Dugu Yang,
Chuntiao.
Do you volunteer to be a coroner?
Yes.
Once a coroner,
always a coroner.
Chuntiao, will you regret it?
No, I won't.
I should host it.
Chuntiao, bow to your teacher.
Bow.
The ceremony is completed.
Congratulations! The coroner family has a successor.
-Congratulations! The coroner family has a successor.
Aren't you cold?
I'm a bit cold.
But it's good to be cold.
Cold makes people sober
and makes me stop indulging
in the illusion of nightmares.
You actually dreamed of the case?
Are you shrewd
or deliberate?
What you said
are not good words.
Scold me if you want.
I just recovered.
I have nowhere to hide.
A notice has been issued in Shiyang.
The Su Wuming from Chang'an
has already died.
You're safe now.
But you haven't.
What do you mean?
The first poison dart
shot by the assassin that day
didn't seem
to be aimed at Dugu Xiashu.
Dugu Xiashu?
It's me.
I'm a magistrate in Shiyang.
-Welcome...
-Step aside!
When I was in the dark,
the assassins had already taken action.
Don't get me involved.
But you already said
that there were two groups of assassins.
Su Wuming.
Are you really not going to explain to me
what happened
in Chang'an?
I did it for my own future.
In order to get promoted and rich,
I went to the palace
and told the new emperor.
But in the end...
This is such an embarrassing thing.
What is there to explain?
If you don't want to explain it, forget it.
I'll see how long you can keep it.
We're departing tomorrow.
Would you like to go with us?
You've been in Shiyang for more than ten days.
Aren't you waiting for me to recover?
If I...
I'm staying here
not for you,
but to help Dugu Xiashu
bring peace back to Shiyang.
Are you going with us or not?
I'm not
an ungrateful person.
But I have to have an identity
if I go west with you.
How about being my personal secretary?
What's my monthly salary?
I'll give you one tenth of mine.
One tenth?
So little?
When you went south with me before,
I...
Did you ever pay me salary?
Didn't I?
Just one tenth.
We're departing tomorrow morning.
If you think it's little,
don't follow us.
Anyway, Yingtao told Xijun
that she'll go with us
to see the magnificent mountains and rivers
of Tang.
Lu Lingfeng.
Lu Lingfeng!
Let's talk about the salary.
Raise it a bit.
Dugu.
From now on,
everything will depend on you.
Remember,
the point of being an official
is to do more practical things for people.
In doing so,
you can sleep well, eat well,
and feel at ease.
I was educated.
By the way,
is
the Dugu Xin Jet Tumbled Stone Multifaceted Seal
a legend
or a real thing?
You have to
solve this mystery.
Okay.
I'll keep that in mind
until I find the answer.
Please wait.
Take the naan I made
to eat on the way.
Mr. Ma, thank you.
General Lu.
You cleared my name.
You're my savior.
Please accept my bow.
Although there is no chicken,
I have to thank you.
Alright.
It's time to say goodbye.
Guys.
Stay.
Goodbye.
Mr. Su.
General Lu.
Physician Fei.
Miss Xijun.
Heroine Yingtao.
If you have friends who know your heart,
Distance cannot keep you apart.
At crossroads where we bid adieu,
Do not shed tears as women do!
With the lines of Wang Zi'an,
I'm sending you off.
I found the right person.
Brother, what do you mean?
If you think this wood carving
is good,
please cherish it
and never give it up.
It'd be better
to pass it down.
Brother!
Why did Brother come to me
in my dream?
This...
This is Brother's family heirloom.
Please take it back and keep it.
There really is such a seal.
Let me see.
What a treasure.
What do you mean?
He entrusted this seal to you.
It's yours.
No.
You must keep it for him.
This isn't just a treasure.
This is the life of Dugu Yang
and the Dugu family.
Physician Fei has treated Mother for days.
My mother
has almost recovered.
She told me that many years ago,
Dugu Yang's father
would rather marry into a coroner family
than sell this seal.
He only had one condition.
If he had descendants, their surname should be Dugu.
He entrusted this seal to you.
It must be because your surname is also Dugu.
Please cherish this seal
and pass it down
from generation to generation.
Please.
I'll keep that in mind.
This seal
is the treasure of our country.
Thousands of years later,
it'll surely shine brightly
and comfort Brother.
By the way,
how interesting it is.
Yesterday, Dugu Yang came to me in my dream
and asked me to invite you to the house for some soup noodles.
If you want to eat,
come anytime.
Thank you.