[English subtitles are available]
[Strange Tales of Tang Dynasty II To the West]
[Episode 35]
I think it's best if I explain it.
Let me try to speculate again
without any evidence.
Ten years ago,
Chu Bin was saved by Ms. Yin.
She was revived from death,
and felt disheartened and hopeless.
She left Yunding,
but didn't
return back to her hometown
because she didn't want to,
and was even more ashamed of meeting
her only family in this world, her elder sister,
Chu Jia.
Chu Jia once said
she was strongly opposed to Chu Bin
returning to Yunding with Li Yun.
Therefore,
Su Wuming's speculation
makes a lot of sense.
Fang Jiong is a merchant
who is well-traveled.
In a foreign land,
he ran into Chu Bin by chance.
Let's go home.
Okay, let's go.
Chu Bin?
It's really you.
Wait a minute.
If you're not dead,
how could Li Yun not marry you?
And how did you end up here?
Also,
was the coffin back then
actually empty?
Why did you cooperate with Li Yun
to deceive Shen Ping?
Fang Jiong learned about
what happened ten years ago,
and thought of Shen Ping's current situation.
His former lover was getting more haggard day by day,
which already broke his heart.
But, Li Yun's behaviour and actions
in Yunding
was even more abhorrent to him.
Fang Jiong's appearance
also further ignited
Chu Bin's determination
for revenge.
Ms. Yin.
Chu Bin.
Fang Jiong found Ms. Yin,
and gave Ms. Yin the capital
to change the paper offering shop into Biluo Inn.
After the inn opened,
Mudan, who often had secret meetings with men,
became a regular customer.
Mudan, also a victim,
thus joined
those seeking vengeance.
Meanwhile,
Changle was unwilling to continue
being fooled by Li Yun,
and even more unwilling
to be an accomplice in poisoning Shen Ping.
Therefore,
she confessed everything to Shen Ping.
Shen Ping then went to find Fang Jiong.
Her childhood sweetheart,
at this time,
became the person she trusted the most.
Fang Jiong then simply
arranged for Chu Bin to meet Shen Ping.
The truth of what happened ten years ago was finally revealed.
The vengeance team
was also fully assembled.
Fang Jiong
had some knowledge
because he had heard of how
one could use the revival skill
to swindle money, as part of the so-called miscellenous arts.
Hence, he planned to take advantage of Li Yun's lust
as part of the scheme
to kill him.
But no one expected
before the revenge even started,
an accident happened.
And that was
Chu Bin, who had just returned to Yunding,
was bumped into by Li Men.
Stop right there!
Are you human or ghost?
Although Li Men does not hold a proper job,
he is candid and naive by nature,
and even have a strong sense of justice.
Li Men.
Choose for yourself.
Trying to scare me?
You think I'm afraid of death?
Fang.
Are you getting involved in this matter
because after Shen Ping married Li Yun,
she continued to have an affair with you?
No!
Do you dare to make a blood oath?
If indeed there was,
may I die a horrible death.
So... was it Chu Bin
who promised herself to you?
How dare you!
If that's true, may the heavens strike me with lightning.
Then why are you involved in this matter?
I saw it with my own eyes,
and it's still vivid in my mind.
I'm passionate about this,
so I had no choice but to act.
So much for your damned passion
and your lack of options.
Why not count me, Li Men, in as well?
Li Men's involvement
gave Shen Ping and Changle
an alibi to prove that they were not at the scene of murder.
By then, everything was in place.
Fang Jiong then took advantage of
the drinks after cockfighting
and pretended to mention
the revival skill to Li Yun unintentionally.
He claimed it could revive Chu Bin.
Li Yun, blinded by greed,
fell right into the trap.
On the night of the crime,
Fang Jiong did not go to Biluo Inn,
but instead hosted a banquet at home
that lasted all night long.
All the guests were
witnesses to his innocence.
Also,
the owner of Anyuan Inn that day,
Mr. Xu and his friend,
were probably also
hired by Fang Jiong to put on a show.
The whole act was meant
to mislead Sheriff Lu.
Thank you, boss.
Thank you.
Amazing!
She can really transform into my cousin.
Moreover, its exactly how my cousin looked
when I was 16 years old.
After all these years, I finally get to see her again.
I can die without regrets now.
Then Mr. Xu,
you can now rekindle your old flames,
and renew your love affair.
Despicable!
Back then, my cousin and I
were completely innocent.
Then, you didn't spend these
few silver ingots in vain.
Look at how petty you are.
How vulgar.
How unbearably vulgar!
Yes.
I've always felt that something was off.
Now that I think about it,
everything was simply too coincidental.
As for that Ding Dade,
he's probably not involved in the murder,
but he was aware of it.
So, he was overly nervous
and couldn't sleep.
Hence, he worked all night to rush out
Xijun's current set of clothing.
I agree with your analysis.
Next,
on the day of the crime,
Lu Lingfeng,
you investigated the crime scene quite thoroughly.
The floor is yours.
[Tianyi Fabric Shop]
The letter was written by Chu Bin.
As for the content of the letter,
it remains unknown.
But just the handwriting
was enough to trigger the curiosity in
lust-ridden Li Yun.
Afterwards,
he drank the soup
he had prepared for Shen Ping.
As it was a slow-acting poison,
drinking it made him drowsy.
You talk too much.
Although I've investigated the scene,
there are still many things
I couldn't figure out.
For example,
the candlestick Li Men used to hit Li Yun.
Why was it on the first floor?
All that can be surmised at this point is that
at that moment,
Li Men regretted it.
After all, Li Yun was his cousin
and they were related by blood.
No need to see me off.
Don't step out of this door.
Cousin!
Are you going upstairs
and have a rendezvous with a woman?
You guessed it, kid.
In your life,
how many women have you hurt?
Aren't you afraid that women will hurt you instead?
It's none of your business.
You've been so poor that in the past year or two,
you have yet to touch a woman, right?
You're a good-looking guy.
Can't you learn from me?
What should I learn from you?
You're a beast.
I'm telling you,
if you want to live,
don't go upstairs.
Are you crazy?
Listen to me, Li Yun.
Don't go upstairs.
Go home quickly,
get on your knees,
and apologize to Shen Ping.
Apologize to all the women that
you owe it to.
Are you crazy?
You're the one who's crazy.
I'm trying to save you.
You are trying to save me?
You're saving me?
Save me?
Bastard!
That bathtub
was specially prepared for Li Yun.
In the entire Shangxian Lane,
you wouldn't find another family inn
that has a bathtub that directly drains water
to the floor below.
With this bathtub,
the evidence can be quickly destroyed.
The old man with the cart
would pass through the back alley
at the same time every day.
Li Men calculated the right time
to climb down from the second floor
just to give himself
an alibi.
Su Wuming,
please repeat the postmortem findings again.
With boiling limewater,
a person would quickly suffocate to death.
And limewater
constricts the blood vessels in one's face,
causing the corpse to look slightly reddish
instead of the bluish-purple color.
As for the blood flowing from the mouth and nose,
it happened to be fully absorbed by the lime,
hence leaving no trace.
Afterwards, the limewater
was drained through the pipes
and the corpse was wiped down,
leaving no signs of murder at all.
It appeared as if he died from a sudden illness.
I think this was how
Li Yun died.
As for the division of labor among the individuals,
we'll need to make some guesses.
First of all,
someone had to strip Li Yun naked
and place him in the bathtub.
I'm going to guess that
Chu Bin did not do it herself.
After all,
she was hurt the worst
and loved the most.
Otherwise, ten years ago,
when she was rescued from the coffin,
she would have gone straight to the authorities to report him.
But she didn't.
These ten years,
how Chu Bin got through them,
we don't know.
But ten years later,
for her to finally choose revenge,
it's definitely not just because of
what had happened to her.
I'm afraid
she found out about
the experiences of
the few other victims.
According to preliminary investigation,
the women deceived by Li Yun
are definitely not limited to those few.
Li Yun should have died long ago.
They did a great job.
Why are you staring at me?
If it was up to me,
I would definitely use a sword
to cut open his chest
and see
what is his heart made of.
Yingtao.
You are now considered to be
working for the government office.
You should have a better sense of
what to say and what not to say.
I don't care.
Then...
how can we close the case?
Yeah.
You two have been talking for a long time.
So what's the conclusion?
There is no murderer in this case.
There is no murderer
in this case.
Sheriff Lu, you are enlightened.
I'm just stating the facts.
No one's actions
directly caused Li Yun's death.
What I just said
was just speculation.
If Li Yun had entered the bathtub himself,
or if those few women
did not collude in advance,
even if they did what I speculated
at another time,
Li Yun would still die,
wouldn't he?
How wise, Sheriff Lu.
Su Wuming.
I know you have a glib tongue,
but flattery won't work on me.
Follow me to
quickly report to Magistrate Huangfu.
[Yunding County Government Office]
Didn't they say there were civilians
surrounding the county government?
Why is no one here?
Indeed.
I'm sure Suo Long
wouldn't have misinformed us.
This case has no murderer?
How is that possible?
The most heinous criminal
has already confessed.
There are no ghosts in this world.
It was an evil person who committed the murder.
Just now, at the entrance of the county government,
I have already shared
this good news with the people.
The night market has already reopened.
The officials and people of Yunding
are drinking and celebrating.
Where did the murderer's confession come from?
It's from Heitou.
You were the one who caught him.
He is
responsible for more than 20 lives.
But Li Yun was not killed by him.
He has already admitted himself.
Why would you say it's not him?
Huangfu Tan,
you tortured him into confessing,
in order to find a scapegoat, right?
Investigating cases and arresting criminals,
that's your job.
Why would I torture him for a confession?
It was Heitou himself
who wanted to die quickly.
He specifically asked for me,
so I went to find him,
and then he confessed.
Here's the confession.
He even signed it.
In less than 24 hours,
this mysterious case was solved.
The rumor of ghosts killing people has been dispelled.
Mr. Lu,
you've made another great contribution.
But this is not the truth of the case.
In my opinion,
this is the truth of the case.
Su...
Shouldn't we go have a drink
to celebrate?
Let's go to the night market
and celebrate with the people, how about that?
That's a good idea, Magistrate.
Let's go.
Alright, let's drink.
Let's go drink, let's go.
Su Wuming.
Why are you kneeling here?
This is in the direction of Luoyang,
where our mentor's tomb is located.
When did you start kneeling here?
After I finished drinking last night.
You knelt for the whole night?
It was already midnight when we got back.
At most, I have only knelt for 6 hours.
Why are you kneeling?
To apologize to our mentor.
Actually, you don't need to kneel.
Our mentor has already forgiven us.
What did our mentor say?
Chu Bin was betrayed,
and carried her hatred for 10 years.
Shen Ping was deceived,
and nearly lost her life.
Mudan was bullied,
and her reputation had been completely ruined.
Changle was humiliated,
and is like a fresh flower which has withered.
These women all deserve sympathy.
They shouldn't be punished.
But as the sheriff,
if I leave this case unsolved,
how am I going to face our mentor
after a hundred years?
Our mentor also said,
the most important thing for an official
is to serve the people.
Sometimes,
what's right and wrong is determined by the people.
The people...
Alright,
help me up.
Hurry up.
I can't get up.
Su Wuming.
I want to see Heitou.
[Upright and honest]
I really killed him.
If I don't kill someone every once in a while,
I feel uncomfortable.
That day, I was just about to leave
when I heard people arguing
in the room next door.
You clearly promised to marry me.
You must have misheard.
When did I ever agree to that?
You definitely said it.
With your family background,
you want me to marry you?
You're crazy.
Then a woman came out,
and she looked quite young.
I was so furious.
I rushed into the room,
grabbed that guy
named Li Yun,
and threw him into the bathtub.
You're lying.
Li Yun didn't die from choking.
That's right.
He didn't die at that time,
he just passed out.
When it comes to killing,
I, Heitou, have tried all kinds of methods,
but I wanted to try something new.
That day,
I had some lime with me.
Perhaps, the truth is that
Heitou is indeed the murderer.
But...
I've investigated.
After Heitou was imprisoned,
there was no collusion with others.
If that's the case, don't think about it anymore.
Forget about this case completely.
Forever.
[Grave of Lee]
[In the ten years we've been apart, I've been so lonely and I think about you all day and night. If you miss me too, let's meet tonight. Chu Bin.]
[Shangxian Lane, Qiongquan Alley, Biluo Inn, the innermost room on the second floor.]
Now that you are back,
why don't you sue Li Yun?
I am all alone,
and have no evidence or proof.
How can I win a lawsuit against him?
Why didn't you come back home to find me?
I didn't listen to your advice back then,
and trusted that heartless man blindly.
How could I face you again?
These past ten years,
you've suffered a lot.
What's the point of living
when I was just like a walking corpse?
But Sister,
you actually mastered remarkable martial arts skills for my sake.
That's the truly arduous part.
Sister.
Bin.
How can I ever repay you?
Don't be silly.
I'd like it
if you never leave me again for the rest of our lives.
Alright.
Looking at their silhouettes from behind,
they really look like two female warriors.
Indeed.
May they roam freely
across the landscapes of our Tang,
and never be apart again.
[Fang's Mansion]
Take the money.
A little less, isn't it?
I can't take this.
Take it.
I really can't.
You and I shared a blood oath,
so we are now brothers.
Going to Shazhou to open up a cave is a tough job.
If you really can't bear it,
then come to Yunding.
Follow me around to do business.
We may be brothers forever,
but I can support myself.
Under the sky of the Tang,
as long as one has a kind heart
and is willing to work hard,
he will never starve.
Brother, I appreciate your kindness.
Goodbye.
Farewell.
[Mudan Lime Shop]
Take care.
I'll have the lime
delivered to your home then.
Alright.
Ms. Mudan,
can I treat you to a drink?
Go away.
I don't have time for drinks.
I'm so busy I could die.
I don't know what's up,
but so many people are buying lime these days.
I'm warning you.
I, Mudan, am a decent woman.
If you don't want to marry me,
then don't come and bother me.
Why did Fed ask us to go to the fabric shop?
How would I know?
Ms. Mudan.
I've heard that
Fed goes there every day to
personally brew medicine for Shen Ping.
He stays there for half a day each time,
and always gives his all.
[Shen’s Fabric Shop]
Bravo!
Great!
Congratulations!
Yes, indeed.
Lu Lingfeng, Su Wuming.
You two are almost late.
Hurry!
Gather around.
Come witness this joyous occasion with me.
My godfather,
I pay my respects to you.
Ping,
please rise.
Today is a really happy day.
I, Fed, will make an exception.
Let's drink!
We're not going home until we're drunk.
H-how's that?
Approved.
Sheriff Lu.
What do you think?
Approved.
Okay.
[Xue Huan]
Master.
Master!
Xue Huan?
I thought I was seeing things.
It's really me!
I'm dirty.
Really dirty.
We haven't seen each other for half a year.
How did you...
get so tall?
Only when I grow taller can I
solve mysterious cases
and kill evildoers with you, Master.
Where did this youth come from?
How arrogant!
What abilities do you have
to kill evildoers?
If you underestimate me,
you're also underestimating my Master.
Try me if you don't believe me.
Alright, let's have a go then.
Xue Huan.
He is a county officer.
I don't care what kind of officer he is.
Think about footwork.
Sheriff Lu.
You're biased towards him.
He is my direct master.
I am his direct disciple.
Who is he going to favor
if he doesn't favor me?
Look at you, kid.
You've not only grown taller in the past six months,
but also became much stronger.
Are you not going to help Officer Suo up?
Yes.
Sheriff Lu.
Is he really your disciple?
What's wrong with that?
I travelled south with my master
and investigated countless of mysterious cases.
I also helped my master slay
the Meteorite Bear in Dongdu.
Alright, stop bragging.
I haven't asked you yet.
Why aren't you studying in Luoyang
and came to Yunding instead?
Master.
I need to speak with you in private.
Everyone, back to your duties.
Yes.
Sheriff Lu!
Magistrate Huangfu.
Congratulations, congratulations.
It's great news!
What do you mean?
The golden peach from Kang
is the best fruit in the world.
The last time it was given as tribute
was during Emperor Taizong's reign.
Now that the new emperor has ascended the throne,
the king of Kang has given 18 crates of golden peaches
to congratulate him.
They will arrive in Shazhou at the beginning of next month.
What does it have to do with me?
Hanzhou's Commandery
sent an official document
saying that they had received an imperial edict
ordering you, Lu Lingfeng,
to escort the golden peaches to the capital.
Mr. Lu,
this is a great turning point
for your career.
This is the official document.
The higher-ups ordered you to depart immediately.
To escort golden peaches?
How has your time been
at Blessing Temple?
There are the best teachers
who taught me how to read.
The daily meals
are also the best.
I grow up fast,
so every two months,
Abbot Guangxiao will
make new clothes for me to wear
I, Xue Huan,
has never lived
such a good life before.
Thank you, Your Highness.
The kids in the temple
all call you Bodhisattva.
You don't need to thank me.
Just remember.
You have to spend your life
repaying Lu Lingfeng.
Her Highness asked me to come to Yunding
to see how you are doing,
and even asked you to write to her to let her know you're safe.
Her Highness also said that
when the situation in Chang'an stabilizes,
she will find a chance to let you go back.
But, now is not the right time.
In that case,
it was not Her Highness' idea to have you
escort the golden peaches back to the capital?
Of course not.
Master.
This trip is bound to be dangerous.
You mustn't go.
Xue Huan.
That was not appropriate.
Since it's not Her Highness,
it must be the new emperor
who summoned you back.
How can you not go?
The new Emperor is the former Crown Prince
who values my master highly.
But Her Highness' care and concern for my master
is also genuine and sincere.
I can definitely feel so.
Now, Her Highness is
seriously pitting herself against the new emperor.
Everyone in Luoyang and Chang'an knows that.
They each have their own power in the court.
It's not too much to say that
they're incompatible.
If Master returns to the capital at this time,
you'll be stuck in the middle
and it'll be hard to stay on the fence.
Xue Huan.
Why are you suddenly
taller than me all of a sudden?
Let's go.
Come to my room for a chat.
I'll go book the best restaurant.
Tonight,
let's all get drunk.
What are you thinking about?
I'm thinking about how I, Lu Lingfeng,
have no chance to fight on the battlefield.
Instead, I have to return to the capital by merit of escorting peaches.
So what if I go back?
Will the dark clouds from the past be lifted?
Are you sensing that
there's an unpredictable danger ahead of you
and want to refuse?
I just don't want to waste my time in vain.
Instead of being dragged into such fights,
why don't we build a canal in the fields of Yunding
for the people?
For you to say something like that,
our late mentor's spirit in heaven
would be happy for you.
But His Majesty has summoned you.
You must return.
Chang'an will always be in my heart.
Even in my dreams,
I'm risking my life for the country.
Now that there is an order from the court,
and Hanzhou's Commandery has also issued an official document,
I must go.
Oh right,
Magistrate Huangfu told me two days ago that
he wanted to hire you, Su Wuming,
as Yunding's Market Supervisor.
I think it's a great idea.
In the future, Yunding's prosperity
and the order of the market
is in your hands.
Together with Fei's Yunding Clinic,
I, Lu Lingfeng,
can consider it as leaving
two noble folks for Yunding.
You...
seem very pessimistic.
In this case,
how can I watch you get sucked into the whirlpool
and yet do nothing about it as your brother?
How can I enjoy peace
in Yunding alone?
For the sake of Xijun,
I beg you to stay in Yunding
and take good care of her.
If she meets someone better...
Stop right there!
Xijun loves you very much.
How can you say such things?
Besides, who can persuade Xijun to
not go back to the capital with you?
What should we do?
Xue Huan!
Fed!
Not even a year,
and you already look a bit like your master
in the way
you carry yourself.
With youths like you,
our Tang is not afraid of
strong enemies in the future.
Well said.
That sentence articulates
the century-long plan of Tang.
You have a heart for the world, Fed.
The restaurant is booked.
Great.
What do you guys think
about going to Shazhou?
I remember at Mo's Inn,
Lu Lingfeng once said
he travelled west to take his family
to Mogao Caves to return a wish.
I thought you were lying at that time.
Now, it seems like
it was premeditated.
The Mogao Caves in Dunhuang
have been famous for its murals
since it opened during the Eastern Jin Dynasty.
We've been travelling west
to come to Yunding.
Sheriff Lu, can you bring Xijun along
to see the Mogao Caves?
It's indeed my dream
to be able to go to Dunhuang.
Lu Lingfeng
has offered to take me there more than once.
I didn't expect
to fulfill this wish so soon.
I'm so happy,
I don't know what to say!
I told you she'd be happy about it.
Of course.
Not only the murals in Dunhuang
are famous,
the brightest pearls are also found
in the Western Region's desert.
And more importantly, there is good wine.
Even better than Yunding's.
Chicken Fed.
Uncle Fed.
-Didn’t you quit drinking?
Y-Yes, I did.
But at the time I said
if I didn't cure all the mute slaves
of Yunding,
I would never drink again.
T-That's what I said, right?
Seems so.
I heard
90% of the mute slaves have been cured.
But there's still 10% left.
That 10%...
My disciples and their disciples
have already mastered
the treatment methods.
Before this summer ends,
I promise all the mute slaves
will be fully recovered.
So on this trip to Shazhou,
I just want to drink a little
and feel good about it.
That...
Is that okay?
Alright.
It's settled then.
The six of us
will set out tomorrow
and continue west
to Dunhuang.
I'd like to make a poem.
The vast desert is boundless.
The plains are boundless.
And that's mainly because
there's no more wine left.
That is not a poem.
I actually thought of two lines
Let's see which one of you can carry it on.
As I walk and lament the distance of the army,
I sit in pity with my coat.
The river meets the skies,
and the small stream meets the quicksand.
This I know too.
It was written by Luo Binwang.
The two sentences behind are,
"As I continue to travel,
I don't know when I'll return.
My heart breaks in despair,
and I cry every night."
This is Luo Binwang's
"Missing the Capital on a Late Night at Tianshan Mountain".
It's a good poem.
I also remember two lines too.
The bowstring embraces the moon of Han,
and the horse's feet trample the dust of Hu.
I don't seek to survive in the frontier,
but I'd die to repay you.