Let's go.
Archery range.
When was the last time you did archery?
2021.
No, wait, didn't you do it in the cabin?
The one in the cabin doesn't count.
I think
I can't lift it, it's so heavy.
Keep your left arm straight.
This is really heavy.
Yeah, it's actually pretty tiring.
Yeah.
That arrow I just shot,
I have no idea where it went.
No, I need to pull myself together.
Where did it go?
I can't see it at all.
At least yours are all grouped together.
Yeah.
Right?
Mine are all over the place.
Only one arrow left.
Imagine you're standing at the Olympic arena.
Calm and composed.
Don't panic.
Raise your bow.
Everyone in the judges' seats is silent.
Everyone is waiting.
I release this final arrow.
You really know how to dramatize things.
Where is it?
It's okay.
This is my last arrow.
Everyone at the judges' table
is waiting
for you to shoot this final arrow.
They aren't expecting a good result either.
But they're really mistaken.
I'm happy as long as I hit the target.
Alright, yellow.
Let this arrow be yellow.
You can do it.
Which one is it?
Which arrow?
Alright.
That's enough exercise for today.
Do you want to record your score?
I'll pick a nice target board.
I'll count that one as mine.
Is it that one?
That's mine.
I didn't expect that just shooting an arrow would
make my left hand useless.
I hit everything
except the target board.
It's ten meters, so we just...
Ten meters is really far.
It's already pretty far.
Really?
It's about this far in the Olympics too.
I think so.
You sound so serious.
Are you sure?
Look it up.
Seventy meters? I don't believe it.
And you said...
It's true.
And I actually believed you.
Karting.
Go-kart.
This hand.
We need to get a two-seater.
This feels amazing.
This is so interesting.
Is that okay?
You’re really good at it now.
You’re so good at riding that bike now.
That’s awesome.
Pro driver.
It’s still fine, right?
Dachshund.
That’s really fun.
Okay.
Each one is funnier than the last.
You were just standing at that street corner.
I just saw you from a distance.
It was like—
You suddenly looked so beautiful—
Like you were on a different layer from everything else.
Even if I’ve heard this a thousand times,
it still makes me happy every time.
But I really mean it.
This time, I also think you
look especially handsome.
Why is that?
It’s because he’s recently
lost a little weight.
So I think his handsomeness
has gone up a level.
Right?
Which side of your face looks better?
This side.
Either is fine.
Just pick the side that looks best on you.
I’ll be your background.
Background buddy.
Have you ever tried this Four Fruit Soup?
Actually, it's a bit like
the iced porridge we have in the north, you know?
Hello.
I'd like a large portion.
Classic Four Fruit Soup.
This teacher is looking at candied hawthorn.
My favorite dessert is
candied hawthorn fed to me by Wo Wo.
You rascal.
Thank you.
Hou treated us to Four Fruit Soup.
This weather is really perfect
for eating this.
It's very refreshing, right?
Are you tempted just by looking at it?
Let me quickly give you a bite.
Otherwise,
Wo Wo will just eat by herself again.
She won't feed Teacher Hou at all.
Careful, it's hot.
Surprisingly delicious.
Well, maybe not that surprisingly delicious.
But it is tasty.
I'm not really sure what its real name is.
But anyway, it's also called "Tusun (jelly)".
Yeah.
I knew you'd eat like this.
I want to eat that too.
You know me a little too well now.
There's a bracelet shop here.
Let's get a souvenir.
Let's go.
Okay.
Come, I'll make one for you.
How is it?
Then let's make one for each other.
Is that okay?
Sure.
I think this stone looks stylish on guys.
It feels really trendy.
What do you think?
It's good, no problem.
Do you prefer small beads or big beads?
I—I also like small beads.
Matching with these kinds of beads.
This one is a bit too big.
She doesn't like the really big ones.
Small ones, there are small ones inside.
Okay, this kind is good.
Thank you.
Yes, I think it looks great.
Really.
It looks better than I imagined.
You underestimated me again.
I'm so touched, a PE teacher making crafts.
Done.
Just right.
It's good.
This doesn't need adjusting.
This one doesn't need adjusting.
Not bad at all.
The bracelets are finished.
Come take a look.
These are for the two of us.
A very similar match.
It means that we
will have our wishes come true and everything go smoothly.
This year, the two of us will definitely have great luck.
Okay.
Let's move a bit to the side.
A bit more to the side.
Hold my hand.
I was always on business trips before.
And every time I went somewhere,
I would check out
the climate and food of the place
to see if it might be
somewhere I'd want to retire in the future.
So after checking out Qingdao,
what do you think?
You do ask good questions.
Qingdao...
How should I put it about Qingdao...
Qingdao might be a good place to live,
but maybe not the best place to retire.
We could live there for a while first,
and then move somewhere else to retire later.
I think Quanzhou is actually pretty suitable for retirement.
That's true.
The temperature is nice too, right?
Yeah, I just feel like
the food here really suits my taste.
It suits me too.
Yeah.
Because you usually want to eat what I want to eat.
It's really lively.
I think this really has
a sense of real life.
It feels truly alive.
Let's go, let's get something to eat.
Thank you.
Do you want some mango pomelo sago?
No, you have it.
Mango pomelo sago must be really sweet.
It'll make you break out.
And if you get pimples on your face again,
you can't blame Lao Luo for giving you snacks.
It's clearly you yourself.
How about putting it back?
It's not opened yet.
No.
I just have to drink something sweet today.
How is it?
It's okay.
And then I had a potato.
Not bad.
So tasty.
It's delicious.
It's a bit like wontons.
I can't say exactly what's good about it.
But sometimes, nothing else can replace it.
How did this turn into confessing to it?
Hello.
I'm actually watching your dating show.
Thank you.
Oh my god.
Can I ask for your contact info, brother?
You already have it.
Don't be like this, I really...
Do you know what goes best with rice?
What makes it taste the best?
What?
Add my contact info.
Just lock me in here.
What's wrong?
Private pet. Please do not feed.
Caught off guard, right?
When asked if I was Hu Yunting,
I really wanted to say I'm Li Junjie.
That's great.
This place really feels like
a paradise.
Seeing the ocean makes me so happy.
Me too, I absolutely love the ocean.
The wind by the sea is a bit strong.
Hairline.
Hairline protection.
If I were to live here,
I think I'd live a bit further inland.
So I wouldn't be so close to the sea.
Because the wind by the sea is pretty strong.
It would also be bad for your skin.
You'd age quickly, that's not good.
It's okay, I'll block it for you.
Right?
How could you possibly block it?
You're just blocking yourself, teacher. Who are you blocking?
I'll use someone to block for you.
And I'll use my hand to block for myself.
That's fine, right? There's no conflict.
No conflict.
That's fine.
What is this?
How did this...
Why are there traps here too?
After you, teacher.
Why am I still the teacher?
Then you're a penguin.
Bichon.
Shoulder strap.
Old "shoulder," super "slippery."
I want to touch the water.
Should we go touch it?
Yes.
Let's go.
I want to touch the water.
It's impossible to come to the seaside and not touch the water.
Not touching the water?
Then why did I even come?
It's actually not as cold as I imagined.
Really.
The two of us are there, chattering our teeth.
While sighing.
Then let's find somewhere warm.
We'll catch a cold.
That's right.
Block the wind.
Aren't you going to...
Tie it up, tie it up, teacher.
Block the wind.
Don't block it anymore.
Actually, from this angle,
it looks kind of creepy.
We left our footprints in Anaya.
It was originally a very romantic phrase.
A very poetic phrase.
But it turned into
Are you good at swimming?
I used to be on the school team.
Impressive.
Used to be on the school team, that's impressive.
It's not that great.
But I'm not bad.
We need to ride fast now, teacher.
Let's see who's faster.
I won't lose.
He took a shortcut.
What's going on? Don't run!
Goodbye.
You...
Can't catch up.
Do you know who else can't catch up?
The camera teacher.
Finally, you're not wearing shoulder pads.
And then you passed the shoulder pads to Wo Wo.
You know,
you actually look good in my jacket.
Auntie's style is pretty good.
Very versatile.
Versatile, yes.
It goes with many styles.
This is very stylish.
That's just how it is.
Yeah.
Hou's taste is pretty good.
Well...
Still praising yourself.
But when it comes to taste,
my taste is even better than yours.
Well, then praise me too.
I've been having auditory hallucinations lately.
Why did I just hear
a voice like yours calling "Wo Wo"?
Was it that little scooter that just passed by?
The sound it made?
It was calling "Wo Wo".
Let's go to the second floor.
I feel like the view is better on the second floor.
This is so nice.
Enjoying the sea breeze and eating seafood.
This one is so thin.
Look, it has two bowls.
I think these are for dipping sauces.
Sauce dishes, right.
Right.
You're so smart.
Lately, you
have been acting a bit like Hou
It's getting a bit serious.
Because in detail,
I've been repeatedly studying some of Hou's sayings.
And I hope that I can also
keep improving in the days to come.
Let's have some crab. Crab, crab.
Crab.
A couple of nights ago, I
called Luo Junfan to chat.
I really regretted it.
At that time, there were many
Actually, there were many things I didn't
didn't do as well as I could have.
I think you already
And I think Lao Luo
doesn't have much room to improve.
There's still a lot of room for improvement.
For example?
Is there anything else you think
could be done better?
It really feels like I tried my best.
So I held it in for so long
just to praise myself.
But something Lao Luo said
I really agree with.
He said that life in the cabin
is just one part of it.
What we need to focus on next
is living our own lives
even better.
We shouldn't let outside voices
interfere with us too much.
I feel the same way.
That's why I keep emphasizing
Let me do it, just leave the bowl there.
The cabin is a very special memory.
But what's more important is real life.
Right?
Sitting here, feeling the sea breeze, eating seafood,
it feels like we've left Qingdao.
But at the same time, it doesn't.
But it also feels like
we've gone back.
We haven't really left Qingdao, right.
It feels like coming home.
There's a spot on the whole Pingtan Island
where the Blue Tears have started to appear.
Let's get a little electric scooter.
Driver Xiao Hou, say hi.
I'm driver Xiao Hou.
Riding my beloved little scooter,
let's go!
Wobbly Teacher Hou.
This light is absolutely amazing.
I'm stunningly beautiful.
What am I even saying?
Teacher Hou is amazing.
It's like
Xiao Hou is taking you to see a house.
Pingtan Island sales staff.
It feels really nice.
Isn't this island romantic?
Yeah, it's perfect for dating.
I can hear the sound of the wind.
Auntie, hugging you makes me feel so safe.
This little electric scooter is so comfortable to ride.
A little breeze, just as expected.
It's really not cold at all.
As long as you like it.
This feels pretty great.
But it feels shakier than when you ride.
No, it's because I'm heavier.
Okay.
Five hundred meters left, two minutes.
Let's go!
I don't feel at all
tired.
That's amazing.
We've been riding the scooter for two and a half hours.
Almost three hours.
But I know
now the tears have already faded.
They're gone.
The blue tears have already
turned into
tears.
My tears.
This pitch-black sea
feels so lonely.
What's wrong?
I don't know what to say.
A bit disappointed we didn't see it, right?
It's okay, Qingdao.
Because it was actually here all along.
We just came too late.
It's okay, they have it in Qingdao too.
Next time, let's go back to Qingdao again.
Alright.
Look.
This blue is just
still here.
Did you see it?
There's more.
Here it comes.
It's really amazing.
I think our trip
has a lot to do with water.
For example,
surfing,
I was protecting you.
And on that boat in Suzhou,
you were filming the scenery,
and I was filming you filming the scenery.
And feeding seagulls by the sea in Qingdao,
and this time chasing the blue tears.
Look at the fireworks.
They're still beautiful.
Some man-made fireworks.
We're setting off fireworks again.
This is our third time setting off fireworks together.
Another memory for our little cabin
Add one, and another, and another.
Sparklers.
Are you happy, Teacher Hou?
I'm happy doing anything with you.
Friends,
Today, Sister Ka came to Beijing to see me.
Now I've already packed up and am ready.
I'm about to go pick her up.
Let's make a guess.
What do you think she'll be wearing when she comes out?
I guess it'll be black.
The answer is revealed.
Black.
Why is it still in portrait mode?
Welcome, welcome!
Maybe this is for warding off evil.
Let me show everyone.
This is what Lao Wan uses for protection and safety.
How can you call this for warding off evil?
This...
What is it?
This is...
This is for attracting good luck.
What, romantic luck?
What?
Let's go have hotpot.
I like this.
Look at this meat.
Hotpot.
You pick it up and bring it over.
Can't I just eat it myself?
No way, that's not okay.
You're so nice.
Then this...
The first bite has to be the one I cook for you.
Brilliant.
Let me have one.
You really get it.
You really understand this joke.
Look at what this is.
That's a big chunk.
Teacher Wan, will you peel shrimp for me?
Of course I can.
Can you be a bit more manly?
I've put my feelings into these crayfish.
Check out our second round of barbecue.
It's bubbling.
Beijing's famous dish, Qianlong Cabbage.
No matter where our Sister Ka goes,
her favorite is always sweet soup, right?
This counts as tasting old Beijing's sweet soup.
Let me make you all crave it.
Let me get you some.
Right now, I'm just looking forward to that spicy hot pot tomorrow.
My expectations are sky-high.
Why?
It just seems really tasty and fragrant.
True.
So in your spicy hot pot,
what do you usually like to eat or add?
Let's count down, three, two, one.
Three, two, one, then we both say one at the same time.
Three, two, one.
Chicken cartilage.
Chicken cartilage is definitely good.
Say another one.
Just say one at random.
Whatever comes to mind.
Three, two, one.
Zero chemistry.
No, let me try again.
Okay, this one.
Come on, three, two, one.
Wait a second.
I haven't thought of one yet.
You haven't thought of one?
Okay, are you ready?
Just say whatever pops into your head.
So that's it.
So let's do three, two, one.
What the heck?
Meat.
Meat doesn't count.
Meat is too broad.
Beef.
Alright.
Our chemistry really is zero.
I've been giving you hints for ages.
So many hints.
Beef tripe.
Ugh, I'm so frustrated.
Your fist is so big.
My hand is big.
That's such a big difference.
Big hand holding little hand.
Not afraid of slipping while walking.
Walk, walk, keep walking.
And you'll grow up.
Us.
I want to wash my hair.
Wash it, you can wash it when we get back.
We've finished eating now.
Let's go out for a walk.
I want to wash my hair.
All this lady can think about is washing her hair.
I've been thinking about it all day.
I've wanted to wash my hair since I woke up this morning.
I want to wash my hair.
Wash your hair, wash.
I can't hear you.
I want to wash my hair.
Look, there's a hair salon right across the street.
Heading out
Now we're getting ready
to take a walk around Taikoo Li in Sanlitun
and let you experience
the busiest intersection in all of Beijing
In my previous short film
I also shot a segment here
I wanted to capture that feeling of being in the crowd
and weaving through people
but unfortunately, I didn't really capture it
They told me
at the next traffic light
to wait in the very middle of the road
I stood there, completely frozen
trying to film myself crossing the street
but I didn't manage to get the shot
So today I asked you to come and film with me
Payment
Five yuan
Eighty
Crossed the street
So many people.
Checking in, checking in at a Beijing mall.
Look at me for a second.
Cool girl.
Giving off a smart older sister vibe.
This works.
Right now we
are getting ready to eat.
Spicy hot pot, Nameless Hot Pot.
Let's do it again.
We're getting ready to eat.
Spicy.
This part fell apart.
We're getting ready to eat spicy food.
Spicy.
We're getting ready to eat.
Spicy hot pot.
It's really not easy.
Okay.
Zero chemistry.
We're here.
We've arrived, Ms. Ka.
The one she's been craving the most.
Yeah, I've been wanting to eat this for so long.
This spicy hot pot.
It must have been a month ago
that I started craving it.
Smells so good.
I'm really excited.
So excited.
Let's eat.
My eyes just lit up.
This is the joy of carbs with carbs.
Rice mixed with big noodles.
There's a big bowl left.
Bro.
Bye.
This lady here.
I want to be a heartless woman.
A heartless woman doesn't look back.
Goodbye.
Goodbye, heartless woman.
Forget it, I'll be a bit more sentimental.
Bye.
520 is coming soon.
I've been preparing little gifts for you lately.
Guess what they are.
It's fine, whatever you buy me,
I'll like it all.
Liang Tian.
You're an archer.
I am.
No wonder you shot straight into my heart.
Lao Wan.
Why am I here?
Why?
Why is it always half?
Because the other half is you.
It's okay.
Don't be mad.
Come on, don't be mad.
Aren't you pretty good at this?
Live passionately and seize your youth.