What does that mean?
What is this?
Please say your goodbyes.
Pack your things as soon as possible.
Check out and leave within an hour.
Check out within an hour.
Seriously?
No way.
Just a moment ago,
everyone was still enjoying hot pot together.
And the next moment, we suddenly have to leave.
It's a bit overwhelming.
But
all good things must come to an end.
Goodbye.
Let me give a hug too.
I can't handle this kind of moment.
Leaving so suddenly like this.
Yeah.
Home is where my heart feels at peace.
If you feel these friendships
or feelings are still there,
then no matter how far apart we are,
as long as you keep it in your heart,
I think this relationship can always continue.
Tomorrow will be the final moment of truth.
If there's someone you want to express your feelings to,
please reply with their name after thinking it over tonight.
That takes a lot of courage.
I've replied.
Hurry and get on the Soul APP
Where interesting souls meet freely
This program
is exclusively sponsored by the Soul APP, popular among young people
as the exclusive title sponsor
Global beauty and health products
available on the Watsons mini program
Thanks to the beauty of health and the health of beauty
jointly sponsored by Watsons
Welcome, friends
Produced by Tencent Video
a mature dating reality show
this is the final episode of Season 4 of "Half-Mature Lovers"
Welcome, everyone
Let's welcome our teacher, Du Sujuan
Hello, everyone
Xu Yiyang
Chun Ye
Yixin
Lu Hu
and also Xia Zhiguang
Welcome, everyone
How did we make it to the final episode?
Guangguang actually made it to the last episode
Maybe it's because of his obsession with the lock
Let's hang one up today
If I don't hang it up, I'm not leaving
That's right
Then tell us
Which couple's final confession are you most looking forward to?
Then I still choose Teacher Hou and Wo Wo.
It feels like Teacher Hou only has
Wo Wo in his mind.
So I'm really curious to know
whether he succeeded or not.
To see the outcome of this favoritism, right?
Yes.
What about Huzi?
Actually, I hope to see
the progress between Xiao Hu and Liang Tian.
I'm very interested in them.
They've always been on my mind.
It's also hard to say
what kind of outcome the two of them will have.
Okay.
Teacher Lu Hu,
there's a problem with your mic.
Please step out to adjust it.
Okay.
Sorry, come on.
Then let's first...
Let's talk first.
Alright.
So, who...
Tang Tang, or...
Okay.
Actually, I feel a bit regretful.
Because I think this season
is almost over,
and we still haven't seen Xiao Hou's flaws.
I really feel regretful about that.
That's right.
Yes.
And I also think
Happy birthday to you
We want to make it up to you
We have regrets too
Guangguang didn't celebrate his eighteenth birthday
Happy birthday
Right, last time
Xiaxia said not to have any regrets
Teacher Du said
Everyone's birthday
is the brightest
and most worth celebrating
The day you arrived
is the most worth celebrating
Then Guangguang said
his eighteenth birthday
wasn't especially perfect for you
and you still have regrets
So a few of us
planned something
and conspired together
Happy birthday, Xia Zhiguang
Thank you
You can make a wish
Make a wish
Careful
You have to close your eyes to make a wish
Happy birthday
Happy 18th birthday
You're an adult now
Happy birthday
Thank you all
Really
I really
Let me hold it for you
My mind went blank for a moment
I'll take it, let me take this
Thank you
It all started because of Xia Xia (Xia Mengting)
And ended with Xia Xia (Xia Zhiguang)
Yes
That gave us this inspiration
We also want to express
Guangguang, you are very precious
To us
We wish you
You are also very worthy of love
You all are so wonderful
Really, so wonderful
Wishing our precious Guangguang
A happy birthday every year
Thank you
Come on, let's take a group photo
Yes, let's take a picture together
Come on, birthday star, stand in the middle
Birthday star in the middle
Hurry, birthday star, come here
Let's do this pose
Eighteen, okay?
Okay
And also wishing Guangguang
Happy 18th birthday
So happy.
This must be one of the
most important moments in my life.
We all love Guangguang.
Thank you all, love you all.
I love you all too.
I really love you.
I really didn't expect
the family I saw in "Half-mature Lovers"
could also become a little family here in real life.
I also really didn't expect
everyone to celebrate this birthday for me.
Honestly, I was really stunned.
Just now, I couldn't think of anything.
And even
didn't know
it just felt so strange.
It felt like I was suddenly given a big hug.
Today I truly felt healed.
Thank you for giving me this birthday.
And thank you for embracing me.
I'm truly grateful to you all.
It's worth it, Guangguang deserves it.
I think we should thank you.
For giving us this opportunity.
Yes.
Right?
That's right.
And to be able to cross time,
cross mountains and seas,
and say "happy birthday" to eighteen-year-old Guangguang.
Thank you.
We have to thank you.
Confession Night is about to begin.
So, for the last time this season,
it's the Soul True Feelings Moment.
We have to guess
which guests
will make it to the confession stage.
We have to get all of them right
to be able to hang the lock.
Global beauty and health products.
Search for the Watsons mini program on WeChat.
Get it in as fast as thirty minutes.
Now, let's watch the Watsons True Deduction Moment.
As long as they participated in the confession,
it counts.
Yes, it counts.
The alternatives.
Yes.
That's actually pretty easy to choose.
I think so.
Okay, I'm done choosing.
I'm done too.
I think it was easy to pick.
Come on, let's reveal together.
Let's do it.
Du's choices are...
I just have those two who didn't go up.
So do we.
So we...
We all have the same.
It's the same, right?
Ours are the same.
They're all the same.
Go on the Soul APP.
Meet interesting souls who understand you.
Next, let's enter the Soul True Feelings Reveal Moment.
Suddenly, this hotel feels real.
It's like pulling them out of one environment
and into another.
Really just left.
It feels pretty strange.
It's a bit hard to let go.
I feel very lost.
It's an empty feeling.
This connection, for me,
is truly special.
I need to reconsider my
thoughts and feelings about him.
What is this?
Prepared some photos.
Sorting out my emotions.
When I left the cabin
I didn't cry
But sitting there
when I saw these photos
I couldn't hold back anymore
A lot of our memories flashed by
It felt like these past days
were replayed all over again
Photos of Luo Junfan
make up a large proportion
I noticed some
perspectives I hadn't seen before
Some show me secretly looking at him
and some show him secretly looking at me
Are you right-handed?
So you push them over there
then it's easier to grab from them
This angle is just right
It looks good
Thank you for yesterday's moment
What moment?
The moment you posted
One more spoonful
Okay, sure
Alright
Scientific pig farming
As I watched
I kept laughing
And then I thought
So when you were in the game
you were in this kind of state
The one in the game is confused
It's really true
Most of the photos
are from the parts where I was present
especially with Liang Tian
Because the two of us really
have been through a lot
in the cabin.
So when I got the message,
of course I wanted to talk to Liang Tian
and have a proper conversation again.
To clarify our relationship.
When I looked at old photos,
I was still really looking forward to tomorrow,
but also very nervous.
I don't know what he'll think in the end.
I'm worried it will turn into
something I didn't expect again.
Actually, what I'm struggling with is
whether I should bother her again.
And whether I should say this
so directly.
I'm really happy.
This is the moment I've been waiting for.
As long as I give my all
and sincerely express my feelings,
and wholeheartedly pursue Wo Wo,
I believe there will be a good outcome.
When this moment
really arrives,
I also have a lot I want to say.
So I'll just face myself honestly and sincerely.
I've said too much before
about how our feelings weren't strong enough.
But I also want to say
that actually, there were many moments
when my heart was moved.
My feelings right now
are already very clear.
I'm just not sure
after Wanwan heard what I said yesterday,
from a sincere perspective,
there's something
I want to tell you.
What kind of answer will he give me?
After a long period of careful consideration,
I ultimately decided
not to confess my feelings to any of the girls.
The changes and breakthroughs I wanted to achieve
I have accomplished successfully.
So I truly have no regrets.
That's why I chose to leave alone in the end.
Today, I have no one to express my feelings to.
Leaving the house is an ending,
but also a beginning.
Who
Kaka
So beautiful
I'm very sure
Right now, my heart is only thinking of Wanwan
Footsteps
Good evening
You look beautiful today
Thank you, you look handsome too
Wait, this scene is a bit...
Let's both take a deep breath, don't be nervous
Deep breath
Okay, here I go
Wait
I want to say something first
Actually,
It's already the last day
I have to tell you
How I'm feeling right now
What my emotions really are
At first, I was actually very conflicted
I do have some
worldly views that influence me.
I sometimes feel
whether
on this path of pursuing love,
it seems like
there's a bit of a discount on me.
Is it that
so-called value
or some practical things
will affect
how the person in front of me judges me?
I actually have these doubts too.
But after I told you about it,
your reaction was beyond my expectations.
Then I started to feel
maybe I was overthinking things.
Maybe sometimes
I'm too cautious, too careful.
I've already seen
your passion and sincerity.
So why should I keep avoiding it?
So I'm really grateful to you.
To a large extent,
you've eased my anxiety.
You've also helped me face you
more openly.
There's one more thing.
Our marriage,
and the child I have with him,
I don't think this will affect
how I see you as a person.
Your good qualities,
your shining points,
your charm,
I still think they're wonderful.
Help!
Don't look at me like that.
I can't take it.
Thank you.
I'm grateful too.
Being able to meet you in the cabin.
And here is a small gift.
I want to give it to you.
This is the first movie we watched together.
You asked me
if I collect movie merchandise.
Just like the name of this movie,
I hope you can live
the life you truly want.
And this is the last movie
we watched together.
We haven't finished it yet.
Still not finished.
Let's find a time to finish it together.
Okay?
Okay.
Actually, we're quite similar.
Before coming to the cabin,
I was also a coward.
I was very passive.
I didn't dare to actively accept
kindness from others.
And I often hid in my shell.
So I'm really grateful
to have met you in the cabin.
You gave me the courage to express
my true feelings.
You helped me break through my own barriers.
I'll choose the one next to me.
Princess carry.
My face is turning red.
Go for it, Wanwan!
I haven't even used much strength yet.
That's enough.
When I went out, I made
some little desserts for you.
Thank you.
Why are there two eggplants?
One portion can't have scallions.
Smart, boss.
This parrot's build is a bit like yours.
Can I invite you tomorrow
to play tennis and have hot pot?
Sure, of course, no problem.
Then let's go have some fun.
Noob number one.
Noob number two.
I'm really grateful for everything we've been through together.
These wonderful memories, I think
I will cherish them
deep in my heart.
I've noticed that now
we're both very cautious about our feelings.
So I hope
if you're willing,
we can have more time
to keep getting to know each other better.
My feelings won't change.
Facing this final
opportunity,
I must
be brave, and even braver.
I hope she can understand what I want to express.
What I want to say is,
I don't have a physical gift for you today
to give you,
but I did check
the first high-speed train after work on Friday.
If I can catch it smoothly
and get to Beijing,
we can go eat crayfish together.
And then,
well,
I've seen your sincerity and courage.
I don't want to retreat
into that little shell anymore.
I think
I've already gained the ability to be brave.
Thank you.
Thank you for our courage.
Thank you for our meeting.
Thanks.
The moment I expressed my feelings,
I
was so happy.
Looking back now,
I can't remember many of the words.
But I can remember his sparkling
eyes.
The look in his eyes was shining with
affection, fondness, and determination.
The moment I looked at him,
I felt I should work hard too.
I also want to pursue that kind of determination.
You deserve it, dear, you deserve it.
That sentence is really worth watching over and over.
Friday.
Friday high-speed train.
Such plain words
must be truly genuine.
Xia Xia.
Xia Xia also has a very versatile temperament.
Right?
I'm very nervous.
I don't know what he'll say.
I don't know in the next five minutes
or ten minutes
how my emotions will be affected by
what kind of ups and downs.
Because everything is unknown.
Because I have no idea
what he thinks.
Are you cold?
Is it cold?
Let me fasten it tighter for you.
Fasten it tighter.
Why are they so adorable together?
Those two.
They're kind of sweet.
It's the last day.
Then let me say a few words.
I feel a little shy.
A bit timid.
I didn't expect to suddenly get nervous.
After spending over twenty days in the cabin,
the one who left the deepest impression on me,
and helped me grow the most,
is you.
Really?
Yes.
That look in your eyes.
It's hard to describe the feeling between those two.
Actually, the depth of feelings between people
often doesn't depend on time.
It depends on quality.
When you were drawing me,
we were still having conflicts then.
But at that moment, I thought,
in such a short time,
how could you understand me so well?
Especially when you were staring at me then,
I just
didn't dare look at you.
If you don't wrap yourself up too tightly,
maybe
someone will truly walk into your heart
and understand you.
Thank you.
After our first interaction, I realized
you're a really good person.
Every time you blush,
and still look at me,
I feel like there's a pool of spring water in your eyes.
But I end up dodging.
But I can't help but want
to take a few more glances.
You said
I'm a coward.
Actually, I don't want to be a coward.
But sometimes
I'm so scared I can't get out of it.
In these last few days,
experiencing life together with you,
I've felt your courage.
She just jumped right down.
She's so cool.
Your sensitivity,
you're wonderful.
Yes, you're really wonderful.
And I find that the more time I spend with you,
the more I think you're great.
Saying things like this,
and your strange sense of humor.
Am I sexy or not?
To put it bluntly,
it just means you don't have feelings for me.
Don't fall into the trap.
Don't dig a pit for me.
Digging over there.
So you have no emotions?
Where are your emotions, Teacher Luo?
You have your day too, Luo Junfan.
And you're a crybaby.
Yes, I'm a coward.
You're a crybaby.
During this experience,
you told me you had some feelings for me.
So today, I also want to express
that I have a lot of feelings for you.
Is there something you want to say to me?
I think in Xishuangbanna,
I saw a more vibrant side of you.
A you with flaws.
I don't think being perfect is a good thing.
I saw some imperfections.
That's when I felt you were more real.
And then, in these past few days,
I never thought I could still be with you.
So relaxed.
I didn't expect it either.
I didn't expect it.
That we would still have some similarities.
I originally thought
I had already let go.
But
Just like yesterday,
when you suddenly said you wanted to take me climbing again,
I felt
like a beautiful circle had been completed.
Everything returned to zero.
As for those
arguments,
regrets,
guilt,
and tears,
let them
stay in Shanghai.
Where exactly are we going?
You still won't tell me now?
A place you're familiar with.
It's so high.
You start jumping down from here.
Is that okay?
Maybe this is
where you should have come down half a month ago.
Doesn't half a month feel like a lifetime ago?
There was a period in between that felt really long to me.
Have you already eaten?
Yes, I did.
How do I draw this?
Why did you come to see?
Just take it off.
Then I went on a date by myself.
Such a slow five seconds.
A bit faster.
These days,
it's definitely you who made me see myself clearly.
And you are my biggest regret here.
Then let's go out and have fun tomorrow.
Okay.
One, two, three.
I want to make you really happy today.
It's really great.
Is it fun?
It's fun.
Press one.
I didn't expect it to be you.
Hello everyone, I'm Xia Xia.
Xia Mengting.
Hello, my name is Luo Junfan.
That day we went to do voice acting.
We mentioned dubbing a line.
It was about whether to date now or not.
If you're willing,
I'd really like to start with you
as good friends.
Just like I wrote in my letter
What I recited in the mountains before
After everything reset to zero
As for the future
Let’s talk about it when the time comes
Because that’s how feelings are
They can slip away if you’re not careful
I truly think you
are really, really wonderful
You deserve to be chosen with certainty
What I want to tell you is
Don’t be afraid of love
You are great
And you are worthy too
Your hands are so cold.
I want to exchange our preserved flowers with you.
I want to display your preserved flower.
And see it in my new home.
Let's have a hug.
Xia Xia is really amazing.
Come on, friends.
We've watched two confessions now.
It was quite an emotional ride, wasn't it?
Starting from the first couple,
Wanwan and our Kaka,
yes,
the most powerful line
I think is
"I've already seen
the high-speed train ticket to Beijing for Friday."
She is very brave.
Before, when she asked Yonghao,
I thought she was very insistent
about not being able to leave Shanghai.
But this time,
she took the initiative
and came up with this solution.
When you really like someone,
nothing is an obstacle.
Yes, exactly,
when you truly like someone,
distance is no longer a problem.
Yes.
I really like their confession.
I can't take it.
I'm getting obsessed.
You already are.
Aren't you?
I really
am obsessed with them because
I think they're so down-to-earth.
In my opinion,
as long as the two of them work hard,
their happiness is
within reach.
Yes.
Can you imagine what life together would look like?
It's realistic.
Right.
And Beijing doesn't just have crayfish.
There are lots of other delicious foods too.
Take your time and enjoy.
Visit a few more times.
Comrade Lao Luo was the first to express himself clearly,
saying he has strong feelings for you.
Yes.
Right, and then the initiative in the conversation
actually shifted to Xia Xia.
That's right.
Xia Xia took the initiative to say that sentence,
to let everything start over.
Let it stay in Shanghai.
It feels like she is more
no matter what the outcome is,
she can accept it calmly.
Yes.
So I feel that
she has already taken back the initiative
into her own hands.
That's impressive.
Let's continue to see
after a night like this,
the confessions of the other couples.
Who is this?
Liang Tian is here.
So beautiful.
What a beautiful night view.
The moon is so bright and round tonight.
I said before
that we would part ways on a full moon night.
I hope I can say
what I truly feel inside.
Who is it?
Yonghao.
You can tell right away it's Yonghao.
I want to try one last time.
To say the last thing
that I should say from my heart.
So I won't have any regrets.
Cold, isn't it?
It's okay.
I'm used to it.
It's just that
today is our last day at the cabin.
We're getting ready to leave.
I've thought about it for a long time.
I feel there are some things
that should be said before we leave the cabin.
Otherwise, I might never get the chance.
Maybe from the first day I met you,
I was captivated.
So I ended up misunderstanding things myself.
Maybe I also brought you
some trouble or guilt.
Because I'm truly grateful to you.
You helped me let my guard down.
But
I've already shared all that with you anyway.
I'll keep looking for you to chat in the future.
Your hometown is either Hong Kong, China
or Macau, China, I'm guessing.
Yes, that's absolutely right.
I hope you have such a happy night that you don't even need aromatherapy.
I actually really like it when you wear glasses.
Really?
This is my favorite song.
They formed a band called 2Cellos.
What are your thoughts after that?
My thoughts after that...
At this stage,
maybe the balance in my heart
leans a bit more toward Yunting.
You two are wearing couple outfits.
So before I leave,
there's one last thing
I want to say to you,
Liang Tian, I like you.
You are someone who deserves to be loved.
You should always look forward to love.
Yonghao is a very warm and cheerful
and understanding boy.
Being with him is very relaxing and comfortable.
I'm really grateful that you just spoke so honestly
and shared your thoughts with me.
Actually, whether or not you said these things to me,
I still wanted to tell you today
just two words: thank you.
But I really mean it, it's not just being polite.
Or anything like that.
When I think back to when I first entered the house
and now as we're about to leave,
I truly feel
that the way you took care of me
was really attentive in every way.
I'm truly very grateful for how well you looked after me.
How about boiling an egg?
Yes, I'll fry an egg.
I'll help you.
Thank you.
Yes.
There's hot water.
Here, pour this.
Okay.
Thank you.
Let's have something to eat.
Dried strawberries, thank you.
When it's cold, hot, hungry, or thirsty,
you always notice.
How about making some mixed noodles? It's really quick.
It's delicious.
Sure.
Let me get it for you.
Thank you.
You're not wearing shoes.
It's fine.
Put your shoes on quickly.
I'll take the apple to your room for you.
And the hot water is ready.
Shouldn't you take your medicine?
It's okay, your guardian is here.
Thank you.
Have fun.
I think I can tell the difference
between being touched and having feelings.
We can be great friends.
But not lovers.
Love is a magical thing.
It's impossible to explain.
Yes.
As a friend,
I truly think
you deserve someone better.
I hope from now on you'll learn
to always put your own feelings first.
Don't neglect yourself.
I really think you are
a friend worth having.
And actually, I also prepared
a small gift for you.
I noticed your glasses
both pairs
seem to be damaged to some extent.
One time was at the sports meet,
and the other was when you went out to play basketball.
So I bought you a new pair of glasses.
Thank you.
I hope these glasses
after you put them on
will not only help you see clearly
the road ahead and the world around you
I also hope you can
always see your own heart clearly
To love others, you must first love yourself
Okay, got it
Alright
Thank you
Can I have a hug?
Sure
Alright, I'm leaving
Goodbye
She kept emphasizing the word "friend" to me
She made it very clear
Honestly, that's a good thing for me
Making our relationship so clear
means there won't be much burden between us later
Looking back at every step
The moon is so round.
I think Yunting might come.
I hope he can be a bit braver.
But I don't know what he'll say.
I'm both looking forward to it and afraid.
But no matter what the outcome is,
I hope I look beautiful.
To welcome whatever is about to come.
Xiao Hu is here.
When I got the message,
of course I wanted to confess to Liang Tian.
To tell her how I feel.
And then listen to her feelings.
Aren't you cold?
I'm not cold.
So beautiful, really so beautiful.
Then I'll speak a bit faster today.
It's okay.
Take your time, organize your thoughts and speak slowly.
I'm not cold.
Xiao Hu, don't let us down.
Okay, let me give you a pot of flowers first.
A basket of flowers.
Thank you.
When I saw it, I thought
I was especially happy.
I hope it can bring you some joy.
There are also some blue elements.
They happen to match your dress today.
It's perfect.
I hope you like it.
Thank you.
The second little gift.
There are two little Bichons.
Actually, I searched all over Shanghai for this yesterday.
I kept looking everywhere.
And finally, I found one.
A smaller Bichon.
But I think it's really cute.
And its clothes can be taken off.
You can hang it anywhere.
And the second one,
is also a Bichon.
But it's a bigger one.
So cute.
I'm a Bichon.
A companion dog.
Yes, a companion dog.
So Bichons really need
someone to be there for them.
After I finished work today,
I was lucky to find it.
I think it's fate.
When I saw it,
it reminded me of that day
when we had our first date.
That was also a fateful opportunity.
So I feel
it symbolizes our destiny together.
Go home with big sister.
Do you want to go home with big sister?
Be happy and joyful.
Thank you.
Super cute.
Go home with big sister.
Next,
there are some things I want to share with you.
But because my ability to express myself is limited,
I wrote some notes.
That's okay, I understand.
Well then,
Liang Tian, I think you are
an open and honest person.
Like that time after you met up with Yonghao,
you even made a point to come to my room
and knock on my door,
letting me know you were giving me space,
and also letting me know what you were thinking.
And I also think you are
someone with a very unique and interesting
soul.
You like drifting,
racing,
playing arcade games,
you can play instruments,
you like singing,
playing the ukulele,
and you can compose music.
You are someone with a very rich life experience,
a person
like a girl carrying
lots of candy in her pocket,
but you are also happy to share
these colorful candies with others.
These are all the reasons
I think you deserve to be loved,
and also the things I like about you.
Standing here at this moment
also means
our time in the cabin is about to end
but it's also when we leave the cabin
and return to the start of real life
I want, in real life,
to see the real you
and I hope you can see
the real me
After we leave the cabin
I'm really looking forward to
us going to eat hotpot together
going to see a play
we can go to an amusement park
we can also enjoy
a day like retirement
That's interesting
So comfortable
So nice, there's a sunset
Handsome side profile
You look good in every photo
So what I want to ask is
would you be willing to take this relationship
into our real lives?
You must have
gathered a lot of courage to say all this
I'll answer you in a moment
I'm a bit nervous
Right? Yes
Okay
I also prepared a gift for you
The gift I prepared for you is
a penguin
This is a baby penguin
Thank you
And the pompom hanging on it
is the one you made
This is from that day
This pompom was handmade by me.
I only made this one.
It represents
my impressions of you in two moments.
This penguin represents
when you said you were like a penguin.
You said penguins are
family-oriented
small social animals.
They are quite devoted.
And they also
stay with one partner for life.
When you said this,
you were sitting to my left
and then you turned right
and looked into my eyes as you spoke.
At that moment, I felt
this boy has such a deep
understanding and belief in love.
So this penguin is for those
gentle, deep eyes.
And this little pompom
is for the day you got off work
and ran to meet me at our date spot.
I saw that from running,
your hands were red from the cold.
Good evening.
You made it just in time.
Your hands were all red.
It's okay.
So this little pompom is a gift for
the hands that bravely ran to me that day.
Those hands.
Actually, after coming back from Xishuangbanna,
my emotions have been very turbulent.
It's just that...
I tried to be brave, and then
for some reason,
I became afraid.
And maybe I got a little hurt.
It left me not knowing what to do.
I've always thought
that courage is a truly
wonderful quality in this world.
An adult's courage
is never about charging forward without hesitation.
It's more like taking one step and pausing three times.
You take a step, then stop for three.
But the direction is always forward.
I feel like neither of us
has that so-called fearless drive.
We both seem to move forward, then pause.
You really are outstanding.
In every way, compared to me.
I think you have a very obvious glow about you.
Our time in the house is almost over.
I hope to quickly
give the remaining time in the house
all back to you.
Hello.
I'm back.
My old crush.
You finally have that title too.
Both of us have moments of hesitation and
struggle.
But in the end
we can all bravely take another step forward.
Are you free tomorrow or the day after?
I want to ask you out.
And have a good talk.
That feels great.
Teacher, help!
It's like this thing has to get out of control first
and then we try to control it.
It feels so good.
My own thought is
I want to continue this relationship.
And work on it together.
This relationship.
Okay.
But as of today, I feel
we've both been pretty brave.
I still want to be a brave person.
So I can bravely tell you again
I like you.
Today, my act of bravery is
I can sincerely say
those four words
which are "I like you."
Because that's truly how I feel.
And there's one more gift.
On the day we went to the Arctic,
you also asked me,
when was the last time I went to an amusement park.
I said it was in 2019.
I went to Universal Studios by myself.
Then I thought,
the next time I go to Disneyland
or Universal Studios,
I hope I won't be alone.
I hope there will be two of us.
So I hand-drew
an invitation card for Universal Studios.
Her gifts are all so special and cute.
Thank you.
Would you like to go to the amusement park with me?
I'd love to.
Sure.
Looking forward to it.
We're both the type who are shy about expressing ourselves.
Giving this ticket
means that after leaving the cabin,
we'll have a stronger bond.
The year on the ticket is 2025.
I hope we can go together as soon as possible this year
and experience it together.
I'm really looking forward to
us nurturing this relationship in the future.
I have one last request.
Can I put my clothes back on? It's so cold.
Of course.
Be careful.
I've finished saying all this
in the best way I could.
This hug really...
Thank you.
For the time we've spent together in the cabin,
thank you.
I'm so glad I came here.
I hope none of us ever doubt
our ability to love,
or our worthiness to be loved.
Don't doubt yourself like that.
We will definitely
find much happiness and love in life.
My bro Hou is about to perform his talent.
Hou bro.
Nervous, really nervous.
Of course you're nervous.
No matter what,
I'll be there
on the last day in the house
to confess to her.
From the moment I firmly chose her,
from that moment on,
I've been working towards this goal.
I hope she can accept me.
I hope in the end there can be
the happiest outcome.
They're all so beautiful.
You can't hide the look in your eyes when you like someone.
Yes.
Hello.
Um, I...
This guitar has been gathering dust for a long time.
And I...
I finally found
the girl I really want to sing to.
Is this what you've been practicing in the house?
Is it?
Yeah.
A little...
A little nervous.
Don't be nervous.
"I'm Really in Love with You"
The lyrics of this song
feel like every line
is something I want to say to Wo Wo.
Let me give you a little round of applause.
You did great.
Sorry, Wo Wo.
It's just that in this little room,
you have to put up with bad sandwiches,
and then
here you also have to
listen to not-so-great music.
No,
it's actually pretty nice.
Better than I imagined.
Really.
Thank you.
Your encouragement means a lot to me.
And then,
I have so many
feelings I want to express to you,
but let me tell you something practical first.
I wrote
a
signed agreement with three rules.
I hope you can always believe
that my feelings for you will always be this passionate and sincere,
just like the high fever you had a couple of days ago,
never going away.
From now on, I will
work hard to learn how to cook the dishes you like.
Of course, if I don't cook well,
you can still put it
in the fridge, just like the sandwiches in the cabin.
Let it stand in the fridge as punishment.
From now on, I'll listen to you on the small things.
You can make a fuss whenever you want.
As for big things,
I'll listen to you too.
But if you can't handle it,
just lean on me.
If we get the chance to live together in the future,
I'll take care of cooking and laundry,
and all the other chores like mopping the floor.
You just need to eat and sleep.
And play games.
Don't worry about me.
After all,
a real man can endure hardship
and it's okay if he can't always stand tall.
We can argue, but never go to bed angry.
No breaking up in the heat of an argument.
No being mean to you or saying harsh words.
I'll never let you lose track of me.
I'll take you to
collect countless moments.
The moment a train whistles,
the moment lightning splits the sky,
the moment a blue whale leaps out of the sea,
the moments of sunrise and sunset.
My signature is on this.
You can add the rest.
Okay.
There's one more gift.
This is for you.
Two "Fly As You Wish" cards.
We can exchange them for plane tickets anytime.
From now on,
there won't be any long-distance issues.
I will
always be by your side, wherever and whenever.
He's just that kind of person.
His sincerity and courage
really moved me.
Hello.
Hi.
Judging by your expression,
do you have an appointment?
I just feel
that in this world, there's no script.
Maybe it's not perfect,
but it's absolutely genuine.
As long as I can talk to one person
and make things clear, that's enough.
Are you willing to
take another step forward?
Then nothing else matters.
Hello.
Nice to meet you.
Me too.
Here.
I've washed my hands.
Should I stick it here?
This spot, right?
Yes.
He's such a great guy.
Thank you.
I also want to use all my courage to reach his true heart.
This...
Then I'll accept it.
I prepared something for you.
A little kangaroo.
Look at this kangaroo.
First of all,
it actually looks a lot like you.
It's a cartoon version.
I know what real kangaroos look like.
I know.
Fighting kangaroos.
That's right.
But the little thing it's holding
could be said to be
the child inside your heart,
or just you yourself.
Your true inner self.
When we were eating
pork ribs with rice cakes that day,
I realized something.
You said when you came to Shanghai,
what you wanted to eat most was pork ribs with rice cakes.
But actually, you never told me
how much you wanted to eat it.
Why didn't you ever mention it to me?
In the end,
I'll definitely find a chance to take you to eat it.
I can feel that
in our relationship,
you've always been
putting my needs and thoughts
first.
And you often
neglect yourself.
I hope that from now on, no matter what,
you can
remember to value yourself
and acknowledge your own needs.
Truly, first of all,
to love others, you must love yourself first.
You need to
know how to protect yourself.
Like the image of a very strong kangaroo,
but it has a very
fragile
and vulnerable little heart that needs protection.
So I want you to remember this.
Thank you.
Lastly, I still have
one more thing I want to say to you.
It's that I
last night,
didn't sleep even at four in the morning.
Then I went out for a run for an hour.
Today,
to make myself look better today,
I even bought a face mask.
I drank two cups of coffee today.
Ate three fried eggs.
I also went to buy a rice cake.
Because I really love eating rice cakes.
When I left the house, I wore the wrong clothes.
So I went back to change.
But after getting in the car, I realized
I was wearing the wrong shoes too.
So I went back again
and changed my shoes.
But no matter what, I still made it here.
Why am I telling you all this?
I want to say
I like you.
I don't think I've ever looked into your eyes and said
it while looking into your eyes.
I really, really like you.
So, will you be my girlfriend?
Will you be my girlfriend?
Okay.
Can I give you a hug?
From now on, I will definitely
protect you well.
I think this is the
best thing I have ever seen.
I think
this is the most beautiful scene in the world.
I wasn't a particularly brave person before.
But this time,
meeting Wo Wo
made me feel
that at my age, in my thirties,
if I don't have the courage this time,
there might not be another chance.
It's because this person gave me courage.
The right time,
the right person.
For me,
it's truly
very charming and moving.
I'm a little happy.
I think Xiao Hou
before he said "I like you,"
what he said before that
about wearing the wrong clothes,
wearing the wrong clothes, the wrong shoes,
and how to tell you all this,
that kind of nervousness felt so real.
It's like being
carefully and tenderly liked by someone.
Held in the palm of their hand.
I thought when he mentioned those three rules earlier,
I already felt
I still couldn't find any flaws in him.
And then he said all this afterwards.
That really hits home.
Sincerity truly moves everything.
Guo Guo is also very touched.
Xiao Hou's way of expressing love
is very humble.
Guo Guo said, "You're willing to love me so humbly,"
but in my love,
I won't allow you to be humble.
Yes.
A lot of people actually really enjoy
this kind of humble love from others.
Yes, they might say, "Alright,"
"I'll enjoy the privilege of love in front of you."
Yes.
I'll just take advantage of you
and your deep love for me.
I'll just be your queen like this.
But for Guo Guo, this is true love.
No.
You can't love me in such a humble way.
Those two are truly a perfect match.
Their love is truly mutual.
I think Teacher Hou
also met the right person.
Really.
Yes.
He was so lucky to fall in love at first sight.
And then he met her.
And just now, for a moment,
I had a feeling.
Everyone also noticed
that in today's whole confession,
there were two lines both said by the girl.
That is, "Love others by loving yourself first."
Yes.
And in that moment,
the word that suddenly popped into my mind was
This season is all about a strong female lead.
Yes.
The women in this show
show
their own strength.
I'm willing to take the initiative to see you,
to feel you,
to respect you.
It's that feeling of being gentle
yet powerful at the same time.
It's like being wrapped up and protected.
Yes.
That feeling.
Just now, Tiantian felt the same way.
Including her analysis of Xiao Hu,
which was actually quite accurate.
But she
was still willing to take that step.
So I think her energy
is very strong
and very brave.
You might wonder,
what does courage mean to you as an adult?
Actually, there are many forms of courage.
Sometimes, it's about forging ahead without hesitation.
Other times, it's about moving forward and pausing along the way.
I think combining these two
is the definition of courage for someone who is somewhat mature or more mature.
It's one way to define courage.
It means being very resilient.
What resonates with me the most is that
for me personally,
in my own romantic experiences,
I might not have been hurt before.
I've imagined
that if I had many romantic experiences,
I might actually find it
harder to meet someone
I could truly trust.
I think I'm lucky because
when I didn't have much experience,
I met such a person
who was the right one for me.
But I think
adult relationships
are more often
filled with difficult experiences.
These can make people afraid to love.
When you think about all they've been through,
and then see them standing here,
speaking to the person in front of them,
it feels even more touching
than a first love or anything like that.
It's even more moving.
It hits even closer to the heart.
Yes.
What is adult courage?
After going through a life full of scars,
you still choose to hold on to hope.
After all the ups and downs in love,
you still believe in love.
So I want to use
a quote from Goethe's book.
Knowing that life is hard
still loving life
Yes
this is the courage of adults
I think
these semi-mature guests
will make those
who once had pure courage
even more confident
Yes
Even if I face setbacks in the future
I will still have a brave heart
I can love myself
and I also have the energy to love others
Yes
I think our viewers in front of the screen
can also gain strength from this
Even if you go through some hardships
or experience things that leave you battered
it doesn't matter
as long as you are willing to believe
then you will have the strength to move forward
Yes, that's right
The power of what we believe in
Now it's time for the lock segment
Teacher Xia has a lock now
It's locked
Teacher Xia, come on, Teacher Xia
I'm also in this segment
I haven't appeared for a long time
Can someone tell me where it is
Just look for the one with the most.
Isn't that you?
She did it on purpose.
Can someone tell me
where mine is?
It's right here.
And it's the most, too.
Tell me where mine is.
Is it that obvious?
Let's have Guangguang say a few words first
about their first time locking.
How should I put it...
Suddenly feeling deep.
Thank you, Tencent Video.
Thank you, everyone.
Thank you to all the brothers and sisters here.
So, after locking, it's
definitely Chun Ye.
She gets it right every time.
Let's invite Teacher Du
to present the certificate to the winner.
What a big certificate!
I'm so jealous.
This is awesome.
Thank you, Teacher Du.
Let's give a round of applause
and welcome this season's final speaker, Zhang Chunye,
to share her thoughts.
There are a few things I'd like to say.
Because just now, everyone was talking,
and Teacher Du also mentioned
that he hopes those watching the show
can then
go on to live their own lives well.
I'm very grateful
and the reason I love this show
is because
every time we discuss something,
I always do my best
to take the good things
and put them into my actions and practice.
And I've truly benefited from it.
So I feel
it brings me
many experiences of happiness.
So I think
you really shouldn't just watch,
but also put things into practice.
And finally,
I'd like to use
a short poem that I really love
to briefly share
with myself,
and also with everyone here, as encouragement.
Sing,
as if no one is listening.
Dance,
as if no one is watching.
Live,
as if today were the end of the world.
Love,
as if you've never been hurt.
This is my favorite.
Was that a bit sudden?
People on TV
Meet-and-greet
Is it this sudden?
Teacher Du prepared some snacks.
Thank you, Kaka.
What's this? Is this giving out sweets?
Are we handing out sweets now?
They're giving out sweets on the spot.
Thank you.
Hello, Brother Hu.
Hello.
Thank you.
It really feels like coming home.
What?
You drew this?
It's so beautiful.
Brother Hu.
Thank you.
Stars.
Yes, stars.
Thank you.
Perilla, peach, and ginger are just sweet.
Okay.
So you two are...
You're mainly in charge of socializing, right?
He's mainly in charge of carrying bags.
Brother Zhang.
Nice to meet you.
Welcome, Yanxing.
Long time no see.
You've lost weight.
Lost weight.
You look good today.
Friends, let's sit down first.
And I know everyone has a lot of questions.
Let's chat slowly.
Come on.
Come, let's welcome our lovely Half-mature Family members.
Couple holding hands version
Pictionary
Holding hands
I just love this kind of segment
Yeah
It's also four characters
The next part is
They hugged
That confirmed they're together now
So far
I've never felt
That he ever said
Anything not so nice
Actually, there isn't
I said I'd secretly come find you
I want a kiss
Kiss
Back to school
Time to go back
Going home
Turn into a penguin
Today I can take Wo Wo back to Qingdao for a visit.
This place really is...
You grew up in a big city.
So, are the crayfish tasty?
I still haven't bought the high-speed rail ticket.
Let me make an announcement here.
This callus on my hand,
I've been picking at it for two months.
Right now, I want to say to myself,
Xia Mengting, you're pretty amazing.
Whenever I'm hesitating,
I always think of your courage.
Your performance,
The obvious nervousness,
Teacher Hou,
Although it's not perfect,
it's very sincere.
There were no sneaky moves behind the scenes.
Mainly, you just didn't notice me.
How did you finish Yunting's beef noodles?
It's fine.
Let me tell you,
Later, Hu Yunting made me a big pot.
I ate it for five days.
Did you add preservatives?
No.
Bro's got some skills.
Still able to play the guitar at a time like this.
This guitar will be put away and forgotten after this.
You look really beautiful when you laugh out loud.
It's something worth cherishing for a lifetime.
A wonderful memory.
Can we ask questions now?
Ms. Wo,
Is there anything I can say?
Now we're living under the same roof.
I need to keep working hard.
To be worthy of how good she is to me.
Brother Hou, what should I do?
At the peak of success.
Anyone want to be the third wheel with me and Lao Wan?
This works.
The one where I really shined.
What the heck?
What is this?
Anti-burnout.
Me.
Rip... rip the comic guy.
You really don't want to admit it, do you?