Hey. So many things in hands.
Where are you going to take them?
Did you not hear?
I'm asking who would you
take all these stuffs to.
They're for Tee.
Tee?
That sweet looking guy?
What a shame.
That person could have been me.
Why does it have to be you?
Even if it's you.
I ain't gonna carry things for you.
Please move out of the way.
I'm in a hurry.
Wait.
Could you help me check my bicycle?
There's noise coming out of the bicycle
all the way up here.
What is the issue?
I don't see anything wrong
with the bicycle.
Stop fooling around.
I'm going back to Tee.
One word, Tee. Another word, also Tee.
Let me try once and I'll never forget.
Let me go now.
If you don't want any problem.
Fine.
I'll let you go this time.
Next time,
Who will be the one
that won't let go?