Shit.
Who is it?
Damn, close people...
Phupha bro, Tee or Wan.
Close people.
Wan...
Yout fate is hanging on a thread.
I can see what's coming.
Take a closer look at people around you.
Who else can be using honey wax?
Honey wax.
The tablet.
These death, and also the honey wax on the corpse.
They must involve with honey wax for sure.
Chok.
I'm just a delivery guy.
When I arrived,
she's already dead.
Moving corpse?
Red mark on the breast and the most
important is honey wax on the nipple.
Honey wax.
Chok.
People around you...
is the most frightening.
They're pretending to be a good guy.
But this village never got incidents like this.
There's honey wax around nipple.
Shit.
Corpse got red mark on the breast.
I'm just delivery guy.
People around you.
Will you have time to come see me?
Before that time comes, you probably...