(Beauty and Mr. Romantic)
Ko Pil Seung!
Pil Seung!
Who do you think you are?
Who are you
to steal everything I have?
What now?
What is the meaning of this?
Move.
Do Ra!
You punk!
(Episode 43)
Jin Dan, why are you here?
- Gosh, what happened to your face?
- My goodness.
Pil Seung, was it you
who punched him?
Who are you to throw punches at him?
Please stay put.
What happened?
It was a one-way assault
by Mr. Gong.
- What?
I'm not the only one
who threw punches.
Just look at my face.
But you threw the first punch.
All the witnesses
said the same thing.
There they are.
Pil Seung, my gosh.
- Pil Seung!
- Hey.
- Are you all right?
- Goodness.
I'm fine.
- Hello, Chairman Gong.
- Hello.
What on earth happened?
Why did a fight occur
between Ma Ri's uncle and Pil Seung?
I'm sorry.
My brother was out of line.
Going around throwing punches
like some neighborhood thug?
Jin Dan, you're a member
of the Gong family...
who will eventually lead us.
So how dare you go around
acting like some common goon?
Was I supposed to do nothing...
when he would soon take
everything from me?
You saw how Jin Taek was.
He couldn't care less about me.
Auntie, you can imagine
how frustrated he must've been.
This is too upsetting.
Jin Dan, you listen to me carefully.
The fight isn't over.
What? What do you mean by that?
We all have skeletons in our closet.
Find anything you can
on Ko Pil Seung to discredit him.
With that,
I'll have the adoption canceled.
I refuse to hand over what we have
to the Ko family.
Hey. I called to ask
how Pil Seung was doing.
He's resting in his room.
I never knew Ma Ri's uncle
would once again attack Pil Seung...
like this.
I know he's a hothead
and that he has a temper,
but this is wrong.
Ma Ri's dad gave him an earful.
It won't happen again,
so don't worry too much. All right?
Sure, Sun Young,
we'll talk in person.
You're having a field day,
aren't you?
Why did you hang up?
You should've talked more smack
about my son.
No one spoke ill of him.
Besides, he misbehaved.
His actions are justified.
Should he sit idly by
and let you take everything from him?
Are you condoning the assault?
Violence can never be justified.
Jang Soo Yeon.
You really have it all, don't you?
You're inspiring.
What was that?
You must be thrilled...
to be able to adopt your son.
Never have I come across
a vixen as cunning as you.
Let me ask you this.
I bet it was always your plan...
to eventually adopt your son.
- Hong Ae Kyo!
- You! The skies have eyes,
and one shouldn't live
her life this way.
For making me shed tears of blood,
you'll shed just as many
down the road.
Have you even thought about
how Jin Dan must feel?
You should've talked your husband
out of adopting Pil Seung.
How could you jump on the bandwagon
and make this mess?
Jin Dan has always been fond of you.
Just you wait and see.
You'll pay for this.
Pil Seung, are you all right?
Yes, I'm fine.
I bet the ordeal startled you.
I'm good,
but Mr. Gong keeps coming after you,
and I don't know what to do.
I didn't go with you
to the police station...
because you told me
to head home, but...
Was it all right without me there?
Everything was fine.
Besides, you're an actress...
and shouldn't get mixed up
in such scandals.
You will continue to stay out of it
no matter what happens...
between me and Mr. Gong.
How can I when this is my fault?
It's not.
There's another issue between us.
I'll explain it some other time.
Also,
I'll solve it all one by one,
so don't worry about anything.
Got it?
Sure. I got it.
Thanks, Pil Seung.
Don't be silly.
I told you to put your trust in me.
Pil Seung.
Now that I remember who I was,
I've been worried about
being outed as Do Ra,
and the thought of people
recognizing me has been terrifying.
But on the other hand,
it's nice to be able
to talk to you...
about such things.
Do Ra.
I mean, Ji Young.
You have me by your side now.
So don't be scared. All right?
Sure.
You know what?
Even when it's just the two of us,
I won't call you "Do Ra."
Ji Young.
You're Ji Young, not Do Ra.
You're Ji Young,
so nothing bad will happen.
Okay?
Okay, Pil Seung.
Yes.
Auntie's right.
He can't beat me. I'm a Gong.
Yes.
Everyone has a dirty secret or two.
I'll do whatever it takes
to find his.
It's not over until it's over.
Darn it. My pretty face.
How many times has he punched me?
How should I crush him?
Do Ra!
Hang on.
When Pil Seung yelled at Ji Young,
he said something like "Do Ra."
What am I thinking?
He wouldn't call her "Do Ra."
Hang on,
Ji Young never called me by my name.
But she calls Pil Seung by his.
The more I think about it,
the more annoying it is.
Shoot.
How was I booked for a beverage ad?
Tell me about it. Isn't it great?
You're being offered
a lot of money too.
- For real?
- Yes.
They'll pay you well.
What's taking them so long?
- Oh, hello.
- Hello.
Hello.
Mr. Gong. What are you doing here?
This is my company.
I suggested we hire Ms. Kim
to model our product.
Yes, that's right.
We work with Mr. Gong,
and we called you
because he insisted on...
working with Ms. Kim.
I apologize.
I'm grateful for the offer,
but I can't accept it.
Goodbye.
We had no idea
this was Mr. Gong's company.
You made things awkward by releasing
a one-sided engagement announcement.
It wouldn't be right
to shoot an ad with you.
I have no choice
but to support my actress's wishes.
Goodbye.
Kim Ji Young.
Let me ask you something.
Mr. Gong.
What do you think you're doing?
Hey. Stay out of it, punk.
What?
Mr. Lee. Wait in the car.
I'll be right out.
Are you sure about that?
I'll be watching you.
Sure. Watch all you want.
Keep watching.
Darn you.
Do you have more to say to me?
Yes. I have a lot more to say.
You wanted us to work things out.
You wanted to get back with me,
and then you wanted out.
Why do you always
want things done your way?
Go and ask any good psychiatrist.
When ending a relationship,
one needs time to get closure.
So even if you want
to end things with me,
you need to give me the time
to get over you, right?
I need to be with you
while I try to move on.
I can't do that.
Why not?
I'm dating Director Ko Pil Seung.
How can you be so shameless?
Why?
Did you fall for him...
because you heard
APP Group's chairman...
would adopt him
and make him his heir?
Because you think
he'll inherit the company?
Wake up, Ji Young.
You're going after the wrong guy.
Pil Seung is a Ko. I'm a true Gong.
As long as I exist,
Pil Seung will never take over
APP Group.
The company belongs to me.
Come back to me
while I give you the chance to.
I'll take you back.
I can't believe
the nonsense I'm hearing.
What? "Nonsense?"
- Did you talk down to me?
- What about it?
Am I not allowed to talk the way
you speak to me?
Hey...
Why are you acting like this to me?
Put a hand on your heart
and think why I'm doing this to you.
Think hard.
What am I to think?
What did I do to her?
Darn it.
Is she the same Ji Young?
She dropped the dialect
and got a makeover, but...
I don't think
she's the Ji Young I once knew.
She's totally different.
Why do I have the chills?
Why did you ask to see me in public?
What if Jin Dan catches us together?
He has no time to mind us.
He has a lot on his plate
and can't care about us.
Sang Gu. I need you to move
somewhere else right away.
Why? Sun Young's a great cook,
and I often drink with Hyun Chul.
I like how comfy the place is.
You can't care about food and drink.
Do you know who they are?
They're our sworn enemies.
Their son stole Jin Dan's spot
as the chairman's adopted son.
He's the biological brother
of our brainless Ma Ri.
Who? Hyun Chul's son?
How can his son be Ma Ri's brother?
Then did Sun Young have a fling...
with Chairman Gong Jin Taek?
No.
Ma Ri's mom abandoned him
at their door after giving birth.
What?
The son
Chairman Gong's wife kept hidden...
is Hyun Chul's son?
Yes.
That's why you need to move out.
When they caught us together,
I managed to say we were cousins.
I don't think they bought it.
Things will get really bad
if people realize we're dating.
You need to leave that place.
Goodness.
Sang Gu.
Sang Gu. Are you in?
Hey.
You're in.
My wife cooked a pot...
of delicious spicy rockfish stew.
Let's have some soju. Come on over.
No, thanks. I'm not in the mood
to have spicy stew with you.
Why not? Is something wrong?
Hyun Chul.
I never pegged you as such a man.
I don't care
how hungry for money you are.
How could you take advantage
of your own son?
What are you talking about?
I heard all about it.
You allowed the APP Group family
to adopt your son.
How could you...
send him to the woman
who kept him a secret for 30 years?
Don't you have pride?
Do you love money that much?
So, how much did the family offer?
What are you talking about?
You can't go and say
whatever you like.
Do you have a death wish?
- You punk...
- Get your hands off me.
You punk.
What?
He said
that you took advantage of your son?
Yes. He said I had no pride
for sending him...
to the woman who left him with us.
He said I did it for money.
I don't believe it.
Did he really say that?
My goodness.
Is that man out of his mind?
I hate him so much.
- I hated him from the start.
- Right?
Why would Sang Gu...
make such a fuss over Mr. Gong
when he isn't even his son?
Is he siding with them...
because Ae Kyo's his cousin?
Goodness. You'd think
Mr. Gong was actually his son.
What? Cousins?
Sang Gu and Mr. Gong's mom
are cousins?
Yes, apparently,
but I don't think so.
Sun Young and I caught them...
eating ramyeon together.
I asked if they were first loves.
They both strongly denied it.
Sun Young.
You heard that too, right?
Mr. Gong's mom
suddenly started stuttering.
At first, she called him
"Honey, Sang Gu."
Then she said he was her cousin.
I mean,
who calls their cousin "honey?"
Goodness. In my opinion,
they're definitely dating.
Yes, I agree. Cousin, my foot.
Goodness. Who cares?
I see. Now, I understand
why Sang Gu lashed out at you.
That must've been why.
If Sang Gu ends up marrying
Mr. Gong's mom later on,
Mr. Gong will become his son.
Is that why he did it?
Mom, that makes total sense.
That must be it!
My goodness.
If that's really true...
I'm so baffled
that I don't even know what to say!
Oh, boy. I should tell Sang Gu
to move out.
I can't believe
he said I took advantage of my son.
How dare he run his mouth
like that? Gosh.
How much time does he have
until his lease expires?
Two years.
What? Two years?
Does that mean I have no choice
but to see him every day...
for the next two years until
he moves out of his own accord?
Darn it! My gosh.
Oh, boy. My goodness.
What happened?
I swear, I put them here.
Did a ghost take them or what?
Where did they all go?
Oh, gosh.
I was planning to use them...
to buy Ji Young...
a ring, a necklace, a bracelet,
a fridge, and even a TV
when she got married.
That's why I collected them
one by one.
Did they suddenly get feet
and walk away?
Or did they suddenly get wheels
and disappear? Oh, dear.
- Hey.
- What?
Are you sure
Grandma really had gold?
Maybe it was just her imagination.
My goodness.
I'm wondering the same thing.
No. I swear I had them.
I really did!
Yes, she did.
I saw her take them out
to clean them once in a while.
Oh, right.
I took a picture of them
a while ago just in case.
Here.
Hey, is this real?
This much gold
would cost quite a bit.
Why did she have to
take a picture of them?
They won't suspect me, right?
If I get caught,
I really will get kicked out.
Where could they be?
We've searched through
the entire house.
Yes, that's right.
I was worried a thief might sneak in
at night and steal them,
so I wrapped them carefully
in a black plastic bag.
I swear.
- A black plastic bag?
- Yes.
My goodness. Did you perhaps think
it was garbage...
and throw it out?
What? I did take out the garbage
yesterday.
Oh, no!
That black plastic bag. I think
I threw it out with the trash.
Move! Oh, no!
- For real? My gosh.
- Grandma!
What do I do? This is crazy!
I already checked every bag.
It's not here. Oh, no...
It's not here. It really isn't here.
This is our trash.
Hey, leave it. I'll tidy up.
Gosh, it stinks. This is crazy.
Oh, dear. It stinks.
Hand it over.
You!
It was you, wasn't it?
I bet it was you.
Gosh, Mom.
Why are you being like this?
When I was admiring my gold,
you came into my room...
and were like,
"My gosh. Is this gold?"
"Is this real gold?"
Then you tried biting them...
and asked me to just give you one.
Mom, when?
When did I say such a thing?
I've never seen any gold here!
You've never even seen it?
So, it wasn't you?
No!
How could I throw out gold
that I haven't even seen?
Besides, why would I throw out
real gold?
Oh, dear.
Then...
Then I must've thrown them out.
Oh, no. What do I do now?
You can do it!
I'll give it a go.
How is it? Are you all right?
Yes, of course.
Amazing!
How will you come down though?
Amazing.
- What do you think?
- You're good.
- Right? Aren't I cool?
- Yes, that was awesome.
- What?
- Are you crying?
Hey, why would I cry? It's just...
I'm just sweating.
It wasn't even scary.
Do Jun, I had so much fun today.
I had a great time too.
You must be tired.
You should go inside.
What?
Just go inside, like this?
What? Aren't you tired?
Don't you remember what today is?
What is today?
You really don't remember?
It's our 30th day as a couple.
Hey, you actually keep track
of these things?
Yes, and I'll keep doing it...
because every day with you
is so precious...
and feels like a miracle.
Ma Ri.
That was a kiss
to celebrate our 30th day!
Really?
This is good.
Anyway, why did you suddenly
call us here, Ma Ri?
Oh, right.
I have an important announcement
to make.
What? You have
an important announcement to make?
Yes. Pil Seung really is going
to become my brother now.
I mean, he was already my brother,
but now that he's becoming
your son on paper too,
I feel like
he's wholly my brother now...
and that we've become a family.
It makes me very happy,
so I wanted to celebrate it.
And I have an important announcement
to make,
so I wanted to treat
all of you today,
but how come Dad isn't here?
It's such a bummer.
He suddenly had a client arrive
from overseas.
Ma Ri, what is
this important announcement?
Have you got a boyfriend?
Pil Seung, how did you know?
How did I know? Ma Ri, I know you
like the back of my hand.
So, tell us everything about him.
Don't leave anything out.
Okay. That's why
I called you here anyway.
Ma Ri, is this really true?
Yes, we've been dating
for over 30 days now.
What? It's been 30 days?
Hey, how come you didn't tell me?
Well, I really wanted to tell you
but held myself back.
They say you shouldn't pop
the champagne too soon.
What? You know that saying?
Anyway, what's he like?
Hey.
Other than Mr. Park, you don't
really have any guy friends.
Mr. Park told me
you weren't seeing anyone.
The truth is, it is Mr. Park.
It's Do Jun.
What? It's Mr. Park?
Mr. Park? You mean,
your driver and bodyguard?
But I think you like him more
than he likes you.
That's right. I like him more.
Is it that obvious?
Yes, it's so obvious.
Hey, Ma Ri. You're blushing now.
Hey, stop.
What? Why are Ma Ri and Mr. Park
holding hands?
What did you say?
Honey, so you knew about it?
I only found out about it today.
They've been dating for 30 days.
Honey, what have you been doing?
She's been seeing Mr. Park
for 30 days,
and you had no idea?
As a driver,
Do Jun does his job well,
and he's a good guy.
But I've never considered him
as Ma Ri's future husband.
At first, I was surprised too.
But, honey.
Let's look on the bright side...
for Ma Ri's sake.
I was wondering
why she had been in a good mood,
and it must be because of Do Jun.
If you think about it,
he truly cares for her.
Do Jun told her
he'd protect her forever.
Men will say anything
to seduce women.
Honey, please.
Have you already forgotten?
They first met
because Do Jun showed up...
to protect her.
But on top of everything,
Ma Ri likes him and is happy.
I'm thrilled to know
that she has a boyfriend.
Aren't you?
I'm also excited to know
she's seeing someone.
But why did it have to be
Mr. Park of all people?
I would've found
a nice young man for her.
Honey.
We went out of our way
to find someone for her,
but it hasn't been easy.
Mr. Park only works for us
because of his financial situation.
He used to study abroad
and is courteous,
smart, and kind.
I believe
he's a diamond in the rough...
with a lot of potential.
I get it for now.
We'll let it play out.
Still, be absolutely clear
with Ma Ri,
and don't let the feelings deepen.
She's only allowed
to hold hands with him.
Also... No, wait.
I'll need to sit down with Mr. Park
and tell him myself.
I know you're biased
when it comes to your daughter,
but this is wrong.
One would laugh at you right now.
Unbelievable. Why did it
have to be him of all people?
My gosh!
What kind of a nightmare was that?
I had dung fall on me from the sky.
Did it have to land on my face?
Hold on.
Doesn't that symbolize a jackpot?
Seeing yellow dung in your dream
means you'll be hit with money.
But what good would the dream do
when I can't do anything about it?
Darn. This is a day
to sit at the table,
but I don't have the money for it.
That's right. There's her.
Do you mean that?
You won't be against me
dating Do Jun?
That's right.
I was wrong to think that way.
You and Do Jun
are head over heels for each other,
and I shouldn't disapprove.
You have my blessing to date him,
so have fun.
I asked you here to tell you that.
Really? Thank you so much...
for giving me your approval
when I lack in many ways.
Mother, I'll only do better.
I'll love Do Jun
the best that I can.
What does she mean by doing
the best she can to love him?
She's giving me a headache.
Anyway, I...
I approved of you two dating,
but I am so sorry to you...
because our family
has nothing to show for itself.
Why? Why would you
say sorry for that?
It's fine by me.
How can I get this rolling
when she doesn't catch my drift?
You've got to be kidding me.
You see, back in the day,
we used to be well off
but then we lost everything.
I'm trying to get the family
back on its feet,
but it's easier said than done.
I'll need money...
to send Do Jun abroad
to study again...
and later on pay
for his wedding and such.
I see.
Mother, don't worry
about things like that.
I can pay
for Do Jun's education abroad,
and the wedding
will be taken care of...
should he want to marry me.
That being said,
could I borrow some money?
I'm trying to open
a side dish store,
but I don't have the money.
What?
You don't have any money?
That's right.
My gosh.
She actually wired the money!
I had nothing to lose...
and said 200,000 dollars
instead of 100,000,
which she gave me.
If I had asked for 300,000 dollars,
that's what I would've gotten.
My gosh.
No, stop. Don't get greedy.
I can open my business
with just 150,000 dollars alone.
Then I have 50,000 dollars to spare!
What?
Ma Ri wired 200,000 dollars
out of her account?
Yes, sir.
This has never happened before,
so I was wondering
if she was phished.
All right. You're dismissed.
(Chairman Gong Jin Taek)
Ma Ri,
you wired 200,000 dollars
from your account.
What did you spend it on?
Why do you ask?
You know
how people are phished these days.
I know that wasn't the case,
but I was worried.
Dad, I'm not stupid
and will never fall victim to that.
I...
I invested the money with someone
who is precious to me.
An investment?
What kind of an investment?
You don't have to know, Dad.
Anyway, don't worry.
Yes, Mr. Kim. It's me.
Find out
who Ma Ri wired the money to...
and do a background check.
That's right.
Sure.
I'm the first player so...
- Lastly...
- I'm on a roll today.
All in, guys.
Gosh.
- I'll fold. It's your turn.
- Ms. Kim, what's wrong?
- Bring it.
- Same here.
Ms. Kim, why did you fold?
Honey.
Maybe I should come to you.
I should've joined you
when you died.
Or maybe...
I should cut off my hand.
Honey, cut my hand off by the wrist.
I can't possibly call myself human.
How could I have gambled away
all that money?
No.
It can't just be my hand.
I'd be better off dead.
That's right.
I'll die right here.
I'll die.
Die, darn it. Why bother living?
Honey, take me to where you are.
Take me to where you are.
Honey, take me to where you are...
You should go inside.
Sure.
Hold on.
Why is Do Jun entering Dad's study?
Ma Ri, you should head upstairs.
Why? Did something happen?
Is this why you came to work here?
To rob Ma Ri of her money?
Mom, is Dad yelling at Do Jun?
What's wrong with him?
You didn't know?
Do you expect me to believe that?
Mr. Gong,
I have no idea
what you're talking about.
It wasn't me.
Dad, why are you yelling at him?
Ma Ri, we should leave.
Dad, why are you yelling at Do Jun?
Park Do Jun's mom
took 200,000 dollars from you,
and he was in on it.
He has been dating you
to gain access to your money.
He's a con artist!
Dad, that's not it.
Do Jun's not like that.
I gave his mother the money
out of the goodness of my heart.
She said she was opening
a side dish store.
Ma Ri,
did you really give money to my mom?
Yes, I did.
She said she needed some.
Mr. Park, you are fired as of today.
Get out of my house this instant!
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, sir.
Do Jun!
Ma Ri, you can't!
Park Do Jun's mom
took 200,000 dollars from you,
and he was in on it.
He has been dating you
to gain access to your money.
He's a con artist!
Do Jun.
Is it true?
Did you and your mom
target me for my money?
Did you date me...
and tell me you'd protect me...
because I was rich?
You didn't, right?
Tell me you didn't.
- Ma Ri...
- Do Jun,
I know you're not
that kind of person.
So please tell me
it's a misunderstanding.
You're not a bad person.
Right.
I wasn't in on it.
I didn't deceive you.
I didn't date you for your money.
But...
it's true that my mom scammed you
out of your money,
which is why
I can't be with you anymore.
Why should we break up
if you didn't do anything wrong?
Do Jun, what did I just hear?
- Do Sik.
- Answer me!
Well, I...
What do you mean
I scammed her out of her money?
Gosh, Do Jun. You have it all wrong.
I just borrowed the money from her.
Your sister cut me off
from managing her money,
and all I could be was an old woman
who mooched off her family.
I briefly borrowed the money
to start my own business.
It was a way
to stand on my own two feet.
At the risk of his reputation?
Her family called him
a scam artist too.
They accused him
of running a con with you!
Those people are impossible.
No one conned anyone.
She voluntarily gave me the money.
Mom!
Do Jun, please.
Ms. Baek,
where's the 200,000 dollars?
We'll believe everything you say,
so give us the 200,000 dollars
you borrowed from her.
I don't have it.
It's all gone.
Mom.
What do you mean
the 200,000 dollars is gone?
Mom, did you perhaps
gamble away that money?
Don't say it's true.
Please don't say it's true.
Mom, I need to pay that money back.
So please,
give me the money right now.
Give it to me!
Do Jun.
Do Jun, I'm sorry.
I had money on my hands
and wanted to double it.
I mean,
I wanted the 200,000 dollars
to become 300,000 dollars...
but lost all of it.
Afterwards, I went to the Han River
to fall in and die.
I mean it.
I was really on that bridge.
Do Jun, Ji Young, Do Sik,
please forgive me.
You know, I...
I'll earn the money
and pay it all back.
Do Jun, Ji Young, Do Sik,
please forgive your mother.
How could you do this?
It's the police!
Right. Just a second.
Please come in.
What is this about?
You reported gold that was missing.
Yes, I filed the report.
We looked into stolen goods...
and found the gold
that was reported.
It was Ms. Baek Mi Ja
who pawned them off.
Hold on a second.
Did you sell Grandma's gold?
Is that it?
Gosh, I'm sorry.
I'm terribly sorry.
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry...
I'm sorry... My goodness.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry!
Mom.
I was willing to look past
what you did to Do Ra.
But from this moment on,
I'm done with you.
Do Sik, don't say that.
I told you I was sorry!
Our baby brother,
who you love and cherish.
Look at what you did to him.
Our family was ruined overnight,
but our baby brother lived his life
holding his head up high.
He was finally at a place
to be in love and be happy,
but you...
made him look like
a shameless gold digger.
Do Sik, I'm sorry.
Please forgive me this once.
I couldn't possibly live
without you.
Please don't abandon me.
Please forgive me.
Do Sik, please. I mean it.
If I ever gamble again,
I'll cut off my hand by the wrist.
Do Sik, please forgive me.
Do Sik, no! Don't go.
Don't go, Do Sik. Take me with you.
Take me with you.
I can't live without you.
I can't live without you, Do Sik.
Do Sik!
Hey, Ji Young.
Do Sik.
It's 200,000 dollars.
Pay the family back.
Where did you even get
this kind of money?
I received payment...
for the episodes I did
and the ad campaign.
I'm sorry about this.
As your brother,
this burden should fall on me.
No, Do Sik.
That's not true.
Please don't say that.
This is the money my mother,
Baek Mi Ja, took from your daughter.
I apologize instead. I'm so sorry.
Thanks. You can go now.
Sir.
My mother...
wronged your daughter terribly.
I'm deeply ashamed and truly sorry.
But...
Do Jun didn't know anything.
He's innocent.
You can put him anywhere...
and he won't stray
from the right path.
Do Jun didn't do
anything bad or wrong.
What I mean is...
I hope you believe me.
If that's all, you can leave.
You know,
I felt sorry for our mom.
When Dad died,
she was in her mid-30s,
so around my age right now.
She was a young woman
with three young kids.
She had to struggle
and suffer on her own.
It was tough.
Do Jun, you were too young then,
so you wouldn't remember
what Mom was like then.
She wasn't like this at first.
She sold apples and Korean melons
in a market...
and washed dishes at diners.
She had a really hard time.
I saw it all.
I don't know since when,
but Mom started to play cards
with people at the market.
I couldn't tell her...
to stop what she was doing.
I thought it was the only joy
in her dreary life.
Even when Do Ra fell into the sea,
I couldn't leave Mom.
I knew she'd done terribly wrong,
but I couldn't leave her. Why not?
Because...
she was our mom.
I couldn't leave her.
If I had then,
your lives now wouldn't be
as tough as they are.
I dragged you down with me.
I'm sorry. It's all on me.
No, Do Sik.
It's not on you.
We no longer have a mom.
I'll pretend Mom died too
when Do Ra did.
That's what I'll think from now on.
You should do the same.
Do Jun.
Do Ra.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
("Seoul Lady" Is a Huge Hit)
(Love Story of North Korean Spy
Disguised as Fashion Designer)
(Director Ko Pil Seung's a Hit
Abroad Too)
"Director Ko Pil Seung's a hit
abroad too."
"Will he continue his success
with new actors?"
There's nothing but praise for you.
Congratulations.
- Well done.
- Congratulations.
Stop it, everyone.
I'm too embarrassed.
I owe it all to every one of you
who worked hard in the summer heat.
All you actors
and the crew members as well.
Let's thank the viewers...
by working hard to the end.
Let's have another great day!
- Yes.
- Let's.
Let's do it.
- Hey.
- What's that?
Who sent that?
- A truck?
- Free snacks?
I wasn't told about this.
Thank you, everyone.
- Darn it.
- Not him again.
I made a lot...
because "Seoul Lady" was a hit
from the start.
I rented this truck...
so you can have
all the coffee you want.
I even brought along some gelato
I had shipped from Italy,
so have some and cool down, okay?
(In support of Actress Kim Ji Young)
Ji Young,
are you really engaged to him?
It was in the news then it wasn't,
then a correction was released,
so I thought it was just a rumor.
Are you seeing him again?
I'm not. There's nothing between us.
Bring out the panel.
Bring it over here,
so it's more visible.
Mr. Gong.
Can I have a word?
I have nothing to say to you.
Director, I'll talk to him.
Mr. Gong.
Let's talk.
Okay. Let's.
(In support of Actress Kim Ji Young)
Mr. Gong. Why are you doing this?
Why do you keep asking me
why I'm doing this?
How much more must I explain?
I told you last time.
I need time to get over you.
I'm not yet ready to let you go.
Ji Young. As a fan,
I'm here to congratulate you
on the hit...
and help you look good.
Why don't you accept
my sincere intentions?
Even if
your intentions are innocent,
forcing yourself onto someone
is the definition of abuse.
I don't want it.
Why keep doing what I don't want?
What will people think of me
when they see what you do?
I don't want to be misunderstood
because of you.
So please stop it.
I can't stop it.
I told you...
that I'm not done with you.
You'll keep this up, then?
Okay. You give me no choice.
I wasn't going to do this
for the sake of your reputation.
I'll report you for stalking me...
and get a restraining order.
Wait. You'll do what?
I'm a stalker?
You'll report me?
Hey. I didn't hit you, lock you up,
or call you hundreds of times.
What did I do that you'd report me?
I'm just an innocent fan of yours.
I'm a fan.
Hey, you, Gong Jin Dan!
My gosh.
What did you just say?
"Hey, you, Gong Jin Dan?"
How dare you talk to me like that?
I'm years older than you.
Are you on something?
You must be on something.
You don't take me seriously.
Stop this
before I turn really nasty.
If you act like a lunatic again,
I'll report you right away!
This is your last warning.
That's not Kim Ji Young.
She still has Ji Young's face,
but her mind has changed.
She's possessed by someone else.
Mr. Gong tried to sign her
to appear in an ad?
Yes. He keeps spending money
to throw himself at Ji Young.
He's just wasting it.
I don't know what he's up to.
So, what happened?
Ji Young walked out
saying she wouldn't do it.
She doesn't care about him at all.
So now, he rented a coffee truck.
What should we do about him?
I'll take care of it,
so it doesn't happen again.
I'm sorry
to stress you out like this.
I should handle it on my end.
It's fine. Thanks for telling me.
Okay.
I'll go now, then.
Yes.
Thank you.
Kim Ji Young is getting engaged.
Here's the article.
(Gong Jin Dan and Kim Ji Young
Engaged After Dating for 1 Year)
We published a correction...
saying that
the engagement wasn't true.
But the articles keep
getting put down.
And we asked them to delete
the articles about my engagement,
but they just kept going viral
on social media.
Mr. Gong locked me...
in the vacation home.
I want to get away from him.
I'm so miserable around him.
He's already giving me a hard time,
so if he finds out that I'm Do Ra,
I don't even know what he will do.
It really scares me.
Ji Young.
Hey. You owe me an apology
about something, don't you?
You've been on pins and needles.
You've been acting weird today.
Give me your hand.
My hand?
Ji Young.
Marry me.
Marry you?
What are you talking about?
Once the drama "Seoul Lady" is over,
let's get married.
Since the moment I found out
that you were Do Ra,
I've been wanting to marry you.
That is absurd.
How can I marry you?
What's absurd about it?
We met again after many hurdles,
and we love each other.
Besides, I feel like...
we must get married
so I can protect you.
Pil Seung.
You know I'm Park Do Ra.
I am dead.
If everyone finds out
that I'm actually Park Do Ra,
then you're doomed too.
I can't marry you
and expose you to such danger.
I'd gladly follow you
into purgatory...
to be with you.
I told you.
I'd never let your hand go again.
And for me to protect you,
we have to get married.
So I can make sure
no one can hurt you.
I will not let anyone...
mistreat you again.
Thanks for telling me how you feel.
Really, thank you so much.
But I can't expose you
to danger too.
All right.
We will get married, but not now.
Once I clear my name...
and can appear as Park Do Ra again
without feeling ashamed.
We'll revisit this conversation
then.
Okay?
Whether you are
Kim Ji Young or Park Do Ra,
it doesn't matter to me.
I will always stay by your side
no matter who you are.
I'll never leave you alone
and make you lonely.
When you're in danger,
I'll be right by your side,
holding your hand.
So, let's get married.
Why are you so dumb?
Because of me, you might get pushed
to the edge of a cliff too.
Because of me, you might also...
Just answer this question.
Do you love me or not?
I do.
I love you.
Then we're good.
It's all good, then.
Just trust me...
and follow my lead.
Don't worry about a thing.
(CEO Gong Jin Dan)
(Jin Taek)
Hi. What's up, Jin Taek?
You never call me first.
You want to grab a drink with me?
Yes.
All right. Sure.
What's going on?
I don't believe this.
Jin Taek called me to suggest
we grab a drink together?
What is this now?
Does he feel bad
he's adopting Ko Pil Seung?
So he wants to give me
a few more subsidiaries?
Jin Taek!
There you are. Have a seat.
Okay.
Anyway, what's up?
I'm surprised you wanted
to grab a drink with me.
Mr. Ko, you're here.
You can sit here.
Sure.
Jin Taek, what is this?
I thought it was going to be
just the two of us.
You called me here to join you
and this jerk, Ko Pil Seung?
Jin Taek.
I refuse...
to have a drink with this punk,
so the two of you can play
pat-a-cake and have fun.
Drink up and enjoy yourselves.
Sit down!
All right, let's drink.
Once Mr. Ko becomes my adopted son,
you two will become family.
Jin Dan, you'll be his uncle.
If you and your nephew ended up
at the police station again,
it wouldn't look good at all.
It shouldn't happen, you know?
So...
if there are any misunderstandings
or grudges between you two,
I thought
you guys should talk it out.
That's why I called you both here.
He and I are family?
Jin Taek,
let me make this clear to you.
This punk, Ko Pil Seung,
becoming your adopted son.
I absolutely cannot accept it.
You have no say in it,
so it doesn't matter.
It's already been decided.
And once it happens,
you'll become Mr. Ko's uncle,
so be mature about it.
How dare you run your mouth
like that?
Who are you to force me
into becoming this jerk's family?
I don't want to be his family!
Mr. Ko.
I'm sorry.
I guess this was a bad idea.
No, it's okay.
Fine.
Then...
I will do as you say...
on one condition.
And what might that be? Tell me.
My ex-girlfriend, Kim Ji Young.
If he ends things with her for good,
I will think about whether or not
I can accept him...
as a member of my family.
Break up with Kim Ji Young.
Then I'll think about it...
since Jin Taek is asking me
so earnestly.
I...
I have no intention
of breaking up with her.
Also, I'm thinking...
about marrying her.
What? You'll marry her?
Says who?
(Beauty and Mr. Romantic)
You'll marry Kim Ji Young?
Ko Pil Seung, that punk, is the one
who drove you to your death!
Enough with the darn lies!
If that's how it's going to be,
I'll tell the whole world
that she's Do Ra.
Kim Ji Young is Park Do Ra!
I don't want to waver,
but I feel like I'm wronging you.
A marriage should be blessed,
but because of me...
No matter what people say
and no matter what happens,
the two of us will stay strong.
If I can't have you,
Ko Pil Seung won't have you either.