(Beauty and Mr. Romantic)
Ma Ri...
(Episode 24)
Pil Seung...
is your brother.
He's your biological brother.
My biological brother?
What do you mean by that?
What do you mean?
That means I gave birth to you...
but I also gave birth to Pil Seung.
He's your biological brother...
which means you are
biological siblings.
That's why you can't be together.
Do you understand...
what I'm saying?
You gave birth to me
but also Mr. Ko?
Mom, what are you talking about?
Ms. Kim is Mr. Ko's mom.
Besides, if he was my brother,
he would be living with us.
Are you that against me liking him?
Why are you making up
such a ridiculous lie?
Did you think
it would make me give up on him?
Why are you treating me
like an idiot?
I'm not an idiot. I'm not stupid!
Ma Ri,
please calm down
and listen to what I'm saying.
You see, I...
I gave birth to Pil Seung...
and then gave him...
to Sun Young.
That's how he grew up
as Sun Young's son.
You had a baby
but gave it to someone else?
How can you give someone your baby?
Why do you keep saying
ridiculous things?
You see...
The truth is,
I...
I left Pil Seung...
at Sun Young's...
doorstep.
I...
You...
abandoned Pil Seung?
Does Dad know?
Did you abandon him
without Dad's approval?
Well...
Pil Seung's dad...
is someone else.
My dad isn't his dad?
Before I married your dad,
when I was studying in the US,
I had a boyfriend.
But...
he...
He went mountain climbing
and died in an accident.
I was so sad
and I couldn't stand being alone.
So I came back to Korea.
That's when I met your dad.
I didn't...
want to marry anyone.
I'd just lost the man I'd loved.
Then...
why did you marry Dad?
At the time...
My family was struggling.
Your grandpa had to
run for the National Assembly,
but he was almost bankrupt.
I agreed...
to marry your dad if his family
promised to help my dad get elected.
That was when I realized...
I was pregnant.
Ma Ri.
There are details
I can't explain to you.
You won't get it.
I did what I did...
to help my family
and your grandpa...
No. I don't get it.
I don't understand
a thing you're saying.
Ma Ri.
My poor baby.
I'm sorry, Ma Ri.
I feel so sorry for you.
Why can't I give her a ride
when we live together?
I asked her to ride with me.
Did you tell Ji Young off
because of it?
Shouldn't we?
The whole neighborhood
talked about...
how you were always riding together.
An unwed man and woman...
are always riding a car together.
Of course the neighbors
would find it weird.
That's why I pleaded with her...
with all my heart
that she be careful.
I apologize.
I won't carpool with him ever again.
Don't apologize.
Why should you apologize?
Mom and Grandma.
Don't be on Ji Young's case again.
If you keep complaining,
she'll feel uncomfortable
riding with me.
I'm the one who likes her
and wants to be with her.
What did you just say?
What are you talking about?
Didn't you hear what he just said?
Pil Seung just said he likes her.
That's why he gives her a ride.
My goodness gracious.
You're a cunning one, you are.
Miss.
When we asked if you were dating,
you stared right back at us
and said you weren't.
Did you sneak around
behind our backs...
to ride his car and go out with him?
No. We're not dating.
There's nothing between us,
so don't get the wrong idea.
What are you on about, Grandma?
Mom and Grandma.
Did you tell Ji Young
not to like me?
Is that why you avoided me
and said you didn't like me?
Why didn't you say that was why?
Stop it, Director Ko.
How will I look
if you act like this?
I think I should go inside.
Ms. So. Ms. Kim.
We're not dating, okay?
Ji Young. Wait...
Are you making all this fuss
because you like her?
Right now,
it's one-sided on my part.
Don't say anything to Ji Young.
What? "Right now?"
Are you saying...
you'll actually date her
or something?
If she accepts me,
I would like to date her.
Now that I know she avoided me...
because of Mom and Grandma,
I'll talk to her somehow...
and make her like me.
That's all you need to know.
My goodness.
Honey. Mother.
What did he just say?
What did I just hear?
Why are you acting like
you didn't hear him?
He's saying he'll chase
that girl around until she gives in.
Oh, my goodness.
You spoiled him rotten growing up.
"Our dear Dae Chung.
Our dear Pil Seung."
That's how you raised him
and look at what it did to you.
It looks like
you raised him for nothing.
Stop it, Mom.
Ms. So and Ms. Kim...
asked me to be careful.
But now, Director Ko
announced he liked me.
How am I to face his family now?
Are you in?
Can we talk?
Oh, gosh. It's Ms. Kim.
I'm coming.
- Hi.
- Hello.
Can we come in?
Yes.
Would you like something to drink?
No, thanks.
Miss.
You said earlier
that you and Pil Seung...
weren't dating.
Are you sure you aren't?
Yes. We aren't dating.
I wrongly thought
that you'd seduced Pil Seung.
I'm sorry I thought that about you.
I apologize.
It looks like...
my Pil Seung likes you.
I'm sorry to ask,
but please don't fall for Pil Seung.
Even if he asks you out,
please say no. I'm begging you.
Pil Seung is my whole life.
I'm not saying this
because he's my son,
but he's kind, upright,
and did well in school.
He has no flaws whatsoever...
Oh, dear.
I shouldn't
speak like that around you.
I understand what you're saying.
Director Ko and I aren't dating,
so don't worry.
Ji Young.
I'm so relieved...
to hear you say that. Thank you.
I heard the project
you were working on...
with Pil Seung is coming to an end.
With that coming to an end,
it would be uncomfortable
and awkward...
to keep crossing paths.
If you find a new place,
tell us
and we'll return your deposit.
Okay?
Okay.
The number is unavailable.
Ji Young. Are you not picking up
because you're angry?
Come outside.
We have a lot to talk about.
And things to explain.
The wind is wafting gently.
It's nice and cool.
Let's take a walk.
Come outside.
(Developer options,
Media transcoding settings)
I wonder...
where Do Jun is and what he's up to.
Gosh.
I must become successful...
and bring Do Jun back home.
Do Sik, come and sit down.
Do Sik. Did you...
break up with that old spinster?
Are you sure you two are broken up?
That's what I told you. We broke up.
How many times
do I have to tell you?
Do Sik, stop fooling around...
and try to look for Do Jun.
You're his older brother.
Aren't you worried about him?
How can you even sleep at night?
Mom, I stay in touch with Do Jun.
I even see him from time to time.
What kind of person do you think...
Darn it.
What?
You see Do Jun from time to time?
Why did you not tell me?
You should've told me the truth.
You know how much I miss him.
How could you do this to me?
I was going to tell you later.
Still, you can't be like this.
Hey, you should call him
and tell him to come right away.
Tell him to come over this instant!
But Do Jun isn't...
ready to see you yet.
What?
Did Do Jun say that?
That's why I didn't tell you.
I didn't want to upset you.
Then let me at least
talk to him on the phone.
I want to hear his voice.
Fine.
Do Jun, it's me.
Hey, Do Sik.
Why are you calling at this hour?
Do Jun! Do...
Actually,
Mom wants to talk to you.
Can you try talking to her
this once for me?
Give me that.
Do Jun, it's your mom.
I'm sorry. It's all my fault.
So can you...
please move back in with us?
You know how much I miss you.
Do Jun. What...
Do Jun? Don't hang up.
- Gosh.
- Do...
See? He doesn't want to talk to you.
You should talk to him later.
You need to give him some time.
Do Sik, how is he doing now?
What does he do for a living?
Mom, Do Jun looks really healthy,
and he looks just neat.
I'm sure he's doing well.
- Are you serious?
- Yes.
He says he's doing fine,
and he just wants us to keep well.
Do Ra and Do Jun.
One died, and I don't even know
how the other is doing.
I will...
be sure to get back on my feet.
I'll succeed no matter what...
and bring Do Jun back.
- Gosh, Mom. Why are you crying?
- Seriously, I'll...
That's enough.
My gosh.
Is it good?
Yes. It's really delicious.
But why aren't you having one?
Well... I don't like ice cream.
It's too cold.
I see.
Your legs hurt?
Do you want me to carry you
on my back?
Yes, I do.
Okay.
All right.
Do Jun, you should study hard.
I will make a lot of money
so you can study abroad.
- Understand?
- Okay, Do Ra.
- Do Jun!
- Do Ra!
What happened to you?
You said you'd be
too busy with studies to come.
I said that to surprise you.
My baby brother.
- I missed you so much.
- My gosh.
Do Jun, you know
who I earn all this money for.
Do Ra.
I'm a fool.
I didn't even know
you liked ice cream...
until I grew up.
No, it shouldn't be happening.
Pil Seung...
The baby is crying in fear.
That's just not right.
How could she do that?
How...
How could she do such a thing?
What? Ma Ri.
What's wrong, Ma Ri?
I don't like you, Mom.
I hate you, Mom.
I can never forgive you.
I will hate you until I die.
I'm scared of you.
I really...
hate you, Mom!
Ma Ri.
My gosh. Ma Ri!
- Ma Ri.
- Ma Ri!
- My gosh.
- Ma Ri.
- What do we do?
- What's wrong with her?
- Ma Ri.
- Ma Ri!
It looks like
she was in quite a shock.
I got her some tranquilizer,
so she will be fine.
We better keep an eye on her
for the time being.
Thank you, Dr. Kim.
Thank you. All right then.
I'm sorry.
I feel really bad for you.
You know Ma Ri is different
from other girls.
I understand she did something
she shouldn't be doing.
And she caused Sun Young's family
a lot of trouble.
But you were being too harsh on her.
How could you slap her
in the face like that?
You didn't have to be so emotional.
We've never hit Ma Ri
while raising her.
And she got slapped in the face.
I mean, by you of all people.
I understand
why she's being like this.
Still, I believe...
Ma Ri will be fine. Don't worry.
I'll come home after the meeting.
If something's wrong with Ma Ri,
call me immediately.
I'll see you later.
Ma Ri, when did you get up?
You should've called for me.
Are you feeling better?
Ma Ri, I made beef porridge,
your favorite.
Please have some of it.
You must be hungry.
I searched online yesterday
and found out...
that a three-day-old baby...
is only...
this big.
It's even smaller than Chi Chi.
How could you have abandoned
a baby that small?
Ma Ri...
I couldn't even dare
to throw Chi Chi out.
I wouldn't be able to sleep...
if by any chance I lost Ru Ru.
So how could you have
thrown away your own baby...
when Pil Seung was so tiny?
What?
Then,
after abandoning your tiny baby,
you lived a normal life...
eating well,
wearing nice clothes,
going on vacations,
and having a good time
with your friends.
How was it even possible?
Ma Ri, please.
I...
don't understand
anything you told me.
You did it for Grandpa's sake?
It was to help your family
that was struggling financially?
How can that be a reason
for abandoning your baby?
If things were that tough,
you should've abandoned the adult...
and not the baby.
Grown-ups...
can walk on their own...
and find food to eat.
But babies...
Unless they're cared for...
They can't live unless they're fed.
They'll die.
You're the worst, Mom.
Get out.
Get out of my room, Mom.
I don't want to see you!
What's going on?
Ma Ri, what's wrong?
Why are you yelling at your mom?
Gosh, Ma Ri.
Why are you this upset?
But being angry isn't an excuse
to treat your mom this way.
Everybody, leave. Now!
I want to be alone.
Gosh, all right.
- Auntie, we should go.
- Goodness.
Ma Ri.
I'm so sorry.
It's true that I can't be forgiven
for what I did.
Ma Ri?
I'm sorry.
It's all my fault.
I did the unthinkable.
Mom.
The person you wronged is Pil Seung.
You should be asking
for his forgiveness,
so why are you apologizing to me?
Say that to Pil Seung instead.
I'm sorry.
Ma Ri, I'm sorry.
I...
love you so much...
that I want to understand you.
But I can't understand you
no matter how much...
I think about it.
I see.
I'm so upset...
that I can't stop crying.
I keep...
I keep thinking about the baby
crying in his basket.
I feel bad for Pil Seung.
He...
deserved better.
Break a leg.
- Got it.
- Sure.
Ji Young, why do you keep
avoiding me?
I haven't been avoiding you at all.
You didn't take my calls last night
or text me back.
I texted you suggesting...
we carpool to work.
You came to work early
just to avoid me, didn't you?
And once I got to the office,
you stayed in the prop room.
Why are you talking to Jae Dong
and not me?
Who do you like? Me or him?
What are you talking about?
Unbelievable.
Never did I expect
this much nonsense.
People will hear you
talking nonsense.
Fine.
We'll talk someplace quieter.
Follow me quietly.
Why do you keep talking nonsense?
I never did such a thing.
More than ever,
I'm talking
with the utmost sincerity.
Are you saying
you were being sincere...
when you told your mom and grandma
that you liked me?
That falls into
the category of nonsense.
How would you telling them
about your feelings make me look?
You being sincere alone
means nothing.
Ji Young.
You like me.
You also...
have feelings for me.
So why do you keep pushing me away?
If it's because of my mom
and the rest of my family,
don't worry about that.
I'll handle them.
So let's not waste time...
being torn or hesitant...
and start dating.
I truly...
like you a lot.
Okay, fine.
What you said is right.
I like you as well.
But your elders
are right about this.
I'm not good enough for you.
You are...
your parents' whole life.
So you're wronging them
by having feelings for me.
Director Ko,
come to your senses...
and find a cool woman
who is on your level.
Ji Young, to me,
you are the best.
I mean that.
Gosh. We can't do this
at our place of work.
Someone might see us.
Let them.
There's nothing wrong about a hug...
between two people
who like each other.
We like each other, don't we?
Ji Young.
It wasn't easy...
for us to finally
admit both our feelings.
Don't think...
about anything else...
and place your trust in me. Just me.
Can I really do that?
Of course.
All you have to do is be by my side.
My feelings for you...
won't change.
Do you mean that?
Are you sure you won't
stab me in the back?
Never will I let go...
of your hands again.
Never.
I'll always...
be there for you.
Ma Ri.
You're keeping me
from going about my day.
I came home today...
after only taking care
of urgent business...
because I was worried about you.
So please...
can you be less angry
with your mom...
for slapping you?
The stunt you pulled
at Pil Seung's house?
You were wrong to do such a thing.
Right?
Ma Ri.
Dad.
Why did you marry Mom?
Why else?
I married her
because I liked her a lot.
Do you...
still love her?
Of course, I do.
I love you and her...
more than anything else
in this world.
Ma Ri.
That's why...
I want you and your mom...
to be on good terms again.
Seeing the two people
I love the most...
upset with each other...
breaks my heart.
Mom's the worst.
I hate her.
Yes, I hear you.
She's the worst!
The worst.
How could she upset you like this?
But that's enough.
It's all right, Ma Ri.
Do...
Do you recognize me?
I've been waiting for you.
I knew we would meet again...
like this.
Cut, okay!
- Good job, everyone.
- Good job.
You all did a great job.
Good job, everyone.
I deeply appreciate...
the hard work you put in
until the very end.
- Good job.
- You did great.
- You too.
I have some good news to share.
"Don't Lie" will not only air
on our network...
but will also air simultaneously
on the streaming service.
Let's wish
for the premiere next week...
to be a success!
- Let's go!
- You all did great.
- Good job, everyone.
- Good job, guys.
- Good job.
Good job.
Hold on.
Ms. Baek, what on earth?
That's a better look on you.
Why would you hide
your pretty shoulders?
Know what makes you stand out
and use that to your advantage.
That's how it works
in this industry.
Do Do, I'm sure you understand
just how much power...
a casting director has.
Yes, I'm aware of it.
I'm glad that you are.
In this industry,
your work will have been for nothing
unless you can grab opportunities.
You only have to do as I say.
Got it?
Sure.
I hope the meal is pleasing enough.
- Allow me to pour you a drink.
- Right.
Thank you.
Do Do, fill their glasses, will you?
What?
Ms. Baek, my gosh.
No one asks actors
to pour drinks these days.
That isn't necessary.
As if pouring a drink
would wear anyone out.
Do Do, go ahead
and fill their glasses.
Goodness. This is how shy she is.
Let me fill your glasses instead.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
Here.
Thank you.
Director,
please give me a call
if any roles open up.
Sure.
Do Do is not only pretty,
but she's a talented actress
and a decent singer.
She's also quite witty.
I could go on and on
about her talents.
Are you also a good singer?
Of course.
Would you like to hear her sing?
After dinner,
why don't we sing some karaoke?
Sure.
Do Do, wait.
You can't just leave.
Not when things are in full swing.
Ms. Baek, this isn't how
I want to be an actor.
- What?
- I hate gatherings like this...
and would rather
keep tackling auditions.
Do Do, once again,
you didn't get a call-back.
When will you make it as an actor
only by auditioning?
I'll try harder.
That's what I'll do.
You'll try harder?
Who in this industry
doesn't try hard?
As if only trying hard
will make you a star.
Everyone works their butts off.
Getting noticed by the right people
is how you build a career.
You can't be an A-list star
by doing nothing.
Fame doesn't fall into your lap.
My professor said
all I needed was my acting skills.
Hey.
I'm doing this
because you aren't good enough.
You aren't a good actor.
I'm not pushing you
just for my sake, you know.
This still isn't how
I want to be an actor.
Do Do, wait!
You can't just walk away.
Not when I spent so much
wining and dining them.
Gosh.
The air is nice and cool,
the ice cream is sweet,
and the moon
shines in the sky for us.
Isn't it nice to walk hand in hand?
As if that needs to be answered.
Since it has come to this,
tomorrow, the day after,
and the day after that,
I'd like to walk with you
hand-in-hand.
You bet we will.
That's what we are.
A couple that walks hand-in-hand.
Oh, gosh.
Why are you sitting here like this?
Are you waiting for Pil Seung?
Give him a call.
I can't do this anymore.
I'll call and ask...
where they are
and if they're together.
Come on. Can you not?
We're home.
- Hey.
- Hey, you...
Pil Seung. You...
Ko Pil Seung.
What are you doing?
Why are you holding hands
in our presence?
Is this a protest?
Ji Young!
Why are you holding my son's hand?
Well...
Mom. Father.
Grandma, Auntie.
Ji Young and I agreed to date
starting today,
so please respect her...
as my girlfriend from here on out.
What? As your girlfriend?
Who says she can be your girlfriend?
Ji Young.
What do you think you're doing?
You said
you weren't dating Pil Seung.
You told me not to worry.
How could you stab me in the back?
Ms. Kim.
I'm really sorry
I couldn't keep my word.
I tried really hard
not to fall for Director Ko,
but I failed.
I'll be really good
to Director Ko...
and to all of you too.
I'll try my best
to make you like me.
And I'll live and work hard
to become a woman...
who is on the director's level.
Could you please accept me?
You want us to accept you?
How are we to accept you?
You're one shameless lady,
aren't you?
There's nothing more to say.
Ji Young.
I want you to move out immediately.
Move out right away.
I don't want to see you again.
Mom.
You have no right to her room.
As long as the contract stands,
as the tenant,
Ji Young has the right to stay.
What?
Ji Young,
how long was the contract for?
For two years.
That means
you have priority for two years.
So Ji Young.
Whatever my mom says,
you don't have to move out. Okay?
How could you say that, Director Ko?
You're upsetting her.
Hold back, okay? Don't go too far.
Okay. I won't do it
if you don't want me to.
Ms. So. Ms. Kim,
Mr. Ko, and Myung Dong.
It's getting late.
I'll go to my room.
I hope you show me some favor.
Please do.
Sleep well, everyone.
I'll walk you back.
Okay.
- Hey.
- Honey.
- Sun Young. Are you okay?
Oh, dear. Darling.
- My goodness...
- What...
My heart's still racing...
and my legs are shaking.
I feel horrible
about how Ms. Kim must feel.
I think your grandmother...
and parents are all shocked.
What should we do now?
Ji Young. It's fine.
You did great today.
Keep it up.
Trust me.
Okay.
I'll trust in you
and keep going from now on.
Good for you, Ji Young.
Goodness.
Ji Young. What is it?
Something crazy good happened...
and I wanted you
to be the first to know.
Since you're my boyfriend now.
That's right.
If you get good news, your boyfriend
should be the first to know.
What is it?
I just got a call from CEO Jae Dong.
Don't you be shocked.
I'll be...
the female lead
in a one-episode drama!
- For real?
- Yes.
Congratulations, Ji Young!
I'm so proud of you.
My goodness.
Ji Young. I have to go to work.
I'll call when I get off.
- Let's celebrate over dinner.
- Okay.
What the...
Gosh...
My goodness.
What did I just see?
We're watching them
with eagle eyes...
and they went and did that
in the garden?
My brother Pil Seung.
Thank you for growing up
to be such a great guy.
I'll be a good little sister
from now on.
As of this moment,
whatever happens,
I'll be on your side.
Ji Young.
I actually felt upset earlier.
What? Why?
How could you forget about me?
Am I that easy to forget?
Oh. I'm sorry about that.
A lot has been going on lately.
The conclusion is...
she forgot about me
because she was distracted?
Ji Young.
This is our last meal together.
Did you make up your mind?
About becoming my girlfriend.
Mr. Gong.
I'm so thankful.
You thought so highly of me,
and let me pay for your suit
with just five meals.
I'm grateful for a lot of things.
But I must refuse the offer to be...
your girlfriend.
Sorry.
Why?
Do you have no feelings for me?
Then why did you say
you'd think about it?
That was because...
you asked out of the blue
during the meal.
I got flustered.
And I'd agreed to treat you
instead of paying for your suit,
and if I rejected your offer then,
it would make
the remaining meals awkward.
I don't believe this.
You strung me along, tested me,
and wasted my time.
Is this a joke?
I should be the one to dislike you.
How dare you reject me?
Gosh.
I apologize.
Thank you for everything so far.
If you'll excuse me...
What just happened?
What did she...
do to me?
Come in.
Ms. Hong.
Kim Tae Hee sent you flowers.
Goodness.
- They're from Tae Hee?
- Yes.
- I'll put them here.
- Okay.
My gosh.
They smell lovely.
Why did she suddenly send flowers?
Tae Hee.
I just got the flowers.
I was about to call you.
What's the occasion?
I was going to meet Jin Dan today,
but he said you suddenly fell ill.
I hope the flowers cheer you up.
Did Jin Dan take you
to see the doctor?
What? The doctor?
What is she talking about?
Mother, is it serious?
Not really. It's just a bad cold.
Tae Hee, thank you so much.
I'll call you later.
Jin Dan, that brat.
He told Tae Hee that I was sick.
What's going on?
My gosh.
Is he seeing someone else?
Mr. Cho, it's me.
Kim Ji Young?
So are you saying
Jin Dan is seeing this hillbilly?
Well... Ms. Hong.
If Mr. Gong finds out
what I've done,
I'll get fired right away.
Mr. Cho, don't worry about that.
I won't let it happen to you.
Thank you, Ms. Hong.
Thank you, Mr. Cho.
You're now dismissed.
He's dating someone
with marriage in mind.
Jin Dan, that brat, must be
out of his mind.
My gosh.
Why does that girl live here?
What is going on?
Sun Young. Come on out now!
My gosh.
Ae Kyo.
Ae Kyo, what brings you here?
What's wrong?
Why do you look so upset?
- Sun Young.
- Yes?
Does a woman named Kim Ji Young
live in this house?
Do you know her?
Kim Ji Young? She's a tenant
renting a room in our house.
Why are you looking for her?
What? She's a tenant?
Are you saying
she's renting the room over there?
Yes.
Hey! Kim Ji Young! Come on out!
Kim Ji Young, come out this instant!
My gosh.
Who are you? I'm Kim Ji Young.
- What? You...
- Yes?
My goodness.
It's you.
You're her.
Hey, you brat!
You darn gold-digger!
How dare you try to seduce Jin Dan?
What do you want from him?
You darn wench!
Why are you being like this?
My gosh.
Who on earth are you?
- Please let go of me.
- Ae Kyo, use your words.
- Stop being like this.
- My gosh.
You darn brat!
Jin Dan is seeing someone
with marriage in mind.
How dare you try to hit on him?
Aren't you too young to sponge off
a man like a gold-digger?
A gold-digger?
What do you mean I hit on him?
I didn't do anything like that.
I don't even know
what you're talking about.
Hey! So this is what you want!
You're following him around...
hoping to get some money
from him like this, right?
Fine. Take this money
and get out of my sight!
But you better
not see Jin Dan ever again.
If you do, I swear I'll kill you.
- Do you understand?
- Ji Young.
Ji Young.
Ms. Hong.
What do you think you're doing?
Well... Pil Seung.
Why are you trying to defend her?
This girl here...
tried to seduce Jin Dan
when he had a girlfriend.
I don't want to hear any of that nonsense!
I want you to leave now!
Get out this instant!
Ae Kyo, you should go.
Let's talk outside.
Just go.
Ji Young.
It's all right, Ji Young.
It's okay now.
Ae Kyo.
Is it true that tenant lady
tried to seduce your son?
Are you sure?
Yes.
Otherwise, why would I have come
all the way here?
By the way,
why is Pil Seung being like that?
Why is he trying
to cover up for her?
Is it because
she seduced Pil Seung too?
Gosh, no. Why would you say that?
Hey. You should
kick her out right away. Okay?
What's all this?
What is going on between
Ji Young and Ae Kyo's son?
I can't believe this.
Ji Young, have some warm water.
Are you feeling better?
Yes.
What happened?
Did you meet Gong Jin Dan?
You know what it is.
I ruined his suit,
so I promised to buy him...
five meals.
We had one meal left,
so I ate with him
for the last time today.
So...
she did all that
because you ate with him?
I don't know.
Mr. Gong asked me out,
but I said no.
So I didn't think...
I would have anything to do
with him anymore.
I had no idea
something like this would happen.
Director Ko.
Nothing happened
between Mr. Gong and me.
I'm serious.
I know, Ji Young.
I believe what you say.
Don't worry.
My goodness. What is this all about?
So are you saying
the tenant lady has been dating...
both Pil Seung
and your friend's son?
Oh, dear. Unbelievable.
I'm at a loss for words.
That can't be it. Maybe
there was some misunderstanding.
Ji Young doesn't like someone
who would do such a thing.
Hey! You can't judge a person
by the way she looks.
She may seem so gentle and naive,
but she's sly enough
to seduce a rich man like him.
That means she's really something.
Pil Seung is being like this...
because he fell for
such a sneaky gold-digger.
Hey, Pil Seung.
I can't let you date that girl.
I was trying to let you
get your own way,
but that brat is just horrible.
Grandma,
how could you say such a thing?
There's nothing going on
between Ji Young and her son.
So please don't get the wrong idea.
What wrong idea?
Are you saying Ae Kyo came here
and made all the fuss for no reason?
Something about her
is really unsettling.
I'm not going to mince words.
You have to break up with her.
Ji Young has nothing to do with him.
They did meet a few times,
but they just ate together
for some reason.
You have to trust me.
And please don't get her wrong.
My gosh.
So what's the reason?
Why would she eat with a man
who has a girlfriend?
Hey. I just don't understand...
why we keep renting out
the room to gold diggers.
Sun Young, we should never...
let a woman move in there again.
Gong Jin Dan.
Why did he want to eat with Ji Young
when he had a girlfriend?
What?
He asked her to be his girlfriend?
Gong Jin Dan, that brat.
What has he got in his head
to do such a thing?
You crazy brat!
Have you lost your mind?
Why did you lie to Tae Hee
just to go out with that hillbilly?
She's such a country bumpkin.
How could you fall for
that country bumpkin?
This is just humiliating!
Mom!
Did you meet Ji Young?
Yes, I did!
I was really humiliated
in front of Sun Young.
How could you be
dating a hillbilly...
who's renting a room
in my friend's house?
Mom, what did you do to Ji Young?
I talked some sense into her! Why?
I said I'd kill her
if she saw you ever again.
- Mom!
- Listen.
Even if that hillbilly seduced you,
how could you
possibly fall for a girl like that?
You stupid fool.
Just end things with her
before Tae Hee finds out.
Mom!
Nineteen.
Twenty.
So this is a thousand dollars.
Hyun Chul,
so how much is this in total?
Don't talk to me.
You're distracting me.
- Okay.
- Hang on.
This is...
50 dollars short of 1,000 dollars.
So it's 9,950 dollars in total.
What?
Oh, right. I guess
she was offering 10,000 dollars.
I don't think she brought
9,950 dollars on purpose.
I guess we lost 50 dollars
in the front yard.
But 10,000 dollars
from a rich family...
seems kind of cheap if you ask me.
Anyway, what should we do...
with all this money?
What else? We should
give it back to its owner.
What?
But we were the ones
who took the time to pick it up.
What are you saying?
Are you kidding me, Mom?
Here you go.
What is it?
It's the money...
Mr. Gong's mother threw at you.
I picked it up.
It's 9,950 dollars in total.
She probably threw
10,000 at your face,
but I can't seem to find
one of the bills.
I didn't keep it,
so don't get the wrong idea.
Search the yard
if you don't believe me.
Why aren't you taking it?
Why should I take it?
I don't need this.
Should we throw money
in the trash, then?
Or should I keep it instead?
The money's yours,
so do whatever you want with it.
Miss,
that is no way to live your life.
Unbelievable.
How dare you...
seduce a man who is already taken?
Ms. So,
I did no such thing.
(CEO Gong Jin Dan)
Hello?
I'm outside your house.
We should meet.
Ji Young.
I heard you met my mom.
Did she act out of line...
or say mean things to you?
If she did, let me apologize.
I don't want
to say anything to you...
nor see your face again,
but I came here to return this.
Take it with you.
It's the money your mom threw at me.
Never in my life...
have I been slapped by money before.
What did I do...
to deserve any of that?
You tell me.
There's nothing going on between us.
So make yourself clear
to your mother...
that there's nothing
going on between us.
Ji Young, wait.
What's your problem? Let go of me.
Ji Young, I like you.
I can't have our relationship
end like this.
Please reconsider where we stand.
Are you in your right mind?
You already agreed
to marry someone else,
so why are you being this way?
If you reciprocate my feelings,
I will break up with her.
What is this nonsense?
You are the worst, you know that?
I have no intention of dating you,
and I hate
how you can be this aggressive.
Kim Ji Young, you.
You...
still don't know
who you're dealing with.
If you date me,
you can have everything you want.
You don't have to live
in that shabby house.
A house, a car, purses, and clothes.
I will buy them all for you.
Hey. That's the kind of person I am.
But I don't need any of that.
Besides, I like someone else,
so don't come looking for me again.
Hey.
I said I liked you!
Let go of me!
So tell me.
Tell me that you like me too!
Gong Jin Dan!
(Beauty and Mr. Romantic)
Mom, I want to share
what I have with Pil Seung.
How can we share
what we have with him?
What? You want to run
a drama production house?
It has been my dream for years now,
and I'm finally
devoting myself to it.
Can I ask for your support?
Never again
will I lose someone I cherish...
just because I lack money and power.
Never again.
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)