(Beauty and Mr. Romantic)
(Episode 36)
Hey. Ko Pil Seung.
How dare you come here?
I'm here to see Ma Ri.
What? To see Ma Ri?
You've got to be kidding me.
Who allowed this?
Hold on.
Did Jang Soo Yeon call you here?
That woman is no longer
a part of this family.
She was kicked out.
So leave this second,
and don't even think
about posing as Ma Ri's brother.
Jin Dan,
that's not how you treat a guest.
I'm the one who asked him here.
You?
Why?
Director Ko.
Ma Ri's room is upstairs.
Let me take you up there.
Sure.
What the...
What is wrong with Jin Taek?
Goodness me.
Who's that? Isn't that Pil Seung?
Did he really ask Pil Seung
to come here?
Mom, what on earth is going on?
Because of Ma Ri,
your brother can't see reason.
She hasn't been able
to even drink water all day...
and has only been asking
for Pil Seung.
That doesn't mean
he should invite him here.
Not when he's the son Soo Yeon
kept hidden for over 30 years.
Is he not thinking straight?
Where's his pride?
Director Ko, how are you here?
I asked him here.
How's Ma Ri?
She must not have the energy...
seeing how she
is constantly sleeping.
Ma Ri.
Pil Seung's here.
It's me.
Are you asleep?
Ma Ri.
Do you recognize me?
Mom.
Yes, Ma Ri.
I must be dreaming.
I can see Pil Seung.
Ma Ri, this isn't a dream.
Pil Seung's here to see you.
Really?
Mom, help me sit up.
Sure.
See for yourself.
It's Pil Seung, right?
Pil Seung.
Ma Ri.
Why are you crying?
I don't know.
Seeing you...
brought tears to my eyes.
Gosh. Why are you crying?
Ma Ri.
Where does it hurt?
You can tell me.
Pil Seung, I...
Right here.
It hurts so badly.
I feel like I can't breathe,
and I can't even drink water.
I didn't know
you were hurting this badly.
I heard you haven't been able
to eat anything,
so I got you strawberry ice cream
which is your favorite.
Really?
The one from the store
we had before?
I think I'll be able to eat
whatever you got me.
I'll have that.
Hold on. Ma Ri, wait.
You haven't even had any water,
so something that cold
could upset your stomach.
Why don't you have some water first?
He's right.
As the chairman said,
have some water first.
All right.
Here.
Ma Ri, were you able to drink that?
Were you able to swallow?
Yes.
It went down
without me even realizing it.
Why don't you take
another sip of water?
It went down again.
Gosh, Ma Ri. Thank you so much.
Pil Seung, can I now
have the ice cream?
Auntie, just look at Ma Ri.
A while ago, she even threw up
the water she drank,
but now she's eating
porridge and ice cream...
because Pil Seung suggested it.
Could they be scheming something
to change Chairman Gong's mind?
Tell me about it.
How did Director Ko manage that
when even Dr. Kim failed?
It's not like he's a doctor himself.
How can Ma Ri be better now...
when she wasn't even able
to drink water?
Auntie, I believe
this is some kind of show.
A show?
Director Ko,
I appreciate what you did today.
I apologize for my actions earlier.
It was harsh of me.
I'm sorry.
Please don't apologize.
It's all right.
If there's anything else you need
regarding Ma Ri,
call me at any time.
Until she gets better,
I'll help in any way I can.
Director Ko, thank you.
I'll get going, then.
Hey, Director Ko.
As if I don't know
what you're playing at.
Your biological mother Jang Soo Yeon
shamelessly moved back in...
using Ma Ri's illness as an excuse.
So what is it that you want?
Now that the cat's out of the bag,
you're trying to take advantage
of the stupid Ma Ri...
to score a position in the company.
Watch your words.
Talk about Ma Ri
like that once more,
and you'll pay dearly.
Got it?
Hey, Ko Pil Seung!
You haven't heard the last of this!
As if I'll let him off the hook
this easily.
Answer us truthfully.
I bet this is a scheme
designed by you and Ma Ri.
What?
What do you mean by that?
Who are you trying to fool?
What are you trying to gain...
by using Ma Ri
to bring your son into our house?
How can you be this audacious?
That's not true.
I'm the one
who asked Director Ko here.
Ma Ri and Soo Yeon
had nothing to do with it.
Chairman Gong,
are you not in your right mind?
I don't care how sick Ma Ri is.
Don't you know who Ko Pil Seung is?
He's the son of this minx,
and he was kept hidden from you.
What other choice did I have
when Ma Ri was sick?
I will gladly invite anyone over
if they can help Ma Ri.
So don't blame Soo Yeon.
Auntie, Chairman Gong must be crazy.
How could he defend
Soo Yeon of all people?
My goodness.
Talk about Ma Ri like that
once more,
and you'll pay dearly.
My gosh.
What should I do with Ko Pil Seung?
Yes.
Right.
Mr. Yoon.
Mr. Yoon!
Yes, sir.
I was reading the script.
Scene eight is set in the rain.
It doesn't have to rain, does it?
I mean, it costs a lot
to hire a sprinkler truck.
Why would you do that?
And this scene here.
Why are there so many extras?
Tell them to film
without them, okay?
And the last scene.
Why would you go to Jeju Island
for this one scene?
Are you insane?
It'll cost a fortune.
Are they using the drama
as an excuse to travel?
If they want to go to Jeju that bad,
they can go on their own dime.
They spend so freely
because it's not their money.
Hey. Go to Director Ko Pil Seung...
and tell him everything I just said.
- Understood?
- Sir.
Director Ko
and Ms. Kim the writer...
insisted they film on Jeju Island.
Director Yoon, who pays your salary?
Very well, I'll pass it on, sir.
Ko Pil Seung.
Nothing will go the way you want.
Let's wait and see who wins.
Even if this drama flops,
I'll bet everything and my life
that I'll get rid of you.
What brought you here...
when you must be busy
writing the script?
I'm here to tell you something
you must know.
Please speak freely.
I've been in this field
for over 20 years.
I've worked
with many production houses,
and this has never happened before.
I was told to kill off the male lead
because they didn't like him...
or to replace him with someone else.
I was even told to delete
an important scene.
If we go over the budget,
then as the writer,
I have a responsibility
to discuss and negotiate.
But I can't stand having someone
who knows nothing about dramas...
demeaning my work like this.
TV dramas are a form of popular art.
My pride as an artist was crushed.
Sir.
Do you also think...
art can be controlled
and manipulated...
with power and money?
Ms. Kim, I understand what you mean.
I'll look into it and handle things.
Ko Pil Seung should be here by now.
Is he with Kim Oh Kyeong
planning a double attack?
Fine.
I'll crush them both.
Yes, Mr. Cho.
What? The chairman wants to see me?
(Chairman Gong Jin Taek)
What are you up to?
What's wrong, Jin Taek?
Chairman, I mean.
What did you do that made
Kim Oh Kyeong come to see me?
Kim Oh Kyeong the scriptwriter?
She was here?
Jin Taek, that woman...
defended Pil Seung
and practically led the protests.
She has a crazy temper
and can't be controlled.
There's nothing to discuss.
I'm taking you off the management
of GOGO Entertainment.
What did you say?
Jin Taek!
Whatever. Fine.
I quit.
I'll just quit.
Darn it!
What's the matter, Jin Dan?
What's this mess?
Jin Taek fired me
as GOGO's temporary CEO.
What's wrong with him?
Why are you so upset about that?
Once you take over
as chairman of APP Group,
you can shut down GOGO or GUGU,
whatever it's called.
Yes, I could do that.
You shouldn't be caring
about things like that.
What did your brother say?
Did he mention the adoption?
No, that's why I'm losing my mind.
Why is he dragging his feet
when he just has to give in?
I'm annoyed to death
and sick of trying to appease him.
Will he even adopt me?
Your brother
tends to overthink things.
I don't get why
when you're his only option.
In any case,
watch what you do and say
for a while.
We'll be back at square one
if your brother gets angry with you.
I got it, okay?
I know that already.
Director,
isn't Mr. Gong harassing
us on purpose?
Why else would he want
a new lead or a scene change?
It makes no sense.
How can we work in this environment?
Ms. Kim was furious.
She said she couldn't work like this.
We risk missing our deadline
if we keep being delayed.
I'll meet with Mr. Gong
and end it once and for all.
Director.
You can stick to the script.
You can go to Jeju Island too.
You're not to change
what Ms. Kim wrote.
- Says who?
- Chairman Gong Jin Taek.
Ms. Kim went straight to him
in his office...
and told him everything.
Chairman Gong got so angry...
that he fired CEO Gong Jin Dan
on the spot.
You can stop worrying...
and film according to the script.
- Is that really true?
- Yes.
I got a call
from the chairman's secretary.
Ms. Kim, it's Director Ko.
You did great.
Concentrate on the script now.
We'll handle the filming
so you don't have to worry.
Keep it up!
- It worked out.
- Jeju Island.
My gosh.
(Incoming call: Tae Hee)
I'd been feeling rotten lately,
but going on a drive with you
lifted my spirits.
You're definitely my vitamin,
Ji Young.
- Your vitamin?
- Yes.
It's a bit hot, isn't it?
Yes.
Reduce the temperature.
(Reduce the temperature.)
You don't have to jump.
Look, Ji Young.
Which finger was it?
I don't know.
It was this one.
Look, I'll do it again.
See if you can guess.
There.
Which finger was it?
This one.
What? My goodness.
You're a genius, Ji Young.
This is no big deal.
Anyway, you got it right.
Go ahead give me a flick
on the forehead.
A flick?
Yes. You won.
Here. Go ahead.
You may not remember...
since the memories are lost on you,
but you and Mr. Gong...
were in love.
Please help your mother this once.
Think about Do Sik and Do Jun.
Please help them this one time.
That's right.
I have to try.
We owe Mr. Gong a lot.
Mr. Gong is...
a really nice person.
I don't like you anymore.
I've decided to like Mr. Gong.
Mr. Gong, thank you
for driving me home.
Get home safely then.
I hate that
I have to leave you here.
Why is it so hard
to let you go home?
My gosh.
What's that?
Isn't that our Ji Young?
What? Shush.
It's her.
But who is the man in front of her?
Isn't that Mr. Gong?
Why is he here with Ji Young?
Ji Young must've lost her mind.
I mean, she has
Director Ko with him.
What is she doing with another man?
- That silly thing...
- Gosh, Mom.
I forgot to buy something.
We should go to the supermarket.
Let's go.
- But...
- Just go.
Ji Young.
What was that?
My gosh. I...
I'm really sorry.
Do you not want to kiss me?
Well...
I don't think...
I'm ready for this.
You don't have to be ready
to kiss someone.
It's just a kiss.
Forget it.
So are you saying I was being hasty?
Fine. I guess
I should give you more time.
Hello?
Director Ko, it's me.
I'm calling you for the last time.
For the last time?
Ms. Lee, what are you talking about?
Ji Young is head over heels
for another man.
So Director, you should move on.
I absolutely had no idea...
she would be like this.
But she changed her mind.
What can we do about it?
Director Ko, I hope
you will find someone better.
Please forget about Ji Young.
Ms. Lee.
Kim Ji Young.
What are you doing here?
It's just pathetic.
Why are you here again?
You shouldn't be doing this.
Ji Young.
What are you doing here?
You're here to see me, right?
But why are you running away?
No.
I...
I didn't come here to see you.
I was in the neighborhood
to take care of something, and...
I think you came here to see me.
Why are you lying?
That's right.
Actually, I came here to see you.
Because I was feeling...
so bad for you.
Feeling bad for me?
Why?
I don't know.
I'm just...
I'm sorry.
Listen, Ji Young.
I'm the one to apologize.
Once you regain your memories,
you'll know why I'm saying this.
I'm aware that I have no right
to say this to you.
But now that you're here,
I have to say it.
Don't date Mr. Gong.
He's not a good man for you.
I shouldn't have come here.
Listen to me, Ji Young.
I'm just worried
you might end up getting hurt.
It's true that you were
going to get engaged to him.
But you had no feelings for him.
I should get going.
Just regain your memories quickly
if you're going to be like this!
Hey.
Ji Young, where have you been?
It's raining now.
Do Sik, what are you doing here?
I saw you in front of the house,
but you weren't coming home.
I had a place to stop by.
Ji Young, are you seeing
Mr. Gong again?
What?
Yes.
Since when?
Well...
It hasn't been that long.
Ji Young, how about
we grab some beer?
Beer?
Ji Young, are you dating Mr. Gong
because you like him?
What?
Well, yes.
Did Mom force you to date him?
Of course not. That's not it.
Really?
Do Sik.
Back when I was Do Ra,
is it true that I was going
to get engaged to Mr. Gong?
Did I really like him that much?
I guess.
You must've liked him
to agree to get engaged to him.
Right, of course.
Ji Young,
are you dating him...
because you two
were almost engaged...
even though you currently
don't have feelings for him?
No, it's not like that.
Ji Young.
then was then, and now is now.
Don't date him if you don't want to.
Why would you force yourself...
when you don't remember
having feelings for him?
I'm all for it...
if you're dating him out of love.
He's a competent man
who found success.
But to be honest,
I'm a little worried
he might find out you're Do Ra.
So don't date him...
if you've only been forcing yourself
to like him. Okay?
Do Sik.
Do you think...
I liked Director Ko more...
or Mr. Gong more?
Do you still have feelings
for Pil Seung?
No, it's not like that.
If I'm being honest,
I still can't forgive him.
He knew you were Do Ra...
but kept you away from us.
That...
Right.
Everyone, may I have your attention?
At 10 p.m. tonight,
"The House of Roses" directed
by our son Ko Pil Seung...
will premiere.
To celebrate
the series' first episode,
steamed eggs will be on the house.
- Thank you.
- Thanks!
Enjoy your eggs.
My goodness.
("The House of Roses")
I want to ruin her face.
Will he then give me his attention?
Gosh, that was entertaining.
You're right. It was entertaining.
Pil Seung, I lost track of time
while watching that.
Pil Seung, I think
it'll be a huge hit.
Gosh, you're a great director.
And how was Ji Young's acting
that good?
Is she really the same girl
who rented our spare unit?
She's even better than Na Bi.
I have a feeling
this will put Ji Young on the map.
Everyone's talking about her
on the real-time chat.
Really?
Pil Seung, I can see
you worked hard on this.
That was golden,
and I think it'll be a huge hit.
Are you sure?
Are you lying to feed my ego?
Gosh. I meant it
when I said it was entertaining.
I wasn't lying at all.
I'm glad to hear
that you all loved it.
Why don't you seem over the moon...
when your show came out nicely?
Is something up?
What? Of course not.
I had a few drinks
with the crew earlier,
and now I'm a bit dazed.
Thank you for enjoying the episode.
- I'll head upstairs.
- Sure.
- You did well.
- We enjoyed it.
Thanks.
Our ex-tenant sure knows...
how to portray
that bitter side of a woman.
Tell me about it. It shocked me too.
Anyway, it seems...
as though their relationship
is over for real...
judging by the look on his face.
Can you not talk about her anymore?
She's someone
who has nothing to do with us now.
She's just another actress.
It's good that they ended things.
Imagine
if they had still been dating.
People would have talked about...
how the director was dating
an actress from his show.
Right.
Where are you coming from
at this hour?
- My gosh!
- Gosh.
Why are you so jumpy?
Did you do something wrong?
Do something wrong?
Isn't this where you live?
You were tiptoeing inside
like a cat burglar...
and then yelped
as if you had seen a ghost.
I didn't want to wake you up.
Is that so?
Hold on. Where were you
at this early hour?
Sorry? Well...
At a Buddhist temple.
You were at a temple?
Why were you there
at the crack of dawn?
You know
how Ma Ri has been sick lately.
I wanted to pray for her recovery...
as well as for the health
and peace...
of our family, you know.
Also, I prayed for Jin Dan
to be adopted...
and to be a good leader
of APP Group.
Our family should only be in bliss.
Gosh. I can't believe
you even thought to do that.
I'm proud of you.
Still,
most early morning prayers
are conducted from dawn to morning.
But you left at night
only to return before daybreak.
Sorry?
Gosh.
What are you doing out here
this early?
- Are you off to work out?
- Yes.
Your mother went
to a temple to pray.
Were you not home last night?
What? Well...
Jin Dan, get going.
Auntie, you should rest.
I should rest as well.
- Gosh, hello.
- Hello.
Oh, right.
You must be our new tenant.
I've been busy with work
from morning till night...
and only got to meet you today.
I should've come by
to introduce myself.
Don't be silly. Just let us know
if anything is bothering you.
- Have a good day, then.
- You too.
Hold on, sir.
Yes?
Haven't we met before?
You seem awfully familiar.
Sorry? I'm not sure...
Wait, aren't you Hyun Chul?
Yes, I am. But do I know you?
It's me, Jin Sang Gu.
What?
Wait. Jin Sang Gu
from Dong Middle School?
That's right. It's me!
My gosh.
Hyun Chul.
Sang Gu, no way.
Gosh, what a small world.
I can't believe...
you ran into your friend
from middle school.
- Tell me about it.
- I know, right?
- It's fascinating.
- It is.
Anyway, are you married?
Do you have children?
Mother, please.
It's rude to ask that these days.
How's that rude...
when he's friends with Hyun Chul...
and used to live
in our neighborhood?
I lost my wife
to a car accident five years ago.
We didn't have any children.
Gosh, silly me.
I'm sorry I asked.
That's all right.
A long time ago,
I remember hearing...
that you moved somewhere abroad.
Right. I just got back to Korea
after living in the Philippines...
for over 30 years.
I moved here for good.
There's no better place
than your homeland.
Of course.
You're young enough to start anew.
Right. That I should.
Goodness.
You must have someone.
What?
Well...
I see.
- Mother, please.
- What?
("The House of Roses" premieres
with a rating of 15.7 percent.)
(Director Ko Pil Seung
proved himself once again!)
(Will Ko Pil Seung and Kim Oh Kyeong
continue to be a success story?)
Director, congratulations.
Director, I appreciate
your hard work.
You all did a great job.
Good job, everyone.
The entire team
should eat out today.
Call everyone over.
Dinner will be on me!
- Kim Oh Kyeong!
- Writer Kim Oh Kyeong!
- Kim Oh Kyeong.
- Writer Kim Oh Kyeong.
Do Jun, over here.
What was so urgent?
Did something happen at home?
Nothing's up.
I called you here to give you this.
What's this?
Meatballs, cucumber kimchi,
jangjorim, and some side dishes.
I made some of your favorite dishes.
Boys your age have huge appetites.
Thank you,
but don't cook for me again.
Why would you thank me in a way...
like you're thanking a stranger?
I eat just fine where I'm staying,
so care more for Ji Young.
All right.
I'll do right by your sister too.
But you're the one
who I feel like I wronged the most.
So just wait a while longer.
Once we have the money,
we'll rent a bigger place.
We'll all live together then.
Also, I'll help you continue
your studies abroad.
Got it?
I'm not a little boy anymore.
I'll take care of myself...
and that includes
going abroad to study.
So don't worry about me anymore.
You're all I worry about though.
I want to do right by you the most,
and you're constantly on my mind.
Also...
Take this.
It's not much,
but spend it on whatever you need.
Mom, isn't this money
Ji Young earned?
If you have more to spare,
spend it on her.
Do Jun, please.
Mom.
Don't make life hard for her
this time around.
Just don't.
I'll get going.
Do Jun, wait.
Do Jun, when we find
a new place to live,
you'll move in with us, okay?
Do Jun...
Why do you keep checking your phone?
It's nothing.
The naengmyeon here is nice,
don't you agree?
Do Sik, do you know
you've been acting weird lately?
Me?
You haven't been
contacting me often...
let alone asking me out on dates.
Even when we're together,
it's like your mind is elsewhere.
Did it seem that way?
That was never the case.
Is something going on at home?
What? Of course not.
Myung Dong, I'm sorry
for making you worry like that.
Well, I'm glad to know
that nothing's up.
Here.
Dig in, will you? The noodles
will go mushy at that rate.
Do Sik, here.
What on earth?
How is it this good?
Is it because you gave this to me?
Gosh.
We haven't been
on a date in a while,
so let's go see a movie.
There's a long list of movies
that I've been meaning...
to see with you.
A movie?
I'm sorry about this,
but can I take a rain check?
I have to get back early today.
What did you say?
You're heading home early...
after having this naengmyeon?
Why don't we order some dumplings?
Myung Dong, I'll be in touch.
Get home safely.
But...
Seriously?
What has gotten into him?
Hold on.
Does he not like me anymore?
This won't do.
Do Sik.
Hey, Ji Young.
Do Sik, I'm sorry.
You always get home early after work
to look after my grandma.
I'm really grateful,
but I also feel guilty.
Why would you even say that?
Of course I should take care
of your grandma in your stead.
- What am I seeing?
- She'll be waiting for us.
Why is Do Sik with Kim Ji Young?
What do you have on your shoulder?
What did I just see?
It isn't with Pil Seung...
or that rich Mr. Gong
for that matter.
Is Ji Young and Do Sik...
living together in that unit?
How... How could this be?
I won't forgive either of them.
No way.
Hey, Myung Dong.
I can't really talk right now,
so I'll call you later.
Of course you can't talk to me
right now.
But you'll meet me this second.
I'm in front of where you live,
so get out here!
Myung Dong, how are you here?
Park Do Sik, you.
Let me ask you this one thing.
Are you...
living with Kim Ji Young?
The same Kim Ji Young
who used to be our tenant?
Yes, you're right
about us living together, but...
You prick.
You...
Don't ever call me again.
Do you hear me?
But...
Myung Dong, wait.
Yes, Chairman Gong.
Right now?
Yes, I'm free.
Sure thing.
Ma Ri, are you still
not feeling well?
You should be eating
and sleeping better by now.
I've been trying to do that,
but I can't help but think
of all these bad things.
When I think about
my parents divorcing,
I get too sad to the point
that my heart might explode.
It feels...
as though I'm alone in this world.
What?
That's why I don't want to eat.
I want to go to sleep,
but I keep waking up.
Ma Ri, why would you think
like that?
Ms. Jang and Mr. Gong
aren't going anywhere.
They will always be by your side.
But...
everything scares me now,
and I don't know
why I'm feeling this way.
Ma Ri.
You also have me now.
You'll never be alone.
Do you mean that?
Will you be by my side?
You won't ever leave me?
Of course I won't.
Then... Then promise.
Okay, I promise.
I want to eat, Pil Seung.
I want to eat,
then go on a walk with you.
Okay, let's eat, then go on a walk.
- Friendship test.
- Friendship.
I won.
- I'll hit hard.
- Okay.
Don't cry.
Gong Ma Ri,
you're better, aren't you?
- I'm not. Let's play again.
- You are.
- Friendship test.
- Friendship.
(Director Ko's "The House of Roses"
Exported to 103 Countries)
("The House of Roses"
No. 1 Worldwide on OTT Platforms)
(APP Group's Stock Price Peaks
Thanks to "The House of Roses")
(Ko's Drama Has Positive Effects
on APP Group-Related Stocks' Prices)
(Chairman Gong Jin Taek)
Thanks to "The House of Roses,"
produced by our subsidiary,
GOGO Entertainment,
APP Group has grown
in status and reputation a lot.
I realized only recently
what an effect one drama can have.
Compared to what we spent
on PR and advertising,
this one drama is showing
much bigger and better results.
I think we should invest
in GOGO Entertainment...
and expand the business.
But GOGO Entertainment
is currently without a CEO.
I'm thinking we should appoint
Director Ko Pil Seung...
as CEO.
(Director Ko Pil Seung)
Ko Pil Seung speaking.
The chairman wants to see me?
The drama...
"The House of Roses."
I really enjoyed it.
I was completely engrossed,
and I hadn't been in a while.
Congratulations on the hit.
Thank you for the compliments.
I owe it to your support.
I got you completely wrong
because of Soo Yeon.
You were misunderstood
when you'd done nothing wrong.
You suffered in many ways
when you shouldn't have had.
No, sir.
I decided to put...
everything else aside
and acknowledge you as a director.
On that note, Director Ko,
I'd like to make you...
an official and permanent CEO
of GOGO Entertainment...
as of today.
What?
How could I...
One drama brought
APP Group's stock prices up...
and practically advertised
our company to the whole world.
You made us go truly global.
I learned through you this time
that a drama...
can have such far-reaching
and powerful effects.
I think that performance proves
you're the only one...
qualified for the job.
But I...
Once "The House of Roses"
is complete,
I plan to leave GOGO Entertainment.
I'm already preparing.
Let's say...
we never had a problem.
Pardon?
That title belongs to Ms. Jang.
I don't think
it would be right for me to take it.
Don't worry about that.
Ms. Jang agreed to your promotion.
She agreed to it?
Director Ko.
I'd like you to become
GOGO Entertainment's CEO...
and produce better dramas
than "The House of Roses"...
so we can both benefit.
Let's improve APP Group's image...
and show the world
what Korea can produce.
From now on, I promise...
to support and invest
in GOGO Entertainment.
What?
Chairman Gong asked you...
to become CEO of GOGO Entertainment?
Is that true?
Yes.
My goodness, and on top of that,
because your drama was such a hit,
he'll give you
company shares as a bonus?
- Yes.
- Oh, my goodness.
Myung Dong, isn't this great news?
To be honest, I thought
you'd get into huge trouble...
because of Ma Ri's mom,
and I was so anxious.
You have no idea.
- Yes, this is such a twist.
- It is.
Pil Seung, you must take the offer.
It's a huge opportunity for you.
Say yes, no questions asked.
I should still ask
what Mom and Dad think.
If you don't like the idea,
I'll reconsider.
Wait.
Sun Young, Hyun Chul.
You won't say no to this, will you?
You shouldn't.
Why refuse such a great opportunity?
Honey, your mother must be right.
Our Pil Seung
must've done really well...
if someone who wanted him gone...
decided to change his mind
and make Pil Seung a CEO.
Sun Young, he didn't just do well.
He did amazingly well.
All the stocks
related to GOGO Entertainment...
are increasing in price.
This is Chairman Gong...
giving Pil Seung something
to bait him with.
Let's be frank.
We know what he is and is like.
He's a chairman of a large company,
and he makes decisions
based on profit and benefits...
as he should.
That's why we don't have to worry...
about grudges or emotions.
Yes, you have a point.
Pil Seung, to be honest,
I was going to tell you to resign
after the drama was done.
But now I don't think you should.
You worked hard
for this opportunity.
Why would you turn down an offer
you earned by doing well?
Your future is at stake.
Honey.
I think he should take the offer.
What do you think?
Well...
Pil Seung's being rewarded
for doing well.
Why would I object or be displeased?
Of course, I'm happy for you.
I am.
Yes, Pil Seung, do it.
Accept the promotion
and do even better.
I'm all for it.
Director Ko.
You're more qualified than anyone...
to take over
GOGO Entertainment as CEO.
Please don't refuse the offer.
I offer my support
as the previous CEO.
CEO Ko Pil Seung.
Take over GOGO Entertainment for me.
Who texted you?
Ms. Jang Soo Yeon.
She wants me to take over...
and offers her support
as the previous CEO.
Soo Yeon said that?
Yes.
(Ko's Drama Has Positive Effects
on APP Group-Related Stocks' Prices)
Where's Ma Ri?
She's out for a walk with Mr. Park.
Is she?
Did you tell Mr. Park...
not to keep her out for too long?
Yes, I did.
They'll stay close to home.
For deciding to make Pil Seung...
I mean, for deciding
to make Director Ko the CEO...
of GOGO Entertainment,
I want to thank you.
Why are you thanking me?
It's the board
that made him the CEO, not me.
And I just accepted it...
based on his performance...
for the good of the company.
So...
don't get the wrong idea.
Okay.
Speaking of which,
now that Ma Ri is feeling better,
I think I should move out now.
What are you talking about?
You didn't close down
GOGO Entertainment,
and Director Ko's dismissal
has been canceled.
This is what
we have already agreed on.
I'll do as you say.
Once the divorce paper is ready,
let me leave.
But Ma Ri still
hasn't fully recovered.
She can't sleep well
without you at night.
And you still want to move out?
If you are okay with it,
I really want to live with Ma Ri.
But me staying in this house...
isn't just right.
It's not like
I want you to stay here.
I'm just doing this
for Ma Ri's sake.
So...
just stay here a little longer
until Ma Ri gets better.
Mom, you're here.
Hey.
What? Did you two fight again?
No, we didn't fight.
Go to your room
with your mom and rest.
Okay.
Let's go, Mom.
All right. Let's go.
Jin Taek!
What's the matter?
Why are you yelling?
Jin Taek is home, right?
Jin Taek! Are you in the study?
What's the matter?
Jin Taek, do you think
this makes any sense?
Fine.
I accept that I was dismissed
as CEO of GOGO Entertainment.
But how could you make that jerk,
Ko Pil Seung, the CEO?
When you were supposed
to kick him out,
how could you let him
take over the company as CEO?
Chairman Gong, is that true?
Chairman Gong.
Jin Taek, what is he talking about?
So...
Soo Yeon's son
whom she had been hiding...
from you for over 30 years...
became the CEO
of one of our subsidiaries?
Are you out of your mind?
Auntie.
GOGO Entertainment was
without a CEO,
so the board voted unanimously
to make him the CEO.
Director Ko Pil Seung
was qualified for the job,
and that was why the board agreed.
End of discussion.
What's wrong with him?
I mean, how could he make
his wife's hidden son...
become the CEO?
I've been trying really hard
to understand him,
but I just can't.
Auntie, can you believe this?
Chairman Gong
must be out of his mind.
What on earth is he up to?
I told him
to adopt Jin Dan as his son,
but he's not taking care of it.
And he's not kicking that witch out.
But he made that witch's hidden son
become the CEO?
My goodness.
I mean, this could be
something serious.
We have to do something
to have Jin Dan adopted.
Yes, we have to.
I don't have a good feeling
about how things are going here.
You should go to meet
Lawyer Kang tomorrow.
Ask him how things are going.
Yes, Auntie.
Mr. Kang, how are things going
about the adoption?
Will there be any legal issues?
There won't be any legal issues.
I told Chairman Gong
about all the necessary procedures.
And I gave him
all the documents needed.
So it's not that Chairman Gong
had a change of heart.
No. Once he makes up his mind,
the procedure won't be
so complicated.
I get it. I appreciate
your hard work, Mr. Kang.
Give me a call
once you hear from Chairman Gong.
Yes, ma'am.
Wait, Mr. Kang.
How are things going
for Chairman Gong's divorce?
The documents are ready,
but they are still
discussing the details.
I see.
Thank you.
All right then.
Yes. It's me, Sang Gu.
We were supposed to meet tomorrow.
Could you not wait?
Did you miss me that much?
Yes.
I just can't get enough
of you, Ae Kyo.
Come on, Sang Gu. Don't be silly.
And I wanted to ask you something.
Ask me? What?
Actually, there's a question
I've been meaning to ask you.
A question you've been
meaning to ask me?
What is it? Just tell me.
There's nothing
we can't talk about now, right?
Ae Kyo.
- Take a look at this.
- What is it?
I think
this is a photo of Jin Dan...
published in a magazine.
Yes.
I cut it out a long time ago,
and I've kept it.
Why did you keep
my son's photo, Sang Gu?
Look at this photo.
Doesn't he look just like my father
in his youth?
So I found it very strange.
What are you talking about?
Ae Kyo.
Do you remember the breakup trip
we went on for the last time?
So I was wondering...
(Special Interview with CEO Gong
of Angel Investment Corp.)
Isn't he my son?
Sang Gu, what are you talking about?
Mom.
Jin Dan.
Do Ra!
Wait, Do Ra!
We love you, Do Ra!
You are my star,
and I'm your moon.
I'm sorry, Mr. Gong.
I can't do this.
I can make two million dollars
after a few hours of a photo shoot.
Can you give me that money instead?
The mistake will be mine to regret,
so shut it and get lost
unless you have two million dollars!
I remember everything now.
Ji Young!
Pil Seung.
(Episode 37 will air August 10, 2024 at 7:55 PM.)
(Beauty and Mr. Romantic)
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)