(Beauty and Mr. Romantic)
So tell me.
Tell me that you like me too!
Gong Jin Dan!
Did you just punch me?
Who do you think you are?
What do you think you're doing?
Director Ko, please don't!
How dare you cause a scene?
Please stop. Let's head back.
Harass Ji Young again like this,
and I will make you pay.
Ji Young, let's go.
(Episode 25)
Ji Young, are you all right?
I bet that startled you.
Right, but I'm fine.
What happened?
Why was Gong Jin Dan here?
He came by to apologize
for how his mother treated me...
at the house.
I didn't want to hear about it
nor see him,
but I had to give back
the money his mother threw at me.
I had no reason to take it.
So I met him to return the money,
but Mr. Gong suddenly grabbed me.
I can't believe him.
Ji Young, I'm glad
nothing happened to you.
Director Ko,
I don't care how angry you were.
You shouldn't throw punches.
Ji Young.
I don't throw punches
whenever I feel like it.
How could I stand by and let him...
assault you like that?
I will take action...
every time he mistreats you.
Director Ko,
I think I'm touched.
As if that should move you.
You're my girlfriend,
so of course I should protect you.
Aren't you glad
you decided to date me?
Don't be alone with him again.
Of course not.
Why would I agree
to meet someone like him?
I haven't been shot in the brain.
What?
Darn it.
Darn.
Jin Dan, you...
Goodness, what happened
to your face?
Who did this to you?
Did someone punch you?
As if. Do you see me
as someone who gets punched?
Then what happened to your face?
Why do you have a busted lip?
And why are your clothes
covered in dirt?
What happened? Tell me this instant.
- This is all your fault!
- My goodness.
- But...
- Get out of my room.
- Wait.
- I don't want to talk to you.
Jin Dan, wait.
Shoot!
Besides, I like someone else,
so don't come looking for me again.
What on earth?
Is she...
dating that punk Ko Pil Seung?
Are you kidding me?
Ma Ri.
I brought you mango cake.
Do Jun, it's me.
Bring the car upfront.
Where are you going?
To Pil Seung's.
Ma Ri.
Why would you go there? What now?
To see Pil Seung.
Ma Ri, why are you being this way?
Mom, why are you startled?
Are you worried...
I might say something
I'm not supposed to say?
That's shameless of you.
What?
Mom, shouldn't you feel guilty
for what you did...
to Pil Seung and Ms. Kim?
But you're only scared
that I might speak out of line.
Is that all you care about?
Ma Ri, please.
I can't just sit around
like you did.
I feel too guilty
for what you did to them...
and must do something.
Hey, Ma Ri.
This is a pearl necklace
for Grandma.
- This is a bag for you, Ms. Kim.
- My goodness.
This is a shirt for Mr. Ko.
These are sunglasses for Myung Dong.
- Why...
- Gosh.
But Ma Ri.
What's all this for?
For raising Pil Seung so well
into the good man he is,
I want to thank you.
- My gosh.
- Ms. Kim.
You're a real angel.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Gosh.
What kind of strategy is this?
Ma Ri. What got into you?
Why would you thank us
and what are the gifts for?
I bought the gifts
as a way to apologize.
I scared you a lot by hiding in...
Pil Seung's closet.
From now on,
that will never happen again.
Because...
I decided to view Pil Seung
not as a man...
but as an older brother.
What?
Grandma, Ms. Kim,
Mr. Ko, Myung Dong.
From now on, think of me
just as Pil Seung's younger sister.
Look.
- This is the male lead's face.
- The TV's too small.
Should I get them a new one?
Did she really say she'd
think of Pil Seung as a brother?
Yes.
She was mistaken because she grew up
as an only child and felt lonely.
She won't be Pil Seung's girlfriend.
Just imagining kissing him
makes her want to throw up.
No way can she be
his girlfriend, then.
That's never possible.
She said she'd visit often...
as Pil Seung's younger sister.
She does this one moment
and that the next and it's crazy.
She really is a bit weird.
We let her manipulate us
without knowing it.
I like it much more that she
changed her mind about Pil Seung.
Ms. Kim, when will
the spicy cold noodles be ready?
Just a moment, Ma Ri.
It's done.
My daughter Ma Ri said that?
Yes. She said
she must've been lonely...
because she grew up an only child.
She liked Pil Seung
as he was like an older brother.
She was mistaken that she wanted to
be his girlfriend.
She doesn't want to marry him.
She just wants to be his sister.
I see.
She sincerely apologized
for hiding in the closet,
and she even thanked me...
for raising Pil Seung
to be the good man he is.
Did she really?
Anyway, Soo Yeon.
Ma Ri bought us all a gift.
A designer bag, clothes...
Everything looked so expensive.
We couldn't accept them,
so I put them all aside.
I'll return them when we next meet.
Why would you say that?
Ma Ri wanted to give you something,
so accept them and don't feel bad.
She must've gone shopping...
because she felt terrible
and wanted to thank you too.
That would make Ma Ri feel better.
Please keep them.
Goodness.
Okay, then.
Anyway,
I called to say Ma Ri's fine.
We had spicy cold noodles,
and she gets along so well
with my mother-in-law.
Okay. I'm sorry
about the nuisance, Sun Young.
Ma Ri's hard to look after,
isn't she?
I'm sorry for the trouble.
Why would you say that?
It's not like that at all.
Don't worry.
Ma Ri's as good as my daughter too.
You have no idea how much
I enjoy her chatter when she visits.
Our house was so quiet,
but now it's full of laughter.
Pil Seung's an only child
and so is Ma Ri.
It would be nice if they could
get along well like siblings.
Hearing you say that...
makes me so happy, Sun Young.
Thanks a lot.
Not that again.
Why do you always say that?
Anyway, Ma Ri wanted to
see Pil Seung,
so I'll send her home later.
Okay. Bye.
Sun Young.
Thanks so much, Sun Young.
Goodness.
Why are you back here?
Kim Ji Young.
Were you two-timing us?
What? What are you talking about?
You don't know?
You were dating Pil Seung,
but when I asked you out,
you said you'd think about it.
You led me on and gave me hope,
and now it's a no?
Compensate me
for toying with my feelings.
Mr. Gong. You know,
I never led you on or gave you hope.
You told me to treat you
in return for the damaged suit.
I had little money then,
and I was so grateful
you let me buy you dinner...
instead of a new suit.
That's the only reason
I ate out with you.
Hey. Do you call that
an explanation?
You shouldn't have said
you'd think about it, then.
I explained to you last time
why I had to say that.
I had to buy you one more meal,
and if I were to reject you then,
it would make the last meal awkward.
That's why I said
I'd think about it.
Also, I said
I'd think about dating you.
I never said
I was interested in you.
If I'd known
you'd get such a wrong idea,
I'd have taken out a loan
to pay you for the suit.
I said my part and I'm busy,
so I have to dash.
Hey.
I'm not done talking.
You can't leave.
If you don't let go,
I'll tell my boyfriend
the director...
to beat you up again.
- Do you get that?
- What?
Go and spoil the woman
you're going to marry.
What a nuisance.
Don't come here again.
You're not welcome.
That country bumpkin...
What should I do about her?
Gosh. You country bumpkin...
Don't call me that!
(Queen Mother)
What do you want?
What?
Tae Hee?
I see.
- I'm back.
- Hello.
Hello, Jin Dan.
Tae Hee.
What happened? Why didn't you call?
I'd have gone to pick you up.
I wanted to surprise you.
Your mother invited me.
Did she?
Chairman Gong and Auntie
were curious and wanted to meet her.
You should visit her family too now.
So, when are your parents free
to meet with our family?
They told me to ask if you're free
for lunch next weekend.
Chairman Gong. Are you free then?
I'll make myself free.
This is a great
and welcome family event.
Soo Yeon, you should help out too.
Yes, Auntie.
- Have some of this.
- Thanks.
Did you take Tae Hee home?
Mom.
Why did you invite her over?
What are you up to?
And what's
the sudden family meet-up about?
It's not sudden.
We'd been talking about it.
What? Do you have regrets
about the other girl?
Is this about her?
Do you want me to
rip into her hair once more?
Mom. If you do that
to Ji Young once more,
no one knows how I might react.
Get a grip, Gong Jin Dan.
I put up with and covered up
all your crazy antics...
and waited for you.
"It won't last forever.
He'll come round."
But why are you being like this?
How far are you going to take this?
Jin Dan.
You can't be doing this to Tae Hee.
It was no big deal...
to end things with the girls
you were seeing before,
but Tae Hee is different.
Think of Auntie, Jin Taek,
and even Soo Yeon.
They all are excited
about your wedding with Tae Hee.
But how could you get distracted
by such a lame girl like her?
Do you really not mind
losing everything you have now?
No, Mom.
I'm not all that crazy.
I won't be like that now.
It won't happen again.
Are you sure?
Do you really mean it?
Fine.
I can't give up on everything
just because of a lowlife like her.
Mom, I told you.
I won't lose Tae Hee.
I'll marry her no matter that.
I knew it. You will, right?
I trust you.
Of course.
I'm finished.
Where are you, Ji Young?
Is the script-reading over?
(Ms. Kim Ji Young)
I'm so sorry, Director Ko.
I'm not finished yet.
Since we're doing the shoot
next week, Director Hong...
and the actors want
to practice reading until late.
You should go home without me.
You want me to go home alone?
I'm bored when I go home by myself.
My gosh.
This is just getting
worse and worse.
How did you manage
without me before?
You must've been bored.
This won't do.
I should call Director Hong
and ask him to wrap things up.
So we can go home together
having a date.
What? Gosh, you can't do that.
I'm joking.
You fall for that every time.
You worked hard today.
You should go home early
and get some rest.
I'll text you when I'm done.
Okay.
Now that we're not
going on a date tonight,
you should at least give me a hug.
Then I'll go home.
My goodness.
Fine.
Just hug me before anyone sees us.
Did you watch "Lovely Runner?"
- My gosh.
- It's really fun.
I'm sorry, Director Ko.
I should get going.
I know.
What are you doing, Director Ko?
Did you fall?
No. It's just that
my shoelaces came undone.
I see.
We will go on ahead then.
Bye.
Grandma, it's really fun
to hear about Pil Seung.
Tell me more about him.
All right then. Do you want to hear
about Pil Seung's childhood now?
- His childhood? That sounds great.
- Yes.
I think it was
after his first birthday...
when he was crawling around.
Pil Seung was sitting
right next to us,
but when we looked at him
a little later, he was missing.
He went missing? Where did he go?
We had no idea back then.
We all were surprised,
so we looked for him everywhere...
searching the whole house.
And you know what?
He was a little baby
crawling around on all fours,
so I have no idea
how he could get there,
but he was found on the rooftop.
- On the rooftop?
- Yes.
So? Didn't he get hurt?
So our whole family was worried...
if he'd fall off.
We were shaking in fear.
But she's a mom, after all.
Pil Seung's mom, Sun Young...
crept up the stairs
to the rooftop...
and caught Pil Seung right away.
- Thank goodness.
- My gosh.
I'm so relieved.
Ms. Kim, you're unbelievable.
What?
And Grandma, Mr. Ko, and Myung Dong.
You all raised Pil Seung well...
into a healthy and brave man.
You must've been through a lot.
I should thank you all.
I will never forget
what you've done.
Oh, dear. How sweet.
I'm home.
- Pil Seung.
- Hey.
Ms. Ma Ri.
Well...
Pil Seung.
Yes, Ms. Ma Ri.
Please don't call me Ms. Ma Ri.
Just call me Ma Ri instead.
Because...
I just want to be
your younger sister.
So you can speak casually to me.
Can I do that?
Fine, Ma Ri.
All right.
Pil Seung, you know,
I grew up as an only child,
so I've always wanted
an older brother.
What I wanted was
an older brother like you.
I was being silly and confused,
so I asked you to be my boyfriend.
Pil Seung, I'm sorry
for what I've done.
I apologize.
I see.
Yes. So I never want you...
to be my boyfriend anymore.
It will never happen again.
So can I just hang out with you...
like an older brother
and a younger sister?
Of course. I'd love that.
I'm glad I got a younger sister.
Really? Thank you so much.
Now that we're
a brother and a sister,
we should shake hands
to celebrate it.
I heard...
Pil Seung and you will be like
a brother and a sister.
Yes. At first, I hated you...
and had a hard time understanding
why you did such a thing.
But Pil Seung said
he'd be my brother,
so I don't hate you as much anymore.
And I'm grateful that you got me
a great brother like him.
Ma Ri.
Thank you so much for saying so.
Mom, I'm just grateful...
that you got me a brother.
But I still don't understand you.
If I were Pil Seung,
I would never forgive you.
Speaking of which, Mom,
if you feel bad for Pil Seung,
you should be nice to him.
What?
Mom, I want to share
what I have with Pil Seung.
How can we make him
as rich as we are now?
What should I do
to share what I have with him?
I can't tell Dad that
I want to share things with him.
We can't tell Dad about Pil Seung.
How can we share
what we have with him?
Thank you, Ma Ri.
You are a way smarter
and better person...
than I am, Ma Ri.
You really are.
("Don't Lie" Got off to a Good Start
With a Rating of 15.2 Percent)
(Number 1 on Streaming Service!
Now streaming)
(KMS Has Revived After 2 Years
Since "Straightforward Romance")
(The First Episode of "Don't Lie"
Recorded the Rating of 15.2 Percent)
It's not just popular,
but it's a huge hit?
Yes, it is.
The first episode recorded
a rating of over 15.2 percent.
- My goodness.
- A rating like this...
is like a miracle these days.
My goodness.
This is amazing news.
My dear Pil Seung.
Hang on.
Then what is going to happen...
to Pil Seung now?
He will be offered jobs everywhere.
After a big hit like this,
he will receive job offers
from all the companies in the industry.
That's so cool.
He'll then take on the job
that pays the most.
Mother, no.
That means he'll have
to quit the broadcasting station.
Sun Young, please.
Many directors freelance these days.
The industry isn't like
how it was before.
Still, I want Pil Seung...
to have a solid job at a company.
One that will let him work
until he retires.
Remember how his father...
quit his job and made a huge fuss
about starting a business?
The anxiety I felt
and all that upset me...
The last thing I want is
for Pil Seung to suffer like that.
The sufferings from back then...
are enough to still wake me
from my sleep.
Sun Young.
Do you have to bring up
Hyun Chul's failure at this moment?
Mother, that's not what I meant.
Anyway Myung Dong,
don't give him any ideas like that.
All right.
But he's not one to listen to me...
even when I give him ideas.
- Gosh.
- Seriously though.
What good does his success do...
when someone else
will benefit from it?
Mom, come on.
Why would you say that?
Can you blame me for saying so?
She isn't just a hillbilly
who has nothing to her name.
He fell for a vixen...
who seduced
a soon-to-be-married man.
Why is it that Pil Seung...
has the worst taste in women?
Don't worry, Mother.
Pil Seung will soon snap out of it.
As if. They live close by and
are together at work all the time.
They'll be glued to the hip!
Mom!
What? It's not like I'm wrong.
Stop it.
Director Ko, did you give
my proposal some thought?
Yes, and I appreciate
how you've been coming to see me...
to talk about your offer.
But I don't have enough experience
to quit the broadcasting station...
and work as a freelancer.
It doesn't seem like the right time.
Goodness. How so?
Was the offer not good enough?
That isn't the case,
but I don't think
I'm ready to quit my job...
at the broadcasting station.
Let us revisit this idea
some other time.
All right. I'll think about it,
and come to you again
with an offer too good...
that is impossible to reject.
When I do,
strongly consider my offer.
Sure thing.
- You should take that.
- Right.
- I'll be in touch.
- Sure.
- Thank you.
- Right.
Hey.
The station director?
Pil Seung.
Rumor has it...
that the best production houses
in the business...
are all trying
to sign a deal with you.
I bet you've been receiving
a lot of offers.
It's not that much.
Have you not been meeting
with production houses?
That I have.
Pil Seung, look.
If you think about it, you could say
I helped build your career.
So for you to quit
the broadcasting station?
If I'm being harsh,
it's a betrayal.
What I'm saying is that...
you should stay...
centered.
You're making it sound
like we went out.
How is this a betrayal?
Pil Seung, the world
only seems like a nice place...
because you're seeing it
from under our roof.
This is a greenhouse,
and it's the Himalayas out there.
You'll be walking on thin ice.
Come on, Mr. Jang.
Why are you scaring
a director on the rise?
What do you mean I'm scaring you?
I'm worried about you,
and I want you
to be smart about this.
All right. I'll keep that in mind.
Of course.
Don't make hasty decisions,
and stay put.
What?
You want to run
a drama production house?
Honey, that's out of the blue.
It's not sudden.
I've been mentioning it
for years now.
You said we'd revisit the idea
after I gained experience...
running the store.
Yes, that's something I said.
Don't you believe in me, honey?
You seem doubtful.
Of course I believe in you.
It's a bit sudden, that's all.
Dad, don't argue with her on this...
and just let her do what she wants.
A man should keep his promise.
Sure. I made a promise
and I should keep it.
How well you ran the store...
does imply that you'll do a good job
running the production house.
Goodness.
Thanks, honey.
Dad, thanks. I love you so much.
Ma Ri seems to be more thrilled
with you running a production house.
Are you that delighted?
Weren't you furious with your mother
these past few days?
When did the two of you make up?
Dad, a quarrel between
a mom and daughter...
is like cutting water with a knife.
What? Cutting water with a knife?
Where did you learn that saying?
Ji Young. Here.
Mr. Lee, the anxiety might kill me.
My heart is beating out of my chest,
and I can't remember
any of my lines.
My head hurts, and I feel queasy.
What? Ji Young, hold on.
I'll get you a calming drink,
so try to hang in there.
Gosh.
What do I do?
Filming will start any time soon.
Why am I this nervous?
Director Ko.
Ji Young, you must be nervous
with this being your first day.
I wish I could be there with you,
but I had too many meetings.
Are you all right?
Yes, I'm... I'm fine.
Besides, I would've been
more nervous with you here.
You don't seem fine to me.
Ji Young.
You weren't nervous at all...
when playing that role
in "Don't Lie."
What is it?
Why are you this nervous?
Tell me about it.
I don't know why I am this way.
It must be because
I have to play the lead.
The whole show will tank
if I don't do a good job.
That thought alone terrifies me,
and I see nothing but darkness.
It's because
you're a responsible person.
But that's never a bad thing.
I guess, but...
I'm a nervous wreck,
and I don't know
if I'll be able to do a good job.
Ji Young, focus and imagine that
you're the character you're playing.
"I am someone else.
Not Kim Ji Young."
Say that to yourself...
just like you did
when filming "Don't Lie."
Got it. I'll do that.
Baby chick.
Sorry? A baby chick?
What baby chick?
There are too many people around me.
If I say "baby chick" to you,
that's me saying "I like you."
What?
Goodness me.
Got it.
Chirp.
- Baby chick.
- Chirp.
How do I look?
Do I look like a city girl?
Will it be okay
for my job interview tomorrow?
Yes, you look like a city girl.
Very good.
Excuse me.
I'll take everything here.
Cut, okay. Nice job!
How is it that the country bumpkin
is this good at putting on an act?
She's not intimidated
despite being a rookie.
Unbelievable.
Mr. Lee, how was I?
Did I do all right?
As if I need to tell you that.
Ji Young, you did great.
- There's no need to be nervous.
- Why is Jae Dong with her?
Jae Dong, hey.
Why were you with
that country bumpkin?
Ms. Baek, I started
an agency of my own.
Also, her name is Kim Ji Young,
not Country Bumpkin.
She's the first actor I signed.
Popcorn Entertainment?
Are you saying...
that she's an actor
signed with your agency?
Yes.
Look at you.
Ji Young.
Director Ko.
Ji Young, what's wrong?
Was there a problem on set?
I was the problem.
I botched my scenes many times...
and didn't do as well
as I wanted to.
Is that why you're so glum?
Yes.
That's how it is at first.
Being nervous leads to errors,
and there are actors...
who forget their lines
in front of the camera.
An actor who only had one line...
could not say it right for 30 takes.
The whole day went by
without making any progress.
That sounds like a lie.
I bet it is.
I'd be lying
if I didn't add some drama to it,
but that's how everyone starts out.
Thank you.
I feel better now...
after hearing you say that,
Director Ko.
Ji Young,
when will you stop addressing me
as Director Ko?
Are we at the office?
I thought we were dating,
but you keep calling me Director.
How should I call you, then?
Well,
Sweetie would be nice.
Wait, what?
Gosh, I can't say
something like that.
Besides, it's not like
we're a family or anything.
It's not appropriate at all.
And I've always been against
addressing a boyfriend like that.
Will you keep calling me
Director Ko, then?
I guess I won't, but...
How about Mr. Ko?
Well, that doesn't sound so bad.
I can't say
I'm excited about it either.
Let me think about it, then.
Meanwhile, how should I address you?
Darling?
What?
- Baby?
- What?
- Honey?
- My gosh!
Stop that already
and stick to my name.
The goosebumps
might actually kill me.
Okay, fine.
I can't have goosebumps kill you,
so I'll stick to Ji Young for now.
I'd like that.
I love it the most
when you call me by my name.
All right.
I prepared something to celebrate
your first day of filming,
so let's get going for now.
What is it?
You'll know once you see it.
But I'm curious.
Can't you tell me in advance?
Director Ko, these are pretty.
There's a treasure box somewhere,
so try to find it.
Sure.
Here. I found it.
Open it.
Sure.
What?
Let it only be rainbows
and sunshine for you.
From Ko Pil Seung,
who will always be...
your number one fan.
Director Ko, my gosh.
If anything brings you down,
look at these and cheer up.
Also, yell at it
when you get mad at me.
Am I allowed to do that?
Are you actually thinking about it?
As if I would have a reason
to yell at you.
I won't, Director Ko.
You're still calling me that.
Fine, Pil Seung.
What was that?
Go ahead and address me like that.
My gosh.
It's my grandma. What do I do?
Director Ko, get going.
My grandma will have a fit
when she finds out.
She'll beat me to a pulp.
What did I do wrong?
- Get going already.
- I'll see myself out.
- Sure. Get going.
- Right.
Gosh. Hey, Grandma.
Did you have to call me
at that particular moment?
I called because
I wanted to hear your voice.
Why are you yelling at me?
When did I yell at you?
Ji Young,
do not date random men in Seoul,
and do not let men into your unit.
Keep that in mind.
Sure thing.
You worry like
it's a habit of yours.
Grandma, we'll talk again soon.
Even from way over there,
she knows what's going on.
Because of her,
I can't get anywhere in life.
Goodness.
What almost happened just now?
Ji Young,
what are you picturing?
Pil Seung.
I'm starting
my own production house.
A production house?
It has been my dream for years now,
and I'm finally
devoting myself to it.
I see.
Before the foundation ceremony,
I've been meeting...
with writers and directors to hire.
Can I ask for your support?
Sorry?
I want you to be the first one...
that is signed
by GOGO Entertainment.
That is why I asked to meet you.
Me?
Yes, I thoroughly enjoyed...
your series "Don't Lie."
Your directing ability
is what made the show sparkle.
Your skills are even
being recognized internationally.
Pil Seung,
join GOGO Entertainment.
Ms. Jang, I appreciate the offer,
but I still lack in many ways
and need more experience.
Gosh, no.
You're already good enough.
Here's the contract.
Why don't you go ahead
and give it a read?
Tell me if there's anything else
you'd like to add.
This...
The signing bonus is too much.
Don't be ridiculous.
You're being offered that
because you're worth every penny.
I did my research,
and other production houses...
are desperately trying to sign you.
Only an offer like this...
would get you to consider
joining us.
Ms. Jang...
My dream is to have
GOGO Entertainment...
be Korea's best
drama production house.
If you agree to join us,
I will support you unsparingly...
and let you tell your own stories.
I'm just getting started
and need someone I can rely on.
Director Ko... I mean, Pil Seung.
I would appreciate your help.
All right. I'll think about it.
Good.
My dream is to have
GOGO Entertainment...
be Korea's best
drama production house.
If you agree to join us,
I will support you unsparingly...
and let you tell your own stories.
I can make two million dollars
after a few hours of a photo shoot.
Can you give me that money instead?
The mistake will be mine to regret,
so shut it and get lost
unless you have two million dollars!
Two million dollars?
No, I don't.
Not two million dollars,
not 200,000 dollars,
not even 20,000 dollars.
I guess I could offer 2,000 dollars.
If I save up...
and scrape up everything I have,
I'll be able to offer 2,000 dollars.
I won't waver again.
Never again
will I lose someone I cherish...
just because I lack money and power.
Never again.
What?
You'll move to the company
Soo Yeon's starting?
Yes.
Are you saying you'll quit
working at the TV station?
Yes.
Ms. Jang offered me...
a crazy deal through the company.
I don't think I'll get another shot
like it, so I'll give it a go.
Yes, but still, Pil Seung.
Can't you think about it
a little more cautiously?
The moment you leave the TV station,
you'll lose all the perks
and protection they offered.
The TV station guarantees a job
until you reach retirement age,
and the work is stable.
Even if you mess up
and your drama flops a few times,
you can get another shot.
But if a contract-based director
messes up just one project,
it becomes much harder
to get another chance.
Yes. Think about it again.
Wouldn't you prefer a stable job?
It will be tougher
once I leave the TV station,
but I want to succeed on my own.
And make money.
I'll trust in myself
and give it a go.
So don't worry too much.
Well, okay, then.
If you made up your mind,
then you must go with it.
I understand.
Since you made the decision,
do your best.
Be successful.
Yes. She offered you
a much better pay.
- Why would you refuse?
- Yes.
Pil Seung. Good for you.
You must strike
while the iron is hot.
A production house
beneath APP Group...
will never go belly up.
I'm happy for you. Congratulations.
Okay.
I trust in you too.
Thank you.
Mom, Dad, Grandma, Auntie.
What?
You'll sign Director Ko
for that amount of money?
Why would you offer
that much money to a small fry?
Are you out of your mind?
Jin Dan. How dare you
talk to my wife like that?
Are you saying she's crazy?
I apologize.
But Jin Taek.
This is out of the ordinary.
If you offer that much money
to a lowly director,
it will drive up
the other directors' pay.
Other production companies
will badmouth her.
It goes against business morals.
Soo Yeon.
Did you offer that much
because he's your friend's son?
Why would you say
it's because he's my friend's son?
How could you?
Director Ko isn't a small fry.
He's one of
the hottest rising directors.
It's true he doesn't have
much experience,
but two years ago,
his one-episode drama won an award
at an international drama festival.
His current drama "Don't Lie"...
is a candidate
for the Juniper Award.
Even people abroad
have begun to notice him.
Another production house
was trying to scout him,
and I barely managed to
get him interested in my offer.
I'm still against it.
I'm the CEO of GOGO Entertainment.
Why are you so involved?
Soo Yeon.
I invested
my company's money in yours...
because Jin Taek told me to.
That gives me a right to comment.
You can't sign Ko Pil Seung.
I object.
Meet some other directors.
Who are you
to talk like that to my mom?
How much did you invest in
that you're being so meddlesome?
How much was it?
Dad, take that amount
from my shares and give it to him.
- Goodness.
- Gong Ma Ri.
You can't talk like that
to your uncle.
Uncle.
Stay out of my mom's business...
and concentrate on your own.
Shall I name
all your projects that flopped?
The Myanmar condo,
the Vietnam condo,
and Lemon Construction.
Did you think I didn't know?
My gosh. Ma Ri.
Ma Ri. Your uncle's saying that
because he's worried...
your mom's starting a business
in drama production,
a field she has no experience in.
Don't worry, Great Auntie.
Pil Seung will become
a massively huge director.
My mom will never flop.
Here. Sign right there.
Okay.
(CEO Jang Soo Yeon,
Director Ko Pil Seung)
Director Ko. I hope things go well.
So do I, Ms. Jang.
Let's make this work.
Okay. I'll do my best.
What's this?
It looks like a bankbook.
Is there money in the account?
Wait.
You got the down-payment already?
Yes.
Pil Seung.
Why would you give me the money?
It's yours. You should manage it.
Mom.
Take it and pay off the mortgage.
Dad, you wanted to start a business.
Pick an item you like.
Gosh, no.
We can't take this money.
You worked so hard
to pay the principal...
and interest for us.
You should keep this safe...
for when you move out
or get married.
Sun Young. Pil Seung wants to do
his duty as a son for once.
Why would you stop him?
Thank you, Pil Seung.
You're a good boy and son.
You handed over
a huge sum for your dad.
Pil Seung.
It was worth raising you.
Gosh, no, Mother.
Pil Seung.
This money wasn't for free.
You must work
to make this much for the company.
So you should manage it.
Mom. This isn't everything I got.
I put some aside.
So don't worry.
I'm going to make much more now.
So it's fine.
Mom and Dad
did so much for me to raise me.
Can't I give you this much?
Pil Seung.
Goodness...
Yes, Pil Seung.
Thanks so much.
Good for you. Thank you.
Good boy.
What should I get?
Sorry.
Aren't you Myung Dong's boyfriend?
Oh... Sorry. I mistook you
for someone else.
I apologize.
What?
What is this?
I felt this last time too.
Also, her name is Kim Ji Young,
not Country Bumpkin.
She's the first actor I signed.
Wait.
Where did Jae Dong find
that gem of a girl?
But then I did teach him...
how to recognize talent
when he was Do Ra's manager.
Do Sik, you're home?
Mom. I saw Do Ra
while I was out making a delivery.
What? You saw whom?
I swear it was Do Ra.
I chased after her
and grabbed her arm and...
It wasn't her.
It was Director Ko's tenant girl.
My goodness.
Will you pull yourself together?
How could you compare
that country bumpkin with my Do Ra?
It was really confusing.
I actually mistook her
for Do Ra before.
This is the second time.
I swear she felt just like Do Ra.
Mom, isn't it that
Do Ra had a twin sister...
and you abandoned her?
You crazy brat.
How dare you say such a thing?
Hey, I will never abandon
my own child...
no matter how hard it gets.
Then did Dad have a daughter
with someone else?
What's wrong with you?
You're giving me a headache.
Just go and wash up.
Let's just eat. My gosh.
- I know, right?
- Gosh.
You silly thing.
Why do you always talk nonsense?
- Hurry and wash up.
- Okay.
Gosh, my head is killing me.
Right.
That country bumpkin
does look a little like Do Ra.
I have this strange feeling
whenever I see her.
There are a lot of people
in the world who look similar.
My goodness.
If only Do Ra could come back alive.
Then we wouldn't be living
so miserably like this.
Right, Do Ra?
Come on. What took you so long?
I signed a contract today.
This is a great day for me.
What do you want to do today?
Just tell me anything.
What if someone sees us?
We can't be doing this
in our neighborhood.
What? I don't care
even if someone sees us.
We're dating now.
My goodness.
Ms. Kim and your family
are still upset...
about what happened
between me and Mr. Gong's mother.
They will be furious
if they see us together.
And it will just give you and me
a hard time.
Things will get better over time.
Ji Young,
just hang in there a little more.
Don't worry
about anything like that.
So what do you want to do?
Just name it,
and we will do it.
Well...
There was something...
I wanted to do
when I got a boyfriend.
What is it?
Just come with me.
Where are we going?
You'll see when we get there.
Ji Young,
we should walk hand in hand.
My gosh.
(Ji Young, Pil Seung)
Is this what you wanted to do?
Yes.
This is what I wanted to do the most
with my boyfriend.
Why? Do you not like it?
Do you think it's childish?
You just thought it was tacky,
didn't you?
No. It's not like that.
I like it
as long as it makes you happy.
Do you really mean that?
I do.
We locked up our love now.
So our love will last forever...
unless the lock comes open.
We should never change, okay?
I will never change.
So this is the love we have.
(Ji Young, Pil Seung)
(GOGO Entertainment
Foundation Ceremony)
- Hello.
- Welcome.
Nice to meet you.
Hello.
Auntie Dae Sook.
I wonder what's gotten into her
all of a sudden.
What is all this?
And I don't understand
Chairman Gong either.
When Jin Dan wanted
to invest in a drama,
he made such a fuss.
But he let his wife
start a production house...
when she had no experience
in the field.
I understand
Jin Taek is a henpecked husband,
but I have no idea
what's going on in his head.
Obviously, she's going to blow it.
It won't even last a year.
It's a waste of money.
I know. He should've given me
the money instead.
I'd like to thank everyone here...
for taking the time
to come in today.
Though I don't have
much experience in business,
I've always wanted...
to make good stories.
And I didn't want
to waste more time,
so I plucked up my courage
and started it.
I hope
GOGO Entertainment will bring...
a lot of joy, hope, and pleasure...
to many people with good stories.
And I will need your help
in doing so.
Now I will try my best...
to discover good directors,
good writers,
and good stories.
Thank you.
Here's the first ever director...
of GOGO Entertainment.
Director Ko Pil Seung,
would you like to say something?
Hello. I'm Director Ko Pil Seung.
I'm grateful to GOGO Entertainment
for choosing me,
and I will return the favor
with good works.
I would appreciate your help.
I'll try hard and do well.
Thank you.
(GOGO Entertainment
Foundation Ceremony)
We appreciate all of you
who came and participated...
in the event today.
I hope GOGO Entertainment,
which is taking off today,
will become a big success.
I'd like to propose a toast...
to GOGO Entertainment
that will hopefully become...
the leader of K-content.
To the growth of GOGO Entertainment.
- To GOGO Entertainment.
- Congratulations.
Sun Young.
Thank you.
- Hey, Pil Seung.
- Director Ko.
- Come on.
- Good luck with your new job.
- Thank you.
- Congratulations.
Pil Seung, let's drink together.
Sure, Ma Ri. Cheers.
I'm so happy
that you're working with my mom.
I'm glad that you're happy.
Thanks.
Ma Ri, what's your favorite genre?
Sun Young.
- Hello.
She will soon set a date
for her wedding with Jin Dan.
Pil Seung should find someone nice
and get married too.
Sure. He will meet someone
when the time comes.
Tell me once you set the date.
She looks so nice and pretty.
You must be happy to get
such a great daughter-in-law.
Yes. I hope you enjoy
the rest of the day.
- Let's go, Tae Hee.
- Please take care.
I wonder why her son
fell for our tenant lady...
when he had such a pretty
and graceful girlfriend.
I would never understand him.
Stop it, Mother.
Someone might hear you.
Director Ko.
I hear you're dating Ji Young.
I just found that out.
How ill-mannered you are.
You're ignoring what I said.
I don't think we're close enough...
to have a private conversation
in a place like this.
All right then.
Fine.
You can have Ji Young.
I just found...
that country bumpkin
a bit interesting and unusual.
So I just hung out with her
a few times.
And I'm not interested anymore.
I think you're here
with someone you will marry.
Don't you think...
you're not supposed to do this
to your fiancee?
Are you admitting to me
that you're human trash?
What? That darn punk.
Hey, what did you say to me?
Hey.
(GOGO Entertainment
Foundation Ceremony)
You impertinent punk.
What did you just say to me?
Human trash?
Hey.
Who are you throwing punches at?
How are you not human trash
when you went...
after another woman
while engaged to someone else?
No decent man would do that.
Whether I date
more than one woman...
is none of your business.
I showed interest in Ji Young first.
You're the one
who took my girl from me!
Darn it.
How dare you take what's mine?
Kim Ji Young is mine!
Pil Seung!
Don't hit my brother.
- Darn you.
- Pil Seung!
Don't hit my brother.
Pil Seung's my brother!
Stop hitting him.
Don't!
- That's my brother!
- Darn!
Stop hitting him.
Get off him!
(Beauty and Mr. Romantic)
They say one's roots never lie.
This is exactly why you're only seen
as the mistress' son.
Is that the woman...
Pil Seung and Jin Dan
were fighting over?
He won't change his mind
no matter how much we object.
You didn't raise him this hard...
to let him marry a girl like her.
I thought Kim Ji Young
was perfect for the role.
I want her to play
the second female lead.
I object to casting Ms. Kim.
I'm nervous to go on a business trip
and leave you behind.
Maybe I shouldn't go.
Please don't say...
anything weird to Ji Young
while I'm away.
I'm looking for a room to rent.
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)