- Pil Sung!
- Go Pil Sung!
Pil Sung!
[Episode 29]
Pil Sung, are you okay?
What happened?
Mom, I'm okay, but the President...
Oh, my! Soo Yeon!
Soo Yeon! Soo Yeon, open your eyes!
Ma Ri, what happened?
A wall fell on her on the set
and Mom tried to protect Pil Sung, and this is what happened.
My mom won't wake up, no matter how much I try to wake her.
What? She was trying to protect Pil Sung?
No... No, not my Pil Sung!
Pil Sung!
Mom, Mom, what are you doing?
Wake up, Mom.
Open your eyes, Mom!
Mom! Mom!
Mom, can you see me?
It's me!
Soo Yeon, are you okay?
Are you awake now?
Where's Pil Sung?
President, I'm here. I'm okay.
Yes, Director Go.
Are you sure you're okay?
Yes.
President Jang, you must've worried a lot about Pil Sung getting hurt.
Doctor, are my mom and oppa okay?
There's nothing wrong with Director Go, according to the test results.
But Ms. Jang bruised her knee and shoulder.
She'll have to take medicine and receive physical therapy for now.
Yes.
Thank you.
I'm glad nothing worse happened.
Pil Sung is totally fine. How did you get so injured, President Jang?
My mom held Pil Sung like this to protect him, and they fell.
Soo Yeon, thank you so much for saving Pil Sung. But...
I'm so sorry you got injured.
I feel so guilty about it. I'm sorry.
It's okay, Seon Yeong.
I'm totally fine. I'm really okay.
The doctor said I was fine, too.
Honey, what happened?
How did you get into an accident?
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
They said I'm totally fine.
My gosh, my gosh.
If it wasn't for your friend, something bad could've happened to Pil Sung.
I know.
How could she throw her fragile body to save Pil Sung?
Your friend must really care for him a lot.
She paid him so much contract money, too.
And now she saved his life.
Pil Sung, you'll have to be loyal to President Jang from now on.
Of course.
I didn't know she cared about me this much, either.
You still need to relax. Rest upstairs.
- Okay, I'll go upstairs.
- Yes, go upstairs.
Hey, Myeong Dong. Get me some water.
My heart is still racing so much.
- Okay.
- Aigoo.
I'm glad Soo Yeon didn't get injured more.
What if something terrible happened to her trying to save Pil Sung?
I felt so bad that I couldn't face Chairman Gong earlier at the hospital.
I know. I don't even want to think about it.
By the way, CEO Jang...
She said, "Pil Sung, my Pil Sung," unconsciously.
Why was she calling for him in that situation?
As if he was her child.
One might've thought he was her son.
It's because she got injured saving him, I'm sure.
Soo Yeon has cared for Pil Sung since he was a baby.
I'm too lucky to have a friend like her.
You sure are lucky to have a good friend.
You're lucky to have your husband, too? Right?
Pardon? My husband? I'm lucky?
W-What? She's right.
Seriously, you always say nothing but truths.
Yes, yes. You're right.
Gosh, I got so scared.
My gosh, how could you throw yourself to save that big man?
We almost had a funeral today.
I know.
We can't break our bones at our age.
How could you throw yourself to save Pil Sung?
Were you that worried about Seon Yeong's son getting hurt?
How could I just let someone get injured?
He got into that dangerous situation working for my company.
Let's go inside for now.
Right. I left the medicine in the car.
Ma Ri, bring her to the room. I'll get her medicine.
Okay, Dad.
Let's go, Mom.
Heavens helped her today. Seriously.
She's so devoted to Seon Yeong's family.
She risked her life to save her son this time.
Seriously, what a touching friendship.
Having a barbecue reminds me of something.
You once got us ribs once.
When we used to live in that grandpa's house.
- Do you remember, Do Jun?
- I do.
I don't know where you got the money, but you told us to eat as much as we'd like.
I think we ate about 15 servings, the four of us.
Ji Yeong must not remember it.
I'm not sure what you're talking about.
Gosh, seriously. Stop talking about something she doesn't even remember.
Let's just eat. Seriously.
Here. Do Ra, say ah.
Mom, we agreed not to call her that.
Oh, right. It came out of nowhere.
We have to call her Ji Yeong from now on, okay?
It'd be a disaster if people found out she was Do Ra.
Ji Yeong, say ah. Ah.
Okay.
It's tasty.
Thank you so much for caring for me so much.
Gosh, don't thank me. We're a family.
Do Jun, you say ah, too. Ah.
I'll eat it myself.
Come on, Mom wants to feed you.
Yes, just take it. Her arms are hurting.
Yes, yes, yes.
Mom, why are you crying?
The four of us having a meal together...
feels like a dream.
I'm so happy.
Gosh, Mom. Why are you doing this now?
You're making me tear up.
Let's not ever...
be separated and live together like this.
We can't afford Korean beef, but pork belly makes us so happy.
Ji Yeong, you don't remember, but you're my daughter,
Do Sik's younger sister, and Do Jun's older sister, okay?
Okay, got it.
I'm so happy, too.
My Do Ra... I mean, Ji Yeong is alive and well like this.
Seriously. Why are we doing this during a meal?
Let's eat.
Things are still awkward, but we'll get used to it once we start living together.
Yes, Ahjumma.
I'm happy to have a family like this, too.
I wish she'd called me "Mom" when it's just us.
She keeps calling me "Ahjumma."
Mom, we agreed to take things slow.
She'll get her memories back soon.
Yes, yes. Let's take it slow. Take it slow.
And Ji Yeong, you can call me "Ahjumma" forever. It's okay. It's okay.
I'm sorry.
Don't apologize. I said it's okay. It's okay.
Let's eat. Let's eat. Come on and eat. Hurry, eat.
Eat, eat.
Let's eat.
Grandma, what are you up to?
What do you mean? I'm about to go to bed.
What? Is something going on?
Do I call only when something's going on?
Everything's fine.
How about you? You're okay, right?
Did you go somewhere random singing the national anthem again?
No, no.
Deok Ja would've called you if I had gone berzerk.
Is it because I'm happy you're in a show?
I'm totally fine these days.
Ji Yeong, the neighbors saw you on TV
and they say you became successful.
My shoulders are almost touching the sky these days because of pride!.
Really?
Yes.
So, don't worry about me at all
and just focus on your job, okay?
Okay, Grandma.
You know... I love you the most in the world, right?
I love you the most in the world, too.
Thank you, Grandma.
I love you.
I love you, Grandma.
Soo Yeon's company made me an amazing offer.
Then, the CEO did that on her own?
Without even asking you?
No, not my Pil Sung!
Pil Sung!
How strange.
This is more than just strange.
Mom, why do you keep mumbling instead of sleeping?
What do you find so strange, exactly?
Myeong Dong, don't you find it strange?
Find what strange?
She almost died because the wall fell on her.
But she wasn't calling for her daughter, Ma Ri, or her husband.
Why did she call for Pil Sung in that situation?
So desperately, too.
Mom, are you still talking about that?
It's probably because she passed out saving Pil Sung.
That's why I find it strange.
Why would she call for Pil Sung in that situation?
And you said this, too.
Amazingly, she offered him that much contract money with Pil Sung's experience.
Why? Why did she pay him twice as much to hire him?
She's always been too generous to Pil Sung.
She always sent tons of presents and food whenever he was celebrating something.
But she risked her life to save him this time.
Who would...
Who would do that for a friend's son?
So? What are you trying to say right now?
Hey...
No, no. It's just strange.
Seriously, why wake me up for this?
It's strange. It's strange.
This isn't more than just strange.
You didn't have to get us a meal, Pil Sung.
I felt so bad and grateful toward you.
You got injured saving me.
Is it okay to come to work already?
Of course. I came out because I'm okay.
I feel okay since I took medicine and got good sleep.
How about you? Are you really okay?
Yes, I'm fine, thanks to you.
Thank you so much.
How many times did you thank me? Stop now.
How long will you thank each other for?
Enough with the pleasantries.
How about we start eating now?
Shall we?
- Let's eat.
- Enjoy, President Jang.
- The blue one.
- This blue one?
Yes, yes, yes.
No! What happened?
Isn't it working?
I got it!
- Try again.
- Okay, okay.
No, no. I can get it. I can get it.
- Again! Get another one!
- Another one? Okay.
Yes, I hope Pil sung and Ma Ri continue to get along like this.
I hope they continue to be happy like this.
- This one, right?
- Yes.
Go further.
Gosh, it's so hot.
- Ji Yeong.
- Yes.
I'll make your favorite, kimchijjim, with ribs.
Whenever you finished a strict diet for a shoot,
you always wanted my kimchijjim with ribs.
You ate two bowls of rice easily.
Was I like that?
I still like kimchijjim with ribs.
Oh, my. You lost your memory, but your taste buds haven't changed.
Yes, this is Baek Mi Ja of Bbaek Entertainment.
A nightclub wants Ms. Kim to perform as the market lady
from "Don't Lie to Me." Do you want her to do it?
There will be 10 shows. I'll negotiate the pay.
Excuse me.
Ji Yeong is about to play a supporting actor in a 30-billion-won show.
She'll be a star once it gets on air.
So, get her something dignified instead.
Such as cosmetics or drinks commercials.
Call me if you get something like that, okay?
Seriously, what was he thinking?
What was it? What was it about?
Huh? You don't have to know.
Why do we keep getting gigs like this?
Hand me those.
You're preparing the restaurant opening well, right?
Of course, I am. Everything is going perfectly.
- You mean it, right?
- Of course. I'll really surprise you this time.
I'm opening a restaurant thanks to Pil Sung.
We raised our son well, right?
Yes, we're so lucky to have him.
Yes, I'll work hard and pay Pil Sung back.
And I'll buy him a nice apartment when he gets married, too.
- Gosh, really?
- Of course.
My gosh! How exciting!
Jin Dan, why did you start drinking again?
You said you'd get your act together.
The in-laws' gathering is next week. You can't be like this.
Mom,
can we push back the in-laws' gathering?
Why would you push it back?
Why are we rushing it so much?
It's not like we'd get married immediately.
Gong Jin Dan, will you keep saying "Do Ra" again?
Is this because of her?
Are you still not back to your senses?
Gosh, I don't know.
I don't know why I'm like this, either.
What do we do with you?
My gosh.
[Goban Restaurant]
Hyeon Cheol, this is our restaurant, right?
Yes, Mom. This is our restaurant.
Congratulations, Oppa.
Thank you.
Congratulations, Father.
I paid off the loan and got a nice restaurant like this, thanks to you.
I'll work hard.
We'll work hard and pay you back in full.
What are you talking about? I gave you that money.
Gosh, no.
You have to work and pay back the contract money.
How could I just take your hard-earned money?
Parents and children need to be financially independent, too.
Yes, I agree with Mom.
Much, much later, then.
It's big. There's endless space back there.
This is so great.
Welcome.
Two people? Over there, please.
Gosh, Soo Yeon! Ma Ri! What brings you here?
What do you mean? We couldn't miss your opening.
Jin Taek wanted to come, too, but he suddenly had to attend a seminar in Jeju-do.
He said he's sorry and he'll make sure to come next time.
He sent us the beautiful garland. That's enough.
Seeing the garland from the APP Group's chairman,
the other store owners asked us how we knew him.
Hyeon Cheol is feeling so confident.
He's been smiling all day.
Should I tell him to send one every day, then?
Gosh, come on.
You came.
- Yes, Pil Sung.
- Hi, Oppa.
Hi, Ma Ri. You should eat.
Come this way.
Let's go.
Give me that.
Pil Sung, have a seat. I'll grill instead.
No, we grill for you here.
I'll make it tasty for you.
Look how sweaty you got.
Thank you.
Why would she wipe the sweat off someone else's son's face?
Why would he do that for a man in his 30s?
I know, huh?
That's a bit much.
I know she's Seon Yeong's friend, but people might get the wrong idea.
Wrong idea?
Like what?
Huh?
- It's nothing.
- Have some, Mother.
Hey, hey. Your friend, Soo Yeon...
just because Pil Sung was sweating...
she wiped it off of his face like this.
Who does that to a friend's son?
Tell her not to do that anymore.
It looks kind of weird.
Mother, come on.
Why is that weird? It's okay to wipe off someone's sweat.
- Go ahead and eat.
- Excuse me.
Yes.
Why would she look at someone else's son like that?
She's so strange.
- Take care.
- Come back with Chairman next time.
- Did you enjoy the food, Ma Ri?
- Yes.
- Come back again.
- Okay.
Thank you for coming.
- Take care.
- Get back safely.
Myeong Dong, this looks like Ma Ri's earring.
I'll give this to her now.
Okay.
Mom, can I hang out here for a little longer?
What do you mean you want to hang out here?
Didn't you see how busy everyone was?
Well, I don't mean I'll just hang out.
I want to help them with Oppa, too.
Do it next time.
Since today's the opening day, it's too crowded and chaotic. Get in the car.
I hate saying goodbye to Oppa like this all the time.
I want to live with him in our house.
PIl Sung is my oppa and your son.
How long do we have to be separated like this?
Ma Ri, you promised not to say that.
Get in the car.
Come on.
Good girl. Get in.
My goodness.
What did I just hear?
What did she say just now?
Have a seat.
Mom, lie down.
Why are you suddenly dizzy?
Did you overdo it today?
What if you have anemia?
Let's go to the hospital and get a blood test.
I don't have anemia.
It's because I'm in shock. I'm in shock.
Shock? About what?
Myeong Dong, I...
I think I know who Pil Sung's biological mother is.
Pil Sung's biological mother?
What are you talking about all of a sudden?
Myeong Dong, this is a secret between us two.
You have to keep it a secret until we die.
Especially from Pil Sung and your sister-in-law.
Come on, seriously!
Today is Oppa's opening day. Why are you wasting time instead of helping?
Myeong Dong, Ma Ri's mom... your sister-in-law's friend, President Jang.
She's Pil Sung's biological mother.
Pil Sung is that woman's son.
What are you talking about?
This is no good. Let's ask the doctor if you have dementia.
Come on! I don't have dementia...
When I followed them to give Ma Ri her earrings back,
I overheard clearly with these two ears.
Do you know what Ma Ri and President Jang said?
"How long do we have to be separated?
Pil Sung is your son and my oppa."
That's what she said.
Mom, you're acting strange.
Let's get you tested for dementia.
Come on. What's wrong with you?
It's because you're talking nonsense.
Don't say stuff like that to anyone.
You'd get arrested for defamation if you say that without evidence.
And Ma Ri has said weird things about him since she likes him. Don't you know that?
Is that why?
I'm going back to the store.
We're so busy because it's Oppa's opening day, but you're talking nonsense.
What's wrong with you?
Did I really hear that wrong?
I don't think so. My ears work just fine.
Am I wrong?
- Cheers!
- Thank you.
Do Sik, don't skip the team dinner from now on.
Stop disappearing all the time.
Okay, I won't.
The soju ad model is Kim Na Bi now.
You're right. Wasn't it Jo Sa Ra before?
Jo Sa Ra got cancelled because of prostitution.
Park Do Ra killed herself because of it, too.
Park Do Ra was innocent of that.
What do you mean? There were articles about it, too.
It was to pay off her mom's gambling debt.
The photos at the hotel were everywhere, too.
It's not true, I said.
Why do you talk about it as if it is?
What do you mean it isn't?
You can still look it up on the internet.
It's all fake news.
Enough is enough, please.
Geez, why is this asshole pissing me off?
That's enough. Why are you ruining the mood?
You're drunk. You're all drunk.
Hey, why would you call it fake news?
Should I show you a photo of Park Do Ra with a man at the hotel?
It says she died out of shame after sleeping with someone for money.
It's not true, you bastard.
Hey, what are you? Are you her cousin or something?
Or are you her older brother?
Yes, I'm Park Do Ra's older brother.
Die, you bastard!
Hey! Park Do Sik!
What happened? Why did you hit someone?
You've never done this before!
Excuse me, are you Mr. Park's mother?
Yes, I'm his mother.
I'm his younger sister.
The victim is at the hospital. Just try to settle.
It'd be a headache if it gets escalated.
Looks like they blew off steam over drinks.
No need to have a criminal record at a young age.
He doesn't even have previous criminal records.
You little. Seriously...
Gosh. My goodness.
Seriously.
W-What did you say? 50 million won (~$36K)?
We have no 50 million. We can't get that money.
Please forgive us just once, sir.
Send him to jail if you don't, then.
Is Park Do Ra his sister or something?
He did this to me by saying Park Do Ra died because she had sex for money.
I can't settle unless you pay me 50 million, okay?
Let the law take care of it! Let's!
He should do time for doing this to me.
My gosh, please have some of this.
This, too. This, too.
Please forgive him just once, Sir.
We're sorry.
I didn't know he got into a fight because of me.
I don't even have five million. How will I get 50 million?
Hold on. Should I call Do Jun?
No, he must be living off his small wage.
He can't have any money.
Calling him would only make him worry.
Have some water and calm down, Ahjumma.
Hey, Ji Yeong. Do you have money, by chance?
Could I use it if you do?
We need to stop your brother from going to jail.
I got five million back for the security deposit when I moved out of Director's house.
Is that all you have?
Yes.
Hey, how about the contract fee you're getting from the drama?
Ask Jae Dong when that'll get deposited. Hurry, hurry.
Okay.
President Lee, it's me.
When will I receive the contract fee?
Is that so? Okay.
No, no. E-E-Everything's fine.
I was just curious.
Okay, okay. Bye.
That won't work, either.
I get 30% after the first shoot, but that needs to be used as project expenses.
Gosh, what are we supposed to do, then?
Oh, how about your grandma in the countryside? Does she have money?
My grandma? Gosh.
How would she have any money?
What are we going to do about Do Sik?
What do we do about Do Sik?
Gosh, Do Ra. I mean, Ji Yeong...
What? Did you come up with a solution?
You can get 30 million if you agree to do something.
What? What is it?
I'll do it right now if there's a solution like that.
What is there to think about?
[Hoho Night Club]
I didn't want you to do stuff like this again,
but this is the only way to make money now.
It's okay.
They'll pay me 30 million if I sing "Pick one, pick one" 10 times.
Of course, I'll do it.
There isn't an easier way to make money than this.
And we can't let Do Sik go to jail.
He did that for his sister, Do Ra.
Do Ra... I mean, Ji Yeong, thank you so much.
Thank you so much, my daughter. Thank you.
Don't worry, Ahjumma.
Everyone!
Thank you so much for waiting.
We barely managed to invite the star of "Don't Lie to Me."
You know her, too, right?
"Pick one, pick one. Look around. Pick one."
Here's Lady "Pick one, pick one," Kim Ji Yeong!
I want to live with him in our house.
PIl Sung is my oppa and your son.
How long do we have to be separated?
Ma Ri...
Yes, I heard them right. I definitely did.
I-Is Pil Sung really President Jang's son?
If that's true... That makes no sense.
What do I do?
Why am I shivering right now?
Where did the other earring go, anyway?
Yes, Grandma.
What? You have my other earring?
Why is no one home, by the way?
Everyone went to the restaurant to work.
By the way, Ma Ri, you and I are true friends, right?
Of course, we are.
You know true friends can't lie to each other, right?
I guess that's true.
Why do you ask that?
The day our restaurant opened,
you left this earring behind.
So, I followed you to give this back to you
and heard everything you and your mom, President Jang, said.
W-What did you hear?
You said...
"Pil Sung is your son and my oppa.
How long do we have to be separated?
I don't like saying goodbye to him all the time.
When can we start living together?"
You said that.
What?
Ma Ri... is Pil Sung your mom's son?
Is Pil Sung your biological brother?
Grandma, no! This is top secret.
No one can find out about this.
My gosh, i-is it true?
M-Ma Ri, is it all true?
Yes. You won't... you won't...
You won't tell anyone about it, right?
My dad can't find out about it. That can never happen.
If so, my mom would get kicked out.
She'd get kicked out?
Does it mean Pil Sung isn't your dad's son?
Yes, he isn't my dad's son. He's my mom's son.
He can't find out about it.
Why did you have to find out about it?
Oh, my God...
W-What...
[Seoul Segwang Police Station]
- Oppa!
- Do Sik! Do Sik!
You shouldn't have come.
Look at your face. You lost so much weight already.
Oppa, are you okay?
Looks like you got injured from the fight, too.
This is no good. Let's go to the hospital first.
No, no. I don't have to.
I can't spend money at the hospital after what I did.
I'm okay.
Mom, I'm sorry.
Ji Yeong, I'm sorry.
Eat tofu. Don't ever come back here.
Don't get into fights because you're angry.
Just eat the tofu.
By the way, how did you settle?
You didn't pay him or anything, right?
You know we have no money!
Just eat the tofu! Eat it!
We didn't spend any money. Don't worry and eat. Hurry.
- Take a big bite! Come on!
- Yes, yes. Eat a lot of it. Eat!
[GOGO Entertainment]
Yes.
President Jang, we have a bit of an issue.
What is it?
Have a look at this.
["Pick One" lady's exclusive show!]
What's this?
Ms. Kim, is it true that you're performing here?
Yes, it's true.
Are you serious?
I-I'm sorry, President Jang.
Director and Writer, I'm so sorry.
Ms. Kim!
Why would you do this after agreeing to be on our drama?
You didn't tell us anything.
Didn't you check the contract?
Didn't you read the pre-shoot reminder?
I'm sorry. I was so desperate for money.
And I had no idea this would be a problem.
You didn't know this would be a problem?
How could you be this thoughtless?
I'm sorry.
I should've taken better care of her since she has no experience.
It's all my fault.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Let's just dismiss her instead of discussing it further.
If we feature an actor who sings and dances at a place like this,
our drama would be considered cheap, too.
Writer, this isn't right. Don't you agree?
I'll understand as we're dismissing Ms. Kim, then.
Director Go, we could've done something if it were just once.
But she needs to keep working at the nightclub.
If all of this is true, we can't continue to work with Ms. Kim.
Can't believe this happened.
Ms. Kim,
how could you do something so careless?
Tell me what happened.
My older brother...
had a team dinner with his colleagues
and one of them said Park Do Ra died because she got caught having sex for money.
I suppose he said bad things about Park Do Ra.
So, Oppa had a fistfight with him and the colleague got injured a bit.
He said he'd send him to jail if he didn't pay him to settle.
The reason he got into a fight was to defend me of all things.
I couldn't let him go to jail for that.
Getting the settlement money was all I could think of then.
The nightclub said they'd pay me 30 million won in advance if I performed 10 times.
That's why I performed just once.
You should've told me first if you were in that situation!
How could I ask you for money?
President Baek made you do this, didn't she?
No, I volunteered.
Tell it to me straight.
How did you know about that place?
You've never even been to a place like that.
President Baek did tell you to do this!
Director Go, why do you keep blaming my mom?
Why do you keep making her a bad person?
I said I'd do it. I did.
And I couldn't send Oppa to jail.
That was all I could think about.
That's why I did it without considering the consequences.
I really didn't know this would be such a serious problem.
I'm so sorry, Director.
It's 100% my fault.
I did the wrong thing without thinking about our drama.
I'm...
getting fired now, right?
I'm so sorry.
President Baek, what the hell is this?
How could you do such a thing?
Ms. Kim is about to get fired because of you.
They're about to cancel her contract right now.
And I'm your co-CEO.
How could you send her there without even telling me?
I mean, she's still unknown as an actor and the shoot hasn't started yet. So I thought it'd be okay.
We were desperate for money. What could we do?
Ji Yeong's brother is my son. Was I supposed to send him to jail?
You should've looked for another solution, then.
As soon as she becomes popular in "House of Roses," what if
videos of her singing dressed up as the "Pick One" lady at a nightclub appears
all over on social media? What are you going to do then?
It's all over once it spreads on social media!
Don't you know how things operate in this field?
So?
Are they firing Ji Yeong?
Yes. And we can't argue about it, either.
What will you do now?
[Hoho Night Club]
I'll give you back what you paid Ms. Kim.
Please cancel the contract for the rest of the shows.
There's a penalty fee. Do you still want to cancel?
Yes, how much is that?
Director Go, can I see you for a moment?
We needed money. I thought I should put out the fire first.
I did it without thinking through it.
I really didn't know this would happen.
And my Do Ra...
I mean, my Ji Yeong can't get fired from the drama.
Please forgive me just once. I beg you.
I know you needed money, but still.
How could you sell Do Ra...
I mean, Ji Yeong to a place like that?
What do you mean, sell? How could you say that?
My son was about to go to jail, but there was no way to get money.
And I didn't force her to do it.
Do Ra said she'd do it. How could I stop her?
Did you already forget...
how much pain Do Ra was in because of you?
Did you already forget what kind of hell she went through because of you?
If she came back to life,
if you're truly her mother, you should've embraced her more warmly than anyone.
But...
how could you make Do Ra sing at a place like that?
Can you call yourself a mother?
What did you say?
This is why I didn't tell you Do Ra was alive. This is why.
That's how desperate I was. That's how...
Don't you feel sorry for me at all?
Seriously, how dare you...
President Baek!
I'm warning you one more time.
If you do something like this again, I swear I won't sit still.
Keep that in mind.
Director Go, it's not like that. Let me...
Wow!
How dare that bastard blabber his mouth at me?
My daughter is mine. Why does he care how I use her?
How dare he tell me what to do?
Wow, that bastard. Seriously, how dare he?
This... Where do I hide this?
No, no, no. I need to tell them about this.
How could I hide something this important?
No, I still promised Ma Ri, though.
How could I...
Gosh, you've got to be kidding me.
Mom, what is it?
Why are you so surprised?
W-What? I didn't do anything.
What's that? Why are you hiding it?
Did you cause trouble again?
Gosh, I said it's nothing. It's nothing.
Geez! Give me that!
This is a DNA test result.
Mom, why do you have something like this?
Did you do this by chance?
Yes. I-I did it.
I took Pil Sung's toothbrush and Ma Ri's hair.
They really are biological siblings.
W-What did you say?
Pil Sung and Ma Ri are s-siblings?
So, Ma Ri's mom gave birth to Pil Sung. She's his biological mother.
What? Hold on...
Gosh, no way!
[A and B are biologically related and are siblings.]
Mom, I'm home.
Seon Yeong has to run an errand somewhere.
Aigoo, aigoo. So tired...
What's with you two? What's going on?
What's that piece of paper?
What's that?
Let me see. What is it?
- Oppa, Pil Sung's biological mother
- Hey, hey! You little...
I promised Ma Ri to keep it a secret!
Oppa needs to know. You think that's important?
He's Pil Sung's father.
What about Pil Sung? Did something happen to him?
What's wrong?
Oppa, have a look at this.
- What's this?
- Pil Sung and Ma Ri...
They're siblings, apparently.
What? Seriously.
Mom, what's she saying?
Cheers!
It's so nice and refreshing.
I know. It's so nice and cold.
Soo Yeon, Hyeon Cheol has always wanted to have his own restaurant so badly.
He achieved his dream, thanks to you. Thank you so much.
Don't say that.
Pil Sung got him to open the restaurant.
It's because you paid him a lot for the contract.
So, it's all thanks to you.
You keep saying I paid him a lot for the contract.
How many times did I say I hired our Director Go because he's talented?
Thank our Pil Sung instead, okay?
Soo Yeon, you must've been an angel in your previous life.
Or my mom sent you to me from heaven.
I don't know what I've done to deserve a friend like you.
Gosh, I'm tired of having to thank you constantly.
I'm thankful, too... that I have a friend like you by my side.
that I have a friend like you by my side.
Without you, I would've gone through a lot of hardship.
You've always been by my side whenever I struggled.
Okay, okay.
I'll treat you properly tonight for that reason.
Should we drink up this cold beer and do karaoke later, too?
and do karaoke later, too?
Yes, yes! Sounds great!
Cheers!
Who are you looking at right now?
I'm standing in front of you right now
Don't make me wait too long
Stay somewhere not too far away
I'll tell you one day
That I love you...
Soo Yeon!
What was that?
Wait...
H-How could this happen?
Thinking back now,
that woman has been frequenting our house ever since we took in Pil Sung.
She said she decided to be friends with Seon Yeong.
Think about how nice she's been to Seon Yeong and Pil Sung.
She did all this on purpose, I'm telling you.
She wanted to keep an eye on her son after abandoning him here.
A character like that is considered a villain in soap operas.
No, no. She's evil. She's evil.
She's the most evil person ever.
Seon Yeong was so proud of her as a friend.
She depended on her and appreciated her so much. How could she do this?
They say there's nothing scarier than humans.
Oppa, will you tell Seon Yeong about this?
What are you talking about? Why would I tell her?
She'd pass out if she heard about it.
No, she'll die. She'll die...
And Pil Sung is my son. My son.
He's not her son, but mine. Okay?
So, Mom, pretend you know nothing about it.
Okay, I will.
Go Myeong Dong, you can't say anything, either.
I won't, Oppa. Don't worry.
Honey! Mother, I'm home!
Oh my gosh, S-Seon Yeong must be here.
What do we do?
What do you mean? Keep your mouth sealed.
What are you all doing here?
We discussed whether we needed anything else at the restaurant.
Where have you been, Honey?
You were able to open the restaurant thanks to Soo Yeon.
So, I treated her to thank her.
We had a beer together like the old days
and we sang together, promising a forever friendship at the karaoke.
I'll go to bed now.
I'm so tired!
They promised a forever friendship.
- What do we do with her?
- My goodness.
What are we going to do now?
She has blind faith in that bitch.
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday to you, dear son
Happy birthday, my dear son.
Blow out the candle and make a wish, Pil Sung.
Gosh, you're embarrassing me.
I told you not to do this. I'm too old.
- What am I, a child?
- Come on.
- Stop complaining and just do it.
- Seriously.
Father, Mom, Grandma, and Auntie, thank you.
- Happy birthday.
Happy birthday.
Gosh, Honey. Are you crying?
Gosh, you're so funny.
I-I'm not crying.
Gosh, seriously.
Father.
I love you!
I'll go to work now.
Gosh, hey. You should have a slice of cake.
Later.
Aigoo, my son is so busy.
It feels like it was yesterday when he was crawling around here.
When did he grow up so much?
Honey, you're so funny.
I heard men go through menopause, too.
You're probably the only man who cried singing "Happy Birthday" to his son.
He used to be this big, but now he's that big.
Of course, he tears up. Why wouldn't he?
Gosh, well... um...
Looks like you're having menopause, too.
Come on now.
- My goodness.
- Is anyone home?
Who's that?
Unni, someone must be here.
Gosh, Soo Yeon.
You shouldn't have sent all this.
You remember Pil Sung's birthday every year.
Yes, thank you.
What?
It's Pil Sung's birthday. Why did you send presents for Hyeon Cheol and me?
Seriously.
Gosh, you're driving me crazy.
Okay, thank you.
It's Pil Sung's birthday.
She sent you and Hyeon Cheol presents, too?
Yes, she's telling us we went through a lot raising Pil Sung all this time or something.
Anyway, she's always coming up with excuses to send presents.
Yes.
This is a purse for me.
This is a belt for you.
Why don't you try this on?
It's okay.
Why does that woman send stuff like this on our son's birthday?
Tell her to care for her daughter instead!
Honey, what's wrong with you?
She's always been generously sending presents for Pil Sung's birthday.
Why are you suddenly doing this?
And what do you mean, "that woman"?
What... What are we, beggars?
Can't we dress or feed ourselves?
We do just fine without stuff like this.
Tell her not to send stuff like this anymore.
You shouldn't accept anything, either.
Gosh, what's wrong with you?
Geez...
Hyeon Cheol, what's wrong with you?
She'd end up finding out at this rate.
You told us to play ignorant.
Why would you do this right now?
Am I supposed to tolerate this, then?
We didn't know anything before.
But now we know what she's thinking.
We know what that cunning woman's intentions are.
Are we supposed to just accept stuff from her?
What else can you do, then?
Do you think we want to?
As you said, if Seon Yeong finds out the truth, she'll die.
And Pil Sung would find out, too.
Do you want that to happen right now?
Yes, I know I shouldn't. But this isn't right.
How dare she say we raised our son well and stuff like that?
She abandoned her child. How dare she? How dare she?
No, Mom. This is no good.
I'll go see her first thing in the morning and warn her.
I'll tell her never to overstep her boundaries.
I'll tell her to stop showing interest to Pil Sung and Seon Yeong.
Honey...
what are you talking about right now?
H-Honey...
A woman who abandoned her baby?
Who are you talking about right now?
S-Seon Yeong.
Mother, by chance...
are you talking about Pil Sung's biological mother?
W-Who is it? Who's that woman?
Well, H-Honey...
You said it just now.
You said you'd go see her!
That you'd warn her!
T-Tell me who it is.
Tell me who that woman is.
Who's the woman you said you'd go and see?!
It's Jang Soo Yeon. Jang Soo Yeon.
Your friend, Jang Soo Yeon.
W-What...
What did you say?
Yes, you need to know, too. Yes.
Pil Sung's biological mother is your friend, Jang Soo Yeon.
So, tell her not to do stuff like this again. Never again.
How...
Honey, Honey!
Seon Yeong, Seon Yeong...
Hyeon Cheol, what do we do? Seon Yeong!
- Honey!
- Seon Yeong, wake up.
Let me see.
How sweet.
- Let's go.
- Gosh.
Gosh. Oh, my! Seon Yeong!
You're Soo Yeon, right? Jang Soo Yeon.
Yes, that's right. Do you recognize me?
Of course. Everyone knew you in high school.
By the way, what brings you to this neighborhood?
I was on my way to meet someone, and I saw you.
Oh, my gosh!
How cute.
I-Is it a boy or a girl?
It's a boy.
Gosh, he's so cute.
O-Oh, S-Seon Yeong, it's so nice to see my high school classmate.
Let's keep in touch from now on.
Gosh, sweetie.
Are you curious?
Seon Yeong, may I hold Dae Chung just once?
Of course, go ahead.
Here.
Gosh, so cute.
It's Soo Yeon.
Soo Yeon, what's wrong?
It's because Dae Chung is so lovely.
I want to have a baby like him, too.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Gosh, come on.
Soo Yeon, you can have a baby, too.
Gosh.
Yes! You beat me!
Huh? It's Auntie Soo Yeon.
- It's Auntie Soo Yeon.
- Dae Chung!
Dae Chung! Gosh, have you been well? Have you been well?
Gosh, you grew so much, Dae Chung.
Give me a kiss.
Aigoo, aigoo.
Honey.
Take this medicine.
Honey, where are you going?
Honey, Honey!
- Seon Yeong, what's wrong?
- Where are you going, Honey?
- Honey!
- Seon Yeong, what's wrong?
[It's Happiness]
Seon Yeong, what brings you here at this hour?
You bitch.
Seon Yeong.
You bitch!
[Beauty and Mr. Romantic]
Why did I fall in love?
I shouldn't have given you my heart at all
I've already fallen for you
I'm not able to free myself anymore
But we're drifting apart
President Baek must've checked your contract.
Do you think she would've done that if she cared about you?
How could she cause trouble like this?
She has no basic understanding. I don't have a good feeling.
What did you want to talk about urgently?
I was fired, right?
What did you do wrong, exactly?
Just tell me. Tell me.
I'll tell you later. Later.
I said I'll tell you later! So, stop this, everyone!
Please don't let Pil Sung know about this.
I don't want to break his heart.
If I could forget you by saying I would