♪Holding a sword that pierces nine heavens
I'm as carefree as I can be♪
♪Not going to waste my youth while I'm young♪
♪I slay demons at the end of the divine path♪
♪I stop by Hell♪
♪I accept all challenges that come my way♪
♪A young man with two lives♪
♪Roaming the martial world
hundreds of nations under his feet♪
♪Had his bloodline awakened in a secret realm♪
♪Refined his body from the inside
in thunderstorms♪
♪A hero of the ancient world♪
♪Boiling hot human blood♪
♪His hand stretches through space♪
♪Which fighter will make it to the top?♪
♪In the 33rd realm
he'll be slashing the great sky♪
♪That's me, a living legend♪
[Dominator of Martial Gods]
[Adapted from original work of "Dominator of Martial Gods",
The Universe Part I by Ruo Hong Culture]
[Episode 26]
Lingshan
is inside this cave?
Oh no.
We must go in there now!
What are you doing?
I don't want you to be cold.
Someone is coming.
Lingshan!
What…
What is going on here?
Qin Chen!
What did you do to Princess Lingshan…
The
two of them
stayed in the same room,
not properly dressed…
Chen is…
Qin Chen!
Get away from her!
What did you do to Lingshan?
You animal!
Lingshan,
let me see
what happened to you.
He didn't do anything to you, did he?
Zixun, what are you saying?
I was attacked by
Nian Wuji's Formless Soul Poison,
and Qin Chen
was helping me detoxify.
Is that so?
Are you sure
that he didn't do anything to you?
Zixun!
Get dressed well.
I'm glad you are okay.
Well…
Where are Nian Wuji and the others?
Why are you here?
Nian Wuji and Cao Heng
have died.
What?
Did they die?
What's going on?
How did that happen?
Why did they die?
Yeah. What…
That's what happened.
Everyone,
since Nian Wuji and Cao Heng died,
the Zhao and the Ghost Immortal Sect
would certainly not let this go.
What happened today
mustn't be leaked to others
except among us.
Whoever goes against it
will be executed!
Your Highness,
and Princess, don't worry.
I, Wang Qiming,
will keep my mouth shut about this.
We will keep our mouths shut.
Xiao Zhan,
the Xuan
has lost over 70 participants this time,
which is twice as many as last time.
Yuchi,
I remember
last time, the Xuan
only had
19 people last to the end.
Seems like this year,
their result will be even more pathetic.
Princess Zixun,
and Qin Chen,
don't let anything happen to you.
Xiao Zhan,
hurry up and check it out.
Maybe another two from the Xuan.
Zuo Tian, Wang Feng!
Why are you two out?
General…
It was Zhao…
Zhao…
Yuchi Cheng,
can't you even recognize
your people from the Zhao?
Don't get too carried away!
Zhou Luo!
What's wrong with you?
I…
I'm fine.
Yuchi Cheng,
this is the karma of the Zhao.
Xiao Zhan,
don't get too excited.
The Zhao
is just
losing a few participants.
Compared to the Xuan,
we are way ahead of you.
Ling Zhong,
maybe
the next one out
is from your Ghost Immortal Sect.
Ridiculous.
Our Ghost Immortal Sect
is not as useless as
the Xuan.
Ling Xiao!
Why are you out?
What…
What on earth happened in there?
People are being sent out
one after another.
Could there be
a brawl happening inside?
-He's right!
-A brawl?
-Yes.
-Right.
Indeed.
How surprising!
He is from the Ghost Immortal Sect!
Xiao Zhan!
Just you wait!
This is not right.
The Ghost Immortal Sect apprentices
and the Zhao people
are knocked out in a row.
Looks like
something has happened in there.
I'll have a doctor treat them.
When they wake up,
we will find out
what exactly happened in there.
Doctor, hurry up!
You must bring him back to life.
How do you feel?
What happened in there?
Tell me!
Sir,
it was Prince Zhao Wei from the Xuan.
He brought people
to surround our Zhao people.
What?
The Xuan still has the power to fight back!
What about Prince Heng and Nian Wuji?
Why didn't those two worthless ones
stop their attacks?
We haven't seen
Prince Heng
and Nian Wuji for a long time.
These two useless guys
must have gone somewhere to mess around.
How many attackers from the Xuan?
I…
I didn't see clearly.
Trash!
A whole bunch of you!
Save him, still.
Time is up.
The test is over.
Li Qingfeng is out.
Go look for the prince and princess!
Yes!
Your Highness.
Princess.
Stop Li Qingfeng!
What is going on?
Li Qingfeng tried to
kill me in the trial area.
If it wasn't for Wang Qiming,
I'm afraid
I would have died in there.
Really?
Yan Huai!
Capture this man.
I will interrogate him later.
Yes,
Your Highness.
King of Lingwu.
It…
Princess,
we are still at the competition.
Let's talk about it when we get back.
Let's go.
How are these brats
still alive?
Prince Heng and Nian Wuji are so useless!
They can't even do such a small thing!
No!
They should have come out a long time ago.
Yuchi Cheng.
Why are
Young Master and Prince Heng
still inside?
Go…
go look for them!
Don't panic.
Let me find them.
Did you find them?
No.
Look more carefully!
Still no.
Is there
something wrong with the array?
Yes.
It must be the array.
Looks like
the Zhao and the Ghost Immortal Sect
lost many talents.
In the last Competition of Five Kingdoms,
the Xuan lost the most people.
But the table has turned this time.
Not only
their ordinary participants
didn't make it,
but also talents
like Cao Heng and Nian Wuji
were still trapped inside.
Could they be
dead already?
Not possible.
They are high-level pros,
with jade plates even.
Who would be able to kill them?
Even if they did encounter danger,
they could teleport.
Are they talking about Cao Heng and Nian Wuji?
They have died already.
We saw their bodies.
What?
What did you say?
Yuchi Cheng!
What are you going to do to my You people?
Wei Tianming!
He said our Prince Heng of the Zhao had died.
I
just wanted to make sure.
What did you see?
Make it clear to him.
Here's what happened:
The day before yesterday,
when we were practicing,
we suddenly heard the sound of fighting nearby,
so we rushed over.
However, when we arrived there,
the battle was already over.
We saw the bodies of
Cao Heng and Nian Wuji on the ground.
No way.
That's not true.
It's not possible.
Are you sure they were Prince Heng
and Young Master Nian?
Yes!
And they all saw them too.
I saw them too.
They were indeed Cao Heng
and Nian Wuji.
There were other martial artists
from the Zhao
and the Ghost Immortal Sect there.
How…
How is that possible?
Right,
where is Qin Feng?
He is right there.
What happened to his arm?
Who injured him?
Qin Feng.
Qin Feng!
Your arm!
I came across a despicable blood beast
in the trial area.
It snuck up on me
while I didn't pay attention.
Qin Chen,
am I right?
Maybe
Heaven thinks
your heart is evil
and wants you to
behave humbly from now on.
This time, all thanks to you, Qin Chen,
so the Xuan could
go through the test so smoothly.
If you didn't
contrive to kill Cao Heng and Nian Wuji,
I'm afraid
the Xuan would suffer a heavy loss.
Chen!
Qin Chen did it…
What?
Qin Feng, what nonsense are you saying?
I saw it with my own eyes.
Princess Lingshan,
you were there too.
Did you forget?
You…
Get him!
You bastard!
I'll kill you!
Get back!
Xiao Zhan,
your Xuan kid
dares to kill the prince of the Zhao!
I will kill this evil bastard today,
even at the cost of my life.
Stop it!
Who do you think you are
to try to stop me?
Get lost!
Qin Chen, you rascal!
Go to hell!
Chen!
Be careful!
You're courting death!
Stay back, you all!
Stop it!
Wei Tianming,
this brat murdered
Prince Cao Heng of the Zhao.
Today,
I must kill him!
Wei Tianming,
stay back.
If this brat does not die,
how can my Ghost Immortal Sect
keep a foothold in the Northwest?
The Competition of Five Kingdoms is over,
And all parties shall not attack afterwards.
This is the rule set down back then.
Who dares to disobey?
You…
Who said that Cao Heng and Nian Wuji
were killed by me?
In the trial area,
you fought Cao Heng and Nian Wuji,
plus what Qin Feng said.
Who else could it be if you weren't the killer?
Only idiots like you two
would believe Qin Feng.
-You!
-What!
What do you mean!
The whole the Xuan kingdom knows
that Qin Feng has grudges against me.
Moreover, he kept saying that
he saw me poisoning them with his own eyes,
indicating that he was ambushed at the scene.
Also,
in terms of strength,
Qin Feng is more like the murderer.
Among the five kingdoms,
except You Qianxue,
only Qin Feng
has the ability to kill Cao Heng and Nian Wuji.
Qin Chen,
don't you try to quibble!
Cao Heng and Nian Wuji
were unable to gather vital energy
after being poisoned by you
and were killed by your sword.
This friend here, please describe
how Cao Heng and Nian Wuji looked
after they died.
I…
Don't worry, just tell the truth.
The corpses of Cao Heng
and Nian Wuji were tragic.
They should have experienced
a fierce battle.
As for whether they were poisoned or not,
I don't know.
You heard him, everyone.
Cao Heng and Nian Wuji
died of a battle.
However,
my meager cultivation
made it difficult
to escape from the two.
[Damn it.]
[In order to make it more convincing,]
[I deliberately said
that the two died of poisoning.]
[Now there is trouble.]
After poisoning,
you naturally tried your best to buy time,
and when the poison took effect,
you made your move to take their lives.
What's wrong with that?
Qin Feng,
you still don't realize it.
You kept saying that
you were at the scene at that time,
but you just stood by
when Princess Lingshan
and I were in danger.
After Princess Lingshan
and I narrowly escaped,
Cao Heng and Nian Wuji were killed
after a fierce battle.
And you,
Qin Feng,
coincidentally, injured your arm.
I don't care whether
the people here believe it or not.
Anyway, I think this
may be too much of a coincidence.
I think
Qin Chen's words make sense.
Yeah!
Hey, friend,
did you think of anything?
No, no, nothing.
Spit it out!
Does it have anything to do
with Prince Heng's death?
Yuchi Cheng,
what are you going to do this time?
Nothing,
just trying to figure out
how Prince Heng died.
Wei Tianming,
if your disciples of the You conceal the truth,
I would definitely not spare you!
Just tell him.
I saw
a piece of cloth on the ground.
The cloth
looked just like
what Qin Feng was wearing before.
Qin Feng!
I understand now.
Qin Feng
must be hiding at the scene
and watching the two sides fight.
After Qin Chen and Princess Lingshan
made a narrow escape,
he secretly killed them.
At that time, the two geniuses
must have been exhausted.
How could they resist
Qin Feng's sneak attack?
Fortunately, the two
had extraordinary martial prowess,
and before dying,
they desperately injured Qin Feng.
This battle was really tragic.
Don't believe his crap!
That's not what happened.
You said I killed Cao Heng and Nian Wuji,
but how did you escape the fight?
Luckily, I had a trans-space talisman
so Princess Lingshan and I could get away.
After using the trans-space talisman,
the space fluctuation
did not fade for a long time.
If you do not believe me,
you can inspect the scene
to see if there are any traces
of using the trans-space talisman.
You!
Everyone,
let me explain.
Qin Feng!
How dare you kill Prince Heng!
Young Master…
Was he really
killed by you?
Qin Chen!
You are so vicious.
It was you who killed them,
but you framed me.
Qin Feng,
the real vicious one
has always been you.
Although
you were heartless to me today,
I cannot be unjust to you.
Life and death are determined
by destiny in the life and death test.
The Zhao and the Ghost Immortal Sect,
you bully the weak with your power
and break the rules.
How can I stand by and do nothing?
If you two want to kill Qin Feng,
you have to step over my corpse first.
There are no cowards
in the Xuan Kingdom.
At this point,
Qin Chen is still speaking up for Qin Feng.
His grace and generosity are admirable!
Though falsely accused,
he still considers the overall situation
and repays resentment with virtue.
He is truly righteous
and admirable!
Look at Qin Chen, and then Qin Feng.
These two have an enormous difference!
You despicable Xuan people!
Even killing all of you
wouldn't be enough to avenge Prince Heng!
Young Master wouldn't die for nothing.
Wei Tianming!
Why would you still stop me!
The five together made the rules
of the Competition of Five Kingdoms.
If you two stubbornly
persist in doing the wrong thing,
don't blame me for being ruthless.
You!
Fine!
The Zhao Kingdom
will never let today's matter be over.
Qin Feng,
your life
shall be taken
by our Ghost Immortal Sect!
Just you wait!
Looks like
the Five Kingdoms are going to
be plunged into turmoil again.
Everyone,
the Trial of Life And Death ends here.
Half a year later
will be the arena contest.
I will await your arrival
in Ancient Southern Capital.
♪Listening to heavenly music
while drinking wine♪
♪Swinging the sword in a white robe♪
♪A palace covered with gold
songs ringing in the ears♪
♪And poems written in ink♪
♪Breathtakingly handsome is the man♪
♪The scenery stays the same
a carefree life ahead♪
♪When boredom strikes♪
♪He indulges in pleasures♪
♪Another good story in the making♪
♪Drinking the strongest wine
sleeping in off in Chang'an's tallest building♪
♪He is the most carefree person in the world♪
♪Breathtakingly handsome is the man♪
♪The scenery stays the same
a carefree life ahead♪
♪When boredom strikes♪
♪He indulges in pleasures♪
♪Another good story in the making♪
♪Drinking the strongest wine♪
♪Sleeping in off in Chang'an's tallest building♪
♪He is the most carefree person in the world♪
♪When boredom strikes♪
♪He indulges in pleasures♪
♪Another good story in the making♪
♪Drinking the strongest wine♪
♪Sleeping in off in Chang'an's tallest building♪
♪He is the most carefree person in the world♪