[The Duel of Hearts]
[Episode 9]
[Hehuan Palace]
This incident has occurred right now.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
How is the Noble Consort now?
No one is allowed to approach Hehuan Palace, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, please leave now.
You mean,
the Noble Consort is now unattended?
-Your Majesty.
Your royal health is of utmost importance.
I beg of you don't go there!
Your Majesty, you bear the duty of realm.
How could you risk it all for a consort,
and put yourself and the nation in peril?
I would like to ask General Lyu,
how this illness came upon the Consort?
What do you mean by that, Your Majesty?
You should return and ask
that Empress Dowager.
Xiao Chan, you stay here.
Yes.
-Your Majesty!
Your Majesty!
[Hehuan Palace]
Why are you up?
Don't come closer. You'll get infected.
♫Stars hanging in the night sky♫
♫And sometimes sparkle in the dark♫
♫The wind is blowing♫
♫The old dream is hidden in my eyes♫
♫Time passes,
but the thousand sorrows remain unresolved♫
With such closeness,
lips and teeth so entwined,
you can't drive me away that easily.
♫Is it true♫
♫If I get through today,
there will be countless days ahead♫
I
♫Trekking thousands of miles,
there's still no end♫
Am I dying?
Don't think nonsense.
♫Endless longing,
yet we never walk hand in hand♫
The early stage is always uncomfortable.
We've struggled to be together,
I will never lose you.
♫Is it true♫
♫That the past is always in my mind♫
Don't lie to me.
I am the Emperor.
♫It's no different from walking against the water♫
My word is my bond.
If I say you can be cured,
♫ No matter how many days I count,
we still can't be together♫
then you will be cured.
You're not the Emperor.
♫I've been thinking about the past.
How can I let it go?♫
You're Thirteen.
And you, what's your name?
I'm the thirteenth child in my family.
Just call me Thirteen.
Thirteen...
I'm sorry.
I never thought that marrying the late Emperor
would bring you even greater harm.
I only wanted to protect you.
I'm sorry.
It is I who am sorry,
it is I who failed to protect you.
Shao,
let's start over.
I will never let you go this time.
Okay?
My brother has a rash temper,
but he is a loyal minister.
If I'm not here in the future,
you must get along well.
I will continue to protect you
in places you cannot see.
I know.
I know Lyu Xun is not bad at heart.
Shao, you must hold on.
I still have so much to tell you.
There are many things we haven’t done yet.
Shao, as long as you can pull through,
I will promise you anything.
If in your next life,
you meet Lyu Shao again,
don't fall for her again.
Please don't.
Promise me.
No.
In this life and the next,
for all eternity, I only want you!
Shao, don't scare me.
Shao, Shao!
Don't scare me, Shao.
Shao!
Shao, don't scare me.
[Hehuan Palace]
Thirteen.
Shao.
I feel hot.
Why is she so burning?
Thirteen.
♫Time flies like
light and shines in your hands♫
♫Look at the blooming flowers♫
♫Day after day,
how can I mention love?♫
♫Who panicked?♫
Thirteen...
♫Your thoughts are hard to remember♫
♫I can't write anything in a rush♫
Thirteen, I feel so hot.
Thirteen...
Don't be afraid.
♫If you get the wrong idea,
time will fade♫
I'm here.
♫Flowers blooming and withering,
I have no choice♫
[Hehuan Palace]
Your Majesty, this epidemic is dangerous.
♫No matter what fate it is,
love and hate will last for years♫
Patients may have a high fever,
speak incoherently,
or even harm themselves.
♫The sea of stars in your eyes.
The love I want in my life♫
I'm afraid the Noble Consort
may not remember what Your Majesty has done for her.
♫Time flies, yet I never forget♫
She might even hurt you, Majesty.
♫In this life,
I only want to keep you in heart♫
Shao,
even if you don't remember what you
♫But everything in the world
can't be fulfilled♫
and what happened today,
I won't allow myself to lose you again.
♫Countless lovers by the sea
beg for destiny in the next life♫
♫I'd rather endure this long calamity♫
♫But the word love in this life
is destined to be unsolvable♫
♫You bring endless snow to fall in my heart♫
♫Flowers blooming and withering, I have no choice♫
♫No matter what fate it is,
love and hate will last for years♫
The starry ocean in your eyes,
and the love I want in my life
♫Time flies, yet I never forget♫
♫In this life,
I only want to keep you in heart♫
♫But everything in the world
can't be fulfilled♫
♫Countless lovers by the sea
beg for destiny in the next life♫
You are fine now.
♫I'd rather endure this long calamity♫
Finally you are fine...
♫But the word love in this life
is destined to be unsolvable♫
♫You bring endless snow to fall in my heart♫
♫In this life,
I only want to keep you in heart♫
♫But everything in the world
can't be fulfilled♫
♫Countless lovers by the sea
beg for destiny in the next life♫
♫I'd rather endure this long calamity♫
♫But the word love in this life
is destined to be unsolvable♫
♫You bring endless snow to fall in my heart♫
Why is she still so hot?
Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, the cause of the illness is found.
[The Yellow Emperor's Inner Canon]
Xiao Chan found it
under the Noble Consort's bed.
It is a contaminated clothing.
Only the Lyu Mansion has these clothes.
Summon Lyu Xun.
Yes, Your Majesty.
[Shoukang Palace]
I did it.
So what?
This is nonsense!
How can you take an epidemic so lightly?
Xun, you promised me
but refused to help,
I can only do it myself.
Shao.
I've already done it,
are you here to punish me?
Do you know how dangerous this epidemic is?
Once it spreads,
what are the consequences?
Shao is not such a reckless person.
I've repeatedly told Yuzhu
to handle this carefully.
Look at the entire palace,
isn't it only that little wench who got infected?
Shao,
you've changed.
You have changed too, Xun.
I have you in my heart,
but what about you?
I have been demoted to Empress Dowager
and confined here.
When you came in,
every word was a reproach.
You showed no concern at all.
Shao.
Just go.
Leave me alone
to die in this palace.
Shao,
I was wrong. I'm sorry.
You were so harsh just now.
You don't care for me anymore.
How could I not care for you?
I was wrong. I'm sorry.
Xun,
in this world,
we only have each other, right?
Yes,
I only have you now.
[Chengqian Palace]
Noble Consort Wen has repeatedly challenged
the Empress Dowager.
I was momentarily foolish
and stood up for my sister.
Please punish me, Your Majesty.
Don't think I don't know,
you're taking the blame for someone else.
This matter was indeed my doing alone.
Lyu Xun,
stand up!
Whatever the punishment,
I am willing to accept it.
Think about it.
Are you really protecting your sister?
It is no related to the Empress Dowager.
Hand over the prescription for the epidemic.
I won't pursue the matter further.
Wen Zhao is planted by the Wen family
as Your Majesty's eyes and ears.
Her death is no loss!
Wen Zhao's death may be insignificant,
but if you don't save her,
not only will I regret this for a lifetime
but you will too.
I don't understand, Your Majesty.
I'm merely stating the facts.
This prescription will leave side effects after use,
but it is indeed the only solution available at present.