[The Duel of Hearts]
[Episode 2]
How dare you hurt the Empress Dowager?
Who gave you the audacity?
Tell me!
Why couldn't I hurt her?
Haven't you always hated
the Empress Dowager?
Stop playing dumb.
I shall wake you up to reality.
I've been accused of killing my mother
and become irreconcilable with General Lyu.
Henceforth, I can only rely on your family.
Isn't this your plan?
I'm warning you.
Don't even think about it.
Do I make myself clear?
Li Dun hates me so much.
Now I can't tell him
I am Lyu Shao.
Otherwise,
he'll definitely trap me
in the palace forever.
[Hehuan Palace]
A'Man said she would help me
out of the palace.
How did I end up switching bodies
with Wen Zhao?
A'Man wouldn't betray me.
She must have been in trouble.
I need to find her first.
How is she?
My condolences, Your Majesty.
I'm afraid the Empress Dowager...
Shut up! Think carefully before you answer.
Your Majesty.
The Empress Dowager's pulse is not good,
but she's blessed by heaven.
Please allow me to go back
and think of another plan.
If you can't save her,
I'll ensure the entire Imperial Hospital
pays the ultimate price.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Your Highness.
It's said that the Empress Dowager's pulse
can still be felt,
but the chances of recovery are slim.
His Majesty said if she couldn't be saved,
the entire Imperial Hospital
would pay the ultimate price.
If Wen Zhao wakes up,
she'll surely use her new identity
to harm the Lyu family
and my brother.
I need to switch back to my own body.
Come with me.
What are you doing?
They are all under my command.
I've got everything arranged.
♫I look at stars hanging in the night sky♫
Li Dun.
Don't act recklessly.
I'm marrying your father
of my own free will.
♫They sometimes sparkle in the darkness♫
♫The wind is blowing♫
If you dare harm him,
♫The old dream is hidden in my eyes♫
I'll hit my head on a pillar.
♫Time flies, but a lot of sorrows remain unresolved♫
♫Is it true?♫
♫We've survived today but more days await♫
♫We've walked a long way but there's no end♫
♫With endless yearnings,
we grow old hand in hand♫
♫Is it true?♫
♫The past keeps chattering in my mind♫
♫It's just like rowing against the current♫
♫Despite counting numerous red beans,
I still can't be with you♫
♫Recollections lingering,
how can I easily let go?♫
Haven't you always wanted to run away?
♫My love for you endures through storms♫
Wake up!
As long as you can wake up,
♫I have to accept your choice to leave♫
I won't stop you no matter where you want to go.
♫Taking all thoughts and sorrows,
how can I easily let go?♫
Your Majesty.
General Lyu requests an audience.
♫Missing you chokes me,
and it's a lifelong wait♫
Let him in.
[Supreme General Lyu Xun]
General Lyu, why don't you kneel
before His Majesty?
I implore Your Majesty
to let the Empress Dowager leave the palace.
I do not approve.
Your Majesty, may I ask
why the disapproval?
She is my sister!
She is my Imperial Mother!
Your Majesty.
The Empress Dowager is dying.
I implore Your Majesty
to grant her dream of returning home.
Your Majesty, in my opinion,
returning to a familiar environment
can indeed be beneficial for a coma patient.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
[Lyu Mansion]
It's all my fault
for not taking good care of you.
[Lyu Mansion]
Noble Consort Wen has arrived!
If Wen Zhao doesn't wake up,
how can I prove my identity to my brother?
Brother.
I was just about to confront you.
You've come to me yourself.
Before you kill me,
may I say something?
Go ahead.
This is the Yuehua jade pendant
you gave me before
you went off to war,
isn't it?
You have Shao's jade pendant.
You're the one who hurt her!
Brother, it's me. I'm Shao.
What are you talking about?
Today you broke into my residence
with malicious intent.
I can kill you on the spot.
I'll kill you now
to avenge Shao!
Stop!
The Noble Consort intentionally harmed
the Empress Dowager.
What are you going to do with her,
Your Majesty?
I'll take no action.
Your Majesty truly favors
the Noble Consort.
I'm protecting you.
The rumor in the court claims
that you intend to rebel,
so you plan to harm the Noble Consort
and deliberately target the Wen family
to undermine my key support.
Since it's just a rumor,
it's not credible.
No.
If the Noble Consort dies,
I'm afraid the rumor will be confirmed.
Back to the palace.
I sent you to offer prayers,
not to cause trouble for me.
Any further malicious intent
towards the Empress Dowager
will meet with severe consequences!
Your Majesty, the Empress Dowager is dying.
Your Majesty, please spare Lyu Xun.
Noble Consort Wen,
this doesn't sound like something
you would say.