Did Han Gi Tak really have a younger sibling?
When should I come see you? One moment please.
Were you really startled?
No, why would I be?
I think your friend's waiting for you.
I'll contact you later.
Let's get off work together.
He says, "Bring Song Yi Yeon as the model."
I felt it since the fashion show. President is really cool.
You're not going to end up getting screwed, are you?
What are you talking about?
I needed a radical strategy to save the department store.
What strategy is more radical than this?
Anyway, I did end up getting great backing from my netherworld alumni.
Please take good care of me, Hyung.
Are we strangers? If you keep acting like that, I'm going to be disappointed.
Let's hurry and get Song Yi Yeon's stamp, and let's go drink.
- What do you think?
- Call!
Sunjin Department store Model Contract
Why would I?
My worth is increasing and your side is decreasing.
What good will come if I get involved with Sunjin again?
It's not getting involved but...
It's fighting Cha Jae Gook, face-to-face.
If I go along with your point of view, I guess Sunjin Department store's image will get better.
But what if another pathetic situation happens, and my image also becomes poop,
who's going to take responsibility then?
Ah. There is no way it'll become poop.
Unlike Cha Jae Gook who only makes cosmetic changes,
I'm fixing it by starting from the rotten inside.
Hey, Song Yi Yeon! Do you know how hard we worked to make this opportunity?
If both of you are going to gloss over this emotionally, both of you get out.
I'm the original Hallyu goddess, Song Yi Yeon.
I only work with pros.
Yes, it's obvious that you would think about it carefully.
And also, did I ask you to do this?
Are you going to be like this? If we worked our butts off, we should be at least be able to enjoy you going along with us.
Don't be so condescending when you did things I didn't even ask you to.
Let's not get angry, and talk it out—
What? Am I doing this so only I can benefit?
Gosh, so pathetic.
Pathetic?!
I'm not pathetic. I'm Lee Hae Joon!
Why didn't you pick up your phone? I said let's go home from work together.
I thought about it, and if I repay you for the two months of advanced rent, please leave.
Since you can't even look me in the eyes, I'm guessing you've started to care for me.
Yes, you're really getting on my nerves.
I'm leaving in one month and never coming back.
I'm just a passing person. Things you can't tell anyone,
you can tell me as if I were a passing breeze.
If you're having a hard time, you can lean on me for a while or get mad and complain. That will be okay with me.
That will be okay with me.
I will take it all for you. Where on earth, like winning a lottery, would you find a chance like this?
Branch Manager. Why go this far...
You can think of it as me doing the things that Kim Yeong Soo couldn't do before leaving.
I just want to protect your family.
♬   I'm sorry   ♬
♬   Don't leave me. Don't leave me  ♬
♬  A day without you, I feel like I'm going to cry   ♬
♬   It hurts a lot, I feel like crying honestly   ♬
Go first.
♬   If I close my eyes  ♬
♬   If I close my eyes again  ♬
If you're tall and your voice is good, does that make you complete?
Why is he playing with my emotions?
What a weirdo.
Gang Ja, don't worry. I won't fall for it.
- Oh.
- Sister-in-law, I didn't hear anything.
Nothing.
Ahjumma, can I request something to eat, with drinks?
Is this a bar or something?
See what happens when he gives up all the stickers.
So, you ran away from home?
Wench! I Must be gone for her to see that I'm valuable.
It's not like I'm even half of a Buddha. I can't stand that ball of rudeness anymore.
Thank you.
Ah, Sister-in-law, have a drink with us.
No, I'm fine.
Don't be like that and sit.
I regretted not being able to drink with you last time.
I'm not really good at drinking.
This is a golden drink.
Next.
Put the napkin on top. Tornado.
Tornado.
There!
What did you just teach her?!
Sister-in-law needs to feel the satisfaction of heaven and earth.
Her heart needs to clear and become filled with truth,
and feel her whole body becoming a statement. That Feeling!
It's good. Good.
Do it more. More.
I'll try now.
It's here.
Let's drink.
Anyway, but how can you cute Da Hye—
No, how did you end up marrying with Yeong Soo?
I, originally didn't want to get married to Yeong Soo
Because he was such a good person.
and I was raised so lonely.
But I really wanted to have lots of babies with him.
So we even got a nice house with a yard.
But cutting the grass is so hard.
Then what about a man like this?
Our Branch manager Lee is so cool.
He is cool.
But...
This man... is kind of weird.
- A lot.
- What is?
Sometimes he seems a lot like Yeong Soo.
Making me confused, really.
I talked too much today, right?
What a waste? And to whom...
What are you doing?
Excuse me, not that. Come over here.
I'll take care of your girl.
Come here.
Ah, so warm. This is nice.
Mom...
What should I do? This is bad.
Han Na...
Han Na... Mom can't breathe.
Mom...
Mom... Hug me..
You joker!
I like you so much, Mom.
I thought I was going to die from suffocation.
No, hug me. Hug me.
It's normal that you've misunderstood!
Dad...ah, Ahjussi went into your mom's room because ummm of momentary memory loss.
Homing instinct... like the instinct that your body finds its way to where you were from.
And because I used to live on the first floor.
And I had a bit of a sickness before...
Really... Oh!
Oh oh I wanted to get your mom's hair clip! Your mom's hair clip!
It was totally my style!
If mom finds out, you'll be kicked out.
Don't be like this. What do you want me to do?
What?
Type in your phone number.
So suddenly?
This wench. The size of her heart is a worm's.
You... Do you by chance know where Hong Nan went?
So you don't know.
Well then, I have another method.
Song Yi Yeon.
Try to eat well and live well without me.
Oh my gosh. Who is she alike that she's so smart and meticulous, even getting my phone number.
Honey... Song Yi Yeon is...!
What?
Song Yi Yeon is really coming here?
It seems as though Branch Manager Lee Hae Joon will really go through with the modeling contract.
Then I will take care of it personally. Send a lawyer to her.
Since she can't live without her child, she'll be careful with her conduct.
I understand.
Get out of my way.
♬   Oh I see it all  ♬
♬  Oh I see it now   ♬
♬  Let it one   ♬
♬  Two   ♬
♬  Three get set go   ♬
♬  Bye bye bye goodbye no no no   ♬
♬  Oh you tell me more   ♬
Those little...
Is it a bit dry in here?
♬   Because I know you  ♬
Please sign this for me!!
You're so pretty!
I guess my leaving the house has had a positive effect.
I know, right?
Making such a scene...
What are you?
Wait a moment.
Song Yi Yeon.
I'd like to see you for a moment.
♬   You choose me  ♬
♬   Let it go  ♬
♬   Thank you make some noise I love you  ♬
♬   Tell me you love everything about me  ♬
Doing everything together now, huh?
Okay, let's hear it. What are your terms?
First, treat me like Class A star, just like when I debuted.
Because you've been on break for such a long time you must have forgotten how negotiating goes.
Okay, deal. We will treat you like a top class actor in the country.
You're too easy, Branch Manager. Are you sane?
Yes, I'm fine.
If it's Song Yi Yeon, she's worth it.
Second, I only deal with top class people.
Make the mall's value good enough for me to put my face on it.
Between you two, whoever does it, then we shall see and decide.
If you mean that value of the...
What kind of senseless demand is that? Give some hints...
No! I ask the questions and you have to find the answers.
We're done talking now. I'll go home to be devoted to our child.
I'll take that deal. I'll raise the value of the department store.
But... I really don't know...
This contract will have a
profound effect on the successor decision. Is that true?
They do say so.
You sent a request for child custody...
What to do? I guess you should work hard.
I'll watch you.
If you decide to sign with Lee Hae Joon, the game is over, but why did you have to provoke Cha Jae Gook?
Again, again, ruining my mood when I'm feeling good again?
Why are you giving him another chance? Do you by chance still have lingering feelings for that guy?
A child's father.
He needs to at least show some effort in front of his child.
And so? You used an opportunity that was directed towards you?
Do you not know what kind of a person he is that you're doing this?
Hey, doesn't it seem like she's jealous about something?
Jealous?! I shouldn't have said anything.
You haven't become that popular yet. Don't go overboard!
-Where are you going?
-None of your business!
-Are you going to sleep out again?!
- That's right!
What's with her, doing things she's never done before?
Why are you following me?
You can't sleep out.
I spent all my youthful days sleeping out, so wha—
- Were you worried about me?
- Na Seok Cheol will be monitoring you.
Don't go around on your own.
This woman's name is Hong Nan?
After Han Gi Tak died, she appeared a month later claiming she's his younger sibling.
Right now she's acting as Song Yi Yeon's manager.
She has gathered all the guys who used to be under Han Gi Tak.
Are you saying you are Han Gi Tak's younger sister?
I don't think I put you in that seat to look at Song Yi Yeon's infuriating face.
I'm saying to get it right!
Don't worry.
The bubble will burst soon and her glory will soon fade.
I do know this field well, don't I, President?
I'm sorry I'm late.
I told you to look into that manager girl. What did you find out?
She's just a girl who wants to get popular.
You don't have to worry about her at all.
I see.
Whenever I assign work to you President Na, you always tell me not to worry about it.
What do I have to believe that I can entrust work to you?
To say something like that...
Song Yi Yeon probably didn't come to the department store just to model.
I thought she was just going to let the other side win, but
seeing how she gave us a chance, I'm sure there is some flexibility.
So, now you want me to hang Song Yi Yeon's face in my department store?
Isn't it more profitable than just handing over the contract to Branch Manager Lee?
How about approaching her manager?
Yes. That's what I've been thinking as well, since she is my actress.
My Jeong Ji Hoon will take charge of work this time.
Pardon?
According to the information, he is digging into Han Gi Tak's car accident.
- Sunjin?
-  His name is Jeong Ji Hoon.
He is Jeong Ji Hoon. I think he is on Cha Jae Gook's side.
Come on. You said you were going to reveal Gi Tak Hyung's cooking secret but what are you doing a taste test for?
Hey! After eating your pasta I almost croaked.
You can't get that bad of a taste without having a sense of taste.
Pick out the salt, sugar, and msg.
Gosh. Making me do everything now.
This one is sugar.
Salt.
Msg.
Sugar.
Na Seok Cheol, that bastard. What has he been feeding you? His sense of taste is totally dead!
This is sugar.
This is salt.
Stop eating it! They're all salt!
Hey pretty one.  Some bastard is digging into your brother's past. What do you think?
What are you talking about?
His name is Jeong Ji Hoon from Sunjin Department Store.
Jeong Ji Hoon?
It's because I thought you will be had by him before you get Cha Jae Gook.
After I gave some freedom to Song Yi Yeon,  my main meal line is about to rot.
So you, pretty one, should exert some more effort, right?
I'm sorry, but we're closed for today.
Hong Nan?
Jeong Ji Hoon?
What are you doing here?
Did Cha Jae Gook send you?
I don't know who this guy is but I think I saw him somewhere. He's making me feel bad.
You're surely not 100% on Branch Manager Lee Hae Joon's side right?
Help us out as well. Song Yi Yeon's mission is too hard.
It is a bit hard.
Although my taste buds are dead, my sense of sight is one of the best.
Oh, oh, oh!
If the pretty one has met with Jeong Ji Hoon, tell me what they talked about immediately.
Is the person in charge here named Han Gi Tak?
Yes, that's correct.
Thank you.
Jeong Ji Hoon is digging into Han Gi Tak Hyung's past? For what?
It's obvious, Cha Jae Gook is trying to dig up weaknesses on Song Yi Yeon.
How could he not only do work at his job but do personal work for him...
Just what is this bastard doing?
He asked for a hint about Song Yi Yeon's contract.
What? What kind of mindless thing...
If I meet him tomorrow...
I must give it to him
Is your back okay?
It's fine.
Your throat doesn't hurt? Did you sleep well?
Yes.
Why are you being like this?
Stay still. I need you right now.
How is it? Is it comfortable?
This pillow is new and is supposed to help you sleep well.
Hello, Sister-in-law.
Oh hello.
I think she really liked that pillow.
You idiot.
She really liked it.
He is a good person but you're an Ahjumma.
Han Na, give me some strength.
Charging power!
Mom! I can't breathe!
Father-in-law!
What's wrong?
Give me your strength.
♬  cuz I’m still waiting for you   ♬
This is the wine you like, right?
I didn't think you'd remember this much.
It seems that you don't know, but I have a lot of interest in you.
That's scary.
Hurry up and get to your point.
If you're going to sign a contract with Sunjin mall, then do it with me. It looks better in every way.
I think doing it with you is the worst option.
I will do what you want and treat you like a Class A person.
Really? What about the store's value?
What? So my face can be on it, what are you willing to do?
Since you're the president, it's not like you don't have thoughts on the matter.
Why and what? Should I put a golden bow on the department's roof for you?
You'll need to try harder.
I am Lee Hae Joon. I am Lee Hae Joon.
I am Lee Hae Joon. You are a genius, Lee Hae Joon.
How can I increase the value of the department store?
This drives me crazy. I can't think of anything!
Now look what he's doing.
He is carrying out a rival mission, with the president, for Song Yi Yeon.
The promise he made about the employee benefits would be all lies.
I almost forgot about this.
Now it's good that you know. Take care of him.
He will be of great help in selling our department store.
Good Afternoon, Branch Manager.
Lee He Sa, Who are you to direct a person to here and there?
This parking lot is for female customers only.
Hey! Since you're doing your job so poorly the cars don't know where to go
I earn $100,000 a minute. You just wasted 10 minutes of my time here.
How much do you earn? What kind of work do you do that makes you think you can get in my way?
Chairman Jang. Welcome!
President Cha! You should train your employees better than this.
Yes, I'll keep that in mind.
Hey, parking attendant. Go home.
Yes?
President. Please wait. I didn't do anything wrong.
What are you doing?
Uh, I'm sorry.
If you don't abide by the employee policy, you have no reason to be here.
Secretary Go, why are you just standing there?
Wait, President! President.
He was fine handling customer vehicles.
He always fires employees whenever they get a complaint from customers.
This is annoying.
I did wrong, President.
I did wrong.
I apologize to you.
If you didn't talk back in the first place this wouldn't be happening,
making a person's face wrinkle.
What are you doing? Remove him.
Yes.
Wait a second.
Here comes Hong Gil Dong again .   (Korean "Robin Hood")
What's up again, Branch Manager Lee Hae Joon?
It seems that you have a problem with my employee.
I just can not let this kind of thing slide.
What? The brothers are fighting to gain favor?
Heol! This is big.
Lee Hae Sang, that name tag is not for someone to threaten you.
Don't bow your head to just anyone.
Yes.
Branch Manager is so arrogant.
Branch Manager Lee. Don't make a fuss and just drop it.
Do you know who you're talking to? What kind of attitude are you giving me right now?
Our department store is the place we sell products, not attitudes.
Selling a product and it's benefit is a fair deal.
We don't need to provide good service to the arrogant customers
who think they are above our employees.
What the owner says is the employee policy. Do you still not get it?
Do you understand?
Yes, Branch Manager.
Branch Manager Lee!
And we should take this opportunity to change the policy.
You should also study the updated policy.
Secretary Go, take care of your boss,
so he won't be embarrassed like he was embarrassed today.
Then I'll get going to greet the real VIP.
Then...
Han Nah!
I thought you were not coming.
Dad promised to teach you how to ride a bike.
I'm teaching you instead of your dad.
Let's do it.
Good job!
To the left. To the left.
Here.
Oh, oh, oh.
Yes, yes.
Then, you should hold on to me.
Great!
You're riding the bike very well.
Don't let go of me.
I won't.
♫   My eyes miss you  ♫
♫  The tears tell me to find you  ♫
♫  The image of you that goes away as I turn around  ♫
♬   It gets harder  ♬
♫  Why haven't I been able to forget?  ♫
♫  Deep inside my heart. I know I need you  ♫
Even the food preference and favorite music,
does the planning department do this kind of work?
Its a basic thing to know about the person who is going to be our department store's model.
Song Yi Yeon has high expectations.
towards guys too.
Anyway, you're very close to Song Yi Yeon?
Yes, we met in the States.
You met Lee Hae Joon in the States too?
Are you a reporter? You have lots of questions today.
At the fashion show I watched you carefully.
I think you are a very attractive person. You might be very good at acting.
I hear that a lot.
Isn't it hard to live somebody else's life?
I know your brother very well.
I mean Han Gi Tak.
I don't think he knows you.
You are Han Gi Tak's little sister?
You're telling a lie, Hong Nan?
He knows I am not the real one.
Who is it? Cha Jae Gook? Na Seok Cheol?
Why do you think I am lying, Jeong Ji Hoon?
If you want to know, let's have dinner together tomorrow.
Explain. I had a makeover.
If Cha Jae Gook had known that I am Han Gi Tak's little sister,
he wouldn't have stayed like this.
There would be no reason for Jeong Ji Hoon to come to me to say I am the fake one.
He's a guy that I can't figure out.
I need to see him tomorrow.
What?
What is this?
I'm waiting for your call--X
Who's X? What pretty lady's heart did you shake up
This look
It's not like I can write "I'm taken" on me.
Hehehehe
I'm going to go crazy.
Our department store is the place we sell products, not attitudes.
Oh my. Awesome!
He is so cool.
We were mistaken about him.
I believed in him, the Branch Manager.
What the heck? Let's watch it again.
Press play.
Our department store is the place we sell products, not attitudes.
Oh Branch Manager. He is awesome.
I knew he would be like that.
Did you want to see me?
Department Manager, Jeong Ji Hoon. You know how important it is for us to enter into a contract with Song Yi Yeon as a model.
Of course.
Knowing that, how could you go around saying her manager is lying about her identity?
Then what are we?
As expected, you two talk to each other often.
Just answer my questions.
- Like people are saying, is it your specialty using a dead person to get to the top?
- What?
To use Song Yi Yeon, Isn't she pretending to be Han Gi Tak's sister?
That woman.
So to get to Cha Jae Gook, you're saying I created Han Gi Tak's sister? Is that it?
Yes. And what is the evidence that makes you say that?
You'll soon find out.
What are you waiting for?
I've brought the document for the new products.
Leave it there
I didn't want to say this because this is going against my pride, but why can't I be with you when Lee Hae Joon can?
Manager!
That night when Sunbae died, was it because we were together?
I feel the same way as you.
I suffered too, from Sunbae's death.
For that reason, I hesitated countless times,
but I was afraid that you were going to get hurt, so I couldn't leave and watch you suffer.
Yes,
I hate myself for sitting at that same seat with you that night.
If I could, I would turn back time.
- Da Hye
- I was always sad whenever I was with Yeong Soo.
At that time, when you appeared, I could be happy again.
But then, when you appeared, Yeong Soo died.
So whenever I see you, Ji Hoon, I remember his death and I am so tired of that.
That night, when we met, do you think that was just a coincidence?
I had something to say to you.
Stop it. I don't want to hear it.
Da Hye.
♬   In my two empty eyes  ♬
♬   The image of you going away from me appears  ♬
I'm sorry.
I misunderstood you, like a stupid bastard.
I couldn't even treat you out for dinner or celebrate our anniversary, like a stupid bastard.
I'm sorry that I left you alone and told you to only look at me.
Because the only thing I can tell you is I'm sorry,
♬  The time you won't come to me  ♬
I'm sorry.
♬  Even if I wish for it and wish for it again  ♬
♬  The person who can't stay with me.  ♬
From when were you here?
Since you were here.
I was always with you by your side.
You just didn't know.
Really?
I'm not going to say I'm sorry, like a stupid bastard,
so I won't have any regrets when I leave here.
♬   Like the star over there,   ♬
♬  With neither a promise nor a hope  ♬
Isn't it hard to live as a different person?
You're Han Gi Tak's sister? Are you lying, Hong Nan?
Jeong Ji Hoon, that bastard.
What does he know?
Does he know the identity of my younger sibling?
Why? What does the person named Jeong Ji Hoon say?
He knows that Hong Nan is Han Gi Tak's sister.
Oh my God. His knowledge is extensive.
We must fix this before it reaches the ears of President Cha.
Right.
If President Cha hears about this, he will be very disturbed.
Right?
Jeez! You surprised me.
Did you put some kind of tracker in my body?
I said to not come up suddenly next to me at any time.
I'm sorry, President.
There was an urgent issue and I felt a bit rushed.
Yes, I'm sorry.
What is it?
You know that younger girl who is Song Yi Yeon's Manager.
I mean Hong Nan. I found out her true identity.
She's Han Gi Tak's little sister.
And the place where Song Yi Yeon is at is...
Hello, this is the Branch Manager.
To all customers who are visiting Sunjin Department Store,
and to all employees of Sunjin Department Store, I will be making an announcement.
- Sunjin Department Store, as we are trying to be family friendly,
- What is he talking about?
- for all customers who are visiting us with the family on Family Day twice a month, we will be giving you special promotions.
And for all employees of Sunjin Department Store, we will be be giving a thirty minute early dismissal.
What is this? A gag?
We are planning to close at 7:30 PM so I hope you'll have no objection.
Don't think of staying overnight and go home early.
What is this I'm hearing?
Customers, it is time for you all to return to your families.
Then, I will be leaving.
What? It's really early dismissal?
This is so great!
How are you leaving work? Get moving!
What are you doing?
Date!
♬  The road I accidentally was walking   ♬
♬  felt familiar and I stopped there  ♬
♬  In the place where I was   ♬
♬  together with beautiful you that stupid night   ♬
♬  How much will it change   ♬
♬  Will you give a smile as bright as moonlight?   ♬
♬  You were always beautiful   ♬
♬  It’s only you who left just me alone   ♬
Wear it.
♬  Moon light  ♬
- Store Manager.
- We will go and eat dinner when you wear that.
♬  Thinking about you tonight   ♬
♬  you appear in my sweet dream   ♬
♬  and I welcome you in my arms   ♬
♬  I wanna stay up all night  ♬
♬  Even though the sleepless times are too long   ♬
♬  I want to experience the day that will get better   ♬
♬  cuz I’m still waiting for you   ♬
Will you trust in me one more time?
♬   Then, because I didn't know everything   ♬
♬   Deep inside my heart, you got bigger   ♬
♬   Then, because of my wicked pride   ♬
♬   I couldn't hold you back when you were leaving me  ♬
- You came.
- Mom!
♬  I could only cry.  ♬
♫   You who called out to me, the hand, the place I rested my eyes,   ♫
Why? Were you disappointed it was your house?
♬   Although we are saying goodbye now  ♬
♬  The painful memory of letting you go   ♫
is left to me. I feel deep regret.  ♬
Does it look delicious?
♫  My eyes missing you  ♫
I will grill it deliciously!
♫  The tears tell me to find you  ♫
♫  The tears tell me to find you but   ♫
It looks really good.
♬   Turning away, going farther away, your imaged is fading.♬
The smell is good, right?
Aren't you guys happy while spending time with your family?
Mom, I'm so hungry.
Yeah, let's eat fast.
Yes, Father.
I think the meat isn't grilling properly.
Did the fire go out?
Han Na, just wait a little. It's almost done.
Father, wait a bit. I will grill it deliciously.
We will spend the night waiting for him to grill meat.
Should I help you?
The man is supposed to do everything outside!
Stay still.
Daughter, why don't we just eat some ramen?
Should we? Han Na, you're hungry, right?
- Ramen.
- That's better, right?
Yeah.
Aigoo, what is this?
Aigoo, Daughter-In-Law, the table things are going to fly off.
Han Na, are you okay?
Father, are you okay?
Han Na's Mom.
What are you doing? Are you crazy?
How can you push away a person who is trying to help?
♫  My eyes miss you, The tears tell me to find you but  ♫
♫   Turning around, going farther away, your image is slowly fading.  ♫
♬   Don't go, don't leave. You know how stupid I am   ♬
♬   The person that is so precious to me, I won't make her cry again   ♬
Mom is now going to appear on TV a lot. You see, your Mom got really popular.
You'll spend the whole day watching me on TV.
Wow.
Is Dad treating you well?
Dad made me fried rice and he even kicked the ball with me.
Really?
He told me say that to you.
I see. I guess you liked it, my son.
Where did the Lightning girl and Uncle go?
I know. I guess both are busy today.
When I come next time, I'll make sure I come with them.
The Last Goodbye
Strongly. Move fast.
Ahhh, yess.
Now, he must have felt a bit of my wrath?
You cute little President Cha Jae Gook bastard.
I think the game will get more interesting.
I want to see it happen quickly!
Welcome.
You who are not Han Gi Tak's younger sibling.
You want to have a beer first?
What's the reason for wanting to see me at your house?
So that I can tell you that you are a fake.
As if Han Gi Tak wasn't enough, did he tell you to get rid of everybody around him?
DId Cha Jae Gook tell you to do that?
If Cha Jae Gook knows, does it become dangerous?
Even knowing this you're pretending to be Hong Gi Tak's sibling
Is it because of money or because of loyalty?
What? That is amazing, however,
now I wish for you to stop, because that person is going to be very sad.
What do you mean by that person?
The real Han Gi Tak's younger sibling?
What?
I know Han Gi Tak's real younger sibling.
Really.
What do you mean, Really?
The real Justice Dude
The real Han Gi Tak's younger sibling is looking for her family.
I intended to keep a promise I made a long time ago but
it cannot get ruined by you.
Who is the person?
Someone who is close...
Where is that child right now?
Where are you going?
♬   Wherever I am filling me with   ♬
♬   A memory which was lost in space   ♬
♬   The memories of a time I turned far away from   ♬
♬   Whether it was a matter of something which was forgotten   ♬
♬   or whether it was matter of going toward somewhere   ♬
♬   I’m spending a day once again among the days I dreamed of.   ♬
♬   It might be too late   ♬
♬   Maybe in a place that I can’t even go back to   ♬
- Is it good?
- It's delicious!
♬   My whole love is alive and breathing.   ♬
Here!
Eat a lot.
I'll cut it for you
♬   The one reason always in my life   ♬
Hey!
Omo! Hong Nan! You came at the perfect time. Come over and eat!
♬   My everything is like that   ♬
Come on!
♬   In the air which is given   ♬
♬   Forever in my every dream   ♬
Punk.
It's been a long time.
Han Yeong Tan.
Epilogue
Five cargo ships, six container ships and
Three planes have passed,
but this is the twelveth ship to pass.
Han Hong Nan. She looked, she looked.
Do you know why I agreed to do that?
Why did you make such a commotion?
This... It belongs to Cha Jae Gook!
I want to play with you, Han Na. But I don't have a lot of time left.
Ahjussi, are you going somewhere?
From now on, don't make things difficult for Da Hye. I'm going to protect her from now on.
In your memories, leave just a small space for me.
-What's wrong?
- What did you say to Han Na when you came over?
She's gone. She disappeared.
Where are you right now?