Get everyone out right now! (Chinese)
What?
Get out!
- Get out now!
- Get out!
Hwang Mi Soon. Im Ye Eun!
Complete
Okay, I'm done.
TOP SECRET - CODE NAME 'GOOD CASTING'
Good Casting
Take them away! (Chinese)
What are you doing? (Japanese)
I'll give you back the money I won. I was going to give it back anyway!
Why are you taking us away!
Chan Mi. Something happened in the hall. I can't get a hold of them.
What?
They don't have anything. (Chinese)
Then... Just kill the two of them.
Do you think it's just us?
Out team is covering the entire area outside.
Your Mandarin is pretty good.
Your Japanese is pretty good too.
So it isn't just you two here?
There's a sniper on standby on the building opposite from us.
You almost got riddled with bullets.
You should know what you're messing with.
That's right! If you harm us, do you think you'll be fine?
If there is really a sniper over there tell them to shoot this.
What?
If they don't hit this in the next minute, we'll shoot you in the head.
Restricted Number
Hello?
Chan Mi.
What are you doing? You should be telling her to come.
I think... you need to come up again.
If you don't want a hole in your head, tell her to come right away!
Right now.
Now that all three of you are here, how much do you think I can sell you for?
You're going to use us for a deal?
It seems like a waste if I just kill you off.
If I bring you to the transaction tomorrow, I think I can get a million bucks per person.
Who said that you'll be able to trade tomorrow?
You want to stop my deal tomorrow.
Isn't that why you ruined my game and snuck into my room?
You can only make a deal if you're alive.
About that gift you gave us last time...
What are you babbling about?
I prepared a gift in return.
What are you doing?
Carefully, carefully.
What's going on?
My apologies.
What are you doing?
Take it off. Won't you take it off right now?
Hey, calm down. It'll explode if you make a wrong move.
What are you saying?
If this explodes, we're all going to die. What should I do?
Push it?
You think this will allow you guys to walk away alive?
You want to die together?
Okay, even if I don't push the button, it'll explode after a minute and forty seconds.
Ah, there's a minute and thirty seconds left.
What are you...
Just let us go.
Then as soon we're out, I'll turn off the switch.
Why should I trust you?
If you don't want to believe me then I'll make it go off now!
- No. No
- No. No.
Which will be faster, you shooting me or me pushing the button?
I'm giving you ten seconds. Choose wisely.
Ten, nine, eight, seven...
Chan Mi, I think ten seconds is too short.
You're counting too fast.
Six, five...
Four...
Okay! Okay.
Don't move!
When did you make the bomb?
You think making a bomb is easy?
That? I asked Moo Hyeok to improvise and quickly make a fake one.
How did you get him to wear the vest?
This noona will dress you in a pretty, colorful thing.
The support team has successfully arrested Wang Kai and his men without sustaining any injury.
Everyone, good job.
There are still a lot of reporters around the exits.
Where's Secretary Byeon?
He said he had to attend to an urgent matter in Jeju Island.
Jeju Island?
If you find out more, you could be in danger like the chairman was.
I could never watch you end up with the same fate.
Let's go to the airport.
Pardon?
Right now.
DK Hotel
Jeju DK Hotel room 423
Come to the address I sent you in ten minutes. (Chinese)
Let's meet at the hotel I'm staying at.
Meeting at a place that I choose is part of our deal.
I came all the way to Jeju Island, is it too much to ask for you to come to my hotel?
Location?
Jeju Casino Hotel... Room 774.
What's wrong?
Seventy-four. It's a number that Chinese people don't use.
He just sent a sign to Michael.
What?
In a democratic country, (Chinese)
you wouldn't fire a bullet in the head of a criminal.
But if I go back to China after a transaction has gone wrong, I will certainly be shot dead.
You really think I'll risk my life to make him come here?
Track the location of his cell phone right now.
It's urgent, hurry!
This idiot. Why get caught and screw it up.
We've been working together for so long. Is he set on screwing me over now?
Why do you chasing me?
Did you get his location?
I can't track it because the phone works with satellite connection.
Satellite phone?
Could it be there is immense power involved in this? If not, then—
That doesn't make sense. If they're trying this hard to hide their identity...
Talk. Where is Michael? (Chinese)
Where is Michael? Talk!
Do you still not know the reason
he hasn't been caught yet? Nobody can meet him
unless he comes to you first!
The only way to find him is to make him come to you himself.
Given the situation, that option seems to have gone down the drain, though.
What are you doing?
Are we going to lose Michael again?
What does that mean?
What you mean, Secretary Byeon is on Jeju Island?
What on earth are you doing on Jeju Island?
- You know that it's top-secret information.
- You're not going to tell me?
I have no option other than going there myself.
Hello? Hello?
What is it? What do you mean Secretary Byeon is here?
I don't know why Secretary Byeon is here in Jeju.
Find Secretary Byeon's location immediately and send it to me. Hurry!
You're quite skilled, as the rumors say.
I'm relieved you seem to know me.
There's no reason for me to stall.
Hand over the chip with the third phase of the technology.
If you want it, try taking it from me.
I've finally found it.
Easy, easy.
Taking it is easy.
But you have to be alive for it.
Darn it.
We lost the tracking around here, so look for him nearby.
I'll try going into the school.
Go.
Go and catch that guy.
Hurry.
I said to go!
Hurry!
Sunbae...
If not now,
you'll never catch him. Hurry!
I said to go! Hurry!
Please go!
Hurry!
Michael.
For violating the Act on Prevention of Divulgence and Protection of Industrial Technology,
I'm arresting you.
So come out you bastard!
Can you speed up a bit?
Hurry up.
Endure it just a little longer.
Woo Seok...
How did you come all the way here?
I told you not to go around alone.
I told you not to go anywhere alone because it's dangerous. What is this?
I'm sorry.
Don't say anything. Stop talking, please.
I promised...
I promised to protect you and the chairman no matter what.
Exactly, so you have to keep your promise. Woo Seok...
I really wanted to...
keep that promise.
You know that you're my only family.
You know, right?
I know. I'm not going anywhere.
I have to get my suit from you.
Okay. I got it, so stop talking.
These are my favorite clothes,
but now they've all been ruined.
CEO Yoon.
Please take care.
What the heck? Why are you acting like you'll never see me again?
I'll wait for you until the end and make sure I get my new suit.
I know you weren't meant for this, and I know this isn't your style.
That's why I'm even more sorry and grateful.
That you threw everything away to be by my side.
If you find out more, you could be in danger like the chairman was.
I could never watch you end up with the same fate.
Try to focus a bit. Focus, Woo Seok.
I-I'm sorry.
I wanted to stay...
stuck right by your side.
Woo Seok, open your eyes.
Woo Seok, open...
Woo Seok. Woo Seok.
Woo Seok... Woo Seok!
Oh no...
Open your eyes!
At the end of last month, the body of a male citizen who went to Jeju Island on vacation was found with a gunshot wound.
The police were dispatched after hearing reports from local residents who heard a gunshot.
We found this in his stomach.
Here, take a look.
It looks like he swallowed it after wrapping it in foil.
I think he knew beforehand the foil wouldn't be melted by the gastric acids.
They found a chip inside Secretary Byeon's stomach.
I think he wanted to catch Michael to prove you were innocent.
How did Secretary Byeon know to go after him?
How could he find someone the National Intelligence Service couldn't find?
That...
We'll have to slowly look into it. Secretary Byeon was no ordinary person, after all.
Check Secretary Byeon's call history, and look into his whereabouts
before he came to Jeju Island. Find out as much as you can.
Let me make one request.
I can't forgive the bastards that killed my dad and Woo Seok.
Bastards?
Whatever you find out, please let me know.
Then I'll decide whether or not to tell you what I know.
I heard it while getting interrogated.
Once you've become White Collar's target, you can never escape.
Who is that guy exactly?
Apparently, there are several bosses at each level that are operating the organization.
Prosecutors concluded that former CEO Yoon Seok Ho was free of charges regarding the technology leak.
Mr. Myeong, who was tried for leaking industrial technology, hiring an assassin,
embezzling public money, and evading taxes, was sentenced to 37 years in prison,
a fine of 15 billion won (≈$15M) and an additional penalty fee of 8.4 billion won (≈ $8.4M).
Celebrity idol Kang Woo Won, who suffered from anxiety caused by aggressive criticism from anti-fans,
announced that he would be taking merciless legal action against all those who had left malicious comments
following the news that his manager Mr. Pi's death was not a suicide, but a homicide.
Stop taking pictures!
Il Gwang HiTech's CEO Sim Hwa Ran announced prior to the inauguration
that she would be stepping down from the CEO position.
The former CEO, Yoon Seok Ho, who recently returned to the business,
explained he will follow his late father’s will and invest in eco-friendly semiconductors,
in order to improve the coexistence of people and technology.
It was a bit awkward coming in. Is it because Secretary Byeon isn't here?
This is the tea you liked, right?
I'm finally getting the treatment that I couldn't even receive while we were married.
Back then, neither of us were interested in each other.
That's true.
You must've only gotten curious about what I liked and disliked after we got a divorce.
Since you'd have to know my tastes if you wanted to keep your management rights.
You're good at steeping tea.
I'm sure you didn't come just to drink some tea.
This is the contract for the transfer of my shares of the company.
Exposing my father's corruption, wanting to cut me off, even when you'd be losing from it,
I understood it.
Congratulations.
You've ultimately gotten everything you want.
Legal proceedings for the transfer of shares will be conducted through an attorney.
What's the reason you're doing all this, so suddenly?
Why do you think I kept these measly shares in the first place?
I had to at least have those...
for you to look at me.
If not for those shares, you wouldn't even have seen me.
Since I've eaten till my stomach feels like bursting thanks to you, I should give you a gift in return.
I like that you're clean about the give and take exchanges.
This is how I'm repaying everything I'm indebted to you for.
I'll have to listen to what it is, first.
There are rumors that Executive Director Myeong has a ledger.
It'll soon get out.
Why get excited over some old tabloid gossip.
It's not just gossip.
Maybe it was three years ago? The connection you had with Executive Director Myeong almost was almost revealed.
Did you really not know that CEO Yoon Seok Ho stopped that from getting out?
What are you talking about?
When the board of directors was protesting against your management rights over LK Aesthetics,
there were talks of secret ties between you and Executive Director Myeong.
CEO Yoon released shares at that time and just barely managed to stop the rumors from spreading.
You know very well that since then, it's been hard for CEO Yoon to defend his management rights.
I thought that was all the big plan you had been drawing since then.
Ugh, I'm dizzy.
My head hurts so much I think I'm going to die.
Don't make me sway with your temporary sympathy.
Her asking me not to make her sway...
means that she was swayed!
Okay.
Kang Woo Won
Is it an emergency?
No, it's not.
The same character kept appearing while investigating the crimes Michael had committed.
Name, Woo Myeong Sook. Age, forty-six.
Woo Myeong Sook? Madam Woo?
Do you know her?
Madam Woo, who died three months ago in solitary confinement.
She should've left it to you.
She's a woman who was managing a ledger for drug traffickers.
But... What does Madam Woo have to do with White Collar?
We'll have to look into it.
Why? What? How?
Okay. Chan Mi will wrap up that case.
Now, since we've recovered the chip and caught Michael...
Are we dispersing now?
Each of you handle the cleanup for your assigned on-site missions, following the rules.
Kang Woo Won
There isn't a problem, is there?
Of course not. It's all been taken care of. There are no issues.
Okay, fine. Let's take it to the end today.
I'll wait for you even if I have to pull an all-nighter.
Come. Down you go.
It's all good.
Isn't it fun?
I want to go on the swings.
The swings?
So Hee, let's go on the see-saw. That's more fun, isn't it?
The swings! Swings! Swings! Swings!
Okay, okay. Let's go on the swings.
One minute, okay?
Yes, Team Leader?
Dads are always busy.
I don't have a dad, though.
Come on.
I only have a mom.
I really wish I had a dad too...
Mom!
So Hee!
Did you have fun?
You came back early today.
It was difficult watching So Hee, right?
You should come in. I went grocery shopping to make curry.
Sure, give that to me.
Let's go.
Woo Won...
What are you doing here?
So not only are you not Im Jeong Eun of the advertising team, but Im Ye Eun of the National Intelligence Service, and
you're also a mom?
That's why I told you
there's no benefit for you
in getting involved with me.
Eat up.
Do you think I am able to swallow any food right now?
Even if you can't, you should try to force it in.
So you'll have the strength to go back home.
And...
don't ever come back here.
Is that something you should be saying to me right now?
It's different from where you live.
This neighborhood has a lot of eyes watching and rumors spread fast.
There's no need for you to become the subject of rumors here by wandering around—
Stop saying things like that! Dammit.
I'll take care of my own image. You don't need to worry about it.
How can I not worry?
I saw very well how difficult a time you had because of that.
I don't care if my entire reputation gets ruined!
Don't cry. Don't cry.
You should make sure to eat your meals.
I have a million followers on social media.
I also have a lot of rich fans, so I get sent tons of expensive gifts from all over the world, but...
this place has never hurt before.
I've received hundreds and thousands of fan letters saying they love me, but this here has never fluttered.
But... why do you make me feel this way?
Woo Won...
Now you're going to tell me to leave and be well?
How can I leave and be well... after you've taken my heart?
I can't go. You take responsibility.
Since you shook my heart, you should take responsibility!
I'm not afraid at all of what people say.
What I'm the most afraid of right now is never being able to see you again, that's all.
So just tell me. Are you going to reject me or not?
Woo Won, instead of doing this here, let's go inside—
Do you want me to say it louder?
Are you going to reject me or not?!
- Hurry up and tell him!
- Don't reject him!
- Go ahead, tell him you won't!
Okay.
What's okay?
I said okay for now.
So you're not rejecting me?
I said okay.
So let go of my hands and—
♫  Let’s love, let’s love  ♫
♫  Sweetly and deeply  ♫
♫  Let's love  ♫
♫  With the world's most precious you  ♫
♫  Should we go on a short vacation or take a walk in the park?  ♫
♫  I'm happy thinking of what we should do  ♫
♫  I picked out a pretty outfit and put on a no-makeup look  ♫
♫  Thinking of how else I can look good for you  ♫
♫  I can’t hide this heart, it's already out  ♫
♫  I can’t hide my feelings for you  ♫
♫  But I can’t wait,   ♫
♫  so should I confess first?  ♫
So Hee, don't look at that. That's unsuitable for spectators under 19.
What's that?
It's a good thing.
If it's good, I want to see it.
No, I said you can't.
♫  Let's love.  ♫
♫  Sweetly and deeply.  ♫
♫  With the world's most precious you  ♫
Letter of Resignation
What if I don't sign this for you?
I want to leave after following the official procedure.
This is my last request.
Wow... You look like you'll go on an unauthorized resignation if I don't sign this.
Do you... have to leave?
I have nobody left next to me. If you leave too...
I'm not leaving.
Just like you've returned to your position,
I'm just returning to my place.
You're cold-hearted to the end.
This must be why they say to not even start a one-sided love.
Secretary Byeon said it's no use to run into your first love again...
Even if you meet your first love again, your feelings will just seem like the unspeakable worst...
of the best memories... which will be amazing beyond words, thus unspeakable.
Letter of Resignation.
CEO's Signature
Now...
Now you're not my teacher or my secretary, so I can call you whatever I want, right?
What do you want to call me?
What is it? Did you forget something?
How should I say it... I feel kind of sad, but also a bit relieved.
It was my first on-site infiltration.
For some reason, I feel sad leaving.
I know that feeling. Your first on-site investigation is like a first love.
It stays stuck in your memory, and sometimes it even makes your heart hurt.
It'll be like that.
A first love is only beautiful if you leave it as a memory.
Since if you meet again, it'll only reopen the wound that had healed.
What are you doing? Let's go.
Just leave without them.
Okay.
Wait, I'm coming! I'm going!
- Hey! Hey!
- Wait!
Hey! Are you serious?
Ssak Ssak Cleaning
I'm back.
You have to eat dinner.
I ate with my friends.
- With your friends?
- Yeah.
Full-coverage medical insurance? Life insurance? Which one is it this time?
Why are you making conversation with me all of a sudden?
If you don't want to talk to me, then never mind.
Joo Yeon, should I quit working in insurance?
Why?
Aren't you embarrassed by it?
Why is that embarrassing? You're working hard to feed and raise me.
It would've been better if my job was a bit more flaunt-worthy.
You're cool even like this.
What?
You're probably more embarrassed than I am, but you're earning that money for me.
Speaking of which... can I go to Kang Woo Won's concert?
That punk! He thinks he's some kind of prince,
and he's a major snob who only knows himself in the world. Why would you like someone like that?
Do you even know my Oppa Woo Won, Mom?
Why is he your oppa? Did I give birth to Kang Woo Won?
Goodness, I really can't converse with you.
- You just try going to Kang Woo Won's concert.
- Forget it.
If you go— You little...! If you go—
I'll just... goodness...
You must have a lot of free time these days.
Your phone is so quiet and you don't go out.
I've fulfilled my performance results, so I'll be quite free for the time being.
You're done?
I told you I would only be busy for a few months.
You were really busy because of work?
Then because of what else would I be busy?
Aren't you tired? Should I do the dishes?
Goodness! Why are my daughter and husband both—
Just act like you normally act, in your annoying ways.
Why are you doing that?
Rest up.
Goodness...
They're really something.
Aunt,
this is really the last time. You have to keep your promise.
It's me. Is there an operation going on today at the Royal Hotel today, perhaps?
Never mind. I'm hanging up.
♫   If you've ever been in love before   ♫
♫   I know you feel this beat   ♫
♫   If you know it,   ♫
♫   Don't be shy   ♫
♫  Don't cry, it's a thing of the past.  ♫
We must really be fated.
Seeing how we meet again, like this.
I wonder... We could be ill-fated.
Oh my.
I've got a phone call.
I'm sorry.
Hello?
Is this Ms. Baek Jang Mi?
This is the financial supervisor.
I was waiting for your call. Please tell me what you need.
Pardon?
Your personal information has been hacked.
Really?
After quickly checking your balance, if you cooperate with us...
Shall we meet?
Pardon? Sure, that would be good but...
If you let me know the location, I will be there right away.
I mean, immediately is...
What should I do?
Track the location of the phone number I just sent you. I think it's voice phishing.
I'm really sorry. Something urgent came up, so I think I need to go.
It was so difficult to meet again. We should at least share a meal together—
I apologize about last time.
About today, I'll put in good word to my aunt.
Goodbye.
I want to date you officially!
I thought about you every Monday as I received physical therapy, and I realized something.
That I fell for you at first sight last time.
That's why I called your aunt and told her
that I wanted to meet you again.
♫   I'm still crying for you   ♫
♫   I love you   ♫
Please date me.
Congratulations!
- Accept him!
- Congratulations!
♫   You know me well, that while loving you   ♫
CEO Yoon?
What to do? I'm sorry, but she's going to be seeing me.
Hey.
How are you here?
Did you submit a letter of resignation and put on makeup on the weekend just to do this?
I'm sorry.
Let's go.
What are you doing?
I told you I was going to call you whatever I wanted now.
If calling me lover is still too awkward, what about boyfriend?
Or if you don't want that either, I can start as your guy friend.
But... I don't want to just have a student-teacher relationship.
Stop joking around.
For real.
I decided 15 years ago,
if I met you again, even by coincidence, I would hold on to you and never let go.
Now you're even speaking casually? Why not just drop all formalities, while you're at it?
I was just about to.
What?
♫  Not just anyone can love her  ♫
♫  This girl of mine is really, really selfish  ♫
♫  No one could ever love her  ♫
♫  That is a really, really big miracle for me  ♫
You've always been the one executing the operations, but never been on the other end, right?
Here is my operation plan:
If you run away 100 times, I'll chase after you 100 times and catch you.
But I have no patience, so I can't do it 101 times. You should come over to me within those 100 times.
You're leaving? You're really just going to leave?
Royal Hotel
If you date me, I'll suddenly disappear, lie as frequently as I eat,
and there'll be countless times I show up as I please after being gone for an entire month.
I'm prepared for that.
I can't take care of anniversaries, or be next to you when you want me to.
You could be more lonely than when you were alone.
That's okay!
Everyone says that at first, that it's okay.
The car in front, in front, in front.
Even when you call, I won't be able to pick up most of the time.
Not only will I get hurt all the time, you could be in danger too.
I said it doesn't matter!
I could... suddenly die!
That one is a bit much...
See? That's why I said we can't work out.
I mean, what kind of person would be understanding about suddenly dying?
Are you trying to die right now?
I'm going to catch a bad guy.
S-S-Slow down a bit! Slow down!
There's a camera. Camera! Camera!
6 months later
Trusted Advanced Corrections
Hi, Barbara Massalitinova.
Over there.
... and repay it with drops of sweat.
Goo Tae Rim had been released due to lack of evidence, but during Executive Director Myeong's trial,
she was revealed to be involved with Division Director Tak and proven guilty. She's now in jail.
I'll be on the lookout for you.
Hurry up.
- Sorry.
- Hey.
Where are you running off to?
Do you know me?
Crazy... Why would I know you?
Ah looks like you haven't heard of me yet. I'm the Lotto of the Southern Prison.
I just want to be in peace while I'm here, so it'd be nice if you can cooperate.
What is this psycho saying?
I dropped it because of you. Pick it up.
Not with your hand, but with your mouth.
What are you looking at? I told you to pick it up!
Can I just pick it up with my hand?
I told you to bite it, you crazy b*tch!
Like this?
Do you know what we found out after tracing Executive Director Myeong's records?
White Collar. You know what it is, right?
I don't know.
So scram.
I know you snitched and sold Director Seo to White Collar.
Director Seo is dead?
Of course, they would kill off Director Seo. Who do you think is going to be next?
Won't it be even easier to get rid of someone in prison?
I especially invited someone special here.
Try acting up with her, too. You'll get completely crushed.
Which crazy b*tch dares to
stir trouble on the first day...
Long time no see.
An upstanding person must always keep their promises. You said you'd keep this place clean.
Why is it you again...?
You said you'd live as a kind person, yet you're still living like this?
That's disappointing.
No...That's not it.
Unni, what happened to you? Do you know this b*tch?
No, I-I-I—
I was in the middle of putting varnish, so—
Stop!
I'm really busy today. Just bring it on.
Lift your arms up straight!
Does MK stand for Michael?
It's Maxim in Russian. Their M tattoo is an acronym for that.
If you go there and say you want to make a deal with White Collar, they'll connect you with them after they verify the item.
I don't know anything else.
Let's end our deal here. Don't find me again, got it?
Let's live as kind people.
Of course! I will.
I'm confident I can do it.
Please speak.
Blood!
What is this?!
Emergency! Call the paramedics!
Emergency in room 1102! Call an ambulance!
Oh no, what do we do!
Please make way!
Slowly, slowly.
- Please call another nurse as well.
- Yes.
One, two, three!
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
I don't think you're fine.
Who are you?
Thank you to our segmenters:hana_860, chemellelott,sophie2you, and miss_rochester.
Thank you to our segmenters cont:hana_860, chemellelott,sophie2you, and miss_rochester.
Don't tell me you really thought I was dead?
Chief's Office
On the other hand, you haven't changed at all after becoming a team leader.
We've got a way to make contact with White Collar now.
- Here.
- What is that?
Personnel Appointment Announcement
Division: Industrial Security team 3 |  Name: Baek Chan Mi | Appointed to: Industrial Security team 1
Michael was murdered.
Who did it?
We analyzed the surveillance footage.
See for yourself.
What we're sure of is that Michael used a satellite phone to plan an escape the day before his trial.
And the fact that he was killed while trying to escape...
Means that someone from the top decided to cut off the tail.
Stopping us from riding it to climb up to them.
This is a big case...
Can you handle it?
That's why I personally brought in a precious person.
What are you waiting for? Get ready.
Turn around.
Thank you to our page designer: rose_shn.
What about my team members?
I gathered only the best players, of course.
I'm looking forward to seeing how amazing are the aces you've gather...ed.
Long time no see.
No wonder you didn't come to visit me in jail!
Congratulations on getting out of jail!
For reference, one candle represents the first day of our operation!
Clap, clap, clap!
You blew it out, so it marks our first day!
Was the plan to gather all of us?
It was a special order from the deputy chief. He said to gather the three of you for this sally no matter what.
That's why we're having premium Korean beef today!
Premium Korean beef is the best of all meat indeed.
I'm definitely not going undercover at a company like last time again.
Don't worry, it's not a company this time.
We'd be better off at a company. I can already see we're going to have a hard time.
I'm a little nervous... and also a little excited.
Where are we going?
Let's just say, being undercover at a company is like a kid's game compared to this.
Where exactly is it?
Is that even important? What's important is who you're with!
No matter if it's an operation or a TV drama, the casting is what's important!
That's right! The three of us make the perfect team!
We're amazing!
We are pretty good. We're exactly that, aren't we?
- What?
Good casting.
♫  Think about it, we have only one life  ♫
♫  One where we can get everything we want in one shot  ♫
♫  Do you perhaps know about perception?
The perception that’s about sense  ♫
♫  Make a choice where you only need that  ♫
♫  We have only one life
One where we can get everything we want in one shot  ♫
♫  Do you perhaps know about perception?  ♫
♫  The perception that’s about sense
Choose a world where you only need that  ♫
♫  Wherever I go, I hold my head high  ♫
♫  I walk as I please  ♫
♫  Crawl and hide as discreetly as you can  ♫
♫  I can knock you off with my eyes closed  ♫
♫  I think of this as the chance I only dreamed of  ♫
♫  I can become anything  ♫
♫  I came running frantically
I’m not like the others  ♫
♫  Go faster, run again, no matter what anyone says
That’s how I lived until now, after all  ♫
♫  This is the world I’ve been seeing  ♫
♫  Think about it, we have only one life  ♫
♫  One where we can get everything we want in one shot  ♫
♫  Do you perhaps know about perception?   ♫
♫  The perception that’s about sense
Make a choice where you only need that  ♫
♫  We have only one life  ♫
♫  One where we can get everything we want in one shot  ♫
♫  Do you perhaps know about perception?  ♫
♫  The perception that’s about sense
Choose a world where you only need that  ♫
♫  Choose  ♫