Episode 4
Identification card - Baek Jang Mi
Secretary Baek Jang Mi's real name is Baek Chan Mi.
Name, Baek Chan Mi. Age, 38.
Affiliated with the NIS Industrial Security Team Three.
Relieved from duty three years ago after failing in the apprehension of Michael.
Agent Gwon Min Seok, who was her immediate subordinate at the time, died then.
I didn't hear a proper introduction from the new secretary. Your name is?
They call me Baek Jang Mi.
HQ VP Tak Sang Gi
Nice.
Yeah, you must live a long life.
I'm seriously going to go crazy.
Division Director Tak will arrive within three minutes.
I heard you are an experienced employee. What did you do before?
You must have a lot of time on your hands these days, seeing that you're taking interest in irrelevant things.
You two looked so close, so it made me curious
if there was a backstory I wasn't aware of.
I'm not interested in things like your backstory with Executive Director Myeong, though. Should I slowly take an interest in it?
I'm starting to get curious all of a sudden.
Let's go.
They said he was a scarecrow of a CEO and now he's got a crow.
How interesting.
Why did this thing have to break? These things should be eat— Oh.
Does he only feed himself with red ginseng?
From Baek Wacko Chan Mi: Division Director Tak will arrive within three minutes.
One, two, three, four, five...
I searched everywhere but nothing comes out.
What in the world did she want me to find?
I can only find something if there's something to find.
Women
Fifteenth, at 8 pm. Red Purple?
I looked into it, and Red Purple is a wine bar managed as a private club.
Membership works on the basis of reservation, and they thoroughly protect the members' privacy.
So that means he secretly met someone there.
But why are you suddenly fixed on Division Director Tak?
Division Director Tak might be Michael.
Division Director Tak?
If he is Michael, with an offer, he had a meeting with someone.
Then, couldn't he have had a transaction at Red Purple?
Let's get the CCTV.
They start business at seven, so let's move as soon as we get off work.
Top Secret -  Code name 'Good Casting'
Good Casting
Il Gwang HiTech
Red Purple
Club Diary / Gangnam - Red Purple
DJ Yuyamuya "Detective Lover" April 4th
First club of my life "Red Purple"
Gangnam clubs Top 3 "Red Purple"
This is a welcome gift. Like a bribe for you to stay for a long time.
Cute. Cute.
Screech
O-oh! My bag!
Oh my! His hands... on her chest... @ㅁ@
Pow! -_-^
Say hello. This is your new tutor.
If there's a scar on a handsome face, it's less handsome.
Stay still. -_-  This small hand of mine has a punch that stings.
Let's work well together in the future! Yoon Seok Ho! ^O^
I love you~♥︎   I love you~♥︎   &gt;_&lt;
6:00 pm!
I'm just asking just in case, but—
I'll be getting off of work now
That toy, that toy, that...
What were you doing?
This... this... this doesn't work very well these days. You know?
Recently, the office equipment has been a mess as well.
There's the issue with the bookcase rail, too.
There are times when it doesn't work.
Did the new secretary take off?
Yes. She very courageously got off work on the dot.
If there's something you need her to do, should I call her back?
No, there's no need. What are you going to do if she quits because we give her too much work?
This guy.
What?
We'll just continue to pretend we don't know anything.
"Kang Woo Won's fan signing event in Taipei for the celebration of the new product launch."
Everything I sign causes me to lose money, geez,
but someone gets money from signing.
I'm jealous.
They say that Kang Woo Won is the hottest star in China and Taiwan these days.
It does deserve three times the original contract fee.
I think everything's just about done
What do we do? I think it's going to overflow.
Hyung, since you always waste your brain on such stupid concerns, that's why your head isn't working.
Just pack another bag! Then it's all good!
Right. We can pack another bag.
No, no. It'd be better to pack the shoes separately.
You're planning to take three suitcases?
You can't even do addition?
Two bags for clothes, one bag for shoes,
and my food.
You forgot my mukbang bag. Mukbang bag. Don't you see?
I was going to pack that at the very end.
I'll pack that when I've finished organizing all the luggage.
You can't pack luggage, can't calculate, and sulk easily.
What is it that you're good at?
Gosh! That son of...
Restricted caller identification
By 9 pm tonight,
get the item from locker 7-49.
When you arrive in Taiwan, Wang Kai will get in touch with you.
You just have to meet him and give him the goods.
Taiwan, my foot.
I can finally escape my shitty life.
I don't know what it is, but I'm sure it's more expensive than the delivery fee.
Red Purple
Ssak Ssak
As soon as you enter Red Purple, Hwang Mi Soon will stick the hacking chip in the security system,
and Moo Hyeok will hack the CCTV.
Bae Moo Hyeok
Baek Chan Mi gets all worthwhile information.
It's easier than eating rice cake lying down (pie), so let's finish within 10 minutes.
Enter.
Mission Clear!
It's the two of us together for the first time in a while.
Then shall we slowly start to pick at Division Director Tak now?
Wait.
Put them in.
Hide Baek Chan Mi for the time being.
Let's wait a bit before reporting it to Executive Director Myeong.
We caught this joker card.
I'm sure we'll find her handy sometime.
Your call cannot be connected, please leave a—
I cannot get in touch with Pi Cheol Woong.
What are you talking about?
Seeing that he completely turned off his phone,
I think he was resolved to go into hiding.
Check his location.
What is this?
Did I see wrong? I think it sparkled.
He is still in Kang Woo Won's house.
Go catch him right away, before he runs off.
Kang Woo Won said this.
That for this advertising contract,
he wanted you to be the one to discuss it with him.
Her character is that of a total loser.
Exactly the type I don't like.
Let's add one more condition.
Then you're saying you'll sign, right?
I didn't say I'd sign yet.
No matter what condition it is,
we are ready to oblige.
It's me. I received the contract well.
Let's make one amendment.
Article four, section five.
On any future event in relation to the advertisement,
the advertising company's employee in charge will be...
- What's your name?
- Pardon?
Your name. What is it?
It's Im Jeong Eun.
The employee in charge will be Im Jeong Eun. I'm hanging up.
What?!
I'm telling you to come take care of the filming site yourself every time a product from Il Gwang HiTech is being shown.
What? Can you not do it?
No, I must do it.
I will do it unconditionally.
And most importantly,
hand me the pictures.
What pictures?
Do you think I'll just let it slide if you feign innocence?
The pictures you took last time!
Why do you have so many baby pictures?
I never took any pictures of you and there will never be any reason to.
I don't even want to take them.
You go through my own private things, as you please!
That's very rude, you know!
Since I checked that you don't have any pictures,
let's terminate this contract.
If you can't, it's over.
End. You know?
The End.
Why aren't they coming?
- He's here, he's here.
- What?
Great Wall
Where is it?
- Why are you so late?
- Geez
Gosh.
Here.
The receipt.
Gosh. Give it back, I'm not selling it to you.
Gosh, why? Never mind.
Where are the danmuji (pickled daikon)?
Gosh!
Gosh, the danmuji...
Hey, you should at least give us danmuji!
Danmuji! Danmuji! Danmuji!
Danmuji!
Gosh, as a human,
he should give us sweet radish.
Hey, press the mic.
Hey, Baek Chan Mi, Hwang Mi Soon!
Come out before we finish eating this jajangmyeon.
Five minutes are enough.
Let's go.
Please go back.
Me? To where?
You're being too hard. It's not like we come here just once or twice.
I think it's our first time seeing you.
Oppa, are you acting like this because you don't know that a girl's face changes all the time?
- Keep up the hard work.
- For her it's her nose. For me.
Gosh, I'm getting annoyed. What's up with this.
We'll see each other again.
In the good old days, I'd just have to play the geomungo (6-string Korean zither) and they'd all fall, even the Russian minister of defense. What do they take me for?
What is this?
Well, I heard you were lacking in staff since it's Friday night. So I came to help in the kitchen.
Asking confirmation for the entrance of kitchen help.
I'm telling you it's true.
How many times do I have to tell you it's true?
People really lack trust toward others.
That's a big problem really.
I think Baek Chan Mi got in,
but where's Hwang Mi Soon?
Hey, Hwang Mi Soon!
Hwang Mi Soon!
On standby in the seventh-floor kitchen.
Ajumma! There are seven fruit tapas to prepare. Hurry up, quickly.
Okay, I'm on it! Quickly, quickly.
Why are you coming out so late? We need to get it to them soon!
- Bring some snacks before they run out of drinks.
- Yes, undestood.
- Oppas!
- Who are you?
My treat.
You must be tired. Take it easy.
You should eat first.
Gosh, what is all this?
Hey, but why are the guys out back not responding?
I don't know either.
Go check, you punk.
What the hell are you waiting for?
Gosh, why do you always pick on me?
Oppas, keep up the good work!
You too.
It's five meters ahead of the fourth floor emergency staircase exit.
Staff Only
There should be a door next to the boiler room that says "Emergency Exit" on it.
Boiler Room
Emergency Exit
- General Manager Park, it was good today, right?
- Oh, yes.
- Oh, Madam Lee. Thank you for the food.
- Did you have a good time?
Red Purple
Oct. 2019
Sept. 2019
Division Director Tak Sang Gi.
HDLive
I put the flag in.
Oh!
- Yessir. I'll wave the flag in two minutes.
- Good, good.
- If we had Sunbae Ye Eun with us, it would have taken her less than a minute.
- Sure.
When you get into Kang Woo Won's house, try to take the opportunity,
- and secure the surveillance cameras.
- Secure them?
Since it's not open circuit, we have no choice but for someone to go in.
But isn't this like surveillance of ordinary civilians?
Exactly, so just get the CCTVs outside.
What, you can't do it?
I have to do it. I'll do it.
Secure Network
I got it!
Hey, you can't take that! Come back. Come back!
Which one, which one, which one should I eat? Guess. Ding dong daeng dong!
What a great job my manager's doing, leaving his main celebrity without even feeding him.
What kind of manager is busier than a top star?
Hey, what is that?
Where'd you get it?
Poppy! You'll get sick if you play with dirty things!
Poppy! Poppy!
Come on, let's go home.
What is that?
Son of a X - Go broke - Nutcase - X personality - Inconsiderate X - See if you live well.
You crazy nutcase jerk, I'm quitting.
Have a good life!
AHHHH!
That crazy...
Th-Th-Thief.
A th-thief!
I don't care how you do it, but bring Pi Cheol Woong in front of me right now!
It's the person you hired, CEO!
How would I know where he ran off to?
He ruined my precious zoom-zooms...
I won't go to Taiwan event until they are returned to their original state.
I'm hanging up.
Gosh, what else isn't going right?
What's the problem?
Ah, it's all in English, dammit.
It's finally working. But only this much came out.
Gosh, you scared me.
Is she crazy?
Now she's sneaking into my house?
Okay, sure.
You're dead.
Hello? This is 112, right?
Someone trespassed here.
B-B-Behind you!
Yes, the address is—
What do I do?
68GA-3877
Six, eight, GA, three, eight, seven, seven.
Six, eight, GA, three, eight, seven, seven. Six, six, eight...
Gosh, what was it, again?
What are you talking about? A girl?
Did that girl see everything too?
Bring her too.
68 GA 3877
It's okay. It's okay.
Asleep or awake, be careful of your left, your right, your front, and your back.
It's me.
I caught Pi Cheol Woong and that woman.
Bring them to the abandoned factory. I'll go there right away.
Connected - Access CCTV data
Okay, finished hacking.
Noonims you can exit the mission, now.
Why isn't Im Ye Eun answering her phone?
Come on, Sunbae. Stop hassling Seonbae Ye Eun.
Data analysis can't be done in a few seconds within a blink of an eye.
Right. Even if it would've taken a year or twelve months,
I should have made you do all the gruntwork, right?
Just backing up the ladies is making my spine distort (he's that burdened).
Oh, why is my stomach hurting so much? I'll go to the bathroom really quick.
Ouch. The bathroom.
Ssak Ssak Clean - Whatever it is, we clean it all up for you!
Dammit.
Gosh, where is this punk?
We have a problem!
What?
Block off all exits!
Get her!
Ah!
68 GA 3877
Help me with this please.
If you press the button here for more than three seconds during an emergency, it'll be a code blue.
Hey, do you really want to die?
Gosh, I should be saying that!
Hey. Hey!
Aish. It's taking him such a long time to poop.
Do I need to be doing this at this age?
Im Ye Eun
Huh? Code blue.
Damn it, no wonder you haven't been answering the phone.
Hey, Baek Chan Mi, Hwang Mi Soon, Im Ye Eun's code blue popped up!
Hurry up!
Baek Chan Mi! Hwang Mi Soon!
Hey!
Hey, come here!
Open the door!
The keys, the keys!
It's open!
Hey! Get her!
Ow!
Whoa!
It's too late! It's all the way down!
Please, please, please!
Hey! Gosh! Get her!
Woohoo!
red purple
Oh my gosh that scared me.
Why do I always have to do this kind of thing?
Aigo, for the second time,
I'm sorry. Let's go.
Hey! What are you doing? Go get her!
Go the other way!
Ssak Ssak Clean
Why are you so late?
- Go on, go, go, get driving. Quick.
- What? What, what's going on?
I almost died!
Hey, Team Leader Dong. For this one, it's a matter of good conscience that we should get quadruple the hazard pay.
Let me see the videos you got first.
But why are you driving?
Ask Moo Hyuk when you see him!
It was 8:30 PM on the 15th, so start playing at 8.
8...
Team Leader! What happened?
He didn't leave me, right?
What is this. What is this. What is this?
Where are they?
Sir, give me the plates!
I'm someone from there.
Bae Moo Hyeok - NIS
I'm busy so let's go.
- You're from the NIS, Ajussi?
- Yes, yes.
Wow! Put on the helmet from the back!
Even the NIS has to wear a helmet. Hold on tight!
Okay, let's go!
What's this? It wasn't Kang Woo Won but his manager?
- Pi Cheol Woong is a Chinese expatriate.
- Dammit.
Our guess was totally wrong, dammit.
Wait. The fact that Division Director Tak met Pi Cheol Woong...
That must mean that Pi Cheol Woong has the item.
But where are we going right now?
Sir, where are we going?
Over there! Over there!
O-O-O-Over... Follow that car!
As for me, it is so exciting!
Ssak Ssak Clean
Im Ye Eun's in code blue? What happened?
I don't know. She said she'd go meet Kang Woo Won.
Could it be that things blew up because of Pi Cheol Woong?
Hold on tight for a little bit, Im Ye Eun.
Go left from here. Left.
What are you talking about? Follow the GPS's instructions!
Hurry and go to the left!
- No, follow the GPS! It's right!
- Left!
Gosh, you're noisy. Be quiet!
Go left from here! Left!
Stop, stop, stop, stop!
- I can see!
- Are you just going to see? Step on it!
- Step on what?
- I'll just do it.
- No! No!
- Hey!
Your driving license has been suspended!
- It's for official duty, so it's fine. I'll just do it.
- Hey hey hey!
- Let go.
- If we get in trouble, insurance won't cover it!
- I'll do it! I can't just watch!
- I said no!
Let go!
Let go of me!
- Stop it, be quiet!
- Turn right!
Let me do it!
- Why are you doing this to me?
- Come here, you.
Ah really.
Ssak Ssak Clean
Is that the scale of the NIS? We don't even have the money for HIpass (wireless toll pass system)!
To get that, we have to request it by submitting a draft plan. Anyway, it's too complicated.
What if they slip through our fingers because of this?
Seeing that they're going toward Pocheon, it's the way to the abandoned factory.
Let's go.
What is that?
Team Leader! It's me!
Open the door!
- Team Leader.
- What's this?
This little. Hey, you! Damn it.
Where were you this whole time?
What?
Hey, keep following our truck!
I can't hear anything you're saying!
Follow us! Follow us!
Follow us!
What... what's wrong with you?
What are you doing?
Let go!
Hey!
- Ajussi!
- I said let go of me!
What did you say?
Ajumma! Ajumma, ajumma!
Hey, you brat!
Are you out of your mind? Let go!
Hey, the car! The car!
What are you two looking at?
Did you see? They flinched!
Pi Cheol Woong.
Pi Cheol Woong?
It's not me. It's not me!
When stealing someone's item, you must have at least put your neck on the line.
No! I'm not Pi Cheol Woong!
Say something!
Hey! This is worth a hundred million won (≈$100K), you scum!
You son of a..
Ssak Ssak Clean
I reported for reinforcements, so keep watch from outside.
I'm saying this in advance but if Michael's in here,
he's all mine no matter what.
I get how you feel about Michael. But I'm saying this again, we're in the middle of an operation.
I won't tolerate anyone diverging from the playbook.
You're so freaking loud.
Sunbaenim!
Hey!
What are they?
Just some little girls.
Sunbaenim!
Im Ye Eun!
You are all dead today.
Let go! You won't?
-  There!
- Aish.
Sunbaenim! Over there!
Are you okay?
How long have you been lying down?
Sunbaenim.
I don't normally take this out, but
for a guy who bothered one of our teammates, a bullet doesn't seem too bad too use.
Oh, sorry. You're not a guy.
Epilogue
Kang Woo Won said this.
For this advertising contract, he wanted you to be the one to discuss it with him.
Hello, Mr. Kang Woo Won.
I came from Il Gwang HiTech, my name is Im Ye—
No, Im Jeong Eun.
You're surprised, right?
Her character is the kind that gives a real headache.
She's exactly the type I don't like.
Is this too fake?
I am Im Jeong Eun from the advertising planning team.
I heard you called me.
Yeah. I did. So what?
I always trusted that a top star such as Kang Woo Won wouldn't be so sullen
as to nullify the contract over such a small happening.
What? A small happening?
I mean, it's not like I made a mistake because I wanted to.
It happened while I was trying really hard.
How can anyone have consideration the size of a pea that they would increase their contract fee quadruple!
You should have a bit of empathy for the past times.
Wow, you've gone crazy insane!
I can't even make a sound when I'm in front of him, and here I am bluffing.
No matter what I say, they're all excuses...
Even I would never want to see me again.
I should've done well like seonbae told me to from the beginning.
But I just had to make a mistake.
How does someone like me handle a well-to-do celebrity?
I'm not even on par for this job, why did they assign it to me? What should I do?
If I don't get his signature, I'll probably get fired though.
Good Casting
Preview
Hand it over to the police and step back.
I put a not so small amount in the trunk.
I'll follow you like you asked.
Do as you see fit. I trust you, after all.
Director! Why did you put me on this operation?
- Where am I?
- He has amnesia?
I found him.
- We found Pi Cheol Woong's location.
- It's headed for Taipei.
It's been a while. Shall we fly?
Be careful!
I'll look for him.
Sir!
What's this? Did the transmission cut off?
For Baek Chan Mi, there's no record of her returning.
Even if you don't catch the tail, you can catch the scent.
He's inside the plane.
You know who I am. Why did you pretend you didn't?
It's you, isn't it? Michael.