You can't let Min Jun-guk go!
Did you get his address?
What about his phone number?
You don't seem
to understand the situation.
You're the one who hit him
and he got beaten up.
You're the attacker
and he is the victim, okay?
Do you know what he said?
He is going to get revenge.
He is going to kill the witness
who testified against him ten years ago.
I got statements
from all of the witnesses.
But he never said that.
Min Jun-guk volunteers
at six different places,
including the soup kitchen
and the abandoned dog shelter.
Why are you framing someone
who is trying to live a new life
without any evidence?
You should at least bring proof.
-I have proof.
-What? What proof?
-I heard it. I can read his--
-Stop it.
Don't say anything foolish.
You'll just become a laughingstock,
just like you were ten years ago.
Park Su-ha.
I finally remembered your name.
Write your social security number,
address,
and phone number here.
He even had a weapon.
Is it okay to release him?
It's not a weapon. It's a hammer.
He brought it to fix my broken door.
Are you close enough to vouch for him?
You're not his family or teacher.
I've known him for ten years.
He is like a brother.
You could say he is family.
You're a lawyer, so I don't expect this,
but you're not lying
to avoid a booking, right?
She is not lying.
It looked as though they live together.
-"Together"?
-Yes.
Remember when they called about
the cell phone?
They called around midnight.
And when I got there, they were together.
And I saw them leave the place together
in the morning, too.
-No, that was--
-Yes, we live together.
He is a high school senior,
so I need to take care of him.
Right?
Call me "Sis." Hurry.
Yes, Sis.
Well, that's cleared then.
Are you repenting for what you did?
Hey, if you harass that man again,
you'll be charged immediately, okay?
Answer him. Say you won't do it again.
Or you can't get out.
I'm sorry. I won't do it again.
Why didn't you just say that before?
Stop it.
I could have you charged with assault.
Hey.
There are no buses left.
Do you have money for a taxi?
Yes.
Please get in. We'll give you a ride.
It's okay. We'll take a taxi.
You can't get taxis here.
We have to go there anyway,
so we'll give you a ride.
Hey, Park Su-ha! Get in already.
I knew you were siblings
when I first saw you.
He asked me to find
who put the phone in your house.
He said you can't sleep at night,
so we should do more rounds.
He was making such a big deal,
others would envy how close you two are.
But what is your relationship
to Min Jun-guk anyway?
He said Min Jun-guk was a suspect
in the phone case, too.
So, did you look into it?
The cell phone had nothing to do with him.
He has been doing volunteer work
since he got out.
What did Min Jun-guk do anyway
for you to be like this?
Min Jun-guk killed
his father ten years ago.
And I was a witness to that case.
I get that you three have a long history.
But you shouldn't be bothering a person
who's living a quiet life.
We'll look into Min Jun-guk
on our day off,
so don't make any more trouble.
There could be more questioning,
so answer your phone.
-Okay?
-Yes.
Ms. Jang?
If he runs away,
you'll be held responsible.
Sure. Don't you worry.
Why don't you go inside?
We should go inside now.
-Let's go in, Su-ha.
-What? Sure...
Sis.
We make rounds very often,
so you can rest without worrying.
Thank you.
These are men's shoes.
Do you live with someone?
I put them there so people would think so.
Is that why you order takeout for two?
Yes.
Have you had dinner?
I'm not hungry. You should eat without me.
Call me "Sis" and I'll give you dinner.
I'm not hungry.
-I should go.
-Just stay here.
We lied to the police
that we live together.
You should stay here for a while.
What if Min Jun-guk turns up here again?
I'll feel better with this kid around.
Give it to me.
Why didn't you tell me?
It took me a while to remember.
I told you that I was Park Su-ha.
I told you, but you didn't recognize me.
Hey. How would I remember
your name after ten years?
I recognized you.
Just by hearing your name.
Even though it's been ten years.
What's with him?
Am I his first love or something?
It's not like that.
Then why are you doing this?
Why did you turn up after ten years
and say you would protect me?
I didn't want to owe you anything.
That's all.
If it weren't for her,
you would've killed me ten years ago.
So I consider my life a borrowed one.
I'm going to protect her.
CENTER FOR MISSING CHILDREN
Sorry.
Are you going like that?
What's with the umbrella?
Do you think you can fight
Min Jun-guk with that?
Can't you control reading people's minds?
You do it too often.
Is it okay to go to work like that?
Don't you have a trial?
I don't care. I don't want to die.
Shall I learn self-defense?
You should carry it,
not hang it on your back.
It could be over
before you even pull it out.
If someone attacks from behind,
strike him like this very quickly.
If there's no umbrella,
use your elbow like this.
Like this?
Or you can kick the shin,
pressure point like this.
Shin, pressure point, stomach.
-What's next?
-Next...
Just run. Run for your life.
When you met Min Jun-guk yesterday,
did you read his mind?
Yes.
Was he the one
who left the cell phone here?
Yes.
Is he going to seek revenge on me?
He won't do anything right away.
The police are watching,
and I'm here, too.
You, too?
Let's go. We'll be late.
I can't get the girl because of him.
Will this way be easier?
HYE-SEONG CHICKEN
MOM
Yes, Mom.
About that date that I told you about.
Do you want me to set a date?
"Date"?
What's he like?
Did you meet him? Is he okay?
Of course.
He doesn't let on that he has money.
He seemed really modest.
No, that's not what I'm asking.
Is he big?
Do you think he can fight?
Does he have a nice body?
"Body"?
Hey, didn't you say money
was the most important thing for a guy?
I've changed. It's body over money now.
What's he like?
I'm not sure
since I didn't strip his clothes off.
But he seems to have sturdy-looking arms.
Okay.
I'll make some time next week.
Bye.
Will I feel safer if I have a boyfriend?
Give me your phone.
Why?
GPS APP
I'm downloading a location-finder app.
What is that?
If we both have this,
we can tell where the other is.
Really?
Does that mean you can find me
if something happens?
Yes.
You seem like a CSI agent.
You look really smart.
I'm not smart.
You're just behind the times.
You have a knack for speaking very rudely.
-What do you want?
-I'll have an I.A.
One iced Americano and a red iced tea.
-And please put the points on this.
-Yes, sir.
-Where are Mr. Cha and Ms. Jjang?
-They've gone to meet the twins.
That is a very complicated case.
At first, they both said
they had stabbed the man, right?
Yes. And then the younger one said
that he had stabbed the man.
And the older one said that he hadn't.
And now they are both saying
they didn't stab him?
Ms. Jang persuaded the younger one
not to take the fall.
Why do they keep changing
their statements?
It's confusing.
I know.
You have a conviction
for theft from two years ago.
Pil-seung was whining so much
that he didn't have tuition money.
So I stole from a few empty houses.
Your brother must be pretty smart.
He had an IQ of 152
when he was in middle school.
He is really effing smart.
Why did your brother steal?
He used to be really reliable.
But then he started to gamble.
Oh, please don't mention his gambling
at the trial.
Sure. I'll think about it.
So why is your brother trying to put this
all on you?
He just hates me.
He always tells me he wants me
out of his life.
So he is trying to put you in jail
with this case?
Yes.
I have a theft conviction.
Everyone will think that I did it.
So why is your brother trying
to put this all on you, Pil-seung?
He was always jealous of my life.
I went to college
and I have no convictions.
He said we have the same face,
but our lives are so different.
He was jealous of everything I have.
So...
is that why your girlfriend...
So one stabbed the victim,
and the other stopped him.
But the prosecutor is saying
that it was premeditated.
And indicted them as co-principals,
even though it's obvious one stopping it
on the security camera video.
You said they're twins.
It may be hard to distinguish who did it.
Mr. Cha and Ms. Jang are both
going to enter not-guilty pleas.
This is going to become complicated.
One of the two killed a man.
But both of them
are saying they each didn't do it.
And they're twins
who look exactly the same.
If they can't figure out
who the killer is,
then it could become an unsolved case,
like the Itaewon-murder case.
And both of them could be released.
The prosecutor charged them
as co-principals to stop that.
Isn't that Ms. Jang?
You're right.
Why does she have an umbrella?
Did they say it would rain today?
No, I don't think so.
There's Mr. Cha.
He is going to give her a scare.
He is a very interesting guy.
Did you hear
what happened at the team dinner?
Mr. Cha carried Ms. Jang on his back.
They might become a couple one day.
They could fall in love.
I envy their age.
Shouldn't you get an X-ray?
I'm okay. Besides, I have a trial soon.
Don't you feel bad about this, Ms. Jang?
Not at all.
You shouldn't have scared me like that.
It was a violation of my hearing organs,
so it's an assault.
And my action was self-defense
against Mr. Cha's assault.
That was too much.
What would you do
if it's broken down there
and he can't have kids?
This isn't just any injury.
This is a serious injury.
It's not a serious injury.
I checked it and it was fine.
See?
He says it's fine.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know you would be so surprised.
Mr. Cha, you are
too nice for your own good.
You're taking her side
and you're apologizing, too.
I should call you Saint Cha from now on.
Okay, I'll apologize.
I was wrong, I'm sorry. Okay?
Is that an apology? Is that an apology?
She would slap the person next to her,
even though she was the one
who passed gas.
And for this case,
they're not co-principals.
I think so, too.
Good. The older one is the one who did it.
No, that's not right.
The younger one did it.
Never mind. Let's not say any more.
Aren't you going to eat with us?
No! I have plans.
I have no strength in my legs.
Are we close enough to eat together?
We lived in the same house
and went to the same school.
We could say we're close.
-What are you up to?
-Nothing.
Did you meet the defendants
in the twin case?
Did you come to ask that?
Be honest with me.
You don't know who did it, right?
You're scared you would be wrong
if you picked one of them.
And you have to let them both go
if you say you don't know.
Isn't that why you charged them
as co-principals?
Yes. How did you know?
What?
Are you admitting that you made a mistake?
Yes, I'm admitting it.
You're right again.
I think I'm wrong.
Are you teasing me?
No, I'm not teasing you.
Why do you think so?
I'm not stupid.
Who would believe you
when you're looking at me like that?
Right? Don't you think so?
Jeong Pil-seung, Jeong Pil-jae.
They both looked at me like this.
They raised the corners of their mouths...
and the middle of their brows.
That was their expression when they said
they weren't joint offenders.
Do you think they were telling the truth?
Do you think so?
So that's the evidence you have?
Are you going to get them with that?
No. I have another strategy.
What is that?
-Will you help?
-Yes.
No, I don't want to.
Why should I do that?
There she goes again.
What is her strategy?
Is Do-yeon just lying?
What if she has something?
This is driving me crazy.
Shall I tell them to confess? No, no.
When are you going home?
I'll come to pick you up.
That's right. I have my stalker.
I have a favor to ask of you.
OKAY, CALL ME WHEN YOU'RE DONE
"Okay, call me when you're done.
I'll come and pick you up."
Teacher! Park Su-ha was texting.
Hey!
You guys have such great lives.
Not only are you texting,
but you're dating someone.
-I envy you.
-It's not like that.
Don't you dare leave detention.
I'm going to keep an eye on you.
Sir.
Can I have the phone?
I'm waiting for an important call.
I'm confiscating it.
Take it after detention.
I can't believe this.
COURT OF KOREA
I am glad that I brought an umbrella.
Ms. Jjang! Ms. Jjang!
Hey...
What? Were you at court as well?
Yes, I followed you from way back.
Why didn't you call me?
We could have shared my umbrella.
I didn't want to surprise you
as I had done before.
Is something going on?
What?
You look nervous
as if you're being chased by someone.
I'm worried.
-It's not like that.
-Okay, then. Let's go in.
Hold on.
About hitting you before.
I think you gave me a reason to hit you.
Yes, I know. I'm sorry.
But I also admit
that I overreacted a little.
So I'll apologize. I'm sorry.
Sure. I'll be more careful.
Could you spare me some time?
I need to talk to you about the twin case.
YEONJU DISTRICT PUBLIC DEFENDER'S OFFICE
Did the prosecutor say she has a strategy?
Yes. Can you guess what it is?
There was no blood trace.
Nor any fingerprints. What could it be?
Are you close friends with Seo Do-yeon?
No, I don't like her.
Not liking isn't even enough.
Just hearing her voice
gives me goosebumps,
just like fingernails scratching
a chalkboard!
We're not close.
But she came to eat with you?
Yes.
Goodness. She doesn't have a strategy.
She is totally bluffing.
I thought so, too. But you never know.
She wouldn't tell you
if she had something.
She is telling you she has something
because she doesn't.
But still...
Don't be shaken or anxious.
An excited bull only sees the red cloth
and not the matador.
The prosecutor is waving
a red cloth to affect you, so...
That means I'm a bull.
I should get mad.
But why am I not getting mad?
First my eyes and now my brain.
-Ouch.
-What should I do?
Ms. Jjang.
Jinx.
What are you doing?
I feel the same way as you.
So, "jinx."
Don't you know "jinx"?
Oh, that.
I know.
I must be crazy. Shoot.
What's with stalker boy?
He isn't answering his phone.
It's early enough to go home alone.
Why aren't you leaving?
I'm going to leave.
It's still raining.
I don't have an umbrella.
Ms. Jjang, can I borrow your umbrella?
No. What about me?
This is what we can do.
First, we go to your place together
with this umbrella.
And when we get there,
you can lend it to me.
What do you think? Okay, right?
What is this? Is he coming on to me?
Do I look so easy?
You should hold the umbrella.
Yes.
Let's go.
EVENING DETENTION
HOW CAN YOU SLEEP WITH GRADES LIKE THAT?
Park Su-ha.
My stomach! My stomach!
-What's wrong?
-What's wrong with her?
I think I have stomach cramps.
Shit, that hurts!
Someone please take me to the nurse.
Hey! Are you okay? I'll take you!
Please, please take me.
-What are you doing? Take her.
-What? Yes.
My stomach!
You can put me down now.
I thought my arms were going to fall off.
Shouldn't you thank me
for getting you out of there?
I never asked for help.
Are you going to meet the lawyer?
Yes, she said she needs to talk to me.
Here's your phone.
I got it when I collapsed.
Thank you so much.
I'll buy you something tomorrow.
I have to go now.
Su-ha...
-The number you have dialed...
-Why isn't she answering?
Is she still at work?
PUBLIC DEFENDER'S OFFICE
She isn't there.
That's right. I can trace her.
136 YEONJU-RO
She is almost home already.
Let's do it this way.
Let's try to get
"co-principals" off the table first.
Then we can figure out
who is innocent or not.
-Before we do that...
-How should I say goodbye?
Should I bow and say "goodbye"?
That's too stiff.
Or should I wave my hand and say "bye"?
No, that would be too much.
What is better? What should I do?
We should meet tomorrow
and match our lips together.
What?
Why do we have to match that?
We're on one team,
so we should be saying the same thing.
Oh, that.
Yes.
Of course we should.
It's raining really hard.
KO SEONG-BIN
-Yes.
-Did you meet the lawyer?
No, not yet. Why?
It's about the first love
you told me about.
It's the lawyer, right?
What an odd question.
Do you still like her?
Of course not. It was a long time ago.
Then why are you so concerned about her?
Well, that...
It's because I owe her something.
I don't like to owe things.
I'll repay her and disappear.
Oh. I see.
Is that why you called?
No.
I called to tell you that I like you.
I know. You told the whole school.
No, not like that.
I really like you a lot.
I realized that today.
I don't care if you don't like me.
I don't mind having a crush.
But when you look at someone else,
think about someone else,
and have feelings for someone,
I feel strange. It's not okay.
My heart hurts when I think about you.
I guess it sort of hurts.
And it also races a lot, too.
I think I really like you a lot.
Hello? Hello, ma'am.
I need to tell you something.
So I don't think I should go
on the blind date you had mentioned.
No, it's not like that.
But there is someone
who piques my interest.
I'm sorry. I know you're trying to help.
I think it's such a shame.
She is my friend's daughter,
so I know her very well.
She is very pretty and a lawyer.
She grew up as an only daughter.
I think she would be a great fit for you.
My gosh. What a shame.
Call me if you change your mind.
I'm not going to give up on you.
Yes, thanks for calling. Sure.
Geez...
Who are you talking about?
"Pretty," "an only daughter,"
and "a lawyer"? Who is it?
Jang Hye-seong.
You said it's a friend's daughter.
If I said it was my daughter,
it would be too much.
I had this planned,
but it's not working out.
Did you tell Hye-seong that it's Mr. Cha?
Of course not.
If I did, she would throw a fit.
She has such a temper.
I need to have a subtle plan
to get her to date someone.
Is that "a subtle plan"?
Of course.
Relationships don't just
form naturally these days.
You must really like that Mr. Cha.
He is really great.
He is the second son
of a family that owns a sauna.
He is a lawyer
and he has a great personality.
He also has very sturdy arms.
But here is the real reason.
-What is that?
-Hold on a moment.
"Man is wood and woman is fire."
"It's as though you've gained a fan
in the summer.
The two love each other
as a married couple.
And they will live a long life together."
I have to make sure he doesn't get away.
-You got their fortunes read?
-Yes.
In this world, speed is everything.
Is that you?
Why didn't you answer your phone?
You said you'd walk me home.
Why are you so wet?
Didn't you take an umbrella?
Stalker, I'm making savory pancakes,
do you want some?
I'm making some for you, too.
Change your clothes. You'll catch a cold.
Wear the blue t-shirt with Mickey Mouse
on it that's in the top drawer.
It should fit you.
Can you come to court
at 2:00 p.m. tomorrow?
I have a really
complicated case this time.
They're twins.
One stabbed a man,
and the other tried to stop him.
But we can't tell
which one is the murderer.
They look so much alike.
Where is the salt?
So you should come to court
and find out who did it.
If they weren't under arrest,
you could come and meet them.
But the only way for you
to see them is to come to court.
Can you make some time?
Why haven't you changed yet?
I called, too. You didn't answer.
I don't want to eat,
and I don't have time tomorrow.
What's wrong with him?
STALKER (12 MISSED CALLS)
So he did call.
Hello.
What brings you here?
We have a few questions
about the assault case.
-I see.
-Are you going somewhere?
Yes.
I thought I should leave.
Leave? Why so suddenly?
The boy who assaulted me, Park Su-ha...
I did something horrible
to him ten years ago.
We heard.
I realized that he must not like
that I live nearby.
He will be reminded of me
and would want to seek revenge.
So I think I should leave.
Have you decided where to go?
Thankfully, there is
someone who will hire me.
It's a little far from here,
but I'm going to try my best.
What were you going to ask me?
Nothing. It's okay.
-Thank you.
-Bye.
If you happen to meet him,
please tell him I'm sorry.
Sure, I will.
That guy is leaving for no reason.
He probably wanted
to make a new life here.
I know.
What should we do
about Ms. Jang's phone case?
-Should we keep investigating?
-But nothing went missing.
-Yes.
-End it.
HYE-SEONG CHICKEN EVENT
Where did this poster go?
Did it fall off?
FOR PUBLIC DEFENDER JANG HYE-SEONG
9,900 WON CHICKEN EVENT
Stalker! Aren't you going to school?
Are you upset?
Okay, I admit we were both at fault.
You didn't answer your phone first
so you're at fault.
I admit that I didn't answer either.
That's my fault. Okay?
Anyway, please don't be mad
and come to my trial today.
I was able to win
the last one because of you.
I was able to do it
because you were there to say I was right.
So please come to this trial, too.
Are you listening?
I feel at ease when I see your eyes.
I need you...
I must be crazy. That was too much.
Hey!
I didn't mean that.
Pretend you didn't hear it.
What a relief.
Oh my gosh.
-What are you doing here?
-We're late. Let's go.
Did you...
Did you hear what I just said?
What?
Nothing.
Can you come to my trial today?
No.
Hey, just come!
Please?
Say you're attending a work-study program
at the courthouse.
Hey!
We used to get extra credit
for work-study programs.
Don't you have that anymore?
Isn't that important
for when you go to college?
Come on.
Hello, Ms. Jang. You're still at home.
Hello.
We thought you might be worried,
but Min Jun-guk has moved.
-Really?
-Yes, we just saw him off.
He said he didn't think
he should live close to you.
He said that he should live far away.
Did you check where he is going?
What about his address?
You've done enough.
He said he is moving to avoid you two.
Anyway, you can forget
about him and live in peace.
It looks as though he is going
to a place where he knows no one.
I felt bad for him.
What do you mean?
Thank you. We have to get going.
-Let's go.
-What? Okay.
Have a nice day.
You won't have to see
Min Jun-guk ever again.
Can I...
Can I believe him?
No.
Crystal. Give me your hand.
You're so good.
You're a cool girl.
So your name will be "Crystal"
from now on.
Is this about that date again?
Hey! Didn't you say you would go
on this date?
You said you would consider it
as a back-up.
Did I?
But I think I should just
concentrate on my career.
If I work hard here,
maybe I will meet someone
to spend my life with.
Is there someone you like already?
There you go again. It's not like that.
I meant that I could meet someone
while I work here.
Anyway, I don't want to go on a date,
so please let him down gently for me.
Hey!
My arrhythmia keeps turning up
because of you.
What does that have to do with me?
My heart can't keep up
with how you change your mind!
I'm hanging up!
Calm down.
Please calm down.
I can't believe her!
Calm down. You have to calm down.
Calm down. What am I to do?
Do I have to give up
on this subtle plan of mine?
What a shame. I think it's such a shame.
HYE-SEONG CHICKEN
HELP WANTED: DELIVERY MAN
FOR HYE-SEONG CHICKEN
Hello.
I came because of the job.
We spoke yesterday.
Oh! You're Kim Gil-dong, right?
Yes, that's right. Hello, Ms. Eo.
Hold on! Hold on.
Did you close the door on purpose?
No.
-I didn't see you.
-What a loser.
You can't fool me.
I don't believe
that you have proof either.
And I'm going to overturn
your co-principal indictment.
Did you read precedent cases?
Of course.
The 2006 Yeongchi-dong murder.
The 2009 Yeongwol murder,
rape and concealment case.
The 2010 Moksan-dong
homicide by robbery case.
The Moksan-dong case
is similar to this one.
Two brothers were involved
and both pleaded not guilty to murder.
But they got 15 years
as co-principals, right?
The judge was a fool.
Really?
Did you check the judge's name?
The name?
It's Kim Gong-suk.
He is our judge, too.
She's right. It's Judge Kim Gong-suk.
I can't believe this.
How could he just try the case with both
as co-principals?
He probably couldn't be bothered.
There was no proof
and both pleaded not guilty.
I think he even extended the sentence
for contempt.
What if he does that again?
I know.
Okay, class, this is the criminal court.
Do you know what a criminal case is?
Yes, it's crimes like
murder, robbery and theft.
Are you thinking what I'm thinking?
Jinx!
From looking at the indictment,
this seems like a complicated case.
They're identical twins
and I couldn't tell them apart.
Just think of it as tough beef.
We have to quickly swallow it.
Chewing on it will ruin our teeth.
The prosecutor indicted them
as co-principals.
Yes, they see each other every day.
They probably knew about the knife.
I think we can see them as co-principals.
Let's get this over.
How about blowfish soup tonight?
-There's a new place.
-Yes, sure.
The judges are here.
All rise.
-Cool.
-He is so amazing.
Please be seated.
IN SESSION
Wow, they really look alike.
They even have the same hairstyle.
Defendants Jeong Pil-seung
and Jeong Pil-jae
conspired to steal money at one location.
When the victim Ham Ki-su turned up,
the defendant Jeong Pil-seung
stabbed the victim with a knife.
Jeong Pil-jae did try to stop his brother
at the crime scene.
However, before that,
he knew his brother was
in possession of a knife.
And he could've predicted
that murder was afoot.
And that establishes them
as co-principals.
Defendants. The term "co-principals"
is difficult, right?
It means that more than two people were
at the same place, at the same time,
and committed a crime together.
So they will be punished together.
Even if one killed and the other stole,
they will both be punished
for killing and stealing.
Okay?
The vocabulary is too difficult.
We should explain to the defendants
so they can understand.
Such small considerations
build trust in the judiciary.
-Cool.
-He's cool.
Jeong Pil-seung's counsel should go first.
Yes.
Defendant Jeong Pil-seung is pleading
not guilty to the charges.
Jeong Pil-seung never
stabbed the victim, Ham Ki-su.
And he didn't know
that his co-defendant had a knife.
So he is not a co-principal
in the homicide.
Are you denying the facts
in the indictment?
Yes.
Jeong Pil-seung only went with his brother
to steal tuition money.
He did not expect
his brother to have brought a knife.
Hey!
You stabbed him and I stopped you!
How dare you lie like that?
Please sit down.
Look, Your Honor. I didn't do it.
He is trying to put it on me
because I have a conviction.
-I really didn't know.
-Please.
Please sit!
Please be quiet.
If you speak up like that again,
you will be removed.
Awesome.
Please continue.
Does the prosecutor have evidence
I don't know about?
I fully understand
why you charged them as co-principals.
Someone was killed,
and there is footage from the crime scene.
But you couldn't figure out
which one of them did it.
As you can see,
they look exactly the same.
And you couldn't let them both go
because they can't be told apart.
A man was murdered because of this crime.
That's why the prosecutor indicted them
as co-principals.
They were put together
because one knew about the other's knife.
But both of them are claiming
not to have known about the other's knife.
One of them must be lying.
That means one
of them must be telling the truth.
And this also means--
That the one telling the truth
will have to go
to prison in vain.
I believe it's the tribunal's mission
to stop it.
Of course, this will be
a long and hard fight.
It was a fight
that even the wise prosecutor gave up.
But I believe the judges
should not give up on that fight.
No, I believe you already agree with me.
The time spent revealing
the truth and protecting justice
is not wasted.
As both counsels stated,
it's hard to consider them
as co-principals.
Your Honor.
If one had known about the knife,
then there wouldn't have been the act
of stopping the action.
The one who stabbed the victim will
be charged with homicide by robbery.
The one who stopped him will be charged
with special larceny.
The prosecutor should
change the indictment
to homicide by robbery
and special larceny.
We will review the evidence after that.
Let me explain.
It means that we don't think
they planned this crime together.
So I'm asking the prosecutor
to indict the two men separately.
Correcting the prosecutor's indictment
is part of our job.
Okay?
It's to build trust in the judiciary.
Mr. Cha!
When shall we have our next meeting?
What meeting?
The twin case.
We've succeeded the first phase.
Let's work on a new plan now.
-We have to work separately.
-What?
It's a fight with you now,
not the prosecutor anymore.
Evidence unfavorable to me
could be favorable to you.
So we can't share evidence.
You do have a point.
I should get going. I have another trial.
Never mind.
Do you think I like working with you?
Do you know what you did?
I know.
Dozens of police officers worked
on this case.
There is no evidence about
who stabbed him or who stopped it.
I know.
You do?
Both of them could be found innocent.
But if I didn't do anything,
both of them could have gone to prison.
How can someone who murdered be released
as an innocent man?
Isn't it better
than someone innocent going to prison?
Even if you miss ten criminals,
do not punish an innocent man.
Didn't you hear that enough
at the Judicial Research Institute?
Do you know
who should leave the world of law?
A lawyer who always loses?
A judge who always makes wrong judgments?
Or a prosecutor
who always makes the wrong charges?
Shut it.
It's none of the above.
The biggest problem is people like you
who won't admit they're wrong.
Remember what I said before?
Apologize to my mother if you lose to me.
You'll be keeping that promise soon.
Be prepared.
You were amazing Jang Hye-seong.
You're so charismatic.
Hey, Stalker.
I was looking for you.
Let's go. I'll buy you dinner.
I was so nervous before.
I thought Do-yeon
might have hidden some evidence.
But when you said there wasn't any,
I became calm and could speak freely.
It felt good to be defending.
You asked about
the firework incident, right?
Yes.
Someone shot fireworks
toward Do-yeon's eyes.
And one of Do-yeon's eyes
was badly injured.
Do-yeon said I had done it,
and I said I hadn't.
People believed her.
And I got expelled.
And ten years later,
we meet again as lawyer and prosecutor.
I didn't really want to become a lawyer.
And I didn't know
why I had become one either.
But I knew
when I saw Do-yeon's expression.
I became a lawyer because of that moment.
To see her expression.
-Are you that happy?
-Yes.
-Why?
-I was right and she was wrong.
What if you were wrong...
and she was right?
What do you mean?
You're wrong. The prosecutor is right.
What?
YEONJU TUNNEL
What do you mean?
I'm wrong and Do-yeon is right?
The twins planned
to kill that man together.
They're co-principals.
They're co-principals?
You're lying, right?
Tell me it's a lie!