[Respect Copyright, Everyone's Responsibility]
[The Eternal Fragrance]
[Adapted from Shisilang's novel, The Eternal Fragrance]
[Episode 18]
No wonder my divination last night warned me
about a backstabber on this trip.
Be cautious.
Xiguang,
the Outcast Tomb
is where demons from overseas are interred.
As they're our enemies,
why bury them formally?
Here.
Because Wuyue Court's elders
are benevolent.
They laid all vanquished monsters
to rest in peace.
Why did Zhuyan sneak in?
Mourning?
Perhaps Demon Lord Yecha's remains
are buried there.
That's why Zhuyan risked everything to get in.
Xiguang,
are Yecha's eyes golden?
Demon Lord Yecha is said to be cruel, bloodthirsty,
and masked,
with blazing golden eyes.
He killed
ruthlessly.
Want a fruit?
School days are long past.
Drop your icy stare
when traveling.
Get along with others.
Got it?
[Xingzheng Hall]
Uncle.
Well done.
Your fire-controlling skill is perfected.
Go into seclusion with me from tomorrow
to cultivate the Hua Sect's advanced inner art.
Seclusion?
I thought
we were going to the Outcast Tomb on the White Cliff.
The tomb was built 500 years ago
by Wuyue Court's ancestors,
deemed useless back then
by other immortal sects.
Now, Cuixuan has summoned all the immortal sects on White Cliff.
Seems disaster looms.
The summons is vague.
A demonic beast is said to have broken into the tomb.
The demon clan
has long lurked,
likely laying traps
for us.
Then anyone going there
will be in danger.
As the Sea Calamity draws near,
all sects are saving their strength,
so few will respond to Wuyue Court.
Cuixuan and his disciples
can handle the demons.
Xingzheng Hall won't step in.
We shall wait and observe.
Lifei has weak spirit power,
and she's not Cuixuan's disciple,
so she probably won't go.
So this is the Outcast Tomb.
What's carved up there?
Outcast Tomb for those from countless states and islands overseas.
Countless states and islands?
Could the traps beyond the Ganhua Realm
be linked to the tomb?
What connection
do those islands have with the demon clan?
They originate from there.
Ancient texts record
that there are countless overseas islands,
each with
unique customs,
swarming with demons.
The texts only mention foreign folk,
not necessarily demons.
The White Cliff is the burial ground of demons,
sealed for centuries after its construction.
Whoever strays will not return.
It's fraught with peril.
This concerns the safety of the Central Plains.
We mustn't take chances.
I will follow you to slay demons,
even at the cost of my life.
Big trouble!
What's wrong?
I just cast a straw divination for this trip
and got the hexagram Earth Over Mountain, Modesty.
Isn't that an auspicious sign?
It's lucky
anywhere else,
but this is
a graveyard.
Mountains are within this land,
and waters run close beside it.
This means
the truth will surface.
Something huge is going to happen.
Oh!
I need to cast another divination.
Really?
Lifei.
Qin.
Back at Lilie Valley,
I underestimated the enemy
and got corrupted by demonic energy.
Sorry to have offended you.
Please grant me
a chance to make amends.
It's overgrown and deserted.
Let's stick together.
Lifei,
something's odd about the bushes.
Stay close.
Coming.
Don't touch it.
This is Wuyue Court's defensive formation.
Once activated,
it'll attack all intruders without discrimination.
Since when have you two grown so close?
As expected, Zhuyan's here.
Stay close, Lifei.
Xiguang,
what hexagram did you just divine?
I didn't even do any divination.
The straws snapped for no reason.
Something's coming.
Go now!
Demon!
So you're behind all this.
Worthless immortals,
you'll all rot in this tomb today!
Demon, meet your end.
Thank you, Immortal.
You've lifted the tomb-sealing talisman
that trapped my kin for centuries.
It won't work.
A formation looms overhead.
Crafted by Wuyue Court's ancestors
masterfully beyond compare,
it's infused with the mystic arts of Qi Men Dun Jia,
turning this place
into an inescapable labyrinth.
As one of those elders,
can't Elder Cuixuan break it?
Before coming here,
I begged my master to let me
read secret scrolls about the tomb.
Elder Cuixuan came here thrice and returned gravely wounded.
No one but the formation's creator
can break it.
Since he can't break it, did he lead us
to die here?
My master said
Elder Cuixuan acts ruthlessly,
risking everything without mercy
for others or himself.
Cultivation has stripped him of all compassion.
His profound power
lets him survive such gambles,
but what about us?
Are we disposable pawns?
No wonder Deng's divination failed.
Don't fear.
You'll live.
We all will.
My master said
no poison or formation
is unbreakable.
I refuse to believe we're trapped forever.
Right.
Man-made barriers
always have an exit.
The Life Gate is located in Gen Palace.
Come.
Lifei.
Run now.
You're just an eyesore.
I wouldn't rest in peace
if we perish together.
Just accept it.
I'll never leave you.
Have you lost your mind?
You're corrupted by a demon spirit.
We need to purge the demonic energy inside you.
You got corrupted too.
Why channel your spirit energy to me?
Save it for yourself.
Shut up.
Lifei.
I never thought we'd die side by side.
I'll die with regret.
I thought that if I practiced hard,
I could keep you safe,
yet we ended up here.
I'm nothing but a jinx.
Why dwell on that now?
You acted for Lu
and had no choice.
♪The warmth within my arms♪
Have you forgiven me?
♪I can no longer hold on to♪
Not yet.
♪In the cold night, how can I♪
So,
once we die...
♪Keep you warm until sunrise?♪
And reach Naihe Bridge...
♪My heartbeat freezes♪
We must drink the Forgetting Soup.
♪I can no longer tell you♪
Make sure we never cross paths in the next life.
♪Looking you in the eyes, I cannot♪
Got it?
♪Utter that line♪
I won't.
♪Knowing love and hate♪
♪Pain and wounds cannot be stopped♪
♪I still linger on♪
♪Unwilling to let go of every inch of our past♪
I'll never drink it.
♪Last night's stars cast faint glimmers♪
You've been a substitute this life,
fleeing for your life since ten.
Homeless,
starving,
living worse off than me.
♪Knowing right and wrong♪
♪Black and gray are all illusions♪
What's there
for you to cling to?
Drink it and be reborn sooner.
In this life,
♪Running relentlessly without regret♪
I was treated unfairly.
♪The storm looms, yet the wind stands in its way♪
Yet life hasn't been entirely cruel.
♪Leaping straight into that heartbreaking past♪
I have Lu
and...
♪Just to keep you safe♪
And you.
I'm really lucky enough.
♪My breath is about to stop♪
♪Those hands can no longer hold yours♪
Truth is...
♪Through the future snow, wind, and fog♪
I don't want to forget you either.
♪Who will be there by your side?♪
♪I smile as it ends♪
I traveled nonstop with my master since childhood...
♪Afraid that you might cry for me♪
Never growing close to anyone.
♪Quietly, I turn into a sky lantern♪
You're the first one to get close to me...
♪To light your way through the night♪
And the one I care for most
besides my master.
I was furious...
♪Unwilling to let go of every inch of our past♪
Because I trusted you,
but you lied to me.
♪Last night's stars cast faint glimmers♪
♪But we thought nothing of it♪
Still,
♪With a heartbroken cry♪
when you took my pain away...
♪I wish you well♪
My heart broken.
I feared for you when you
shielded me from harm.
♪You're still screaming♪
Now...
♪Running relentlessly without regret♪
I understand the line from the storybook.
♪The storm looms, yet the wind stands in its way♪
Love blooms unawares.
♪Torn inside, still I burn bright♪
Deepening without end.
♪With the light from my fingertips, I build a paradise♪
♪To wander with you♪
Xiuyuan!
Demon chants?
Could it be...?
Lifei,
why is your spirit power so faint?
What's wrong?
Where is Lei?
Watch out!
It's Demon Lord!
Demon Lord Yecha has revived!
Lifei, it's too dangerous here.
Let's leave at once.
Lifei!
Xiuyuan,
it's Lifei.
don't you recognize me?
Xiuyuan.
Master,
why do those spirits keep pestering me?
You're different from others.
They crave your hair
and blood.
♪I trade all the mortal world's splendor♪
♪For a fleeting moment with you♪
♪Our fates intertwined, embracing yet fighting♪
♪The hardest bond to balance♪
♪Obsessed and struggling, a thousand thoughts arise♪
♪Love sprouts again in this lifetime♪
♪No calamity can rival♪
♪The lingering thread of a fragrance♪
♪With you, through mountains falling and seas turning to sand♪
♪Withered branches burst into bloom♪
♪Hand in hand on the Naihe Bridge, past the pagoda♪
♪In fine robes on galloping horses♪
♪Always, at the very end of obsession♪
♪Comes that one moment of softness♪
♪Betrayed by all, I still♪
♪Reign supreme♪
♪With you, we melt into mist and haze♪
♪I trade the highest heaven and endless clouds♪
♪For a fleeting moment with you♪
♪Pierced by countless arrows, pain and illness pile on♪
♪Yet I remain silent♪
♪Deep love and long yearning, a kiss falls into a dream♪
♪In the distant night, bitterness blooms♪
♪The grand chapter is rewritten♪
♪Startling the whole world♪
♪With you, through mountains falling and seas turning to sand♪
♪Withered branches burst into bloom♪
♪Hand in hand on the Naihe Bridge, past the pagoda♪
♪In fine robes on galloping horses♪
♪Always, at the very end of obsession♪
♪Comes that one moment of softness♪
♪Betrayed by all, I still♪
♪Reign supreme♪
♪If the seal can't be broken, then let it go♪
♪Where the heart finds peace, there is home♪
♪Side by side, we fly through seas of clouds♪
♪Break through the waves♪
♪The heart's ocean knows no shore♪
♪Always, at the very end of fate♪
♪Comes that one moment of defiance♪
♪In the human world or above, like flowing water♪
♪And falling petals♪
Lifei!
♪Let this fleeting life be whatever it may♪
Fish!
Run!
Don't overthink it.
You're so weak
that you were possessed by the demonic energy,
like being haunted.
It's nothing serious.
Don't
misinterpret what I did.
I was only saving you.
This scent...
This way.
What's wrong?
The aura of the Divine Tree.
It's really here.
I think I saw it
somewhere before.
This scent is the same as Lifei's.
Could I be Yecha?
No,
I've never hurt Lifei.
Xiuyuan,
this wound looks like it was torn off.
What are you doing?
The aura is gone.
Lifei!
Lifei.
Where have you two been?
Are you alright?
We're fine.
Master,
the tomb sank into the sea,
so the demon threat should be gone.
The White Cliff lies in ruins,
yet we found no trace of the Demon Lord's corpse.
I cannot rest easy.
This tomb disaster means
the demon clan will strike again.
Send word to all immortal sects
across the nine states to prepare.
Understood.
Lifei.
I told you the hexagram Earth Over Mountain, Modesty was ill-omened.
Earth over mountain
signals a great shock.
The White Cliff collapsed.
Do you think
Demon Lord Yecha perished?
I once thought my master's tales
of Yecha were overblown,
but now I know
they were not.
You know what?
When his gaze fell on me,
my legs froze.
Luckily,
he just revived
with power yet to return.
Otherwise...
Xiguang,
did Yecha truly slaughter countless souls?
He slaughtered countless people,
like a nightmare for all the immortal sects.
Xiguang,
have you seen
a huge transparent fish?
There's a fish in the Northern Ocean
named Kun.
Its size
is beyond imagination.
You saw something
no mortal has ever witnessed.
Legends say the Kun fish comes from overseas.
It's a sacred spirit
and is rarely seen.
Are those rock piles
linked to Master?
Whose severed arm
was it?
Jiang Lifei.
Why come here alone?
I lost
my Xiaying Sword,
and it was forged specially by my master.
I dare not return
if I can't find it.
Where did you drop it?
I don't know.
Everything was a mess yesterday.
Those demons kept chasing me,
and I don't know where I dropped it.
Where is it?
Yangling told me
you were there when Yecha appeared,
but he lost sight of you during the escape.
Where did you go afterward?
My cultivation is weak,
and Qin vanished at once.
Found it!
I found it.
Yecha has returned,
and the demon clan stirs restlessly.
Facing the Sea Calamity,
the Central Plains face grave danger.
I hereby invite all immortals
to Duanming City by the East Sea
for the Shanhai Gathering.
Immortal Cuixuan, we await your arrival with your disciples.
[Duanming City]
Aren't people here afraid of spirits?
Not at all.
Sea Sects excel at taming them.
Every spirit
you see here
serves humans.
So in Duanming City,
humans and monsters coexist.
It's a unique sight of the Central Plains.
Elder Cuixuan,
Qin,
my father awaits you
at Luxin Hall of Wanxian Sect.
This way.
Many thanks, Ms. Shen.
Lifei,
congratulations on joining Wuyue Court as you wished.
Credit goes to the masters' teaching.
Where's Mr. Mo?
Fearing you'd take Yanfan away,
we sent him on an overseas task early.
Didn't you want to break the Fragrance Bond?
What?
Made up now?
Where's Gelin?
She left on business with Lu Li.
She said
she'll come to you later.
Will you head to Wanxian Sect with me,
or wander around?
Walk around.
Lifei,
want candied hawthorns?
Fine, you take them.
Sir, two, please.
Okay.
- How much? - Here you are.
There's an aromatic shop.
Zhaomin would love it.
You only care about her, not me.
[Wanxian Sect]
Yecha'd been slain by ancient immortals,
yet revived with evil arts,
filled with raging resentment.
Recent disturbances in the mountain-sea barrier
are likely tied to his return.
The barrier was built by Wuyue Court's ancestors.
A catastrophe looms.
We must protect the barrier at all costs.
Since the barrier lies off the East Sea,
let disciples of both sects
patrol nearby islands
during this gathering
to root out dangers.
Humans and spirits coexist here.
Shen, do not let your guard down.
Tongzhou?
[The Eternal Fragrance]
[Adapted from Shisilang's novel, The Eternal Fragrance]
♪The warmth within my arms♪
♪I can no longer hold on to♪
♪In the cold night, how can I♪
♪Keep you warm until sunrise?♪
♪My heartbeat freezes♪
♪I can no longer tell you♪
♪Looking you in the eyes, I cannot♪
♪Utter that line♪
♪Knowing love and hate♪
♪Pain and wounds cannot be stopped♪
♪I still linger on♪
♪Unwilling to let go of every inch of our past♪
♪Last night's stars cast faint glimmers♪
♪But we thought nothing of it♪
♪With a heartbroken cry♪
♪I wish you well♪
♪Knowing right and wrong♪
♪Black and gray are all illusions♪
♪You're still screaming♪
♪Running relentlessly without regret♪
♪The storm looms, yet the wind stands in its way♪
♪A final farewell left on the cliff♪
♪Leaping straight into♪
♪That heartbreaking past♪
♪Just to keep you safe♪
♪My breath is about to stop♪
♪Those hands can no longer hold yours♪
♪Through the future snow, wind, and fog♪
♪Who will be there by your side?♪
♪I smile as it ends♪
♪Afraid that you might cry for me♪
♪Quietly, I turn into a sky lantern♪
♪To light your way through the night♪
♪Knowing love and hate♪
♪Pain and wounds cannot be stopped♪
♪I still linger on♪
♪Unwilling to let go of every inch of our past♪
♪The storm looms, yet I stand in its way♪
♪Torn inside, still I burn bright♪
♪With the light from my fingertips♪
♪I build a paradise♪
♪To wander with you♪