[English subtitles are available]
Why are the semester starting so soon?
Have you read Tieba?
Guru Qing He fell and got hurt.
That's why the signing event
was postponed.
[Xi Hai High School]
Goodness, is he all right?
Oh no.
Does that mean we won't hear
anything about his new comic too?
Look at her uniform.
She must be White Swan,
who has just transferred here.
Her skirt is super short.
Look at her skirt.
What's going on?
Why is everyone staring at me?
I'm feeling embarrassed.
I'd better act confident.
Girl, where is your uniform?
She's a new student.
She hasn't got her uniform yet.
You've just transferred here
from Da Cheng, right?
No wonder.
Go in.
Thank you.
The transfer student is a goddess.
When I was in Da Cheng,
I had never been treated like this.
It's so nice to be regarded as a goddess.
I'm so blessed.
[Teachers' Office]
[Liberal Arts Teaching And Research Group]
She's really beautiful.
Mr. Jia, is she joining our class?
What are you doing?
Move along.
She just smiled to me, she smiled to me.
Tong Xi,
so you're a local.
I've always thought
you're from Da Cheng.
Sir, actually,
my parents are locals.
I transferred to Da Cheng
when I was in elementary school.
Okay, I'll send
your transfer papers to the
administration office.
I'll take care of it.
Come on, let's get you to your class.
Okay.
I never thought we would have
such a talented kid like you in Xi Hai.
I heard that you even shot a drama.
And you've got an international award.
[Me? International award?]
Kids these days are really extraordinary.
[Drama?]
Let's go.
[Summer Again]
[Summer Again.
Episode 2: A Girl's Vanity]
They're coming! They're coming!
[Adapted from Huo He's comic, "Mint Love"]
All right, all right.
Mr. Jia is going to introduce her.
Kids, today is the
first day of the semester.
Allow me to introduce.
I'd like you to welcome
a new student of our class, Tong Xi.
Welcome, welcome!
We're thrilled to have you here!
Coast is clear.
As expected, the nuisance
who knows my background
isn't here.
Now I can be the legendary goddess
without worries.
Where did you get this kitten?
[Blue Elephant]
You're not keeping it
in the shop, are you?
No way.
Don't you know that
I'm afraid of furry creatures?
What about these
and those?
My Andre is allergic to cat hair.
What if he comes here...
Andre?
So he really exists?
I've been working here
for over a year now.
And I've never seen him.
My Andre is a busy man.
He is the CEO of a
multinational corporation.
He flies around the world
every day for his business.
Like Iceland, New Zealand,
New Orleans.
He said he would come to China this year.
I think
we're going to meet each other soon.
Tong Xi is a transfer student
from Da Cheng City.
She is still unfamiliar with our school,
so please take care of her.
Tong Xi has very good grades
and she can dance ballet.
Tong Xi, can you dance for us?
We've never seen anyone
dance ballet in real life.
Yes, I really want to see it too!
Dance for us! Dance for us!
Tong Xi! Tong Xi! Tong Xi!
That's enough, that's enough.
Leave her alone.
Tong Xi,
let me put you at...
Beside me, Sir!
She has to sit here.
Wang Yi Ming,
I know the seat next to you is taken.
He...
Sir, why don't you put her here?
My grades are bad. I can help her.
Sure.
Tong Xi, you can sit with Tao Zhu.
She meant her grades are bad,
and you can help her.
Okay, thank you, Mr. Jia.
Hi there, I'm Tao Zhu.
[Although it is a little overstated,]
[what they said]
[are not completely baseless.]
[For example, the fabled
international award,]
[that's group award.]
[And that so-called
celebrity backup dancer,]
[that's group dance.]
[And]
[I shot a drama.]
[That's actually true.]
[There is picture to prove it.]
[But I just have one shot.]
[As for the description
of female celebrity,]
[my waist is slimmer than my leg,]
[Waist is slimmer than leg,
a celebrity, a fashion icon.]
[and I'm a fashion icon,]
[that's a little too much indeed.]
You were just meeting a friend,
how did you injure your leg so badly?
By the way,
didn't the new semester start today?
You skipped school?
It's the first day of the new semester,
whether I report in or not
makes no difference.
You get it.
[The press conference of Aimei Comics]
[was concluded yesterday.]
[Despite the drizzle,]
[the number of attendees
far exceeded expectation,]
[which proves the enthusiasm of the
Animation, Comics and Games (ACG) fans.]
[Do you have any thoughts you would like]
[to share with us about the conference?]
[It's been a joyful experience.]
[I met many authors I'm familiar with.]
[My biggest disappointment is]
[I didn't get to meet my idol, Qing He.]
[It's such a pity.]
[We heard that Guru Qing He's injured.]
[We hope he could get better soon.]
[We look forward to our
next meeting and book signing.]
[And we look forward to his new comic.]
[Guru Qing He, we'll always love you.]
[Guru Qing He, we'll always support you.]
[Guru Qing He, hang in there.]
Looks like
Qing He had an
unfortunate accident like you had.
Are you having a run of bad luck lately?
Why do you all get hurt so easily?
[Wang Yi Ming: Lin, the transfer student,
White Swan, was assigned to our class.]
[Why didn't you come in the first day of
new semester? Have you read my message?]
[I heard that she won
an international award.]
[And she shot a drama before.]
[She really is a White Swan.]
[Come to school early tomorrow.]
Nice shot, nice one.
Nice shot!
Good one, good one.
Throw it, throw it.
Nice shot.
Come on, throw it, throw it.
Go on.
Nice shot.
That's a good one, you look so cool.
You're indeed the best small forward
of the basketball club.
What are you guys up to?
You've been acting weird today.
Nothing, nothing.
You're in form.
I guess I am in good form today.
Ming, can you do us a favour?
What favour?
It's about
the new student in your class,
the White Swan.
Can you get her
contact information for us?
Here, Ming. Put on a cloth.
So you won't catch a cold.
Come on.
Let's go.
Phone number, Weibo or QQ.
Anything.
No way.
They've let me scored several times.
Wang Yi Ming,
you really are something.
Just because they let you score,
you're trying to trick
the goddess for her contact?
Do you even know her well enough
to ask for her contact information?
I...
Do you know them?
They're from drama club.
Do you think
I have an secret admirer there?
They are looking at me.
How am I going to turn him down later?
Aren't you just in charge of
floor sweeping in drama club?
Why would someone admire you?
Tao Zhu,
you have a new student
in your class right?
Can you give me her contact information?
President.
Asking a girl
for another girl's contact information,
are you sure
this is the way to talk to a girl?
You're right, President.
See you, President.
Senior Xu Ao.
Ignore them.
Want some squid?
I bought some extra sticks.
Thank you, Senior.
Afternoon, Senior.
Sorry again that I couldn't make it
to the press conference.
But I heard that Guru Qing He
was also absent due to his injury.
I think there should be a
new arrangement soon.
I hope we can go together again when
there is another book signing event.
I wonder if Senior Wei Ze
would find it interesting
if he knew how I am treated here.
Are you that pleased to be in my class?
You must be Tong Xi.
Hello, Mr. Xu.
Okay, let's start our class.
Stretch your leg.
Good.
Two, three, four, move.
[That was only my first day in class,]
[the practice was already so intense.]
[Isn't this]
[the same place I used
to go when I was a kid?]
[This is the mint garden left by grandpa.]
[It's so beautiful.]
[Let's hang out here
more often from now on.]
[Qing He Fans Club, group notification.]
[Evening, Guru.]
[I saw the news.]
[The other day I was still upset that]
[I would miss your
first public book signing,]
[I thought I was going to
regret it for the rest of my life.]
[I didn't expect that]
[you would change the date tacitly.]
[Don't worry,]
[I'll be there on time next time.]
[Today is my first day in the new school.]
[I had an extraordinary experience.]
[It's the first time I knew
what it was like to be noticed.]
[I suppose you're accustomed to it.]
[But for someone like me, who is ordinary]
[and has no idea about
what to do in the future,]
[it made me really nervous and excited.]
[I decided to view White Swan as my goal,]
[I'll work hard to train myself]
[and become a real goddess.]
[After all, everyone is so enthusiastic,]
[how could I let them down?]
Why is it broken? I'd better fix it.
Someone lives here.
Oh my, look at her teeth.
She's so pretty.
I want to watch her movie.
White Swan is stunning.
What are you doing?
That's a real goddess.
Her hair is so smooth.
Look.
[Even if we're bullying him,]
[is it any of your business?]
[Of course it is.]
[Everyone in the alley knows that]
[he's my fiance.]
[I'm going to marry him in the future.]
What do you call this?
A food for the eyes.
Food?
It's feast. How many times
have I corrected you on that?
Your leg hasn't recovered yet.
What happened to your face?
It's fine.
Based on my observation,
our White Swan here is
really friendly, despite she's a goddess.
Goddess, you meant her?
[Climb up, I'll give you a hand.]
[They say you can see the sea]
[from the highest position.]
[Tong Xi, come down here.]
[It's too dangerous.]
[How is it dangerous?]
[The ladder is so short.]
[It's only dangerous for those]
[who are smart but clumsy.]
[Forget it.]
[You're so no fun.]
[I'm going to keep climbing.]
[I'll leave you alone.]
[Lin Nan Yi, you're useless.]
[Tong Xi, why would you
want to marry this loser?]
[Run!]
[Stop there!]
[I'm going to beat you all
until you're handicapped.]
[Tong Xi, you can't keep doing this.]
[You're a girl.]
[You can't always
solve problems with violence.]
[It's not that I want to
solve problems with violence,]
[but they keep picking on you,]
[I have to stand up for you, right?]
[What will happen to you
when you grow up?]
[If you do this when you're adult,]
[you'll be arrested by the police.]
[Well, I'll just let you]
[protect me when we grow up, okay?]
Where are you going?
I need to talk to her.
Sit down.
I get it.
You can't resist the temptation
to talk to White Swan.
But don't you think
your appearance will be
obtrusive in such a beautiful view?
[About how to become a goddess.]
[Find a book.]
[The recommendations are]
[Marguerite Duras, Eileen Chang, Sanmao.]
[In Search of Lost Time]
[Find a window.]
[Choose the best lighting time]
[to show your perfect backlit side face.]
[Your hair is important.]
[Keep it loose, let the
wind blow through it.]
[The highlight is]
[smiling a little]
[to show the pleasure of reading.]
[I've been reading for 20 minutes.]
[That should be enough.]
You...
So this seat is taken.
Hello there, new classmate.
She's a goddess?
Don't be silly.
I've known her since childhood.
She had beaten every boy in the alley.
Is she that scary?
Not just scary,
she's simply terrifying.
Look at my leg,
I was hurt
because she pushed me to the ground
at the station two days ago.
Scary, right?
Tong Xi,
were you looking at Lin Nan Yi?
No.
I have nothing to be afraid of.
Since I've come this far,
if he dares to say anything,
I'm going to let him
wait and see.
Lin Nan Yi?
Is Lin Nan Yi
the student who just came today?
What were you looking at just now?
I was just looking around.
Alas! Beautiful place
doesn't stand forever.
A grand banquet doesn't reappear.
The Orchid Pavilion Gathering is gone,
the Golden Valley Garden is in ruins.
Can anyone translate this for me?
Tao Zhu, I pick you.
You seem to be really relishing
the Teng Prince's Pavilion Preface.
Come on, translate this to our class.
Sir, let me do it.
Go ahead, Tong Xi.
This means that
a beautiful place doesn't last forever.
It is difficult to reunite again
even for a grand party.
The spectacle of Orchid Pavilion Gathering
has become history.
Even the Golden Valley Garden
has turned into a ruin.
Well done.
Excellent.
Tong Xi has obviously
prepared for the class.
Well done.
Sit.
Come on, others.
Come on, everyone,
I want you to write this down.
This poem
expresses the author's
sentimental and sensitive feelings.
Take it out and share it with me.
I...
Good for you.
You like English so much?
If your English teacher saw this,
he's going to be really happy.
A fresh start in the new semester.
Your spirit is encouraging.
However,
your next class is English class.
You can work hard on it later.
Come on, let's carry on with the class.
Thank you for helping me, Goddess.
Goddess, do you like Guru Qing He too?
[Are you a fan of Guru Qing He too?]
I don't really read comic.
I usually read Shakespeare
and Tagore's books.
I thought
you're a fan of Guru Qing He like me,
that's why you helped me just now.
By the way,
kids, listen up.
I just remember that
our blackboard bulletin contest
is coming up next week.
You all know the rules, right?
Anyone who is interested,
please come and register with me actively.
All right?
It's time to show your true talent.
It's now or never.
Okay?
Okay.
Blackboard bulletin contest?
Ignore him.
The contest is held once a month.
The winner is always
the student from Class 5,
who wants to enrol in
Central Academy of Fine Arts.
Everyone else who registered always
received "Thanks for Participating".
By the way, Goddess,
[Early Summer]
debut work of Guru Qing He,
a super popular new comic artist,
are you interested?
It's not about romance,
its themes are family love and warmth.
I guarantee that you'll fall in love
with it once you start reading.
Take a look at it.
Oh please,
I know every word in it, okay?
Sure.
I'll take a look when I have time.
Don't wait.
How about tonight?
Since we couldn't go to
Guru Qing He's book signing event,
we can pilgrimage at Blue Elephant.
Blue Elephant?
Sister Mi Ya,
since when did you keep a cat in the shop?
You mean Monroe, she came here yesterday.
Why do I feel like
I saw this cat before?
Young lady,
this is your first time here, right?
Hi, Sister Mi Ya.
I'm Tong Xi.
Hi.
You can make yourself
at home here from now on.
Make yourself comfortable.
Monroe, what a strange name.
I came up with it.
Is it not good?
Look,
it has a mole on the corner of its mouth.
Oh no,
Andre is calling me.
He can't find out that I'm keeping a cat.
Otherwise, he would misunderstand
that I don't love him anymore.
Knock yourself out.
Andre?
Andre has been Mia's boyfriend
from when she was studying in France.
She said he's some sort of
CEO of a multinational corporation.
Sister Mi Ya has been waiting for him.
But sometimes, we all think that
Andre is just Sister Mi Ya's
imaginary boyfriend.
Never mind, let's go and read some comics.
Come on.
So this is Blue Elephant.
It's the best comic coffee bar in Xi Hai.
And of course,
it's the only one in the city.
What do you think?
It's not bad compared
to Da Cheng, right?
It's nice indeed.
I think so too.
Look around first, Tong Xi.
I'll go order us some beverages.
[Early Summer Bonus Collection.]
[I never thought that I could find]
[Guru Qing He's comics
in the cafe in Xi Hai.]
[My idol is so popular.]
[Let me take a picture
and post it on Tieba.]
Thank you, thank you.
I thought you only read
Shakespeare, Goddess.
You...
What are you doing here?
I work here.
You work here?
Why do you look so surprised?
Goddess, if you're very interested in this
Early Summer Bonus Collection,
you can register with me.
You can buy it or borrow it.
I'm just looking around because
Tao Zhu kept recommending me this place.
Careful there.
There're a lot of people here,
be careful not to lose the cover.
Lin Nan Yi.
I'm talking about book.
Book became old when
it's been read many times.
Be careful with the book cover.
You...
Tong Xi, come here.
Tong Xi, allow me to introduce.
This is Ke'er from our class.
You know her too, right?
I'm here to read comic book.
I ran into Tao Zi.
Do you mind if I sit here?
Not at all.
Sir Lin.
Since there are only few customers today,
and Sister Mi Ya has
important things to do,
why don't you join us?
What do you say?
Coming.
Well, indeed.
Let's begin our horoscope
fortune telling for tonight.
Tong Xi, I'll do yours first.
When's your birthday?
What time were you born?
July 7.
I don't remember the exact time.
Around 7 p.m. or 8 p.m.
What a good date.
That means before 9 p.m. right?
Before 9 p.m.
Where were you born?
The location?
Xi Hai Town.
You were born in Xi Hai Town?
I transferred to Da Cheng
when I was in elementary school.
So we came from the same hometown.
Now I feel closer to you.
Listen,
but
where did you live?
Xi Hai is a small town.
I never saw you when I was a kid.
That's right.
I lived in Xi Zhao Alley.
When she was a kid,
she was a shy girl.
She rarely left home.
There was no way you would know her.
That's right, I was shy.
You guys knew each other
when you were kids?
Yes.
Then why did you
ask me about Lin Nan Yi's name before?
I thought you've never met each other.
I... I...
We barely knew each other.
Besides, it's been a long time.
I didn't even remember
her name when I saw her.
Lin Nan Yi.
Yes, he seemed familiar to me.
And I couldn't remember his name just now.
And I thought you were peeking at
Wang Yi Ming with the mirror last time.
You gave me a fright.
Tao Zhu,
are you talking bad about me
behind my back again?
No.
I was just thinking that
why would such a beautiful girl
have such a bad taste in man?
No, she doesn't.
Tong Xi obviously has good eyes...
[Blue Elephant]
Lin Nan Yi, what's wrong with you?
What do you mean by that?
Why did you tell them that
we knew each other when we were kids?
I'm begging you.
I have a weak heart.
Can you please watch your mouth?
You hate me for knowing too much
and I would ruin your image
as a Goddess, right?
Fine.
But I just don't get it.
What's the reason with all these pretense?
Why can't I pose as a goddess?
I've been a common girl when I grew up.
I want to try this feeling now.
What's wrong about it?
Also,
why can't you treat me
like I'm your common classmate?
Stop asking me so much
and stay out of my business.
We are not that close anyway.
It's getting late,
do you need me to take you home?
You are crippled on one leg.
Who dares to sit on your bike?
Such a hothead.
Lin Nan Yi, you really are my kryptonite.
But
isn't he just a freshman in high school?
Why is he working in Blue Elephant?
Can high school freshman
work part-time now?
Forget it.
What does it have to do with me?
I'll stay out of his business,
he'd better stay out of mine too.
About the blackboard bulletin contest,
although the first place
is booked by Class 5,
but the second, third, fourth and
fifth places are still available, right?
Look at you all being gutless.
Do you what this is called?
This is called losing before the battle.
Do you hear me?
All right, class dismissed.
Goodbye, Sir.
Tong Xi,
I'm going to the supermarket.
Do you need anything?
I have enough space here.
It's fine, thank you.
You don't have to be
so polite with me, Tong Xi.
By the way,
there were boys asking me
for your contact information today.
But I turned them down.
They are not handsome.
I'm a good friend, right?
Really?
Thank you, Tao Zhu.
You're so kind.
You saved me a lot of trouble.
Don't mention it.
I'm going now.
[Someone actually asked
for my contact information.]
This is actually happening on me.
I wonder if they are handsome boys.
Tao Zhu is so insensible.
I wish that ticking time bomb is not here.
What do you want?
You scared me.
I want to talk to you.
Tong Xi.
Mr. Jia.
I've been looking for you.
How may I help you?
About
the blackboard bulletin contest,
I think that since you
came back from Da Cheng City,
your idea, creativeness and insights
are certainly different.
So I figure that
maybe you should give it a try.
I'm not very good at
decorating the blackboard,
Mr. Jia.
No pressure.
The most important thing
is to participate in it.
Of course,
if you don't know how to draw at all,
I won't force you.
But if you think you're okay,
we can give it a try.
Right, Nan Yi?
Yes.
I believe Tong Xi can handle it.
It's settled then.
Good.
This is great.
Misfortunes never come alone.
High school's bag is heavier
than the junior high school's bag.
High school's bag is heavier than
the junior high school's bag indeed.
What are you trying to say?
I'm just talking.
You're still mad at me?
You pushed me into fire pit
when Mr. Jia talked about
the contest in the afternoon,
I'll hold onto it forever.
How would I know you can't draw?
How wouldn't you know I can't draw?
You did all my art work for me
when we were kids.
It's not like we're close.
We're just common classmates.
How would a common classmate know
you can't draw?
I knew it.
You're getting back at me, aren't you?
How about this?
Let's each take a step back.
Stop being so harsh on me.
This is who I am, a petty person.
And I don't need you to help me draw.
Draw?
It's so frustrating.
[Guru Qing He,]
[life is so tough.]
[The big problem is not solved,]
[another small problem emerges.]
[The point is that there is someone]
[who tried to screw me
in the small problem.]
[At this moment,]
[how I wish]
[I could have one ten thousandth
of your drawing ability.]
[Even if I don't,]
[I wish you will give me the power]
[to help me solve all the problems.]
[Qing He's Only Designated Girlfriend]
It's read?
It's read!
Oh my god!
Guru Qing He read my private message.
You're sprouting too.
[This is for you, mint is easy to grow.]
[Okay, wherever I go,]
[I'll keep it with me.]