[English subtitles are available]
Something's not right.
Look,
Tao Zi suffered bad
stomach ache in the morning.
But, Tong Xi took her away.
She didn't even take my call.
Something's wrong.
Lin Nan Yi,
I bet you know something.
Spill the beans.
Want to know?
Hold on.
What's up?
Where?
Alright, I'm on my way.
Oh, come on!
You haven't said a thing!
How did this bunch of people
become so weird?
[Tourist haven't found]
[blue tears on the beach.]
[We urge you to...]
Senior?
You've come around.
How do you feel? Better?
How...
How did I end up here?
You fainted because of low blood sugar.
Did you not eat well
when you came back here?
Well yeah,
this place has nothing nice to eat.
Uhm... Sorry to have
troubled you, Senior.
Nah, it's the other way around.
Thanks for coming to fetch me
even when you need to go to school.
Oh, right. I used
your mobile phone to
contact your classmate.
He'll be here in any minute.
I'll
need to be at the school
to do student registration procedures.
If you're feeling better,
then, I'll just...
Forget it.
I'll just wait for
your classmate to be here.
No, no.
Just go about your business.
We'll keep in touch after that.
Okay.
I've paid the hospital bills.
When your IV drip is done,
just ring for the nurse
to remove everything.
See you around, Tong Xi.
Bye, Senior.
Bye.
[Outpatient]
Lin Nan Yi,
what brings you here?
So, you were the one Senior contacted?
Where's that Senior of yours?
He needed to handle some
student registration procedure.
He's gone back to school.
How undependable,
leaving you here alone.
He's tight on time.
It's just reasonable for him
to attend to important matters.
Are you saying a living, breathing
human that just fainted
is an unimportant matter?
Why are you getting upset?
Upset?
I'm not upset.
I'm just disappointed for you.
After all you've done for that Senior,
acting like a lady,
go on a diet, skip classes and
end up fainting in front of him.
And he?
Sent you to a hospital and left you.
Any normal person
wouldn't have done such a thing.
Lin Nan Yi,
you're crude!
Senior wanted to stay,
I asked him to leave.
So,
you yourself created these troubles.
I shouldn't have come.
I...
Hello, Tao Zi?
[Hello, Tong Xi.]
[I just looked at the time on my phone.]
[It's 1.30 p.m. now.]
You and Senior should hurry back.
Or else,
Ni Xiao Wan's going to ask me
for the medical leave slip.
I won't have an excuse.
Okay, I'm on my way.
You're not well yet.
Just rest for the rest of the afternoon.
I'll apply medical leave for you.
No way.
I promised Tao Zi that I'll go back.
Or else, we'd be exposed.
Change into your school uniform.
I'll be waiting outside.
[Summer Again]
[Summer Again. Episode 9:
The Fairy Tale of the Blue Tears]
Not bad.
I've seen your report card before.
[Adapted from
Huo He's comic, "Mint Love".]
I could tell that you're a good student.
It's pleasant to see that you're also
well-developed in moral, intellectual,
fitness and appreciation of aesthetics,
music, sports,
as well as eloquence.
When you enter this school next semester,
you'd be the pride of Xi Zhong.
Another pride of Xi Zhong
is Tong Xi from Mr. Jia's class.
I think she switched school from
Yu Cai High School in Da Cheng too.
Right, Mr. Jia?
What a coincidence!
You are...
Wei Ze.
Wei Ze, do you happen to know Tong Xi?
She's exceptional at ballet.
I know her.
When she was in Da Cheng,
she enrolled into the school's art club.
I'm the president of the art club.
Yeah?
That's awesome. You must be excellent.
Sir,
I'm going back to class.
P.E. class right?
Okay, go on.
Goodbye, sir.
Okay.
This is the receipt.
Keep it with you.
Bring it with you next semester
when you start classes here
then you can participate in the
National College Entrance Exam here.
Will do. Thank you, teacher.
That's tortuous.
How are you feeling now? You okay?
I've never thought of
welcoming Senior in this way.
This is bad.
I think Senior's impression of me
is a lousy one.
How would that be?
Such situation
would awaken his sympathy
and touch his heart.
He can't despise you, can he?
You might not know this,
but Senior treats people strictly.
Once,
he led the choir to perform.
One of the girls had the
slightest wrinkle on her attire.
Once they're back stage,
he told her off straight.
I heard,
the girl ran out crying.
Wow, that's scary.
What's that Senior
of yours like?
This is basketball,
not your enemy.
See that?
Stuck like glue once she's back.
Something's up for sure.
Just tell me what you know already.
I'm left in the dark!
Hey.
Senior, are you calling me?
I'd like to ask
if you're in the same class as Tong Xi?
There's something I need to see her for.
Can you take me to her?
Senior, I bet you're close to Tong Xi
back in Da Cheng?
Our class heard that
she's gotten international awards
and danced with mega stars
and starred in drama series.
Are those true?
This way.
Didn't you notice that Tong Xi and Tao Zhu
are being affected by
something weird recently?
Such as?
Both of them
each has a Senior.
I know about Tao Zhu's Senior.
That ugly squidhead, Xu Ao.
What's Tong Xi's Senior like?
Senior.
What? Where?
My gosh. So handsome.
There he is.
Let's go.
The bell has rung!
Where are you looking at?
Sir,
this Senior
switched from Da Cheng to our school.
He's come to look for Tong Xi.
Enough of the chatter.
Tong Xi,
go.
Thank you, sir.
He's Tong Xi's friend.
The White Swan and Senior,
what a matchless handsome couple!
Exactly!
What a handsome couple, I envy them.
Living thing.
Senior.
Enough chatter.
Let's resume with P.E. class.
For today, we're having basketball
one-on-one match.
Pick your opponent.
Senior, are you done
with the registration?
Yes. How are you feeling?
Are you better now?
Sorry to have troubled you just now.
Is it okay for you to wait for me?
I'd like to treat you
to dinner after class.
Okay.
I'll find a place to do revision.
The girls can practise volleyball
or watch the boys in their match,
but no running around.
Or else, other teacher will be
taking over P.E. class next time.
What?
Cut it out!
Begin practising. Dismiss.
Okay.
So? Is it the both of us?
Get your own opponent.
Go back to class.
See you later.
Okay.
Senior, want to play?
One-on-one.
There's one spot left.
Alright.
We have a friendly match.
Game at three points.
Ready?
Go! Go! Go!
I don't even know
who to support.
Gosh, Lin Nan Yi,
why wouldn't he compete with Senior
in piano-playing?
Senior, go!
Hey, how could you support an outsider?
Lin Nan Yi! Go!
Nan Yi! Go!
Lin, guard his right hand!
Guard his right hand!
Lin Nan Yi! Go!
Go!
Go! Go! Go!
Lin Nan Yi! Go!
Good one!
Isn't this attacking?
Don't talk nonsense.
He's broken no rules.
Okay.
The score's two-two now.
Last shot.
Go!
Go! Go! Go!
Lin Nan Yi! Go!
Lin Nan Yi wins!
Incredible!
You identified my weakness in no time.
Lin, you're so cool!
Lin Nan Yi.
Senior, is your hand alright?
Yeah.
Congratulations, Lin Nan Yi.
You were exceptional!
Senior's not bad too.
Lin Nan Yi, why are you smiling?
Can't you play basketball properly?
Must you attack others?
He didn't. Why did you have to blame...
Tong Xi,
he didn't break any rule.
But, Senior, your wrist...
You heard it,
Senior said he didn't break any rule.
Why do you keep biting on to it?
Am I?
Pressing down the opponent's hand
in an acceptable way is normal.
There's nothing to be ashamed of.
Thank you for the match.
It's a good game.
I'll train well,
you won't stand a chance the next round.
Well, yeah!
Senior wasn't ready today.
He didn't even have the right shoes on.
[Ocean of Love hawker food stall]
Senior, I apologize.
My friend's gotten arrogant today.
Lin Nan Yi isn't normally like that.
I don't know what's gotten into him.
So, I'm sorry for that.
He doesn't know you well
but he came up to challenge you.
It's fine. Come to think of it,
I kind of like him.
Don't misread it. I mean, I admire him.
Although it's only
my first time meeting him,
I can feel that he's got
the spirit of excellence.
I like people like this.
That's why I agreed to play against him.
Yeah?
Yeah. And, I'm switching to this school
in the next semester.
It's not a bad thing to get to know
some
excellent people.
Stop wiping. It's clean already.
Is that Senior we saw
Tong Xi's crush?
From what I saw,
Tong Xi's been supporting him
all the way despite being from our class.
She went, "Senior! Go!"
"Senior! Go!"
She didn't even care to cheer for you.
However, that senior does have skills.
No wonder he's captured
the heart of our White Swan.
Lin,
you've got to get a grip.
Of what?
What do you think?
It's obvious.
If it wasn't for Tong Xi,
you wouldn't have challenged that Wei Ze.
And, you had to win it!
Someone
is jealous.
Just look at how you react.
I'm right, huh?
You are indeed jealous.
I've told you that you and
White Swan are not normal.
But that's normal.
Which guy doesn't want a fair lady?
Ouch, ouch, ouch. What?
You're really nosy.
Have you sorted out Tao Zi's letter?
I read and understood it crystal clear.
It's too messy between girls and boys.
This brain of mine
just can't get it.
So, better a finger off than aye wagging.
I shall give it a clean cut.
Cut away Tao Zi's
feelings for me.
[Xi Hai High School Drama Club]
My joints are rusted.
Can you oil them for me,
so that I can move about freely?
Can you get the lubricant for me?
It's in that shack.
Aunty Emmy, I'm home.
I'm very happy.
I want a heart.
It makes a person happy.
And, happiness is the most
wonderful thing on earth.
I need a brain.
You need a heart?
How in the world
are we left with such regret?
Aunty Emmy, I'm home!
I'm happy,
and blissful!
Senior,
besides
playing the main female lead,
I played other characters as well.
What do you think?
It's full of Fauvism.
I'll think about it and get back to you.
Okay, Senior.
Next.
Senior,
I apologize.
I didn't know you don't take seafood.
It's fine.
It's not that I don't eat at all.
I usually have them at
Izakaya restaurants.
[Don't judge this restaurant by its look,]
the food here is sublime.
It could just be the best restaurant
in Xi Hai.
This place may appear a little dirty,
but the food here is sublime.
It could just be the best restaurant
in Xi Hai.
I can see that it's popular.
However,
seafood needs to be prepared in
a much more hygienic environment.
Plus, I have a sensitive
stomach.
So...
Of course,
there's much space for improvement
for customer service.
But,
I bet there aren't
decent restaurants in Xi Hai, huh?
To be honest, after going to Da Cheng,
I didn't feel like coming back here.
If it wasn't because of family matters
that I failed to register into
the school in Da Cheng,
I won't be forced to come back to take
the National College Entrance Exam.
Did you come back here to take the
National College Entrance Exam too?
I'm here with my mum due to
her job transfer.
She brought you back with her
because of her job transfer?
Isn't that too hasty?
You could have stayed in Da Cheng
and continued your studies there.
And,
I bet, it's hard for you to get used
to the environment here, huh?
My mum raised me alone all these years.
The thought of leaving me alone in
Da Cheng worries her.
So...
I struggled to get used to things
here when I just came back.
But, after some time, things are fine now.
It seems like you've made friends.
However,
do you fit in well with the others
after living in Da Cheng for so long?
What do you usually talk about?
Is it about
how to fish?
Xiao Wan,
when people here were your age,
we were skilled in fishing,
drying nets and all sorts of things.
But youngsters at your age now
don't know many of these things.
Yeah.
So, why don't you train
my younger brother?
With such results,
he should be learning a skill
or two as back up.
Forget it.
Your dad hopes that your younger brother
gets in university
and be someone.
Let him mull on it.
Xiao Wan,
do you have good news to share?
I rarely see you that happy
and smiley.
It's nothing, really.
A Senior of
one of my friends
is switching schools back
here from Da Cheng.
She's happy.
I'm just happy for my friend.
I hope that they get along well soon.
[Then,]
[Lin Nan Yi and Tong Xi
would have nothing in between them.]
Alright. That's good.
Senior, I apologize.
Since you've made it back,
this one should be on me.
It's alright.
You're the only friend I have in Xi Hai,
after all.
And, I'm switching back here
to study next semester.
You could treat me then.
Senior, you haven't eaten a lot.
You should be hungry, huh?
Let me treat you to some street food.
It's okay.
It's better to eat less at night.
Especially you, a ballerina.
You need to maintain your figure.
So, you should be careful of what you eat.
[What does he mean?]
Does Senior mean
I'm a glutton?
I wanted to take a look-see around Xi Hai
to see if there's any difference
from how my parents described it
since I'm here for the registration.
But, it appears that
nothing has changed.
However, this place
has nothing nice about it,
so, it isn't worth staying here.
It's not like that!
[Blue tears is produced by]
[biofluorescence of organisms in the sea.]
[Every year, big groups of tourists
flock to Xi Hai]
[Expert: Blue tears won't appear
this year due to climate factors]
[to watch this wonder.]
[But according to experts,]
[as it is affected by factors such as
temperature and weather]
[there might be a delay in
the blue tears appearance.]
What blue tears?
"The most beautiful scene in Xi Hai"?
What a joke.
It's a lie.
See? Nothing!
It's real!
Haven't you heard of this fairy tale?
Hades and Menthe fell in love,
but, they were forced to be apart.
Menthe's tears fell into the sea,
forming blue tears.
Fairy tales like this are for
wheedling little girls.
How could you, a boy believe it?
And,
aren't blue tears
the fireflies in the ocean?
How does it represent Xi Hai?
Tong Xi, do you believe in miracles?
Senior,
do you believe in miracles?
[Blue tears]
[is actually a type of sea sparkle.]
[It lives in the ocean,]
[swayed by the waves.]
[What did Senior say?]
[Did he agree?]
Yes.
I plan to bring Senior
to Five Rainbow Beach.
There should be the most beautiful place
to see the blue tears.
[Yeah.]
But, I heard that the blue tears
hadn't appeared in a few years now.
The news said that
there won't be any too this year.
So, no one's gone there.
What if it doesn't appear?
Wouldn't that be awkward, Tong Xi?
That's why I said to
wait for a miracle.
I want Senior to see
a different Xi Hai.
A Xi Hai that's most beautiful.
Well, the Heavens
might be touched by my sincerity
and grant my wish.
[Make sense.]
If it really appears,
then, at the romantic sight
of the blue tears,
you and Senior cozying up to each other,
hugging each other so tightly...
[Stop!]
[You read too many young-love comics.]
[Senior and I are not like that.]
We don't stick to each other
and do the mushy things.
Moreover, he...
[What about him?]
I don't know how to put it.
I just feel that
he's not the same as I imagined him to be.
Why?
Perhaps,
this is my first time
interacting with him up-close.
I realised
I don't know him as well as
I thought I did.
[He doesn't appear to be]
[exactly like how I imagined him.]
Why does it sound like
you're not pursuing him anymore?
No, no way!
I still adore him.
Forget it.
Maybe my mind is a little messed up
because I fainted this morning.
I'll just talk to Senior
when we go to see the blue tears
[tomorrow.]
You need to know someone
to really understand them.
But, the closer you get,
the more you expose your true colours.
Be careful not to blow
your perfect goddess cover.
[But, Tong Xi, have you seen]
the latest updated content on Mint?
Besides Qiu Ke,
the female lead
met a long-time friend as well.
How handsome,
my gosh!
Although the story between these two
has just started,
I'm already smelling
the scent of sweet suffering.
Hurry, go see.
On it!
[Quick, quick. Let's read together.]
[Qing He: Thanks for your support,
I look forward to our next conversation.]
Tao Zi,
can you believe it?
Guru Qing He sent me a message!
[It's obvious.]
[You wouldn't have challenged that Wei Ze]
[if it wasn't for Tong Xi.]
[And, you had to win it.]
[Someone]
[is jealous.]
No way.
Jealous?
Impossible.
He's just a show-off Senior.
What's to be jealous of?
[Guru,]
[my gosh, I can't believe it!]
You DM-ed me!
Sorry, I was busy before this.
I didn't manage to go through the posts.
I hope to interact with
you more regularly, Guru,
to improve together.
Yeah?
Mint's updated. Did you see?
Do you like it?
My gosh,
how am I so lucky today?
Guru replied me in a split second!
I just finished reading it. I loved it!
And, the female lead...
And, the updated content
is so familiar to my school life.
I can feel what the female lead
has felt and experienced.
It's awesome!
Yeah?
You mean there happened to be
such an adorable girl like you
who met a long-time friend
after meeting Qiu Ke?
My gosh, my gosh!
Guru is really chatting with me!
I need to ask more questions
to get the conversation going.
Yes.
That girl is super adorable,
and she's reunited with
a long-time friend.
She loves ballet too.
Well,
I might bring you lots of inspiration.
Do you mind
if I share more of my life
with you from now on?
Calling yourself "that girl".
Narcissistic.
Sure.
You may do so.
[Woohoo!]
Go on.
What did you say when
he asked you whether
that adorable girl met
an old friend like Qiu Ke?
I said that I didn't meet
some guy named Qiu Ke
but I did meet an old friend.
I also told him
I have a friend who goes
to dance class with me.
It's the person that I met
when I was little
and got reacquainted again.
Although there were misunderstandings
when we first met,
when we went through
some hardships together,
things became good gradually.
You're talking about Lin Nan Yi, huh?
Then, why are you being
difficult with him these days?
It's he who can't bear the sight of
Senior and I getting on well.
Well, who wouldn't want to
get on well with Senior?
I was inspired by you yesterday,
I also wanted to see the blue tears
with the guy I adore.
I know it might not happen.
But, if it does,
that's a miracle from the Heavens.
So,
I've also contacted Senior Xu Ao.
Did Xu Ao agree to it?
He hasn't replied.
[Sorry.]
[I need to make up
for the missed classes at night.]
What is it?
The day's wait was in vain. I'm rejected.
Forget it.
Senior's going to be in twelfth grade
the next semester.
He must be busy studying.
Then, he's got practise too,
then, tuition.
He won't have time
for these imaginary things.
It's just normal.
I envy you.
Besides getting Prince Charming
to initiate contact with you,
you also get to go to the beach
with Senior Wei Ze.
Just look at me.
But, don't worry,
I've greeted the Emperor of the Sea.
Blue tears will appear.
Just enjoy your night.
As for me,
I'll go out and get some air.
Tong Xi.
Who is Senior Wei Ze to you?
When I bumped into Senior yesterday,
he told me that
when you were in Da Cheng,
you enrolled into the art club.
He was the interviewer.
In that case, the both of you
are really fated to meet.
Yeah?
Tong Xi, I really think
you and Senior Wei Ze are a perfect match.
You're the White Swan,
he's the prince.
It would be a fairy tale-come-true
if the both of you get together.
I sincerely wish you all the best.
I hope you do your best.
Thank you.
Go! Tong Xi!
Hold it.
All dressed up. Where are you going?
I have some matters to sort out.
What matters can a student have?
Going out when you're done with homework?
Don't forget you need to practise ballet.
Mum, can't I practise when I'm back?
I've...
No!
I'm meeting someone.
Who?
It's...
Keep mum and
you're not stepping out this door.
Dad.
I'm meeting Dad.
Since I don't have much homework,
I'm going to see Dad.
Seriously!
You dad's good for nothing
except delaying your time.
I raised you with my own hands
and you're cozying up to your dad.
I'm off, then.
Come back early!
Let me help you.
Thanks.
You slept through English class today.
I'm sure you didn't get much in, huh?
Today's lesson is extremely important.
It's the past participle tense of verbs.
Let me help you revise later.
It's okay.
Then, read through this.
I know you might find me annoying.
This is my notes,
it's complete.
Oh no,
did Senior loathe me being late
and left?
Hello, Senior?
Sorry, I left home late.
[Tong Xi, I'm sorry.
There's a change of plan.]
[I left for the bus stop.]