[English subtitles are available]
Do you think I should
ask Sun Jie Ping out for a meal?
Go ahead and ask her out.
You're a grown man,
you're shilly-shallying on
whether you should ask a girl out.
I can't stand you.
But I've thought about it.
It's so hard.
[You see,]
[how should I invite her?]
After I invite her,
what should we eat?
[What should I say when we are eating?]
What should we do after we eat?
I'm vexed.
[Turn on your messaging app.]
Type this down.
Can I take you out for dinner?
Then, click send.
I will
send it now?
Send it.
[I'm really going to send it.]
Hurry up.
I sent it.
Bye.
Seriously, Tao Zhu, you're so...
[Sure.]
[See you in the square this afternoon.]
This is something.
[Blue Elephant]
After your talk with Nan Yi,
have you figured out what you want to do?
No.
Sister Mi Ya,
what about you?
Is there anything in particular
you want to do?
Yes.
I want to marry Andre.
That counts as something you want to do?
How does that not count?
It's what I want more than anything now.
Look at this pillow cover.
[I'd Wait For Life]
I sewed it for him.
He is coming to see me soon.
I want him to sleep
comfortably and peacefully.
Sister Mi Ya,
so how do you determine
that's what you want to do?
For something you want to do,
it must bring you joy,
give you a sense of accomplishment,
but also full of challenges.
Just like Andre and I.
We have to cross a thousand miles
to be together,
it has been hard.
However,
it's full of expectations as well.
Because I can see myself
being happy and joyful
in every second I spend with him.
Sometimes,
the thing you want to do
could be overlooked because of
some unpleasant experiences.
For example, I would have
certain emotion towards Andre
because I can't see him all the time.
So maybe
you should try look at it another way.
Is there anything that you
love and hate at the same time?
Such as
ballet?
Or
Lin Nan Yi?
Maybe
you have ill-fated
relationships with them.
I do love and hate
these two things at the same time.
[Summer Again]
[Summer Again.
Episode 21: Follow Your Heart]
[Adapted from Huo He's comic, "Mint Love"]
Relax.
We're doing pre-recording today.
If there is any part you feel
that you could do better later,
you can tell me,
we can always record it again.
Thank you.
So, shall we start?
Three, two, one, go.
Dear viewers,
welcome to today's Lindong Icon Interview.
Today on the show
we have the new and emerging
comic artist Qing He.
Come on, Qing He, say hi to everyone.
Hi, everyone. I'm Qing He.
Qing He here is really adorable.
Before our interview today,
I did some homework.
I went through
your two comics very seriously.
Early Summer and Mint.
I think they are
two outstanding comic works.
And I really want to know
what set you
on the path of comic drawing?
Actually, I don't consider
myself a comic artist.
Because this path is
something I didn't plan on.
When I started drawing comic,
I just wanted to kill some time.
So, I drew
some random four-panel comic
and posted them online.
I just wanted to share it with
other comic lovers.
Everyone knows you as Guru Qing He.
I believe you too,
have your own perspective on comic.
I...
I hope that through my comic,
I can express
some longing for the world, for emotions.
Take Early Summer for example,
its story is about a little boy
and his mother's
everyday life together.
What many netizens see in the comic
is the mother's concern for her son.
But what I also want to express
is the son's reliance
and care for his mother.
We can see that Qing He
is a very sentimental person.
Every comic artist has a...
Wang Yi Ming.
[What do I do? What do I do?]
[She's here.]
Tong Xi, pass me the rag.
I need to wipe Table 3.
Tong Xi, Tao Zi,
thank you for your help.
You guys are on a school break,
you still came to help me out at my shop.
It's fine, Sister Mi Ya.
Well, Nan Yi isn't around,
you're short-handed.
This is what we should do.
Thank you.
It's a beautiful day today.
Yes, it is.
So, let's go and grab something to eat.
Sure, what should we get?
What do you want to eat?
I'm fine with anything, you decide.
[I know this test.]
[When a girl says she's fine with
anything, she doesn't really mean it.]
[If I pick something
she doesn't like to eat,]
[she'll be mad at me.]
No way.
You decide.
You have to decide.
Oh, I need to use the restroom.
Can we decide
after I come back?
Sure, go on.
Wang Yi Ming likes grilled seafood
and fried stinky tofu.
[But eating fried stinky tofu
during our first date,]
[that's not very romantic,
don't you think?]
Then just pick something you like to eat.
He's omnivorous.
He isn't picky on food.
[I see.]
[I got it.]
[Thank you, Tao Zi.]
Hold on, hold on, Jie Ping,
you mustn't let him eat dairy food.
Otherwise,
he'll definitely have diarrhoea
within three minutes.
Hello?
Tao Zi,
is the new beverage in Blue Elephant
hundred-year-old vinegar?
Someone's getting really jealous.
Don't be absurd.
He's always around bugging me,
I'm getting sick of him.
Now that someone is finally
going to take him away,
I'm really happy about it.
There's no way I would get jealous.
You may not want to admit it,
but perhaps during these long years,
you have long developed
unique feelings for Wang Yi Ming.
So, you flipped.
I flipped?
That's impossible.
I'm not, I won't allow it.
I'm going back to work.
I know you like grilled seafood
and stinky tofu.
You...
You know about that?
But I still think
this is our first date.
I wanted to do it properly,
so I chose this restaurant.
What do you think of it?
It's nice, really nice.
I'm fine with anything.
As long as you like it.
Thanks.
This is smooth and bouncy.
What is it made of, Tao Zi?
Sorry, I... I mean...
It's fine.
Try this.
This is my favourite dessert.
It's good.
Good, right?
This is made with full cream milk.
It can be considered the
most authentic one in town.
I really love it.
What is it made of?
Milk.
Where is their restroom?
Thank you for your hard work today.
You were great.
Thank you.
I'll keep it up.
Look forward to seeing you again.
Nan Yi.
Wait.
Let go.
Nan Yi, can we talk?
Give me some time.
Let's have a talk, please?
I've read these two comics.
I didn't know
you were so good and so talented
at drawing.
You even had a book signing in Da Cheng.
I only found out about it lately.
Is this all you wanted to talk about?
No, no.
I just want to tell you that
I showed these two comics
to the teachers at Academy of
Fine Arts Affiliated High School.
They thought you're very talented.
If you want,
I can transfer you to the Academy
of Fine Arts Affiliated High School.
This way, if you want to
attend the Academy of Fine Arts
or study abroad,
I'll be able to help you.
No need.
Thank you.
Nan Yi.
I've been plagued by
guilt all these years.
Although
it's true that I had
some difficulties back then,
no matter what,
I shouldn't have given you away
when you were so little.
I really wanted to make it up
to you over the past years.
I don't need you to make up for it.
I just want to live my life well now.
It's getting late.
I should go back to Xi Hai now.
You should go home too.
Goodbye.
Nan Yi.
Tao Zi, are you all right?
I'm fine.
I dropped it by accident.
Don't use your hand.
Leave it, I'll clean it up.
Wait here.
Tong Xi, you're so attentive.
I wish I can be as attentive as you.
Tao Zi, during Xu Ao's birthday last time,
after he turned down
the fried squid you offered him,
you said the same thing to me
in the same place.
What's the matter?
Did you say this again because
you had the same feeling like last time?
What do you mean by that?
Tao Zi, although you refused to admit it,
Wang Yi Ming and Sun Jie Ping
were having a date
actually bothered you a lot, didn't it?
I...
All right.
You don't have to tell me, I know.
I just want to tell you that
you don't have to make it
difficult for yourself.
You're obviously upset,
yet you still gave Wang Yi Ming
and Sun Jie Ping advice
to teach them how to befriend each other.
It's getting late.
[Calling. Wang Yi Ming]
Go home first.
I'll take care of the rest.
What happened to you?
What took you so long?
I've been calling you.
Why can't I get through?
The moment I turned on my phone,
I received a call from Sun Jie Ping
crying to me that
you seemed unhappy.
I was going to confront you about it.
How did you get
yourself into this situation?
It's a long story.
My dad is away on business
while my mum is working overtime.
No one can take care of me.
When I used the toilet just now,
I got no one to help me.
My one hand was injected with drip,
while I held my pants with the other one,
I almost...
Do me a favour.
Buy me some food.
My colon is cleaner than face now.
You should've asked Sun Jie Ping
to be with you now.
How can I find a girl
for this kind of thing?
I kind of figured out now.
You are the most important person to me.
You are mankind's best friend.
Really.
I called her
by your name several times today,
it was really awkward.
Only you could do such a thing
like calling the wrong name.
Seriously, man, you're...
Forget it.
You want small steamed bun or stinky tofu?
Small steamed bun.
And stinky tofu.
Wait here.
By the way, why are you wearing shorts?
Don't ask.
Just go.
Wait for me.
You've been feeling unwell
since you got up this morning,
I didn't even notice it.
It's fine.
I've been a bit stressed about work.
It's recurring ailment.
It's holiday,
why are you stressed out at work again?
The National Day Golden Week
is coming soon.
The company has invited
the provincial ballet company
to perform here.
I need to arrange for
the rehearsals and interview.
Speaking of which,
tomorrow I have to take
some video or photos for them.
I've been so busy every day,
I don't even have time to rest.
The provincial ballet company?
Mum, why don't you bring me with you?
I can take photos for you.
No, no.
I've been dancing ballet
for many years too.
Besides,
I'm much better than you when it
comes to using the phone camera.
Leave it to me.
We're using this.
I know how to use this too.
I made it home safely.
[Lin Nan Yi. Voice message]
[I have to go to my mother's company
tomorrow to help her take pictures.]
Hang in there.
[Nan Yi,]
it's true that I had
some difficulties back then.
No matter what,
I shouldn't have given you away
when you were so little.
I really wanted to make it up
to you over the past years.
You want to see me so early,
how can I help you?
I just contacted Tong Xi.
She said she was still in class,
so I can only come to you.
What's the matter with you?
You seem really tired.
I couldn't sleep.
Why do you want to see me?
I received this this morning.
I wanted to give this
to you as soon as I can.
[Thank you, Brother Qing He.
Thank you, Sister Tong Xi.]
This...
This is drawn by Xiao Bei?
He asked me to give it to you and Tong Xi.
Help me give it to her.
How is Xiao Bei recovering?
I heard that he's recovering well.
Xiao Bei's mum
asked me to apologize
to you on her behalf.
She's really glad that
Xiao Bei is getting better.
She only wrote that article
because she was grateful for you.
She didn't expect
it would bring you trouble.
It's fine.
Tell her
not to worry about it.
Thank you again.
Xiao Bei is really happy.
So that's all. I still have class.
See you.
Five, six, seven, eight.
[Xi Hai Theatre]
One, two, three, four.
Five, six, seven, eight.
Steady.
Three, two, three, four.
Five, six, seven, eight.
Mr. Xu.
I'm here today to help my mum
record some videos.
I'll need your help on this.
No problem.
How do you want us to help you?
How?
I just want to record something
that is not on stage,
that is more natural and relaxed,
like off-stage.
I don't know how I should explain it.
I got what you meant.
How about this?
I'll put on some music,
let's improvise the dance.
Sure.
Let's shoot this first.
Okay.
Ready.
Music.
Your arm.
Slower, slower.
Stretch it out, extend it.
[Since I was little,]
[every time I danced,
it's because my mum asked me to.]
[Ballet is her dream,]
[but it isn't mine.]
What about your dream?
I don't know yet.
[You must be tired, Mum.]
[Boost your blood sugar.]
This child.
Junior, is there something wrong?
Don't worry, Senior.
The shooting went well.
We've got everything we need.
So, I let Tong Xi go home first.
That's good.
It's getting late.
You should go back too.
That can wait.
Senior, take a look at this first.
What?
Tong Xi really surprised me.
When she danced with heart,
she looked a lot like you back then,
it was captivating.
[I thought video shooting
would be very tiring,]
I didn't expect I would feel so happy.
I haven't been this happy in a long time.
Are you really that happy?
Of course.
Happiness like this,
for someone like you
who has been sleeping at home all day
wouldn't understand.
Let me show you this.
Maybe it can make you happier.
Xiao Bei drew this?
For you?
For us.
There's a letter too.
Brother Qing He, Sister Tong Xi,
hello.
Thank you for visiting me.
I've gotten a lot better now.
I was very afraid of surgery before,
but after I found you guys,
I'm not so afraid anymore.
I want to get well soon.
Because when I get well,
I can do many things.
I want to learn drawing
with Brother Qing He.
I want to watch Sister Tong Xi
dance ballet.
Mummy said
you both gave me courage.
That's what I thought too.
I drew this for you.
I'll do my best.
Xiao Bei.
Really?
You're touched by this?
I have another big move.
Maybe after watching it,
you will be more surprised.
[What I'm about to say next,]
[it's for my best friend.]
[You once asked me]
[why I like drawing.]
[Because drawing brings me passion]
[and makes me happy.]
[I've thought about it many times too.]
[What drawing can bring me?]
[I figured out later that]
[passion itself]
[is the greatest meaning.]
[I know you're been trying hard]
[to find your dream.]
[Even if something really did]
[bring you passion,]
[don't be afraid of it,]
[don't resist it.]
[Even if after you try it,]
[you realize that it's not right
for you, you want to give up,]
[that's okay too.]
[Because growing up]
[is a process of trial and error.]
[We will ponder about it]
[and we will do our best for it.]
[I'll be with you.]
[I'll always be with you]
[until you find]
[the passion that belongs to you.]
Lin Nan Yi, why are you so nice?
Tong Tong, you...
Mum.
I looked at those
photos and videos you shot.
They were great.
Also, you danced well.
It was really nice.
You were as good as how I was back then.
Mum.
What's wrong?
I didn't criticize you.
All right, that's all I wanted to say.
Rest early.
I'm going to organize these videos.
Mum.
Can I continue to study ballet
with Mr. Xu?
Yes.
Absolutely!
[Nan Yi, no matter what,]
[I hope you will consider my suggestion.]
Let's be friends.