[A River Runs Through It]
[Episode 30: Even if it's fake, I'm willing Part Ⅱ]
Actually, when Datu doesn't talk,
he's quite gentle.
If you like looking at me that much,
you can do so openly.
Who is watching you?
My girlfriend.
Can you also be shy?
It's none of your business.
Lu Shiyi, I have a letter for you.
Four p.m. tomorrow afternoon,
[To: Lu Shiyi]
I'll await for your reply at the university gate.
I'm going then.
Wait a minute.
I'm sorry.
I have a girlfriend.
I'm sorry. I will get going.
Bye.
No, I'm not...
Looks like this method works the best.
If anyone confesses to me in the future,
I can just use you as my excuse.
You are trying to have everyone know about us.
Yes, I want everyone to know.
I want everyone to know that you have a boyfriend,
so that those handsome guys from your faculty and campus
will voluntarily keep away from you.
- Rascal!
- Keep studying.
Where are you going?
- Shiyi, let's play CS.
- No, I'm busy.
I'm helping research sources
for Xia Xiaoju's thesis defense.
You play first.
Acting like a hipster, being all different?
Seriously?
[Not Just Surviving, but Thriving: Perceived Strengths of Successful US-based Travel Agencies...]
Is this post about you and Xia Xiaoju?
What post?
I forwarded it to you.
[Jiang Zhou University Forum]
[OP: So embarrassing! I actually confessed to the Medical Department's Prince Charming in front of his girlfriend?]
The post is quite popular. It got a lot of likes in a short amount of time.
[Is it Senior Brother Lu Shiyi?]
[OP Reply: TT (Crying face)]
Within half a day, your relationship with Xia Xiaoju
will be known by the whole campus.
- Xiaoling, I'm back.
- You're back?
Xiaoju, congratulations.
Congratulations on finding love as an "elderly couple"
on campus before graduation.
Didn't you say a few days ago
you'd absolutely not date in college?
Why have you started dating Lu Shiyi then?
There must have been a large turnaround in between.
Hurry and tell me!
I'll write it in my novel.
How do you know... I'm with Lu Shiyi?
It's all over our campus forum.
I want everyone to know.
Datu must have said something.
Hurry and let me see!
Why is the network down again?
[Internet Explorer is unable to connect.]
Refresh the site. Refresh it.
Let me try... It's lagging.
Try again. Refresh.
- What? Do you miss me?
- Did you make that post online?
[Cheng Lang]
Wait a second. I've to answer the phone.
Hello, Cheng Lang.
I came to your dorm to ask you about the post online.
Can you help me—
Lu Shiyi, do you know how annoying you are?
Can you respect what I want?
What did I do?
Why did you post online that we are dating?
- Let me explain...
- Listen,
even if you tell everyone that we're together
it's still fake.
It will always be fake. It is impossible for me to like you.
Just give up!
Say that again.
I said, it will always be fake!
It's impossible for me to like you!
[Building 25, Girls' Dormitory]
- Sisters, come look!
- What is it?
Things.
Who sent these to you?
Secret. Just eat.
Come on, Huang Chan.
- Thanks.
- Xiaoju, hurry and come eat!
I won't eat.
Come on, have some chocolate.
Here!
No, I won't.
What's wrong? Don't you like chocolate?
No wonder. Shiyi bought so many snacks for you.
Of course, you won't like my chocolate.
Don't ever mention Lu Shiyi to me again!
Shiyi, why isn't your headstrong girlfriend here today?
Shut up!
- Let's continue.
- Go on.
I won't let go of you this time.
[Jiangzhou University]
[Xu Menglu]
Hello, Xu Menglu.
Huang Jun, I have an opportunity for a band performance. Do you want to do it?
No, I've no interest.
[Xu Menglu]
[Lu Shiyi: Shared a tourism article. Fighting!]
I don't think Shiyi would do something like that.
You shouldn't have fought with him before even seeing the post.
I personally heard him talking with Cheng Lang about the post.
What did he say?
He...
See? You can't even say anything.
Why are you so impulsive whenever Shiyi is mentioned?
You don't know how annoying he is.
Why can't I find the post?
What post?
[Lu Shiyi: I don't have a girlfriend.]
What's wrong?
What exactly is going on between the two of you?
That's good. He's helping me clear things up.
The two of you really—
I'm going to wash up then sleep.
I contacted the girl who made the post.
She agreed to delete the post.
I just deleted the post.
You don't need to tell me.
Go and tell Xia Xiaoju directly.
Did you fight with Xiaoju again?
I told you not to bully her, but to be tolerant.
No matter what, she's a girl.
I bully her?
You don't know how she wronged me.
She didn't know anything, but she came over here to blame me.
I'm a bad guy in her heart.
She just misunderstood. It's not a big deal. Go and explain it to her.
No, I refuse.
Lu Shiyi, are you a man or not?
Be more broad minded, all right?
You two just got together.
Are you going to break up over this matter?
Shiyi, didn't you say you like Xiaoju very much?
Can't you apologize to her first?
Forget it. I'll help you explain it to her.
That post said nothing.
I don't know why you two are reacting so strongly.
No, I'll go explain it to her myself.
By the way,
help me delete the post I made yesterday.
What did you post this time?
Listen, even if you tell everyone that we're together it's still fake.
It will always be fake.
It is impossible for me to like you. Just give up!
Say that again.
Did I go too far?
What?
Come with me.
What are you doing?
What are you doing? I still have to study.
The post online was posted by the girl who gave me the love letter in the library.
I knew you'd be angry on seeing it,
so I asked Cheng Lang to help delete the post for me.
Let me summarize the key points for you now.
First, I wasn't the one who made the post.
Second, I didn't intend to let everyone know
we are a pretend couple, so you would be put in a hard place.
Third, I didn't disrespect your thoughts.
I just want to give both of us a chance,
but if you refuse to accept...
Okay.
I'll give up.
Sorry.
I'm sorry. I wronged you.
I'm sorry. I did wrong you.
Don't...
♫ Warm just like a sunny day ♫
♫ I greatly want to let time stop ♫
I'm not as good as Cheng Lang,
♫ I discover only at this moment ♫
but I'm also not that bad.
♫ Those two worlds are walking farther away ♫
♫ The only thing left is my longing ♫
♫ Who also once yearned to exchange using the souls? ♫
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have been so impulsive.
♫ Carrying the bags to wander about in the opposite direction ♫
What's the use in saying sorry to me?
I was so angry that I couldn't sleep last night.
How are you going to make it up for me?
What do you want?
I'm afraid what I say you won't agree to.
As long as you don't make an outrageous request, I'll agree.
Really?
Really!
♫ I go off wandering with a facade of happiness ♫
Go on a date with me.
♫ The snow outside the window accompanies my thoughts ♫
I fell into your trap again.
Xia Xiaoju, don't go back on your word!
Class is finally over!
Bye bye!
Look at how happy you are!
What shall we eat for lunch today?
[Datu]
Is Shiyi reminding you again about the date?
He reminds me over 800 times a day.
I think Shiyi is quite a nice person.
Maybe after several dates,
you'll find something different about him.
It's so embarrassing for me to go on a date with him. I'm thinking...
Don't worry. You definitely won't be embarrassed on our date.
Have you been following us all this way?
I told you many times
not to think this poorly of me.
Do I really look like a pervert?
Look, it's currently 12:00 p.m.
Who isn't going to eat at the canteen? Right?
I just happened to run into you two as I was headed to the canteen,
but since we happened to meet,
I'll treat you two to lunch.
Let's go.
- Let's go.
- No, I'm not going.
Let's go.
Taotao, you...
Taotao, why didn't you tell me you were going out to eat?
He just told me he was waiting for me online,
so I've to head back to the dorms.
No wonder you seem strange recently.
You often send messages secretly and giggle alone.
Say it! Who is that guy?
When will you introduce him to us?
It's a secret!
I'm leaving. Enjoy your lunch, bye bye!
Don't stand here.
Let's go eat.
Let's go.
- Let's eat quickly and go.
- Okay.
Shiyi, Xiaoju, here!
Let's go.
Here, Lin You, eat some more.
I can't eat any more. I've gained a lot of weight.
Fat? Who said so? You aren't fat at all.
You're too skinny. Eat some more.
Really?
All right.
Xiaoju, you aren't fat as well.
Eat some more.
Take a bite.
Eat it.
Good girl.
By the way, Xiaoju, when are you planning to have our date?
I know. Can't you stop pushing me about it?
Where are you guys going on a date?
I haven't decided yet.
We haven't been on a date for a long time either.
Do you want to go? I'm free tonight.
- Where do you want to go?
- What about the night fair?
I heard it has been quite lively down there the past few days.
Okay.
Xiaoju, want to go together?
I am planning to go with Xiaoju ourselves.
No problem.
Let's go together.
What? I didn't agree.
I promised to go on a date with you,
but I didn't promise to go on a date with you alone.
- You!
- Are you going?
Forget it.
Go. Why not? Let's go!
Darling, take a bite.
Good boy.
Xiaoju, the night fair was so much fun.
Let's go together next time.
Okay.
Lin You, do you think because I don't take pictures often,
I look a bit silly in some of these pictures?
Not at all, I think you're quite cute.
Really? You are quite cute.
What are you doing?
If you don't go with me,
you'll interrupt Cheng Lang and Lin You.
Let's not be the third wheel.
Let's go.
Why must you...
Choose a picture.
This one.
You have to take good care of it.
If any girl confesses to you in the future,
just show this photo to them.
I will definitely take good care of it.
I didn't expect you would like that.
No, I don't.
Who asked you to buy it for me?
So why did you stare at it for so long?
It's pretty cute.
Do you like it?
If you like it, I'll give it to you.
Just pick one, only one.
Okay, this way.
Shiyi, thank you.
Actually, I don't really like...
- I...
- If a girl says she doesn't like something, it means she likes it.
Can't you be honest with me?
Besides,
isn't it natural to give my girlfriend gifts on a date?
Can't you stop mentioning the word "girlfriend?"
Besides, we're not a real couple.
You can say it louder.
Xiaoju, walk a bit faster.
We're coming. Let's go!
[Building 25, Girls' Dormitory]
Xiaoju, did Shiyi buy that for you?
What's wrong?
Why are you not happy after going out to have fun?
Did you fight with him again?
Do you remember the nickname I made for Cheng Lang in the past?
Cheng Lang...
Does Cheng Lang like this?
Silly dog.
It's Da Bai, not a silly dog.
I remember. It's Da Bai. It looks exactly like that.
What's wrong?
I feel it was such a long time ago.
Yes, it really was a long time ago.
But people have to look forward.
No one has to be with someone.
Xiaoju, you're the same.
You have to try accepting other people.
- I think Shiyi...
- I know I should try accepting other people.
I can for anyone, but not Datu.
Why not?
He is my best friend.
When he bought this dog for me today,
as I held it in my arms,
I didn't know what I was doing.
You feel guilty.
Do you feel uncomfortable?
I feel guilt towards all three of them.
They're all my best friends,
but I took advantage of Datu
to deceive Cheng Lang and Lin You.
I...
Anyway, I can't continue pretending to be a couple with Datu.
Do you think I'll act out a breakup with you
in front of Lin You?
Just help with this one time. Okay?
No.
I'm begging you.
I feel like I'm a liar recently.
And I'm lying to my best friends.
I really can't continue acting anymore.
Let's make it real then.
Then you won't feel like you're lying to them.
Lu Shiyi, I'm seriously discussing this with you.
I'm serious, too.
Suit yourself!
Anyway, I am going to explain it to Lin You.
Okay, I'll go with you to tell Lin You
CL is Cheng Lang.
Okay! I'll go now!
Go on. Why did you stop?
The computer room is right there.
You rascal!
Go ahead and yell at me. I'm a rascal in this aspect.
Why are you leaving?
Don't walk so quickly!
I still have something to say to you.
What do you think of my performance on the date yesterday?
Just so-so.
Not romantic at all, but very annoying.
So what kind of romance do you want?
Other couples go to the cinema for dates,
but we, as a couple, have not.
Why don't you go to the cinema with me today?
Do you really think I would go with you?
Yes.
In your dreams!
If you don't want to go today, we can go tomorrow.
From now on, I'll buy two movie tickets every day.
There will be a day you would want to watch a movie with me.
Do you havea lot of money to spend?
Not at all.
I can't even pay for my meal.
I'm starving.
But it's okay.
My priority is to make my girlfriend happy.
Okay. Watching a movie, right?
I'll go. I want to watch the scariest movie at midnight.
No problem.
You were the one to say it. Remember what you said.
I'll buy the movie tickets later.
[Xi Nan Theatre]
[Playing Today: Texas Chainsaw Massacre]
Why are the movies all so bloody?
Excuse me, is this the only movie playing at midnight tonight?
Yes, only this one.
Thank you.
Two tickets, please.
By the way, I also want a couple package.
Okay, please wait a second.
Xiaoling, can I borrow this book to read?
You have good taste!
That one is really good.
Gui Xiaoling, in the four years of college,
you have read volumes of books.
I'm flattered.
I just have a fulfilling spiritual world.
Save it.
Aren't you going to watch a movie at midnight with Shiyi?
Why are you still here?
Let him watch it alone.
I won't go anyway.
Has Lu Shiyi's hemophobia been cured?
This week's midnight films
are all super scary and bloody.
Will he have a relapse?
Are this week's films very bloody?
Super bloody!
I just went to see it with my fellow-townsman.
He was so scared he vomited.
I'm going out.
Where are you going?
[Xi Nan Theatre]
Miss, please wait!
Where's your ticket?
Hello, I'm looking for someone.
Who are you looking for?
My... My boyfriend.
He's over 180 cm tall, with a centre parting,
wears blue-and-white sportswear, and looks...
quite handsome.
Sorry, I haven't seen such a man.
Please let me in to find him.
Sorry, I can't help you. Please get out.
- Please go out, Miss.
- Don't.
If you don't let me in, I'll cry.
Xia Xiaoju!
Datu, you!
Why aren't you late today?
The tickets I bought start in five minutes.
Luckily, you didn't go in.
Listen, let's not watch this.
- Let's go.
- No., no, no.
Wait, why must we leave?
- But...
- My hemophobia is cured.
Let's go, the film is about to start.
[Projection Hall]
- Let's not watch it! Let's go.
- Listen,
we got the whole theater booked.
There are only the two of us.
I've bought popcorn and coke.
[Projection Hall]
- What's up?
- I'm just worried about you.
Do you have any problems watching such a film?
It's all right.
Datu, why don't we stop watching?
What if you have a relapse from watching it?
I won't know what to do then.
I should be fine.
Are you sure?
Look, I'm fine.
Hurry and watch.
My god, Datu.
Are you sure you're okay?
Datu?
Datu!
I said we shouldn't have come to watch this.
Oh gosh! He's too heavy.
- Datu.
- Xia Xiaoju!
Were you scared?
I was so worried about you. How could you pretend to faint and lie to me?
You care a lot about me.
You're my brother.
Of course, I care about you.
If someone has hemophobia,
anyone else would care about it as well.
Are you still laughing? I was worried about you over nothing.
I know I was wrong.
I'm sorry. I swear I'll never make jokes about this again.
We're already here. Let's at least finish the movie.
Sit.
I'm sorry.
Let me apologize to you.
- It's all mine.
- All yours.
This is yours, too.
I won't eat or drink. How about that?
- Keep holding it then.
- Okay, no problem.
It tastes really good.
I know it's wrong to force you,
but I really can't
let you go now.
It's almost time for lunch.
Let's eat together.
I still have another tour group this afternoon.
I won't go eat. I have to get going.
That won't do. How can you not eat anything?
You've already missed several meals before.
Be careful that you'll have a stomachache.
- Don't worry. I'm quite healthy.
- No way.
Xia Xiaoju! Xiaoju!
Here you are.
Your favorite soy-braised pork and ribs.
So considerate!
Take it.
You got food for Xiaoju?
Every time she goes with a tour group, she never has time to eat.
I had no other way, but to pack food for her.
After all I'm her boyfriend.
Brother, well done!
I've something to do within my faculty.
I have to go.
I'll pick you up when you're off work tonight.
Don't you have a class?
How do you have the time to pick me up?
How could I forget?
I'll take a taxi back. You don't need to pick me up.
All right. When you return, take care of yourself.
Remember to eat.
Call me when you're free.
- I'll get going then. Bye bye.
- Bye.
Who would believe you two are a pretend couple?
What's wrong?
Shiyi tends to be a casual guy,
but he specifically packed food for you
and look after you carefully
while you normally are so careless
that you forget your own classes,
but you remember the Medical Faculty's timetable.
I don't believe the two of you don't like each other.
It's because he always forces me to go to his class with him.
Don't try to explain.
Explaining means you are hiding something.
Why don't you two just become a real couple?
How can we be a real couple? We're friends.
Really?
Why do I think Shiyi treats this seriously and has fallen quite deeply?
Aren't you the same?
You don't just take Shiyi as a friend, do you?
Let's go. Why are you talking so much?
[Jiangzhou University]
Thank you, Sir.
Why are you back so late?
Why are you here? Don't you have a class?
It was canceled. Our professor had something come up last minute, so it was moved to the day after tomorrow.
You didn't answer my calls,
so I could wait for you here.
You must be exhausted.
Here, let me treat you to some midnight snacks.
And then we'll head back to the dorms so you can get some rest.
What do you want to eat?
What's wrong?
Datu, let's...
end it here.
What are you doing?
You want me to act out a breakup with you again?
Xia Xiaoju, you know how frequently you ask me to break up?
If you keep doing this, I'll tell Lin You.
Just go tell her CL is Cheng Lang.
I'm not afraid.
I said that just to frighten you
or else I can't find any better reason
for you to continue to be with me.
What happened today?
Wasn't everything good just a few days ago?
Why do you suddenly feel we can't go on like this?
I don't want to keep using you.
Are you worried I'll fall too deeply
and then get hurt?
I'm not afraid. What are you afraid of?
Are you afraid you'll like me?
♫ There you are, running wildly through the highlands ♫
♫ Another you is sighing silently ♫
♫ No one is able to understand you ♫
♫ Happiness is not transparent and pain is not thorough ♫
♫ I'm glad you're not willing to give up like this ♫
♫ It hurts to see the stubbornness in your eyes ♫
♫ I'm a bit tired and need to rest ♫
♫ The marks we leave in life ♫
♫ How I wish to travel everywhere with you ♫
♫ To find the meaning of my existence along the way ♫
♫ The hard journey of life lets the soul recuperate ♫
♫ Be brave and find yourself ♫
♫ The red, green, and black colors of the forest ♫
♫ The purity, joy, and freedom of oneself ♫
♫ I wish for you to see clearly ♫
♫ The true you within all the dust ♫