[A River Runs Through It]
[Episode 19: I like you, but I don't know how to bring it up, part 1]
Xia Xiaoju, who did you like in the past?
You...
Why are you suddenly asking me this?
Do you still like him?
Things will eventually pass.
We... should be looking forward, right?
Don't mention it anymore.
Okay, no problem.
Here, catch it, okay?
It's okay. Keep it up!
Watch me.
Okay, you try it.
Like this.
Look! I'm better than you!
Take a look. How is it?
Not bad, right?
Speakers and drums.
Who bought them?
Thanks to me, our school bought them specially for our Ultimate Band.
Not bad!
This place... is where our Ultimate Band's dream begins.
Let's do it!
Your paycheck this month.
Manager, it's not correct.
You've just advanced my paycheck.
Me and my bad memories! I gave you the wrong amount.
It's for Lu Shiyi. I gave you the wrong amount.
What? For Lu Shiyi?
Me and my big mouth.
That Lu Shiyi asked me many times not to tell you, but I still spilled the beans.
What's the matter?
Why are you being so mysterious?
Do you want to know?
Tell me.
One day, Lu Shiyi came to me and gave me 300 yuan.
Boss, give this 300 yuan to Xia Xiaoju later as her advancement this month.
She really needs this money right now.
Besides, as a girl, it's hard for her to make a living.
What do you mean?
Tell me the truth.
You like her, right?
Just take it first.
Fine, I'll help you.
By the way, remember to return my money when you give her the paycheck at the end of this month.
You mustn't expose it!
Exposing it is a good thing!
I can see that you're a good guy.
How about I tell her on purpose?
If Xia Xiaoju knows you help her a lot in secret,
maybe she'll be touched and promise herself to you!
She won't.
You mustn't tell her. I don't want to give her any burden.
No problem.
You scared me to death!
Why are you here?
I was going to look for you.
What for?
I had an extra 300 yuan for last month's food expenses
Datu, thank you.
Since when did you start becoming grateful? It's not your style.
When... When am I not grateful?
This is more like it. This fierce look is more like you.
You spoiled such a great atmosphere.
I was just thinking of how to thank you.
How about I do not hand in the red envelope money to my mom this year?
How about I buy you the whole set of Jin Yong's novels?
(T/N: One of the most renowned wuxia novelists.)
If you really want to thank me,
then be at my beck and call from now on. How about that?
Instead of the whole set of novels, you're exchanging it for me to become your servant?
You're really good at calculating!
What's wrong with you?
Is there a need to calculate everything so clearly between us?
If that's the case, then when
Auntie told you to bring me nice food before, how do we calculate that?
Fine. Then come home with me this weekend.
I'll have my mom cook you some good food, okay?
Okay.
Okay. Help pass them to me.
- I'll rearrange them up there.
- Okay.
- This one?
- Yes.
Shiyi!
My goodness! Why are you bleeding so much?
I'm fine. I'm fine.
How did you get cut?
What should I do, Shiyi? Are you all right?
Shiyi? Shiyi! Does it hurt, Shiyi?
Wait for me. I'll go get some bandaids.
Wait for me!
Shiyi! Shiyi!
[Outpatient]
[Jiangzhou Hospital]
Don't let the wound touch water.
Come and change the dressing every other day.
Doctor, we don't know why he suddenly fainted.
Does he need to do other examinations?
Did he faint? Does he have low blood sugar?
I don't know.
There are many reasons for suddenly fainting.
I suggest that he get a thorough examination first to find the reason.
Okay, okay. What kind of examination does he need?
I'm not a porcelain doll.
With you being this careful, others might think I have some terminal disease.
Hurry and knock on wood!
Knock on wood! Knock on wood!
What nonsense are you saying?
How could you curse yourself?
I just think you're overreacting.
Actually, I don't have to take a blood test.
Let's go back now. Let's go.
Come back!
Let me tell you. Getting examined can put your heart at ease.
I didn't say I won't get a check up.
Can I go and get a check up alone?
- No.
- You can go back first.
- I won't run away!
- Lu Shiyi?
- Are we going or not?
Xia Xiaoju?
Senior Shen, why are you here?
I'm an intern in the Psychology Department.
What has happened to his hand?
It's nothing.
His arm was scratched by a hook.
Then he fainted just now so the doctor said he should get further examined.
It's nothing. She's just overreacting.
Fainting is a serious matter. You need to get examined!
See? Even Senior Shen said that.
Yes, yes. Everything you said was right, okay?
How about this? Since we bumped into Senior Shen, let her accompany me to take the blood test.
And you hurry back to the convenience store right now.
Otherwise, your boss will really fire you. What will you do then?
Senior Shen is working.
Xiaoju, you can go back to work.
I'm not busy today. I'll take him there.
Don't worry. Senior Shen is here. How can I run away?
I'll definitely be obedient and get examined.
Really?
Yes. Go.
Then... Then I'm leaving first.
Senior, sorry for bothering you.
It's all right.
Wait. Put on the coat. It's too cold outside.
Hurry and put it back on.
- I'm leaving now.
- Okay.
Bye.
Be careful on the way.
- Okay, got it!
- Bye bye.
I can see you care about Xia Xiaoju quite a lot.
You're afraid of her losing her job, but why are you not afraid of bothering me?
Didn't you just say so yourself that you have nothing else to do later?
But it doesn't matter.
I can also do the check up on my own.
If you're busy, go on with your work.
I was just kidding.
As long as it is your business, I'll always have the time.
Come on, let's go.
I've promised Xia Xiaoju to take care of you.
If you don't want me to take care of you,
I'll ask Xia Xiaoju to return right now.
She shouldn't have gone too far.
Slow down.
Shiyi.
Shiyi!
Shiyi, what's wrong?
Shiyi. Shiyi.
Shiyi.
What's wrong with him?
Why did you buy another guitar?
Don't you already have one?
The band doesn't have much money left.
The funds were raised by everyone.
Big Huang, be more frugal
or else there will be nothing left.
I know.
This guitar is too awesome!
The strings are also light. It's especially suitable for girls.
Why did you spend such money?
I can't play the guitar.
It's not for you. It's for Xu Menglu.
How is it?
Is this color beautiful?
Yes.
Doesn't she already have a guitar?
The one she has is an acoustic guitar.
We're a rock band.
Besides, she's the face of our band.
Her appearance is very important.
Xu Menglu! The guitar!
Huang Jun.
Is it beautiful?
You really bought a pink guitar?
Of course!
When do I not keep my promises?
Hurry and give it a try.
I just tuned it.
I love you so much!
How is it? Do you like it?
Don't misunderstand.
It's not that kind of love.
Hurry, hurry! Play that... Play that song!
It's distorted. Just strum it directly.
Huang Jun, I still have classes. I'm leaving first.
♪ I just don't want to lie to myself ♪
♪ No matter how complicated the world is ♪
♪ I'm not afraid of regrets ♪
♪ Embracing the hottest dream ♪
♪ Trying hard to not be afraid of the onlookers ♪
♪ Even if I fall, I'm still good looking ♪
Okay everyone. We'll end today's class here.
What's wrong with you? Are you sick?
No.
Did Huang Jun make you angry?
He bought Xu Menglu a guitar, and it's even a pink one.
Just now, they talked about music.
I felt that I was an outsider.
Especially that Xu Menglu.
She actually said "I love you" to Huang Jun right in front of me.
So you're saying that little lead singer is interested in Huang Jun?
Perhaps you're overthinking it.
No way!
A woman's intuition is very accurate.
There's definitely something wrong with her.
Then how about Huang Jun? Is he interested in that little lead singer?
I don't know.
I'm very confused right now.
How about this? Go and talk it out with Huang Jun.
You need to get him to understand that he already has a girlfriend
so he should keep an appropriate distance from other girls.
It'll be all right.
I'll talk to him.
How about you?
How are you with Cheng Lang?
What else can there be?
Just... continue to be penpals.
You hiding your identity like this,
no matter how touched he is, he won't know it's you.
I just hope he can be happy.
I really lost to you.
Love needs to be fought for by yourself.
Didn't you know?
Oh, by the way.
I still need to go see Datu.
Could you take my bag back to our dorm?
- I'm leaving!
- No, wait!
Where are you going?
What's wrong with Shiyi?
Nothing. I'll tell you later when I come back.
I'm leaving now. Bye bye!
What's the result of the examination this morning?
Nothing is wrong, right?
There's really nothing wrong?
I'm fine. Look at me.
I'm as strong as a bull right now.
This small injury is nothing. It doesn't hurt at all.
It was more painful when you used firecrackers to blow up my bottom last time.
Then the doctor didn't say
- when you scraped your arm...
- It hurts!
- Be gentle!
- Okay, I'll be more gentle.
The doctor didn't say why you fainted when you scraped your arm?
He...
He said I had low blood sugar.
You didn't have breakfast, again?
I'm too lazy to buy it.
Too lazy to buy it?
Do you know how important breakfast is to a person?
And yet you're someone who will become a doctor!
You always make me worried.
These are the bread and biscuits that I bought for you.
Leave them in your dorm.
When you're too lazy to buy food, at least eat a bit.
Once you finish them, just tell me.
I work at the convenience store so the boss will give me a staff discount.
What's wrong with you?
A-Are you feeling dizzy again?
Don't move.
I'm very tired.
Let me hug you for a while.
Just for a while.
Are you too tired these days?
Listen to me.
Don't come to the convenience store to help me during this time.
You have a lot of schoolwork and you're also training with the basketball team.
Your body can't handle it.
Did you hear me?
Got it.
Okay, okay. Our Datu has worked hard during this time.
Older Sis will hug you. Older Sis will hug you.
♪ Are you still sleeping ♪
♪ Treat the relationship seriously ♪
♪ Don't be stubborn like a child ♪
♪ that I can't bear to lie to ♪
♪ A resolution is needed ♪
♪ Standing on both sides of the road ♪
Da Huang, it's time for breakfast.
Just put it there first.
Where did we leave off?
♪ I can see that you have something to say ♪
♪ Your arm is covered in bright red ♪
♪ You hide behind that wall ♪
♪ Compared to the people in oil paintings, the edges of you are more clear ♪
♪ Don't ask for time again ♪
♪ The me in your eyes ♪
♪ Have some flaws ♪
♪ They're no better than the fleeting clouds ♪
♪ Waiting for it all to vanish ♪
♪ You can lie here ♪
♪ And wait for everything to be run over ♪
Adjust it just like this. This is really awesome!
With your support, it'll be hard for our band to not become popular.
You're our band's soul.
You know how to highlight my strengths.
No. You're really too modest.
Huang Jun.
Time for breakfast.
Yes, right.
Like this. Adjust it like we did just now.
It's amazing.
Thanks, Taotao.
Yummy.
You guys continue eating.
I'm leaving.
Why not eat together?
No, thanks.
It's all right. Let's eat together.
Sit down.
Hurry up.
Thank you then.
You're welcome. Here.
Chopsticks.
- I've used them.
- It's okay.
Da Huang.
Did you forget that you promised me yesterday to eat breakfast with me?
I haven't eaten yet either.
But I just bought two sets. I didn't buy any for others.
You can have mine.
We can share one set.
Come on.
Take it.
If you want to eat, then buy your own!
Le Tao!
Mind your words later.
Don't make her angry.
Cheng Lang. Huang Jun.
Over here! Over here!
If you guys fought, then you guys should talk things through.
Having a cold war is bad.
I don't want to talk to him.
Taotao.
Why didn't you tell me you came to the library?
Who are you?
I know
that forgetting to have breakfast with you is my fault.
But you can't pretend you don't know me.
Your words make me feel wronged.
You're the soul of the band.
Leave your sweet words to your little lead singer.
I'm sleepy. I'm going back to the dorm to sleep.
Taotao! Taotao!
Go after her!
If I chase her, I'll just be adding oil to the fire.
(T/N: Make it worse.)
Sit down.
Don't blame me for not warning you.
Taotao is really mad this time.
Not the type where you can just say a few sweet words to make her happy.
Since you have a girlfriend,
why are you still messing with other girls?
Do you know what being faithful is?
How can you say that? Lower your voice!
What do you mean messing around?
You're talking as if I'm a lewd demon.
There's nothing between me and Xu Menglu.
Taotao is just too jealous.
Stop writing. Say something reasonable for me.
All I know is that Le Tao is not the type of girl who makes trouble for no reason.
See?
Don't be ignorant of your blessings.
If she's so angry that she breaks up with you,
let's see who you can cry to.
I... Let me tell you.
You guys better not irritate me.
Taotao loves me.
She won't break up with me.
What's this?
- Shiyi. Here.
- Shiyi.
Lu Shiyi, take a seat.
- Shen Duo?
- Senior Shen?
Take these books and study them.
I think they can help you.
Thank you, Senior Shen.
One important thing.
Will you tell your situation
to your family and friends?
I've never felt dizzy because of blood before.
Why would I have hemophobia?
Hemophobia
in essence is a type of mental illness
which belongs to a kind of phobia.
However, if you keep concealing it,
I mean, if something wrong happens,
I won't know how to tell them.
Later when everyone's not as busy, I'll find a time to tell them.
By the way, there's a specialist in the hospital where I intern at,
but he's been doing academic exchanges abroad these days.
After he returns,
I'll introduce you to him.
The most important thing for you right now
is to relax.
Bear in mind that
being nervous is not good for your illness.
So how is it? Back to the subject.
I have something serious to tell you.
I'll sit over there and tell you.
Okay.
What's going on between them?
When did Shiyi become so close to Senior Shen Duo?
Senior Shen Duo has coveted Lu Shiyi for a long time.
Everybody knows that.
But is Lu Shiyi also interested?
What?
Are you saying that Datu is interested in Senior Shen?
I didn't say that.
What I'm saying is, if they're not interested in each other,
would they have a date privately?
No way.
Right?
If you say that Datu likes Cheng Lang, that I'll believe.
But liking Senior Shen...
What does this have to do with me?
Don't say it too definitively.
Didn't you also say that you've never seen Lu Shiyi
be alone with other girls before, right?
Besides, Senior Shen Duo is the campus belle of the Department of Medicine.
Even if he's stubborn,
he knows how to appreciate beauty.
I heard that the last time Shiyi was sick and went to the hospital, Senior Shen Duo took good care of him and was very gentle.
Really?
I think... it'll be soon.
It'll be soon?
(T/N: For them to become a couple.)
I see.
[Male Dormitory Building No. 29]
What are you doing? Acting so stealthily.
If you're my bro, then do me a favor.
What's the matter?
I quarreled with Le Tao.
She won't forgive me no matter how I coax her.
You... Help me.
You made your girlfriend angry.
What does that have to do with me?
You...
Is this how you treat me as your brother?
To think that I didn't forget to plan for you even when I quarreled with my girlfriend.
What do you mean?
I even tested Xia Xiaoju when we were in the library.
I said that you might like Senior Shen Duo more.
What did you say?
I... I imitated your handwriting
and wrote a letter to Cheng Lang.
I asked him to meet Friday evening at 6:00 p.m.
So when I asked you to help me mail the letter, you actually switched it?
No.
I-I didn't read it.
How could you do that?
Her expression changed right away.
She was most likely jealous.
You're with her every day, but she doesn't notice your merits.
You just need to make her realize
that you actually have many girls around you. She'll definitely become anxious.
It's playing cat and mouse.
You think I don't know how to play cat and mouse?
I'm telling you now, Huang Jun. I'll rip off that lousy mouth of yours one day!
Let's see how you can keep running your mouth!
With you being like this, you won't win her over even if I give you many years.
Shut up! I can see that you're itching for a beating again.
No.
What is this? So bloody!
I already told you I don't want Cheng Lang to know that Mango Pudding is me!
You... You doing this will make the both of us feel awkward when we see each other in the future!
But you have to take that first step to let Cheng Lang know you like him.
I just want to help you.
But not in this way!
I must hurry and get the letter back.
He must have already received the letter.
Xiaoju, don't be angry.
I just want to help you.
You're killing me!
I didn't, Xiaoju.
Xiaoju, just in time. I was looking for you.
- No, no. I'm in a hurry.
- Come on.
I also have something urgent to do with you. Come on.
Xiaoju. Wait!
They need to talk, why are you butting in?
Go away! I don't want to see you.
If you're not going to say anything, I'm going to leave.
I'm in a hurry.
A-Actually, it's nothing serious.
Nothing serious? Then why did you drag me here?
I'm really in a hurry!
Well... In the library,
Shen Duo had something to tell me
so I didn't sit with you. Are you angry?
You really misunderstood me.
I only formed a band with Xu Menglu.
It's just normal socializing between us.
- Normal socializing?
- Yes.
You even bought her a guitar and practiced songs alone together.
You guys were giving each other flirtatious glances. You're telling me this is normal?
What kind of abnormal do you want?
Holding hands, kissing, and hugging?
Okay, fine. I understand.
I'm not angry. I'm not angry, okay?
I'm really in a hurry. I have to go.
Wait. What is so urgent?
How about I help you?
You're just being unreasonable!
I'm being unreasonable? Fine.
Then I won't bother you to stay here being unreasonable with me.
- Please go back.
- You!
This matter... Even if I tell you, I can't explain it clearly.
Anyway, I'm in a hurry.
Go on with your work.
Da Huang, what's wrong with you?
Da Huang! Da Huang, what's wrong with you?
What's wrong? What happened?
Taotao, can you forgive me?
What happened, Taotao?
Da Huang! Da Huang, what happened to you?
- Taotao, what happened?
- Da Huang, don't scare me.
Why did he spit out blood?
Da Huang!
Da Huang, what's wrong?
- Shiyi! Shiyi!
- Shiyi!
- Are you okay, Shiyi?
[Improve medical quality. Improve service attitude. Promote collaboration between the government and the people.]
How can everything be normal?
Doctor, he fainted just now.
And it's not the first time he has fainted for no reason.
Can you please examine him carefully again?
Looking at his examination results,
there's nothing wrong with him.
Doctor, can you please examine him again?
He's awake! He's awake! Shiyi's awake!
- What happened to you? Why did you suddenly spit out blood?
- Shiyi.
Shiyi, are you okay?
- How are you?
- Why did he spit out blood?
He was faking it.
He wanted to feign sickness to get Taotao's forgiveness.
So childish.
I'm okay. Are you okay?
Your friend said
that it's not the first time you've fainted.
Our school has limited resources.
I suggest that you go to a big hospital and get a further check up.
I'm fine. Thank you, Doctor.
I still have things to do. Take good care of him.
- Thank you, Doctor.
- Thank you for your hard work, Doctor.
- Goodbye, Doctor
- Thank you.
Okay. Let's go back to the dorm.
What?
What do you mean by going back to the dorm?
The doctor said to go to a big hospital.
- Let's go.
- I'm fine. Why do I need to go to the hospital?
Are you going to take care of your health or not?
Why don't you want to go to the hospital? Are you hiding something from me?
No. I major in medicine.
If there's something wrong with my health, wouldn't I know it? Right?
If you don't tell me, then I'll become angry.
Fine then.
I'll call your father and let him ask you.
No, don't! I'll tell you.
Say it then.
What's the matter?
I... I have hemophobia.
Hemophobia?
I was never afraid of blood before.
I don't know why I suddenly started to become afraid of blood.
We major in medicine.
If you have hemophobia, how can you become a doctor?
How can you say that?
Isn't just hemophobia?
Shiyi. Don't worry.
Let's cure it, shall we?
Yes, that's right. Together. We'll be with you.
Yes, that's right. We'll be with you.
I'll be with you.
[Applied Psychology]
[History of Psychology]
[Dictionary of Psychology]
Xiaoju?
Cheng Lang?
Why are you here?
[Psychological Research Methods]
Did you also find out?
[Mental Health Guidance]
I don't know how to help Shiyi.
And I couldn't sit still
so I came to the library to look around.
I didn't expect we were both thinking the same thing.
Then let's research it together.
Let's divide the books. That way it'll be faster.
Okay.
Let's go there.
[Chapter 4: Preventing Hemophobia]
How about I copy it instead.
You'd better have a rest.
Okay.
What's wrong?
I'm thinking
if Datu's hemophobia can't be cured,
what will he do if he can't become a surgeon?
Shiyi's dream is to be a surgeon.
He definitely won't give up.
What we need to do now
is to see if we can help him.
Cheng Lang, it's great to have a friend like you.
Why are you suddenly saying that?
Because no matter who has a problem in our group,
you're always the one who quickly calms down and comes up with ideas.
So we feel especially at ease with you around.
We're best friends.
It's what I should be doing.
Cheng Lang.
No matter what happens in the future,
you'll always be my best friend.
Of course.
[Male Dormitory Building No. 29]
Hello.
Lu Shiyi.
What are you doing?
Cure your disease.
Taotao likes eating this, too.
I also want braised eggplant.
She likes to eat this, too.
And this one. This one.
- Got it.
- This one.
- Sauteed bacon with small bamboo shoots.
- Do you also want to order this?
- Yes.
- And this one.
- OK.
- I like to eat this, too.
- Let's order some vegetables.
OK. Scrambled egg with tomato.
Okay, Shiyi likes to eat this.
This one.
That's all. Thank you.
Thanks.
What are you doing?
Stay far away from me. What you're wearing is too ugly!
I... No, I'm wearing it because Shiyi is ill.
Have a soda.
- Thanks.
- Drink some.
I don't want it.
There are so many people here.
Give me some face.
I have a rehearsal tomorrow. Do you want to come and watch?
No.
Okay.
Anyway, A'Wen and Xiao Wei asked for a leave.
I'll just quietly rehearse with Xu Menglu.
Xiaoju, does wearing that really work?
Can it be cured?
Yes. The books that I've read said
that having more contact and overcoming the fear
is the most direct way to cure it.
Right?
Then he must see real blood!
You...
Even Taotao consider it ugly.
This is too ugly!
See real blood?
Turn around. Hurry!
Don't you want to be a doctor?
Look.
Guess who I am.
You came?
What's the matter?
I haven't played the piano with you in a long time.
Could you play a tune with me?
Then if I make a mistake, don't be angry at me.
What's wrong?
My tutor recommended me to study in Europe.
You... agreed?
When will you leave?
When the visa is available.
Have you already applied for a visa?
Why didn't you tell me?
I've always supported you in pursuing your dream.
I also know you'll study abroad sooner or later.
But why didn't you... Why didn't you tell me in advance?
I'm your girlfriend.
You should have discussed it with me.
♫ There you are, running wildly through the highlands ♫
♫ Another you is sighing silently ♫
♫ No one is able to understand you ♫
♫ Happiness is not transparent and pain is not thorough ♫
♫ I'm glad you're not willing to give up like this ♫
♫ It hurts to see the stubbornness in your eyes ♫
♫ I'm a bit tired and need to rest ♫
♫ The marks we leave in life ♫
♫ How I wish to travel everywhere with you ♫
♫ To find the meaning of my existence along the way ♫
♫ The hard journey of life lets the soul recuperate ♫
♫ Be brave and find yourself ♫
♫ The red, green, and black colors of the forest ♫
♫ The purity, joy, and freedom of oneself ♫
♫ I wish for you to see clearly ♫
♫ The true you within all the dust ♫