[A River Runs Through It]
[Episode 7: Growing up starts with a farewell, part 1]
- Baobao!
- Bao Xiangxiang!
Baobao! Baobao!
Baobao!
[He Ji Cafe]
These past few days, Cheng Lang only went out to submit his college application.
Do you think he's taking it too hard?
(T/N: In regards to physically hurting himself.)
What nonsense are you talking about? Can't you hope for something good?
But Cheng Lang is truly very strange these days.
The college entrance exam did impact him a lot,
but it's not as exaggerated as Baobao is saying.
Anyway, if this were to happen to me,
I'd definitely cry for at least ten days or half a month.
Then we should hurry and think of something.
We can't just let him stay at home.
Sooner or later, he will get sick.
But what ideas are there?
After the college entrance exam, I must go and see the ocean!
We'll go with you!
I have a plan.
Time to wake up!
- Hurry! Hurry and get up! Hurry and get up!
- What are you doing?
What are you doing? What are you doing?
What do you mean, "What are you doing?" We're going out for fun.
Hurry and pack his things.
Hurry and get ready!
- Hurry!
- Grab his shoes.
We're going to a fun place. Hurry and get up!
Bag, pass me his bag.
Here, here. His clothes.
Get dressed.
Hurry up, there's no time!
- Hurry!
- Hurry and get dressed.
I'm up now! I'm up now!
I'm up now. I'm up now.
Shoes, his shoes. Grab his shoes.
Let's go, go, go.
What are you guys doing this early in the morning?
Wait! What are you guys doing?
A secret.
You'll find out later.
I guarantee you'll be satisfied.
Wait! What in the world are you guys doing?
- Let's go!
- Bye, Auntie!
- Mom, I'm leaving!
Be careful! Be safe!
Auntie, don't worry.
We'll definitely bring back a happy Cheng Lang
and come back safely.
Bye, Auntie. Don't worry, okay?
Be careful on the way.
Bye bye!
Wait for me.
- Uncle Han, you're getting off work?
- Uncle Han.
- Uncle Han, we're leaving!
- Bye-bye.
[Jiangzhou Station]
Taotao, look at Cheng Lang.
What should we do?
Datu.
What's wrong?
What should we do to make him happy?
I have no ideas.
Baobao. Baobao. Come here! Come here!
Hurry and think of something!
- Baobao!
- Cheng Lang, beat him.
Baobao.
Don't be angry. Don't be angry.
We're all going out for fun.
Be happy. Don't get angry.
Come on. Smile. Smile.
Cheng Lang, don't mind him.
Baobao is an idiot.
You're an idiot.
You're the idiot.
- You're the idiot.
- Aren't you guys a bit childish?
- It's you!
- Stop it!
Xiaoju, my pocket is a bit shallow.
Why don't you hold onto my money?
- Okay.
- What are you doing?
- Let me tell you, my little bag has not only a zipper but also an inner pocket.
- It's because the money will fall out.
I definitely won't lose the money.
- Then why don't you keep all of our money?
- Are you crazy? If you give the money to her, what will we do?
This way it'll be more convenient.
- Great idea.
- You'll regret it later.
I think it will work.
Okay. Time to collect money!
Here you are.
What are you guys doing?
Cheng Lang, you have so much money.
Money.
Give me your money.
No.
You're the most unreliable one among all of us.
I feel more at ease holding onto my own money.
Fine, then don't give it to me.
But why did you have to hurt me?
What I said is the truth.
Fine, I'm feeling happy today
so I won't bother with you.
Okay. Hello, everyone.
I'm the tour guide of this group.
Xia "beautiful" Ju.
Everyone, please remember my pretty face deeply in your minds.
I hope everyone will have a nice and easy trip!
You're great, Xiaoju.
You have a hidden talent.
- But I have to point out one thing.
- What?
You're wrong about one thing.
We can't accept your "pretty" face.
- You!
- Right?
It's a long journey, and we have no intentions to sleep.
How about we play some cards? What do you think?
I want to play, too!
Okay, okay. Come on.
Let's play 5, 10, K.
(T/N: Card game similar to Big Two, but the 5, 10, and K combo is the highest.)
Xia Xiaoju, go and sit over here.
Cheng Lang and I will be a team.
- Wait.
- I'm telling you. Today, I'll beat you all.
Get up, get up. I want to play, too.
- You go over there.
- No.
Fine, then I won't play.
Xiaoju, hold my bag.
- There's a magazine in there that you can read.
- Okay.
Oh my gosh, Taotao.
Did you move the small shop here?
Isn't this already very fast?
- Don't rush me.
- Cheng Lang.
This one tastes delicious. Here.
Thank you.
Double Three.
Double five.
Double five and double two.
Queen, King, and Ace.
No.
- Pass.
- I don't have anything.
No one has anything, right?
I win.
Baobao, it's four times the points.
Your hand is at least thirty points, right?
Do you really have 30 points?
Are you a fool? My god.
Cheng Lang, you're awesome.
Cheng Lang, Shiyi. Either one of you has to leave.
Or else, with our intelligence, we will be entirely crushed.
Change it to someone who has a low IQ.
Xia Xiaoju, you play.
What do you mean?
Hurry and come here.
Let me tell you. Only with your low IQ can we win.
- You're the one with a low IQ! You're the one with a low IQ! You're the one with a low IQ!
- What are you doing?
- You brat!
- Your grades aren't good.
- He's in my team. Don't hit him!
- You're the one in last place!
[Guanghui Hair Salon]
[Perm, Hair cut]
[Good fortune as one wishes]
Our children went on a trip together.
Will anything wrong happen to them?
The college entrance exams are already over.
Won't you even let them go and relax a bit?
Moreover, they have Shiyi and Cheng Lang.
What are you worrying about?
Indeed.
Wanfang.
You didn't want to let Cheng Lang
to repeat a year of school?
I already asked Cheng Lang.
He said that even though he didn't get admitted into the computer science major,
he can still get into one of Jiangzhou University's top majors.
So we didn't consider repeating a year.
Jiangzhou University is not bad,
and it's close to our home, right?
Yes.
Cheng Lang said that, too.
But in my heart,
I always feel sorry for him.
I keep thinking that if I had gone with him that day,
then it would have been me who helped that person,
and he wouldn't have missed the exam.
But now, he can't even get into the major that he wants.
Then won't you say that I feel...
It's okay. It's okay.
Don't keep blaming yourself.
Cheng Lang did well on his exams.
It's all over now.
Why are you still thinking about it?
Cheng Lang didn't worry you all these years.
Don't worry. That kid will have a promising future.
That's right. That's right.
What? Do you want me to use my dirty hands to wipe your tears?
Stop playing around. Stop playing around.
- Come here. Come here.
- Stop playing around. Stop playing around.
Stop playing around.
It's okay now. Don't be sad.
By the way, how are Old Lu and Shiyi?
The exams are over now.
Is the war between them over, too?
Thinking on it, it's strange.
This time, those two are strangely harmonious.
Old Lu told him to apply for Tsinghua University's architecture major,
and he agreed.
Seriously. I don't know why,
but I'm still really worried.
- What?
- What are you looking at for you to be so excited?
Look, look at this sentence.
Here.
Right?
When you fall in love with someone,
your whole heart will be attracted to him.
You'll be captivated by him..
You'll care for him.
You'll also blush, and your heart will beat faster for him.
You'll think about him when you don't see him,
but when you see him,
you'll feel too shy to face him.
One card.
What are you doing?
Like a fool.
Taotao, I'm going to the restroom.
Wait, I'll go with you.
Xiaoju.
Is there something that you didn't tell me?
What do you mean?
Are you sure?
You clearly behaved very strangely just now.
Wh-Wh-What do you mean strange?
I'm going to the restroom.
You two have a promising son.
There's no hope for my Xiaoju.
How about one of your boys get engaged to my daughter?
- This way I can get some luck from it, too.
- I say we can.
I like a lively and cute girl like Xiaoju.
Forget it. If Xiaoju ends up with your Shiyi, then even your house's roof would be torn off.
She's more suitable to be with my Cheng Lang.
What do you know? It's called being quarrelsome lovers.
I tell you. In my eyes, Xiaoju and my Cheng Lang are a perfect match and the most suitable.
- It's a deal then.
- Don't steal her from me.
You don't steal her from me!
Now, it seems like having a daughter is something to be proud of.
Just wait to enjoy your happiness. Life as a mother-in-law is great.
(T/N: For the daughter's husband)
Not like us,
life as a mother-in-law.
(T/N: Because of the son's wife)
You're blessed.
It's really great.
[Yunhai]
Hello, everyone. We're arriving at Yunhai Station.
Tourists getting off at Yunhai Station,
please remember to have your tickets and don't forget your belongings.
You can get off at both ends of the car.
Cheng Lang, we've arrived.
Really?
Okay then. I'll go and grab our luggage.
We've arrived.
I'll grab the luggage.
I'll help you.
It's okay. I can do it myself.
It's okay. I can do it.
Be careful.
Shiyi. Shiyi. Wake up. Wake up.
We arrived at the station.
Did we arrive?
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up!
What's wrong with you, Xia Xiaoju?
Why is your face so red?
Are you having a fever?
N-No. I just feel very hot.
T-Taotao, I already helped you grab your backpack.
You can just get off the train.
Come on, let's go. Follow them.
My bag.
Two rooms. 140 yuan in all.
Okay.
- What's wrong?
- Where's my bag?
Taotao, where's my bag?
What can you actually do?
It's all right. Don't be too anxious. Search for it carefully. It can't be lost.
Right, right. It's okay. We'll find it together.
Taotao, hurry and check to see if it's in your bag.
Y-Y-You guys also check to see if it's in your bags.
Carefully think,
when was the last time you had the bag and where was it?
It was there when I got on the train.
It was also there when I was reading the magazine.
When I got off...
I'll grab the luggage.
- I'll help you.
- It's okay. I can do it myself.
It's okay. I can do it.
Stupid.
- How is it?
- There's not even a bank around here.
We can't withdraw money even if we want to.
I'm so sorry. It's all my fault.
I told you we can't just give her all of our money.
Luckily, I still have some with me, but there's not much left.
Xiaoju, it's not a big problem. Don't blame yourself too much.
That's right. That's right.
If you weren't our tour guide today, we would've gotten lost.
I came up with many travel strategies,
but now, instead of having fun,
we don't even have enough money to buy our return tickets.
This problem is quite serious.
You guys don't have to worry about the return tickets.
We can buy it with the money I have left.
Then... Should we be going back now?
Baobao, wipe off your sweat first.
Xia Xiaoju, don't forget the reason why we came here.
Since we're already out here, then let's have fun today before going back.
How can we have fun if we don't have money?
There's a way to have fun without money.
I have an idea. Follow me.
Fine, we'll follow you.
- Let's go.
Okay, let's go.
Xia Xiaoju, what kind of place are you taking us to?
- It's so desolate here.
- Stop complaining. Hurry up and walk!
It's only desolate for now.
Once we climb over this mountain,
we'll be able to see an amazing view.
Really?
It's true!
Behind this mountain lies a really famous landscape.
But if we go through the main entrance, it'll be quite far.
So we can only take this route to get around it.
That's fine.
We can hike and see the beautiful scenery.
That's right.
- Let's go.
- Then, let's go. I can't wait!
- Get up!
- Let's go. Let's go.
I can't go anymore. I can't go anymore.
Let me take a break.
- Let's go!
- Let me take a break.
- Let's go.
- Let's go. Let's go.
Bao Xiangxiang!
You want a beating, don't you?
- Hurry! Hurry and get up!
- I...
- Hurry and get up!
- Let me take a break.
They already left.
Hurry up.
What is this mountain actually?
It's so beautiful.
Since you're so interested, then let me give you an introduction.
This mountain is called Mount Green.
(T/N: "Qing" means green.)
The name you just made up is too lame.
Then according to your logic,
since this lake is green,
is it called Green Lake?
Shiyi, I really admire you.
Do you even know about this?
What do the both of you know?
Although the altitude of Mount Green is not high, it is surrounded by clouds and mist all year round.
Due to this, it is called the "Drunken Mist of Mount Green."
That's where the "cloud" of Yunhai County comes from.
Xiaoju, you're really impressive.
I think you can be a host of the outdoor locations on Zhengda Variety Show.
Of course!
I didn't watch Zhengda Variety Show all these years for nothing.
How is it? Isn't the mountainous scenery very beautiful?
Not at all.
Are you okay?
Give me your bag.
I told you to give me your bag. Why did you give me your hand?
Xiaoju, are you okay?
I'm good.
It's just slippery, so I fell down.
Are you hurt?
No.
Wait for me. Wait for me.
Xia Xiaoju, where are you taking me?
What is it?
The sea.
- It's the sea!
Hurry, hurry! Hurry, let's go!
It's the sea!
It's my first time seeing the ocean!
What do you think? Are you satisfied?
Xia Xiaoju knows that you like the ocean,
so she specifically organized it for you.
- Xiaoju—
- What are you doing just standing there? Let's go!
Come on!
Taotao, look! Look at them.
Lu Shiyi, come down here.
- I'm not interested.
- Let's go!
- What are you doing?
- Taotao, come on.
- Come on.
- What are you doing?
- My shoes, my shoes!
Lu Shiyi, there are times when even you are afraid?
I can't swim.
Xiaoju, Shiyi is really afraid of the water.
Why doesn't he try to learn?
He went to play near a lake and almost drowned when he was young, so he has Aquaphobia.
- Lu Shiyi, you...
- Come!
Are you ready?
Come on.
Stand closer.
One, two, three.
Okay, come here.
Cheng, come here and take a picture of us.
Here, hurry up.
Be happier.
- Cheese!
How do you like it here, Cheng Lang?
It's comfortable.
It's perfect!
Not only is it perfect,
it's ultra perfect, okay?
I don't want to leave.
Then you can just sleep here tonight, Baobao.
I hope time would pass by slowly today.
It's really amazing here.
There are many here.
Xiaoju, hurry and look. There are many shells here!
This one also looks nice.
I really want to stay here one more day.
Xiaoju, what are you looking at?
Look. There are some restaurants over there.
I have an idea that will allow us to stay here one more day.
- Boss.
I beg you.
- We're very good workers.
- It's true. It's true!
We're very fast at cleaning tables, sweeping the floor, and washing dishes.
If you don't believe me, I can show you.
- I beg you.
- Boss.
- Okay, fine. Stop, stop talking.
- I beg you!
- I've had enough of you guys
that my head is starting to hurt.
How about this?
There are a few baskets of oysters that you can help me peel.
Once you're done, I'll give you 50 yuan.
50 yuan per person?
What are you thinking? 50 yuan in total.
It's one person's work.
Do a good job.
Thank you, Boss!
You're welcome.
50 yuan is not enough for us to stay in a hotel.
It's enough, Baobao. Look!
50 yuan is enough for us to rent two tents.
You're smart!
Then the sooner we finish, the sooner we can go and have fun.
- Sure!
Everyone, have some energy.
- Everyone, fighting!
- Fighting! Fighting!
What's wrong?
It's nothing, Taotao.
You only know how to show off your abilities.
Can you be more careful?
That's right. Let me see.
It's nothing. It's nothing. It's only a small cut.
Even if you're working hard, safety comes first.
Do you understand?
I understand.
I was thinking that if we finish it sooner,
then we can hurry and go have fun.
When you said that we'd sleep in tents near the sea,
I was quite excited.
Have you never slept in a tent before?
No.
And it's by the sea.
So I'm really looking forward to it.
What's there to look forward to?
We still have a lot of work to do.
Hurry and come back here to work.
Coming.
Boss Lu has given the order.
Do it lightly.
Don't cut your hands.
I got it. I got it.
Xiaoju.
- What?
- There's something strange with you today.
No, same as usual.
No.
I felt that there was already something wrong with you when we were on the train.
There's nothing wrong with me.
Do you like Cheng Lang?
Lower your voice!
What are you talking about? I...
Why would I like him?
Okay, fine.
Here is your pay.
70 yuan?
B-Boss, did you give us too much?
Just take it if the boss gives you too much.
I didn't give you too much.
Didn't you lose your money?
I believe that this 50 yuan is not enough for you guys to spend.
So I gave you an extra 20 yuan.
You haven't had dinner, right?
I've prepared a few servings of fried rice.
Consider it as my treat. Hurry and go eat.
- Thank you, Boss!
You're welcome. Go eat!
Let's go.
[The community is a family. Love between everyone.]
Sister Ding!
Xiao Yang.
Hello! Hello!
Congratulations, Sister Ding.
Your son has a promising fortune.
- A letter of Admission?
- Jiangzhou University.
Hurry! Hurry and open it!
[To: Cheng Lang]
[Jiangzhou University]
That's great.
- Take a look!
- That's great!
Let me see how the letter of admission from Jiangzhou University looks like.
Also, congratulations to both of you, too.
- Is there even one for us?
- Yes.
Xia Xiaoju?
[To: Xia Xiaoju]
[Jiangzhou University]
My Xia Xiaoju got accepted!
Good things keep coming.
Okay then. I'll leave you guys to it.
I still have things to do so I'll be going now.
- Okay.
- Thank you, Xiao Yang.
You're welcome!
[Letter of Admission: Cheng Lang is admitted as a Philosophy major. Please bring this Letter of Admission and Admission Card, and report to school on September 1. - Jiangzhou University]
[Letter of Admission: Xia Xiaoju is admitted as an Accounting major. Please bring this Letter of Admission and Admission Card, and report to school on September 1. - Jiangzhou University]
That's excellent!
Even though it's a second major,
it's still Jiangzhou University.
That's right!
She's classmates with my Cheng Lang again.
Congratulations! Congratulations!
- Your daughter is awesome!
- Look!
My Xia Xiaoju made it!
Oh no, something's wrong.
What's going on?
Is there something wrong with your Shiyi's Letter of Admission?
The issue is big.
♫ There you are, running wildly through the highlands ♫
♫ Another you is sighing silently ♫
♫ No one is able to understand you ♫
♫ Happiness is not transparent and pain is not thorough ♫
♫ I'm glad you're not willing to give up like this ♫
♫ It hurts to see the stubbornness in your eyes ♫
♫ I'm a bit tired and need to rest ♫
♫ The marks we leave in life ♫
♫ How I wish to travel everywhere with you ♫
♫ To find the meaning of my existence along the way ♫
♫ The hard journey of life lets the soul recuperate ♫
♫ Be brave and find yourself ♫
♫ The red, green, and black colors of the forest ♫
♫ The purity, joy, and freedom of oneself ♫
♫ I wish for you to see clearly ♫
♫ The true you within all the dust ♫