[A River Runs Through It]
[Episode 10: Friends mean "I" am alone, but "We" are not alone.]
What are you doing?
How dare you connect wires secretly?
Do you know how dangerous that is?
What if there's a fire?
Do you think this is your home? This is a dorm.
Do you have any sense of community?
- Yes, we do!
- Yes!
Uncle, I think you are right to scold them.
How about this? I'll help you supervise them.
If everyone is like you, I wouldn't have to worry.
Any prohibited electrical appliances
or connected wires found in the dorm again,
I won't let you go easily with a warning.
- No, we won't.
- We will never do it again!
- I'll take these things away.
- Uncle, wait!
You can take away everything, but please let us keep the DVD.
No way!
This is our school's regulation.
Yes, you're right.
- We know we were wrong!
- Uncle!
Uncle!
Please do us a favor, Uncle!
Do you smoke, Uncle?
- Uncle!
Uncle, go slowly!
All of you go away!
I don't even have a temper anymore.
How could we, such smart people, get caught just for connecting wires?
It's unscientific!
You're talking nonsense!
Last night in this building, only your room was lit up.
Who else would have been caught?
But it was really hard to buy the DVD.
Cheng Lang, can't you say something good for your brothers?
Aren't we still brothers?
That's right!
You didn't think of me when watching the DVD,
but now you are thinking of me?
The DVD was confiscated!
We have become indifferent to one another.
Are you blaming me for neglecting you?
All right. Go away!
Let's go out for a walk.
Literature Club.
[School Advertisement Board]
Chinese opera club.
Xiaoju, have you decided on what clubs to join?
Not yet.
Xiaoju, is this the Lu Shiyi we know?
[Notice of Punishment]
"Lu Shiyi, a freshman from the Department of Medicine,
and Huang Jun, a freshman from the Department of Veterinary Medicine,
- privately connected wires to watch DVDs in the dorms."
- Watch DVDs?
Taotao, the Lu Shiyi you mentioned
is exactly the one we know.
Datu, aren't you very smart?
Why were you caught?
At least, I'm smarter than you.
You are much smarter. Didn't you get caught right away?
Which side are you on, Cheng Lang?
What DVD were you watching in your dorm?
That engrossed?
- You didn't even notice the housemaster–
- Shut up!
Forget about this matter!
Uncle is so ungrateful! He even put up a notice.
Why don't we go look at which clubs are recruiting?
Let's go.
- So smart.
- Let's go!
Come have a look.
Come take a look! Our club is recurring!
[Wing of Wind Roller Skating Club]
- Amazing!
- That's right!
Our Painting and Calligraphy Club has many activities.
- So many people.
- That's right.
Taotao, that suits you well,
that big head.
You're the one with the big head!
The Track and Field Club is also recruiting members.
Shall I sign up for it?
I think you should!
You're sure to make it.
You?
You are just an amateur runner.
Don't hold the team back.
Did you forget how you shamelessly begged me
to take part in the competition?
It's because I had no choice.
Don't you know about having to pick the best out of a mediocre bunch?
Your mouth is really...
I really want to sew your mouth up!
There's a Tailor's Club over there. Do you want to join?
Sew it if you have the ability to. Sew it!
- Just do it.
- Come on, you two.
As seniors in the kindergarten,
be mature, Lu Shiyi.
By the way, Xiaoju,
mostly boys participate in Track and Field.
Are you sure you want to join?
What about you guys?
I will if you guys join.
Classmate, are you interested in joining?
Basketball Club.
Do yant to join the Basketball Club with me?
I've two specialized courses and I have to work.
Where do I have the time to play basketball?
Then you have to exercise more, right?
Just treat it as accompanying me.
Let me think.
I also want to join!
All right.
You?
Looking at your short stature, do you still want to play basketball?
Come on. They won't recruit girls.
- You!
- Classmate, who said we didn't recruit girls?
Who said short girls can't play basketball?
I don't think you're very tall either.
Besides, I haven't seen if you can actually play.
Who are you?
Does this have to do with you?
I'm Shen Duo, the coach assistant for the Basketball Club.
Is that all?
I thought you were some kind of big shot.
How can a coach assistant be so arrogant?
If she's here, I don't really want to join.
- What do you mean?
- Nothing.
Oh, God!
Let's go.
How did you make it?
- I got lucky.
- You got lucky, didn't you?
- Wasn't that cool?
- Yes!
That was really easy for me.
Amazing! You're really something!
He's pretty good.
Help me inquire about him.
You must persuade him into joining us.
I'm on it.
Which clubs have you signed up for?
I signed up for the Student Union.
I signed up for the Literature Club.
Are you sure you didn't sign up for the Romance Literature Club?
Xiaoju, how about you?
I originally was going to sign up for Track and Field,
but there are too many boys in it.
Cheng Lang advised me not to join.
Xiaoju, do you still remember Article Three in the Youth Story?
Of course. It says if a boy likes you,
he doesn't want you to be close to other men.
I think it's pretty much true.
What is almost true?
- Nothing.
Taotao, can you accompany me
to where Cheng Lang works tomorrow at noon?
- I want to invite him.
- Your birthday.
I understand. No problem.
What are you talking about?
I also want to take the CPA exam.
Did you start preparing this early?
After all, the test is rather difficult, so I am starting early.
- Let me have a look.
- Okay.
Oh, my God!
Do you have to take this test to be an accountant?
As far as I know,
the national pass rate is very low.
There're six subjects,
including auditing, accounting, economic law, tax law and...
I can't remember.
I announce that I give up.
I won't take it!
I'm Professor Wu, the professor for Fundamentals of Accounting.
Every year, before I start teaching,
I like to give a few words of advice to the freshman in the major.
In this field, you must be meticulous.
You can't make accounting errors.
More importantly, you must be cautious.
You must never manipulate accounts for a boss or company.
You can not afford the consequences of doing so.
Once the situation has been uncovered and you are discovered,
you'll be liable for it.
All right. Let's begin class.
Everyone open your textbooks to page one.
Our course will be mainly focusing on an introduction to Computer Science.
Look at this one.
I'll share my classmate's.
Thanks.
There's quite a lot of people that are here in our class today.
I believe many of you are from other majors here sitting in.
Every year when freshmen come,
we always have so many students here like today,
But as time goes by, there are fewer and fewer people.
Though Computer Science is a popular major,
but it is not easy to truly master.
First, I'll talk about how the computer was invented.
The first electronic computer was invented in 1946
at the University of Pennsylvania in USA.
Does anyone know who designed it?
Professor, it's Von Neumann.
Right. This student answered it correctly.
It's Von Neumann.
He was a famous computer scientist in the 20th century.
You're in my way, Senior.
Don't call me Senior. Call me Shen Duo.
What do you want?
Do you want me to join the Basketball Club again?
I told him
that I think you aren't qualified to train me.
It's not a matter of if I can do so. It's about whether you can or not.
The college basketball league is about to start.
Don't you want to compete with the best players in this city?
Don't keep hesitating.
Only by joining our club you can play in the league.
We really need you.
I'll take two more for my brothers.
No problem.
I'll fill out the form first, thanks.
See you on the basketball court!
Senior Shen, are you recruiting him for our club
or finding yourself a boyfriend?
Both. Can't I?
[Classic Audio & Video]
Hi, Cheng Lang.
Surprise!
Hi.
Why are you here?
We came to see you.
Your work place is so nice.
Remember to give me a discount when I come to buy tapes later.
Not only a discount but I also give you a poster.
Okay.
Some new goods just came in. I haven't finished sorting them yet.
Both of you can go look around. If there's anything you like, just tell me.
Okay, go on and do your work.
- We'll talk later.
- Okay.
Xiaoju, you'll need to grasp the chance well.
Cheng Lang, let Xiaoju help you.
You're probably too busy if you do it yourself.
I am going to look for my idol's tapes.
What do you need help with? Let me help.
I don't need help with anything specific.
Look around and tell me if there's anything you like.
I'll give it to you for free.
It's okay, I...
Go on. Choose one.
Cheng Lang...
Welcome. Hello, what can I help you with?
Can you help me find Jacky Cheung's album 'Jacky's Love Songs Collection?'
Okay.
I know where it is. Let me go get it.
This one?
38 yuan.
This is...
[Li Xiao Lin: 415-7342]
I know you're Cheng Lang.
We go to the same university.
Can we get to know each other?
This is my name and phone number.
Can you give me yours?
Sorry, it's not really convenient for me.
Take this back.
Bye.
Please come again.
Cheng Lang, it seems like there are many girls that are trying to hit on you.
There are not that many.
That means there are.
Nothing.
Cheng Lang, are you free tonight?
Tonight I'm going back to stay with my mom.
What's wrong? Is there something urgent?
I want to...
Nothing.
I'll go look at CDs.
[Christina Aguilera, Jeremy Chang...]
[Secret Police - 'Beyond']
You!
Aren't you... that Tao who broke into the boys' dorm?
You're the Rocker Veterinarian... Jun?
Do you want this?
I am taking it.
No, why? Wait!
- I saw it first.
- First come, first served!
"What first come, first served?" Do you understand what a gentleman is?
Do you understand, "A person of great moral stature doesn't take what others love?"
- You!
- What about it?
I don't want it!
Come on, I was just joking with you.
Here you are.
Thanks.
Well, I can lend it to you after I finish listening to it.
Just take it. I've many at home.
I was just joking with you.
Do you also like 'Beyond?'
Yes, very much.
I have every one of their tapes, except this one.
Which song do you like?
My favorite song is "Like You."
You have quite a good taste!
Let me tell you. The guitar arrangement for the song is very nice!
- I can play it.
- Really?
Don't you believe me?
Come, I have to show you then.
Come on. If you don't believe me, come here to listen.
Someone must show off his talent.
Come on, listen.
♪ A light drizzle with wind drenches the streets at dusk ♪
♪ My eyes look up for no reason while wiping the rain away ♪
♪ Gazing at the lonely evening lights ♪
♪ It's all those sad memories ♪
♪ The countless longings in my heart start to surface once more ♪
♪ A fleeting moment of joy is still on my face ♪
♪ I wish you could know right now ♪
♪ That I want to say from the bottom of my heart ♪
♪ I like you, your eyes are so touching ♪
♪ Your laugh even more so ♪
♪ I wish I could caress again ♪
♪ Your lovely face ♪
♪ Holding our hands while sleep talking ♪
♪ Like yesterday you and me ♪
You sang quite well. I never expected that.
You aren't bad either.
Why're you looking at me?
What's up?
Do you have a sense of crisis?
Do you know how many girls like Cheng Lang?
Why aren't you hurrying to the next step yet?
What next step?
Hurry and confess your feelings to Cheng Lang.
Didn't you ask him to meet with you tonight?
I'm not sure if he likes me.
There are two more conditions in the magazine that I haven't reached yet.
And...
He said he's going home.
What a good chance this was!
If you can celebrate your birthday with him,
this matter might come true!
Forget it. I didn't even get a chance to arrange a meeting with him.
You!
By the way, who called you just now?
My dad.
He said he'd take my mom and me to travel.
He also said that it was rare that our family rarely fine time to travel together.
He said it was very urgent,
and I must go back tonight.
I told him, "I can't!"
"I have no time. I must celebrate Xiaoju's birthday with her."
No, you should hurry back!
Why do you have to be with me?
Xiaoju.
You can be with me any time, but it's rare for your parents to have time.
- Go quickly.
- No.
Quickly go! Don't stay with me!
- Don't stay with me!
- But I...
- It's your birthday.
- I'll be fine.
It's okay. Just quickly go!
Both you and Jiashu are flesh that came from our bodies.
You're both the same.
♫ There you are, running wildly through the highlands ♫
I've been away from home for so long.
Have they missed me, even a bit?
♫ No one is able to understand you ♫
♫ Happiness is not transparent and pain is not thorough ♫
Xiaoju.
Xiaoju, quickly come and taste this!
Is it salty enough?
Mom, you forget again.
Sister Xiaoju has gone to college.
Look at my memory!
Mom, today's her birthday.
Should we...
What?
She'll come back if she wants to.
Hurry and go study.
Wicked girl.
♫ How I wish to travel everywhere with you ♫
What should I say when I call them?
Classmate, will you make a call or not?
Sorry, I won't. You can go ahead.
♫ Be brave and find yourself ♫
Hi, Mom. It's me.
I miss you!
I started to miss you even though college started a few days ago.
Have you and dad eaten?
I have eaten.
I ate with my new classmate.
I ate braised chicken wings,
pork ribs, and stir-fried vegetables today.
♫ The true you within all the dust ♫
Lu Shiyi!
Lu Shiyi! Here.
Next one!
You must be hungry after training.
I'll treat you to dinner.
Don't you see? I'm practicing. I've no time.
You don't have time even if I'm treating?
What day is it today? New Years?
You, miser, is actually willing to treat me to dinner?
If I can find anyone else, I won't treat you.
That reluctant?
Then forget it. Just be alone.
Go eat by yourself, bye bye!
- I'm kidding.
- Next one!
How can you be so heartless?
Am I really going to celebrate my birthday alone?
Keep up!
You really aren't going?
Next one.
♫ You walked into my sight ♫
♫ Warm just like a sunny day ♫
♫ I greatly want to let time stop ♫
♫ Who also once yearned to exchange using the souls? ♫
♫ Yet only to be left stranded before forgetting ♫
♫ Carrying the bags to wander about in the opposite direction ♫
♫ I wish dearly that besides you ♫
♫ You can have the most considerate companion ♫
♫ Someone that can replace me to fly with you ♫
♫ I can only pretend and lie ♫
♫ I go off wandering with a facade of happiness ♫
Am I really going to celebrate my birthday alone?
Who is it?
Did I hear it wrong?
Xia Xiaoju!
Silly girl, are you really going to celebrate your birthday alone?
Liars!
[Happy Birthday]
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
Happy birthday to you!
Thank you, everyone! I thought all of you had forgotten!
I did forget, but Cheng Lang and Le Tao didn't.
To prepare this surprise for you, they forced me to act with them.
I was so annoyed!
Come on. Xiaoju, this cake was bought by Datu.
Alright. Quickly make a wish and blow out the candles.
What wish did you make?
I won't tell you.
Xiaoju, since it's your birthday,
what about going home with me tomorrow?
Let me think over it.
Let me give a toast to everyone!
- Cheers.
- Happy birthday!
Cheers.
- Happy birthday.
- Thanks.
- You continue.
- Come on.
- I'll take you to a good place later.
- Okay.
- Let's go together.
- Let's go!
- Take hers.
- I have none.
Lin You, what are you doing?
You guys continue. I'm going out for a second.
- I'm sorry.
- You want to run?
Pay for my liquor.
Let go of me! Let go of me!
Are you deaf? Pay for my liquor.
Lin You.
I'm sorry. I'll pay.
- Lin You.
- What's wrong?
- Is this enough?
Get out of my way!
I must straighten it out with her today.
What do you want? Want to fight?
- Don't make trouble.
- Don't pull me!
- Calm down.
- Want to fight?
Someone says he wants to fight!
Who wants to fight?
Someone said they wanted to fight?
Run!
Chase them!
Quickly.
- Stop!
- Faster.
Stop!
Don't run!
Chase them!
Quickly!
Bastards, chase me!
Xiaoju, hurry and run!
- Quickly!
- This way!
- Stop!
I can't run any longer.
Neither can I.
I'll give you a hand.
Where did they all go?
I don't know.
Maybe they went to the restrooms.
Stop!
Don't run.
They left.
Those bastards ran really fast.
My legs are almost worn out by all the running.
I have to buy new shoes again.
That's right, where are Huang Jun and Qiu Le Tao?
Where did they go?
Don't worry. Huang Jun that kid is quite smart.
Now they may have already arrived at the campus on the motorcycle.
Xiaoju,
I'm sorry.
It's because of me that your birthday turned out like this.
It's okay.
I'm really happy that you remembered my birthday,
and this birthday is unforgettable, isn't it?
Isn't it?
All right, it's not safe here.
Let's hurry and go back to campus.
Let's go.
[No.25 Girls' Dorm]
Xiaoju, you're back.
Your mom's here. I took her to your room.
My mom?
- Thank you.
- Your welcome.
Xiaoju, you're back.
How has it been?
Are you used to living here at school?
Have you been busy recently with your studies?
Today's your birthday.
I thought you'd come back home.
I cooked your favorite longevity noodles,
and red-dyed eggs,
but you didn't come home.
As a college student,
why are you still acting like a child? Having a temper
and leaving without a word?
Come have a look.
I brought some food for you.
Look. It's all your favorites.
And this,
look.
All your favorites.
What's wrong? Are you still angry at me?
I just said those things when I was angry.
I don't hate you at all.
It's you who dislikes me.
Nonsense!
How can I dislike you?
You're my daughter. You are my own child.
Eighteen years ago, who did I give birth to?
Your brother Jiashu is young,
so I normally care more about him.
But I have neglected you.
It's my fault.
I'll change from now on.
Mom, has Jiashu's head recovered?
Last time I really didn't mean to push him.
I know.
He has recovered. He's okay.
Don't worry.`
All right, today's your birthday.
Have you had some cake?
Do you still want to eat these?
Happy birthday!
Happy 18th birthday!
Mom!
You silly girl.
You're my daughter.
How can I dislike you?
Mom, I'm sorry.
It's fine.
You don't need to apologize.
♫ There you are, running wildly through the highlands ♫
♫ Another you is sighing silently ♫
♫ No one is able to understand you ♫
♫ Happiness is not transparent and pain is not thorough ♫
♫ I'm glad you're not willing to give up like this ♫
♫ It hurts to see the stubbornness in your eyes ♫
♫ I'm a bit tired and need to rest ♫
♫ The marks we leave in life ♫
♫ How I wish to travel everywhere with you ♫
♫ To find the meaning of my existence along the way ♫
♫ The hard journey of life lets the soul recuperate ♫
♫ Be brave and find yourself ♫
♫ The red, green, and black colors of the forest ♫
♫ The purity, joy, and freedom of oneself ♫
♫ I wish for you to see clearly ♫
♫ The true you within all the dust ♫