Equinox
Burnly
I'm tired of looking for my old man
My sincerity can't buy a home
I don't need to be a man to walk through this life in peace
But I heard the wind from the sea
The sky says don't bow down, don't bow down, don't go to the cage
You are the waves, the smoke is the wind
How can you be wrong?
That
I am me
The most beautiful night is cold
I don't want to be the world
To break through it
Become me
Episode 18
There are rules for the precedence of the English word
For example
Come is come
Go is go
And?
Mommy, I love you
You can learn these rules in a few words
Thank you, Mr. Xia
I'll think about it when I go back
Looking forward to your good score next time
Sure
Come on
What's wrong?
Nothing
By the way, how is your mother these days?
In the hospital
Is she sick?
No, she is angry with me and my brother
Because of me?
It has nothing to do with you
She didn't think it through
Then do you think I can do something?
No need
I understand her
I lost a lot of family members too
I know the pain
So I hope you don't get into a fight with your family because of me
She is angry now
I'm afraid whatever you do
You can't change her mind about you
What she thinks about me is not important
The most important thing is that as your son
You should make your mother happy
It's not easy for your mother to live her life
It's easy to make her happy
Follow her will
But I will never compromise on this
No, Xia Chu
Xia Chu
I think you don't know your mother
What your mother wants most is not a son's obedience
What is it?
Shanghai Women's Association held the second temporary meeting and issued a statement
Is it 17th today?
Yes
Really?
It's written here
Shanghai Women's Association
They all forgot me
Forgot what?
Shanghai Women's Association held the second temporary meeting
You are here
Are you feeling better?
Yes, I am
Why are you alone?
Xia Yuan is very busy these days
He can't go to the store
What about Xia Chu?
I don't know
I haven't seen him for days
What about Youwen and Youze?
They are still in school
What about you?
Forget it
No one can count on me
What's wrong?
Are you in a bad mood?
No
I will go out with you
You must go
The doctor told me that you have a heart disease
You should go out more
Look, the weather is so good today
I will go out with you
Let's go
I won't go
Hurry up
You are like a child
Let's go out for a walk
You will get better soon
Are you tired?
Let's take a rest
I am not tired
I want to know what day it is
Today is the 17th
What day is the 17th?
Oh, no
I forgot to pay the bill with the Ministry of Finance
Look at me
Ok, ok
I changed my clothes for nothing
I will go back and wait for death
Mom, you look so beautiful
The weather is so good
Let's go out for a walk
I won't go
Go, go
Take a walk
Go, go, go
Look ahead
Grandma is here
Grandma
Aren't they my grandchildren?
Why are you...
You are here too
Mom
What are you doing?
You are so rude
You will know it later
What are you doing?
Why do you take me here?
This is...
Mom
This is the opera troupe
that I invited from my hometown
Hebei Gang
Yes
Sing Hua Mulan
Open your eyes
Hurry up
Wait a minute
What are you waiting for?
Sing it
I haven't prepared the opera troupe yet
Then...
Mom
We have a gift for you
A gift?
Of course
Dad
Mom
I knew it from the beginning
that you really like to hide this kind of thing
I often saw you
taking it out when you were alone at night
You kept looking at it
and touching it
Later, I went out to do business
and lacked money
You sold it without hesitation
Is this the same one as mine?
It's a copy of the old photo
that you took back then
I'm so sorry for your filial piety
Mom
Put it on
Put it on?
Yes, mom
You are a ten-year-old singer
The most popular one is this Hua Mulan
If you hadn't married my dad
you might be a famous singer now
Come on
Put it on
Let's open our eyes
No, no
I'm old now
I can't sing
Mom
You always say that
you are very beautiful on stage
The days of singing opera
are the happiest and most relaxing days in your life
Let's do it again today
No, no
I can't sing
Mom
No, I can't sing
Mom, look
There are no outsiders today
Sing for us
Yes
I want to sing Hua Mulan for grandma too
Me too
Grandma, just sing
Okay
I'll sing
The late emperor
Big mistake
I'm waiting here
I don't know if you want to come or not
I want to think about my hometown tomorrow
and be with my old friends
Put it on the table
Wait a minute
Let me see
Ok, slow down
Come here
Good
Grandma, you sing so well
Mom
I'm old
I can't sing at all
Great
Mom
How do you feel on stage again?
I feel like I'm back to the old days
Mom
Are you happy?
Happy
Today is my 60th year
The happiest day
That's good
Do you know who arranged all this?
Who?
All of this today
Including the custom-made form of the hall and the opera class
It was all arranged by Chu Shaohua
Shaohua said
You have been working hard for the Xia family all your life
It's almost time to relax
So you must find the happiest time of your life on your 60th birthday
Where is he now?
We also booked a birthday party for you
He should be busy there
Go, go see him
Go
Madam, congratulations
Thank you, please have a seat
Please
Madam, please have a seat
Thank you
Congratulations
Please have a seat
Thank you
Let's go
Hello, Mr. Zuo, hurry up
Hurry up
Madam
Shaohua, thank you
It's my pleasure
It must be hard for you all the way here
No
Xia Chu
You will have a better life with Xia Chu
Mother, you agree to my marriage with Shaohua
As long as you two think you are a good match
Don't care what others say
As long as you two feel happy
Nothing else matters
Madam, thank you
You are welcome
I have to thank you today
If you want me to be happy
You should get married
I will have more grandchildren
Mother, we will get married when the North French army comes back
How long will it take?
Soon
We will get married
The Chinese unification is coming
Xia Chu is right
Xia Chu is the most political-minded among the students who studied in Japan
It seems that I agreed to let him be a politician
But I was wrong
You need to sign the salary of the
The Chinese unification is coming
I will sign it
You have signed it
It is the salary of the North French army
The salary of the North French army
Let's go together
Ok
Zhixiu
Xia Chu and Miss Chu are preparing for the wedding
I think you and Miss Chu are good friends
I didn't expect that fate is not easy
I hope it won't affect our cooperation
Don't worry
I can't live without money
Mr. Xia, tell me if you need anything
Thank you
How is it?
So beautiful
I feel like I am dreaming
It is more beautiful than a dream
How far is it?
I finally marry you
We are finally together
We will never be apart
Sorry
Miss Chu, do you want to try this cheongsam?
Don't you have wedding dress?
You need to wear cheongsam for the wedding and the wedding banquet
Try it
I haven't seen you wear a red cheongsam
Ok
Ok, come
Miss, this way please
Thank you
Xiaohua, I have something urgent to deal with
I need to go now
You can go home after you finish the cheongsam
Why are you so anxious?
I am here to see you
Miss Chu
You...
I am leaving
Miss Chu
You look so beautiful in this dress
Xiaohua
Miss Chu
You are awake
I am in the hospital
You fainted
We will send you back
Be careful
What day is it today?
14th
Xiaohua
What are you doing?
The wedding will be held in two days
Many things haven't been settled yet
Xiaohua
Xia Chu
I know
He is busy
I have discussed with him
Leave the wedding to me
He just needs to attend the wedding
Why are you here?
He has been waiting for you all day and night
You are free
You don't care about the wedding room?
Hello
Dahua Restaurant?
Yes
I am Chu Xiaohua, the wedding planner for No.16
I want to add two more dishes of leeks
Is it ok?
Ok, thank you
Hello, the flower shop
I am Chu Xiaohua
I want to confirm with you
Are the flowers ready for my wedding?
Ok, thank you
Ok
You are really free, right?
If you are free, help me to get the wedding cake
At the station
Xiaohua
There is no wedding
Erniang, I should get the ring of the ring circle
Or you can go with me
Go
What's wrong with him?
He is not a good man
Madam Xia
Where is Boss Xia?
He is handling the post of Xia Chu
Jie Ai
How is he?
He is in the hospital now
You Ze and You Wen are there with him
What is wrong with Shao Hua?
He has been preparing for the wedding
Still unwilling to accept the fact
No matter how we persuade
No matter how we say
He doesn't believe
I can only invite you
Maybe what Xia Jiaen said
He can believe
Shao Hua
Sister-in-law
You are here just in time
Come and help me look at the wedding menu for tomorrow
Shao Hua
Stop working for me
There will be no wedding tomorrow
Xia Chu
He has left
Where did he go?
He will never come back again
Impossible
He will definitely come back
Shao Hua
Listen to me
Xia Chu is dead
He will come back to life
He will not come back to life
But Xia Chu can
There was no news of him for many years
Everyone thought he might be dead
He held a funeral for him
And made a tombstone
But in the end
He came back
This time it's real
It's really Xia Chu
Sister-in-law
Don't cry
Don't worry
He will definitely come tomorrow
He will definitely attend the wedding on time
This wedding dress is so beautiful
So good
Tomorrow is my wedding with Xia Chu
Don't cry
I know you can't bear to leave me
Erniu
Don't worry
Even if I get married
We can still meet again
We are still good sisters
A lifelong good sister
Do you know
Do you know how many years I have been waiting for this day
Eleven years
I know
Sleep
Come
Sleep well
Ok, you should sleep too
Sleep
Have a good sleep
Tomorrow
I will come to see you
I still have to hold the wedding
Shaohuan
Wang Gente, are you all right?
I'm fine.
I want to answer the phone.
Go on in.
Are like the little Blood
Soft taste
You'll be quite cheeksy
Alsora
It's totally bothering me
This
What?
He got shot in the chest with five guns.
He's still waiting for me at the Taohua Hotel.
We all saw his body, including you.
Today is the day of my wedding with Xia Chu.
Today is the day of his funeral.
Let go!
The wedding is about to start.
If I don't go now, I won't make it.
Xia Chu!
Stop it!
Calm down.
Look at yourself.
You disappoint me.
You wouldn't have fallen down no matter what you've been through.
You know what happened.
But you chose to be a coward.
You chose to be a coward.
You chose to escape.
You're a coward.
I'm not.
Then face the reality.
Xia Chu is dead.
Xia Yao!
I found the murderer who killed Xia Chu.
Who is it?
Mu Ziru.
He's dead.
I'm sorry.
Let's go try some...
better world food.
What do you want for dinner?
I'm not.
Do you like it?
You're rich.
Can't I be rich and have a good reputation?
If you take it out,
their eyes will be blinded.
Oh my god.
I love you so much, Wang Mo.
If you love me,
then marry me.
Are you proposing to me?
Look.
We've been together for years.
I should have been married by now.
And my master is about to change his career.
I don't have to fight anymore.
I just want to live a good life with you.
Marry me.
Shaohua.
Look.
Shaohua, what are you doing?
Miss Chu.
What do you mean?
Don't kill Xia Chu.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Stop pretending, Captain Wu.
Who did this?
Who?
Shaohua.
Did you make a mistake?
Okay.
Tell me.
How did you make it?
And how did you get the prize?
Who told you?
If you don't know,
you're dead.
Don't shoot.
It's a misunderstanding.
Xia Chu is dead.
The gun is on fire.
I swear.
I didn't want to shoot.
Five bullets are on her body.
They're all on fire.
It was a mess.
The gunmen were shooting.
I don't know who they were.
It's really you.
I was on duty.
I swear.
I didn't mean to kill Xia Chu.
And there was no name on the list.
She suddenly appeared there.
You shot her.
Someone was shouting.
Someone was
I was really confused.
I really didn't know what I did.
I still regret it now, Shaohua.
Regret?
Captain Wu.
You said it on the celebration banquet.
If you knew how to kill the Communist Party,
you would kill more people.
I know.
I don't have anything to say now.
Please give me a chance
to make up for your relationship with An Zheng.
You can say whatever you want.
As long as I can do it,
I will do it.
Don't drag us down.
You can talk about the conditions.
Go to see Xia Chu.
If he can forgive you,
we will have a fight.
No.
Erzhuang, get out of the way.
Don't shoot.
Get out of the way.
Xia Chu is dead.
I want to take care of Xia Chu.
I know.
But I beg you.
Don't shoot.
Go.
Put down the gun.
You almost killed me.
I told you to put down the gun.
Get out.
Captain Wu.
If you dare to shoot,
I will make sure you never see me again.
You...
Slow down.
They are all here.
Wen Zhiqiu.
Mu.
You are so rude.
You are shooting at a woman.
Don't move.
Brother.
And your daughter.
Don't touch the gun.
Put it down.
It's none of your business.
Go.
Didn't we agree to watch a movie?
What is this place?
You can come and go as you want.
Okay.
Don't go.
You can go.
But he can't.
No.
The movie ticket is full.
If he doesn't go with me,
you will have to watch it with me.
Go to the front.
Watch the movie.
Go.
Damn it.
Get out.
I and Shaohua
have been best friends since childhood.
For a man like you.
I know you are good to me.
I will pay you back more.
Mu Ziru.
We are not meant to be.
What do you mean?
I saved your life today.
I have paid back
the love you have been giving me for so many years.
From now on,
I will never let you go.
we will be on different paths.
Why?
You killed Xia Chu.
If I am with you again,
I will be so sorry to Shaohua.
You broke up with me
for a man you don't love?
You don't know
what Xia Chu means to Shaohua.
From now on,
you are not allowed to go to Shaohua.
You can't touch her.
Even if I don't touch her,
she won't let me go.
I am begging you.
Do you miss me?
I miss you.
How do you know I took your gun?
You have my key.
You know where I hid my gun.
You don't need to hide it from me.
I am sorry.
What are you thinking?
You don't want me to go to the same place as Wang Guodong.
You are here to find Mu Ziru
and take him to the grave.
What about your brain?
I really want to avenge Xia Chu.
Then use this method.
You are smart.
You can judge
and even use your hatred as a bait.
You are about to be killed.
A little bit of white dew melts.
Love is in the snow.
It's your eyes in your heart.
The little wind and the coldness are all gone.
The little peony hidden in his heart.
It warms his heart a little bit.
He speaks the words of the day.
He says winter is short.
The eternal love is looking at him.
Day by day, night by night, night by night.
I am not lonely anymore.
The wind and fire are burning.
I will fight for you.
The green and the green are all over the place.
The eternal love is looking at him.
Day by day, night by night, night by night.
I am not lonely anymore.
The wind and fire are burning.
I will fight for you.
The green and the green are all over the place.
The wind and fire are burning.
I am not lonely anymore.
The green and fire are burning.
Day by day, night by night, night by night.
I am not lonely anymore.
The wind and fire are burning.
I will fight for you.
The green and the green are all over the place.
The eternal love is looking at him.