Episode 28
If
I kill myself,
what will I be left?
For success, maybe I will do more unfair things.
This martial art represents the last struggle of Yu Lian's heart.
Dear audience, you have just heard the famous musical performance of Yue Du.
The winner is the cleaners. Thank you for listening.
After hearing it in the taxi, I went back to check it.
I found that the app of Qiming Yue Du has been turned into a special listening app.
It's very popular.
Except for the cleaners, there are almost no other people who applied.
Did you check the time of the cleaners updating the list?
On the day of He Zong Yi's death.
Wei Zhou, do you think this is a coincidence?
We must always remember who I eat with.
This question is the essence of the character and the whole story.
Do you remember the label Zhou Hong Chuan gave to Pei Su?
No.
Whether it's a coincidence or not, I always think this case is not over.
Who sent a message to He Zong Yi?
Why did Chen Zhen suddenly break into Hong Fu and take the coffin to find his own death?
And how did the fake reception table evaporate in the mortal world?
All these things cannot be simply explained.
There must be a bigger conspiracy behind it.
Wait for us to investigate to the end.
Master, go to No. 13.
The murder of the 503 express delivery case is suspected of being a trap.
The crime of drug trafficking and protection in the West West District is also suspected of being a threat to the local community.
The rapid investigation of this case is like a strong blow to the public.
Teacher.
Due to the change in the attitude of the special investigation team in the West West District,
the frequency of the genetic test bill has also dropped to the lowest point in the last six months.
The case is over.
Go.
Luo Bing.
How stupid do you think they are?
They still believe in them.
Do you think
the ignorant people are more worth being cleared than those monsters who are born with genetic defects?
Yes
But it's a pity
Chen Zhen...
Chen Zhen
sacrificed himself for all of us
Mo Bing
Don't worry
I believe someone else will marry us
Don't you think so?
Miao Xiaowei
Go
You OK?
I just skip by
You guys talk first
I go to work
I shall go
So you put the flowers
You put the flowers
Be gentle.
I'll come back sometimes.
This is the first case I handled.
So it's impressive?
But it's not impressive to your mother.
What kind of body did you fall into?
Of course, it's because of your persistence.
I remember the weather was not good that day.
At the point of the patrol,
there were only me and Tao Zi, two newbies.
We were shocked when we received your call.
We called to ask for help,
and tried our best to go to your house.
We were afraid that we would be together to murder and kill.
So we went to your house.
We were afraid that we would be together to kill and kill.
We were afraid that we would be together to murder and kill.
The murderer didn't go far,
and you wouldn't leave.
Where was a child?
What kind of danger did you encounter?
When you arrived,
you were standing in your living room.
You didn't move.
You were looking at your mother.
I will never forget your eyes at that time.
You reminded me of you.
My master once mentioned a case.
It was many years ago.
When he mentioned it,
he was still thinking about it.
It was a case of missing girls.
Several young girls were lost before and after.
They were released from school.
Those who were supposed to go home didn't go home.
They just disappeared without knowing the truth.
One of the victims' father
couldn't stand this stimulation.
He went to several institutions
and ran hundreds of times.
He never made it through the case.
My master saw him playing with life
and persuaded him.
He must have known
that no one would persuade him about this.
My master once described
his eyes at that time.
He said that the father's eyes
were like a body that couldn't be seen.
He said that
the father's eyes were like a body that couldn't be seen.
But if you look at it again,
you can see
the light in the body.
That light
is not working.
When my master told me this,
you were the first one I thought of.
Out of rebuild
Thanks for helping me.
My master told me
if someone looked at you
Don't let your expectation down.
You!
Help me!
Calm down!
Go ahead.
Aren't you my friend?
No.
Just for a reason.
I made you uncomfortable.
performing butt kiss, right?
Absolutely.
According to Escape's new place plan,
the rather this week,
both sides move together.
Hey, I hear from the senior.
Are you going?
Thrash.
manure
plants
Thethree several month
The
Tao Fu, you bought this painting so beautifully.
And this bird cage is also nice.
On this wall,
we should put a baroque clock.
It can show the time.
It looks very special.
But I think we can put some
plant-based balls on the floor.
Otherwise, it looks a bit empty.
Yanjia, what do you think?
I...
My name is Qiao Han Yang.
Okay, okay.
Remember.
Since you are in the special team,
you can be like Xiaowu.
Call me Senior Sister.
I'll treat you.
Xiaowu is older than you.
Han Yang, leave her alone.
Tao Fu, don't be biased.
You can't take care of her
because she's new here.
Little Su,
you have the time to bully the newbies here.
Why don't you go to the kitchen
and help your boss?
Go back.
Oh my god.
Boss, you can cook.
It's a Chinese dish.
I'll let you try my cooking.
Tao Zi hasn't eaten for a long time.
Okay, go out.
Don't help Dao Meng.
Come on.
You don't have any rules.
He seduced me first.
I haven't eaten Chinese food for a long time.
Boss, you're so good at cooking.
Why do you always go to the canteen?
Otherwise, I'll cook a big meal at home
and eat with the cat.
I'm sick.
When will Pei Su arrive?
Pei Su?
Will Pei Su come?
Why are you asking him?
Nothing.
I met Zhu when I was reporting.
He asked me to bring this to him.
A man who is brave and brave,
a man who is a man of heart.
a man of heart.
Hello?
Brother,
how many floors do you live in?
Twelve.
By the way,
the elevator is broken.
Thank you for walking for a while.
You didn't take anything, right?
See you later.
Hello, which floor are you going?
Do you need help?
Excuse me.
Are you late?
No.
You should have climbed up in five minutes.
Why haven't you climbed up yet?
Maybe I'm still trying to be brave.
Another floor is broken.
Do you have rock candy?
No.
I'm going downstairs to check on Pei Su.
I'll bring a pack of it.
What do you want?
You need to know the answer when you go upstairs.
You're really a young master.
What are you doing?
Buy rock candy.
You don't know what I want.
What are you looking at?
I found that you seem to have
got along with Pei recently.
Those are the things I know.
But I didn't fall for that bastard anymore.
Go away.
They've all gone.
Then shall we...?
I don't think so.
But I guess it will be fixed soon
It's okay, I'm not in a hurry
Besides, I can't live without you
I said, Mr. Pei
Your legs are for going out
It's so tiring to climb stairs
Delicious
Tao...Tang Anni
Taozi
Why are you here
I just moved here
I will live here in the future
Why are you...
I live here
We are so fated
By the way, I'm sorry
I was just a little careless
I'm sorry
You have a job, I can understand
Brother, I need your handkerchief
Ok
You are going out
You
You go my place today
Ok
on the 17th floor.
Let's go.
It's not easy to raise a pig.
I'm in a complicated mood.
You young people.
Why are you so quiet?
Coffee.
Come on.
Cheers.
Thank you, everyone.
Eat.
Sister Cang Jun.
You and Tao Fu were in the same high school.
And you met each other on a blind date.
Isn't that so fated?
Are you serious?
It was meant to be like this.
Is Tao Fu
always so heels in the export industry?
Yes,
but he worked so hard at the time.
Turned out his further education was additional degrees.
Although his skills
are less than five years,
his assembled ability is horas.
He is obsessed with WHGA.
He loves well-known meals
and small animals.
Besides,
for so many years,
in order to protect our impersonators,
he assists Ma Long
I've let go of the struggle of the hard-working table tennis players.
It's all because of Tao Fu.
He's the one who's been working hard.
I'm so glad to remember you for him.
Brother Tao is very patient.
Tao Fu is quite good.
Good.
If he has his own child in the future,
he will definitely be a good father.
I've been bothering him a lot when I was a kid.
My mother died young.
My father didn't care about me much.
He took good care of me.
Actually, I was over ten at that time.
I was hungry even if no one cared about me.
But I was with him
until I knew what serious life is.
Sister,
don't think that he treats others like this
in his daily life.
But if he really takes care of his family,
he can think of anything.
You all praise him so much.
It seems that Tao Fu's staff is really good.
Yes.
No, really.
I didn't take care of Pei Su alone.
Everyone cares about you.
Even my master heard it later
and asked him a few times.
And that person, Lao Luo.
Don't think that he doesn't talk usually.
He cares about you a lot.
And that game console of yours.
Or he...
No.
Really?
My boss has done this kind of thing before.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
It's okay. I accidentally slipped.
It's okay.
It's okay. Eat.
Eat something.
taste
Lao Luo.
His laptop
is actually with you?
These are all cases that I was went gracias.
Mrs.ova says
these are all wishes won by Lao Yang.
He gave me everything after he died.
Captain Luo and his team have a mentor.
Why didn't I hear about it?
Call me Senior Sister.
Senior Sister.
Old Yang was the captain when they transferred to the 6th Division.
They've always been close.
He was killed by a wanted criminal before retirement.
What?
I forgot to pay the electricity bill. I'll go get it.
Brother Tao.
I'll go.
Brother, it's too stuffy in the room.
Can I go outside with you?
Go.
Okay. Be careful.
Let's go.
Boss, who is this?
It's Lian Huashan, right?
I didn't find the missing six girls.
I've been thinking about Lian Huashan for half my life.
I couldn't forget it before retirement.
Lian Huashan
It's about time. Let's go upstairs.
No.
You just treated me to a puff.
Why don't I invite you back?
I want to eat a matcha one.
At least, let me finish this puff.
Was this the missing girl?
She was the victim of the first intervention of the special investigation team.
Special investigation team?
Wasn't the missing girls always in charge of the special investigation team?
Not before.
It was because of these cases.
The propaganda that was caused by the case
eventually became a popular demand among the citizens.
After this incident, the government adopted a suggestion.
They included the special investigation team's scope when Wei Cheng Nian left.
They also set up an emergency start-up system.
It's what you all know. Failing alert.
Failing alert?
Guo Feiling?
Feiling is him?
That's right. It was for this year.
At that time,
Lao Yang was still in the inspection team.
I'm sorry.
One day, I received a report from my father.
He said that he lost his child.
And this girl's father, Guo Shi Nan,
received a call from the telephone booth.
This call was answered for a long time, but no one answered.
What crime is this?
You didn't tell me about the kid and you even called to torture their parents.
It's hard to imagine how sad their parents must have been.
What happened later? Did the murderer get caught?
Later, Guo Feiling's case was solved.
All clues were broken. Lao Yang felt suspicious.
He informed the inspection team that the Beidong Police Department had intervened.
He then discovered the whole Xinzhou city, including the nearby district.
A similar case of missing girls actually happened.
She was caught with the same criminal method.
Shen state, sheng state, you're investigating a crime case.
Please tell me how you fell into the novelty.
I wasn't involved in the case but I thus was recovered.
We thought about this on the next morning.
I would like to thank you for saving my life.
Big brother?
If they are not here,
my sister will take me to the subway.
If my sister works overtime,
I will stay in the school for a while.
Have you seen any suspicious people
nearby?
Or...
Suspicious old people?
Brother,
are you really driving?
What are you looking at?
Nothing.
I just found
a very suspicious person.
Chen Zhen,
when you are alone outside,
you should stay away from strangers.
I know.
I am not a child.
I am already 14 years old.
I should keep a distance from strangers.
I should not eat the food given by strangers.
Listen carefully.
People who are not strangers should be more careful.
Do not get into the car of an adult alone.
Do not stay in a place
where there is no one else.
For example,
it is very unsafe
for you to stay with me now.
What if I am a bad person?
I am just giving you an example.
Do I look like a bad person?
Brother,
I am a little scared when you say that.
It is good to be scared.
Boss,
you just said
that there is no interaction between these lost children.
What is the common point?
Are you done dressing up?
What is the matter?
It is okay.
Let's eat.
Brother Tao.
In the
hidden case,
Wu Guangchang is the suspect
who was killed by the victim's father.
Why do you care about this?
It says
that these girls
have a common feature
besides their age.
It is a flower dress.
Are you going to die?
When Chenchen and I went out,
you were talking about this case.
After we came back,
Lan Qiao asked what the common point was.
You looked at Chenchen.
She is the same as the girls on it.
They are all wearing flower dress.
But you didn't say anything at that time.
You can teach children to be careful
in preventing strangers.
And you can improve their alertness.
But you can't let them
be afraid to wear a flower dress.
It is not the victim's fault
to meet the murderer.
Otherwise, what's the use of us?
Brother Luo is right.
So,
you can teach them
to be careful.
But you can't let them
be afraid to wear a flower dress.
I don't think
the game console
was given to me by Tao Zai Luo.
What are you doing?
I'm busy.
What are you busy with?
That boy is here again.
Wei Zhao, you should know
that it's hard for his mother
to be killed.
Give me some more time.
If this is the end,
I will tell him personally.
But can he accept it?
Sometimes,
I want to wait for
an impossible result.
It's better not to
give him this chance at the beginning.
It's too late.
I have agreed with the child.
Let's not talk about this now.
The most urgent thing now is
to send this boy
back to school and go to school.
What are you doing here every day?
I scolded him yesterday.
You go today.
I...
Okay.
I'll go to get you out of here.
Wait a minute.
That boy
likes this kind of retro style.
I didn't drag him...
No.
I... I stole it from my friend
in the dark.
Take it back.
Okay.
What's wrong again?
Don't say I took it back.
I got it.
I found that
Dongbin,
who has been bitten by you for so many years,
is a good person.
You are not at ease now?
You didn't eat much just now
and drank a lot of wine.
Don't drink this.
Most importantly,
it has been hard on you.
Do you want some soda?
Thank you very much
for your concern, uncle.
I'm afraid I can't see your master's handwriting.
I'm afraid I can't see the words you said in the cemetery.
I'm afraid I can't see the victim, Guo Feilin's father,
start to investigate by himself,
claiming that he found the suspect,
and stabbed him to death with a watermelon knife.
I'm afraid I can't see the words you said in the cemetery.
I'm afraid I can't see the victim, Guo Feilin's father,
and stabbed him to death with a watermelon knife.
Don't worry.
This case is not for me.
I won't stab anyone.
It's my style to kill people with a knife.
But I'm not the kind of person
who would kill people with a knife at any time
and kill his father's
to be in this state.
It's rare to have no obstacle.
I really want to thank team Luo
for taking care of me all the time.
I'm leaving.
Help me tell Tao Zi.
The rest of the dishes are in the refrigerator.
Heat them yourself.
If you have time tonight,
remember to bring some gifts to the 1701 upstairs.
That's Tang Ning's house.
Thank her and Chen Chen for being our guests.
Let your single-handedly friend
to be the guest.
I'm leaving.
Definitely.
I'm going.
Thank you.
There's a person, probably an old man.
He seems to be following her.
Please be careful, parents.
Protect the child.
So,
the current level of technology
can make the correct rate of genetic testing
to more than 99%.
We've been doing genetic testing with SID.
There's almost no mistake.
Almost?
One percent
is probably a genius.
So you think genetic abnormality
won't lead to crime 100%?
The cause of crime is very complicated.
The environment, family, and education
may affect one's thinking and behavior.
Master.
It's a pulse.
Pulse 88.6.
Twelve point five.
Eighty-eight.
Dear audience,
this is Tiaopin FM 88.6.
Now we have
a mass award from The famous music accident,
the award for Dog Conf
I'm afraid I can't be alone