how about me?
I am veryмет up
Don't worry
I am fed up
No
Brother
I feel bad
Tieencing Music
Boss,
There's a spy.
Don't worry.
How about disелейing the money
and finding other runs of Vijay Jho's foil?
Besides, that house is so small.
It's okay to live there for a day or two.
It's not suitable for you to keep living there.
Take your car.
What's going on?
You want to kill me?
The
Excuse me, Mr. Lu.
The car that was stolen by my subordinate at midnight.
Did you say something?
I haven't seen this brother.
I'll introduce you.
Hello, sir.
I'm Du Jia.
Mr. Pei is my boss.
Misunderstanding.
What are you doing at Mr. Pei's house?
Do everything.
The main species
May be excavated.
Is this a robot?
I'm going to ask you something.
Go back and talk.
What's going on?
We were talking.
Do you want to play a game?
Do you want to play Hello Kitty?
I've been to the basement.
I know everything.
That villa.
That basement.
Pei Su.
Let me ask you.
Since you're a normal person,
you don't know the pervert of love and hate,
why do you have
such a complicated and complicated equipment?
I've been working in the first-tier hospital for so many years.
I've never seen anyone
who likes to make trouble for himself.
And the wound on your body
was left when you were a pilot, right?
Aren't you afraid of being hit by a internal injury?
Aren't you afraid of being careless
and dying in your basement
without any reason?
What do you want?
I don't mean anything else.
I just want to tell you.
In my place,
you'll never be the pervert you talk about.
I want to know
why.
Have you ever been
angry at me?
When I'm angry,
you've always been my fantasy partner.
I thought I could use a Avenue,
give you a hard time by finding you inside.
But then,
Tao Zi didn't say anything at that time.
We didn't care.
Teacher Pei, did you buy you a cold fish?
No one cares about this detail.
What are you doing?
Yes.
Later, Tao Zi told me that you went to several market
and bought the same pen and paper.
You mentioned it so carefully
because you were afraid that the master of the market would see it.
I thought that although you were always in the way,
sometimes it hurts.
If you go wrong, you will be late for work.
So I was always strict with you.
I didn't go back and forth with anyone
when I was with you.
You were obviously having a fight with a group of friends
in the special team that day.
I was always in the way.
But in the end,
I was always with He Zong Yi's mother.
I didn't understand at that time.
I thought you were pretending.
I really understood until I was in the basement.
Even if you said it to yourself,
you lack compassion in your instinct.
But you still have pity for this world.
So I thought,
even if I didn't care about you,
I would treat you every day.
You also don't love me.
That's right.
I am a person
who is sometimes hard-hearted and doesn't care about you.
I am not sharp enough in observation.
Many times in the past,
I may have missed your help,
entrust,
or even trust.
I regret it.
I let you walk in the dark for so long.
But this time,
I will stop you.
I will definitely do it.
About you,
I have a story in the basement.
You can tell me when you want to.
If you still don't believe me,
don't want to be honest with me,
it doesn't matter.
I understand.
I don't want to force you.
I don't want to make you embarrassed.
It's late.
Have a rest.
Senior.
That basement room
used to belong to Pei Zhongyu.
I don't know where he is.
The Long Ballad
Episode 1
Pei Chang Yu is that kind of person.
He is the most dangerous person
among the spiritual leaders.
In his world,
except himself,
everyone else is just
a wild animal
that has his own killing power.
He can control everything.
Just like the owner can kill a bug.
At home,
he is everything.
If my mom breaks his rules,
she will be dragged into the basement to punish him.
Since I was a child,
I've been thinking about getting rid of him.
But I've always thought that I've never done anything
until he committed suicide.
He was trapped in the devil's cage.
There was only me
beside him.
Before he slept,
Pei Chang Yu asked me to read an hour's book.
He spent two years
to mix his words
into the reading books.
He tried to tell me
the concept of freedom.
Maybe it's because I inherited his genes.
His reaction was too cold.
So until he finished the last book,
he finally showed me
what freedom is.
Freedom of thought.
I'm sorry.
Actually, I knew he committed suicide
from the beginning.
I didn't agree with his suicide conclusion
and kept pestering you
and forcing you to investigate.
I just wanted to use you
to make trouble for Pei Chang Yu and them.
They?
Do you know what is
the relationship between the two?
I don't know.
It's the relationship between the two.
You gave him nutrients,
carbon dioxide and water.
He gave you the protection of the sea.
Pei Chang Yu had a
parasite like this.
The parasite you mentioned
is just a fund, right?
But the company is a shell.
It has no value.
The person who really
controls everything in the dark
is the real parasite.
How did you know about this?
Pei Chang Yu didn't
avoid you in these things?
It's about
my grandfather's death.
My grandfather got the news
that my mother was pregnant.
He couldn't help but want to see her.
The car hit him.
A car hit him.
Does it sound
like a version of Zhou's music?
I asked Pei Chang Yu
I said,
what if someone suspected the driver's background?
What if someone suspected that
it was not an accident,
but a deliberate murder?
As a heritage beneficiary,
Pei Cheng Yu was too suspicious.
Pei Cheng Yu said to me in a strange way.
These things are handled by professionals.
It won't be judged.
This is the first time I've heard from him
the existence of the organization.
Pei Cheng Yu regularly sends money to the organization.
And these people,
whether it's illegal crime,
murder, or murder,
in short, they will do everything
to clear all his obstacles.
Pei Cheng Yu once told me
that this organization
is a treasure knife in his hand.
He can pass it on to me in the future.
I can take it now.
But don't worry.
Don't worry.
I can't get this knife.
Because Pei Cheng Yu
is against this knife.
They are in trouble
because of the plan to go to the ice beach.
Through the case of the Su family,
we can't reject the purpose of the ice beach.
If it's just to build
a private powder factory for rent,
it shouldn't violate your father's interests.
No.
On the contrary,
it's the ice and sea project
that makes Pei Cheng Yu feel uneasy.
Pei Cheng Yu is a monster
who is extremely strong
and extremely self-reliant.
He wants to establish his own system.
He will never allow anything
to go beyond his control.
He is organizing
the behavior of this circle
and the powder factory.
He is predicted
that they are not satisfied
with the knife in his hand.
The organization is using
the ice and sea project
to build a huge network
to attract all the people
who are hiding in the dark
and to hold them in their hands
to establish their own kingdom and order.
So, at first,
Pei Cheng Yu thought
he had raised this monster by himself.
But he didn't expect
that after he raised it,
he planned to build his own store
and make Pei Cheng Yu
a common partner.
Is that what you mean?
But Pei Cheng Yu refused to pay.
They still took away that land.
The organization found
other sponsors.
Do you remember what Zhou Huai Jing
said in the interrogation room?
Twenty years ago,
he heard that Zheng Kaifeng
and Zhou Junhao were secretly
talking about a murder case
of a fake city.
If Zhou Huai Jing didn't lie,
then this organization
has been building
more than one gold mine from the beginning.
Pei Cheng Yu
is such a person
who thinks he is a bad guy.
He might not be able to
see through the truth.
Are you done?
Is it my turn?
What do you mean?
Don't you want to know
what my master Yang Zheng Feng
wrote in his heart?
How did I get it?
How did you know that Qi Ming read it?
When you found out
Jun Hao's case,
you already knew it.
Everyone thinks that
Ma Er Kang and Dao Na Ben
killed their kind father.
What?
Did Luo De Yue see this scene?
Actually, when Xu Dong Yu's case was on,
I was hinting at you.
Maybe someone told Su Ruowan
about the details
in the pencil and the bell.
I was already suspecting
your reaction.
So, Senior,
how did you start to notice
Qi Ming read it?
The sample...
28 days...
I don't know
where did Yang find this ID.
But you said
there was an organization
that provides the service
of murdering people.
I was sure of a guess.
Yang found this organization
with some clues
provided by the cleaners.
He was very careful,
but they found out.
Then,
they created his death
with a perfect accident.
There's only one thing
I don't understand.
What role
did the cleaners play?
What were their goals?
I had a guess.
I don't know if you heard it.
Senior, don't you think it's strange?
Why did Du Guosheng
let Xia Xin'nan go?
Isn't it obvious
that he told the special investigation team
about this girl
and wanted you to interrogate her?
And,
who told Su Ruowan
about the details of the case?
Why did she suddenly
imitate Su Lin'nan
and the case of Su Lin'nan
that happened many years ago?
I think
many seniors
want to know
the mystery of the case.
I think
the case of Su Lin'nan
is a very important case.
I think
the mystery of the case
is a very important case.
I have a reasonable explanation.
Do you want to hear it?
It's not a good idea.
That is, some people
know that they may be used by you,
but they still provide clues
to the special investigation team
and let you keep investigating.
Those organizations that
are confused and make mistakes
and almost expose themselves
three times
in a row
will eventually be out of control.
The direct-intentioned cleaners
will be pushed out
as a shield.
But these cleaners
are not too many.
Because there are not many real perverts.
And
the more money they have,
the more they can afford
to be rich.
When these people
seek for self-protection
and cut themselves
into a official commander,
they will break through
the need for new funds
and find new investors.
For example...
Shut up.
For example, the successor of Pei Cheng Yu
I...
I meet all their requirements.
And I should have been
one of them.
If it weren't for
the fight with them before,
I would have
taken this knife long ago.
And
I've been thinking about
making Pei Cheng Yu
a born leader-in-chief.
He wouldn't have
pursued the so-called killer.
Moreover,
I sneaked into the special investigation team
and participated in the investigation
of the water and water station.
I was blinded by it.
Shut up.
In fact, the organization
has been trying to
contact me before.
But I never answered.
Because I didn't want to show
that he knew about the money.
But if they
try to
get into the new gold and gold,
they will soon
become four-faced.
They will break through the need
for new funds.
Then they can only
kneel on the ground
and beg me for help.
I have a chance to
break their wings
and make this parasite
completely
become my guard dog.
I'm afraid this is
what Pei Cheng Yu
always wanted to do,
but failed.
They have contacted you.
When did it happen?
Why didn't you tell me?
Maybe because
I haven't prepared
for the death.
Let go.
I said I was going to hold you.
Why did you say
you were suspicious?
Senior.
I haven't told you yet
that the investment agreement
of Qi Ming Yue Du
was made in the basement
of Pei Cheng Yu's.
No matter what,
I'm the biggest suspect
of the invaders.
The new intern
from Xinzhou
who is a psychology master
and a new student
of Xinzhou Political and Legal Affairs.
Captain Luo.
He has entered the special investigation.
Is he also
holding other purposes?
I think I lost my watch.
Have you seen it?
It should be in the study.
This is
the dead body.
What?
Has Captain Luo
seen this scene?
If it can be
the development area
of the humanoid robot,
it will be great.
The murderer
committed a serial murder
in 327.
He has been wanted for 10 years.
But he failed.
Do you want to know
what the sign of this pen is?
I don't believe it.
I don't believe
a person who doesn't trust
Zhou Yan and He Zong Yi
will be the one
who led Zhou Hong Chuan
to kill his son.
I don't believe
a person who has been
involved in this several times
will be the one
who led Zhou Hong Chuan
to kill his son.
I don't believe
a person who will die for Zhou Huai Xing
and who is sad
will be the one
who led Dou Xiao Qing
to kill his son.
I don't believe
you will deliberately
lead Feng Bin to resist
and watch him
being killed by Du Guo Sheng.
Pei Su,
I don't believe
you will be the one
who led Zhou Hong Chuan
to kill his son.
Don't use your
secret strategy
to fool me.
You know
I don't believe in these.
I only believe
in a person's will to be free.
I believe you.
You are not the same as them.
You can trust me.
Since you said that,
can I ask you
to help me?
What?
You will know later.
Whoever can
stop life from going out
will become a new person.
Whoever can
overcome pain and fear
will become the master.
Even the best person
can't do that.
There is no pain in stone,
but there is pain
in the fear of stone.
The master is the pain
caused by the fear of death.
Whoever can overcome
pain and fear
will become the best person.
Then
a new life will appear.
Then a new person will appear.
Everything
is new.
Today,
I wrote this letter
to tell everyone
what really happened
in this wall.
I'm sorry.
I was very scared,
so I blocked my eyes
and pretended not to see
and covered my ears
I want to say that we are all wrong.
We should all say sorry to him.
I want to apologize to my classmates, friends, parents,
and the family of the lost classmate.
I want to say sorry to them.
I know it's too late.
Sir, don't call people here to ask questions.
We are here to talk about the situation.
Can you ask Wang Xiao to come here and talk to us?
He can come here once, but twice.
Do you think he is a thief?
Don't talk nonsense. Let's go.
You can contact me anytime.
Wait for me.
Wang Xiao's parents?
Yes.
The victim ran faster than the reporter.
Boss, if Wang Xiao doesn't want to show up,
we should just let him be.
Besides, this is a big and small matter.
Our focus is still on Feng Bin's case.
You are right.
But the case is a case.
Other cases are also cases.
We can't just split the case into two.
The SED's principle of work never has a big and small case.
Yes.
All right.
When Wen Wenxuan comes, I will go to interrogate him.
I will go to the dormitory with Wang Xiao.
Okay.
Boss, there is someone waiting for you in your office.
Captain Luo.
You are not at home.
Come and sit here.
Captain Luo, I wrote the inspection.
Please go back.
You can go back after writing the inspection?
You are at home.
Go and stay here.
I...
Boss, Wei Wenxuan is here.
Go.
Let's go.
No need.
My house is not far.
I can go back.
I didn't say I would send you.
I want to go to that girl, Miss Wang.
But I forgot her registration address and door number.
Do you remember?
I remember.
But I have already quit my job.
Do you want to go?
This is it.
Wang Xiao's home is here?
Wang Xiao's parents have official jobs.
They work in a public company.
Their income is not bad.
But for her to go abroad to study,
her parents have not given up a penny.
Why did she have to study abroad?
It is said that it is because she couldn't keep up with her high school.
The teachers at the school are not good.
The teachers at the school recommended her parents
to go to the community university to learn the skills.
In the future, it will be considered a one-time job.
But her parents quit one day.
They don't want her to go on her own old path.
They pursue her high school education.
They don't know where they found out about the 2 plus 2 channel of the jade.
They spent all the money to buy the house.
That's why they sent her in.
217, let's go.
Is someone there?
What is Huang Xiao?
We are the scouts in the special investigation team.
We're the scouts of the special investigation team.
You've probably seen this Officer Xiao before.
I know
you have something to tell us.
Don't open the door.
Didn't the officer tell you
not to open the door
to strangers when you're alone at home?
It's not safe.
How about this?
I'll write my phone number
on this piece of paper.
Then Officer Xiao and I
will go to your backyard and wait for you.
You can look at us from the window.
When you want to leave,
call this piece of paper.
Is that okay?
Why didn't you let him open the door?
Two strangers knock on the door.
No matter how big the door is,
girls will hesitate.
Moreover,
girls like Wang Xiao
won't open the door for us.
I guess
he has a knife chain
in his door.
He wants to
drive away from the door.
And the corridor is soundproofed.
The house next door is so dense.
I don't know how many ears are in the wall.
Under such a tense
soundproofed situation,
Wang Xiao won't say anything.
So
I'll tell him the phone number.
It's also an initiative
to put it in his hands.
There is a anti-corrosive net outside their window.
He looks out of the window from the window.
The room itself
will also increase his sense of security.
Do you want to know what it is?
defeats
Reasons to特別調查
You love Chen dortside
Option it
Play game
Pellet
ен
You don't know this yet.
檢讨
Chen
Although there are
some strange things
What happened that day
например
The secret in Chen day
ini
My parents
Have already been to the top of the special investigation team this morning
I...
I have nothing to say.
I've answered all the questions.
I don't know about the others.
If there's nothing else, you can go.
Do you know Xia Xinnan's goal of being selected this year?
If she doesn't run,
maybe in the future,
she will be bullied by others.
I know.
Feng Bing said.
I said it.
How are you and Feng Bing and Xia Xinnan?
Are you friends?
No.
I just said a few words to Feng Bing.
He helped me.
Xia Xinnan is not familiar with me.
I...
I'm very lonely in school.
I don't like people.
I don't have friends.
Since you're not friends,
why are you willing to run with them?
You know if Xia Xinnan changes your position,
those people who bully you will transfer their interest to her.
You will be much better in the future.
But even if you know they ran away,
you didn't tell anyone.
Right?
Actually, sometimes,
you can't be free for four hours.
Because the outsiders are always
trying to hide you.
They will force you to accept the responsibility.
They will force you to listen to the most cruel opinion of that voice.
It's really illogical.
It doesn't fit the human nature.
It even defends your interests.
But as long as there is a little bit of survival on the battlefield,
there will always be a gentle voice, right?
Just like before, he told you
to run away with Feng Bing and try to resist.
He told you to protect those
who are actually your classmates.
What about now?
Does he want to pay the price
to those bad guys?
I...
I heard about that person.
The murderer who killed Feng Bing.
What did you say?
You heard about it?
Who told you?
I remember that we haven't
announced the identity of the murderer yet.
The murderer is still in the hospital.
I heard that he was killed by Feng Bing.
What did you hear about the murderer?
Once,
when we were in the special investigation team,
a sister asked me
if I had seen
a man in his forties
or over 40 years old outside.
She said
that he had a little bit of a pulse.
He looked very scary.
I never left the hotel.
I've never seen him.
But...
I'm not sure.
It's okay.
Just tell me.
It's okay even if it's a misunderstanding.
Once,
I heard Liang Yu Jing and the others
talking about
Wei Wen Xuan's birthday party
in the bathroom.
What did Wei Wen Xuan's friend do?
He was so arrogant.
What did he do?
He didn't drink water
for five minutes
and didn't take off his gloves.
I don't think he's a big guy.
He looked a little fierce
and had eyes.
It's scary.
Where was it?
Do you remember?
I don't know.
They didn't say.
I remember
a girl said
the restaurant's
Fu Tao Qiang was very unprofessional.
There was a piece of cabbage in it.
She laughed so hard.
Liang Yu Jing
always liked Wei Wen Xuan.
She was so angry when she heard that.
She told him not to talk nonsense.
She said that he was making
a change.
I know.
Long Yun Cheng.
Thank you.
You've done a great job.
I...
I'm ugly.
I'm bad at studying.
I'm not good at being a part of the team.
And I always drag my parents down.
I'm so glad
to be part of the team.
I'm so happy
that I can become a part of the team.
Thank you.
and always drag my parents down.
They said
we still live in a place like this.
It's all because of me.
They make me work hard every day.
But I just can't make it.
I also spent so much money at home.
I don't even know if I can go abroad now.
People like me
should die.
You...
I was weird when I was a kid.
Now I'm even more weird.
Maybe it's because I was born with it.
Since I was a kid,
no one liked to play with me.
I didn't have a good relationship with my colleagues.
When my parents divorced,
my dad said that
I was a bad son to my mom.
My dad told my mom that
I should take this thunderbolt away
and give you more money.
I was useless all the time.
Look.
I entered SID
and became a scout.
But one day,
I went home after work
and saw a thief.
I wanted to catch him.
But he pushed me to the ground
and saw him escape.
But I still want to continue to try.
The days in the future are so long.
Maybe one day it will be better.
What if?
You can go to SID.
I will go to SID.
If one day you want those people to pay off,
you can make this call.
I'll take you to SID directly.
Flowing through the night
The heart is frozen
Even if it's destroyed, there's no way to be reborn
It's just a piece of cake
Touching the future with my hands
The future is still unknown
I'll be there for you
I still can't measure the world
Even if the pain is gone
Like a song, but without words
The truth has crossed my fingers
How many times have I been called by my name
I call out to you from the bottom of the sea
The wind blows away the hidden meaning, and the white light waits for you
I don't care about the existence of tomorrow
I'll try my best to come back to the color in my dreams
No matter right or wrong, I'm still a white bird
Just go forward
I'll take the pain alone
The wind in the dark, I'll be your one and only
Go forward
Pass through the fog
Don't forget the silence
In the abyss