Hello, a short notice for a comment.
You're late because ofcoca
I'll leave first.
I'm just...
You can leave, not you.
A meeting will be held within two hours.
Go.
How long will it take?
Hello, I'm Mr. Su's assistant, Li Wei Lan.
This is Mr. Su.
Mr. Su.
Long time no see.
Boss.
This is Yu Bin's student's phone.
Call him immediately.
This...
Tell him to call me.
I'm sorry.
You must tell him to come here.
Yu Bin took them to the ice and sea bay.
All the pictures of the bloodline.
What bloodline?
Su Feng told me.
They're all in the notebook.
Check it yourself.
Go.
Yes.
Hello.
Su Feng.
This is the last one.
Here, have some water.
Okay.
Thank you.
The person you asked about
is probably quite stubborn.
Although our family lives on the island,
my father
can't remember anything
about this place.
You said you've always lived on the island.
Have you seen
Zhuo Yingchun?
Dad, have some water.
On our island,
there seems to be no one like this.
It was more than ten years ago.
He was still young at that time.
I guess he doesn't remember.
I'll go find some other clues.
Sorry to bother you.
It's okay.
Dad,
what did you say?
Little...
Little?
The person you asked about
turns out to be Little?
Little?
You can't remember me.
The case of Zou Feng,
there's some evidence that needs your cooperation.
Mrs. Shen.
Did you get any result from Mr. Shen's case?
Zou Feng said
he handed all the belongings of Yu Bin to you.
There's an important evidence in it.
Evidence?
The winter when Yu Bin was murdered,
he took his classmates to go abroad to study.
The first night he was about to leave,
a student lost his camera.
So Yu Bin took his classmates to the school.
He was so angry that he took his classmates
to the school.
So Yu Bin drove back to the beach alone.
He got into a car with someone.
He bumped into two people who shouldn't be together.
In order to find someone to compensate,
he carefully drew the portrait of the two people.
Zou Feng thinks
this is the reason he was killed by Xu Yi.
Zou Feng said
he handed all the belongings of Yu Bin to you.
Because you were the student
who lost his camera.
I think I should hand it to you personally.
Sorry.
Xiao Hao is used to it.
He never knows what his real name is.
But does he have a son?
He is about my age.
Yes, his name is Yang Bo.
I don't know what his real name is.
But Xiao Hao is quite famous on our island.
He immigrated here.
He married a disabled person on our island as his wife.
But he died in a few days.
After that,
he married a disabled person's cousin.
At that time,
the people on the island always talked nonsense behind his back.
They thought Xiao Hao was a good-looking man.
They liked to wear flower dresses like the female celebrities on TV.
So they gave him this nickname.
Not long after that,
his second husband died.
I heard it was a car accident.
It seems to be quite a big deal.
At that time, people said Xiao Hao was dying.
He took his son and went to the other place.
Do you know where he immigrated from?
How can I know?
It's been decades.
They must not know.
But I heard from the old people on the island that
the person who helped Xiao Hao immigrate here cooperated with the foreign countries.
The people he immigrated to
are all orphans from the welfare center.
Welfare center?
Did he tell the people around him where it was?
For example, the climate and the food of the specialties.
Oh, right.
When Xiao Hao first came here, he was very sharp.
I don't know where he said it.
It's like...
It's like what the foreigners in the news said.
Is it Dongyue?
Come.
You want to go down? I'll go down.
Watch. Watch.
Watch.
Let's go.
Everyone, everybody.
Let's do our best.
The factory is open early today.
Today, all of your annual leave expenses,
I, Zhang Dongyue, will pay for it.
I'm so angry.
Do you think it's fate or coincidence?
The annual leave of your company is arranged.
This time and this place is like a custom.
President Pei said last year that the annual leave is here.
Tell Pei Su that I love him. I love him to death.
It's a good thing that it's here.
Otherwise, I'll be fired. I can't catch up.
What's wrong?
Do you not like those?
I...
It's okay. It's okay. Don't worry.
There's a big surprise waiting for us.
Guess what it is.
What?
A mermaid performance.
Please look forward to it.
Here it comes.
Please notice that your temporal cortex is good enough is the time and position.
Where's the
So he arranged a good job for me.
Did you get it?
Yes.
The Heng'an welfare center
closed down because the dean disappeared 20 years ago.
But I found an old man in the Heng'an welfare center.
He gave me a picture.
Just one picture.
I don't know if you need it.
Okay.
Give me the pass.
Right away.
Hello, sir.
I'm Li Chunsheng.
I brought you the painting.
Okay, thank you.
If you have nothing to do, I'll go first.
Okay.
Thank you.
You have to be prepared.
Whoever was in the welfare center
may have serious injuries.
Hello, Yanjia.
Yes.
Hello, Captain Lu.
I found an old man who knew Zhuo Yinchun in the village.
According to his son's memory,
Zhuo Yinchun was bought from an foreign welfare center.
Captain Lu.
I suspect Zhuo Yinchun is the same as Su Fei.
They all came out of the Heng'an welfare center.
Do you think the person behind this
was also an orphan in the Heng'an welfare center?
Boss.
It's Zhang Zhaolin.
On the night the worries came to hand.
So
of the
Chinese police.
What do you mean?
Mr. Zhang,
you don't want to tell me,
you don't know anything, right?
I know.
You asked me to come
because of my brother.
Believe it or not,
these things have nothing to do with me.
I have my dignity
in the special investigation team.
I have my bottom line.
The matter has developed to today.
I sit here to cooperate with the investigation.
It's all because
because of my brother.
I didn't take good care of him.
It's my problem to let him make mistakes.
I and Zhao Lin
are orphans in Heng'an welfare home.
We were together when we were six or seven years old.
Su Fei was younger.
But
he was the longest-serving in the orphanage.
At that time,
Zhou Ya Hong
was eager to adopt him.
She was eager to adopt him.
Hurry, run.
Hurry.
Stop.
Let me go.
It's okay.
Hurry.
True True
White
white
true true
White
white
Black
White
Stop.
Stop, stop.
Jiu Ling, Jiu Ling stop.
Jiu Ling stop
Jiu Ling
You two seem one second away.
Trueks
Take their eventually
No
Let go of me!
Si Bai, don't run!
Zhang Liu!
I told you to run!
Zhang Ji!
Zhang Liu!
Run!
I told you to run!
Hit him!
From then on,
I thought that although we didn't have blood relations,
but
in this lifetime,
we are all brothers.
He is your father.
He is your family.
What about Huo Xiao and Lao Yang?
The friendship that lasted for twenty years,
the comrades who were on the back of each other,
and the friends who were separated from their families.
They didn't do anything wrong to you.
They were killed by your father.
What were you doing?
What were you thinking?
Lao Yang,
Xiao Huo,
Lao Yang, Xiao Huo,
are the people I have the most regret.
I have let them down.
Even if I die,
I don't have the face to see them.
They are so careful.
I was also so careful.
I know.
I let you down.
After Xiao Huo's accident,
we found Sena He.
Of course I know that Sena He
is Zhao Lin's property.
I also know that
he has a lot of businessmen
that he can't get on the table.
But I thought
that he was a good man.
But
I didn't expect
I told you just now.
You have to believe me.
Sena He is Zhao Lin's property.
He is Zhao Lin's property.
I don't know
if you believe me.
Sena He is mine.
He is not fake.
But this thing
has nothing to do with me.
I am just an entertainment city.
All the guests are here.
Don't care about Du Guosheng, Li Guosheng.
You can't just ask them
if they are wanted criminals.
Brother,
brother,
you can't investigate anymore.
If you investigate,
I will be the first one to be caught.
Which entertainment city police
doesn't have anything to do with it?
But this thing has nothing to do with me.
Who knows that his life is so...
Shut up!
Brother,
you have to let me go.
Don't investigate anymore.
I don't want to compete.
You went to college.
You entered SID.
What about me?
It's not easy for me to get here.
Can you be like that?
Come back and save me again.
Brother,
can you?
I was persuaded by him.
At that time,
many people came to me
to remind me
not to investigate anymore.
Not to investigate anymore?
A few dozen years' brother
can't be compared to a few politicians.
So that year,
I was really convinced.
I was convinced.
It was indeed Zhang Zhaolin's order
to kill my brother.
Then destroy the city,
and create a fire.
Stop SID from investigating
along this line.
Then pass on the old
wanted criminal.
It's a trap.
If there is no old lady
of that country,
that wanted criminal will also attack the passers-by.
Nothing is better than
an old man
who is full of ideas and is righteous.
It's easier to plot.
Right?
I failed Lao Yang.
You not only failed him,
but also failed his wife and children.
One of them died in an unknown way.
One was blinded by hatred
and became a murderer.
He could have not died.
But he was still alive.
He was still alive.
He could have not died.
His family
didn't have to be destroyed.
From the beginning,
you said you didn't know
what you did to Zhang Zhaolin.
He was a wanted criminal
in Sena River.
You didn't know.
He framed Huo Xiao.
He set up a trap to kill Lao Yang.
You didn't know.
Then what about the truth behind him?
In order to get the position
of SID leader in FUNIAN,
did you know
the answers he got?
I didn't know.
I've heard more than once
such rumors.
They said you were lucky
when you were young.
You could even meet a wanted criminal
when you went out to buy food.
I never doubted you.
Even if Fan Siyuan
pushed the evidence in front of me,
I didn't have it.
Especially because you were my master
and teacher.
It's because I still remember
the day I was interviewed.
You lied.
It was the effort of our two generations
that made SID
the light of the new state.
Don't let your own will
take away the effort
of the people in your heart.
You not only failed Lao Yang,
but also Huo Xiao.
You failed
to get yourself into the bottom.
You failed to get yourself into the bottom.
Act.
Boss.
We found his passport and ticket
in Zhang Zhaolin's study.
The ticket was at eight o'clock in the evening.
Why didn't he run away?
Something very important must have happened.
He ruined his plan.
Retreat.
Yes.
Chief.
You came at the right time.
Zhang Zhaolin ran away.
Everyone, pay attention.
All the city gates are closed.
Yes.
Chief.
What task do you have for us next?
I want to know
what task you have for us next.
What task you have for us next?
Now the black-handed has been found.
This case is closely related to the special investigation team.
The rest of the case
will be handed over to the surveillance team.
Hand over?
Isn't the person in the surveillance team always there?
Chief.
Whether I'm responsible or not,
I will listen to the organization's arrangement.
But there are some things I have to ask you.
You also suspect Zhang Zhaolin.
You and Chief Luo have been monitoring him.
How did he escape from your eyes?
We don't know.
The person in the surveillance team
is a member of the surveillance team.
We don't know.
You two,
take them outside.
Yes.
Wei Zhao.
You and Chief Luo.
When did you start working together?
Chief.
Thank you.
You came out of the investigation team.
You were taken away from the investigation.
The person who informed you about the body-shedding case
is him, right?
It should be earlier.
The person who agreed to restart the second 0-degree plan
is also him, right?
And
this is an anonymous report.
Those reports
are given to you by Chief Luo, right?
You have already noticed
the existence of the organization and the suspect from the beginning.
In recent years,
Zhang Zhaolin and his team
have been controlling the 0-degree accomplice
and committed several serial murders.
The surveillance team has noticed that
every time the SID intervenes,
they do nothing.
Chief Luo has to suspect
that there is something wrong with the SID.
The SID has a problem.
The Zhang Shouqianlian has withdrawn
from the He Zongyi case.
Chief Luo thinks
that since the cleaners have a plan,
he will take the opportunity
to set up this plan.
Then why didn't you tell me?
Why didn't you tell me
when I suspected you?
Am I unreliable
or are you suspecting me too?
Wei Zhao,
you have been working hard these days.
Go back and have a good rest.
Du Du,
I don't care why the organization
didn't believe me before.
But before I get
the action tonight,
I will not leave.
Du Du,
you are just doing whatever you want.
Once Zhang Zhaolin
is caught by the SID,
he who succeeds in revenge
will probably take the remains
of the cleaners
and sink into the ground forever.
So you should
go back and have a good rest.
I will go back and have a good rest.
So you deliberately
let Zhang Zhaolin go.
You want to use Zhang Zhaolin
to overthrow the SID.
But
you want to
pull off
the two sides of the power chain without any hesitation.
You still have a chance
to get a chance.
So Du Du,
you...
I will go back and have a good rest.
Let's ask Mr. Pei
to go back and cooperate with the investigation.
I will go back and have a good rest.
You don't go.
It's too late, Senior.
If the cleaners
completely clean up the organization,
sink into the ground, disappear and disappear,
everything will be too late.
Why do you have to
put in all your effort
to join the re-establishment plan?
What did you talk to Du Zu?
There is a new lead
who is the first to establish the plan.
How did you know about Zou Feng's case?
I knew that
I had already
figured out the key to the plan.
What is Pei Song doing in the nose?
In fact, the organization has already
figured out the hidden truth.
But if they
try to make a new plan again,
they will only kneel on the ground and beg for the truth.
Then they will have a chance to break their wings.
Did someone contact you?
The cleaners or the organization?
I asked you to tell me something before.
What is it?
I didn't tell you.
But now
I have to go to the inside.
Since they asked me to stay silent,
I will go to the procurator's office now
to be the safest.
We should believe that Du Zu and Lu Chacha
are both dead.
Pei Song is the bait this time.
The Procurator's Office
Du Zu.
Thank you for your protection.
Thank you.
Did Mr. Su from our company
contact you obediently?
Now
can I
gain full trust?
Su Cheng has already taken the initiative
to explain all the operating routes
of Guangyao Fund.
As you said,
there is direct evidence
that Zhang Zhaolin has been
committing all illegal crimes for years.
This also involves
your father,
Pei Cheng Yu.
Du Zu.
I don't need to worry about you.
Since the first call
between you and me,
I have already thought about
all the consequences.
I will go now.
Du Zu.
I am Pei Song.
I am here to cooperate with you.
I think you have always wanted to
separate the organization from the perpetrators.
Luozhao
is a nagging person.
But he has taught me a lot of things.
The most important thing is
that anyone
will be judged
for any illegal behavior.
And this judge
is only a law.
When I called you
on the first call,
I have already thought about it.
No matter who it involves,
in the past 30 years,
I am willing to
hand over
all the grudges and disputes
between the two of you
and the procurator Lu.
I will hand them over to the legal judge.
Du Zu.
Can I know now
that since Zhang Zhaolin
has been exposed,
what should we do next?
Zhang Zhaolin
has been exposed.
As soon as he moves,
we will arrest him immediately.
What about Fan Siyuan?
Fan Siyuan has been hiding
quite a lot.
He has not been exposed.
Although your memory is effective,
you cannot use it as a direct evidence.
So we have to wait
for Fan Siyuan.
No.
I have to go.
We have to wait
for Fan Siyuan.
No.
Why?
Du Zu.
Although you think
you know Fan Siyuan earlier,
but since he started killing people,
he has changed.
He is no longer
the professor of the old Longzhi Hospital.
He is now like Zhang Zhaolin.
He is a devil.
And there is a group of people
around this devil
who are more bitter than hatred,
hard to talk, soft to heart,
and hard to learn.
Once they escape
and sink into the underground,
these little people
will be the permanent bombs
buried in Xinzhou's underground forever.
What do you think?
We have to take the initiative
to turn the situation around.
What plan?
The best way now is
to let Zhang Zhaolin go for now.
Then use Zhang Donglan
to be the bait.
Then let Fan Siyuan
be the bait.
And we
will be the yellow birds
behind them.
Zhang Zhaolin
is a cold-blooded monster
who is completely out of control.
In this world,
except for himself,
he doesn't care about anything.
Except for one person.
The successor of the dark empire he established,
his son, Zhang Donglan.
Now everything is ready,
just wait for the prey to be hooked.
The night I'm still
and waiting in the silence
until you come
and settle well with me
You raise me up
so I can stand on my own feet
to welcome something sweet
And I'm strong
when there's hope in your touch
Hello, Mr. Zhang.
Hello.
I was just thinking
when you would call me.
You really can take it.
You came out from the investigation team?
Yes.
Thanks to Mr. Su.
The company is so big.
I'm in the second team.
Usually it's all thanks to him.
Now something happened.
He ran into Mr. Yu.
I lost my suspicion.
What do you want?
Pei Cheng Yu once told me
he had a ship
and wanted to give me the knife.
Although he may not remember it,
I'm thinking
it's something personal.
I'll take it back.
You're really Pei Cheng Yu's son.
You two are so close.
You're both greedy and vicious.
How can you say that?
I'm better than
that useless Pei Cheng Yu.
I have a special team.
And I have a good relationship
with Mr. Lin.
I don't care about
your relationship with Pei Cheng Yu.
What do you think?
Am I an ideal
partner?
No.
My requirements are not high.
I just need a little loyalty.
I don't need to
be a
loyal and righteous person.
What can I gain
from this?
Mr. Zhang,
you should have
a good experience
about this.
Fan Si Yuan,
that old man,
we didn't expect
that he would
take advantage of you
in this game.
Alright.
You'd better
worry about yourself.
Money,
brotherhood,
reputation,
status,
all of them are gone.
Mr. Zhang,
are you willing to
hide from the world
and live alone
from now on,
or
are you willing
to listen to me
and let me take care of you
and those who
are capable
in your hands?
I'm willing to.
After all,
I have a good relationship
with Dong Lan.
I'm not willing
to see him sad.
How do I know
you didn't cheat?
Mr. Zhang,
you don't
let me cheat anymore.
To be honest,
you used to
hide behind the scenes
and save the country.
Now,
you're sharing
a lost country.
And Dong Lan is in my hands.
If you can give up,
you should be
on the plane to Dong Yue.
I've heard it.
If Dong Lan
is not on the right track,
you'll be in trouble.
I'll send someone
to pick you up.
Mr. Pei,
don't you dare come.
Mr. Du.
Can you
do me a small favor?
not tell them
about our plan?
Although
it seems like
it's a perfect plan,
I'm afraid
it's not the right time
to tell them.
But there's a small problem.
I might not
come back alive.
I'm sorry.
Boss, we found the location of Pei Su.
He's in the airport.
Where is he?
The location hasn't changed.
I'm sorry.
Boss.
Mr. Zhang, everyone is already much better
I Allison's fact
and there are nools
The person in the big room died early.
Search your men for a while.
I've been gone for too long.
The people in the East and the South might be worried.
Something might happen
that no one is willing to see.
Pei Su, don't push too hard.
Let him go.
One hour?
If you don't show up,
I'm afraid it's too late.
Take him away.
Go up.
We meet again,
Mr. Pei.
Go.
Captain Lu, we got it.
The tracking device used by the Du family
is the latest technology.
Once it's connected to the air,
it will record sound and send it back to the cloud.
Hello?
Mr. Zhang.
Long time no see.
Fan Siyuan?
It's him.
You still remember me?
You have Pei Su?
For the truth,
I've been waiting for ten years.
Now it's finally the end.
All wisdom in the world
is about waiting and hope.
Patience and hope
are the driving force
for the future.
They can surely
bring the dawn of dawn.
You still like to pretend to be a god?
Tell me where you are.
The beginning
is the end.
What does it mean?
Where is the beginning?
Could it be Sena and Youan?
Didn't Mr. Pei say
Fan Siyuan wants to kill people with ceremony?
He even wants to take revenge on Zhang Zu
with a gold bar worth 500,000 yuan.
Does he want to burn Zhang Zhaolin
to death in Sena River?
I'll take him to Sena River.
He's not there.
Why?
He's taking revenge on Zhang Zhaolin.
It's impossible
to reveal his location to the third party.
It should be a place
only he and Zhang Zhaolin know.
Then where is he?
Mr. Fang.
So wild.
Your friend
has been attacking me all the way.
I think
this is not the attitude
of the most intimate partner.
Let's go.
Long time no see.
Good boy.
I'm afraid I can't protect you.
I dare to come back to the color in the dream.
No matter right or wrong, I'm just a fly.
Just go forward.
I'm the only one with a wound.
The wind in the dark night,
I'm the only one who doesn't know.
Keep going forward.
The lost step.
The silent silence.
In the silence.
I'm willing to be with you.
The End