[1995]
Yeah.
I'm home!
Did you bring something tasty?
No. It's something better than that.
Ta-da.
Isn't it so stylish?
Isn't it cool?
It's so pretty.
I bought it at a department store at a sale.
Here. Don't I look like a French actress?
Dad told you to be just pretty like a flower.
Don't spend money.
You think flowers only need water?
They become more fragrant with the sun and wind.
If I become a famous actress someday,
I'll be traveling often for shoots.
I invested in myself in advance.
Mom,
let's beg Dad and...
go on a trip.
Should we suggest going to Onyang Hot Springs?
If I carry this suitcase,
they'll think we're traveling abroad.
Wasn't it a good purchase?
- It is.
- Of course, it is.
Let's go. Let's go.
I took too long, didn't I?
My daughter, have you been waiting for me?
[Episode 5. My Love from the Sad Star]
I know this lady.
I've met her before.
Where?
She's from this neighborhood, then.
Are you angry that I took too long?
And you pretend not to know me?
My mom died more than 20 years ago.
Grandma, you're mistaken.
She's not your daughter.
You know nothing. Don't meddle.
She's my friend.
What's this about?
Well...
Gosh. Hello, ma'am.
She lives in that mansion in the forest.
- I see.
- Do you remember me, ma'am?
About two years ago,
you and your husband were leaving the beach
and we gave you a ride on our tractor.
You were too afraid to ride the tractor,
but your husband said, "I'm your seatbelt."
He held you tightly the whole time.
Don't you remember?
My husband is dead.
Aigoo.
I heard you scared wild dogs away.
They're basically like thugs.
They go around in packs.
I gave them sausages.
Good job. Good job.
Ma'am, let's go home now.
Yes. We'll take you back home.
- This is her suitcase, right?
- Yes.
- You carry it.
- Okay, okay.
Let's go.
Hello?
Is this Ms. Lee Ji An?
Yes.
This is Seoul Metropolitan Police Agency.
You know Ms. Hwang Hyeon Sun, right?
Hello?
Why do you ask?
You're her daughter, right?
Well, she passed away in Vietnam.
- So, I'm contacting her family-
- I don't know her.
Pardon?
I said I don't know her.
Why are you out so early?
I didn't know the colors were
so pretty in the early morning.
It beats the evening sunset.
There's a morning smell, too.
It smells like land and sky touching.
That's the luxury of living in the forest.
You're lucky to have a mom like me.
Why did you get up so early, Mom?
Did you not sleep well because of that lady?
No. I don't worry about stuff like that.
Of course, you shouldn't.
All sorts of things happen in life.
- Did you sleep well?
- Auntie.
Seeing you makes me hungry.
You're hungry?
I should show off my skills, then.
Stretch, stretch. Let me rest a bit first.
I love you, Hyo Ri.
Me, too.
Gosh, you sweetie.
Did you sleep well, Hyo Ri?
I'll give you some beef.
Taste it.
What do you think?
It tastes just like short ribs.
Really? It's too soon to be impressed.
I'll work my magic now.
Where's soy sauce?
Yes.
Let's add some.
Here I come. Okay. Come, come.
No one can say no to this.
- Here it is.
- Open it.
Open it. Open it.
- Let's eat.
- Try it.
- What should I start with?
- Let me try it.
It looks so tasty.
Try it. Try it. What do you think?
What do you think?
Tell me.
You can be my mom.
I'm sorry.
- Be my husband.
- Should I?
I'm not that easy.
Is it delicious?
It's great.
Did I make this?
- It's so good.
- So good.
It's missing something.
- Is it?
- It's tasty.
- Just one second.
- What's missing?
Hey, where are you going? What's missing?
It's so pretty.
- Wow.
- Nature is the greatest masterpiece.
"Nature is a masterpiece"?
We have the name of the shop.
"Nature is a Masterpiece."
Hey.
It suits the environment perfectly.
Nature is a Masterpiece.
Yes.
It suits you, too. It's perfect.
Does it suit me?
My body is a sujak*, right?
(Means "masterpiece")
Sujakjil*. Make a pass and you fall for him.
(Means "make a pass")
Hey.
Don't be rude to Unni.
Making a pass isn't a bad thing.
You look a bit old,
but only healthy single women can make a pass.
Who else?
Don't say I look old.
Do you want me to...
- teach you a thing or two?
- You look older than your age.
Lee Ji An, should I teach you a lesson?
Should I? Use your muscles.
Come on!
Where did the old lady go?
Shouldn't we fix up the shop's garden?
- I already asked Bo Hyeon.
- Really?
He did landscaping for Oppa's office building, too.
- Yes.
He looks too studious.
Do you think he could work in the field?
I'm not sure.
He's not studious-looking.
He's reasonable and efficient.
What's his MBTI?
He's obviously ENFJ.
What's his blood type?
Type O, probably. He's positive.
- What's his favorite color?
- White.
He only wears white.
You know everything about him.
You sound like Wikipedia.
I can just tell because I'm smart.
Okay. You have a job since you're so smart.
Friends can talk about anything, right?
Anything?
Like what?
- Friend discount.
- Dream on.
Why? You can bring it up naturally.
It's hard to say no, too.
He might give you a neighbor discount, but-
- What?
- Watch what you say.
Don't say that. Friend discount?
You're putting him on the spot.
Pretend you didn't hear it, Bo Hyeon.
What's with her?
Of course, I can offer it.
But it's farming season now.
So, we're short-handed.
Don't worry about that. She has two hands.
I won't go easy on you or anything.
Want to start now?
Yes. We need to pick something up.
You two go ahead.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
Are you that happy? Look at her smile.
She must be so happy.
Walking so peppy.
Are you that happy, Hyo Ri?
Look at her. She's dancing.
It might not look like much,
but tilling the land is the most important part.
We're pretty much ready here.
Let's put down fertilizer and
plant a few veggies and edible flowers like
nasturtium, violet, and cornflower.
Okay. Got it, but...
this is...
It's...
Seriously.
Look.
Farming isn't just about using force.
Don't just use force.
Dig around the root with a hand plow
and pull out like this... Hold on.
- Use both hands.
- Okay.
Hold on. This is strange.
Move.
- Let's do it together.
- Together?
I'll make sure to pull this out today.
Let's go.
One. One.
- One.
Two. Three.
Hey.
I said I'd pull it out, didn't I?
Wow. I'm a weeding expert starting today.
I'll weed this entire place today.
I'll turn this place upside down.
Dig with a hand plow...
Easy.
Why are you smiling?
Me?
I wasn't. I just have a smiley face.
I'm seeing Tae Oh later.
Let's call it a day.
I'm on a roll. I'll do a little more.
You go ahead.
One more.
Okay...
Crazy. I'm crazy.
Definitely crazy.
If we make this smaller,
we can have some parking space.
Or tilt it a bit to make space.
Okay.
- Fix it.
- Pardon?
Me?
I'm busy with the Forestry Committee project, too.
I need to check all those documents
for the welfare center.
Who's busier? Me or you?
Yes, sir.
- Mr. Ryu.
- Yes.
Here is the invoice for the forest restaurant.
Leave it here.
After I get off-
It's lunchtime.
I have time. I'll go.
I thought he was busy.
Hey, your oppa must have something exciting today.
But he's headed toward our shop.
Why is he going there?
He's too fast.
Hello.
Hey, Hyo Ri.
Oppa.
What is it? Is something going on?
You were in such a hurry.
We came because we were worried.
Well, I wanted to give you something.
- What?
- What is it?
Isn't it a love letter? A love letter?
- A love letter?
- Come on.
I can tell.
Geez, I knew it.
[Invoice for Architectural Services]
Are you that excited to get paid?
It's exciting. It's exciting.
Woohoo!
Have lunch since you're here.
It's lunchtime, right?
Yes, lunchtime.
You must love money.
A little.
Everything's good, right?
It's delicious.
You eat well. Here's the abalone.
Do you like meat or veggies?
- I like meat and veggies.
- Together?
You're so much fun.
I crack up whenever you talk.
Okay. Let's get to business now.
Okay.
I need to pay in this order, right?
Yes.
Is she a guest?
You used to beg me to come.
How could you treat me like this now?
Why do you make your mom
come down out of hunger?
M-Mom?
No, no. Pay no attention. She's a bit ill.
The payment dates are here.
I just need to check the amounts.
It's a bit more than I expected.
The numbers don't add up.
Try adding these two. It's incorrect.
Huh? It really is incorrect.
I told you to be thorough.
You need to care for yourself without me.
Grandma.
Grandma, have you eaten?
Yes, well...
Would you like to eat something? Lunch.
You know I can't come.
Why would you tell me that?
The school needs parental consent.
You can just sign it and hand it in.
Are you doing this to make me feel guilty?
Take care of yourself smartly
based on the situation.
- How frustrating.
- Just die.
I won't have to make a call like this
if you didn't exist.
Just die, I said!
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
Should we discuss money to refresh the mood?
I'd be happy to discuss money with you.
Well, there was one article missing.
I see. One was missing.
Will it change the total?
No, no, no, let's just leave it at that.
Really?
Forget about it.
Thank you.
How nice. It's so airy.
- Isn't it great?
- So refreshing.
Hyo Ri, go home and bring me an egg.
Okay.
Move, move, move!
Gosh. Ji An!
Fire!
Fire.
- Fire extinguisher!
- Get out of the way!
Gosh, wait.
How scary...
Oh, no. Looks like she's in shock.
My goodness.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
- Did you get hurt, Oppa?
- No...
I'm okay.
I got injured here, daughter.
How am I your daughter?
I tolerated you since you're sick.
But I can't take it anymore.
Give me the number of
your daughter, son, or anyone.
I'll call the police otherwise.
Stop. You're scaring her.
Stop? She needs to compensate for the damage.
Mom.
Why are you so angry at me?
Is it because I came too late?
My mom died!
To seek happiness,
she left with a man, leaving me behind
and died in an accident.
I hate to even think about it.
It's painful enough that you're reminding me of it.
So, stop saying I'm your daughter.
I can't take it anymore.
You know she's ill. Why would you berate her?
Keep it together.
You know nothing. Don't tell me that.
Do you know how I endured that time?
Why should I keep it together?
Yeah, I wouldn't know.
Fine. Do as you wish.
Come on.
I'll drive her back home.
Come with me, ma'am.
What are you doing in front of my house?
What the hell are you doing?
Why cause a scene in front of my house?
How ridiculous.
Go home and get to bed if you drank.
Why are you lying on the streets?
Did you buy me a drink?
Huh?
Don't you know who I am?
I'm an actress! An actress!
Give me a break. How ridiculous.
Was she in a TV drama as a passerby
- for 2 seconds?
- Yes.
How many years did you milk that?
Gosh.
Let's go.
My daughter's here.
My pretty daughter.
It's because I'm upset.
I'm upset.
Why am I living like this?
I shouldn't be living like this.
I shouldn't be here like this!
It's so unfair...
What's going on?
Let go.
It's so unfair.
That kid doesn't deserve this.
Her dad cherished her and
raised her with all his devotion.
Hey.
Well...
I won't tell anyone.
Don't worry.
Yes, Mr. Kim.
This is Ryu Jeong Seok.
I have a favor to ask you.
I should test anaphalis and anemone.
I can test them on lines one and two, right?
Huh? What?
What is it?
What do you mean?
This is no good. Let's stop and go there.
I'm not going. I'm not in the mood today.
- No whining. Let's go.
- No, I'm not going.
- Listen to your boss. Let's go.
- I'll work hard, boss.
- I won't be distracted.
- Let's go. Let's go.
You go on your own.
I'm not going anywhere.
We come as a set. Let's go together.
Let's go. Let's go.
Where are you going?
I definitely want to go, too.
There was a fire?
Knowing your mother, she must've been furious.
Yes. I witnessed her fury and rage.
So, did you have a fight with her again?
Wow. How could you fight endlessly?
You have so much energy...
Are you angry that your mom was mean to the lady?
Hyo Ri seems very angry, right?
Don't you know her?
She's not angry.
It's because she feels bad.
She feels bad for the sick old lady
and she feels even worse for you.
That's why, probably.
I'm not angry. I just feel bad.
Since I didn't know how to express that,
I just let it out.
My mom died!
I saw the way she was looking at the lady.
She left with a man, leaving me behind...
Her mom brings my mom...
that much stress and pain.
I could totally feel that pain.
That's why I felt bad.
Once you start not getting along with your mom,
it's hopeless.
Today is my mom's birthday.
I got a call from my older brother this morning.
He said he called just in case I came by.
Mom didn't want me to.
Where should I begin?
I used to play baseball.
When I used to...
be successful as a baseball player,
I got into a huge motorcycle
accident and couldn't play anymore.
After that, I became a total mess and a loser
and upset my mom.
Since then, Mom refuses to see me.
She gave up on me.
So, did you give up on her, too?
One thing I learned from my mom is that
if one of the two doesn't give up,
a family can never cut ties.
That's why I'm curious if you
gave up on your mom, too.
My head... Bo Hyeon, oh, no...
I used my brain too much today.
Well, I will contemplate for a while
and think about the answer to your question. Bye.
Don't sleep.
How could I sleep right now?
Have a good time.
Stop saying I'm your daughter.
I can't take it anymore.
It really must be my time to go.
[Professor Kim Ju Hong]
Yes, Professor Kim.
Of course, I remember.
Yeah...
I can go on my own. Don't worry.
Okay. See you tomorrow.
- Be careful.
- Okay.
- Come this way.
Hello.
- What's the problem area?
- Have a look here.
The valve is here. Please check.
Let's see.
It's the range valve issue.
Since you turned it on while it was loose,
a flame suddenly erupted here.
You should just replace the equipment.
I'm glad you noticed it before you opened.
Hey, what a relief it didn't happen
in front of customers.
Might as well check the gas pipe back there, too.
Gosh, okay.
Today was my day off.
Mr. Ryu came to my office
and kept insisting that I have to come.
- So, I made an exception.
- Thank you.
Let's go.
A blessing in disguise, they say.
Life has its ups and downs.
Gosh, it's too bad.
The technician left. Everything else is fine.
You don't have to worry.
- Okay.
- Geez.
Mr. Ryu never contacts me.
But he suddenly reached out,
saying it was an emergency.
I was so scared for a moment.
I know.
This isn't a big deal at all.
But if Mr. Ryu calls me...
Geez. He never plays along.
Will it cost you anything?
Well, once Bo Hyeon starts settling down,
you should...
consider joining a temple.
It'd improve your personality
and the rest of us won't be so traumatized.
It sounds like a good plan in many ways.
As I always say, I can take care-
Gosh.
Wipe all corners thoroughly. Right here.
Geez.
Does my face make people nag?
It kind of does.
They always nag when they see me.
Why can't you be more thorough?
Hyung will sleep for two nights if we leave him.
Your mom would be worried. You should...
call her in advance.
Are you scared?
I'm not.
Public display of affection is legally a crime.
You and Ahjumma.
Stop showing off your affection.
You're making a person without a mom sad.
Well,
is your mother...
She's in Germany.
Go back on your own.
I need to go somewhere because
of you and Ahjumma.
Because of us?
Where?
Thank you for taking the time to help us.
You went through a lot.
We'll treat you properly to celebrate the opening.
Don't worry about the fire too much.
According to the village tradition,
if you have a fire at your home,
- something good happens immediately.
- Really?
The rice shop owner had a fire last winter
- and hit the jackpot.
- Did his business hit it off?
He got remarried.
To someone 12 years younger!
I've never felt jealous.
Anyway, your daughter is so
smart and looks just like you.
You look like twins from a distance.
- That much?
- Yes.
- I'm a little better looking, right?
- Sure.
She has a good personality, unlike her mom.
- She's a sweetheart.
- Shut your mouth.
I'm sorry. It's my fault.
Let's cut the nonsense and get some rest.
- Take care.
- See you.
Bye.
- Thank you.
Why bring that up?
- Being too honest is my problem.
- Geez.
Why isn't Hyo Ri coming? She must be hungry.
She's not a kid. She can eat on her own.
She probably didn't take her medicine.
She needs to take it on time.
I'm sure she took that, too.
There are wild dogs in our village.
What if she runs into one?
I hope she runs away.
What if she tries to fight it?
Just have a funeral already.
I got too imaginative, didn't I?
Try calling her, at least.
- I don't want to.
- Seriously.
You two are making me old.
Whatever. I'll go inside. Wait for her
to come back, okay?
I don't want to.
By the way, that Ahjussi...
Why can't he bring himself to go home?
I'm leaving.
I don't know where we're going,
but the route isn't so pleasant.
So, why did you follow me?
- I-I think it's a boar over there.
- A boar?
- Hey.
- It's a tree.
No.
You must've committed a lot of sins.
You should've been a nicer person.
Geez.
Don't pretend you aren't scared.
Ever since I saw a real ghost as a kid,
I don't get scared like that.
Ghost?
G-Ghost? Stop lying.
People think ghosts don't have feet,
have holes instead of eyes,
or have a tongue dangling and bleed like this-
Geez.
They think they bleed or something like that.
But that's all a lie.
The ghost I saw looks just like us,
but he kept smiling.
I don't know if we should talk
about this right now.
I didn't know he was a ghost at first.
But I thought, "Why does he keep smiling?"
I looked at him closer,
and his mouth kept widening.
Endlessly.
Hey. I'm not scared of stuff like that at all.
- But what's even scarier is that...
- Yeah.
behind the smiley face, there was
another white face...
It was a branch.
Are you okay?
- You must've been scared.
- Huh?
You got scared by your own story. How funny.
No... I was just acting scared.
How far do we have to go?
I'm tired.
What?
Will you tell me a ghost story again?
Stop testing your courage.
I've never seen this many stars in my life.
It's so nice.
Why did my mom and I make you want to come here?
I come here whenever I'm reminded of my mom.
Because she's an alien.
Around when I was in third grade,
my mom and dad got divorced.
She's been living in Germany since then.
I visited her or she visited me every vacation.
That was the only way I saw her.
So, I always missed her.
Dad.
Yes.
Where's Mom?
She lives on that star over there.
Do you see it? Over there.
That was it.
Mom was an alien.
"Yes.
My mom is an alien.
Unlike the earth moms
who are always by their children,
she has to protect her planet.
That's why she isn't here.
Mom probably misses me, too.
Since the two planets are far away,
we can't communicate well.
I should be patient and wait."
Whenever I thought of Mom,
I comforted myself while looking at the stars.
But hearing about you and Ahjumma,
I was reminded of my mom.
There's a mom like her, too.
She tirelessly tries to land on her daughter's
planet, no matter what.
There's a mom like that, too.
But why is my mom...
And...
you're heartbroken about your mom's childhood.
What star are you from?
I'm jealous.
You two are like each other's first love.
You're awkward, clumsy like first love.
But you're completely sincere.
That makes me annoyingly jealous.
My mom...
is my second mom.
They were apparently childhood friends.
Gosh.
You're good at drawing.
You came.
Their grandpas had stores side by side.
People mistook them for twins.
They wore the same clothes
and had the same hairstyle.
They grew up like sisters.
They couldn't be without each other.
In happy or sad times,
they kept each other company.
They were more than just friends.
Cho Rong,
my mom...
My mom left me.
Anyway, they grew up together,
went to beauty school together,
and moved to Seoul together.
Ji An...
My first mom, who was a single mom,
had a car accident.
That's why my mom ended up with me.
So, we...
are very desperate for each other.
Because we don't take each other for granted,
we've always been desperate for each other.
Because we had to be mother
and daughter more than anyone.
But I guess we've tried too hard.
I got tired...
and my mom doesn't understand me.
On top of that, I...
So, don't be jealous.
You know, Ahjumma?
More than when her mom left her,
she must've felt sadder about
herself who waited for her every day.
Let's go.
She knew she won't come back,
but she kept waiting for her return.
She couldn't give up hope.
And that time she spent hating herself.
That pain lasts longer.
So, go home and give her a hug.
Don't make her wait for you.
Here.
Pretty.
What?
The stars. The stars are pretty.
Yes, the stars, right? I was
talking about them, too.
You're kind of pretty, too.
Aren't you too enthusiastic?
Let me make it clear. I won't pay you extra.
I'm not being excessive. I'm detail-oriented.
Details make a difference in the end.
Does this make any difference?
Just look normally. Why do you hurt your arms?
D-Don't come into my space like this.
Sorry.
I'll go inside.
Y-You raised Hyo Ri well.
You're so harsh to her,
but she says exactly what she wants to say.
She's smart. She turned out well.
I'm no good, but she's great.
Okay.
This is perfect.
Have a seat.
Use your hands.
Extend all the way.
I'm giving you an opening gift ahead of time.
How did you know I like to draw?
I thought a lot about what gift I should get you.
In the end, I wanted to gift you...
the time for you to be yourself.
You must be busy caring for Hyo Ri and the shop,
but you should set time for yourself aside, too.
Roam around the neighborhood on the bike,
stop somewhere you like,
and catch a break.
Let yourself be nothing but yourself.
And that lady...
Don't try too hard.
It's okay if you don't.
I know you very well.
It's okay for you to not try.
You should stop suffering.
You probably never tried,
but run away when it's too much.
That's not cowardly. It's self-preservation.
If you still don't want to run away
and want to endure it,
then, let me know.
I'll support you.
While living here,
rely on nature and people.
You should feel at ease now.
I'll actually tell you everything.
Hyung.
He's not here.
So, did you give up on her, too?
[Mom]
- What?
- Put Mom on the phone.
She doesn't want to see you.
Hand me the phone.
Okay. I'll tell you directly since
you want to hear from me.
It's hard for me to see you.
I don't want you contacting me, either.
You were a successful athlete,
but you ruined your life yourself.
That's when you ruined my life
after I've been devoted to you.
So, are you giving up on your child?
When you suffered from alcoholism,
you abandoned your family first.
Geez.
Please come to your senses.
- You'll hurt yourself!
- Let go!
So what if I hurt myself?
I can't even play. I'm useless.
What a shitty life.
Shit!
Shit. So what if I hurt myself?
So what if I hurt myself?
I broke down because I knew.
I knew so well that your life depended on me.
That's why I broke down when
my career ended. Okay?
Stop playing a martyr. I can't stand it.
I planned this for you.
Wow...
It's quite grand, just like me.
Does looking at the night sky
make you feel close to it
and you feel like the stars are yours?
What are you saying?
Someone told me...
that moms are aliens.
What?
But you're nice for an alien.
Really?
Should you feel that attached to your mom?
[Hyung, have we been hating Mom or missing her?]
Have we been hating Mom...
or missing her?
Why are we so attached to her?
Hey, I think I just saw a shooting star.
Don't lie.
Don't let go.
Should we take a photo?
Let's.
Stand here.
- Here?
- By myself?
Here?
- Take sequential photos.
- No.
Gosh, stop.
Try to be more natural.
Be natural. No, don't look at the camera.
Look at the stars.
Don't look at me and look at the stars.
That's right. That's right.
I'll take one.
Hurry up. My face is going numb.
Hurry, Hyo Ri. Hurry.
Hyo Ri!
Why are we so attached?
[Episode 5]
Some things are leading now
We're looking through the stars and the sun
No need to talk or prove
When you're one that I admire
Live for rather than me
Breathe in and let the ocean flow in
I'll never hear a sound
For you, it leads to where I'm meant to be
What makes my heart flutter...
Honey.
could be too sudden and confusing to others.
I was scared.
Call me when you're having a hard time.
W-What are you doing here?
I feel supported having her around.
It feels like you have a mom, too.
Things got complicated after I got sick.
Do you like her, by chance?
I need to tell you something.
Live forever in me, honey