He's here.
Who is it?
You again?
I left my stuff at your house.
I'll leave when I find it.
I said I didn't see it.
Don't you understand?
Please!
I lost my jade pendant.
Let me go in and look for it.
I'll leave when I find it.
It's just a blood transfusion.
Are you relying on the Huo family?
Get lost!
Please.
I just need to find my own things.
Go away.
Let go!
Please.
I just want to find my jade pendant.
I beg you.
Let go!
Shut up!
My lady.
This woman is crazy.
She just came to donate her blood to Master.
He said he lost the jade pendant.
and insisted on looking for it.
Look.
My mother gave me that jade pendant before she died.
Open the door.
Don't you understand?
Yes.
Thank you.
Is it enough?
Oh.
It seems not enough
Is that enough?
I'm not lying.
I've seen a lot of people like you.
I'm warning you.
Don't imagine things that don't belong to you.
I only want my jade pendant.
If I can't find it,
I'll leave immediately.
Do you think I'll believe you?
Looks like
you're being hard on me.
Let go of me!
My lady.
Please let her go.
Why?
Because
Master is awake.
He wants to see his own daughter.
Lady Ruan.
Long time no see.
Welcome home.
We meet again.
Have you forgotten me?
And I
still thinking about you.
Sister.
Hurry up.
This is what the future master's wife wants.
Hurry up. Over there.
Gently. Gently.
Hurry up.
Hurry up!
Ms Huo.
You are...
Send a message to Wen Liyan.
He doesn’t even know
his Dragon Tiger Gang.
Yes.
Follow me.
How dare you touch Huo's stuff?
Huo Ran, you'll die a horrible death.
Really?
Too bad you can't see it.
What are you doing?
The rope fell off.
Get rid of it.
Yes.
Let's go.
Thank you.
If it weren't for you,
I would have been crushed by the train.
I am a businessman.
I did some small business to make a living.
If Huo Ran hadn't gone too far,
and lowering the price in the name of the Huo family,
I...
I wouldn't have...
Thank you for saving my life.
I will never forget.
One day,
I'll pay you back.
will be today.
Huo Zhi Jie,
Go ahead.
I hate you.
Huo Ran.
I like it
I like, love, love
You're always noisy.
Look at you.
Master, you don't understand.
They are close.
Ran.
How was your trip to the dock today?
Everything went well.
Sorry to disappoint you.
Huo Zhi Jie.
You gave him the money, didn't you?
I...
Brother, I have a suggestion.
If you want to inquire about shipping next time,
don't go there yourself.
Father, don't worry.
Although the information was leaked,
I've taken care of it.
Aunt Mei.
Yes.
Take the money to buy a dress.
Zhi Jie.
Give the goods to your sister.
Ran.
Thank you.
But no matter how busy you are,
take care of yourself.
Yes.
Father.
Did you take care of him?
He didn't die.
He was saved.
What?
Please come in.
Take care, Mr. Huo.
Huo Ting Shan, die!
Catch him!
Master.
How could you leave Ying'er behind?
Everyone.
My master needs blood urgently.
Please help him.
I promise
as long as the blood can match,
five silver dollars.
I won't lie to you.
Mr. Huo seems to be badly injured.
It costs so much blood.
I can't afford it.
Ten silver dollars.
She's coming.
No.
I don't want to.
Are you crazy?
Little girl.
I feed you and feed you.
and make some money.
Stop dawdling.
Behave yourself.
Just smoke.
She's thick-skinned. She's not afraid of pain.
Let's go.
Go!
What's wrong with that fisherwoman?
Why are there two ladies?
You're late.
It's normal that you don't know.
Actually, Ms Huo
was adopted by Her Ladyship.
Ah.
Back then, Madam thought
she was the only child at home.
I was afraid you would be bored.
So I found a girl who is about the same age
to play with you.
Why is there only one left?
I don't know the details.
I think it's a disaster.
Her wife escaped from death.
and carried only one girl back.
and passed away soon.
This has always been the pain in Master's heart.
Don't mention it again.
Okay.
I didn't expect
Ms Huo is usually fierce
is a fake daughter.
Do you think this fisher girl is real?
I really don't know.
I only know that
the Huo Mansion is going to change.
Miss.
Young Lady.
What is this?
Miss,
Madam asked me to...
Miss.
I'll give you a decent dress.
Meizing.
Give it to me.
But Madam told me...
Yes.