By the way,
you asked me to investigate her.
she was adopted by a fisherman.
But...
Just what?
That family didn't treat her well.
She'll get beaten up whenever she's hurt.
Life is tough.
Did I ask you to find out if she had a hard life?
I want to know
why she came back
to come back this time?
Since you suspect Lady Ruan,
why did you ask her to interfere in the engagement banquet?
Aren't you afraid she'll ruin it?
You need to keep dangerous things with you.
That's it. You can leave now.
Lady Ruoxi, this is the pipa.
Young Lady Yu Zhu asked you to send it to her for maintenance.
On the day of the banquet, she wants to play it herself.
Be careful.
This pipa
was left to her.
Her skills
You really live up to your cultivation.
Don't break it.
This is my favorite pipa.
It's okay.
Here.
Do you like it?
Yes.
Try it.
Our lady doesn't like pipa.
It's a waste of your qin skills.
I didn't expect a new lady
to meet you.
Unfortunately, this new lady
Actually...
Hey.
Oh.
Miss, are you okay?
Why did you
Why did you...
This is Miss Leng's favorite pipa.
What's going on?
Oh.
Miss Leng, don't worry.
I'll ask someone to change the strings.
You did it on purpose.
Yes, I don't like it.
I'm not happy.
Do you know
Mother made every string herself?
She mended every crack herself.
Go to the ancestral hall and kneel.
and apologize to Mother.
A fake daughter
really regards other's mother as her own mother.
What did you say?
I said...
Darn it.
Mother.
When you abandoned me,
Have you ever thought
I would return to this mansion one day?
Huo Ran is so nice.
that you can abandon your own daughter
for her.
Do you want to hear
how I've been through these years?
When the train broke down,
I walked
walking in the wilderness.
He fainted in shock.
Fortunately,
There's a fishing village nearby.
A passing fisherman saved me.
Unexpectedly,
he sold me to a human trafficker.
and only got a bag of rough rice.
Can you add some?
This kind of little fool
It's worth it.
Get up.
Go.
Later,
I escaped.
Hello.
Okay.
Cross the bridge.
I fought with a wild dog for rotten rice.
When I was 12,
I learned to blackmail and steal wallets.
Stop!
Stop running.
I didn't shed a single tear
I didn't shed a single tear.
But every time
But every time I close my eyes,
I think of how you let go of my hand.
Mom, help me.
Jiayu.
Huo Ran.
Mom.
But it's okay.
Now that I'm back,
I won't give up easily.
Sister.
Since that engagement is the most important to you,
I'll destroy it.
Boss.
Mr. Tang invited you to dinner when you're free.
Don't pretend to be a good son.
Exactly.
He saw us swallowing the Hong Gang.
to share the soup.
Fortunately, you arranged it in advance.
They will only see old scores
and trash.
Oh, right.
Huo family sent a letter
saying that the dress size
was lost by a servant.
Please go to the tailor shop
to try it on.
Try on the clothes.
Do I need to go in person?
Okay.
I'll tell Lady Ruan
to find a way.
Give it to me.
Mr. Wen, you are here.
Please.
When you broke into my warehouse that day,
when you broke into my warehouse.
Mr. Wen knows I'm a member of the Huo family.
He didn’t say he’s the son-in-law of the Huo family.
You just want to see my surprised face.
Since you're my brother-in-law,
you should be polite.
Your time is precious.
Let's start.
Are you scared?
I'll do it myself.
If you're thirsty,
I'll get you some water.
No need.
Who knows if you'll poison me in the water?
What did you do to me?
Brother-in-law.
Don't you dare?
Thank you.
Brother-in-law.
Boss, what's wrong?
Bad news!
Something happened.
Song Jiayu.
Bastard!
If I put up with it,
people will look down upon us.
How can we face the Huo family in the future?
If you can't bear it,
Longhu Gang and Tang Jing will harm the Huo family.
Don't you understand
Don't you understand?
Don't think I'll treat you like my own daughter.
If you lose your value,
you know the consequences.
Humph.