I can tell you the reason.
Your mother helped me.
And you are her only concern.
Actually,
she never gave up looking for you.
Before she died, I promised her
to protect you.
Is that all?
That's all.
I don't lie in front of my mother.
Burn the incense.
I just want to fulfill my promise.
Don't think too much.
You and I
are destined to be enemies.
Nothing has changed.
Jiayu.
We are enemies.
Didn't you say you lost it?
You have to go.
Don't let her down.
Let's go.
Where can I go?
There will always be
There will always be.
Huo Ran.
I can't leave.
You too.
The only way
is to turn into flame.
But one day,
the fire will go out.
I will let you live.
I believe
I won't lie
I don't lie either.
Do you know why they are there?
Mr. Tang
of course you have your own consideration.
Because they are playing tricks under my nose.
Mr. Huo,
Don't you have anything to say to me?
You must be joking.
How could I?
The drug guide that escaped
was Young Lady Yu Zhu, right?
Huo Ting Shan, how dare you!
Mr. Tang.
I was wrong.
Enough.
Stop acting.
One month.
I'll make sure she gets married.
That girl
to buy time.
One month.
just an excuse.
to lower her guard.
A gentleman keeps his word.
Unfortunately, I'm never a gentleman.
Do you understand?
Father-in-law.
I'll deliver them to you.
Have you checked everything?
Watch the door today.
Don't let anyone out.
Okay.
Count everything.
What is this?
My lady,
These are Lady Ruan's dowries.
How dare you bring shame on this kind of girl?
Forget it.
For the sake of the Huo family,
I'll pick one for her.
You don't have to do this.
Move.
Miss Leng.
Master specifically ordered that
marriage is a big deal.
Before Lady Ruan leaves,
no one is allowed to walk around.
Please forgive me.
Where is Steward Zhong?
Tell him to tell me.
Steward Zhong went home for his funeral.
He's not at home.
Please forgive me.
Goodbye, Young Lady.
I got it.
That day, Master went out in the morning
he went to Tang Jing's house.
Steward Zhong didn't leave the city.
He bought a kind of medicine in the dark market these days.
called
Unconsciously.
It's a hallucinogenic incense.
Tsukki!
I'll find a way to solve this.
You hide it from Lady Ruan.
By then...
Sister.
What are you trying to hide from me?
Tell me.
A few days ago,
Mount Huo went to Tang Jing's hunting ground.
He sealed the mansion after he came back.
Steward Zhong is a trusted aide of Mount Huo.
But now, he lied about going back to his hometown for his funeral.
But he bought some drugs.
I suspect...
You suspect
they want to do it in advance?
What do you want to do?
Let's play along.
I'll take you away halfway.
If you can't hand him over,
Tang Jing won't let Huo Ting Shan off.
Okay.
I'll wait for you to save me.
So obedient.
It hurts.
Just kidding.
Huo Ran.
This is the last time I lied to you.
Our lives are tied together.
I don't want to waste more time to doubt and hide.
Huo Ran.
From now on,
you can't lie to me.
Okay?
Okay.
This way.
Hurry up.
Oh no.
It's all thanks to you.
That's right.
If you hadn't been suspicious,
how could it be so smooth
How did it go so smoothly?
Humph.
Almost.
It's done after this intersection.
Miss.
Who are you?
Looks like I underestimated Mount Huo.
I didn't expect that besides the Huo family,
he has a backup plan.
Jiayu.
Huo Ran.
What are you doing?
I didn't expect
your relationship
is so deep.
Why did you save her?
In your eyes,
your daughter is a living Buddha?
You know better than I do.
How can a kind person
can't stand in Yuncheng.
I'm just not convinced.
Why?
Song Jiayu will be promoted by a noble lady and make a comeback?
I've been working hard for more than ten years.
I can't compare to a country girl.
In this world,
in this world is me.
I was just pretending.
and said something nice.
she takes it seriously.
Shallow.
The Huo family is equally equal.
You don't even understand such a simple thing.
Go back and reflect on your mistakes.
Tonight,
I'll send her out myself.
We'll share weal and woe.
Father.
Are you sure?
Mr. Tang values her so much.
One day,
if she climbs up the ladder,
how can she not forget her origin?
You did give her a life,
but you didn't raise her.
In her heart,
the Huo family is nothing.
Father.
Don't make wedding clothes for others.
Tell me, what should we do?
In the Huo family,
even a dog
even if it's a dog.
Well said.
In that case,
I'll leave this to you.
If you fail,
we must send her out tonight.