WARNING THE FOLLOWING CONTAIN ELEMENTS OF BULLYING.
IT IS NOT TO BE FOLLOWED. VIEWER DISCRETION ADVISED.
SAY NO TO BULLY!
What are you doing?
How naughty.
As usual, those guys are always annoying.
If you want to be responsible,
better to fire her now.
Luckily, there is one man who is very caring.
His name is Jordan. He always helps me.
His smile made my heart flutter.
I warn you, don't get close to Fely.
Me, Naviro, Helga, are tired trying
to make sure she doesn't feel at home here.
If you really don't like me,
I'll get out of this house.
Let go!
Are you not satisfied with insulting me?
Girls are like that when they get angry.
Scarier than me.
Dear Mother,
are poor people considered despicable in the eyes of rich people?
But if I give up,
it means I lost.
She pretends to be good with dad, so that she can win his heart.
After that? Taking advantage of us.
Do you not think like that?
I can't lose.
I have to prove that Raga's words are wrong.
In my heart, I have no intention of taking advantage of your wealth.
Where's the tea?
Ouch.
What are you looking for?
Looking for tea
to make me relax.
Next time, if you need help just say so.
Let me make the tea.
Fely?
-Fely? -Yeah.
Thanks for treating me.
Thank you.
By the way,
next time, if something like that happens,
don't respond it.
Even though I agree,
sometimes they have to be scolded.
So, your suggestion is that I should still be nice to them?
No matter how hard a rock is, it will be crushed by water droplets.
Dear Mother,
today seems to be the deciding factor for me to fall in love with him.
Jordan.
His gentle voice greeted my ears tonight,
like the rhythm of a song before sleeping.
Miss Fely?
Please go to the dining room because it's time for brunch.
We going to visit mom's grave, right?
Dad said yes.
What's wrong?
Is it weird?
Beautiful.
It suits you.
Where are you going?
You look different.
Not going anywhere.
I just want to be neat.
There you go.
It doesn't hurt my eyes.
Not like before.
Well, thanks to Jordan.
He gave it to me.
By the way,
as a token of my gratitude,
I want to cook for you.
What do you want me to cook?
Do not bother.
That's okay. I want to do it.
How about fried rice? Jordan likes fried rice.
Really?
Very fitting.
At the orphanage, I really like cooking fried rice.
Okay then
four portions at a time.
No problem.
But after I cook for you,
you can't be annoying to me.
Just cook it first.
And you'll see.
Okay.
Hi.
What do you need at my stall?
Any special requests?
Can I cook?
You can't.
In this kitchen, the one who can cook is only me.
Okay.
It looks really delicious.
Miss Fely.
Can I borrow
the cauldron? I want to cook fried rice.
-Let me cook it for you. -Don't. No need.
I want to use my recipe for the Four Prince.
I mean for those ugly kids.
Then I'll help you prepare the ingredients.
Okay.
Ta-da!
Who wants it?
This is called orphanage fried rice.
Is it really you who cooks?
Of course.
Okay.
Give it here.
-Are you done? -Not yet.
Don't take too much.
Jordan hasn't gotten the fried rice yet.
If it's for Jordan, it means for us too.
Give me the fried rice.
Here it is.
This is for you.
Thank you.
I'm not lying.
Delicious.
This fried rice is delicious.
Very delicious.
Don't you want to try it?
I lost my appetite just from seeing it.
Okay then. Good.
Raga?
I don't know what this is made of.
But the taste is...
Hello.
-Mr. Johan? -Yes?
Please try it. I made this.
Really?
I'll get it for you.
I'll taste it.
Very delicious.
I remember my late wife
often cooked fried rice like this.
After eating,
let's visit your mom's grave.
Fely?
Are you coming?
Dad, usually only five of us going to mom's grave.
Then I don't have to come, sir.
I want you to get to know my late wife.
Flora.
After eating, we'll leave.
You got a big guts.
You brave to come with us.
Please understand.
They are still adapting to you.
Furthermore, if it's about mom, they are more sensitive.
Alright.
I'm here again, darling.
With our children.
I miss you, Mom.
Mom.
Fely?
You can sow the flowers.
Darling, if you were still around,
you will definitely be very happy to have a daughter like Fely.
Fely?
Lead the prayer, okay?
Praise be to God,
please keep Aunt Flora in Your arms.
Give her the best place by Your side.
And always look after Mr. Johan and his children.
Amen.
You should have rejected my dad's invitation.
Because you're not part of this family.
You're lucky.
You still can come
to visit your mom's grave.
That's why
this should be
my family time.
I'm happy to come along.
So, I come to know
that maybe you treat women like this,
because your mom didn't have enough time to educate you properly.
What's going on, Vin? Good?
-Good Boss. -Good.
Okay then.
Raga, do you want to expand this workshop?
I'm looking for a new place, Dad.
You're great.
You can turn your hobby into a career
at your age now.
I'm proud of you.
Thank you.
I'll go first.
There is a meeting with a client.
Don't come home late at night, okay?
Okay.
Where are you going?
Toilet.
I miss Mom.
Do you know
we are calm
if we visit mom's grave.
I wish she is still here.
Me too.
-Same. -Me too.
Hey.
By the way,
how did you feel just now
when Fely comes along?
Definitely, we weren't the ones who invited her.
Dad invited her.
That is true.
Honestly,
I feel uncomfortable with Fely.
Well, I am not used to
having a stranger who suddenly joined.
Yeah, you're not used to it yet.
After a while you'll got used to it.
There's nothing wrong with him
uncomfortable with Fely's presence.
It is true
she is just a stranger who suddenly appeared in our family.
Fely?
Sorry to make you uncomfortable.
-That's not what it means. -That's what it means.
That's okay.
I understand.
I'll say goodbye first.
You don't need to worry either.
I won't make you feel uncomfortable anymore.
Because soon, I will leave your house.
Mr. Johan?
Where are you going, Fely?
I just want to go back to the orphanage, sir.
But it's late, Fely.
If you miss going to the orphanage,
I'll take you tomorrow morning.
I just want to go back to the orphanage.
Thank you, sir.
For taking me to the grave of Aunt Flora.
That pilgrimage was very memorable for me.
But
before the conflict with Helga, Naviro or Raga arises,
I think it's better if I just get out of here, sir.
Come with me.
There's something I want to show you.
Since my wife died,
I didn't display anything of my wife in this house.
Because I don't want
my children to always get reminded of their mother's absence.
But when I'm alone,
almost every day I watch this video
in memory of my wife.
Sit down, Fely.
Hi darling.
Looks like it's very busy.
Of course.
Here's to welcoming my cute baby.
That's why everything has to be neat.
Darling?
I want to know
what do you wish for our first son?
I wish that
our first baby boy is healthy
and safe.
Also be a tough guy.
And look just like me.
After this we'll have a baby
girl, huh?
You've heard it yourself, right?
What is my wife's wish that has not come true?
You haven't stay for three months yet.
I just started feeling the warmth in this house
since your arrival in our family.
But, sir...
Fely, I know
it's hard to get close to my children.
That's why I asked for help so that you can enter Budi Dharma.
So that you all can be in one house and one school.
Isn't it your wish to study at Budi Dharma since long time ago?
So, you can have lots of time to get to know each other.
Fely?
Thank you sir.
It turns out that you gave me opportunity to go to Budi Dharma school.
That means a lot to me.
I have long wanted to go to a top school.
Because I want the best education for you.
You have to be a successful person.
So that you can help your younger siblings at the orphanage.
And be able to find your biological parents.
But I beg you,
please
stay here.
At least
for three months as per our agreement.
If you're still uncomfortable later,
I will take you back to the orphanage myself.
Excuse me.
-Please. -Thank you.
-Thank you. -You're welcome.
Finally, there is a girl that you would choose.
We can go on a double date.
Same. Me too.
Don't fall in love to my crush.
You're the one who shouldn't like the girl I like.
Impossible.
My tastes are much higher than yours.
Okay.
What's important is getting married together, right?
Certainly.
Hi.
Sorry you guys waited too long.
-Sit down. -Please sit.
Thank you for coming.
You're welcome.
I should be the one saying thank you.
I invited her.
What are you doing? I invited her.
More precisely, it was the two of you who invited me here.
When you invited me,
I deliberately chose this place.
So that the three of us can meet together.
So tell me. What's going on?
Everyone, let's go downstairs first.
I've got pizza for all of us.
Come on, quickly.
Please eat. Where...
Let's eat.
We celebrate because we managed to get Fely out of the house.
Come on.
Hello.
Who said that?
I will stay here.
You said you wanted to leave?
Yeah, but it doesn't happen.
Besides, it's up to me whether to leave or change my mind.
What a drama queen!
Hey!
You are the devil king.
What the hell? Hey, who let you eat?
Very delicious.
Just act normal. No need to overdo it.
Watch out!
Usually if you like to fight, later on you will love each other.
Hoax girl.
It was she herself said that she wanted to leave here.
Who told you to be easily lied to?
You...
Can you stop following me?
Don't follow me just because you're my twin.
Who wants to be your twin brother?
You just never want to give in.
It's rare that they fight like dogs and cats.
Where are you going?
Music room.
Why do you keep looking at me?
Don't flatter yourself. Who keeps looking at you?
Hi, Fely. I'll go first, okay?
Hey!
What are you doing? Return it.
-Borrow me just for awhile. -Nope. Return it.
-Two minutes. -Nope. No cheating allowed.
One minute. Okay, 30 seconds.
-Thirty seconds. -You can't cheat.
Give it back! This is mine.
So stingy.
Do your homework at home, not at school.
Fely?
Annoying!
Let me borrow your homework. Thank you.
I like Raga.
It's been a year.
So what does that have to do with me?
Obviously there is.
Because you're flirtatious,
attention-seeking,
sassy.
From now on, it's better that you stay away from him.
Moreover,
you're just an orphanage kid.
Not suitable for Raga.
Aren't you the same?
No need to bring up the orphanage!
Quiet!
You start it first.
I didn't expect you to change like this.
You're like this because you want to be considered cool
and commensurate with them?
Is this so important to you?
Fely, you won't exposed me, right?
What do you think?
MY ALBUMS
ORPHANAGE
Why are you taking so long in the toilet?
Watch out! Did you post a picture?
Who is it?
Just act normal. Why is your face so pale?
Nothing happened.
Okay. You'd better go to class first.
Why are you guys so curious? Go.
Sassy.
Sorry.
Are you going home?
I am involved in extracurricular cheerleading.
So, what time do you come home?
Afternoon.
Why do you ask?
Alright.
Good then.
So random.
Hi, Fely.
Let's go to the field. The others are waiting to practice.
Okay.
Hi guys. Welcome to the cheerleading club.
Before we start,
I want us all to warm up first.
Starting with you. Count from one to eight, alright?
Follow the clockwise direction.
Okay, let's go.
Let's go.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
Lastly, the feet. Let's go.
Let's go, guys.
Budi Dharma let's go!
Pay attention to the senior first.
Five, six, seven, eight.
One, two, three, four.
Chicken heart formation.
The key is for the flyer to look one way ahead.
Don't look down, you will be afraid of falling.
The key is that the flyer has to trust the base.
Four, five, six.
Now I want one of the juniors to try being a flyer.
I want Fely to be the one.
But
it's my first time.
If you're always afraid, when will you be able to do it?
Come on.
I'm the base. You can trust me.
I'm scared.
You have to trust me.
The key is trust.
-Okay. I'll count. -Okay.
-Five. -Five, six, seven, eight.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight. One.
Hold.
Five, six, seven, eight, one, two, three, four.
Ouch.
Fely?
Climb onto me, Fely.
No need, Jordan.
I can walk by myself.
-Climb onto me, let me carry you. -That's okay.
Ouch.
But your feet hurt. Let me help you.
Wait!
Jordan wait.
Let me go.
I don't want to look weak in front of Chloe.
Open it!
We'll open this door in an hour.
Watch out if you're still fighting.
This gift is to express my feelings for you.
Me too.
We like you, Monica.
-This way, Fely! -This way, Fely!
I told you. Keep your distance from Fely.
You will destroy our plans to make her uncomfortable with us.
Chef, can you cook something that contains a lot of seafood
but it doesn't get noticed?
This has shrimp in it. Are you allergic to seafood?