《I Will Never Give Up》
我的生命从不为谁后悔
陪你浪漫燃烧直到熄灭
珍惜生命中的每次眼泪
有天我会勇敢不再更叶
而我盲目的追 低头妥协
想保护着谁
我想许愿 拥有你的明天
我只想在我一边
每天都能将面对
生命总会有机会
而你准备要浪费
在我一边
《I Will Never Give Up》
It hurts! What are you doing?
You're going to eavesdrop on it.
I'll close the door and open it.
If you're going to eavesdrop on it,
it's not going to hurt your ears.
Go away.
Sit on my bed.
Sit.
No.
How did you know my house was here?
I wanted something from Uncle Sun.
I wanted to tell you.
You wanted to be with me?
No.
I wanted to say I knew it wasn't your house.
How did you know it wasn't my house?
You're not that kind of person.
You're not going to marry me.
I don't care if you believe it or not.
I know it wasn't your house.
It must be the midterm exam.
They thought you hated me.
That's why they used this method.
You don't have to come to the court.
But...
But I came.
And I said it was my house.
I said the photo was taken by me.
You've never been to a bar.
You were beaten and locked up at home.
I know you know what I mean.
I don't.
I believe you know what I mean.
I know.
You've always liked me.
I didn't.
You didn't?
Liu Meifeng gave me 132 photos of you.
How could that be?
Don't lie. I have evidence.
This one.
Your vision is on me.
I used the red circle to look up.
You said you didn't.
Yes.
I did look at you.
Of course.
You said you didn't like me.
I didn't like you.
I was just curious.
Curious?
What are you curious about?
I...
You know I care about my grades.
So I go to the school card.
The second-place exam...
I got the second place in the school.
Yes.
I was four points behind.
I thought you were my rival.
I was wrong.
You were my rival.
Wait.
No way.
So you started to notice me because of this?
Yes.
I thought...
But after that, you kept your discipline.
I thought you were special.
I did whatever I wanted.
I didn't get restricted.
I didn't care about others.
It's like...
You were holding everything in your hands.
Don't praise me.
I'm not praising you.
I really envy you.
What?
I can't be like you.
Why?
I don't want to burden others.
I can't be the burden of others.
Why?
How can you be the burden of others?
I really envy you.
I grew up with my aunt.
She got married and had a baby.
She was tired.
I had to be independent.
I had to be strong.
I had to rely on myself.
I really want to be like you.
I can laugh and be angry.
I can easily be a burden to others.
I don't care about being punished or sent to prison.
Just looking at you...
I feel a little bit more independent.
Do you know?
After I met you...
I started to think...
I thought...
If parents didn't leave so early...
Would everything be different?
From now on, you and I...
I will give you everything I have.
When it's time to
I'm sorry.
You're right.
But Xiang Hao Ting is still protecting him.
Listen.
Xiao Guo won't have any problems if you don't date him.
Don't hate Xiang Hao Ting.
If you know him longer,
you'll know he's a real man.
You're saying you're a real man after a few years.
You're old enough.
I'm angry.
You're angry so easily.
That means you're still a little boy.
But you're my little boy.
Whatever.
My brother sent me to work out this week.
Why don't you come to work out later?
Go to work with me.
Okay.
Did you work out that day?
I was so busy.
Okay. Did you work out that day?
Let's go.
Okay.
Good morning.
Breakfast.
I miss you so much.
Why did you call me?
I prepared breakfast.
You eat that.
And eat that.
I prepared it.
Thank you.
You really want to give it to me?
Of course.
I'm sorry.
Actually, I have one more important thing.
Please.
My dad is still angry.
I want to say that
I'll do better next time.
To make him happy.
Please count me as the second place.
I'll do better next time.
Okay.
You're so good at your homework.
It's no problem.
And I can follow you.
I'm not working.
I'm at school.
I'm going to study.
My class schedule is less.
Especially on weekends.
Then let's do it on weekends.
Okay.
I'll go to your house on weekends.
Thank you, Mr. Yu.
Okay.
Go home. Don't be scolded.
I'm going to class.
You like this?
Don't you think it's cute?
What's its name?
It has no name.
Just call it Xiao Bai.
Xiao Bai?
Xiao Bai.
Xiao Bai, eat jelly.
Yu.
Eat chocolate.
I'm going to work.
Okay.
I'll go to your house on weekends.
I'm going to class.
Okay.
I'm going to work.
I'm going to class.
Okay.
I'm going to work.
I'll go to class.
Okay.
What's wrong with her today?
She said that her classmate is coming to teach her.
Is she working?
I don't know.
Come here.
Is she a girl?
If she is, the door will open.
Yu Xi Gu.
Hello, I'm Hao Ting's classmate.
I'm Yu Xi Gu.
Not bad.
She's awesome.
She's the best in every class.
She's the best student in the whole school.
You're so nice.
Welcome.
I'm glad you have a good classmate.
Come here.
Sit down.
She's coming to study with me.
Don't disturb her.
Okay.
Go to work.
Do you want to eat or drink?
I'll prepare it.
Thank you.
Mommy.
I saw this person in the phone.
She didn't let me talk to her.
I think it's weird.
It's okay.
It's a boy.
Since it's a guest, you should prepare to eat.
I drew some points.
Put it away.
I'll do it later.
Come with me.
Call me.
I want to make your dad happy.
You're happy when you come to my dad.
You said studying hard won't be a waste of time.
I have.
Focus.
I'll study.
I've always been modest to teachers.
But I don't have to be modest to face the truth of the new person.
People who recite usually should know...
Hello.
Mommy.
Be careful.
You've worked hard.
Drink some water if you feel sore or tired.
And fruit.
Don't be shy.
Why don't we eat some apples now?
Here.
Thank you.
I want to thank you.
Why are you so naughty?
Auntie.
Mission accomplished.
Yes.
Keep going.
Mom, close the door.
I'm more focused.
It's reasonable.
If you're free tonight,
you can stay for dinner.
Auntie, don't bother.
It's okay.
Keep going.
I'll do my best.
I'll go get ready.
Love you, mom.
Goodbye.
Bye-bye, mom.
Mom.
Goodbye.
Bye-bye.
line
Miwa
Bye-bye, Miwa wildly.
Miwa.
Goodbye.
You're fine by yourself, right?
I'm fine.
I'm looking for a girlfriend.
Okay.
You have to clean up everything.
Also, I know.
The equipment is back in place.
The lights are off, so you can get some air.
The security system.
Yes, yes, yes. I remember.
Don't worry.
Shhh.
Hello, Baby.
Yes, I'm on my way. I'm almost there.
I'm downstairs at your place. In five seconds, he'll...
Five, four, three, five, five...
Do you have a ticket?
No.
Hurry up and pack up. I'll take you to eat later.
Okay.
Why are you here?
For you.
You must be tired from working so hard.
Be considerate.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Merry Christmas.
Happy Birthday.
But I'm not ready.
I have you.
Yes.
What are you doing?
I'm happy.
Idiot.
Let's go.
Wait for me.
What are you doing?
I'm calling a cab.
No, it's expensive.
How do you get home at this time?
At the convenience store.
I have my books.
You just finished work. What books are you reading?
You need to relax now.
I'll take you to a place.
I don't have a bus right now.
I have a car.
Ta-da. Get in the car.
I have everything you want.
Is it convenient?
Idiot.
Let's go.
Follow me.
Wait for me.
Where are we going?
I can't tell you yet.
Why?
Where are we going?
It's almost done. I'll help you later.
Okay.
I'm sorry.