《I Will Never Give Up》
我的生命从不为谁后悔
陪你浪漫燃烧直到熄灭
珍惜生命中的每次眼泪
有天我会勇敢不再更叠
而我盲目的追不低头妥协
想保护着谁
我想许愿拥有你的明天
我只想在我一边
每天都能叫面对
生命总会有机会
而你准备要浪费
在我一边
Miss
Sorry, sorry
Is there any other color in this?
Yes, blue and yellow
Where is this?
That one over there
Okay
Brother
I remember that Phoebe also likes to wear
Dali's colorful clothes
Yes
How do you think of this one?
Not bad
You don't have a phone
So you can't go out without it
You have to keep drawing
I believe in your taste
Do you think this one suits her?
Since we came in
The staff there has been looking at you
Xia Houding
You are?
I didn't expect to meet you there
Girls go to your store there
What a coincidence
If I can hang out with old friends like this
That would be great
Tony's
It feels good
Are your eyes real or fake?
They are real
When did you start wearing glasses?
And wearing necklace to pretend to be Wen Qing
You have changed a lot
You haven't changed a lot
Of course, I am Li Siyu
I told my boyfriend that
I look like a high schooler
Did I?
You look more mature and stable
than before
Where did you go when you were like a crab?
I didn't expect that
You changed a lot
I was so happy
I didn't expect that
You have changed a lot
How about you?
Are you doing well?
I am doing well
I thought it would be easy to find a job after graduation
But I didn't expect it to be so easy
So I went to this company for an interview
and worked as a waitress
I didn't expect that
your sister likes our clothes
Tell her to come to me next time
I will give her a bonus
Ok, thank you
You are welcome
Where did you go to college?
I just graduated from college
You are so talented
You are the captain of the award
You are the best student in the school
You are the most promising student
The next lucky boy is you
You are so blinded
I took the postgraduate exam for 2 years
and I only got into the physics department
Physics department?
Really?
That's so hard
You got into the physics department after you graduated
We didn't have the chance to find a job at that time
That accident was so sudden
I heard from Meifang that
she didn't have a parents
So
she is the aunt of her parents
She wants to be simple and low-key
No one knows the time and place of the farewell
So I can't see the end of the journey
I will miss you
If I didn't see you today
I wouldn't miss him either
I know you are doing well now
I am so happy for you
I will miss you
You are Yu Xigu
I really like you
I love you
The deepest comfort
Then I bring you by my side
Your tears
I hurt you
I want to say it gently in the rain
I have washed it
Bye
Everyone is looking for you
Do you know why we are worried?
What are you thinking?
I have changed
We have changed
But he hasn't changed
When time still stays at 18
I can only go on
The sky will not come down
I always want to be able to pull into the galaxy
So I keep climbing
Keep going
Can go closer to the starry sky
It seems that I can touch the stars with my hands
Can touch it immediately
I can't
Exactly
Even if I want to get closer to him
In fact, the distance between me and him is
It will get further and further
He is still 18 years old
Only I changed
I am very afraid
I am very scared
But he is 18 years old
You have always been 18 years old
I still
I still often dream of that intersection
That car
He is lying there
But I have no way
I can't do anything
Finally
The things left are really familiar
But you know
You know, every one is a picture
Every one is a memory
That thing stuffed me so full
Full that I can't hold it anymore
What
You know
I have been trying to forget him
I can't do it
The only thing I can do is to remember him
Remember
Live with him
But I'm really in pain like this
I really miss him
It hurts to be hurt
I can't hold it anymore
You don't need to forget him
You just need to keep going
You have brought him here
If you can't find the direction
You follow the current you go
How can you get out
I can't
I really don't know how to walk alone
How about you
You can walk alone from here
I can't
It smells so good
Dad, you are getting better
I didn't know you have this
Unknowing talent
You are good at playing cards
You are not inferior to the breakfast restaurants outside
Is it delicious
Then call it like mommy
You say it yourself
Oh, no, Xiao Ting
Xiao Ting, get up, don't sleep anymore
Didn't you ask me to call you
It's more than ten o'clock
You have an appointment with someone, right?
She came back so late last night
She can go home and let her sleep a little longer
I want her to sleep longer too
But she didn't answer the phone yesterday
I called her twice in the morning
She's back to the store
Sister, come to eat
Sister, come on
Xiao Ting, get up
Don't sleep
Sister, come on
Xiao Ting
Go to bed
Come on
Good morning
My head hurts
Headache
Sister, go get the portable phone
She must be drunk
She came back last night and drank a lot
Yes, she must have drunk too much
Why don't you go home and go to the convenience store
Buy some alcohol
Okay
Dad, you are biased towards her now
Okay, brother is going abroad
We don't have much time at home
Don't mind your brother and sister
Go quickly
Hao Ting
I said Phoebe is a good girl
Okay
Phoebe
Yes, you have to remember
Don't say it wrong when others come
It's embarrassing
Phoebe is a good girl
You went abroad with her this time
Do you want to get used to it?
If you think it's good, just settle down
Such a good girl
If you are not sure
It's easy to be chased by others
Really, dad is right
Good girls are not desirable
And you two are so fated
You two are so talkative, right?
But if you have any plans
You have to tell others in advance
Don't delay others
I'm going to take a shower
Come and eat after you finish washing
Dad made it
You are not answering
I didn't answer
Continue asking after you finish washing
Dad, what are you cooking?
It's burnt, right?
My hot dog
You can't be the boss
Uncle, you are back
Why are you suddenly here?
I came to see you
What have you been busy with recently?
I just finished filming
I'm so tired
Thank you
Cool
I can imagine your life
You don't have to imagine
It's not made by people
Busy man
Why are you free today?
Okay
I'm thinking
How to apologize to you two
For the mistakes I made before
Why do you want to apologize?
I know how to draw
What do you mean?
It's okay if you have something to say
That healthy food
Grandpa didn't want me to give it to you
I thought that's all
But it has other meanings
What else?
I hope you two
Don't give it to me anymore
If grandpa doesn't like those things
We can give you something else
It's not about giving something
No matter how much you give
Grandpa still can't understand
Grandpa wants to say
Wait
If it's those negative things again
You don't have to say it
You two can imagine
Grandpa wants me to tell you two
Uncle
You can go home
You said
Can you go home by yourself?
Grandpa allows you
You can go with me
I
I can do it too
Did you just say
Are you serious?
Grandpa is waiting for you two to go back
I'll go see him
You sit down
Okay
Don't cry
Isn't this a happy thing?
I'll go home with you tomorrow
I'll go with you
I'm here
Where are you
At five, is it Сам worldwide
Yes
I'm at the beach
You came to Am testing
This feels like Ser tiring
Hello
I'm Yibo
Yummy
Are you eating swap?
Come here
No
Ah
Excuse me
Wei
I'm going abroad.
I'll call you,
send you a message,
and you'll disappear.
Don't even think of being my brother.
I won't.
What about after you?
What's your plan after you finish your studies?
I want to stay abroad for another two years.
I want to go to different places.
I want to meet people and do more things.
This world is really big.
Really.
I've been wanting to ask you something.
It's okay if you don't want to answer.
You told me that you don't like boys.
You only like girls.
But now you meet him.
Why don't you have feelings for him?
Or do you want to try?
Because no one can be him.
I'm here.
I'm going to the Himalayas.
I think I'm ready to see them.
Don't keep talking about me.
What about you?
Do you have any plans?
You're all blushing.
Plans?
I really want to get married.
But he's very busy.
Busy.
I've told you before.
And you know that day,
we argued because of the little dog.
I found out that we argued about something
that's very complicated.
When I read it,
I couldn't stand it.
Do you know what we argued about?
I said I wanted to raise a soldier.
He's very handsome.
He said he wanted to raise a bean.
The cute thing is,
we argued and argued and argued
and argued about something.
We decided to go to the zoo together.
He said he wanted to remove the dog from our family.
What do you mean?
Just let him raise you.
I'll raise him.
Please.
I still don't understand why you left.
I still don't understand why I'm waiting.
Waiting for someone to remember their dependence.
I'm wandering alone in the abyss.
When the blue sky and white clouds disappear,
When the red shoes and red coat take you away,
When all colors leave with you,
My tears don't stop falling and accompany me.
I still don't understand why you left.
I still don't understand why I'm waiting.
Waiting for someone to remember their dependence.
Why can't I stop crying?