Every tear in my life
Someday I will be brave and never change
And I'm blinded by it
I bow my head and compromise
Who do I want to protect?
I want to make a wish
To have your tomorrow
I just want to be in my side
I can face it every day
Life will have an opportunity
And you are ready to waste it
One more time
The End
Hey, it's itchy!
What are you doing?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I...
Are you okay?
Are you afraid of me?
I'm sorry.
You didn't mean it.
Thank you for coming.
Black sugar cocoa bread is delicious.
Remember to try it next time.
Bye bye.
The most exciting Pg game on the line.
The mahjong is over.
The golden queen.
Find the treasure of the golden city.
Summon the rich cat.
The golden captain.
The highest target is up to 500,000 times 100,000 times.
The next lucky child is you.
Macau New Peking Entertainment City 9 31931.com
You watch something?
I didn't.
I think Xiao Mu is strange.
It seems he has something on his mind.
Yes, he has something on his mind.
He is going out with Xiao Ping tomorrow.
I'm going on a trip.
Are you jealous again?
You care about him, you care about me.
Every day, besides sleeping for four hours,
the rest of the time is not with you,
but with you.
What about when you sleep?
Did you have a dream about me?
Did I appear in your dream?
Yes.
And you told me that you would go out with me for two days and one night.
Okay.
You said it?
Yes.
Ming Hao Tian and Xia Erlin, they are a double date.
Ming Hao Tian, good night.
Good night.
Don't be shy.
I'll just ask Judy to come to work.
Okay, I'll arrange it.
You decide.
Then, I'll see what's delicious.
Food, food, looking for food.
Dad's stone soup.
Very romantic, want to eat, want to eat.
Finally arrived.
Damn, this is like Paris.
How is it? Have you been there?
I have.
Then, you can go with me in the future.
What about your staff?
Even if there are staff, they will take me there.
It depends on your performance.
You're so smart.
I'll check in first.
Wait a minute.
Take a picture first.
Take a picture.
Xiao Lu, come here.
Come, come take a picture.
Hurry up.
It's rare to come out and play.
One, two, three.
Be happy, come out and play.
Okay, okay.
I'll take a picture with you.
Hello, are you Mr. Xiang?
This is your room card.
Thank you.
Please help me pick up the information.
Yours.
Yes.
Xiao Gu, what's wrong?
You don't like this environment?
No, it's beautiful here.
Come on, let's go and see.
Okay.
Go, go, let's go up.
Go.
Sorry, I'm sorry.
Excuse me, you only have a double bed.
There are no two single beds.
Yes, our rooms are all double beds.
Okay, thank you.
You're welcome.
Xiao Gu.
Like to experiment possible inventions.
I'll go take a look.
The house is really pretty. You can take a walk.
But...
The key is here.
I'll be back later.
I'm so sorry.
Zilan, I really don't know what to do.
He asks me if I'm afraid of him, but I'm not.
I really like to be with him.
I really like to see her smile at me.
But I really don't know why it's like this.
As long as she treats me well,
and gets close to me,
I'll...
You want to get away from her?
Yes.
This is love.
She does this because she cares about you.
If you really have any problem,
just tell her.
You have to have confidence in yourself.
Believe in your true feelings.
Be brave and follow your heart.
It's almost time.
You can go to eat.
I really like you.
I'm so happy every day
when I'm with you.
I'm so happy
that I can have everything.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry that I pushed you.
I've never liked anyone.
So I'm afraid.
I don't know where I can
be loved.
I'm sorry.
From now on, you don't have to be afraid.
Because you're here.
You're the perfect person for me.
I love you.
I love you too.
I'm sorry.
We're out for fun today.
You should take a break too.
Where are you going?
I'm going there.
Go.
Go to your own home.
I can't stand you.
It's already 7.30.
Why hasn't Xiao Ting come yet?
I'm serious.
Don't you think they're weird today?
I've been bored
since I entered the restaurant.
Come out and play.
Be comfortable.
Come on.
Don't be naughty.
I won't.
I'm sorry.
No.
This restaurant is specially reserved for Xiao Ting.
If she doesn't come,
what will she eat?
I'll call her.
Si Mu Qiang.
You've been saying sorry since you sat down.
Do you love me?
If you keep doing this, I'll go to the next room.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Eat.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
You said you didn't.
You're so naughty.
No.
I love to eat.
But I like it.
You're so naughty.
Xiao Ting?
Xiao Ting.
I'm sorry.
You should have told me earlier.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
I have to leave now.
You don't have to.
That's right.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Xiao Ting.
Hey!
Are you shooting an ad?
What do you know?
This is romantic, okay?
Romantic?
Yeah.
Let me help you.
Have you said it?
I said it.
Let's do it again.
Okay.
Let's go travel the world, okay?
We can go to Africa,
see the elephants,
and the long-distance road.
Then we can go to the island of ice to see the aurora.
We can go to the Arctic to see the aurora.
Or we can go to Siberia.
Wait a minute.
The Arctic doesn't have aurora.
The Antarctic has aurora.
You're laughing at me.
I don't know
how you got into the college.
I did it with my heart.
With your heart?
Are you sure?
I'm not sure.
Look at this little boy.
He's going to be a bullfighter.
Come on.
Give me a kiss.
Okay, don't be angry.
Let me ask you.
If you could choose one place to go,
where would you go?
I can only choose one place?
I want to go with you...
Back to my room.
No.
Why not?
I want to go back to my room.
You want to sleep?
Yes.
You want to sleep so early?
I can't sleep.
No.
Morning.
Don't I feel like...
Good morning.
I think it's all because of me.
Little Hola Max is a distance like agencies.
So they already know
that I can be arrogant.
Great.
But I wanted to tell them
that часто.
I'm sorry.
Let's have breakfast.
I don't want it.
Then what do you want to do?
I want to hug you all day today.
I don't want to go anywhere.
Gu.
Come and look.
It's not wrong.
I'm sorry.
Hey, you only have this one.
My parents bought it for me.
They said it's easier to travel like this.
You can go to the train station.
So cool.
But don't you have a driver's license?
It's hot.
I just got it this morning.
Your app is very powerful.
Of course.
I'll help you.
Okay.
It's raining heavily.
Do you still want to ride?
Of course.
Don't you think it's romantic to ride in the rain?
You are the first person I want to be with.
Let's go.
But won't the car break down?
How could it be?
Get in the car.
Let's go.
Okay.
The weather is really like you.
Why?
Just change.
The more you eat, the more dizzy you are.
It's raining.
I hope it won't rain again.
Trust me.
It won't.
Why?
Because my sun is right behind me.
Zhongli and Taipei are really far away.
Okay.
I'm worried about you.
You are making excuses again.
You said you didn't have time to study.
It's possible.
Call the police.
Okay.
I'm sorry.