SKIPPING CLASS TODAY?
WANT TO HANG OUT TONIGHT?
How?
Do you want to jump again?
You are crazy?
I never wanted to
suicide, never.
Just feeling tired.
Don't want to meet anyone.
I see RJ
and he keeps looking for you.
I know. It sucks.
Look.
He likes to send me his photos
bare chested.
If he wants to make love,
then he should use his money...
...instead of doing this
to others.
What is so funny?
I laughed at RJ.
You want to know the secret?
What secret?
He is gay.
What?
- Are you serious?
- Correct.
Who am I?
I am not Makham,
I'm not rambling.
If I knew
someone's secret...
...then it must be true.
Why is he trying to approach me?
He is still confused
with himself.
One must
pass through this phase.
Don't be mad at him, okay?
What?
You don't believe me?
It is not like that.
Just confused
how do you know the secret.
My special talent.
Queen is not
gossip loving type.
If that's the case...
...then he can't
be my friend.
But he knows
the secret of many people.
Hard to believe...
...he keeps his secret
like this.
I told you so
someone like Queen...
...shouldn't be friends
with anyone.
I don't know why he did this.
For fun
or does it satisfy him?
Queen didn't do it
to find excitement.
He keeps this information
for later use.
If so,
I have to keep my secret.
What should we do?
with the others?
Should we return it?
to the owner?
Maybe we can
watch it first.
We can find
something useful.
You better not.
This is a secret.
We should
not violate it.
How?
We'll talk about it later.
I'm more worried
Gale's safety.
Of course, Toy.
I will be here with you.
I will not run away from you.
I will stay here,
by your side.
I will wait to see
your life burns in hell.
I will be by your side.
When you're not paying attention...
...I am...
...which will
ruin your life.
What do you mean?
It's not that complicated.
You don't let me go.
You can't expect
everything will be the same.
Okay.
When the time comes...
...you will understand...
...if you and I
inseparable.
Yes, I am a monster.
I'm a bad man.
How about you?
You think
you are better than me?
So I need to thank you
to Queen?
Because it makes me
see your true self.
You are just…
Watch your attitude.
You have to accept...
...that your life and my life...
...already tightly bound.
If my life is ruined,
so is your life.
I told you...
...From now on
nothing will be the same.
I won't let you be the only one
the person who destroyed me.
RJ
Hello? What do you want?
I've had enough of this.
Enough? Enough with what?
I will be honest
to the police.
What's wrong with you?
You still don't understand.
Everything is out of control.
I can't either
contact Guy.
And I don't know if Peanut
say something to the police.
Unlucky.
You said your parents
help hide him.
That's what I know but who
who knows the truth.
Unlucky!
Listen to me.
I don't care...
...their words
to the police.
But you have to keep your mouth shut.
You understand?
Give me money.
What did you say?
I will hide
at another place.
And I need money.
How many?
3 million.
You bastard!
Give me money
and I will live somewhere else.
And there is nothing
who can track me.
If not,
I will confess to the police.
I am tired
live like this.
I need the money tomorrow, okay?
Excuse me.
You came here alone
or...
...waiting for someone?
1 bottle of beer.
Why?
You will say
if this is not you?
Are you following me?
Don't say things like that.
I'm just curious.
I heard a lot of people
talking about you. And...
...they can only talk
but did nothing.
If I want to find out about
something, I need to know what the problem is.
Do you want my story to spread?
Are you unemployed?
Why?
What I do
none of your business.
I like this one.
I think you should
tell everyone this.
- I have to upload this on my IG.
- Give it to me.
WIPE
EMPTY FOLDER
Have you deleted everything?
You want to delete it
How many times?
I have a copy.
Hey, Queen!
I don't think I need to
show it to many people.
I just show it
to your father.
Queen.
Why?
You don't accept who you are?
RJ.
I know it's hard and...
...need time...
...while your father
conservative.
Actually,
your sexuality and...
...are you going to tell me?
everyone is up to you.
It's not your fault.
What's the point of doing that?
Who knows I…
...need your help.
About what?
What do you want me to do?
Everything I command.
I can give you 1 million.
Okay. Tomorrow, yeah.
Hey.
How long
do i have to pay you?
Until you are ready
to release Gale.
When I told Gale
your secret...
...he will definitely leave you.
Do not forget...
...Gale agrees to go on a date with you
because of your good reputation.
If he knew...
...nobles like you...
...failed in everything
and even sell drugs...
...he will definitely leave you.
Come on, don't be stingy.
Your Business with Pepper
going well, right?
Don't forget me who
introducing you two.
Just think of it as your way
thank me.
You will blackmail me
until I have nothing left?
Just think, between...
...give me money,
and lost Gale...
...which is worse?
How much is Gale worth to you?
Gale, I don't know.
if I'm still alive tomorrow.
If something happens to me...
...I want to give you something.
Your own secret.
Stored in the desk drawer
in my bedroom.
There is a key on the table.
Oh. There's a secret, Toy, too.
You can watch it.
It can be useful for your life.
Gale doesn't answer his phone.
I tried calling his mother.
He says
Gale with Toy.
Wait!
Where are you going?
I have to meet him.
I need to talk to him.
What is the point
meet him now?
Toy will be even angrier
if I see you.
Gale could be in big trouble.
I will save him
from him.
How to?
Why don't men think about it?
You think
you can punch Toy...
...and Gale will
free from it?
I guess he's right.
If Toy really
holding Gale's secret...
...nothing can
save him.
Let's make it like this.
I know
you're worried about Gale.
But wait until
I talked to him.
At least, I can hear from him.
about the real problem.
Will he talk to you?
You call him and he
not answering his phone.
I will meet him
tomorrow at school.
Then I can
ask him.
I think you should
go home now.
Never mind, maybe the circumstances
not as bad as you think.
You know... when Queen
said he had a problem...
...I thought so too
nothing will happen.
Eventually...
...I can't
save him.
What do you think?
Gale's Secret
which is kept by Queen?
Anything.
How do I know?
You said that sometimes Queen can talk too much
and tells RJ his secret.
Maybe Queen let it slip
and said something about Gale.
Well...
Queen talks about people's secrets
from time to time.
Some are true, and some are not.
I can't remember everything.
Do you remember anything?
Well...
Gale's mother is addicted to gambling,
very serious.
They live in a big house.
But his mother
struggling with debt.
Gale has to find a job
in the entertainment business...
...to pay off his mother's debt.
It's probably no secret...
...which can be used Toy
towards Gale.
Yes, right?
Or…
...about the incident
in the first year?
What's that?
I can't tell you this.
And I won't tell you.
Let Gale do it
tell you about it.
What is it?
Why?
You look tense.
Your disaster comes sooner
than you think?
Up to you.
As long as you are with me...
...that's the most important thing.
You're the one who messed up
my drama job offer?
You got a role in this drama,
to replace Queen...
...because I asked the team
to choose you.
If you want to break up with me...
...then you lose
this job offer. That's all.
So, this is what you want?
I told you...
...we need to hold on tight...
...in difficult times like these.
Every time
you let go of my hand...
...both of us
will be destroyed together.
Let it disintegrate.
What did you say?
I don't care
what are you going to do.
Tell them to fire me
from this drama, i don't care.
If you think someone like me
can't live without you...
...I have to tell you
if you are wrong.
Are you sure about that?
Of course.
I'm sure we're over.
If you break up with me...
...not just your drama...
...but I will definitely
ruin your life.
No.
I can't say
I will be the one to destroy it.
Queen did it.
He did not destroy
fully.
Eventually...
...you did it yourself.
- What do you mean?
- Why?
Don't tell me you don't remember...
...embarrassing thing
what you do.
I take this
from Queen's place.
It seems like all this time
he kept this.
Give it to me.
Look?
I actually
can ruin your life.
Hey, what's this?
Gale.
Did you sleep very well?
What are you doing?
I told you...
...after this,
nothing will be the same again.
I will not remain silent...
...and let you be
the only person who hurt me.
Where is the USB?
In your safe?
Tell me the combination number?
What if I don't want to?
What will you do?
You dare
do something to me?
You want to tell me
or not?
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8.
All 8, right?
You have to do that?
Correct.
Chivas asks us to keep it
until we know what to do.
This means we need
responsible for it.
I told you to keep it
at my place and you forbid me.
No.
You can check it out.
You don't want to know?
- No.
- Even just a little?
But inside
There's a secret, Coach Kwang.
You don't want to know
what's the secret?
Not at all.
Queen is dead and we
don't act like Queen.
You are a hypocrite.
Huh?
I will give you a chance
to say it.
Look at yourself,
you force your nature.
I can tell you don't
say what you want.
Oh yeah? You think?
am I that kind of person?
I think you just
describe yourself.
What?
Hey!
Wait!
Where are you going?
We need to talk.
What do you mean by that?
What do you want?
That's who you are.
You didn't say
What do you think.
You are a hypocrite and your actions
different from your thoughts.
What? I'm sincere.
I'm easy to read.
Oh yes?
Can you swear...
...reason
you want to stay away from me...
...that I am just
your one night stand is true?
If you can't
say it...
...stop convincing me
if you are easy to read.
Hey!
Hey?
Hey...
- What should we do?
- Enough.
The elevator is stuck.
Don't just press the button.
Step back.
Say
what is the combination number!
I don't want to say.
Gale?
It's enough.
Gale...
Okay.
I'll tell you.
OPEN
The technician is fixing it
the damage within 10 minutes.
Thank You.
Just like that? That's not enough.
You should sleep with him,
then record and share with me.
I will rise from my grave
and be your witness.
Be honest with me,
you lied to me, right?
You don't have anything, do you?
Trust me now?
This is just an example.
I have more than this.
I already have...
...what happened that night.
Can you
not playing around now?
My friend is having trouble.
If you have something,
then send it to me.
I have to make sure Athens
really get away from you.
Wait.
You were just chatting
with Queen?
Yeah. I know that…
I know
that's not the real Queen.
But he said
he had proof that night.
He will send it to me
if I follow his orders.
What does he want you to do?
What is the order?
He told me
away from you.
I know
This sounds stupid but…
...I really don't know
what to do.
How can you be sure?
he has proof...
He sent something
but he deleted it.
I'm sure he does.
What else is this?
What kind of ridiculous joke is this?
I investigate my secret
which is kept by Queen.
I wonder what he wants
reveal what secret.
It's nothing really.
Just a photo of me drunk
and wearing minimal clothing.
Everyone has seen this.
I'm a bit disappointed.
I think it's more than this.
You know better than Queen.
You know my secret
more than Queen.
Actually...
...you said I didn't say
according to my heart's desire...
...and I think that's true.
I never followed my heart,
never even once.
I lied to myself
I'm great at many things.
Actually it is...
...I am a coward
and losers.
That is not true.
I never thought
I deserve you.
The closer we get...
...the more I feel…
...I don't deserve it
a good man like you.
And someone like you...
...shouldn't date
people like me.
This is it…
...my secret.
How?
When you hear me
said it yourself...
...sad, isn't it?
Sounds like a loser.
You want to know...
...my kept secret
by Queen?
This.
This photo.
I used to be just...
...fat kid...
...the ugly one.
I don't look handsome
or cute at all.
It's so ugly, look at this.
Just that?
You think
it doesn't matter, right?
But I was devastated
Actually.
Just think,
someone like Queen...
...trying to dig up my shame
to expose me.
And only this
that he could find.
Meaning of my life
very boring.
There's nothing special about me,
so boring.
But my life is simple.
To be honest...
...it doesn't matter if you...
...facing some things
the horrible...
...whatever happens...
...your grades haven't changed...
...at least, in my eyes.
And I'm very ordinary...
...nothing special.
I used to be fat.
Do you know?
Actually...
...it's not even me
in the video.
I'm too lazy
to deny it.
If I say something, anyway
people think of me as a liar.
So I…
...just admit it.
That didn't happen either
on RJ.
As I said,
so i...
...act as if...
...I don't care
other people's thoughts.
But deep down,
you care, right?
The board...
...you don't need to
prove anything.
You just need to know
who are you...
...and how valuable you are.
Just that.
Do you know?
Hey.
How?
- Okay.
Gale?
I have to go.
Can you clear it?
this tub first?
Untie me, now.
Someone is coming
and save you.
I have to go.
Gale.
You know everything
what i do...
...is because
I love you.
I really love you.
Please don't leave me.
Gale.
Gale?
Can I come in?
Are you okay?
I'm really worried about you.
I don't know
where to go.
If I go home, my mother will force me
reconcile with Toy.
If I meet Papang,
Toy will see me there.
I don't want to
he got into trouble.
I know
we just met.
- But I…
- It doesn't matter.
You can stay here.
I promise...
...will protect you.
Isn't it...
...i don't like you
but you don't have to force yourself.
I want to be free from him.
You can help me, right?
How are you?
Gale replied to my message.
He told me not to worry,
he is with Chivas now.
What is the relationship between the two of them?
What is their relationship?
as we thought?
I also do not know.
But it's good that he finally
could break up with Toy.
How about you?
Are you still waiting for proof?
from that fake Queen?
I do not think so.
I can't wait any longer.
Okay?
Let's talk about myself
in 5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
Why did you do that?
You don't want any proof, do you?
SWIPE UP
SO THAT THE MESSAGE IS NOT SEEN
I've been here for a long time
waiting for you to jump.
Why still not?
Why did you change your mind?
How did you get in here?
Where is Athens?
You don't see
he's not here?
Tell me where he is!
Otherwise, I will broadcast it live.
did you use drugs here?
Your stupid fans
will see your true self...
...the rotten one.
Please.
Just do it!
Please expose me.
And I will
expose you again.
And you will
see who really is...
...who will have no place
in society.
It's a good thing Athens isn't here.
At least, he knows not to
humble yourself like this.
One day, later...
...I'll show you what he's supposed to be
not being around someone like you.
He just said...
...he likes Papang.
What did you say?
A woman like her?
Not true.
Impossible.
Just admit it.
No matter how hard you try,
he still doesn't want you.
He never saw you.
But I guess...
...he's rejecting me now.
But I guess I can steal it.
When the time comes...
...I will make sure
if he loves and adores me.
And I will break her heart
like he broke my heart.
He won't be able to
sleep or eat.
How?
I will do that.
Just wait.
Damn woman!
Crazy bitch!
What a psychopath!
Go to hell! Come on!
Jump! Do it!
Huh?
Why did you
don't just push me?
You say
you want me dead.
You don't dare to push me?
Just push me!
Come on, just do it!