Is this your friend?
Yes
" One day ago "
Nong, you have arrived.
190 baht.
Hello. Good morning everyone
I woke up early today because I had a morning class
Are you awake yet?
" Good morning P'Queen "
Good morning
"p'Queen, what time did you wake up?
At 3.
Just kidding! Who wakes up at three in the morning?
I woke up at six.
the morning so that they are beautiful quickly But if anyone wants to know how to get up in
please like and share, I will share my skills with you.
But now I want to study first
I hope today is a good day for everyone. Bye.
I just want to have my own freedom.
Live the life that I want.
I just want to be an ordinary girl.
Why?
Can't I love someone with all my heart?
P', can you stop and don't send my video to the director?
I'll get a new one and send it within an hour.
Why? What's wrong with this video?
I think I ended up being a bit of a waste. I want to try acting with emotion.
I think it fits the character more
Please let me take one last shot and send it to you?
You acted really well. The director really compliments you
-But I...
Don't worry
Let the director decide who he chooses, I'll tell you
Are you here?
Smile.
Thank you very much
I really like you, P'Queen.
I can pass the entrance exam here because I want to study'at the same school as you
am very happy to be your senior sister
If you happen to be passing by,don't forget to say hello.-- Then I'll go first.
-Bye-Bye.
It's time for class. Let's go
Where's Papa eng
Hello?
- Where are you? It's eight o'clock
Can I skip today?
Crazy! You said you were coming?
Yes, but now no. I want to sleep
You have missed this class many times.
Professor still threatens you, right? If you don't pass another class he will kick you out of school
Do you want to study for one more semester?
Don't complain. Come here quickly
Gale and I will be waiting for you under the building.
Did you sleep well last night?
-I'll take you back - Let go!
Just touching you, why are you overreacting?
You've gone further, haven't you?
-Hey!
I give up. Sorry, why are you angry? It's just a joke.
Bee.
Where are you going in such a hurry?
Let's talk first.
Bee.
Oh what more could you want?!
Fine, if you scold me like that, I feel overwhelmed too
Where are you going tonight? One Night Stand hosts a Happy Fool Night Party
- Are you going? - No.
- You're not going?
- None of your business!
What you're doing to me is following like a shitty dog! It's annoying!
Hey that's outrageous.
Seriously, what are you so sick of even though we were..?
Were what?
Speak up.
You will say you own me, right?
Like how you speak about me behind my back
Do you dare say it to my face now?
But don't think that I care.
You love to play and tell everyone that you are always with me
Don't expect me to date someone like you
Because if I had to date someone who I had sex with, I would've dated everyone in college!
He slept with the whole university
Dubbed the Goddess of One Night Stand
Not by luck.
Are you gossiping about me?
- You want to die?
- Papa eng!
Papa eng! You are l crazy?!
Get off me! - I'm not crazy!
Let me see if Ip pissed off anyone in your head.
But I didn't see anything when I looked here, or I slept with your parents?
Crazy!
Bee, calm down.
-Go!
Could you stop meddling in my business?!
Hey I'm curious, is your life so worthless if you don't gossip about other people?
When did I gossip about you?
Why? You're saying you weren't talking about me?
You really think that I don't know you're the one who created this nickname for me?
To be honest, you gossip about me many times now.
Let's just say that if you're I ying, I hope whoever you have sex with, you never [censored word ] for the rest of your life
Don't forget you [censored word ]
Nobody wants anything to do with you! - Papa eng!
- What?! You think I'm afraid of you?
Do you want to know before I got this nickname,what was my nickname?!
Papa eng.
Papa eng,stop it.
Come on.
What?!
Are you stupid or crazy or are you unconscious? Keep adding more so those idiots will gossip about you.
on +
Just keep gossiping, I'm not begging them for anything
Ugh, I thought that RJ was annoying, then those bitches deserve a slap.
But you can attack him without blowing up.
Plan ahead instead of blowing yourself up over something stupid like this.
But your business is up to you. You gave yourself to RJ.
Are you blaming me?
Not blaming just telling the truth.
What could anyone do if you knew how to control yourself and not sleep around with everyone?
You reap the consequences of your actions
Gale, why don't you worry about yourself first?
Now I think you think you're fantasizing that you're so high and untouchable
Are you lying to others or yourself?
Honestly,who are you lying to?
What do you mean?
Tonight on April Fool's Day, I made a VIP
reservat ion at the One Night Stand bar.
Let's go to the shopping mall to dress up and go out together.
Tonight? It's only March 31st.
After tonight will be tomorrow.
Why? You're stuck? You're talking like you're not going to go.
Well, Toy just got back from Paris and he said he'd come over to my house tonight.
I told Toy that you were going with me.
Queen, you know if I could pass tonight? I'm still hung over.
Also, RJ will definitely be going tonight, I don't want to see him.
No. Can't.
Hello,what do-you think about VIP One Night Stand?
It was easy to make an appointment even if it was me?
I don't know. You can ditch me anytime but not today.
if you're planning to go again?
Well it's sudden
But tonight there is a plan
Mer played two nights in a row and you can't stand it.
Athens
Queen
Happy birthday.
Is it your birthday?
You're asking a ridiculous question I just wished him a happy birthday
Thank you very much Queen.
Where will you celebrate?
Tonight, " One Night Stand Bar " will host April Fool's Day, are you going to the party?
Me, Gale, Papa eng are going
I should probably go because RJ invited me.
And some of the club people said they would celebrate a birthday too.
Really? Then see you later.
That's why I have to go to the party tonight.
You guys have to help me.
Welcome to Princess Gae wal in's Palace
- Papa eng, are you surprised?
Is that funny?
What? I'm just laughing at myself.
Princess,please
Did you audition for the Korean drama remake?
Asking me?
Yeah, you are the only star here.
I still don't know. But at first I didn't want.
to audition.
It doesn't seem like much.
But his team insisted I audition.
Waiting to see my friend Gae we lin's work
Did you tell Toy?
The audition results will be announced tonight?
Hello, did you tell Toy?
Yeah.
Can I take him there?
How will it be fun bringing your boyfriend?
I'm just asking.
Geez
May be for someone like you, just keep having sex and you'll be satisfied.
I don't want to argue. Try on clothes. I want to wash my face first.
So hurry up and try it.
See who can be faster.
Then let me try this. -Hmm.
- You don't have to be very fit, coach's not here
-Okay.
So? Tonight
are you still expecting Papa eng? - It's so insulting
Just wait and see.
Let her drink 4-5 glasses
Curses will turn into moans
Hey you want to come with us?
Maybe not. I should go back to my room first.
It's not because you're going to ditch us again, right?
You haven't been with me since you joined the club
No way. I'll go back and pack my things first
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Be there
Today is your birthday, right?
Wait a minute and I'll find something fun for you.
Well yeah, you guys go first
bye
Ah Toy, why are you here?
Gale didn't tell you she's going with us?
She did.
But today I have an appointment with Gale's
mother. So I brought something and stopped by
Then let me borrow her for today,okay
I hope this doesn't cause problems in your relationship
Why do you say that? I do not mind.
Gale, have fun with your friends
Let's go now. I sn't the show at 9? I can't wait to go
I can't go against it. Excuse me. I thought we'd be together today.
Then I'll come with you?
Sorry
No boyfriend tonight.
Okay, I'll pick you up at 1:00 in the morning.
But where are you guys going? So, I'll go to the right place.
You can wait for a phone call to let you know
Today I don't know how many places we will visit and what time we will finish.
If you are really impatient, you can sleep first.
In fact, there are people who take care of her today, so don't worry.
So where are you going?
Don't be pushy
Okay, then remember to call me
Come on.
I'm going.
Are you guys ready?
Ready
Let's party
Hey
RJ is coming, why isn't Athens here yet?
Gale.
If you want to play on your phone, just stay at home then.
You don't have to be nosy
Let's make tonight even more fun. Let's go on another mission.
This again?
-Yes
have my things and tonight I will make Athens my boyfriend.
Think quickly, what are you going to do?
Let's start with Miss Gale
I'll go home at one o'clock.
Not like that. Hey, think something creative. Rethink.
Papa eng, I guess your mission is.
Tonight I'm not going to get drunk at the bar, I'm going to be sober
And no men.
No, I'm tired.
You know what's funny about that? I don't believe you can do it.
A h, I'll wait and see.
Then you Gale, after midnight, how about it?
If you can't figure it out
I want you
you have to have a one night stand with someone tonight
Are you crazy? You know I've never done anything like this
Oh, I know you've never done this before, so I hope you give it a try
Let's release the excitement for one night
Make yourself happy and forget about tomorrow, okay?
No, I'm not going to do a one night stand. Okay?
Do you believe that?
Hey, what's up with you and Queen?
- I don't know and we're still talking.
You got her, yet?
Oh you, do you want her tonight? I'll arrange it for you too
You guys too,let me know if you're looking for someone,and I'll arrange for you
Let's toast!
Very excited.
Wait for me
Good
Athens
Come over here
I don't think he needs you
What kind of person is really handsome Look at Queen
- Let's talk about this level.
Shut up!
Happy birthday.
Oh this is so intense Queen.
Well, I know
you can't drink too much because you're worried about class.
But if you don't drink, it's no fun.
Please?
Come on.
Okay
Cheers.
Queen is very serious about Athens, you know that, right?
-Yes Whether it's serious or not
men are not something that can be shared with friends
What do you mean?
So you think I'm going to steal my friend's man?
How can you think of something so low? What do you think about me?
Papa eng, what have you made here?
You are a student but you act uneducated Beautiful face with the habits of a beast
I know her well because we go to the same school
Because she slept with all the guys in college.
What's wrong with you?
Nothing.
How was this morning?
Bee, where are you going? - Want to puke!
I saw your face and I wanted to vomit!
Play hard to get all you want. Wait until 2am.
Gale
You think you're so beautiful? Snobby bitch.
But your business is up to you.
You gave yourself to RJ.
Are you going to blame me for this?
Not blaming just telling the truth
What could anyone do if you knew how to control yourself and not sleep around with everyone?
You reap the consequences of your actions.
Hello Toy?
What are you doing? Why don't you answer the phone?
- Where are you?
Where do you want me to go?
Giri friend left me to stay home alone, where can I go?
-Toy Then, did you have fun?
So what if I'm drunk?
Are you drunk?
You can still hang out with friends and leave me alone
Where are you? I'll catch up with you.
How can you come?
Don't drive here when you are very drunk.
Never mind that. Just tell me where you are!
- What are you going to do if I don't tell you?
What did you say?
Stop pretending to be the master of my life!
Nong Gale,thanks for the audition,next time there will definitely be a chance
He has chosen someone else for this role.
Who got it?
Can you tell me?
Nong Queen
u Queen is also casting?
es
Gosh, Gale. Shouldn't you worry about yourself first?
Now I think you think you're fantasizing about how high and untouchable you are
Honestly, who are you lying to? Are you lying to others or yourself?
What are you photographing?
I took a picture of you by accident.
- But my face is ugly.
- It's cute
I'll send it to you.
-Okay.
Melting ice cream.
an ian
Where are your friends?
What's up Queen?
What are we going to do?
I want to find a quiet place to talk to you
Hey,
can Task you
what is the relationship between us?
Are you awake?
Hey
How did I get here?
picked you up from the bar
When did you pick me up? How do you know? I didn't tell you
saln nounaunsnousn)
You really don't remember, do you?
What did you do last night?
A surprising thing happened
The body of a young woman was found in a park
By the way,the police have confirmed the deceased is Katariya Kritneungalso known as Queen
A famous net celebrity with more than a million fans.
But now many netizens question and comment on social media
Is she your friend?
Yes