[My Uncanny Destiny]
♫ Listening to the wind blow while watching clouds sway ♫
♫ The moon hangs on treetops and links the romantic Magpie Bridge ♫
♫ You liven up everything ♫
♫ Why, why did fate let us meet? ♫
♫ My Lord, things are looking bad ♫
♫ She has forgotten all about the past ♫
♫ The Milky Way is far distant ♫
♫ That day, by some mistake ♫
♫ You landed in my arms ♫
♫ My Lord, things are looking bad ♫
♫ Why do I smile when I see her? ♫
♫ It's unpredictable ♫
♫ I want to stay with you till the end of the world ♫
♫ Oh, only then I realized ♫
♫ You tugged at my heartstrings ♫
♫ Look at that boundless longing ♫
♫ Daily, little by little, it spreads in the world ♫
♫ Listening to the wind blow while watching clouds sway ♫
♫ The moon hangs on treetops and links the romantic Magpie Bridge ♫
♫ You liven up everything ♫
♫ Why, why did we have to meet? ♫
♫ Listen to my heart beat and see your eyes drift ♫
♫ I hold your hand and fall for your gentleness ♫
♫ Is Cupid to blame for making a mistake? ♫
♫ Or... or is it meant to be? ♫
[My Uncanny Destiny]
[Longevity Hall]
[My Uncanny Destiny: Episode 7]
Don't you want to assassinate me?
Here is your chance.
There is no ambush.
Did you throw a knife at me?
It never crossed my mind that
the person I entrusted my life to
would throw a knife at me.
- You—
- Put away your hypocrisy!
Didn't you enter the palace just to assassinate me?
Did you yell at me?
How could you yell at me?
- Did I?
- Yes.
I...
Don't repeat the old tricks
and try to get out of this by pretending to be hurt!
Okay, don't you want to know the truth?
I will show you the truth!
This is so nice.
How dare you lie to me?
Your Majesty, I wouldn't dare.
We had to do it just because of my infatuated daughter.
Please spare us, Your Majesty.
- Please spare us, Your Majesty.
"Daughter"?
Your Majesty, these were found at Sanitation Department.
Liu Xuan Ming won't trust me easily
so we have to do two things.
I will do the first thing.
I will ask Queen Mother to convince Liu Xuan Ming that I truly have a crush on him,
and I won't hesitate to force a marriage on him by Queen Mother.
You need to do the second thing, and the sooner the better.
We must finish it before Liu Xuan Ming finds out!
What is it?
Draw as many portraits of Liu Xuan Ming as possible.
"Portraits"? No way,
we can't draw.
We can't.
I can do it.
These were all drawn by San Mei before entering the palace.
San Mei saw Your Majesty once by chance and has been vowing to marry Your Majesty ever since.
Later, our family was in decline, and we entered the palace as eunuchs.
In order to help San Mei fulfill her dream,
we thought of digging a tunnel to get close to Your Majesty.
Did you also arrange to let her save me that time?
Your Majesty,
we told San Mei about your traveling plan.
San Mei planned to take the opportunity to approach Your Majesty,
but the assassin came out of nowhere
so she was desperate to save you.
Were you also the ones hiding in the closet after drugging the guards?
Your Majesty, we wanted to dig to the bedchamber
so we tried to get into the bedchamber to find the most suitable exit.
The closet was safest and least likely to be discovered.
You three did such absurd things for her!
Your Majesty,
she is my only daughter!
Whatever she wants,
I will let her have at any cost,
even my life!
- Your Majesty, please spare us.
Dad!
Your Majesty, please spare us.
- Dad.
- Daughter.
- My poor girl.
- San Mei.
San Mei. San Mei.
Life is so harsh on us,
so harsh.
How dare you!
What do you think this place is?
Stop flattering yourselves. His Majesty is wise, mighty, and brave.
Numerous women lose their hearts to His Majesty.
You are so basic that even I wouldn't lay my eyes on you, let alone His Majesty!
Do you think he is blind?
- Yao Hu.
- Yes.
- Get out.
- All right.
How are you?
Water.
We barely survived.
Do you think Liu Xuan Ming believed us?
If we don't stick our necks out in the next few days, he shouldn't suspect us.
All right.
But I don't think Liu Xuan Ming is a bad person.
Could there be something hidden about our family being exterminated back then?
San Mei, don't be fooled by his looks.
Did you fall in love with him?
- With whom?
- With Liu Xuan Ming.
No way!
San Mei, don't forget that Liu Xuan Ming has a sworn feud with us!
Guan San Mei, when shall we take action?
Not now.
After all, Yi Yang is keeping an eye on us now.
Apparently, we can only wait until Liu Xuan Ming and Qi Meng's wedding.
All right.
- Where is Guan?
- Where is my dad?
Didn't we come back together?
He seems to have fainted.
Dad, Dad!
It must be warm-heat disease.
It was because he was scared!
- Guan.
- Dad.
No matter what you say, I will never believe you again.
I am going to tear you to pieces!
I have asthma. My medicine...
You are really good at acting. Do you think I will believe you?
Please, save me.
Save me.
Okay.
I shall get you the medicine and torture you slowly.
This one?
You do have a poor memory.
I am not the one to blame this time.
What is wrong with you?
I am the best assassin in the world,
yet I repeatedly get defeated by you.
There is no point in living.
- Just kill me.
- Don't say that.
Think about it; you threaten me with a knife every time.
I am just protecting myself.
There is no use in discussing it. Just do it.
You!
All right, let's make peace.
Don't try to kill me, and I won't ever lie to you again.
All right?
Why is it so dark?
Why can't I see anything?
Why am I not seeing anything?
My eyes!
Why can't I see anything?
Why don't I see anything?
Do you know what this is?
This is the face of a handsome man.
Of course, I know.
I am talking about this wet place.
This is a tear stain.
When San Mei was painting,
she must have shed tears of sadness
because she missed me too much.
It's a little hot.
Okay, okay.
Dad,
are you feeling better?
Daughter.
Dad.
You are pinning me down.
Dad, are you feeling better?
I now feel much better, apart from wanting to go to the bathroom.
It is cold.
Thank you.
You don't have to say that to me.
I should thank you anyway.
Dad, I should thank you.
I dreamed several times that my father had died.
But when I woke up, I found that my father was still here.
Yes.
It gave me a sense of lost and found.
So, Dad, thank you for giving me the opportunity
to show you filial piety.
San Mei,
if... I mean just in case...
If I weren't your...
Look. Liu Xuan Ming gave us so much money.
Guan, money! San Mei, we are rich now!
What is wrong with you?
Get well soon. I will buy you delicious food.
What a fortune.
Princess Qi Meng, are these all for us?
Of course.
Princess Qi Meng, you are so generous.
Princess Qi Meng, how could we receive these?
Baby, does it look good on me?
Mom, you look gorgeous.
Nanny Ke, you are welcome.
Brother Xuan Ming has been under your care since childhood.
I should show filial respect to you.
Thank you, Princess.
Miss Ke, I really treat you like my own sister.
Just take them all.
Otherwise, we would be like strangers.
Princess Qi Meng, since you have said so,
if I push back, I won't be generous enough.
Baby, does it look good on me?
Mom, it fits me better.
- It fits me better.
- It fits me better!
Amazing, Sister Qian Yue.
Recently, have you heard anything about Xuan Ming and San Mei?
Whenever anyone mentions her, I get really angry.
She not only framed me, but also seduced His Majesty.
I have to find a chance to punish her!
Sister, don't say that.
I think San Mei really likes Xuan Ming.
We can't be jealous.
Princess Qi Meng, you are right.
- Harmony is precious. Harmony is precious.
- Nonsense.
Qi Meng, you are way too innocent and kind.
San Mei is just a temptress.
Enough, look how angry Qian Yue is.
Well,
recently, 1,000 war horses arrived as dowry in Tian Mu City.
Xuan Ming and San Mei will go take a look.
Let's also watch the fun.
I am not going!
I get angry when I see that temptress!
Calm down. Just go with me and have a look.
The war horses of Tian Mu City are extremely temperamental.
Once when my father was on an inspection tour,
someone accidentally poked a war horse,
the horse immediately went crazy
and even kicked an attendant to death.
It is amazing.
Princess Qi Meng, your bracelet looks so nice.
If you like it, it is yours.
- Thank you, Princess. Thank you, Princess.
- And Qian Yue.
Whatever you like, just take it.
Since you said so, it would be disrespectful for us to decline.
Watch out. Don't drop anything.
Baby, just forget it.
You are not that temptress' opponent.
I have a way to deal with her.
Mom, Tian Mu City is really rich.
Just take them back.
I will use them as your dowry in the future.
Lord Liu.
To express our sincerity in the marriage,
Lord Yang Cheng sent 1,000 war horses as Qi Meng's dowry.
Brother Xuan Ming, do you like them?
The war horses of Tian Mu City live up to their reputation.
Everyone says Tian Mu City's war horses are unparalleled in the world.
It is a pity I don't know how to spot (pick) horses.
Bo Le once wrote a book named "Art of Spotting Horses," detailing how to choose a horse.
I will teach you the easiest way.
A good horse has a protruding forehead, eyes like those of a frog,
and hooves like piles of distiller's yeast (lifting).
Judging by that, you can choose a good horse.
Brother Xuan Ming is really talented and knowledgeable.
That is just the simplest way of spotting horses.
To judge whether it is really a good horse,
you observe the horse's head, eyes, ears, mouth,
nose, chest, abdomen, spine, hooves, tail, hair, tendons,
skeleton, and flesh.
It turns out San Mei also knows how to spot horses.
It is nothing difficult. Even fools know how.
These are tribute horses from Tian Mu City. How could you ride them?
Nice horse.
With them, Xuan Yue City will double with might.
San Mei, watch out!
- Xuan Ming, watch out!
- Your Majesty! Your Majesty!
Your Majesty!
Your Majesty! Your Majesty!
Brother Xuan Ming! Brother Xuan Ming!
Liu Xuan Ming, find a way to make it stop.
Liar!
You said that the horse would stop when it was tired.
But it got tired in water!
I am so cold!
I just met that horse so I am unfamiliar with it.
You said and did everything you could.
Now you say you are not familiar with it.
Someone doesn't even know how to speak.
You never did what you said, never understood what you did,
never listened to what you understood, and made mistakes,
but you never admitted a fault.
It's all your fault!
All right, I was wrong.
Even it can't stand anymore.
You are hungry.
You are hungry!
You never listened to others.
Tan Rang, look what I brought you.
I don't think I can see.
I went to the imperial clinic, and the imperial doctor prescribed this to treat your eyes.
Five Qian (25 gr) of baby tangerine and three cups of pure water.
After at least one day, at most one 1,000 days, you will be healed.
I don't think I will believe you.
I am talking seriously. I am a princess.
How could a princess lie?
Are you willing to believe me one last time?
[Auspiciousness]
♫ Don't know why I can't let go ♫
♫ Even if my heart says so ♫
♫ Just look how far apart we've grown ♫
♫ We're like strangers now, to love again ♫
Look. I picked this with a lot of work.
How beautiful it is, just make do with it.
Mix them,
and have a try.
Here, have a sip.
Does it taste good?
Take more.
Here.
Have some more.
- Here.
- No, no.
Take it yourself.
And one more... What is wrong with you, San Mei?
San Mei...
It is so sunny.
The sunshine!
What a good-looking man.
Kiss.
San Mei. San Mei.
Calm down, San Mei.
I am very conservative. I am very conservative!
San Mei.
If you keep doing this, I will take action.
Kiss me. Kiss me. Kiss me.
San Mei, I know your feelings.
However, the more distracted and swoony you are,
the more you should restrain yourself, return to propriety and doctrines of Confucius and Mencius.
As the old saying, "Certain things gentlemen do and don't do."
"A gentleman's actions are moral."
"A gentleman's words must be justified."
"A gentleman's conduct is in line with justice."
"A gentleman, must be honest when poor, righteous when he is rich,"
"kind to the living, and mournful to the dead."
"These virtues cannot be fake, but truly possessed."
"His behavior is extremely humble, and his speech is very tame."
"Those who let these virtues flow freely in the limbs and skin,"
"refuse to give up before gray hair or baldness, and are likely saints!"
"As the old saying, certain things gentlemen do and don't do."
Your Majesty!
- Your Majesty!
- Your Majesty! Your Majesty!
Your Majesty!
Liu Xuan Ming, what did you do to me last night?
Did you forget about last night?
What happened last night?
San Mei. San Mei.
Calm down, San Mei.
I am very conservative.
- Over there.
- Yes.
Let's go!
Don't be shy.
It is normal to be mesmerized by my looks.
Wow, so exciting.
Stop crying.
Yao Hu.
It will never be your turn to cry.
The tribute horses of Tian Mu City are a lavish gift.
Ke Qian Yue from the inner city
hurt the ponytail, disregarded law and discipline.
She went against law and reason and is full of evil.
According to law, she will be punished by washing thousands of horses
to serve as an example to others.
Mr. Horse, I will wash your crapper in a while.
Don't kick me.
Have you heard?
His Majesty and San Mei were in rags in the grove,
and they got discovered by Yao Hu and Princess Qi Meng.
Shall we go to the grove tonight?
I have a juicy story.
His Majesty and San Mei were in the grove...
- I am too embarrassed to say it.
- Is it true?
The birds in the forest were stunned and all flew away.
Even the nearby mountains trembled.
His Majesty and San Mei made a solemn pledge of love.
His Majesty promised to marry San Mei.
Listen. Keep it a secret.
Don't worry; my lips are sealed.
Come here. Let me tell you.
His Majesty and San Mei were having fun last night in the grove.
- Is it true?
- Their clothes were torn off.
And they were caught by Miss Ke on the spot. Don't tell anyone else.
Don't worry. I will keep it to myself.
Come here. Let me tell you a secret.
Don't tell anyone else.
It is so embarrassing.
The imperial doctor has checked on San Mei
and said she got impregnated by His Majesty.
Bai Lu, you bullied San Mei before.
You are done for!
Daughter, how could you do such an absurd thing as a girl?
You are embarrassing us.
Dad, how could I—
San Mei, stop making excuses!
Now no man will be your husband!
It shouldn't be, but everyone knows it.
It is the same!
San Mei, I don't want to blame you...
But you are a girl.
A girl must value her good name.
Enough, save it.
So embarrassing!
I am ashamed for you.
Gosh.
Domestic shame shouldn't be public.
You embarrassed the Guan Family!
Now the news you are pregnant has spread in the city.
Do you believe it?
Of course, I don't believe it.
How could you do such a thing?
You have no idea the exaggerated rumors in the city these days.
In a few days, I guess I can be a grandma!
Why are you laughing?
Isn't that good?
Haven't you noticed inner city servants are respectful to you now?
In a few days, you can walk around Xuan Yue City sideways.
Why should I walk in Xuan Yue City sideways?
How about flipping around
vertically, walking in the sky?
How do I walk in the sky?
So naïve...
I washed the horses all day today.
Xuan Ming and San Mei really love each other.
We should be happy for them.
"Be happy for them"?
Princess Qi Meng, you are so innocent.
I can't wait to kill that temptress.
Maybe it is my fate.
No one could manage it with effort,
just like some people live long
and others live short lives.
Some people don't die if they fall off a cliff.
Some people get choked to death by drinking tea.
I really hope that tea can choke her to death.
There is no poison in the tea.
How could you kill her?
San Mei, Miss Ke was ignorant before and offended you.
She ordered me to make this hangover tea.
Please pardon her.
Snobs like you are everywhere.
I don't have enough time to be angry with any of you.
I must stay on my knees till you drink this tea.
Have you poisoned the tea?
I...
- I...
- I dare you!
♫ Secretly hiding, secretly thinking of you ♫
♫ Burying my feelings for you in my heart ♫
♫ The esteemed lord ♫
♫ Should not show vulnerability ♫
♫ Before the people so easily ♫
♫ When you appear, when you approach ♫
♫ When someone understands that I'm not a god ♫
♫ Your words ♫
♫ Are etched in my mind ♫
♫ That tender heart of yours ♫
♫ I want to protect you while navigating the storm ♫
♫ Braving the glint and flash of cold steel ♫
♫ I want to take you to see scenery you've never seen ♫
♫ I really want to be with you forever ♫
♫ Whether we are on opposing sides or archenemies ♫
♫ Only my love for you is everlasting ♫
♫ A deep-rooted affection ♫