[My Uncanny Destiny]
♫ Listening to the wind blow while watching clouds sway ♫
♫ The moon hangs on treetops and links the romantic Magpie Bridge ♫
♫ You liven up everything ♫
♫ Why, why did fate let us meet? ♫
♫ My Lord, things are looking bad ♫
♫ She has forgotten all about the past ♫
♫ The Milky Way is far distant ♫
♫ That day, by some mistake ♫
♫ You landed in my arms ♫
♫ My Lord, things are looking bad ♫
♫ Why do I smile when I see her? ♫
♫ It's unpredictable ♫
♫ I want to stay with you till the end of the world ♫
♫ Oh, only then I realized ♫
♫ You tugged at my heartstrings ♫
♫ Look at that boundless longing ♫
♫ Daily, little by little, it spreads in the world ♫
♫ Listening to the wind blow while watching clouds sway ♫
♫ The moon hangs on treetops and links the romantic Magpie Bridge ♫
♫ You liven up everything ♫
♫ Why, why did we have to meet? ♫
♫ Listen to my heart beat and see your eyes drift ♫
♫ I hold your hand and fall for your gentleness ♫
♫ Is Cupid to blame for making a mistake? ♫
♫ Or... or is it meant to be? ♫
[My Uncanny Destiny]
[General's Manor]
My Lord! Greetings to Your Lordship.
[My Uncanny Destiny: Episode 18]
Quickly get up.
- General.
- Let me down. Let me down.
She is my sister. She was emotionally hurt and became insane
thinking of marrying His Majesty all day long.
What are you saying? I wanted to marry His Majesty before. But now...
See? She's really insane.
- Leave now! Don't make a fool of yourself.
- I am leaving.
I am leaving.
Doorkeeper!
General.
When was my manor changed into a city gate so anyone can enter?
Why don't you just let the Lord of Xuan Yue City in someday, too?
General, please forgive me. I will instantly warn doorkeepers to tighten security.
- Leave!
- Yes.
She just called Your Lordship.
Probably another person who recognized me as Lord Ye.
Indeed.
Anyone who sees you for the first time will likely mistake you.
This way, it will be more secure.
Have a good night!
Does Ye Zhao Nan really look like you?
Do you think it's a coincidence?
- Here.
- Is it okay?
- Come on. Here.
- Put her down.
I think she will always be a scourge. We must find a way to deal with her.
What did I say before? We should have chopped her up.
Why do you always want to chop her up? Guan San Mei and Liu Xuan Ming already saw her.
How about we leave her to them?
Okay.
I think it's best to chop her up.
Rude!
Where is the envoy?
As long as you serve me well,
not to mention meeting the envoy,
you can even meet His Lordship.
What do you want to do? Don't mess around.
I am Princess Yun Luo, younger sister of Xuan Yue City's Lord, Liu Xuan Ming.
Liu Xuan Ming's younger sister?
Great.
Tonight I will be your man!
Baby, I am coming.
Give me a kiss.
Stay away from me! Get away!
The more you resist,
the stronger I am.
Girl.
When I get you, see how I'll torture you.
Baby.
Where are you running to?
- Stay away from me!
- Baby, I am coming.
Stay away from me!
I love tough women.
Don't run off!
San Mei. Stay here and take care of her. I'll find Yun Luo.
I will go with you.
Help!
- Stop!
- Help!
Yun Luo!
- Come back. Here.
- Yun Luo!
- Eldest Sister. Brother.
- Hush.
Baby.
Someone, come!
What's going on? Why are you not sleeping at midnight and calling "Yun Luo, Yun Luo?"
Yun Luo?
Are you Liu Xuan Ming's younger sister, Princess Yun Luo?
We have Lord's wife and Princess Yun Luo.
My General's Manor will soon become the palace of Xuan Yue City!
This woman bit me.
It was he who plotted wrongdoing first.
What do you want to do?
Kill him.
This is General's Manor, not Xuan Yue City.
So what?
Yun Luo is the princess of Xuan Yue City and my sworn sister.
Vice General Zhou sexually harassed Yun Luo.
So what if we kill him?
San Mei.
As you said, she is the princess of Xuan Yue City, not Mu Xi City.
Not to mention sexually harassing her, what if I kill her?
- You!
- Just take a try.
If Yun Luo loses even one piece of hair today,
I will let the entire General's Manor
be buried with her.
You!
San Mei!
You've challenged me again and again!
Aren't you afraid that I'll crush you?
Just you?
I have thirty thousand elite soldiers in the city.
Can't I kill you?
- There seems to be a fight over there. Who shall we help?
- What's wrong with you? What do you think?
Of course, we should help San Mei. But isn't this Jin Fu's territory?
Who cares whose territory it is?
Whoever dares to hurt San Mei, that's whom I'll kill.
- Let's go.
- Okay, let's go.
- Wait.
- Yi Yang Jun.
Zhao Jing, Feng Lei. Go and block the gate.
If they fight, don't let anyone go out to tip-off.
Old Guan. Go to the woodshed and prepare some wood.
- If they fight, burn the General's Manor.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
Let's go.
General, you don't think we came unprepared, do you?
At the border between Mu Xi and Xuan Yue,
fifty thousand soldiers of Xuan Yue are waiting for our signal.
Would you like to give it a try?
He is indeed the city's Lord. He planned thoroughly.
- Who are you scaring?
- Then just try!
San Mei. Oh, San Mei.
You guys have worse tempers than me, a warrior on the battlefield.
Without a bad temper, no one would fear you.
All right. Okay.
It's getting late. Go rest early.
We have important things to do tomorrow.
Hold on.
Princess Yun Luo's business wasn't settled yet.
After all, Vice General Zhou failed
to sexually harass Princess Yun Luo.
According to what you mean, we can hold him accountable only if he succeeds.
If not, we can only let it go.
Yes. Isn't that reasonable?
By what you mean, when your mother conceived you,
if she had given birth to you, you were a human being. But if you were a stillborn,
- you wouldn't even be a human being?
- Guan San Mei!
Shut up!
Envoy Guan.
Are you satisfied now?
Let's go.
Your Majesty.
Let me kill him.
None of you should meddle in this matter.
I will definitely help Yun Luo vent this anger.
What's wrong with you?
You even dared touch Liu Xuan Ming's sister.
Do you want to die?
Who would have thought that Liu Xuan Ming's younger sister could come here?
General. Guan San Mei doesn't take you seriously.
Tomorrow, ask Zhao Jing and the others to bury Ye Zhao Nan's body in the backyard.
After Guan San Mei reads the abdication edict, her life will be in my hands.
By then, I will surely tear Guan San Mei into pieces.
[Room of Elegance]
Why did you come to Mu Xi?
Enough. She's already here. What's the use of you blaming her?
- Can't I blame my own sister?
- You!
Yes, you can. If you rescue Tan Rang, you can blame me however you want.
Don't worry. Your Tan Rang is fine right now.
We won't let anything happen to him.
- Go back to Xuan Yue City tomorrow.
- I am not going back.
- If Tan Rang doesn't come back, I won't go anywhere.
- You...
You go too far! It's inappropriate for Xuan Yue's princess to come to Mu Xi City for a man.
Why aren't you ashamed to say that about me?
As the lord, you are not in Xuan Yue City,
but came to Mu Xi City for your wife.
You are so obedient to your wife. Aren't you ashamed?
How dare you!
Sister. He's angry at me.
You!
Your brother is worried about you.
Look at you.
You know Yun Luo's temperament.
She won't go back without rescuing Tan Rang.
Why don't you just let her stay by my side
and follow me into the inner city tomorrow?
That way, I can take care of her safety.
- All right?
- Brother, please.
By the way, what about the signal arrow?
I planned to give it to you when we met, but I was so preoccupied I forgot to.
The elite soldiers of Xuan Yue City are all here,
and they are all at your disposal.
So you came prepared.
Madam, you have no idea. The day you left, His Majesty dispatched troops, horses and prepared for backup.
Once someone dares to hurt you in the slightest, all Xuan Yue City will attack.
Enough.
Your Majesty.
Yao Hu.
Princess Yun Luo.
Am I back in Xuan Yue City?
I'm back to Xuan Yue City. I'm back to Xuan Yue...
Ke Qian Yue. I don't know why you are here,
but if you want to survive,
you can't let anyone know the true identity of His Majesty.
He is now acting as my servant. You must do the same.
This is not just about your personal safety,
it is about all of our lives.
Understand?
Sister. Is Tan Rang going to be okay?
Don't worry.
I assure you that nothing will happen to Tan Rang.
Big field mouse.
Don't eat the millet I planted.
I worked hard to serve you many years,
but you never took care of me.
I swear to get rid of you
and go to that happy paradise.
That paradise is my good destination.
Your Majesty. When I snuck into the General's Manor,
I heard Guan San Mei plans to enter the palace tomorrow as Ye Zhao Nan.
Big field mouse.
Don't eat the wheat I planted.
I worked hard to serve you many years, but you never treated me well.
I swear to get rid of you
and go to that happy paradise.
That paradise will pay me what I am worthy of.
So tired. Let's get some rest.
We must copy it quickly and put it back where it was.
So vivid.
[Xuan Shang]
There is a riddle here about two apes in the tree, one male and one female.
An old man was shepherding below the tree. He suddenly saw a tiger devouring his sheep.
The female monkey exclaimed five words.
The male monkey teased the female monkey.
The question is what did the female monkey exclaim?
Why is there no answer in the back?
Liu Xuan Ming. Do you know what the answer is?
Guan San Mei. What are you doing here?
Just to have a chat with you.
It's not appropriate for me to enter the inner city
so I prayed for a safety talisman to protect you.
Yi Yang Jun. Thanks a lot.
But it's Liu Xuan Ming's luck.
I thought I could get rid of him after I came to Mu Xi City.
It suddenly occurred to me that before coming to Mu Xi City,
you told me to pretend to be hostile in order to confuse General Jin Fu.
Looking back now, you did this to alienate me, right?
Yi Yang Jun. I see you as a confidant.
But even if we are confidants, the red line cannot be crossed.
Otherwise, doing shameful things in the name of confidants will tarnish the word "confidant."
My heart is for Liu Xuan Ming alone.
And you treat me well.
I cannot bear this kindness.
I hope you will never put more emotion on me in the future.
Otherwise, I can only alienate you even more.
What are you thinking? The reason I treat you well is to let you achieve universal peace quickly.
Don't be so sentimental.
It's good this way.
Haven't you noticed that servants in the inner city are respectful to you now?
In a few days, you can walk around Xuan Yue City sideways.
General Jin Fu is so stingy. We spied in Xuan Yue City for him for many years.
- After we returned, we do this job, but he didn't raise our wages.
- Indeed.
Enough. Save it.
Why are you not reconciled? Isn't it just a cat's-paw?
Why do you complain about doing this job? The unwilling should be me.
With my intelligence, I should at least be a military adviser.
Besides, the key issue now is San Mei.
General Jin Fu asked us to enter the palace with San Mei and to watch her.
It seems he still has doubts.
I think so, too. San Mei surely has a way.
Now we should be thankful we won't face this stinking corpse anymore. Let's just work.
Exactly.
- What?
- Are you still thinking of Zhi Lan?
Let the past be the past. Love without being together is not true fate.
I predicted it for you. Your fate is coming soon.
Enough. Hurry. We must go to the inner city with San Mei after we finish.
- Hurry.
- Quick.
[Fortune and Luck]
[Room of Elegance]
Envoy Guan.
Alike,
so alike.
Almost the same, it's hard to distinguish.
From today onward, you are the Lord of Mu Xi City,
Ye Zhao Nan.
After entering the inner city, remember to proceed with caution and never make a slip.
You just have to hold on until tomorrow morning and read the edict of abdication.
If there is a slight mistake, everyone around you will die.
General, don't worry. I know what to do.
But I have a question.
Please go ahead.
Anyway, I am playing the Lord.
This procession is way too shabby.
You have no idea.
All officials believe that the lord is recovering.
If we do this too grand, something is wrong.
This road is a small trail leading to the inner city, and no one knows it.
Catch her!
Stop there!
Hunt them down.
Princess.
Hui Rou?
Do I have blurred vision? They look too much alike.
- This... Am I seeing a ghost? Isn't this Princess Qi Meng?
It's Qi Meng's twin sister, Princess Qian Hui Rou.
"Qian Hui Rou"?
Sister. We should save her. She is different from Qi Meng.
After the death of the Lord of Tian Mu City, she fled here.
Her brother must have chased her here.
- How do you know?
- I met her in Mu Xi City a few days ago.
She is really pitiful.
- Someone, come!
- Wait!
- Yes.
Guan San Mei. I don't believe you dare to kill me.
My older sister is very terrifying.
She will make you want to die more than live.
I haven't watched a play in a long time.
I'd like to see how long it takes for these killers to kill her.
This is a rare good show.
Since you said that, there must be something else hidden.
Why not be an onlooker?
Princess. What if they don't fall for it?
That's because our act is not real enough.
What should we do?
When someone dies, it's real enough.
So fake.
Do you think that sword is real?
It looks real.
Could the blood be fake?
It did cost a lot.
Sister. Will you really watch her die?
It's wrong to see others die without doing anything.
But she's not dead yet. How can we save her?
Try harder.
- Save her!
- Come on.
- Hurry.
- Quick.
- Brother. The soldiers are coming.
Let's go.
So alike.
Listen carefully.
Qi Meng killed my most important person so I killed her.
But I never regretted it.
If you came here to avenge Qi Meng,
I will surely let you suffer the consequences
and be doomed eternally.
♫ Secretly hiding, secretly thinking of you ♫
♫ Burying my feelings for you in my heart ♫
♫ The esteemed lord ♫
♫ Should not show vulnerability ♫
♫ Before the people so easily ♫
♫ When you appear, when you approach ♫
♫ When someone understands that I'm not a god ♫
♫ Your words ♫
♫ Are etched in my mind ♫
♫ That tender heart of yours ♫
♫ I want to protect you while navigating the storm ♫
♫ Braving the glint and flash of cold steel ♫
♫ I want to take you to see scenery you've never seen ♫
♫ I really want to be with you forever ♫
♫ Whether we are on opposing sides or archenemies ♫
♫ Only my love for you is everlasting ♫
♫ A deep-rooted affection ♫