It seems like destiny.
The two of us?
I'm sorry.
I thought I should do that.
What?
I thought it was appropriate.
Where are you going?
Now that we've satisfied your curiosity,
we should go home and sleep.
Together?
No. In our own places.
We have no reason to sleep together now.
Why?
Aren't you sleepy?
Me too.
I thought I should do that, too.
I see.
Don't you have anything to say?
No.
I feel like I'm not myself.
I feel like I'm a different person.
I feel very complicated,
and uncomfortable...
You are Han Segye.
You're not someone else.
I think I know...
...what you want to hear.
Then just say it.
I won't say it.
So...
...sleep tight.
(Uncle)
Why won't he call?
Why hasn't he called?
It's already been an hour.
Shouldn't he let me know
if he reached home?
It's been an hour and a minute.
Did you get home safely?
Is he asleep?
He's asleep in this situation?
No, it can't be.
Is he ignoring my message?
Is he serious right now?
(Did you get home safely?)
Why won't you eat?
Who can digest meat in the morning?
I have a wardrobe briefing
with the director later.
If I don't want to be outshined
by young actresses...
...I need to control what I eat.
Just take a tiny bite.
You won't get fat
if you eat only this much.
We're going on a trip this week.
What trip?
A read-through session and a trip.
To read the script and
get to know each other.
Since it's this week,
I told them immediately that we're going.
It's your safe days.
Yeah. A trip is nice.
Let's go.
By the way...
What does it mean when a guy kisses
you and then pretends he didn't?
Maybe he didn't want to kiss.
Why do you ask?
Did you kiss?
No.
I just remembered...
You know, the movie I was in...?
I was just thinking
about that kissing scene.
I messed up more than 20 times
when I was filming that scene.
But...
... I didn't feel any emotions.
I didn't say anything.
I don't have any emotions...
...either.
Are you dating?
No, I'm not dating.
Hey, dating's not a big deal.
Look.
Peel some shrimps.
Cook some meat.
That's all dating.
I didn't peel shrimps for him.
Maybe you haven't eaten
shrimps with him.
What the hell? Does that mean
you and me are dating?
This is more than just dating.
It's a business relationship.
Right.
Of course.
I knew it.
Aren't you too old to run away from home?
You ran away for real
because mom told you to?
You obeyed Mom all your life.
Why are you doing this?
I'm unleashing all my
pent-up insubordination.
Why don't you disobey a little bit
at a time like I do...
... instead of unleashing it all at once.
Keep saying "hey" and watch what happens.
Sure, I will.
Hey. Where do you sleep?
Why you...
It's none of your business.
I sleep on the streets.
Are you really going to be a priest?
If you don't get married,
then I'll have to.
I'm a celibate.
My life is screwed because of you.
Don't let me or anyone
else ruin your life.
That's why I left home.
Bro.
Are you not going to come home?
How's Mom?
She won't come out of bed.
You're lucky Dad's not home
because of an emergency.
If he saw what happened, he would've...
...shot you with a gun.
Honey, are you okay?
Why did you come home?
I ought to knock some sense
into that punk.
-Yeah.
-Captain.
We have the CCTV results
from the Dogok-dong case.
-Did you see the suspected vehicle?
-We confirmed the plate number.
Now, we're trying to locate the suspect.
Okay. I'm on my way.
You're leaving again?
I'll be right back.
Change your socks first.
Why are there so many
bad guys in the world?
The worst one is in our family.
How dare he break my wife's heart.
Then go catch your son first.
I caught many bad guys before
who actually turned out to be good.
Go back to bed. I'll be back.
Let's go!
Of course he takes after his father.
The apple never falls far from the tree.
Don't get hurt!
The sales numbers
of this event is serious.
What does it mean?
I mean it's seriously high...
...that it's incomparable
to the sales of previous years.
Congratulations.
What does it mean?
Did you hear what I said?
No, I wasn't listening.
What does it mean when someone
kisses you and then apologizes for it?
It means she's sorry.
And if she asks if I have anything to say?
In that case, there are two answers
she wants to hear.
"I love you."
Or "I'm sorry."
What if I don't want to say sorry?
You should tell her you love her.
And what if...
...I don't want to say that either?
You should pay me
if you're going to keep asking.
This is emotional labor.
Where do you get that cheeky attitude?
My face.
If you keep lying to me because I can't
recognize faces, you'll be in trouble.
You're the one who's
about to be in trouble.
You have an appointment with Dr. Oh.
Time to get what's coming to you.
-What about you?
-I already have plans.
Is it more important than me?
It's not important, but a little scarier.
I guess you're talking about my mother.
It's strictly confidential.
No matter what my mother says...
...don't get the wrong idea.
Maybe it's not so confidential.
Since the character's a cold person...
...we prepared mostly black
for a mannish and modern vibe.
These are the same
as Chae Yoori's outfits.
This one's intended to give
a vivid look in the darkness.
We prepared a fancy floral print dress.
Chae Yoori has that one as well.
This one, and this one too.
She brought...
...all of these?
Go get Chae Yoori.
Okay.
That's very strange.
We may have the same taste in clothes,
but how can all of them be the same?
Since I'll be playing six characters,
I needed a variety of clothes.
Are you wearing this one too?
Oops. This is awkward.
I have that one too.
The new editions of this season
look pretty much the same.
When would a hermit
who lives in fear of death...
...wear such vivid, colorful clothes?
In which scene?
A girl who lives in hiding
doesn't have to be gloomy.
She may want to wear
those kind of clothes sometimes.
Looks like you want to wear
all the clothes in Korea.
Fine. Just wear them all.
I'll be naked during the shoot.
That would generate a lot of buzz.
Whatever. Clothes don't play
the character, actors do.
Segye.
Why? Do you have something to say?
Are you upset?
What?
I won't wear them.
I don't have to wear them.
You are important.
You wear them.
I'll prepare mine again.
I'm sorry...
...that I upset you.
Chae Yoori did that on purpose.
I found out that her styling
team went around...
...and checked all of our
sponsored outfits.
And then she had the audacity to...
That manipulative witch.
Forget it.
It's been a while since someone
paid me so much attention.
It's impressive how she tries
so hard to screw me over.
I'm not letting this go.
Watch what I'll do to her on the trip.
I definitely lost today.
Some days are like this.
Losing days.
(Did you get home safely?)
Forget it. I'm not doing this.
I won't do it.
Won't do what?
If you're talking about retiring again...
I meant my schedule.
I don't want any schedule.
Clear my schedule so I can practice
acting for a while.
I've already rearranged your schedule.
I cleared everything
except that thing tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
I have a schedule tomorrow?
What is it?
-You have a date.
-Again?
Tomorrow?
With Seo Dojae?
I asked you here so we can talk.
How far are you willing to go for Dojae?
Can you...
...give me a little pay raise?
Why?
It seems like I'll have
another secret to keep.
I should get paid more for my work.
What do you do with the money you make?
Make installments for savings.
How diligent of you.
Did you know?
Dojae is...
Ga...
"Ga"...?
Dojae and a ma....
"Ma"...?
Never mind.
What about Han Segye?
Is he seeing her again?
He never broke up with her.
They will go on a date
tomorrow, in public.
Good.
Keep an eye on everything he does.
In regards to what exactly?
I think...
...it would be all right
if they got married.
All of a sudden?
Dojae will make the headlines
in the national section...
...instead of the entertainment section.
I have to stop that from happening.
I'm unbiased, but...
...a high school kid is too much.
What are you talking about...?
You're always hang out with him
so you should know.
He's seeing a guy, too.
What?
I heard you'll go abroad again.
That's right. Now, tell me
how you're doing these days.
I have butterflies in my stomach.
I think I miss her.
That's pretty good.
Is it?
You always dreaded seeing people.
Your condition has improved in a way.
But...
...I don't feel quite like myself.
Which part of you?
The basics of business are saying
what the opposite party wants to hear...
...to get what I want in the end.
And I'm very good at doing business.
But suddenly, I don't feel like
doing that anymore.
Do you know exactly...
...what the opposite party wants to hear?
I believe I know it exactly.
What is it?
I'm sorry.
"I'm sorry."
If you don't want to say
that word, then don't.
Say what you want to say,
looking at the face you want to see.
Do not be afraid.
It only means that you've found a new you.
These are absolutely necessary
for housework. Please prepare them.
All of it?
By the way...
... what on earth are you wearing?
I don't get along with my sister.
Me too.
If it's disturbing,
then just look at my face.
You know you're handsome, don't you?
Everyone says I'm more
on the pretty side.
You say that without batting an eye.
You should be humble.
I didn't need them right away.
It's because I'm busy.
I won't have time for except now.
I've been wanting to tell you.
Thank you for letting me stay
at your place.
I'll try to make you feel comfortable.
The house is empty
most of the time anyway.
I prefer if someone manages
the house for me.
That's why I agreed.
Don't take it the wrong way.
I'll pay my debts and leave
as soon as possible.
As you wish.
I've been meaning to say something too.
I am not interested either.
-In me?
-In a younger guy.
Oh my, look who it is. It's Eunho.
Hello.
Our seasonal promotion will start soon.
Aren't you coming to work?
Our sales increased
last time thanks to you.
If I was the owner of the mart,
I would've given it to you.
I've found a very good job.
Bye.
Just how many part-time jobs do you have?
Do you work using your popularity?
Let's just say my popularity is
like public property.
Now it's private property.
I'm the one who's paying you.
I think you should get paid for smiling.
It has commodity value.
That was an assessment, not a compliment.
Do you want money?
No.
How's this one? Isn't it nice?
It's nice.
-How about this one?
-Nice.
This one?
You're lost in your own thoughts.
Where's your head right now?
-The control tower.
-The control tower?
Why are you over there?
What?
"Uncle?"
Are you in touch with your uncle?
What are you saying? Why would I...
Yeah, I totally stay in touch
with my uncle. He's a good man.
Hello, Uncle.
Where are you now?
How's your family and your business?
I'm at home. Why?
Let's meet. I'm at the cafe
in front of your house.
You call me out of the blue asking
to meet without any explanation?
I need to tell you something.
Fine.
I'll be on my way.
My uncle's asking to meet. He's nearby.
-I'm going out.
-Can I go and say hello?
No!
You scared me. Why did you yell?
Well...
My uncle is very shy of strangers
and an introvert.
He can't even make eye contact.
He can't stand people.
Fine. Just go.
I'll be right back.
Why are you staring?
To avoid making a mistake.
It's my first time to see
your hair like this.
I was at home just now.
I'm sorry. It must've made you nervous.
You don't have to be apologetic.
So, what do you want to tell me?
There's one good thing
about our relationship going public.
We can meet openly in public.
This is the interview questions list
for tomorrow.
This is what you wanted to tell me?
We need to plan what we're going to say.
Right.
We are the couple of the century.
What else could I expect?
-What happened that time...
-A mistake.
It was in the heat of the moment.
So stop avoiding me.
There's no need to do that.
Did I avoid you?
What are you going to wear tomorrow?
We should wear matching clothes
since we'll be working.
What else should we match?
I didn't reply to your text
because too much time has...
I'll send my answers in writing.
Ms. Han.
Let's not overwork ourselves.
It feels like I'm working overtime.
Here.
No, thank you.
I'm on a diet.
That must be hard for you.
Not as hard as this.
What's next? The interview?
Next...
...is this.
Open it.
This is to thank you
for your gift on our last date.
I guess I should open it
with a happy look on face.
What a detailed act.
Would this be enough?
It's not an act.
I gave them to you because I wanted to.
Because they're pretty.
I thought they would look great on you.
Since you already have a necklace...
...I can't change that.
Many people are curious
about your love story.
Who was the first
to confess their feelings?
It was me.
May I ask how you said it?
"You're the kindest women I've ever met."
I fell for her because
she's so kind-hearted.
In just one week after we met.
Segye, you must be having a flashback.
You're blushing.
It's a little hot out here.
What names did you use to save
each other in your contacts?
-Well...
-"Auntie."
Pardon?
Yes, I used "Uncle."
Does it mean anything?
No.
It just came up.
No one would be suspicious about it.
I did it because someone told me to.
The way she thinks is cute, isn't it?
How did you come up with that?
Excuse me for asking...
...but when did you have your first kiss?
No comment for this question.
We haven't.
We haven't kissed.
I informed you that
the interview will be off...
...if you ask a question
that is not on the list.
That's enough interview for today.
I gave you enough for your article.
You didn't have to drive me all this way.
I don't think so.
Right. This is work.
You're always meticulous in your work.
Thank you. Bye.
What are you doing tomorrow?
I'm going for a read-through to somewhere
very far, for a long time.
Why?
-The day after tomorrow?
-I have work.
-And the next day?
-I have work too.
-Exactly.
We're both busy.
Speaking of work...
... great job today.
It was a great business
for both of us today.
How many more times do we need to do this?
This?
Work.
Let's get it done as soon as possible.
So we can end our contract.
It make me uncomfortable...
...in many ways.
We didn't kiss?
We didn't?
Fine.
Let's just say we didn't.
We never did.
Such a coward.
Oh my gosh.
Are you angry because
I had the interview my own way?
I did it for your sake...
Is that what you came here to say?
Ms. Han...
For my sake?
Nothing good will be left in this world
if you act for my sake again.
-What are you...?
-Things like expectation, trust and hope.
You don't know how I feel
right now, do you?
Right. You can't even remember me anyway.
How could you possibly know how I feel?
How would you know what's in my mind?
Do you want me to say I'm sorry?
If that's what you want...
...I don't want to say it.
Then don't.
It's too late for that.
So annoying.
(Confidentiality Agreement)
Why do you look so weary?
You didn't sleep last night?
The crickets were crying too much.
Where? From your heart?
Sometimes...
...I wonder how much you know.
I know a lot...
...but I just pretend not to know.
Did you have breakfast?
I have gimbap in the car.
Later. I'll get an upset stomach
if I eat in the car.
Come on. We're late.
Hey, buddy. It looks like
you stirred things up again.
Top star H took away
C's wardrobe out of jealousy.
H, the biggest celebrity troublemaker...
...recently participated in the audition
for a supporting role in L's project.
It seems like old habits die hard.
This time, she stole the wardrobe
of C, the lead actress.
C had no choice...
...but to forfeit her wardrobe
to H, who is her senior.
Despite C's generosity,
H did not even thank her once.
The concerned parties
collectively said that H did this...
...out of jealousy because
she lost the lead role to C.
"H" for Han Segye, C
"C" for Chae Yoori.
That crazy...
God damn it, that witch set this up!
That witch with a capital B!
I'll beat the shit out of this witch!
I'm so pissed, god darn it!
Witch I'll end you!
-Good shot!
How far did the ball go?
Men need time for some male bonding.
Isn't that right?
I need some time for myself right now.
Then how would you like
to be unemployed?
-Good shot!
-Good shot.
Good shot, Director Kim.
That was Mr. Seo, not Director Kim.
Really?
Good shot, Mr. Seo.
Why you little brat!
It's fine, Mr. Chairman.
Chief Seo has a naughty sense of humor.
He's so mischievous all the time.
The three of you are
very similar in style.
It's hard to tell
no matter how much I look.
It must be so troublesome
looking after this rascal.
No, sir. I didn't do anything.
Chief Seo excels in both work and dating.
He's dating?
Are you dating that model?
You're so far behind.
You should check out the Internet.
What did you...
You little punk...!
Good shot.
I've increased the sales.
You shouldn't treat me like a golf ball.
So...
...when my daughter said
she wanted to have Segye...
... she didn't mean Segye as in
"the world," but that model?
-Actress.
-Yes. The model.
Bring her over sometimes
so we can eat together.
For what?
My daughter wants to have her.
You need to know that there are
some things you cannot buy...
...in this world, Mr. Chairman.
Don't get smart with me.
I'm holding a golf club.
I'm holding one too.
And it's my turn.
Chief Seo, I got you a juice.
Did you mix something in here?
No way.
Joohwan, drink this.
I don't get hazard pay. You drink it.
My dear Chief Seo...
You should stay sharp if you don't
want to lose the war of succession.
It's about CEO Kang of One Air.
She even went to Mr. Kim's luncheon.
-What did you say just now?
-You know...
The only women invite to that luncheon...
...are all either actresses or singers.
Isn't that amazing?
No matter what they said,
she only said "yes, yes"...
...with a big smile on her face.
It takes a lot of ambition to do that.
She may be a woman, but we should...
...learn that from her.
Bravo, CEO Kang. Impressive.
"Miss."
What?
That's "Miss Kang" to you.
"CEO Miss Kang."
You should have some respect
to the member of the owner's family.
Director Kim?
And my sister doesn't exist
to hear your compliment.
You need to know your place.
I put that down because
I'm relatively nice.
If CEO Kang was here,
it won't be the juice.
It would be the glass that hits you.
Jeez!
"Murder? I can't.
I pass out when I see blood."
"Then you get out of here now, Princess."
"Or go and die first."
"You're getting in my way."
"Number Two's cell phone rings.
Number Two's very startled."
"It's her. It must be her."
"She said she's coming here to kill me."
"She's coming for me."
"Number Three picks up the phone
without hesitation."
"Hello?"
"Say something if you called."
"You're not the owner of the phone."
"Are you all gathered together
to make it easier for me?"
I'm sorry.
I need to go to the ladies' room.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
Shall we continue?
"You're not the owner of the phone."
"Are you all gathered together
to make it easier for me?"
-"I'm now..."
-Sir?
Let's just call it a day and have a drink.
Yoori.
I'm really tired. I had so many lines.
Everyone's exhausted.
Can you give us a break?
Hey.
Bring them in.
(Like a Girlfriend)
No big deal.
Just in case there's not enough
booze for everyone.
Oh, my.
Not only we have the same taste in
clothes, but we also think alike.
Ms. Yoo.
What's that?
(A Fine Day)
(Like a Girlfriend) (A Fine Day)
Don't worry about Kingkang.
Worry about yourself.
Hey, where are you?
I work at the owner's place
and sleep in the storage.
-I'm a slave.
-Hey...
Do you want me to buy you a house?
-Are you drunk?
-Hey, I can afford a house.
I'm rich.
Then transfer 100 million won
to my account now.
Hey.
Well... anyway...
Please look after Kingkang.
She's only half-drunk.
One hot vanilla latte, take-away.
Do you have the coupon?
No.
What's this?
Because you're a good person.
By any chance, do you like dogs?
Anyone who likes dogs is a good person.
The atmosphere is nice
with a beautiful lady around.
That's right.
You're still young at heart.
Mr. Kim adores me so much...
...that I get to be here even though
I'm just a young actress.
Thank you very much.
Oh, no.
A woman shouldn't pour drinks.
Look who it is.
Chief Seo of T'road Airline.
What brings you here after
rejecting all our invitations?
I just happened to pass by.
I feel like drinking for many reasons.
Of course. We must drink
in a historic moment like this.
Here.
I should pour you a drink.
Stop.
What do you think you're doing?
I poured enough for the next person
who will sit here.
Stop inviting us
to this ridiculous gathering.
We are not the kind of people
who you can invite any time.
Me or CEO Kang.
This one's on me.
Hey.
-Why that...
-Hey, Chief Seo!
Why are you looking after Han Segye's dog?
She offered money.
You'll do anything for money?
Not just anything, but most.
Did you invite someone other than the dog?
Of course not. It's not even my house.
Isn't it your guest?
That can't be.
I have no friends.
It's your brother.
-Who?
-It's your brother.
When did I get a brother...
Mr. Seo Dojae.
Hurry up and hide.
Take that with you.
Okay.
Eunho.
No matter what happens,
do not come out of the room.
There's nothing more dangerous
than you coming out.
Were we close enough for you
to show up at my house unannounced?
I have a confession to make.
Do you have some time?
You can speak there.
Why don't we go in and talk?
You might start shouting.
Speak where you stand.
It's about the luncheon you went.
I roughed them up for you.
-What?
-See? I knew you'd shout.
Who do you think you are!
That's intimidating and authoritative.
Why didn't you give them this attitude?
(Mr. Kim)
This is just wonderful.
Ms. Kang, what did you say to your brother
to make him do that?
I didn't think you were like that.
You're like a little girl
tattling to your brother!
Mr. Kim, you have a very happy,
comfortable life, don't you?
That's all because...
...you're ignorant.
-Because you don't learn.
-What?
Don't make it so obvious
that you failed to learn anything.
Have you no shame?
Oh well. You wouldn't feel shame
since you don't know anything
Hey!
Pipe down.
Is that a dog barking?
Why is a dog talking to a human?
See?
I had to listen to that
because you interfered.
Do you think I can't talk back?
I just didn't want to.
I know what you're good at.
So do what you do best.
Because I hate seeing you...
...lose to someone.
Yeah, right.
Who do you think you are?
Me?
Your older brother.
Since when were you my brother?
Well...
...I think it's been about 10 years
since I became your brother.
You have a dog?
What are you talking about?
I don't like dogs.
Just now, that was me coughing.
Is there someone inside?
No.
Why are you getting in my way?
Do you think I get in your way
all the time?
Don't kid yourself.
Do you hear yourself right now?
No.
I'm tired. Just go.
If you want to say thank you,
call me when you don't have a guest.
No one's inside.
And I'm not thankful at all.
Introduce me sometime.
It seems like he's a dog owner.
No one's here!
I am sorry.
Are you rearing me or something?
The maid became my weakness...
I ruined everyone's mood.
I'm sorry.
Have you eaten?
I haven't seen you eat at all.
I'm a little nervous
after the read-through.
I can't eat.
You're still the same as before.
People said you've changed.
I guess they were all lies.
You were never the kind
of person who gives excuses.
You'd rather withstand all the criticisms.
I know you're all bitter and sad.
It's okay.
I'm used to all that now.
I'm fine.
Things like that are difficult
to get used to.
And you can't be fine with it.
I don't have a choice.
You said you wanted to kill her
out of compassion.
During the reading last time.
You want to kill her when you pity her?
Her heartfelt sympathy
could've blinded her.
Can't you be compassionate to yourself?
Why?
Because you might kill yourself?
You can kill someone out of compassion.
But you can also...
...hug that person out of compassion.
Life...
...is different from movies.
So...
...just give yourself a hug.
Or you can find someone who can hug you.
Take a walk before you come in.
The stars are pretty.
It seems like they're all up there
to comfort me.
Someone who can hug me...?
Someone...
...who really knows me.
The booze tastes sweet
when I drink with you.
Have a drink with me.
Let me take a break.
I drank too much.
Just this one time.
Okay. I will let you off this time.
Instead...
...look pretty and drink.
-Pardon?
-There's a scene where you drink.
Think of it as practice.
I can't do that all of a sudden.
Why?
Don't want to?
Jeez. You're such a party pooper.
You're ruining the moment.
That's not right.
Why wouldn't I want to?
I'll do it.
I won't use a glass.
I'll drink from the bottle.
That's the spirit.
Try biting your lip lightly.
Go ahead. Looking good.
Okay, just like that. Drink.
That's sexy.
If you want to continue,
I'll be your drinking buddy.
Darn it, that soju was strong.
(Mom)
Yeah, what's up?
I saw your interview.
You two looked great together.
Did they Photoshop
your boyfriend's picture?
Or does he really look like that?
Mom...
You sound tipsy again.
Hey, did you drink?
Mom...
What was it like dating Dad?
Why would you talking about
your dad all of a sudden?
Tell me some stories from
when you were dating him.
Your dad?
There was nothing much.
He suddenly showed up
and he was suddenly sweet...
Suddenly I was in love and
suddenly he disappeared.
Dad is so bad.
Why did he suddenly show up...
...and was suddenly sweet?
Right?
What's really bad is...
...that he suddenly made me fall in love
and then suddenly disappeared.
You're right.
Why?
-Did you fight with your boyfriend?
-No.
I was wondering if all
relationships are like this.
I was curious.
What's your relationship like?
Just...
...very happy.
It feels...
...very real.
Right.
This one feels real, but the ones
before that seems fake, right?
Maybe you've finally met your match.
I need to hang up now.
Okay.
Don't forget to relieve
your hangover tomorrow morning.
Tell your boyfriend that I said hi.
Okay.
Now that I think about it,
this pisses me off.
Why should I be like this?
(Auntie)
Why didn't you call me? Why?
Because...
...you said you'll be working.
Still, you should've called me.
If I can't take the call because of work,
you should call again and again.
How could you have me call first?
Ms. Han?
Did you drink again?
So annoying.
Why did you suddenly show up...
...and suddenly be all sweet?
Where are you now?
Why?
You want to come?
I wish...
I wish you would appear
right before my eyes now, but...!
I'll stop.
I want to stop.
I feel...
...so stupid and I hate it.
Ms. Han?
Who do you think you are?
Let's talk later.
Who are you to meddle?
Who said I needed your help?
Did you just hit me?
Yeah.
I hit you and so what?
You didn't like that?
Have you lost it
because nobody's around?
Were you having a good time back there?
It sure didn't look like it.
Yeah.
I was having a good time.
If you put up with behaviors like that...
...and let it all slide, the other girls
will go through worse.
If the lead actress
tolerates everything...
...they will walk all over
the other girls.
What does it have to do with me?
Mind your own business.
You're nothing but a supporting actress.
Fine. Let's just I didn't like
what happened earlier and stop this.
What did you dislike about?
Who are you to dislike anything?
Canceling your schedules.
Running away from the set.
Dating just about anybody.
I don't do those things.
Those are all you.
Enough. We can talk later...
Why?
You think you're untouchable now that
you have a rich guy in your pocket?
You're so naive.
Who would like a girl like you?
Don't you get it?
He's just playing games with you.
What now?
Are you acting?
Han Segye.
Hello?
I need help!
Segye.
Are you okay?
How...?
You're crazy.
You collapsed because
you weren't eating well.
You poured alcohol down
in an empty stomach.
I'm sorry.
You must've been scared.
Why is that guy...
He called me because
you weren't picking up.
You had me worried...
Segye.
I'll go.
Ms. Han Segye.
That's not me.
Yes it is.
You can't recognize me when you should...
...and you recognize me
when you shouldn't.
You always have it your way.
I told you not to run away.
I was clear on that.
Let's cancel our contract.
Let's cancel our confidentiality or
or dating agreement or whatever.
All right.
Yeah.
Publish an article.
We broke up.
All good?
If you're going to do this,
why did you kiss me?
That's what I should be asking.
Are you stupid? Don't you know any better?
I don't know.
I'm not used to this kind of thing.
I can't get used to it
no matter how hard I try.
Making guesses on things I cannot see.
And for that...
...I hate myself.
I have never loved myself since that day.
Not once.
When asked if you have
anything to say after a kiss...
...I heard there are two answers.
"I love you"...
...or "I'm sorry."
I don't want to say I'm sorry.
That leaves only one answer.
So I couldn't say it.
How am I supposed to say it?
When I'm a total mess?
Say it.
Just say it.
I'm a mess, too.
If I give a name to this feeling...
...things will get out of hand.
We won't forget it for a long time.
I can't forget it anyway.
I will never forget
for the rest of my life.
You're the man who recognized me.
Will you be all right...
...with me?
Do you mean it?
I mean it.
I don't believe you.
Prove it.