(Aunt)
Are you okay?
I heard from Woomi.
I'll explain to Woomi...
Hello?
What are you doing?
Is it true?
Tell me if it's true.
That you can't recognize people's faces.
I'm sorry. I'll call you again.
What's this?
Proof that you're ill.
Records of your accident.
I'm sure...
...I've already...
Already got rid of them?
Is that what you care about, right now?
No matter how you use my weakness...
Do you think that low of me?
Why are you making me a cheap coward?
Who do you think you are?
Who are you to go easy on me?
Let's go in.
We can talk when we get inside.
(Medical Record Seo Dojae)
All this time...
...I thought you've been
ignoring me on purpose.
But it was all a misunderstanding.
You're ill...
...and here I thought...
I did recognize you.
Though there were times that I couldn't,
but I do recognize you most of the time.
You walk very straight.
And you're always...
...bold.
You're usually mad at me
when we run into each other.
And when you do...
...I get to hear your voice first.
The reason I was mad...
It's because of me, right?
I know.
I'm sorry.
What about Dad?
How do you recognize Dad?
As for Dad...
...I didn't really...
...have to try hard to tell him apart.
Whenever I see him, he's usually
the one to greet me first.
And he also held my hand first.
Even though...
...he had no idea about my condition.
To tell you the truth,
I'm a little surprised.
I've imagined...
...situations like this a lot of times.
It's always the worst-case scenario
every single time.
I didn't expect for you to say that.
What do you mean?
You sound like...
...a real younger sister.
You're really making me feel horrible.
You better tell me the truth.
What is there to tell you?
He just made a mistake.
He definitely made eye contact with me.
Well...
...that's because it's too dark.
Not that dark enough
that he couldn't see my face.
All right.
Last time, you said
that he wasn't even shocked...
...when he saw you change, right?
Why wasn't he shocked?
Woomi...
I know...
You would've told me
if it's something you can tell people.
I don't even know anymore.
I'm so dumbfounded.
Why is everyone being so careless?
Just go get some sleep.
I'm leaving.
(Uncle)
Dr. Oh.
Is it possible for Mr. Seo's
condition to get worse?
Regarding that illness,
there's no such thing as "getting worse".
It doesn't get worse nor better.
But...
...he's been receiving treatment
from you for years.
That illness is incurable.
There is no way to cure it.
All this time...
...I've only been helping Seo Dojae
with the things that he needs to do.
Like what?
Coming to terms with it.
Even though it won't...
...improve or deteriorate his condition...
...it makes his life better.
I've simply been helping Seo Dojae...
...so that he won't torture himself.
Sara knows about my condition now.
I'll resign.
It's my fault.
I'll take responsibility for it.
Why is my condition your responsibility?
I didn't take you as someone
who runs away when things get bad.
I thought wrong of you.
What happened?
She found my medical records.
That's impossible. We've already...
...got rid of the records.
Or so we thought.
But looks like someone
made the effort to find it.
Do you think Director Kim did it?
I don't know...
I'm not sure yet.
I will keep an eye on him for now.
Joohwan.
Thanks.
Give me a raise then.
I think Woomi had it figured out.
There's nothing I can do
because I'm so worried.
I have a girlfriend
who is worried about me.
I like it.
I'm being really serious right now.
I'm also being serious about liking you.
Well, of course
I seriously like you too...
I like you, but...
What does...
...she mean to you?
What does she mean to me?
Well...
...we've always been there for each other.
And we'll continue to be
there for each other.
You'll be friends forever?
Yes.
Even if Woomi runs away
because she hates me...
I'll hold on to her so she won't leave me.
I have no choice then.
I'll have to hold on to her as well.
If I want to stay with you forever.
I'm seriously so done with drinking.
I refuse to drink even a drop of alcohol
for the time being.
Goodness.
The hangover must have been terrible.
Geez. You always went on
about being a priest.
Hi. You're here?
What's going on?
I don't think we can do this sober.
Sit down. What are you waiting for?
Drink up! Drink up!
Bottoms up! Bottoms up!
Let me pour you a shot.
You drank it all up.
So that's what happened.
That's why you're such a jerk.
-Hey!
-What?
You're the one who called him a jerk
in the first place.
Did I really come across as a jerk?
No. No.
It's okay.
That's how people are.
When you're in that situation...
...you tend to become very passive
and sensitive.
I understand you.
I mean, you also know, right?
Segye is also like that.
She's really like that.
What do you mean by "really like that?"
You're really...
You can be...
...really mean.
You get what I mean, right?
Geez.
Do you want to see
how mean I can really be?
Sorry.
I'm sorry...
...for hating you...
...this whole time.
You hated me?
Well, we weren't exactly
fond of you anyway.
Geez. How can you say that to his face?
You should've told him that long ago.
Oh my.
You must be drunk. You're laughing.
I'm not drunk. I'm just...
...in a good mood.
That's exactly what it means to be drunk.
What about tomorrow?
Do you have anything on your schedule?
Of course, she does.
But that's okay.
Drink up! Drink up!
What are you talking about?
Hey!
Just because you're going to change
your hairstyle a little bit,
it doesn't mean you can't get drunk.
You're changing your hairstyle?
She has a commercial to shoot.
It'll just be a tiny change.
It's going to be a tiny change to us,
but it's going to look
totally different on camera.
That's right.
You might get confused
if she changes her hairstyle.
Then, should I send you a picture of her,
whenever she changes her hairstyle?
-Would that be helpful?
-Great idea.
Why would you send
pictures to my boyfriend?
Geez... you lovesick fool.
I didn't raise her to be like that.
There's something I've always
been curious about.
When you answered her phone last time...
...why did you tell me
that she's taking a shower?
Oh no.
What should we do?
This guy, he may be an adult,
but he doesn't know anything.
That's not true. I do know a little.
You do?
Is that so?
Then, why did you...
It's true.
I know stuff.
Oh my. Really?
What do you know?
-Why did you tell me that...
-I know how babies are made!
What?
You know how babies are made?
Babies come out of your belly button.
That's how you become a parent.
The baby will come out
of your belly button like this...
That's okay.
I don't really care.
-Our Eunho is all grown up.
-That's correct.
Are you feeling better after this walk?
That's what I want to ask you.
Are you sober now?
I'm not drunk.
Yet, you were smiling all the time.
That's because...
...I was happy.
I was happy and surprised.
Thank you for being nice to my friends.
I'm more thankful to you.
I thought I won't be able
to do this my whole life.
I thought...
...I will never have any friends.
Isn't it interesting?
I found love...
...but I've also got friendship.
Actually...
...those two come together.
Friendship is a type of love.
I couldn't find any information on her.
She doesn't have any children.
It seems like she has a boyfriend...
...but that's Seo Dojae.
Well, that's something you can find
on the Internet though.
You called me over at this hour
to tell me that?
You're not doing enough
for the amount I paid you.
There's one more thing.
This might seem strange in a way.
You don't see her entering the toilet.
You only see her coming out.
What's this?
Does it make sense?
Why don't we...
...have a mom?
Where did that kid suddenly pop out from?
Five days before and after
have always been risky.
It's okay.
"Five days before and after"?
(Han Segye Disappears While Filming)
(Han Segye and Seo Dojae
Decided to Stay Friends)
(Han Segye and Seo Dojae Breakup?)
(Han Segye is Dating
a Third Generation Heir?)
(Han Segye is a single mother?)
(Han Segye Disappeared During
an Award Ceremony Again)
Am I going crazy because
I'm digging too deep into this?
Wait a second.
There is a reasonable explanation.
-I'll be in the waiting room.
-Okay.
Oh my. Segye.
How have you been?
Fancy to meet you here.
See?
I told you we might see
each other again soon.
Are you here to get your hair done?
I'm starting a reality show soon.
It's a show where they'll film me 24/7.
Is that so?
I think I've seen an article or two.
By the way...
...do you remember the child actor
that suddenly show up at our filming set?
A child actor?
Who?
You probably don't know...
...after you suddenly disappeared.
A little boy suddenly appeared.
It was as if he was replacing you.
Do you think this is some kind of magic?
A person doesn't disappear or appear
suddenly like that.
My point exactly.
It sounds like magic right?
No matter how hard I try to find.
I don't know his name nor his number.
He's my relative.
His name is Yoo Woojoo. He's 10 years old.
He's not in Korea now, though. Why?
Do you want to meet him?
Ms. Yoo...
Can I really meet him?
He was so cute.
I want him to appear in my reality show.
It's so noisy.
You.
Over there.
Why are you being so loud?
Are you...
...talking to me?
Then...
...does this shop belong to you?
Even if it's yours...
...you're bothering the customers
by being so loud.
Don't you know who I am?
This is my first time seeing you.
I don't know who you are.
So do you want to introduce yourself?
Who is this person?
Who is she?
Huh?
You said only VIPs come here.
That's why I started coming here.
VIP?
Who?
That person?
I know her though.
Geez. I should go to another salon.
Let's go.
Okay.
I owe you another one.
I wasn't helping you.
She was really being loud.
Do you come here often?
No.
This is my first time.
But...
...I don't think I'll be coming back.
It's been unpleasant.
Eunho...
...must be waiting for your call.
Tell him to wait a little longer.
That's...
...the least he could do.
Did Eunho really find
himself a rich girlfriend?
We don't know that yet.
Ryu Eunho, that brat. Seriously.
I'm so proud of him.
-Surprise!
What's going on?
I've made up my mind.
I'm going to let you do whatever you want.
Today...
...a day to celebrate.
We're celebrating your rebirth.
Eunho...
...you're one year old today.
Treat me as your older sister from now on.
Blow the candle.
Should I...
...not be a priest?
What?
I'm going to work.
What has gotten into him all of a sudden?
What do you think?
The Lord has answered my prayers.
I've seen that kind of look a lot before.
Guys stare at me like that when...
Hey! Ryu Eunho!
-Why?
-What's wrong?
I think...
...he has a girlfriend.
What?
Nonsense.
I know that look though.
Did it go well with Ms. Kang?
Was there any problem?
Weren't you the one
who has a problem with her?
Don't say something upsetting like that.
I was just encouraging her to do better.
I'm just giving her a slight nudge.
Don't take it the wrong way.
By the way...
...did Ms. Kang change her mind?
Is she on the same page as you?
Why does her opinion matters?
What's more important
is to bring Seo Dojae down...
...and put Ms. Kang in his position.
And after that...
Shh...
We don't need to go over
what happens next.
I will help you out.
Okay?
By the way...
...about Seo Dojae's weakness...
Tell me about it too, Mr. Choi.
We're in this big scheme together...
...how can you hide it from me?
There will be time for this.
You're right.
There's time for everything.
You changed your hairstyle.
Did you do it for me?
I don't change my hairstyle for others.
Do you like the gift I gave you?
I'm not sure if it's a gift or a bomb.
It depends on how you use it.
It also depends on who I send it to.
Have you forgotten?
You came to me first.
You said you wanted
to take over the company.
You're right.
I did say that.
I can't believe I used to be that person.
Is it because of that guy?
That jerk from the other day?
Are you okay?
Excuse me...
Is this enough?
Go.
What? Do you want more?
-Geez. You...
-Let's go.
Let's just leave.
Do you not know how to apologize?
Apologize for what?
Just go buy another pair of shoes.
I guess...
...I did change my hair for him to see.
You two are pathetic.
Why didn't you call me?
You said you would.
I'll call you now.
I can't leave right now.
I have to sell those.
That shouldn't be a problem.
I'll buy them all.
Do you mind drinking here?
That's what I should ask.
Don't you mind being here?
Is it really okay to bring me
to your favorite hangout?
I've just...
...taken one more step
into your personal life.
Right now.
Well...
Why did you have to appear
and wipe my shoes?
Your shirt got dirty, right?
I can just wash it.
I don't think it'll come off.
Then, I'll just throw it away.
Aren't you spending too
much money because of me?
It's fine.
I'll just earn more.
What made you want to become a priest?
No reason.
No reason?
What made you want to become a cool lady?
What made you want to do well?
As for me, it's just my gut feeling.
A reason?
I don't have one.
It's my dream.
One I've had for a long time.
That's nice.
To not have a reason.
As for me...
...I've always had a reason.
I wanted to survive.
I don't want to be looked down upon.
Those are the reasons...
...that made me who I am.
That became my habit.
Fine.
I understand now.
I'll step back.
I'll let God have you.
Why are giving me away?
I also want to find it.
The reason...
...why my dream has changed...
...to you.
You said you like nice people.
I do.
I'm a bad person.
I even lied to you.
I know.
What can a nice person
and a bad person...
...do together?
Should we become friends?
There's no such thing as friends
between a man and a woman.
Why do you have a white porcelain vase
from the Joseon dynasty in your house?
Why? Why are you smiling?
It's nothing.
Don't try to fool me.
What is it?
Come on. What is it?
If you don't tell me, I'm going to
imagine something very weird.
Then, I'm going to go home and
bury my face in my pillow, and cry.
Do you like that?
I just thought...
...you look similar.
"Look similar"?
Me..
...and that thing?
In what way?
Do I have a round face or something?
Well...
...sort of.
Unbelievable.
Then, you would think of me
every day when you see this?
-Not every day.
-Not every day, but very often?
When did you start thinking of me?
Since we first met?
Since the day...
...I started to understand your condition.
And that's the day...
...I started wanting to understand...
...this person named Han Segye.
So did you come to understand her?
I've come to love you.
I went from being afraid of everything
...to not being afraid of anything.
I feel like I've transformed.
Because you met me.
Because I met you.
I'm so glad...
...that we found each other.
It'll be that day soon, right?
Wow. You have a great memory.
When the day comes, you have
to be with me all day. Okay?
Don't go anywhere.
Come on.
Let's go home, Kingkang.
Let's head inside. Are you tired?
Let's get you to bed... Oh my god!
Who are you?
It's me.
You...
Hey.
Is it that day already?
It's not supposed to be today.
What?
Yes.
Is it because you're tired?
Why did this happen so suddenly?
Do you have any other symptoms?
Not really.
Where are you going right now?
Just over there.
Are you going to see Seo Dojae?
Gosh...
Of course. You still have your boyfriend.
Good for you.
You still have someone to call you fondly
even when you look like that.
Kingkang, what's wrong?
I think she's cold.
I'm going inside.
Don't take too long. You shouldn't
be walking around looking like that.
Gosh. Good times.
Kingkang, it's your friend.
- What on earth?!
- My gosh! What?
Why did you change again?
Did I change?
No.
I didn't change.
You...
Earlier...
I'm sure I saw you...
We're in trouble.
What the?
Who are you?
Darn it.
Who hired you?
Chae Yoori, I could kill her...
-You're reporting her to the police?
-No.
It's me.
Can we meet?
Have you lost your mind?
You hired someone to tail me?
Do you want to get sued?
Sue me if you want.
But I need to know what this is
before I go to jail.
Are you my fan?
You even have a video of me on your phone.
It's weird, you know.
I don't see you going in.
But I see you leaving.
I watched the footage
from the very beginning.
But you never went into that washroom.
I could only see you walking out of there.
On top of that...
...your manager, who never leaves
your side, saw a stranger...
...and calls him by your name.
Doesn't it sound weird to you?
What are you trying to say?
I think you're the one
who has something to say.
I have no idea what you're talking about.
Right.
I have no idea
what this is all about either.
But then, I remembered something...
Every time you sign a contract,
you ask for a week of break
every month without exception.
If they don't let you, you run away.
Is this your secret?
You must have gone crazy.
You've been watching too many movies.
I don't watch movies that often.
I don't even watch the ones I starred in.
I'll know if I'm crazy or
not in a few days.
Yeah.
I've been doing some calculations,
since the day you disappeared on set,
and the boy appeared.
It's coming up soon, right?
Are you scared?
Then, you should just spill it to me now.
I might be nice and keep your secret
after hearing it.
Why are you running away?
It's not worth my time
to hear more of your nonsense.
I see. So you are running away.
Do you think people will believe you?
Whether they believe it or not, I'm right.
That you change appearances.
Wow, this is so fascinating.
Is it a virus or something?
What is this?
What are you doing right now?
We should find out, then.
We both can't leave this elevator
until I change.
We'll stay here together all night.
Wow.
I really have to give you credit.
You really are good at acting.
Why waste your energy on this?
There are easier ways.
I'm starting a reality show soon.
Have I told you that before?
You should appear on the show.
The cameras will be recording
24 hours a day.
Why?
Are you turning me down?
Sure. Let's do it.
If you really don't believe me.
Our ratings points are going to skyrocket.
Thank you, Segye.
(In case of an emergency, ring bell)
Hello?
-Hello?
-Yes?
We're stuck in the elevator.
We'll be right there.
The press release
has already been sent out.
That witch. It's as if she's
been waiting for this moment.
It's a miracle that I managed to
keep this a secret all there years.
Don't worry.
I'll sort it out no matter what.
You?
What are you planning to do?
Han Segye.
You trust me, right?
Dojae...
I get that you don't like me,
but how can you ignore me like this?
-It's not that...
-Director Kim.
Are you also going to ignore me?
When we haven't seen
each other in a while.
It's not that.
My eyesight is getting worse these days.
I didn't recognize you for a second.
But still...
...it's an honor to be greeted
by such a beauty.
Director Kim, maybe it's
time for you to retire.
No way.
What are you doing? Let's go.
Something is fishy.
But I don't know what.
Thank you.
It's nothing.
I don't like the sight of
someone else beating up...
...something I'm already beating.
It's the fish I gave you.
It's still alive.
It's my favorite fish.
I thought it wasn't you
since you called my name.
You're not dressed as usual, either.
Did you come to check
if my illness is real or not?
No.
I came to check how I would feel.
Whether I would feel okay
or uncomfortable.
So how do you feel?
I think I'll be uncomfortable.
I got your medical records...
...from Kiho.
Choi Kiho and Director Kim
are conspiring...
..to take you down.
What's your reason for telling me this?
To be frank, I used to be on their side.
But I just decided to betray them.
Why?
Because you pity me?
No.
Because the person I like...
...doesn't like bad people.
Hey.
Are you in a relationship?
With whom?
What does he do?
Oh, no.
(Chae Yoori)
What do we do?
Segye isn't picking up the phone.
This is crazy.
We arranged everything
because she said she's come.
I know.
Why isn't she here yet?
She must have run away again.
I'm sorry.
I wanted to take this chance to
resolve my misunderstanding with her,
and make up with her.
But I guess the feeling wasn't mutual.
I wasn't being considerate
of her feelings.
No. Don't say that.
It's not your fault, Yoori.
You didn't know
Han Segye would run off again.
Get ready to pack up, everyone.
I did know.
(If you're not coming here,
then I'll come to you)
Wait! Segye says to
come over to her house.
She has it all set up over there.
If you're not coming here,
then I'll come to you.
(Yoo Woomi)
I'll take care of it.
Go over to my place for now.
You trust me, right?
Wait for me over there.
I'll be right there.
Mister, please take care of him.
(Ryu Eunho)
Yes. What is it?
Hey.
Listen to me.
I can hear you fine. What is it?
Go over to my place later.
Why?
Segye...
Just go there.
What was that?
Reporter Park...
...I was in a car accident.
Alright.
I need to think rationally.
I made a mistake.
This situation is happening because of me.
I am Han Segye's manager.
I am Han Segye's friend.
So I have to take responsibility.
The CEO of World Entertainment
had a car accident.
She's been hospitalized.
So Han Segye's scheduled appointments
are canceled for the day.
She can't make it.
And here I thought she ran away.
Wow. So this is how she's
getting herself out of this?
Don't you think it's a lie?
No way. It can't be a lie.
It doesn't seem like a serious accident...
...but the manager is
unconscious from the shock.
Excuse me, what number
is Yoo Woomi's room?
Yoo Woomi.
Woomi.
(Han Segye's manager
was in a car accident)
(Han Segye's manager was involved in a
car accident. The scene looks horrific)
(Top star, Han Segye misses commitments
due to manager's accident)
(Ryu Eunho)
(Department of Radiology)
I'm at the hospital where Woomi is.
I'm on my way. Stay at Woomi's house
and wait for me.
It's my fault.
This is all because of me.
Excuse me, do you have any records
of a patient named Han Segye?
No, we don't.
Then, what about...
...an unidentified man?
I mean, a woman...
Or maybe a child.
Was anyone admitted
with the patient Yoo Woomi?
Whoever it is.
Was there anyone?
No, there are no records of anyone.
Thank you.
-Hello.
-This is Seo Dojae.
I can't get in touch with Han Segye.
I'm worried.
I'm on the way to Woomi's house.
Before Woomi got into the accident,
she told me to go there.
I'm sure Segye will be there.
I'll call you when I'm there.
Segye!
Han Segye!
Segye is not here.
I need to be away...
...for a while.
I'm sorry.
Mr. Seo, the aircraft we purchased
had some slight issues,
but I already took care of it for you.
We're planning to purchase
a different model of aircraft next time...
This...
(Sunho Group executives meeting
October 6th, 2018 at 4:30PM)
It's already been more than a week.
Han Segye.
Are you okay?
Where are you?
I'll go to where you are.
Answer your phone.
Please call me.
Where on earth are you?
Please.
Stop the car!
I'm sorry.
Han Segye.
(Aunt)
How could you...
I'm sorry.
My face is...
My face...
...isn't turning back to normal.