-Are you better? -have
That's good
...Festival site
More than 70 stalls have been set up
Local specialties are also sold
Fuji Asada Winter Festival
Booking for rehearsal this Sunday
Fuji Asada's new mayor announces the end of his term as former mayor
Currently and new...
-Is it too late? -Can
Are there any club activities today?
Yes, but it shouldn't end too late
- Remember to bring everything-Okay
alright
-I'm out-going - Go slow
I only have 20 minutes to ride a bicycle from my house.
I could drive before
But around last fall, I started to ride a bicycle for my health.
I ride a bicycle for health reasons
But now this season is really good and riding a bicycle is simply harmful to health
This is where I work
- Arrived at 8:45 am - Good morning
Good morning
It's so cold today
yes
I really regret riding a bicycle to work
-Be careful not to catch a cold - OK
Hotel Manager Okuda
Not arrogant, quite friendly
We just need to wash our shirts at home
I wash my shirt once a week
Although it sounds incredible, it's still very common
Some people wash less
Sorry for a long time, this is your receipt
-Thank you -Thank you
-Please walk slowly - Good morning
-Good morning - Do you want to check out?
-Yes-Thank you
I want to confirm the information, please wait
Good morning
Payment is completed, I will provide you with the receipt
The first thing I have to do when I start my duty
Just confirm the handover with your colleagues
that is…
This guest moved from Room 302 to Room 305
-Okay-That's it
-I got it-I'm going to patrol the room
OK
- Sorry for keeping you waiting for a long time - Thank you
Thank you
Please go slowly
-Good morning -Good morning
I'll get off work first
Thanks for your hard work
There are usually two people responsible at the counter
Today I changed shifts with Takahashi after duty at Takahashi
So I was on duty with Yumi, who was on duty until 4 pm
After work
You have to keep check-out until 11:00 in the morning
Please wait
Please go slowly
By the way
There is a female guest who doesn't like to live in a corner room
Why?
Because of the hotel's corner room
-All will be haunted - Really?
I don't know, that's what the female guest said
This is the first time I've heard it
Then she clamored to change rooms
But there were no rooms available at that time
So she...
Good morning
-Do you want to check out? -Please trouble you
Please go slowly
(counter)
What did she do?
Where did I talk about?
You said she couldn't change the room
right
Then she asked me to see if there were any ghosts together
It's so annoying, can you see the ghost?
I can't see it at all, I'm just pretending to be looking for a ghost
Just look at the back of the TV, under the bed, etc.
Is there really a ghost there?
Otherwise what else can I do?
Where were the guests at that time?
She was watching me at the door
-She is really scared - Yes
Then, she whispered...
Good morning
-Good morning -Good morning
-Do you want to check out? -right
I want to confirm the information, please wait
Please go slowly
This is the counter
Very sorry, we'll give it to you right away
-I'll get the remote control battery-Okay
We can't chat well during this time
-Good morning -Good morning
Need to check out?
-Thank you -Thank you
Please go slowly
Then what?
What are you talking about?
You just said that the guest was watching you at the door
Yes, that's right
She asked me in a low voice, "Did you see a ghost?"
I said no
-Because you can't see it - Yes
Later she felt more at ease and decided to stay
It's actually useful
So she can't see the ghost
yes
Qingmei, do you believe there are ghosts?
I can't see ghosts, so I don't know
What about the aliens?
alien?
-I don't know - I think there are aliens
They may be somewhere in the universe
What do you think of that news?
What news?
It seems that some schools have discovered the ground painting
I don't know if this is happening
Really?
A while ago, on the playgrounds of primary and secondary schools
Landscape paintings similar to Nasca have appeared one after another
This is the first time I heard it, who drew it?
Who knows?
-But some people say it was painted by aliens - Someone must have had a prank
-is that so? -yes
Didn't something similar happened before
What? I don't know this
I didn't hear it at that time
I saw it later on the special show
What's going on?
that is…
A long time ago I forgot whether it was in elementary school or in junior high school
But the playground is full of desks
If I remember correctly, they are arranged into a number
-What number? -have no idea
So everyone started to guess that it was a good thing for aliens to do
Or someone wants to send some message
In the end, the initiator was caught
Really?
-I'll leave first - Thank you for your hard work
Thanks for your hard work
Every time Takahashi is on duty, he stays behind for a long time, right?
I really don't know what he is doing
It was obvious that the duty was over, but he was still at the back
- Very annoying feeling-I understand
Not bad, but it's just...
Not wrong at all
Just like when I go back, I just see him there
- Will worry about him - That's right
By the way, Takahashi must have used a bathhouse at night
-Really? -Yes, he will go there when he is on duty and rest
That's it
There is nothing wrong with using it during duty breaks
- Also right - Actually
-But I didn't see anyone using it - When I was still a newcomer
Used twice
-It's for women after all - but I decided not to tell her
-Even in men's bathhouse - only two times
-He is the only one who uses it, right? -I'm not using it now
The manager occasionally uses it
We'll take turns having lunch
I'll make my own bento on weekdays
I'll make one for my daughter
Sawada, who is on duty at mid-time from 1:00 pm, will also come
There will be three people at the counter
Until Yumi gets off work at 4 pm
-Thank you - By the way, our hotel
There are many regular customers
Like this man
-Good morning - Welcome
I'm glad to serve you again, Mr. Maruyama
-Please trouble you - He often lives here when he is on a business trip
And always take away unused spare parts like shavers and combs
- Just use your name - I always treat regular customers
Express gratitude
But when you see such a guest, you have to be very careful
-Welcome-Welcome
-Do you want to check in? -Yes, I'm Miyamoto
Please wait
Just a male guest with a female companion
The reason is
They may not bring their female companions every time
Yes, that's right
If he brought a different female companion this time
But I expressed my gratitude to him
There will be conflict
So I always
Treat them like new guests
-Welcome back -Welcome back
I'm back, this kind of weather is the best
Enjoy the beautiful scenery of Mount Fuji
This has been living here for about three months
-Mr. Murakami-Please remember to keep warm
Sometimes there are guests like him in the hotel
But of course I can't inquire about the privacy of the guests
So I have no idea where he comes from
But the only thing that can be confirmed is that he is a rich man
Wish you a happy stay
There are many staff who hate helping customers carry luggage
I do it as a rest so I don't feel annoying
I see cleaning staff very often
But I won't talk to them during non-working hours
But they secretly track their social media accounts
She feels like a person who loves traveling alone
(Preparation area)
There is a regular customer named Maruyama, right?
Is that the person who will take away the spare parts?
Yes, it's him, it's really getting more and more exaggerated
Just take away the shave and toothbrush, but recently, he even took a towel.
Really?
Although there are occasional guests
-But as a regular, he is too exaggerated - Really
Don't you tell him?
I really want to say it, but I noticed it after he left
-That's it, so there's no evidence - did you tell the manager?
To be on the safe side, I said
But he said that after all, he is a regular customer, so it is difficult to speak
Yes
It would be easier if he could catch him on the spot to get things
But it should be difficult to catch him right?
When he checked out, we could stay in the parking lot first
Wait until he's about to get on the bus
We said we wanted to check his bag
If he said, "Why?"
We can say, "You may have taken a towel into your bag by mistake."
So that's it, you're giving him a step
Yes, if that happens, he will be more cooperative
Speaking of this, I met Sawada in the supermarket before...
Yes, but...
...I saw her take a lot of free plastic bags
I really hope she took it by mistake
Our hotel has a product provisioning rule
It's a product that the customer has never used
Just put it in the office basket
Can be requested freely
This is actually taking care of the livelihood of employees
After get off work at 6 pm
I'll buy dinner ingredients in the supermarket
I'll prepare dinner when my daughter comes back around 8 pm
This is my daily life
How much money have we saved?
This weekend
My daughter is going to participate in the club training
So I took the opportunity to go with my old classmate Xiaomei
And the younger generation Xiao Ye recounts the old
-Ask them to have a meal-about 27,000 yen
We used to be together very often
But in recent years, we are busy with each other
Only meet a few times a year
Do you still participate in the Mom's Volleyball Team?
Yes, they all become captains
Really?
After all, there are not many experienced team members and they have a high opinion of me
If you join, you will definitely become a regular team member soon
I haven't touched volleyball for more than 20 years
- Just practice a little - Practice
Xiaomei, your school often practices football in our school, right?
Yes, we will go to Xu Primary School
Xiaoye, are you working at Xu Primary School?
It's been the fourth year
Really?
-What grade are you responsible for now? - Grade 6
Graduated this year
That's right
Will you miss them?
Yes, after all, there are many good students in my class
I see
Do you cry when you attend the graduation ceremony?
It's hard to say, maybe I'll shed a few tears
But I have more to consider at the graduation ceremony
for example?
Students take it for granted to be the protagonists of the graduation ceremony
But the class director was also the focus of the day
Just like the bride and father at the wedding
That's right
-So the situation will be a little complicated - What does it mean?
I have to pay attention to which teachers it is
Teach them from first grade to fifth grade
-Why? -Well
We only teach our children for one year
But only the sixth grade teachers showed off
I see
That's different from the bride's father
What you insist on is probably like the last kick of the relay race
I understand it's like only the last stick standing on the podium
Everyone knows that things will turn out like this
But if all the credit is taken away, the scene will become a bit ugly
Makes sense
I was their fourth-grade tutor when I graduated last year
As a result, their class director is that kind of person
They were super rebellious in the fourth grade
I suffered a lot, but he didn't say anything
Just say you're taking care of all the work
- It's clear that everyone is working together - That's right
That's why I have to be cautious and not become a person like him
-Don't rob the protagonist - Yes, so that you won't mess with others
-Thank you so hard - That's it
-Are you still working in a hotel? -right
Speaking of this, I'll tell you
An incredible thing happened when I came home the day before yesterday
What's up?
After get off work
Just ride a bicycle home
Are you okay?
I'm fine
Anyone were injured?
No
Are you okay?
I'm fine
Then I'll leave first, I'm very sorry just now
Takahashi?
that…
Can you please keep the matter secret just now?
good
Then I'll leave first
See you tomorrow
-Are you sure? -Really
-Isn't it very fierce? - It's really unimaginable
He must be able to do it with great strength
How does he look?
He is my senior at work
-Are you colleagues? -Yes, his name is Takahashi
Maybe he used to be a sports person
I don't know this
-Is it a rugby? -If it's a rugby player, it makes sense
-I really want to see what he looks like - Yes, I want to feel his arm strength
I said
Do you think Takahashi is that handsome and macho man?
-Yes - OK
This is Takahashi
Slow down
-Isn't it him? -No, it's him
Are you serious?
It's true, this is the one who lifted me and my bike up
And I haven't finished speaking yet
The next day...is not right
It should be another day later
After all, I was in the same hotel, so I went to thank him
Thank you for saving me the day before yesterday
That's nothing
Keep it confidential, okay?
What?
Please don't say it out
knew
Is something happening?
No, not that
I just think it would be better not to let others know
Don't you want others to know where you are?
Not that true
Did you have an affair?
No
Could it be that you were involved in the crime?
No, you're too far
You made me curious, what was going on?
OK, I'll tell you
But don't say it out
I promise you
that is…
Actually I am...
alien
I mean I'm an alien
So I hope you can keep it confidential
I got it, I won't say it out.
-Wait a minute - Yes?
Did you think I was sick just now?
No
You seem to think I'm talking crazy so you want to interrupt me
There is no such thing
Wait a moment
I'll explain it to you clearly
No
This won't work, I want to explain clearly
Please sit down, please trouble you
That's... the day before yesterday
Didn’t I save you?
Just lifting you and your bike
right
The reason I can do it
It's because I'm an alien
Does what you mean by "alien"?
Not many people will say that excellent athletes are monsters or something?
I know what you said, but that's a metaphor
What I just said
It's not a metaphor, but telling you the facts
-fact? -right
I'm really an alien
That's it
Don't you believe me?
That's it...
That doesn't matter
As long as you don't tell others
That's it
Don't worry, I won't tell anyone
-You will definitely say it - No
You will definitely tell your friends
"I have a colleague who has an abnormal mind"
I won't say it
-Really? -Believe me
But you must think I am a lunatic, right?
-No - There is definitely
-I didn't - Then why did you pause just now?
Please come to the counter
I'll go there right away
I'll leave first
Good morning
I want to confirm the information, please wait
The bill has been settled and the payment procedures have been completed
Please go slowly
-Good morning, do you need to check out? -right
I want to confirm the information, please wait
Come on
Please come here
-What's up? -Sorry, I just want you to see
Sorry, but I still have to go to work
I know, it will be fine soon
You may believe me after you read it
-It's time to start-Okay
No, right?
Too irritating
Very awesome, right?
Slowly, you were
-Do you use your fingers to force it? -right
This kind of thing should not be possible for ordinary people, right?
-Yes-I can do it
It's because I'm an alien
Do you believe me now?
What...what should I say?
You just ask
Obviously you have strange power
But it's a bit ridiculous to treat you as an alien with this point
I understand what you mean
I'll explain
I know I've said it many times but I must keep it confidential
no problem
Then let's start with
I'm from the planet.
At first my parents...
- Please come to the counter - I'll go there right away
Feel sorry
I've been busy with work since then
Not able to finish listening
-What do you think? -What's the meaning?
Do you believe his words?
He's just a madman
Really? Not an alien?
It's the Earthling who has a problem with his head
That's it
But
I thought so at first
But he is really powerful
After all, you saw it with your own eyes
I began to think he was telling the truth
Show me his photos
-He doesn't look strange at all - strange?
He looks too ordinary
Yes, that's the kind of person you can see everywhere
There are about 5,000 people in Japan who look like this
That's right
Can we find time to meet him?
Takahashi?
We want to confirm his abilities first
Yes, if we have the ability to see him with our own eyes, we might believe him
What should I do?
What's wrong?
that is
I've promised him to keep it a secret
You can't ask him to show his abilities so that you can believe him
Yes
Otherwise this would be better
First ask him if he can tell his friends since childhood
If he agrees
You can say that they don't believe you and ask him to show his abilities
In this way, you won't be breaking your promise
Yes
That might work
Of course not
I think so
No
I didn't want you to know at first
But it's all because of that happening
Considering the situation, I can only tell you
But those two people
I was a friend when I was in the middle of the country
And I never tell the secret
You can rest assured of this
But that's all the secrets between friends, right?
I'm just an ordinary uncle and they will definitely tell you
No, they will never say it as long as I speak
Wait a moment
You might have told them already?
No, I didn't say it
-You must have said it - I don't
Then why did you pause suddenly?
Not that
That must be true
You've told your friends
Then they want to see it with their own eyes
But because you promised to keep it confidential
So I'll ask for my consent
I'll prove it to them later
Not that, I didn't tell anyone
-Really? -right
Then why did you come to me to talk about this?
They are my frequent friends
If it were hidden from them, such a shocking thing
I'll feel very stressed
-Really? -right
Keep going like this
We will meet less and less
They are
My only close friend here in my hometown
If I don't meet them anymore
My life only revolves around work and family...
OK, I get it
-Is it really possible? -They are the only ones, right?
May I? thank you very much
Nothing below
Can you really believe them?
Absolutely no problem
Oh well
But relatively speaking, I won't meet them
Or show them abilities, do you understand?
That...can they see it?
-You definitely said that, right? -No
These two are my friends Xiaomei and Xiaoye who have been together since childhood
-Hello -Hello
Please rest assured, they are trustworthy people
I'll never say it
My mouth is very tight
Really no problem, right?
right
first
Can they see that?
Want to do it here?
Is there any problem?
It's okay
Does anyone have ten yuan coins?
Of course there is
Really prepared
It's about to start
That's it
-So awesome-Yes
That's nothing, actually
That, Mr. Takahashi
I heard you are an alien
Is it true?
right
But you look like an ordinary human
Yes, it doesn't look like an alien at all
But my muscle structure is very different
How to say it?
Simply put, compared to humans
My back is round and my chest is slightly lower.
So you have a hunchback?
No, I know hunchback, but that's two different things
Otherwise, you will understand what I mean by touching my back
Touch it
That way you're more understanding
All right
Unruly
I think it's just a hunch
How could humans have such a round back?
No, someone's back is rounder than you
Really?
By the way, what else are there for you to be different from ordinary people?
I'll think about any other things that are easy to understand
My teeth will be sensitive when I eat iced
So you have any perceptual allergies?
No, I know allergies
But it's so different from mine
I have experience, too
-Your teeth will also be sensitive? -Yes
Really?
It seems that we are in the same way
yes
No matter what, you really have different abilities than ordinary people
Yes, I'm really different from others in this regard
Do people on that planet have the same abilities?
After all, I am a child born in Asada
Actually, I don't know much about my planet
But that should be true
So you haven't been to your planet?
No
My father is from that planet
My mother is a Earthling, I am a mixed-race alien
My appearance should be inherited from my mother
Did you get injured when you just put pressure?
No, it'll just be itchy
itch?
-Is it a side effect - Side effect?
My hands itch when I use this ability
Does this happen very often?
It depends on the situation
But something like this is a little bit of a slight itchy
Sorry, if we knew, we wouldn't have asked you to do it
It doesn't matter, that's nothing
If so, can we see other abilities?
-Other abilities? -No?
It's the ability to not have serious side effects
Yes, I want to see it again
May I?
Oh well
Very good
But relatively
You must keep it confidential
No problem, we're very nervous
-Don't forget the agreement - OK
If the world knew about this
I will be surrounded by the media, and it will be very troublesome at that time
That's it
If not handled properly, it will be the same as "ET Alien"
Very likely
I'll be hunted by government agencies
- "ET Alien"? - "ET Alien"?
Don’t you know?
have no idea
That's the blockbuster movie
oh
The story is about an alien being left on Earth
Finally hunted down by government agents
-Oh-I just don't want that to happen
We will keep it confidential
Can you show us your abilities?
I'll go there for a moment
You just chat casually
Chatting nonsense?
I'll go there and listen to what you're talking about
What? Can you hear it?
Probably
Very awesome
- Then start - OK
-Okay - Please trouble you
What should I talk about?
Xiaoye, how about it?
-I? I don't know - I can talk about anything
What about you?
-It's okay to talk about anything--this is it
Talk about something casually
Xiaomei, what do you want to talk about?
Anything you can talk about
We really don't know what to talk about
All is OK, why are you restless like this?
But you know we have nothing to talk about
That's right
-So amazing - Do you believe it now?
-Yes-that's good
He's really amazing
-How are you? -Wait me a moment
Do you have ear pain?
There's a little
But it feels stuffy, like flying
Ear pressure
Yes, but it will be fine soon
Wait, then when you saved me the day before yesterday
Are there any side effects?
I had a fever that night
About 38 degrees
I don't know about this
I'm sorry
It doesn't matter
After all, life is at stake
-You are so nice-yes, so kind
What?
You think too much of me
But it's just a little bit of a fever
Thank you for saving my life
When I was young, I acted impulsively because I was indifferent to the consequences.
I regretted it later
Can you show us other abilities?
Aren't you curious?
I said I acted impulsively
Shouldn't you just ask me what I did?
I slowly began to feel that you were just curious about my abilities
- Not that - We want to hear your story
What did you do?
-You really want to hear it? -think
Really?
When I was in my 20s, I was walking on the road once
Get trouble by a group of gangsters
At that time, there were about five or six of them.
I don't like being treated as a coward and I fight them
Are you dealing with them alone?
right
There's a guy inside that seems to know some boxing
But after all, I have extraordinary abilities
So they were knocked down
It's boring to hear an uncle boast
-But since Takahashi is my savior - I have a fever of 40 degrees
-I have done so many things for us - I have diarrhea
-I had to concentrate on listening - I suffered more than they
That's it
-Please walk slowly -Please walk slowly
I kept my promise and didn't tell his secret...
- Thank you for your hard work -...Interact with him as usual
I really don't know how long he will stay today
yes
But he is not bad either
But he always makes us feel stressed
That should be considered a bad guy, right?
But he has no malice either
I'll start to say something nice to Takahashi a little
Endo, speak with one step
good
What's wrong?
Today I went to clean room 405
-Seeing the TV is missing - TV?
It's Mr. Maruyama's room
What?
Before, he took away the spare parts and towels
But taking the TV is too exaggerating
That's it
What bag did he get today?
-It seems that I can install the TV-Yes
Otherwise, call him and ask him to come here
-Call to Mr. Maruyama? -Yes, use other excuses
We check his car when he distracts...
No, even if he returns to the hotel
It should have left the TV somewhere else
Yes
If he pretends to be innocent, then he will be helpless. After all, we have no evidence.
Yes, after all, we are not
-Seeing him taking it with your own eyes-Yes
Then I have to call the police
The manager probably won't want to pull the police in
That's right
Then I'll leave first
Thanks for your hard work
-Takahashi-Is that?
-Can you please help me? -What's up?
You can use your abilities
Have you found evidence that Mr. Maruyama stole the TV home?
evidence?
for example
You can peek at his room and use the picture in your mind
Have you taken a photo of him stealing the TV?
Can't do it
Can't do it?
-That's considered a superpower-this is
I can only enhance my existing capabilities
Apart from that, I can do nothing
I see
What?
Existing capabilities, right?
Can you know just by the smell of the TV?
There is also the smell of the base here
A little bit of dust mixed
It should be no problem
How about it?
After all, he didn't drag the TV to the ground, so it was quite difficult
But there is still a faint smell
Really?
But it almost disbanded
Do you want to strengthen your sense of smell a little more?
That's OK, but...
Why do you want to look back?
I'm curious about how you look at me now
- Of course, it's a curious expression - that's fine
-Here? -right
Really?
This is a place that the monitor can't capture
(Hushui Hotel)
He passed by here and put the TV on the car
That should be true
So
As long as the smell disappears
It means that Mr. Maruyama parked the car there, which proved that he had stolen it.
How do you prove this?
What's the meaning?
-You can't tell him my abilities - Yes
It's this car
No, right?
His car is still there?
In other words, he is still nearby
Isn't that a TV?
That's right
This is the ironclad evidence
But this is not Mr. Maruyama's car
Whose car is that?
It's Miss Nakamoto's car
What?
That TV is mine
-Really? -I bought it myself
But there is no packaging
Wrapped in a restaurant towel
Sorry, I borrowed a towel
But the TV is mine and it is second-hand, so there is no packaging
That's it
Since that's the case
To be on the safe side, I'd better call the police and ask the police to investigate.
-If that happens, Miss Nakamoto... - Sorry
I stole it
I was impulsive, I'm really sorry
Really, what are you thinking?
Sorry, I'll put it back immediately
Can you please don’t call the police?
-Okay-Thank you
But I have to tell the manager about this
I would be grateful if you don't tell the manager.
-But I won't tell him... -Please please
I'm a single mother
Without this job, I would have a hard time living
I see
Anyway, put the TV back before the manager notices
Thank you very much, I will put it back immediately
It's so bitter, right?
-Thank you -Thank you
Thanks for your hard work
manager
Today, the cleaning staff Ms. Nakamoto stole the TV from the hotel.
What? What's going on?
She said the TV in Room 405 was gone
But after we searched, we found that the TV was in her car
Really?
She admitted it herself, so it's absolutely right
That's it
Where is Miss Nakamoto now?
She went to put the TV back
That's it
-I'll check the situation-Okay
Didn’t you promise she won’t tell the manager?
Of course, this is a crime
So
But you've promised her
It doesn't matter
And she is not a single mother
Really?
yes
I have a social media account tracking her
She's enjoying a single life, you see
(Long-lost trip to Korea)
(Two days and one night trip)
Really
-It's just that kind of thing - but you show her on the spot
It's really like your style
Not all because she lies
Say I am a single mother, obviously not
-It's so insulting - It's really a big deal
Has she been arrested?
No
The manager doesn't want to make a big deal
I didn't call the police, I fired her directly
That's it
She should be thankful for not handing her over to the police
But Mr. Takahashi's performance is really amazing
yes
But because he can't tell his abilities
Later I became the hero of finding the TV
What? Have you taken away the credit?
The manager kept praising me in front of everyone
Is this OK? Are you proud?
There seems to be a little
No, you will mess with others
-So I invited him to have a meal - Then why didn't he come?
He seemed to have side effects in order to find a TV and had rhinitis
Now eating has no taste
So pitiful
Subtitle translation: Wang Guiyi