Chief Editor,
the media are all here.
Hurry up.
Okay.
I know many people think online literature is not up to standard,
and that only classic literature
has profound philosophical thoughts.
But I don't think so.
I think online literature
has always been at the forefront of social emotions.
Sweet stories,
thrilling stories,
and farming stories
The popularity of cultivation novels
matches the complex emotions
of the public.
To provide a better environment for authors,
we've reached an acquisition agreement
with the website of Far and Wide.
You said you'd provide a good environment,
but why are you canceling so many contracts?
I believe authors
sell dreams.
Our publishing house
has always been a dreamland.
I don't want it to become a junkyard.
What's your view on the relationship
between the author,
the work, and the characters?
I believe that the process of an author
creating a work and characters
is a continuous process of peering into their own heart
and expressing themselves.
And the characters in the author's work
always bear the author's imprint
and flow with his blood.
But at the same time,
they are also truly independent individuals.
has its own will
and follows its own fate
towards the end.
This is
the world where the person who writes my fate lives.
Where is that person now?
Can I go back to the previous world?
Hello, Yan Ying.
The rules of this world have been loaded for you.
You now have the basic knowledge and life skills of this world.
This world and the world in the book are parallel universes.
The entrance connecting the two worlds
is the Qixi star chart.
[and brought you to this world.]
[You have only one chance to change your fate.]
[Good luck.]
Where's the Star Token?
I must rewrite my ending.
Yeah.
Cancel all my appointments.
I have more important things to do.
Okay.
Hand over the Star Token,
and I'll spare your life.
This is a society governed by law.
You can't hurt people at will.
Don't play any tricks.
Tell me,
where is the Star Token?
Let me go first.
I don't know what you're talking about.
But if you're going to be like this,
I can't cooperate with you.
One more chance.
Tell me.
Where is the Star Symbol?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Let me go first.
If your stuff is with me,
I can help you look for it.
Wow.
That was really fast.
The bike just passed us.
You, you, you...
Hold it back.
Don't spit on the car.
Where is the Star Symbol?
Have some water.
It'll be easier on the stomach.
I can sit.
I'll go change my clothes first.
No.
He's been dodging the whole time.
In war,
deception is key.
If he hides the Star Mark somewhere else,
and says he doesn't have it,
I can't do anything about it.
What are you doing?
I'm afraid you'll run away.
This is my home.
You think I'll run?
Let's talk.
Wait till I change.
Out.
You're hiding the star talisman
because you're guilty.
I found it.
So,
you're kicking me out.
You're a girl.
Under my command,
who dares treat me as a girl?
Speak.
Where is the Star Symbol?
You won't tell me, right?
I'll say it again.
I don't have it.
I don't believe you.
Have you finished searching?
Yes.
Get out.
Tell me about your background and purpose first.
You don't need to know that.
You just need to tell me
where you hid the Star Symbol.
It seems that
there's no need to continue the negotiation.
You want to go back on your word?
In any form of negotiation,
sincerity is the premise.
If you want me to help you,
you must tell me the truth.
I'm General Yan Ying of Qingyun State.
I came from a book called Galaxy Chronicle.
This is our national treasure,
the Qixi Star Chart.
There used to be a star mark on it.
But after I met you,
it disappears.
So?
It's on you.
Regardless of your origins,
you say
the Star Seal is a mark.
How could it be on me?
I saw it.
When?
When you kissed me.
Who dares to disturb me?
A vacuum robot.