=Those Days=
(Adapted from iceread.com novel
"You Xi" by Qingyang Wanxi)
=Episode 34=
- Slowly.
It's fine. We are here.
Walk slowly.
- Grab hold of that.
- Sure.
That's good enough.
Here you go.
Well,
Minghui's room isn't that great.
Just make do with it.
Is that fine?
Mrs. Xu,
thank you.
You only know
who's the closest to you
when you're in trouble.
Don't say that. We're a family.
Family members don't thank each other.
Come and sit.
Don't act like this.
Sorry.
I didn't protect Mingzhu's house.
It's all right.
Mingzhu told me
you started from scratch.
Perhaps Mingzhu can do the same, right?
It's fine for young people
to go through some obstacles.
Don't overthink.
All right.
Sorry for troubling you.
Not at all.
We are home.
Both of you can stay in this room.
Make do with it.
I heard Mingzhu say
you built this bed yourself.
Don't worry about the materials.
It's free from formaldehyde.
Yes.
Here. This is your room.
Aren't you going to get a bowl?
I've eaten, Dad.
Quick. Try it. I made it myself.
Let me try it.
The noodle looks delicious.
It smells really nice.
Isn't it delicious?
What do you think of the noodles?
It's too salty.
Mrs. Feng,
life is too bland for me.
My life is meaningless
if my noodles aren't salty.
Brat,
you don't study well
yet you have a sharp tongue.
It's salty?
I don't think it's too salty.
No.
I'm used to eating light food.
Go and get Mrs. Feng a bowl of soup.
It's fine.
- Minghui.
- Add some soup.
I took your room.
I'm really sorry.
- It's fine, Mrs. Feng.
- Where will you sleep now?
I am now
a minor influencer.
I can just arrange
a suite in a luxury hotel.
Is that true?
Don't listen to his nonsense. Hotel?
He's a young man.
His bed has been arranged.
Young people can sleep anywhere.
I'm telling you. When he's sleeping,
you can put him at the village entrance
and he can still sleep.
Mom.
Are you fine with sleeping there?
Of course.
If it doesn't work, we'll change it
for him. This is a big house.
He will surely have a place to sleep.
Don't worry.
Don't worry. It's fine.
Thank you.
- It's all right, Mrs. Feng.
- Thank you.
Don't need to thank us.
Here you go.
Is this mine?
I'm impressed.
Mingzhu.
Ms. Shen.
Please take good care of me, Ms. Shen.
I plan to leave this restaurant
to my sister-in-law,
Ms. Feng, to manage it.
Why?
Pregnancy doesn't affect your job
as the boss.
Who was it who said no department wanted
to hire a pregnant lady?
I was wrong.
You are the one hiring now.
Mr. Zhao, please take good care of me
in the future.
Let's take care of each other.
Mingzhu.
How is it over at Mom's?
Everything's prepared. Don't worry.
Ms. Feng,
you'll manage the restaurant
in the future.
I'll help you out.
(Nanxi Hotel
Food and Beverage Department Contract)
I hope you do well.
What's wrong with you?
What's that reaction?
Shouldn't you cry when you're touched?
It's different.
I'm going to the toilet.
That's...
Who is it?
Wait.
Is she all right?
How many times have you been pregnant?
It's my first time.
Why don't you want the child?
I'm not married yet.
Children born to a single mother
can also be registered
to the family household.
Getting registered is easy
but raising a child is difficult.
If you know
it's a problem
that can be solved by a condom,
why must you wait
until an abortion surgery?
It's bad for your body.
It's too late to regret it now.
I want it to be done
on the 14th or 15th.
Is that OK?
You need to do a checkup first.
If everything's fine,
we can schedule the time of operation.
Let me give you a receipt.
Hello.
Let me know
how many people are in front of me
and how long I have to wait.
You are No. 156.
You probably need another two hours.
I'll come over later. Thank you.
Meiqi.
Mr. Guan.
Why are you here?
I came to take a look.
It's time for lunch. Let's eat together.
I'm not eating, Mr. Guan.
I'm not that hungry.
It's bad not to eat during meal hours.
I've told you before.
I used to do renovations.
Rest assured.
Yes.
Thank you so much, Mr. Guan.
But you are renovating
the banquet hall today.
I still have many details
to confirm with you.
Sure. Let's go. Let's go and take a look.
Sure.
Why did you forget the 4D Ultrasound
I arranged for you?
I argued with my husband
and forgot about it.
It has been changed to next week.
Mr. Mao,
I've sent the draft to the group.
Please take a look when you're free.
You're still as busy.
I accepted a job
to promote a baby care product.
I'm doing it until I give birth.
I can earn the baby formula money
before the child turns one.
You must be careful
about premature birth, then.
Dr. Li.
If it wasn't for your
close relationship with Mingzhu,
I would never find a dull guy
to find my attending doctor.
Don't speak nonsense.
We are normal friends.
I was just joking.
I was planning to give birth at the
Maternal and Child Healthcare
because it's close to our house.
To be closer to you,
I transferred to the People's Hospital
and made an appointment
with Dr. Li Jingzhe.
The first day we met,
he was being so sarcastic.
I didn't.
When she came to me,
the first thing she told me
was that middle-aged women
like to gossip.
The gears of fate
started turning at my place.
They are not turning
but vibrating.
Turning is too smooth.
Mingzhu's and my fate
are a little out of control.
No. Mine isn't out of control.
It's quite good.
Hello, Hao.
Jiao scratched Wu's car?
Insurance company doesn't pay
for manmade damages, right?
Sure.
Why is it so serious?
I got it.
Hao,
what do you think?
Wu, I'm really sorry.
Jiao.
Apologize to Mr. Wu.
I'm not apologizing.
Pay him with my red packet money.
- What are you talking about?
- Mr. Wu, I'm sorry.
I'll pay for the repairs.
Hao.
It's a full spray.
That's about 6,000 yuan.
I'll pay it.
You'll pay?
I'll pay.
All right.
Hao. Zhixia.
Educate your child
before society educates her.
No. He...
It's all right.
Coming. Sorry.
You're late.
Pull up your shirt.
Higher.
I can see the gestational sac.
My grandson might be asleep.
I can't hear anything.
Did he kick you today?
Not today.
He kicked me furiously two days ago.
When I was pregnant with Jianqi,
his arms
would come out from here
and his leg would come out from here.
Then,
I'd comfort him and put him back.
I can see the gestational sac.
There's a chocolate cyst here.
If you get an abortion,
pregnancy will be difficult
in the future.
I suggest you think it through.
Hello, Mingzhu.
Hello, Meiqi.
Where are you?
Why haven't you come home?
I'll go home soon.
Don't wait for me.
Do you think I have a lot of money?
Do you think I have too few troubles?
Tell me. Are you wrong?
No.
Don't be angry.
You are still pregnant.
This is not Jiao's fault.
She saw me argue with Wu.
You argued with Wu?
Are you saying
that she's avenging you?
Jiao, all right.
It's fine.
Don't cry.
- You must feel aggrieved.
- Sorry.
Jiao is the most righteous person.
Our Jiao is a heroine.
What?
Jiao, it's like this.
Well,
I know you are avenging Dad.
However, you need
to choose the right way.
You can choose a free method
that doesn't spend my money.
You...
You could trip him
so he would fall flat on his face.
Then, quickly bow and say,
"Sorry, Mr. Wu.
I didn't do it on purpose."
That's free. Isn't it great?
You can educate her like this.
How should I do it then?
Keeping quiet while feeling aggrieved
and be at a loss?
Well done.
Mom.
Wu bullied Dad
because Dad didn't get promoted.
I'm the only one
who can force him to be the manager.
You shouldn't say that.
It's because you are not the manager.
What's wrong with you?
Are you pregnant?
With whom?
Well,
after I resigned, I went to Shanghai.
I met a lawyer, Simon.
His surname is Yao.
He once pursued me.
So...
Does he know about this?
He doesn't.
Call him and tell him now.
I don't want to marry him.
You don't want to marry him?
Why are you
so irresponsible with yourself?
What do you plan to do now?
My original plan
was to get an abortion on the 14th.
After that, I'll rest for two weeks.
The restaurant's renovation
will be done during this period.
Removing formaldehyde,
moving furniture, and fire safety.
I can use the time
without any interruption.
It's easy to say.
I'll be busy with the opening.
I have no time to take care of you.
I don't need anyone.
I just need to lie down.
When Madam Yue and Madam Yu
deliver nutritious soup for you and Mom,
I'll just have some.
Consider that as
a nutritious confinement period.
You planned it well.
However, plans change.
Doctor said I have a chocolate cyst.
If I get an abortion,
it'll be difficult for me
to get pregnant again.
So,
after thinking about it,
I think this baby is here to save me.
You want to give birth to the child?
I don't know.
What should I do, Mingzhu?
You're asking me now?
It's your child. Make your own decision.
Why did you stop Bichen
when she wanted to get an abortion?
Was it because her husband
was your younger brother?
Because Yuan Bichen
was about to marry Xu Zhidong back then.
Is an abortion not recommended
when one has a chocolate cyst?
Yes. During pregnancy,
Estrogen and
progesterone levels will rise.
The cyst might
decrease in size or vanish completely.
Menopause, too, is actually
a way for the ovaries
to rest and recover.
What's wrong?
There's trouble again.
Go back and rest.
I'm not tired.
I went to ask Dr. Li today.
Why did you look for him?
This is my problem.
It's none of your business.
I am the mother.
I have a right to give birth.
Yes.
Every woman has a right to give birth
but not every woman is suitable
to become a mother.
Your biological mother
gave you away.
Does she deserve to become a mother?
Why didn't you scold her, but got closer
to their family instead?
Everyone,
take a break and get a drink outside.
- Sure.
- All right.
Feng Meiqi.
Did pregnancy make you
lose your conscience?
When they rushed to the hospital
to pay your mom's bills
when she was in the ICU,
why didn't you say
she didn't deserve to become a mother?
Now that you got pregnant accidentally
and couldn't make a decision,
you hope for everyone
to stand on your side.
Do you think this is a drama?
Meiqi, give birth to him.
We'll raise him for you.
What?
Are you attacking all of us
because we don't act
according to your script?
Do we owe you anything?
Look in the mirror.
How old are you now?
You don't want me
to give birth after all.
No wonder
you hesitated so long back then.
If my parents hadn't promised
to give you the house and money,
you'd probably not give birth, right?
Where's the house? Where's the money?
I'm not talking to you anymore.
Your child, your decision.
My child, my decision.
Drinking soup isn't enough
You need to eat the meat.
Leave me alone.
The nutrition is in the meat.
The baby needs protein.
All of you are ready to become mothers,
but I'm not prepared at all.
I wasn't prepared for my dad's death.
I wasn't prepared
for my brother's death.
I was also not prepared
for Mom's stroke.
Our family had to
carry so much debt for no reason.
I suddenly have a younger brother
for no reason.
In the end, I even got pregnant.
Why do things end up like this?
But I'm not prepared for anything?
Doesn't eating meat
mean you are making preparations?
What should I do?
Think about it carefully.
If you're getting an abortion,
I'll go with you.
If you want to give birth,
we'll raise the child together.
We've really owed your family so much.
Sorry.
Sorry, Mingzhu.
But you're not escaping.
♪Lost in the heart of the city♪
♪Love is the shore I hold my faith in♪
Have you thought it through?
♪Keep your eyes ahead
and don't doubt yourself♪
♪Don't glorify pain
or cling to the past♪
I want the child.
♪Turn embarrassment to gorgeous♪
What about the restaurant?
I calculated it.
Our pregnancies are half a year apart.
When you give birth, I'll work.
When I give birth,
you'll work.
Who'll take care of your child
after you give birth?
I'll take care of the child myself.
Eat the meat.
(A harmonious family brings prosperity)
(Rights Holder: Hu Gang, Ni Xiao)
Look.
Our names are together.
Joint first.
As long as the score is the same.
Whether it's first or last,
we are still joint together.
Hu Gang.
Let me ask you.
Do you really not have anything to say
about me buying Mingzhu's house?
What's wrong with her house?
Well,
there'll be traces of Feng Meiqi.
I can't see any traces.
I'm a materialist.
Do you really not see it?
Are you sure?
I remember I bought you
a pair of red shoes.
You've never worn it before.
If you have time,
you should go and take a look
at our original workshop.
I'm not going.
I've never been there for many years.
That place must be so dirty
and messy.
Why should I go?
It's exactly
because it's messy and dirty
that you need to tidy it up.
Remember.
We achieved what we have
by taking one step at a time.
That is our blessed land.
Meiqi.
I have a few photos of Jianmei Workshop.
Where did you put them?
It's inside my room's drawer.
All right.
I want to look at them.
- Slowly.
- You too.
When do you plan to tell Mom?
Feng Meiqi!
Tell me.
Who does the child belong to?
Simon Yao.
My former classmate.
What's that name?
What does he do?
A lawyer.
Fine. A lawyer.
Go and
call this lawyer here.
I want to talk to him.
It won't happen.
He's in Shanghai.
Even if he's on the moon,
you must call him back
and marry you!
We aren't close.
I don't have his contact.
Feng Meiqi,
who are you?
You slept with him
when you weren't close to him
and got pregnant with his child?
You're still talking as if you're right?
I'm telling you.
You can't keep this child!
A family like ours...
What's wrong with a family like ours?
Stop talking about this family!
Our family is rare in Nanzhou
and unparalleled in the Ancient City!
What are you talking about?
What nonsense is this?
Didn't we acquire
Nanxi Hotel?
We will rise again!
Mom,
we didn't acquire Nanxi Hotel.
It's just
the food and beverage department.
It's even the money we obtained
from selling the house.
Sowe must get rid of this trouble.
How is this a trouble?
It's a life!
Whatever I do
is wrong.
Listen, Mom! I'll give birth to this child!
I dare you to speak again!
And I will speak again!
I'll give birth
and take care of this child on my own.
No one has the right to stop me
even if you are my mom.
Mom,
you are going to become a grandmother.
Aren't you happy?
Feng...
Enough, Mom.
You know
Meiqi's temper.
Go to Shanghai
and find the lawyer.
He must take responsibility.
Meiqi
cannot suffer a loss in silence
for no reason.
I'm busy with the opening
and have had no time recently.
I'll find my younger brother, Minghui,
and ask him to go to Shanghai.
Yes. That's right.
- Minghui!
- Minghui, come upstairs!
What is it, Mingzhu?
I'll ask him to go instead. Calm down.
What's wrong?
Go to Shanghai and find someone for me.
Who?
A lawyer called Yao.
He works at a firm in Jing'an.
I'll send you the address later.
Sure.
Minghui,
I beg you.
You must go to Shanghai,
find the lawyer called Yao,
and bring him back.
He must take responsibility for Meiqi.
Meiqi is pregnant with his child.
I'll go immediately.
Let me pack up
and I'll depart tomorrow morning.
Sure.
- Thank you, Minghui.
- Don't worry, Mrs. Feng.
Thank you, Minghui.
It's all right.
Let me bring you to rest.
Why would
Mingzhu suddenly become pregnant?
Right. I wonder.
She said she wasn't close to him.
Mingzhu.
Will Minghui really go to Shanghai?
No. He didn't ask for money from me.
All right.
Hello, Minghui.
Mingzhu,
send me Yao's details.
Are you really going to Shanghai?
(Nanzhou Station)
Yes. I'm at the High Speed Rail station.
Let me talk to him.
Minghui, listen to me.
Don't go. You won't find him
even if you go there.
Come back immediately.
Go home.
Mingzhu,
I was joking.
I only came to the station
to take a picture.
Don't you know
how smart your mother-in-law is?
We must complete the whole act.
You are right. Come back
as soon as you are done taking pictures.
Stay safe.
Got it.
I'm hanging up.
Take pictures of what?
He is worried
that your mom might not believe him
so he went to take pictures
at the railway station.
What do you think?
Is my younger brother smart?
All right.
He only studied for five years
in high school.
Yes.
You are an ace student
and you are smart.
Let me ask you.
Do you want to inform
the lawyer called Yao?
No.
I don't want
to guilt-trip him with a child.
It's not guilt-tripping.
Both of you did it willingly
and he didn't use any contraceptives.
You can get
half of the child support fee.
Doctor.
Do many people ask
whether it's a boy or a girl?
We won't tell no matter what.
Try to turn to the side
and let me take a good look.
What's wrong?
Is something wrong?
There's a small problem.
Is your husband here?
Yes. He's outside.
Can you ask him to come inside?
His name is Zhang Hao.
Zhang Hao.
Yes.
Thank you.
What's wrong?
There's an extra finger
on the child's left hand.
It's fine.
There's no need to worry.
It's a small issue.
When the baby is three months old,
you can remove it with surgery.
Is it dangerous?
It's not dangerous. Don't worry.
Just a small issue.
It's fine.
However, I suggest you
find your attending doctor
to take another look.
It's all right.
Let's try this.
Chef Liu,
thank you.
We'll have a chat about this.
Why don't you go back
and wait for our updates?
Sure.
Thank you.
All right. Call me anytime.
Sure.
It's so sickening.
- When I first took that bite.
- Me too.
Mingzhu,
your family runs a restaurant.
I'm sure you know
how important a good chef is.
Of course.
Our problem now is
we can't afford
to pay good chefs
and the chefs we can afford to pay
aren't good.
It's a never-ending cycle.
Finding a good chef
is just like finding a good boyfriend.
They are difficult.
It's all right. Let's be patient.
I'm sure we can find the right one.
I hope so.
God bless us.
A good chef who is affordable,
please appear soon.
Come here, Zhu.
Come.
It's not bad.
- What do you think?
- It's luxurious.
Yes, it is.
Zhilu.
Mr. Xu.
Slowly.
I renovated this place with Meiqi.
We wanted to give our guests
a good experience.
Not bad.
All right.
If you like this place so much,
why don't you book two tables?
When you open,
I'll support you
by reserving two tables.
If you support us
and we still make you spend money,
we are really bad at business.
Exactly. I'm just joking.
How can I support you
without spending money?
It's free.
Drinks are on us as well.
Sure. Anything you say.
Are both of you
looking for a chef now?
Zhu, come here.
This is the chef I'm introducing you to.
Chef,
where did you cook before this?
He was the sous chef
at Jinling Restaurant.
Jinling Restaurant?
He's amazing.
Chef Zhu.
If you are
Jinling Restaurant's sous chef,
I'm sure you are incredibly skilled.
Naturally, you can also handle
big and small banquets.
However, I'll be honest with you.
We just took over this place.
We need to spend money on everything.
Our budget...
Zhilu,
no matter what,
you are also the boss of a restaurant.
No one talks about pay immediately.
The procedure of hiring a chef
is to first try his cooking
before discussing his pay.
Am I right, Zhu?
Yes.
Why don't you try my cooking first?
The rest can wait until later.
That works.
Hurry, try them.
Bosses.
Try this.
Chef Zhu, you cook really well.
Amazing.
Right?
What do you think?
It's really delicious.
Great. You're amazing.
Chef Zhu, sit down.
All right.
We are very satisfied
with the dishes you make.
I wonder
what is
your expected pay.
Zhilu,
don't trouble him.
Just tell him
how much you can pay him a month.
It's better
to let us know your expected pay.
Me?
Sure.
Can we do
8,000 yuan a month?
8,000 yuan?
8,000 yuan? Are you joking?
No.
But can we skip
the probation period?
Sure. No problem.
It's decided, then.
Then...
Wait.
See? You're thinking nonsense again.
Chef Zhu
is loyal.
I saved him before.
Now, it's time for him to pay me back.
All right. It's decided, then.
Dacheng is right.
He is my savior.
It's what I'm supposed to do.
Both of you are hiring a chef
and Chef Zhu
is making money with his skills.
It's just that simple.
Meiqi, am I right?
Thank you, Mr. Xu.
I'll bring Chef Zhu
to sign the contract.
Go on.
This way, Mr. Zhu.
Both of you,
please take good care of me.
8,000 yuan?
Don't overthink.
The renovation is nice.
Did you design it yourself
or did you hire someone to do it?
We designed everything.
How interesting.
It's really interesting
to hang bedsheets on the ceiling.
We don't have money.
Mom.
What are you doing?
What am I doing? What kind of trouble
are you causing again?
No. This is serious.
Is Madam He here?
How rude of you.
Ms. He.
Is Ms. He home?
Are you looking for her? Why?
Why am I looking for her?
I'm trying to avoid her.
Wait.
What are you doing?
You look like you're in a rush.
Don't worry.
Don't cause trouble!
Why are you here?
Shouldn't you be in Shanghai?
Ms. He,
hear me out.
What is it?
Something so serious happened to Meiqi.
Ask your conscience.
Do you think it's too much
for me to make such a request
as her mom?
Great.
All of you worked together
and lied to me.
You won't go, right?
Fine. I'll go there on my own.
Move.
Ms. He.
There are so many people in Shanghai.
We have no details.
How are we supposed to find him?
We have enough troubling matters at home.
If something happens to you,
what should we do?
This is none of your business.
Ms. He,
how are you going to Shanghai alone?
This isn't as simple as you think.
Listen to me.
We shouldn't go
so it also makes my life easier
when I deal with them.
Don't trouble everyone.
Fine.
I don't need to go to Shanghai,
but you need to go to
another place with me.
It's in Nanzhou.
It's in Nanzhou?
Sure. I can go anywhere in Nanzhou.
(We achieved what we have)
(by taking one step at a time.)
(That is our blessed land.)
Hold it.
Hold it for me.
Be careful, Ms. He.
Come here.
This table.
We used to eat here.
Back then, we didn't have much money
and we ate simple food,
but everything tasted delicious.
Ms. He,
you had a difficult life back then.
Perhaps one day,
the Shen's restaurant will be
as good as Lijun Hotel's.
That depends on how good you are.
This is our first machine.
We used it
to make our first pot of gold.
This is our second machine.
The third, the fourth, the fifth...
(Natural Mulberry Silk)
Minghui, come here.
Help me remove the tarp.
Come. Take them down.
These are...
Open it.
What is this, Ms. He?
What is this?
Is this worth anything?
Money.
This is all money.
(For Lihua)
(Lihua.)
(Many things have happened)
(to the company.)
(I don't know whether it's good or bad.)
(So, I made some preparations.)
(It might help you in the future.)
(However, I hope you don't need it.)
(Xiaoqi is)
(one of my life's biggest mistakes.)
(Until today,
I still can't make up for it.)
(I can only
leave these materials to you.)
(I hope you and Meiqi)
(can live a good life in the future.)
(I've let this family,)
(you, and the children down.)
(There are
too many unexpected things in life.)
(You must take good care of yourself)
(and Meiqi.)
I'm going to Shanghai.
I want to meet Yao, the lawyer.
Take me to Shanghai.
♪The world is noisy♪
♪Turning around,
it's already a distant view♪
♪Once I didn’t know what to do♪
♪What to hold quietly♪
♪Like a silent care♪
♪Seasons pass by♪
♪Time ticks away♪
♪Seems like I understand a little♪
♪And also let go of some things♪
♪All the bittersweet flavors
are the essence of youth♪
♪A long letter is written down♪
♪Gently spreading love♪
♪To all the forks in fate♪
♪Loving all the moments
that deserve to be loved♪