Your Majesty.
General Huaihua Tianbuwei.
Embezzling military funds and colluding with outsiders.
Treason. Execution by beheading.
I've been wronged!
I must survive.
I must live on.
Madam, I'd like to pay. Five coins. All right, here you go.
Thank you for your business.
All right.
Child, you must be hungry.
Come, sit down and have something to eat.
Ma'am, please let me stay.
Child, get up.
Quickly now. Listen to me and get up.
Don't you have parents, sister?
My mother said my father was killed by bandits.
Ma'am, please let me stay.
I can do any kind of work.
I can cook and do laundry.
I learn quickly and eat very little.
Mom, please let her stay.
I want someone to keep me company while working.
Alright, child. Fine, she can stay.
Then it's settled.
Mom.
Get up.
Jinjin, hurry up. It's almost done.
Okay.
Tian Jinjin, Tian Jinjin.
Yun'er, you little brat.
So disrespectful, calling your sister by her name.
You're only a few months older. Stop acting so mature.
You're just in time.
Take these two dishes to the customers at table 3.
The customers at tables 3 and 4 are difficult.
They're about to fight over a dish.
I'll go check.
Go quickly.
Boss, let me go instead.
No need. You keep working.
Alright.
Everything should follow the principle of first come, first served.
We ordered this dish first.
As if we came here later.
We arrived almost at the same time.
We're regular customers here.
As if others aren't.
Please don't be angry, gentlemen. Anger is bad for your health.
This is our waiter's fault.
He didn't explain clearly. The dishes weren't served incorrectly.
I've brought your dishes.
One serving for each table.
These two dishes are compliments from our humble establishment.
For my sake,
please return to your seats
and enjoy your meal happily, alright?
Since Miss Jinjin has spoken,
Fine, I'll give you face.
Come, let's drink.
Innkeeper Tian, I'm doing this for your sake.
Thank you, Master Du.
Come, let's drink.
You really do have a silver tongue.
This is our new dessert. Please try it.
Jinjin, are you alright?
Don't worry, Mother. It was a piece of cake.
That's good, that's good.
Young Master.
What are you doing here?
My father sent you again, didn't he?
Master Fu only has your best interests at heart.
Investigating the unjust case from 10 years ago
is my duty.
You were demoted for refusing that marriage.
Now you plan to investigate behind the court's back.
They won't let this go.
So what? I've never feared death.
Don't misunderstand your father.
General Tian, as your father's subordinate, knows best.
The blank appointment letter you took
was intentionally left for you by your father.
I understand.
Young Master, this is a secret letter from Prince Ning.
To help you proceed with your plans.
Hya!
Where to?
Master Fu specifically instructed
that I accompany you.
Hya!
Sister, you're thinking about them again.
Yes, it's been 10 years.
Sister, don't be sad.
You still have me.
Whatever decision you make,
I'll be by your side.
Innkeeper, it's about time.
Okay.
Yun'er, go home and get some rest.
Liu Zi.
Don't think I don't know what you're up to.
You're going to sneak into the magistrate's office tonight
to investigate my sister's father's wrongful case.
Take good care of my sister.
If anything happens to her,
I won't let you off.
Mind your own business.
You.
We've been tricked! Let's go!
Guards!
Young Master, there's something wrong with the smoke.