It's a trap! Run!
Guards!
Young master, there's something wrong with the smoke.
Go quickly!
Fu Dong!
Go back!
Murderer!
You're the one who killed the magistrate.
Tell me, why did you frame me?
I didn't. You still deny it?
You were hiding in the inner chamber when the magistrate died.
If not a murderer, then a thief.
Tell me, what did you steal?
Let go of that girl!
You're choking my Jinjin to death.
What else is there to explain?
Why are you everywhere?
How could you repay kindness with enmity?
How do I know if you're working together?
Right, we are working together.
She's the tenant and I'm the landlord.
Together. Why do you talk so much?
Xiaoliuzi.
Take this food to feed the dogs.
Move.
Move quickly.
Talk now.
Where is my young master?
Don't be rash. Wait.
Or I'll kill her.
No, don't do anything rash.
Manager Tian.
Let that girl go.
Take me instead.
Yun'er.
Sister.
You.
What are you doing, Fudong?
Leave me alone. Do what you want.
I bet she wouldn't dare kill anyone. Shut up.
Let go of my young master.
You're running a criminal establishment here.
Kidnapping my young master and attempting murder.
What evidence do you have?
Were you two just on a sightseeing trip to the magistrate's house yesterday?
We're in the same boat.
If we make this public,
we'll all go down together. At least we won't be lonely in the afterlife.
How does that sound?
That's a bit extreme.
Young Master! Yun'er!
Are you alright? Are you hurt?
Sister, I'm fine.
Get out of here. You're repaying kindness with enmity.
People with mental problems
aren't welcome here.
She saved me.
Thank you, Manager Tian. I don't deserve it.
Just don't cause any trouble.
Small business like ours can't afford life-threatening situations.
Let's go.
Sis, what happened to your neck? Does it hurt?
It's nothing. Just had bad luck today. Got choked by a little brat.
Yun'er, let's go.
The show is about to begin.
The official seal
isn't with me.
Not with you?
Without the appointment letter,
how can you take office, young master?
We'll see about that.
An official who lost his seal, a soldier who forgot his sword,
might as well go home and take care of children.
Insulting an imperial official is a punishable offense.
A ninth-rank official wants to punish me?
I'm so scared.
Sis, I'm so cold.
Yun'er, I have a piece of waste paper here.
Why don't we use it to make a fire and warm ourselves?
Good.
Burning important imperial documents is punishable by imprisonment.
Is that so? But I've never been to school
and can't read.
After we burn it, you can go report us.
Negotiate.
Manager Tian.
We can talk about this.
You can name your conditions.
We can agree to anything.
I want you to tell me what information you've found.
These days even scumbags look this handsome.
This girl looks quite pleasing to the eye,
but she's so shallow.
Do you have a thick skin?
Information exchange. How about it?
Information exchange.
If I didn't find you attractive, I would...
Let me take office first, then we'll talk.
Fu Dong.
Mr. Liu is busy with official duties.
Please wait a little longer.
Young master.
Calm down.
Brother, they're from the capital after all.
It's not nice to keep them waiting like this.
Is rice from the capital somehow better?
Let them wait. It won't hurt them.
Right, let them wait.
My name is Fu Mingyang.
I was a fifth-rank cavalry general at the border.
Listen to him brag. A cavalry general?
How could someone like that end up in a place like this?
Listen to what he has to say.
I've been temporarily assigned to this post station
to evaluate the connection between post stations and the capital
and find ways to improve mail delivery speed.
What does he mean?
He's been demoted.
Demoted! He's been demoted!
It's not a demotion.
Don't you understand it's a temporary reassignment?
I get it.
Official Liu asked you to temporarily take over the postal guard position.
Let's go. I'll show you around to familiarize yourself with the place.
Move along, everyone!
This way.
Follow me.
Those two rooms we just passed - one is for storing provisions
and the other is for archives.
This room is for storing weapons.
Can you open it? I'd like to take a look.
I can't open this.
Official Liu keeps the key.
Oh, by the way,
there are three horses in the back yard. They're Official Liu's mounts.
Don't feed them or touch them.
They're extremely valuable.
Come, let me show you around.
Mealtime! Mealtime!
Hurry!
Dinner's ready, young master. Hurry up!
Here you go.
This is your new one.
The new one.
Let's eat.
Come on, eat up.
Have a drink. Come on.
Come on.
Hurry up.
Come again next time. Sure!
Thank you, madam. I'm leaving.
Innkeeper, Officer Du.
Officer Du, Innkeeper Tian. Please sit.
Do you know that these days, at 9-11 pm,
there are carriages transporting government silver
passing through the small woods behind the mountain?
Where do you think the government is taking all this silver?
Mr. Tian, do you know why the Chinese character for 'official' has two 'mouths'?
Why are they connected?
It means you need to learn to keep your mouth shut.
Misfortune comes from the mouth.
Come, Mr. Tian, have a drink.
I understand. Please enjoy yourself.
Sir Fu.
Our post station only has shared sleeping quarters.
I'm afraid you two will have to make do with this corner.
The two of us?
Is that appropriate? Yes, it is.
Young master, can you bear this?
I can't. What about you?
I can't bear it either.
Let's talk to them.
Go easy this time.
What are you doing?
Take it easy.
Tell us.
I don't know anything.
Station Master Liu ordered me to do this.
What did Station Master Liu order?
He didn't say much.
Just that you two
should sleep in the beds used by the previous station guards.
The previous station guards, right.
Where did they go?
In mourning for their parents.
Really?
Yes, really.
You two take a rest first.
I have something to do. I'll go first.
Mourning leave.
Sis, look what I brought you.
This is the newest fragrance pouch.
I chose calming incense for you.
It guarantees no more nightmares at night.
Where did it go again?
Come drink. Cheers!
Tonight we're not leaving until we're drunk.
Come, eat. Help yourself to some food.
So annoying.
What a mess.
Fu Dong.
Sleep a bit longer. I'll stand for a while.
I'm not tired, young master. You sleep.
Fu Dong, come here.