Miss Shen.
Where's Zhao Wudi?
He was reading the materials here before.
I got back after buying the coffee...
Miss Shen, here you are.
What's with the hotel?
I don't know.
This is the information copied from
the Han family.
Wudi said Han was merely a pawn.
He plans to find out who's behind this.
(Rainbow Hotel)
(You came quite fast.)
Who are you?
(Rainbow Hotel)
(is the clue I left for you.)
(Cang Ming.)
(Mr. Han is a brainless idiot,)
(but he's finally done something nice.)
(He found out your true identity.)
I've got here.
Why are you still hiding?
Such a trap isn't fun.
(No, no.)
(Next is the fun part.)
(A squad was sent to execute the task,)
(but only you came back alive.)
(How do you feel about this?)
What has this got to do
with you?
(Shen Xingchen is a tough guy.)
(He'd rather die than come clean.)
(You're the only person he met
before he died.)
(So, Wushuang must be in your hands.)
(Give me Wushuang)
(and I'll let you die with a full body.)
Indeed, you're doing this for Wushuang.
Let's talk face to face then.
=My Name Is Zhao Wudi=
=Episode 15=
Hello.
Okay, I got it.
I'll be there now.
Ma Ling.
Miss Shen, what's the matter?
My uncle asked me to go meet him,
saying Xingyu Optoelectronics has got
serious financial problems.
No kidding.
The financial situation
is always kept in order.
Nothing can be wrong.
Besides,
even if it has any problems,
it has nothing to do with the Group.
I assume it can't be that simple.
Did you reach Zhao Wudi?
No, he isn't answering his phone.
Never mind. I'll go there now.
Ali, why are you here?
(The smoke is deadly poisonous.)
(The poison will take effect
in one minute.)
(There are two antidotes on the table.)
(One is real and the other is fake.)
(You'll identify them yourselves.)
Pick one. I don't wanna die.
You can eat it if you wanna die.
But I'll die if I don't eat it.
Then I'll die with you.
(Good.)
(How did you recognize it?)
The two pills smell the same.
So, the smoke isn't poisonous.
The pills are poisonous.
If you're in on this scheme against me,
that'll be too boring.
You've known it.
It looks like you didn't touch the pills.
But your hand does smell of them.
So, the pills were placed there by you.
I was acting cooperatively just now.
I knew you wouldn't buy that.
Don't play this kind of trick again.
It's a waste of time.
Is it?
I think it's fun.
If your beautiful hand
gets some corrosive poison on it,
my face will be ruined.
How can I bear to ruin
this pretty face?
What do you know
about Dragon Slaying Action?
Never heard of it.
I only know
Trapping Dragon Action.
I can leave anytime if I want to.
These tricks can't keep me.
Zhao Wudi,
you should know trapping you
isn't our goal.
More importantly,
it's a distraction.
Your target is Xingyu Optoelectronics?
We're not that petty.
We're gonna take down the Shen Group.
Nothing's wrong with the finance
of Xingyu Optoelectronics.
Even if there is,
you don't have to worry about it.
No problem with the financial situation
doesn't mean no other problems.
Anyway, Xingyu Optoelectronics
was a part of the Shen Group.
They're somewhat related.
My brother got Xingyu Optoelectronics
at the cost of giving up
the right of inheritance.
It has nothing to do with the Shen family.
The ties of blood can't be cut off.
We merely want to help you.
When you forced my brother to leave,
you showed no regard
for the ties of blood at all.
That's a family affair.
You'd rather
accept an outsider's investment
than the purchase of your family.
Then it won't be a family affair.
Let's do it business-wise.
You want the shares? Sure,
but no intervening in the management.
I just hope you can come back.
I've underestimated your goal.
Turns out you're not coming for the shares.
Instead,
you want to get the company for nothing.
You...
Our family has spent
so many resources on you.
How can you not have a heart at all?
I'll call you uncle for the last time.
I hope you can understand
it's that the family
is in my brother's debt.
My brother and I
owe the Shen family nothing.
You...
Stop it.
Brother, you're old.
It's time for you to rest.
Hello.
(Uncle Shen died of a heart attack.)
You woke up so quickly.
Cang Ming of Black Bat indeed.
Turns out you're Mr. Hu.
The plan has worked.
It's time to meet you then.
What on earth are you up to?
The former chairman was old
and disobedient.
So, I sent him to hell.
The current chairman, Shen Zhongtian,
is my man.
How scheming of you!
You've got such a submissive pawn.
Yeah, that's right.
I like playing chess.
You're a good pawn too.
But there's another good show to come.
♪You are God's fallen angel♪
♪You fell from grace for saving me♪
♪This story has no script,
love is hidden between the lines♪
♪Get going and you won't be lost again♪
♪You are the devil's beloved angel♪
♪Lucifer would give up his kingdom for you♪
♪This story has no script,
the audience is still captivated♪
♪Get going and you won't be lost again♪
♪You gave me the courage
to love fearlessly♪
♪Are you my cure?
I can't control my thoughts♪
♪Angel, you make me hesitant
to match my lyrics to the rhythm♪
♪I hope you will find
this acrostic poem interesting♪
♪I will walk with you from dusk to dawn♪
♪Hand in hand,
until our hair turns from black to white♪
♪We will keep studying our future♪
♪We will base it on all your tenderness♪
♪Maybe we have different personalities♪
♪Maybe we have different experiences♪
♪Maybe these might not even be problems♪
♪Loving you is an open secret♪
♪I don't know, I can't figure it out♪
♪You are like a router,
catching all my signals♪
♪Behind your mysteriousness
is a terrifying smile♪
♪This is my fault for myself
landing in hot water♪