You're so rough.
- Liu.
- Miss Shen.
There's an intrusion.
Come with me, now.
Run, run.
Oh, no.
This way, this way.
Get back in, get back in.
Miss Shen,
there might not be a way out later.
I'll stop them outside.
Ling, protect Miss Shen.
- Don't come out.
- Okay.
Don't open the door.
=My Name Is Zhao Wudi=
=Episode 17=
It's me.
- Wudi.
- Turn on the lights.
Are you okay?
I'm really confused.
I finally got away.
I didn't get hit by the bad guys
but I got hit by my own wife.
I thought it was that bunch of people.
Sit over there.
Here, sit.
Wudi, where is my brother?
He is outside.
Let me see.
Does it hurt?
Honey, you hit me too hard.
You have to take good care of me tonight.
You're covering the wrong eye.
It's this side.
I can't believe the pain transfers.
Do you know how worried I was
when you didn't come back?
Are you worried about me or the company?
You, of course.
I'm sorry, Xingyu.
This is the first night
I wasn't by your side.
I made you worry.
Through this incident, I am certain
that Uncle Zhongtian
and those who captured me
are accomplices.
They lured me away
to deal with the Shen Group
and you.
I guessed it.
There must be a reason
for Uncle Shen's death.
Although Uncle Shen kept targeting you,
he never wanted to listen to them.
That's why they removed him
and put Uncle Zhongtian there.
You need to be careful from now on.
With you by my side,
I'm not worried at all.
Wudi,
I managed to hold on until you came back.
I thought I was a goner.
Did you know
that I just fought off
eight of them alone?
Miss Shen, I...
I didn't interrupt you two, did I?
Ma Liu, you did very well tonight.
I'll reward you
with a six-month salary bonus.
That's too kind.
Hurry up and thank Miss Shen.
Thank you, Miss Shen.
How many times have I mentioned
that my goal is Wushuang?
It's Wushuang.
But why did you attack Zhao Wudi?
It's troublesome with Zhao Wudi around.
Then, you have to find a way
to get around it.
Who do you take me for?
Another fool
like Mr. Han and Mr. Hu?
You will outsmart him.
Okay, I understand.
Any progress on that matter
I asked you to investigate?
This is the person in charge
of the R&D team.
The chief scientist, Dr. Zhou.
Let's invite Dr. Zhou
for a cup of coffee.
Okay.
Dr. Zhou, please calm down.
Subordinates don't know any better.
Mr. Shen, this is kidnapping.
You are the chief scientist
of Xingyu Optoelectronics.
You must know
that I value talented researchers
like you.
I invited you here today
to give you a chance
to realize a grand ambition.
Thank you for the offer, Mr. Shen.
I don't have such a big ambition.
Don't refuse me so quickly.
As long as you agree to my conditions,
you will become the chief scientist
of the Shen Group.
You have the company's word
that all decisions are yours to make.
No one can interfere with what you do.
Most importantly,
I can offer you
an annual research grant of 500 million.
500 million?
It's really simple.
Shen Xingyu
has a very important
new energy research project in her hands.
Codename Wushuang.
Wushuang?
I shall be honest.
Wushuang is very advanced
and its theory is well-developed.
However, its safety and stability
cannot be guaranteed.
Further research is needed
before it can proceed
to large-scale mass production
and practical application.
I love challenges.
Dr. Zhou, I believe
you and I are the same.
We have a great ambition
to change the world.
Knowledge changes fate.
I know you love coffee.
I brewed this cup of coffee myself.
Try it.
Please have a seat.
Didn't you always wanna know
what Wushuang is?
Wushuang is a new energy technology
10 years ahead of its time
that my parents developed.
Once introduced,
it will transform the existing
new energy landscape.
It can even change the fate of mankind.
That Hu guy mentioned
that one unit of Wushuang
can support a mobile phone for half a year
and keep a car running for 3,000 miles.
More than that.
One unit of Wushuang
has that much of energy.
Just imagine it.
This invention is comparable
to a controlled nuclear fusion.
The four keys that Han Renxin found
are the keys to where Wushuang is stored.
But I've transferred them back now.
The rest are destroyed.
My brother is very cautious
about this technology.
It will be a disaster
if the bad guys get it.
Since my brother asked you to protect me,
I believe he meant for you
to protect Wushuang.
What kind of people
wants to steal this technology?
I don't know.
Once they understand
the power of Wushuang,
I think everyone will want to steal it.
Xingyu,
what is your plan?
It's better to take action
than to defend blindly.
The company has sufficient funds now.
I've decided to manufacture
and mass-produce Wushuang.
As long as we can ensure
its safety and stability,
they will give up on it.
What's wrong?
Uncle Zhongtian wants me to attend
a meeting at Shen Group at 2:00 PM.
He's settling into his position
as the chairman.
Looks like Shen Zhongtian
is making his move.
♪You are God's fallen angel♪
♪You fell from grace for saving me♪
♪This story has no script,
love is hidden between the lines♪
♪Get going and you won't be lost again♪
♪You are the devil's beloved angel♪
♪Lucifer would give up his kingdom for you♪
♪This story has no script,
the audience is still captivated♪
♪Get going and you won't be lost again♪
♪You gave me the courage
to love fearlessly♪
♪Are you my cure?
I can't control my thoughts♪
♪Angel, you make me hesitant
to match my lyrics to the rhythm♪
♪I hope you will find
this acrostic poem interesting♪
♪I will walk with you from dusk to dawn♪
♪Hand in hand,
until our hair turns from black to white♪
♪We will keep studying our future♪
♪We will base it on all your tenderness♪
♪Maybe we have different personalities♪
♪Maybe we have different experiences♪
♪Maybe these might not even be problems♪
♪Loving you is an open secret♪
♪I don't know, I can't figure it out♪
♪You are like a router,
catching all my signals♪
♪Behind your mysteriousness
is a terrifying smile♪
♪This is my fault for myself
landing in hot water♪