Honey, let me hold the bag for you.
Miss is an old acquaintance.
She insisted on making me her master.
It's true.
Her father is a well-known
international tycoon.
He wants me to protect her.
He even wants me
to marry into her family.
I don't believe you.
Why would I lie to you?
At that time, the shares document
and a 10 billion dollar property document
were placed in front of me.
I only need to sign
and Aibora Manor would've been mine.
Why don't you say you'll become
the king of the oil country?
Keep it down.
How do you know about that?
Miss Shen, please wait.
Miss and Mr. Zhao are old acquaintances,
so she specifically told me
to strongly support Miss Shen.
I've decided to invest 100 million
in the Greater China region.
This is the contract.
You may sign it right away.
She did it on her own.
I'm innocent.
Congratulations on the
successful contract, honey.
To celebrate this success,
let's go drinking.
Go drinking?
Do you wanna have
a great time drinking with me
and then...
You're overthinking it.
Okay, I'll go.
How can I not celebrate
my wife's success?
Let's go.
What's the progress with the server?
Mr. Han, we've cracked 20% of it.
Tell them to hurry up.
Xingyu,
don't blame my appetite
after I swallowed your company.
=My Name Is Zhao Wudi=
=Episode 8=
Please enjoy.
Thank you.
Shady?
Pink beauty?
Get drunk or else?
Honey, are you hinting me?
What else?
You have a nightclub girl on your left,
and the daughter of
the Qatar Group on your right.
So many people are interested in you.
I really can't sleep well.
Let me sleep in your bed tonight
and I guarantee a good night's sleep.
I wasn't joking with you.
Don't be so kinky during the day.
Come here.
Let me ask you.
Am I pretty
or is the daughter
of the Qatar Group prettier?
Xingchen.
What are you doing here?
I've been looking for you.
Wudi, do you regret joining this profession?
I am
a single man
with no one to care about.
What's there to regret?
What about you, Xingchen?
I feel like I let my sister down.
She is always scared for me.
Don't think too much.
In my heart,
you're like this.
I'm like this.
So, tell me.
Which one are you?
I'm like this, too.
It's so rare to spend a day in peace.
Ours is a contract marriage.
You're gonna cross the line.
Fine. I'll ask you a question
that doesn't cross the line.
How do you know my brother?
Your brother did me a favor.
So, I owe him one.
Then, do you also know
that my brother died?
I'm not sure about the details.
Anyway, it's not like what they say.
They? Who are they?
I only heard others chatting about it.
I forgot.
- Hello.
- Miss Shen, the firewall is down.
There are no traces of any intrusion.
What?
Okay, I got it. I'm coming back.
What happened?
Ma Ling said important files
in the company got leaked.
The server's firewall
should have been encrypted.
How could it leak?
There were no traces of an intrusion.
The server room.
Miss Shen.
What happened?
I don't know
how the other party got connected.
Without your permission,
we couldn't shut it down.
Fingerprint unlocked.
Enabling iris scan.
(Iris Scan Approved)
I've authorized it.
Why is the data still being transferred?
I don't know.
Call the police.
(23% Transmission Aborted)
I found this behind the server.
A wireless signal transmitter?
Lan Lan must have left this behind
when she stole the files.
But the files in here
require my fingerprint and iris to unlock.
It's easy to get your fingerprint.
As for your iris...
Was there any instrument
that might have scanned your eyes lately?
Hello, please cooperate.
That Han guy went through so much
just to get your iris information
and steal the files.
This place
doesn't look safe anymore.
(23% Transmission Aborted)
Mr. Han,
I think they found the transmitter.
The transmission is terminated.
We only received about 23% of the data.
- What about shareholder information?
- Only found one.
In the high-end parts
manufacturing industry.
About 45 years old.
(Suspicious Website Alert)
The Gray Zone?
Isn't this the rumored kill list?
Kill list?
Let's help Zhao Wudi get on this list.
(One Car Per Entry,
Please Slow Down)
Wudi.
What happened?
Is this you?
You got it wrong.
I'm dumb, not blind.
This is you.
The bounty is 100,000 dollars.
Wudi, you're really valuable.
What now?
Do you wanna kill me and take the bounty?
What?
How did you get onto the Gray Zone?
All the bad guys are on this list.
- You're just a security guard.
- What about a security guard?
Be honest and tell me what you used to do.
Do you have any sort of connections
- and get me on the list too?
- Stop reading web novels.
Why would you trust
a bounty on a dumb website?
Why do you wanna get on the list?
Why not get to Heaven?
Wudi, do me this favor
and I'll get to brag for a lifetime.
Wudi, you must have
a lot of stories to tell.
I have wine. I'll treat you.
Hi, we meet again.
Don't worry. There is no one else here.
I don't want anyone to disturb our date.
You're quite special
for choosing this dating spot.
A man who is on the Gray Zone
willingly works as a security guard.
I think you are the special one.
So,
do you also want 100,000 dollars?
I might wanna warn you
that I happen to have the same name.
That's a better news.
I wouldn't have the heart to kill you.
I just want your...
You're still so ruthless.
I really like it.
Unfortunately,
I don't like the way you smile.
What's this? I stabbed you once
and you wanna stab me back?
Can't do it?
You can do it without a knife.
You're very alert.
Now I don't feel worried.
A word of advice.
Everyone who gets on the Gray Zone
is eventually removed from it,
except for Cang Ming.
Watch your back.
That's none of my business.
I don't wanna earn this 100,000.
♪You are God's fallen angel♪
♪You fell from grace for saving me♪
♪This story has no script,
love is hidden between the lines♪
♪Get going and you won't be lost again♪
♪You are the devil's beloved angel♪
♪Lucifer would give up his kingdom for you♪
♪This story has no script,
the audience is still captivated♪
♪Get going and you won't be lost again♪
♪You gave me the courage
to love fearlessly♪
♪Are you my cure?
I can't control my thoughts♪
♪Angel, you make me hesitant
to match my lyrics to the rhythm♪
♪I hope you will find
this acrostic poem interesting♪
♪I will walk with you from dusk to dawn♪
♪Hand in hand,
until our hair turns from black to white♪
♪We will keep studying our future♪
♪We will base it on all your tenderness♪
♪Maybe we have different personalities♪
♪Maybe we have different experiences♪
♪Maybe these might not even be problems♪
♪Loving you is an open secret♪
♪I don't know, I can't figure it out♪
♪You are like a router,
catching all my signals♪
♪Behind your mysteriousness
is a terrifying smile♪
♪This is my fault for myself
landing in hot water♪