I'm worried because…
I like you, Sarach.
Mr. Din, It really is you.
It's been, what, ten years?
Didn't think you'd remember me.
If you knew from the start,
why didn't you say something?
You knew too and stayed quiet.
Don't you want to know what the girl
Nam's crazy about looks like?
So, you mean, you want me
to go after her or destroy her?
Figure out which one would please me more.
Do you know how humiliating it was for me
to pawn my jewelry
just to cover your interest payment?
And look at you.
You can't get a single thing done.
If you run PD into the ground,
don't say I didn't warn you.
You really like her that much, huh?
You know, why even ask?
Then let me tell you something.
Sarah, or Sara,
is that pimple-faced,
thick-browed, tick-chinned girl,
the daughter of Uncle Suthee,
you used to look down on.
Once the family decides
about the surgery, please let me know.
Yes, Doctor.
Sara.
Yes, Dad?
Get me some water.
Oh, sure.
Mr. Nam?
Hello, Uncle.
You've really grown up, Mr. Nam.
I came as soon as Din
told me what happened.
Thank you, but you didn't
have to trouble yourself.
I wanted to.
Excuse me. I'm here
to take Mr. Suthee for a blood test.
-Let's go, Dad.
-Oh, it's fine.
Stay here and chat with Mr. Nam.
I'll be right back.
Okay.
-Yes.
-This way, please.
Well…
Ms. Sarah,
I wanted to apologize for everything
I did to you when we were kids.
It's alright. That was a long time ago.
But I really do feel bad.
Can you forgive me?
I've already forgotten about it.
It was just a bad childhood memory.
But it wasn't all bad, you know.
It made me stronger.
Made me who I am today.
The more you say that, the worse I feel.
I'm over it.
It doesn't affect me anymore,
so please don't worry.
Thank you.
Hearing you say that
makes me feel a lot better.
If it's possible,
could I have a chance
to make it up to you?
Din already has a head start on me.
And now he's even further ahead
because of this.
What do you mean?
I mean, Din's always been nice to you.
Hey! Nam, give that back!
Let's see. Who's this love letter for?
Give it back!
"Don't cry, okay?
Everyone's got strengths and flaws.
Don't give up. Keep your spirits up.
I'm rooting for you."
Reading someone else's letter? That's bad!
Huh?
Why do you even care about that ugly girl?
She's just staying at our house.
You've done wrong and still aren't sorry?
Dad didn't raise us like that.
We don't get to choose how we're born.
I'm sure she didn't want to be that way.
Think about it. If you were her,
would you like being teased
and bullied like that?
Don't cry, okay?
Everyone's got strengths and flaws.
Don't give up. Keep your spirits up.
I'm rooting for you.
P.S. Eat the lollipop.
It'll make you smile.
Thanks.
So, Mr. Din was the one
who wrote that letter.
Another presentation tomorrow.
These days never seem to end.
Right.
Here. This is to make up
for the other day.
What are you plotting now?
I'm serious. I bought it to apologize.
Keep it and eat it then.
Take it as me accepting your apology.
If you don't take it,
that means you're still mad at me.
I told you I'm not mad. Now move.
Oh!
You shouldn't have done that.
Yeah, Rach. You went too far this time.
Yo even came over to apologize to you.
If it were me, I'd be scared too,
with that act.
-Cherry!
Sorry I snapped at you.
I thought
you were gonna mess with me again.
So, in your eyes, I'm just all bad,
nothing good about me, huh?
My dad's been sick lately.
I've just been stressed.
Sorry about that.
Uncle Suthee's unwell? Is it serious?
Yeah, pretty serious.
I'm sorry for everything I've done before.
I don't even know
why I treated you so badly.
But from now on,
I promise I won't do it again.
Okay?
Pinky swear? Isn't that a bit childish?
If you won't, that means
you haven't forgiven me.
Or do you want it official?
I'll print a peace treaty and sign it.
That's a bit much.
Your father's muscular heart disease
is caused by blocked coronary arteries.
It's been getting worse, and right now,
it's reached a critical stage.
How much time do we have left, Doctor?
I can't say exactly,
but we need to act fast.
As soon as there's a donor heart,
we operate immediately.
Mr. Din?
You forgot to update me
on Uncle Suthee's condition.
A heart transplant
is going to cost a lot.
-I'll mortgage the house and land--
-It won't be fast enough. You know that.
But I can help you.
It's just that… I have one condition.
You'll have to marry me.
-Uncle Perm.
-Yes, sir?
Is Ms. Sarah in today?
Oh, I thought you knew. She's on leave.
I see.
There's no telling
when a donor heart will appear
or if it will be a match.
And once it's removed,
it's only viable for four hours.
Yes, Doctor.
What we can do is keep
the patient ready at all times.
For now, all we can do is pray
that a heart arrives in time
and hope your father can hold on.
Please take care of him, Doctor.
We will.
Once you finish this, send it right in.
And be extra careful
with the heart documents.
The factory says the gift set Ms. Sarah
designed and submitted is almost done.
They'll let us know
when the prototype is ready.
Okay.
Once they confirm,
have them come present it.
Got it.
Come in.
Mr. Din, I'll get going now.
I accept your offer.
But it's only a marriage in name.
Don't you dare lay a finger on me.
Agreed.
I need to get the surgery money ready
as soon as possible.
Here you go, Mom.
Chicken feet.
-Eat up.
-Okay.
So you'll have strength.
Mom.
Sara and I…
We're getting married.
-Really, Din?
-Yes.
-What did you do?
-Nam!
-Nam.
-What did you do?
How did you get her to say yes in one day?
-What dirty trick did you play? Say it.
-Nam…
She and I love each other.
You couldn't win her.
Don't take it out on me.
-Nam! Yo, stop your brother!
-Nam.
-Nam, stop!
She loves me. Never mind punching.
Even if you kill me,
she still won't choose you.
-Din…
-Nam!
-Nam, stop. Stop! Yo.
-Get him out of here. Go. Nam, stop.
-Let go!
Nam, stop.
Go now!
-Out here. Come on.
-Let go.
-Nam.
-Nam, come here.
-Calm down, son.
-Calm down, Nam.
Let go! Didn't you see what he did?
He stole the woman I love!
I'm not letting him get away with it.
-Nam!
Get a grip!
They've agreed to get married.
What else can you do besides accept it?
No, Mom. A guy like Din
doesn't even know how to love.
He only loves his work and himself!
Nam.
-Listen to me. Listen.
-I…
will wait until
Ms. Sarah changes her mind.
Nam.
Wouldn't it be better to love someone
who actually loves you back?
That'd just be lying to myself, Mom.
Someone like me…
If I can't be with the one I love,
then I won't be with anyone at all.
-Nam.
Are you happy you got a surgery slot?
Of course I'm happy.
But I'm worried about something else.
Tell me.
Who did you borrow the money from?
Right, you said mortgaging the house
and land would take too long.
So, where did you get the money from?
I…
I borrowed it from Mr. Din, Dad.
He'll deduct it from my salary,
and I'll pay him back
It's not much for him anyway.
He won't mind.
And since you were close with his father,
he's confident
we won't run off with the debt.
Excuse me.
Are you ready, Mr. Suthee?
Ready.
Good luck, Dad.
We'll be waiting to hug you after, okay?
We'll be here.
Hang in there, Dad.
Alright.
Where's Uncle?
He's already in surgery.
Sorry I'm late.
I called the office
and heard you took leave,
so I figured you'd be here
and rushed over.
Dad got an emergency surgery slot.
Thanks so much for coming.
Are you really going to marry Din?
I know you're not doing it willingly.
Just tell me.
What dirty trick did he use
to make you agree?
There's no trick.
I'll tell you the truth.
I've secretly fallen
for the person who wrote that letter
since I was a kid.
And when I found out
that person was Mr. Din,
everything just made sense, because I know
he loves me too.
But I don't believe he does.
A guy like him can't love anyone.
He only cares about himself
and the company.
Thanks for the warning.
If I get married and end up unhappy,
that's between me and him.
But thank you again
for caring.
Sorry, we're closed.
Nam.
What's wrong?
What happened? Why are you crying?
I'm heartbroken.
I've never hurt this much in my life.
What happened?
Did Ms. Sarah turn you down?
Not just turn me down,
she's marrying Din.
-Hello, Ms. Sarah.
-Hello.
Hello, Ms. Sarah.
Hello.
-Mr. Perm.
-Yes?
Why's everyone acting so weird
and greeting me like this?
Oh, everyone knows
you and Mr. Din are getting married.
I'm thrilled, really.
Hello.
Don't start lecturing me about knocking.
I've got bigger news.
Our wedding, you mean?
Huh?
Don't tell me you're the one
who told the whole company.
Uncle Perm knows, the world knows.
End of story.
Why didn't you stop him?
Why would I?
Sooner or later,
everyone would find out anyway.
Why are you so mad about it?
Because it's not just that.
Do you know how far the rumors have gone?
Hey, they say Mr. Din's only marrying
to fix the company's bad luck,
since it's struggling.
Really?
I think so.
At first, I thought
she'd end up with Mr. Apo,
he promoted her that hard.
Won't the brothers
kill each other over this?
Exactly.
I've been leading him on for years,
and somehow I lose to the new girl?
She totally came here to bag Mr. Din.
That's what I think too.
Rush a wedding like this,
what else could it be?
She's probably pregnant.
Gossiping
like my title means nothing, huh?
Yeah. But you're a guy. No harm done.
Me, though…
Guess I should wear a ButterBear mascot
suit just to walk into the building.
It's not that bad.
But don't worry.
I won't let your reputation take a hit.
What so funny?
ENJOY YOUR WORK, ALRIGHT?
This is your plan to kill the rumors?
They're gossiping even more.
Except now they're saying
I'm crazy about you,
chasing you till you agreed to marry me.
No harm done to you. And I'm a man.
I can take it.
I'll settle the bill.
You go see your dad first.
Okay.
You're still as kind as ever.
Oh my…
Am I sick or something?
I can't stop smiling.
You first.
Thank you.
Once the gift set's ready,
can I let people outside test it?
It's not work hours yet.
No need to wait. I'm impatient.
Then today, we can go to…
Din.
Eyes?
Choked on it, Mr. Perm?
Thanks.
I didn't think Ms. Eyes
would come back to Mr. Din.
Come back?
No need to look so tense, Mr. Perm.
One look at Mr. Din's face and I knew
she's an ex.
But don't worry.
I'm not petty. I just want to know
and understand the situation, that's all.
Ms. Eyes dated Mr. Din back in college.
No idea why they broke up.
Classic tight-lipped CEO.
Thanks.
Wow.
I haven't been here in ages.
But your office looks exactly the same.
The office is the same,
but everything else has changed.
When you first came here,
PD was still one
of the top five cosmetics companies.
But now…
I've heard the rumors too.
But I believe in you.
You'll get through this,
just like you always have.
Thanks.
So, what brings you here, Eyes?
Are you crazy?
Why'd you bring
that woman back to see Din?
I didn't.
I just saw on Facebook
she was back in Thailand, so I said hi.
I just told her
to go check on him, that's all.
There's more.
She's divorced.
What?
Whoa, hey. Come on.
That'll stain, hard to wash out.
You set her up for Din, didn't you?
If Din doesn't like her,
what can I do, right?
Have you forgotten
how bad it was
when he got his heart broken?
I remember, but that's his business.
Eyes has always been nice to me.
Are you mad because you're worried
or because you're jealous?
If you can tease me like that,
you must be pretty confident
she can make Din dump Ms. Sarah.
Wow.
Din! You scared me.
Congrats to our new project lead.
You knew?
They only announced it this evening.
Then how would it be a surprise?
Din.
-Do you like it?
-I love it.
Thanks, Din. I love you.
We promised we'd do our master's together.
Why did you do this?
Eyes…
My dad's sick,
and the company's in trouble.
I really can't leave, Eyes.
What about me? What about our life?
You're always like this.
Family. Company.
Those are the only two things
that matter to you.
That's not true. I care about you a lot.
Well, good thing you won't go with me.
Let's take a break.
Eyes. Eyes.
Don't go.
I love you.
I think…
we should renegotiate our deal.
Deal?
Call off the wedding.
Let me pay for Dad's treatment
in installments.
That way, I won't have to force myself,
and you'll have a chance to get back
with Ms. Eyes.
Win-win for both of us.
No.
Nothing's changing.
Thanks for the ride.
Anyone could see from the moon
you still haven't gotten over her.
Why did you send Eyes to see me?
It's early, bro. I'm not arguing with you.
I'm not arguing, just asking.
Or is it that you can do it,
but can't admit it?
Honestly, whether Eyes
came or not doesn't matter.
What really matters
is how you feel.
Lost my appetite. I'm out.
Hello, Sara.
Hi, Mr. Din.
Are you ready
to go look at wedding dresses?
Wedding dresses?
When did you schedule that?
Alright then.
I want to see you in a wedding dress too.
Wait, I haven't said anything yet.
See you there.
You mocking me?
You brought Eyes to see me,
hoping I'd get distracted,
or better yet, fight with Sara.
So, I showed you it didn't work.
Sara and I will never fall apart
over your cheap tricks.
I just came to warn you. Be careful.
The person who asked you to work
with them isn't exactly clean.
But my offer still stands.
Call off the wedding.
Are you a human or the Yellow River?
You really let your fiancé
go out with his ex?
Are you free today?
I really need to talk to you.
Can you come to my condo?
Eyes! Eyes!
Eyes!
Subtitle translation by: Praeploy Mahawan