Why is the house so quiet today?
Your dear brother Din got Baicha pregnant.
So Sara packed up and went back home.
If this child is mine,
I will never let my child
call someone else Dad.
Let me go.
I'm begging you.
If I can't kill you all outright,
I'll make you suffer while you're alive.
Who are you here to see?
I don't know his name.
I just know he's Krongthong's son.
Hey, what happened?
What's wrong with my mom?
Your mother had a TIA.
A transient ischemic attack.
But the doctor says she'll recover soon.
Thank you so much
for bringing my mom to the hospital
and staying to look after her.
It's just something
that needed to be done, isn't it?
I know that she doesn't
want anything to do with you,
but when she's sick, I'm sure
you'd never abandon her.
So you stepped in and did my part.
Like a…
a nurse…
You don't need to dance around it.
I was doing my duty
as her daughter-in-law.
But once we divorce,
you'll need to find someone else
to take care of her.
Sara…
I should head home now. It's late.
Then let me drive you home.
I'm going back to Dad's place.
Well, it's pretty late.
Why don't you just stay here tonight, Din?
Dad.
He already drove me home.
Why make him stay?
Besides, it's probably
inconvenient for him.
- I'm fine with it.
- See? He says it's fine.
But Dad…
Come on. Be considerate.
It's already late,
and he drove all this way.
Driving back again would exhaust him.
That's true. I am pretty tired and sleepy.
I'm worried I might get
into an accident if I drive back.
Then go ahead and take a shower.
I'll prepare some clothes for you.
Thank you.
Dad.
Why does he have to sleep in my room?
Sarach is already asleep,
and my room is too small.
Two people would be uncomfortable.
My room isn't that big either.
Well, still bigger than mine.
Come on. It's just one night.
It's late. Go to sleep,
you two. I'll go now.
Dad, wait… Dad!
Hey, hey.
- Wait.
- Huh?
What are you doing?
Going to sleep.
On the floor.
Blankets and pillows are in the closet.
Help yourself.
This space is tiny.
I'll be really uncomfortable.
I should sleep on the bed instead.
Hey.
- Hey, hey!
- Whoa!
Seriously…
Do you want to sleep on the floor nicely
or pass out on the floor?
Your choice.
Honestly, I kind of like
sleeping on the floor.
It's actually pretty comfortable.
Hey, that thing's
really powerful, you know?
Let me put this here for a bit.
Hey.
- Sorry, sorry.
- Don't sneak up on me like that.
If I had a heart attack,
you'd be the first one I'd haunt.
So… what are you doing here?
To see my baby.
I already told you.
The baby is Din's, not yours.
Then… I'm here to see my niece or nephew.
Are you arguing that too?
Oh, right.
Have you started prenatal care?
Not yet. Why?
‪PHARMACY
All done.
These are supplements.
Take them on time.
And this is your appointment card
for next time.
Fine. So you're not going to talk?
My dear nibling…
If your mom's this stubborn,
you'll need to be patient.
Get up right now.
Hey, wait, I'm talking to my nibling.
My dear nibling…
Hang in there a little longer.
Your mom will grow up soon, okay?
- Hey.
- What?
I'm talking to my nibling.
‪COUPLE CHECKUP PROGRAM
My dear nibling… What's that?
Really?
Right? Your mom still hasn't grown up.
Let me hear that again.
Okay, let me listen.
The test results are out.
The doctor says there's nothing serious.
He's prescribed medication.
But you'll need to follow
a controlled diet as instructed.
Why did you help me?
Don't expect me to thank you.
You did this on your own.
I'm just doing what I should.
Even if you don't see me as your son…
when you're sick,
I can't just stand by and do nothing.
Enough already!
Do you have any idea how bad it feels
for a mother who abandoned her child,
only to have him come back
and take care of her?
All this time, the reason
I never went to see you
was because I didn't
want to feel this way.
Guilty. Like a terrible person.
Mom.
I've already forgiven you.
You should forgive yourself too.
From now on, unless
it's absolutely necessary,
I won't contact you again.
The person you should
really be taking care of
is Namnuan.
Namnuan, my stepmother?
Think about it carefully.
She raised you until you grew up.
She gave you everything
a child should have.
As your real mother,
what did I ever give you? Nothing.
But…
But she doesn't love me.
Even if she doesn't love you,
she's the only one who raised you.
She devoted everything to you…
even though she never had to.
Alright.
That concludes today's meeting.
I have an important announcement to make.
I've been serving as CEO
of PD Group for a while now,
and during my time in this role,
I've realized
this position doesn't suit me.
I hereby
resign from my position as CEO.
And I appoint Mr. Chakrit
to assume the position
effective immediately.
Congratulations.
PD is in your hands now.
Why say it like that?
I'll still be relying on you, Din.
From now on, you will work with Nina.
You want me to work with Nina?
Yes. While Nina is in the U.S.,
you'll have the same authority as her.
Please look after her.
She's still very inexperienced.
You already have Chakrit.
I don't think I'm necessary.
Two heads are better than one.
This is all for PD.
You want to see PD thrive too, don't you?
Please excuse me.
What is this supposed to mean?
Why would you do this?
Having Din work with Nina,
isn't that the same
as having him work for us?
Chakrit is trying to take Din down.
That's exactly why I have to help Din.
Don't you feel it? Chakrit's
getting more arrogant every day.
Now that he's the CEO,
he'll think he's untouchable.
I won't let him control everything.
Let them keep each other in check.
That way, we benefit.
Nam.
If you want to yell at me, go ahead.
I know what I did was wrong.
If you want to hit me, I'll accept it.
That's not what this is about.
Sara and I,
we need to talk to you.
Ms. Sarah?
Let's take a walk, one or two laps.
Pregnant women
are supposed to keep moving,
exercise regularly, so they stay healthy.
Thank you so much, Din,
for taking care of me.
Hello?
What?
Nam was assaulted?
Chakrit. It had to be Chakrit.
Nam!
Nam, what happened to you?
Where are you hurt? Wake up!
Wake up, Nam. Talk to me.
You're really sly
and calculating, aren't you?
If you hadn't backed me up,
I wouldn't have pulled it off.
Here's the real problem
with Ms. Baicha right now.
She thinks Mr. Nam doesn't love her,
that he doesn't want her.
Is that so?
Believe me, speaking as a woman,
when women overthink things,
they become insecure and easily hurt.
And with pregnancy hormones,
it's even worse.
So, in the end, it all comes down to you.
What you choose to do.
I love Baicha.
I love her as a friend,
as my significant other,
and as the mother of my child.
I just didn't realize it before.
But once everything happened,
I knew.
I realized I was afraid of losing her,
afraid she'd disappear from my life.
Then that means
you both feel the same way.
I have a plan.
You still have the nerve to blame me?
Honestly,
if you hadn't been sure
and helped confirm it, would I have dared?
I love Baicha like my own little sister.
So whatever I do,
I have to think it through.
If something went wrong,
it would only hurt her more.
Nam…
Nam!
Baicha…
Let go. Let go of me.
I said let go, you liar!
Let go.
I told you, call me "dear."
Nam, let go!
Say it. Call me "dear."
Or this time, it won't just be your cheek.
I love you, Baicha.
I don't know when it started.
But once I found out you were pregnant,
there wasn't a single second
I regretted it.
I was only worried.
When I realized you'd disappeared,
I nearly lost my mind.
That's when I knew
I'd do anything not to lose you.
There, there.
Don't cry.
I'm sorry.
I know I hurt you.
But at the time, Baicha
threatened to have an abortion.
Chakrit was furious,
and I was afraid he'd hurt Nam.
So, I had no choice
but to take responsibility
as the child's father.
Sara.
I wanted to explain everything to you,
but…
I hesitated.
I was worried about Nam and Baicha,
afraid the company would be damaged.
So…
I chose to stay silent.
I thought I'd talk to you
once everything settled down.
But it only hurt you.
Please forgive me.
You chose to do this
because you weren't confident in me.
You didn't trust that I could stand by you
through everything.
You hid the truth from me
and carried everything on your own.
So…
I can't forgive you.
Sara…
Mom, we've already
registered our marriage.
You're legally married?
What is all this?
Mom.
My child will have to call you "grandma."
Your child? Isn't the baby Din's?
No.
Din only took responsibility on my behalf.
But I won't run away anymore.
I want to take responsibility
for my wife and my child.
Please give us your blessing.
Please take care of me, Auntie.
What is this nonsense?
Have you lost your mind, Nam?
Everything we're dealing with right now,
isn't it all because of Chakrit?
And now you go and marry his sister?
Mom, Baicha may be Krit's sister,
but the baby she's carrying
is my child, your grandchild.
Mom,
things have gone this far already.
Please don't be angry anymore. Alright?
I won't accept this.
What a model big brother you are.
If you're going to be the father,
why not see it through?
Mom, we're one family.
When there's a problem, we work
through it and support each other,
not make things worse
or pile on more trouble.
Are you saying I'm the problem?
Didn't the company end up like this
because of your poor decisions?
If you'd held my hand tight back then,
we wouldn't be here today.
The same goes for Nam.
Do you really think what you're doing
will make things better?
You're pushing your own children
and grandchildren away.
But Baicha is Chakrit's sister.
They're two different people.
We shouldn't take one generation's
problems out on the next.
Otherwise, we're no different
from Chakrit.
Mom.
Baicha.
Fine.
You're Nam's wife now, so you're family.
Take good care of yourself,
for the baby's sake.
Thank you, Mom.
Hm. What about Chakrit?
He won't cause trouble for you two, right?
Baicha and I already texted him
and told him everything.
He hasn't responded yet.
Increase capital and list
the shares on the exchange?
Yes. Funding isn't a problem for me.
PD needs to move forward.
But none of us has cash
anywhere near yours.
Even if we inject more capital,
we still can't buy
enough shares to compete.
The shares I hold would lose
their power immediately.
Then sell them.
Use the IPO window
and make a big profit.
You're an investor type anyway.
I don't need to teach you that.
And my authority as CEO?
No need to overthink it.
Just do your job and follow my orders.
Oh, one more thing.
Din agrees with this.
Din!
Are you stupid or crazy,
taking Praphop's side?
Not calling him "sir" anymore?
What you're doing will hurt you too.
So what? What can I even do right now?
Isn't this on you?
You wanted PD for revenge. Did you get it?
You wanted Phimarndech to fall.
Did it go the way you hoped?
In the end, it's you
who became a pawn in their game.
We're here because you
chose this yourself.
You let imaginary grudges control you.
No reason, no self-control.
You acted like a rabid dog,
and look where that got you!
Din, listen to me.
Someone like me
won't lose to you or Praphop.
Just wait. Just wait.
Hello. What can I get--
What is it?
He won't dare do anything right now.
Why are you acting like that, Nam?
I'm just here to see my sister
and my unborn nibling.
Hi, Baicha.
How are you?
I'm fine, Krit.
You promised you'd let Baicha go
if I helped you become CEO.
Wow. Cutting me off before I even speak.
I'm a man of my word.
You don't need to worry.
But today, I'm here
to talk about something else.
If it's about taking PD public, I'm out.
Not just that, everything at PD.
Right now, I'm focusing
on Baicha and the baby.
I won't stop you from that,
but I want you to think about the future.
The baby Baicha's carrying
is my niece or nephew too.
If we keep the company, one day,
it'll belong to your child anyway.
Belong to my child?
You hate me and Din this much.
Even if it's your blood, if it carries
our name, you'd never give it up.
You're just looking for allies because
Uncle Praphop is taking your power.
Nam.
Go home. I won't
let you use my child as a tool.
They deserve the freedom
to choose their own life,
not to carry anyone's expectations
or ambitions.
Nam, you're so damn stupid.
Can you come into the office this morning?
Our partner wants to congratulate us
on the sales surge.
I have to take my dad to the doctor.
I'll come in this afternoon.
What a shame. You're a key part of this.
Then give me a raise.
Seriously…
Alright. Take your dad to the doctor.
We'll meet this afternoon.
Talk to you later.
Hold on.
Yes?
I missed you.
Our key man has arrived!
Come on, Din. Here, take the flowers.
Here, our guest made the trip specially.
Congratulations on the sales,
Mr. Pathawee.
Thank you very much.
Alright, let's take a photo.
Please, please.
This way. Please stand closer.
Smile, cheese!
I came to talk about a raise--
He's not here?
Why aren't you answering?
You disappear without saying a word.
Uncle?
Uncle!
Uncle, can you hear me?
This is brutal.
Praphop is in a coma.
I've gone over the timeline carefully.
There's a very strong possibility
that I was…
Drugged.
We have evidence from CCTV footage.
It clearly shows the last person
with Mr. Praphop was you.
If you ever fall,
I'll sit right by your side,
until you're back on your feet.
You!
Who sent you?
Subtitle translation by: Praeploy Mahawan