[Silent Honor]
[Episode 13]
From November 1st, 1949
to December 27th, 1949,
the PLA spent 57 days
liberating most parts of Sichuan, Xikang,
Yunnan and Guizhou,
as well as over 500 cities and towns
in Hunan, Hubei, Shaanxi and Gansu.
Chiang Kai-shek personally
directed the battles,
yet he could not reverse
the tide of defeat.
On December 10th,
he flew from Chengdu to Taiwan,
and never set foot
on the Chinese mainland again.
[Caoshan Villa]
President.
These are several plans
from the Ministry of Defense about
recapturing Kunming
and punishing the traitor Lu Han,
including deploying troops
from nearby areas to close in on Kunming
and carrying out
a direct air force bombing
on Wuhua Mountain
where the Yunnan Provincial Government is.
It seems everyone
at the Ministry of Defense
is filled with righteous indignation.
We're just waiting for your order,
President.
No hurry.
Zhirou.
To suppress the rebellion
and save the nation,
punishing Lu Han alone
is far from enough.
I have more important arrangements
for the air force.
Yes, sir.
We lost the Southwest Campaign
and there is the deciphered content
of the telegram.
I suspect there's a Communist spy
in the military top brass.
Where is Gu Zhengwen now?
[BIS of the Ministry of Defense]
Director.
The terrain in Taichung's
mountainous areas is complex.
And inter-village transportation
is often inconvenient.
Posing as a school teacher,
I built closer relations
with local villagers.
Through extensive investigations,
it wasn't until recently
that I discovered that a group of people,
under the pretext of land reclamation,
were engaging in large-scale purchases
of weapons left behind
by the Japanese army.
Combined with the previously collected
information,
I think that
one of armed bases
of the Communist spies
is likely located in the area
between Zhuzikeng and Baimao Mountain.
As for the exact location,
we still need
further detailed investigations.
You go compile this into a document.
I'll send others
to conduct the investigation.
Yes, sir.
Now that the Nationalist Army
keeps retreating in defeat,
intelligence personnel
from all over the country
have come to Taiwan.
But in Taiwan,
there can't be
too many Communist spies.
We don't need so many people.
So rectification and downsizing
are imperative.
Only those who deliver results
get to keep their positions.
Yes, sir.
We've almost run out of the credit we got
from our success
with the Guangming News case.
It's time to reopen the Zhang Hao case.
Yes, sir.
Well,
your last trip to Hong Kong
wasn't in vain.
Using the key and codebook
you brought back,
the Section 4 deciphered a telegram
that was intercepted
on September 21st.
It contained military deployments
for Kinmen and Xiamen.
And according to Liu Kangfu's confession,
he was sending the telegram
to a Communist spy team called East Sea.
So I suspect that the East Sea
is hiding within the upper echelons
of the Nationalist Government.
Comrade Jianfeng has agreed
that from now on,
you'll be reinstated
to your original position.
Go find out that Communist spy.
Yes, sir!
Captain Liu.
The numbers don't add up.
It's short by about 100 kg.
That can't be right.
Did you count wrong?
How could I possibly count wrong?
Captain Liu.
You can't keep giving us less each month.
That's not proper, right?
There're so many men in my team.
How am I supposed
to distribute this?
I'm just the delivery man.
I deliver exactly
what is allocated to you.
We're colleagues working together.
I wouldn't cut your food short,
would I?
I'm off.
Captain Liu!
The numbers just don't add up.
What do you mean?
If you're not satisfied,
I'll just take it all back.
I can just send someone else
to drop it off,
and it'll end up another 100 kg short.
It's not about my satisfaction.
There are so many people in my team.
We can let everyone see
if it gets less and less each month.
I'm not lying to you!
Lianwang.
Come here and be the judge.
Lianwang, come take a look.
See if they're skimming off
the army rations.
I don't really understand
these things.
How can you not understand this?
Come here.
You...
I left my folder inside.
I forgot to bring my folder.
Lianwang.
See?
Nobody wants to get involved.
In the army, it's always the superiors
that take advantage
of the ones below them.
Captain Liu.
If you don't make up the shortage today,
you don't even think about leaving.
Are you asking for trouble?
Yes, I am asking for trouble.
You!
Stop, stop, stop!
Leader!
You're finally back, Leader.
They've been holding back
our food supplies.
Nonsense!
Holding back the army rations?
Mr. Gu.
Captain Liu, that's impossible, right?
We both work
for the Nationalist Government.
Times are tough for everyone now.
I understand that.
It's not easy, but that's okay.
I'm back now.
By the way,
here's some money,
which is not much to share.
Take it and get everyone something to eat.
Captain Liu.
If there's really not enough food
for us,
just take all this away.
That won't be necessary, Mr. Gu.
No need.
I mean it.
When there's a proper opportunity later,
I'll get more for you to make up for it.
Really?
Yes.
Thank you.
Leader.
I thank you on behalf of everyone.
You've finally returned.
You don't know when you were gone...
Enough. Don't dwell
on these small matters.
Get me the schedule number
for the Ping'an Ship. I need it.
Help me take the stuff upstairs.
Be careful!
-Yes.
Leader.
I'm going to read the newspaper.
I'm going to read the newspaper
for a while.
Be good.
[Communist Party Members' Remains
Were Found on Coast After Over Ten Days]
At 10 PM on September 19th,
it arrived at Keelung Harbor.
It departed at 6 AM on the 21st.
Leader, I found it.
So Zhang Hao
sent the telegram right after
the ship departed on the 21st.
But at 10 PM on the 19th,
the ship arrived in Keelung.
Keelung was under curfew at that time.
That means
he could only get the content
for the telegram
during the daytime of the 20th.
What telegram?
It has been deciphered!
Take Liu Kangfu
to the interrogation room.
Do you know why you're here?
I previously
ruined your big plan.
And now this is my chance
to atone for my mistakes.
It's not some big plan.
Things are always changing.
It's not all your fault.
This time your mission is very simple.
You just need to
tell me every single detail
about Zhang Hao and you
since you met,
including what he said,
what he did,
even what clothes he wore,
and his habitual phrases
and gestures.
Tell me everything in detail.
Okay, I'll tell you.
I'll tell you everything.
I first met Zhang Hao
at the end of August.
At that time, I had been assigned to work
on the Ping'an Ship
by the Taiwan Work Committee
for more than two months.
He was the first mate on the ship.
Right.
I was practicing
throwing mooring lines that day
when he suddenly came up to me.
Deputy Chief Wu.
The Chief hasn't returned yet?
Not yet.
There's no meeting
at the ministry today.
Where did he go for a meeting?
I'm not quite sure about the details.
How about I call you
when the Chief returns?
You're the First Secretary.
And you don't know?
General Huang Jie has sent
three urgent telegrams in one day.
I'm waiting for the Chief's decision.
Well...
The Chief went to the Hsinchu base
for a meeting.
He specifically ordered
that no one should disturb him.
Fine.
Let me know as soon as he returns.
Yes, sir!
September 20th?
The question is so sudden
that I can't remember now.
It has been over three months.
It has indeed been
over three months.
But look,
the Ping'an Ship arrived at Keelung Harbor
on the evening of the 19th.
But in the early morning of the 21st,
it left Keelung Harbor for Guangzhou.
That means Zhang Hao
could only have gone to Taipei
during the day on the 20th.
Now that you mention it, I remember.
That docking was particularly hasty.
We weren't allowed
to get off the ship at all.
As for whether Zhang Hao got off
or where he went,
I have no idea.
Mr. Gu,
I've only met Zhang Hao
a few times in total.
I've already told you everything I know
and I can remember.
I believe you.
Was there any informal contact
between Zhang Hao and you
that was not related to your party work
or your duties on the Ping'an Ship?
Now that you mention it,
there was indeed one time.
When I was eating
at a restaurant in Keelung,
I ran into Zhang Hao.
When was this?
Who did he meet?
Did he see you?
It was probably also in late September.
I really don't remember what he was doing.
I was sitting in the restaurant.
He probably didn't see me.
It was very hot that day.
There were a lot of salted fish
drying on the street,
with a fishy smell everywhere.
What did you eat?
Sanxian Noodles.
Sir.
You think there's something wrong
with Zhou Zhirou
rushing to Hsinchu for the meeting?
It's definitely unusual.
It seems that
the air force will take action soon.
That's possible.
Mr. Chiang
is furious about Lu Han's uprising.
Is the air force planning to retaliate
against Lu Han
by bombing Kunming?
Or will they send the air force
to support Hu Zongnan
at the Chengdu front?
China is so vast.
We can't rule out that Mr. Chiang
might have other plans.
Mr. Gu, aren't you eating?
Never mind. I'm not hungry anyway.
It tastes good?
It's fine.
Both taste
and smell
can help you remember.
Have you thought of anything?
No.
That's okay.
Well then...
When you saw Zhang Hao that day,
was he right in front of you
or was he on your
left
or right?
Right.
On your right?
On your right.
On your left?
This side.
On your left.
You were eating Sanxian Noodles that day.
You turned your head to the left
and saw Zhang Hao.
Xiaonan.
Come here.
Stand here.
Hurry.
You play Zhang Hao. Here.
Was Zhang Hao talking with...
Yes.
So Zhang Hao was talking to someone
and you couldn't see that person
due to this position, right?
That person was behind the wall.
There was a wall on this side?
Yes.
No wonder.
Turn around.
-Turn around.
-Yeah.
Right. Zhang Hao turned around,
and that's how I saw him.
I remember that day
he seemed reluctant to leave.
Reluctant to leave?
Well, it seems
the person behind the wall
had a special relationship with Zhang Hao.
I'll take you to Keelung Harbor tomorrow.
Wait.
I think it's here.
Don't stop now.
Find a place to pull over ahead.
I remember it was around here.
There were many snack stands
in this area.
Here.
This way.
I was sitting right in this spot
and he was standing over there.
Isn't this on your right?
Sorry, I made a mistake.
So you were looking
at that direction?
Yes.
Are you sure?
Definitely. Right here.
Let me know if you have dried oysters.
Hold this.
Thank you.
Hello.
What kind of fish is this?
It's the local Sipo fish,
also called Balang.
It adds great flavor to congee and soup.
I was worried
you couldn't understand what I said.
Are you not a local either?
In business, customers come
from all over the world.
Learning some local dialect
helps with business, right?
Yes, indeed.
I'll take some of this.
Sure.
These are good.
Let me weigh some for you.
Great.
Leader,
do you think there's something wrong
with this shop?
Why isn't Mrs. Ma here today?
She loves playing mahjong the most,
doesn't she?
Director Ma has got another mistress.
Director Ma is such a playboy.
He changes mistresses every month.
You really don't want to know
who that woman is?
Who is she?
The the lead songstress at Huadu Ballroom.
She's also an air force widow.
She was a college student.
After graduation, she married a pilot.
The day after their wedding,
her husband's plane
fell from the sky.
She came to Taiwan
and became a songstress.
I've seen her.
She's incredibly beautiful.
No wonder Director Ma can't resist her
and never goes home.
Mrs. Huang, would you play for me
for a while?
I suddenly got a headache.
I'll go rest over there.
All right, I'll take over.
Where do you pick up
all these gossipy bits?
My husband told me!
His job is basically gathering information
about others, isn't it?
Your husband knows
so much gossip.
Aren't you afraid he might
follow Director Ma to Huadu Ballroom?
If he really wants to do that,
how can I possibly stop him?
As long as he doesn't bring
his mistress home, it's fine.
You're so open-minded.
What else can I do?
That's true.
You can't exactly
tie your husband down with a rope.
Mrs. Wu, I really envy you.
You never have to worry about such things,
right?
My husband also said
that Deputy Chief Wu is a really good man,
who never flirts with other women
and only focuses on his work.
Exactly.
I've heard that too.
You can't judge people by appearances.
I've heard that
a woman went
to Power Company Guesthouse
to see Deputy Chief Wu.
Keep your voice down.
Your husband is really something,
spying even
on his superior's personal life.
Deputy Chief Wu?
Didn't he just move?
Could it have been a female colleague
or something?
She was dressed like a rich madam,
so she definitely is not a colleague.
Enough.
Stop gossiping behind people's backs.
Mrs. Dou.
I'm really sorry,
but I'm just too tired.
I'll leave first, okay?
Please enjoy yourselves.
Goodbye, Mrs. Wu.
See you next time.
Alright, goodbye.
-Goodbye.
Liu, bring Mrs. Wu's shawl over here.
Coming.
Here. Give it to me.
Thank you.
I'm sorry about today.
I've ruined everyone's mood.
Not at all.
You're always welcome here.
It's my fault.
I should invite just anyone to my home.
It's fine.
Go back inside.
Goodbye.
She's angry with me?
Did I say something wrong?
Liu,
bring Mrs. Duan's coat over here.
She should be leaving too.
I'm a straightforward person.
I hate gossip the most.
You're no longer welcome at Dou's Mansion.
Please leave.
How could you be like this?
Why is it so hard
to tell the truth these days?
When your husband becomes
Deputy Chief Duan, then we'll talk.
Madam, you're back.
Didn't you go to Dou's Mansion
to play mahjong?
Why are you back so early?
You didn't work overtime today?
No. We've made that agreement, haven't we?
I should come home on time.
Nice talk.
I'd rather believe pigs can fly
than believe a man's smooth talk.
What's wrong?
Did you hear something
at Dou's Mansion?
All these years you've worked
so hard outside.
I know that and understand you.
For a high-ranking official like you,
it's normal to have a mistress.
But I only have one request.
Don't lie to me.
Did you hear something from those madams?
What did they say?
Mrs. Ma wasn't there today.
And they said that
Director Ma got another mistress.
Then Mrs. Dou said she envied me.
But Mrs. Duan sitting nearby
started to stir things up,
saying something ridiculous.
Which madam?
Mrs. Duan.
What ridiculous things did she say?
Don't ask anymore.
It was nothing.
Yuxun.
I only have one request.
No matter what,
don't lie to me.
Bikui.
We met and fell in love when you were 18.
We've been married for 30 years.
Doesn't all of this
outweigh their gossip?
I shouldn't have listened to them.
I shouldn't have listened.
It was nonsense.
Come on, Bikui.
Listen to this.
No matter what you hear,
you must believe
I won't lie to you.
Trust me.
Your hairstyle looks beautiful.
Morning, Sir.
Duan Tuizhi is investigating Mrs. Chen.
Just because of what happened
at Power Company Guesthouse?
At that time,
she claimed to be my wife's friend.
If the investigation continues,
her cover will be blown soon.
So we must send her back.
Get her the exit permit
as soon as possible.
Alright. I'll do it today.
[Deputy Chief's Wife Leads Christmas
Charity Sale to Support Zhoushan]
Many people know about the telegram
regarding Kinmen and Xiamen.
Are you still suspecting Deputy Chief Wu?
There are indeed quite a few people
with access to the deployment information
in Kinmen and Xiaman.
But...
But only Deputy Chief Wu
also had the chance
to meet Zhang Hao on September 20th
and also actually met Zhang Hao
at the entrance of NTUH.
What does this have to do
with this Mr. Lin?
I suspect that the person Zhang Hao met
at Sanrong Trading in September
was Lin Yiliang.
And according to Liu Kangfu,
these two had a deep connection.
I believe
they might be brothers
or
Communist spy partners
having worked together for a long time.
But regardless of their relationship,
as long as we investigate him thoroughly,
it will lead to a major breakthrough
in the case.
Birds of a feather flock together.
This kind of situation
is quite common.
It's not enough.
It's still too peripheral.
Since you're suspecting Deputy Chief Wu,
you must get the first-hand information.
Yes, sir. I'm working on it.
Where else can we
find such a good employer
who even works alongside us?
Anywhere else,
we'd have to carry everything ourselves.
What are you looking at?
Keep working.
I've been working all along.
The sooner you finish,
the sooner you get paid.
Just put it by the door.
Put it by the door too.
Hello. What are you doing?
I need to use the restroom.
Wait.
This way, please.
No, the one inside...
Turn left here,
and you'll find it to your right.
The staff in the shop are very vigilant.
And they're also very tight-lipped.
I've been looking for a chance,
but I couldn't even get one foot inside.
Leader,
I think
there's definitely something fishy
about the shop.
Alright, let me sum this up for you.
So with an ordinary identity,
you can't go inside, right?
Yes.
I think
Sanrong Trading
is impenetrable
and sealed off.
For us to break in
is indeed quite difficult.
How many Keelung Work Committee members
we arrested for the Guangming News case
are still in custody?
About 30.
You mean
we'll pretend to be
from the Keelung Work Committee, right?
That's a great idea, Leader.
I've been wrongly accused.
I didn't do it!
Please.
Let me go!
Please release me!
It really wasn't me!
Mr. Zhuang.
It has been a long time.
You've lost weight.
No, no, no.
You bastard.
Forty-seven lives lost
at Keelung Middle School.
Can you sleep at night?
Yes, I can.
You know, I'm also a materialist.
You'll die a terrible death.
It really is suitable.
Bring him out.
Let's stop here for today.
Deputy Chief Wu, please stay.
Senior.
The Ministry of Foreign Affairs told me
that the French government
finally agreed to let Huang Jie's corps
withdraw to Vietnam.
That's good.
Better to get some back than none.
It's better than letting Lin Biao
capture 30,000 more men.
The condition is
that the troops
must surrender their weapons.
Surrender the weapons?
Surrender the weapons to the French?
Come in.
Leader, you wanted to see me?
Have a seat.
How has your harvest been lately?
W-What harvest?
I heard that
you've been frequently helping out
at the Operations Division lately.
Leader,
I didn't keep it all to myself.
While you were away,
our colleagues were almost out of food.
So I came up with a way
to improve everyone's living conditions.
Do you remember
the full name of our team?
The Counterintelligence Section
of the BIS.
of the BIS
actually has a very short history.
When you were still at the Taiwan station,
it was just a unit
under the Operations Division.
After the Guangming News case,
the Director appreciated
our competence
in capturing Communist spies,
so he made our team a separate section.
However,
if
our future work doesn't go smoothly
and we fail to catch Communist spies,
then I'm afraid you'll end up
on the streets
checking IDs.
Just as you said,
"I speak both Mandarin and Hokkien,
which comes in handy,
while Yu Xiaonan is so inarticulate
that he can't even check IDs properly."
Leader,
how did you know that?
Isn't this what you said?
I believe those were your exact words.
I'm sorry, Leader.
I...
I was indeed speaking out of turn.
How is that speaking out of turn?
It was precisely
because you have these skills
that I specifically transferred you here
from Director Ye.
You're overthinking it. It's fine.
Sit down.
Even if
the Ministry of Defense
orders Huang Jie's corps
not to surrender their weapons
and hold their position,
do you think they would listen?
They've fled all the way from Hunan,
running over 1,000 kilometers.
They're just one step away
from crossing the border
to safety.
Huang Jie's corps
had been retreating
under the PLA's pursuit.
They could only detour through Vietnam
to return to Taiwan.
Wu Shi had approached Zhou Zhirou
several times before
but failed to get any information.
Now that Zhou Zhirou brought up
the matter himself,
Wu Shi keenly realized
this was the perfect opportunity
to pry into the air force's
secret operation.
Wu Shi then seized the chance,
using his opposition to Huang Jie's corps
surrendering their weapons to the French
to probe Zhou Zhirou's true thoughts
on the matter
and then act accordingly.
In any case, it's better than
being annihilated
by the Communist Army, isn't it?
Chief,
what are you going to do?
After Huang Jie's corps
surrender their weapons,
they'll assemble and stand by
in Haiphong, Vietnam.
This involves many parties.
Therefore,
someone from our ministry
must take charge.
I'll have to trouble you
to coordinate with various parties.
Yes.
I understand.
I'll take charge of this.
I'll report directly to you.
For 30,000 men,
I need transport ships.
I've made a rough estimation.
In total,
we need 3 to 10 transport ships.
Good.
You can go
to Director Ma directly.
He is currently in charge
of coordinating military logistics.
If it's really impossible
to arrange the ships,
then we'll have to postpone it.
It cannot be postponed.
Chief.
Huang Jie was the former
Deputy Chief of Staff after all.
If he's really captured,
it'll be embarrassing for all of us.
If we can bring back Huang Jie's corps,
that's 30,000 combat-ready soldiers
after all.
Good.
Then I'll trouble you with this task.
Rest assured. I'll do my best.
I will definitely work hard
and catch more Communist spies for you,
making the Counterintelligence Section
live up to its name.
It's not for me.
Even if you don't say doing it
for our party and our ideology,
you should at least mention doing it
for the welfare of everyone
in our section.
You just said yourself
that you're concerned
about our colleagues' livelihoods.
That's good.
Yes, sir! I'll catch more Communist spies
for our section.
Good.
Weng Lianwang,
I have a mission right now
for you to carry out.
Director Ma, Deputy Chief Wu is here.
Deputy Chief Wu, what brings you here?
Director Ma, what a refined hobby
you have.
Doing this in front of you is really
showing off my poor skills to an expert.
It's just a way to kill time.
This is really something.
Luo Zhenyu.
You're truly an expert.
Sir,
when will you also write
a piece of calligraphy for me?
Director Duan got
a piece of your calligraphy
and keeps showing it off to me.
No problem.
Just tell me what content you want,
and I'll write it for you.
Please, have a seat.
You're a great scholar
and also a master calligrapher.
Anything you write would be wonderful.
Please.
Have some tea.
Recently,
I managed to get
some precious calligraphy supplies
from Guangzhou.
The rice paper is from Jingxian.
And among them, there was
a Wushi Qiyan ink stick.
That ink stick
is truly rare.
I've already sent someone
to deliver it to Wu's Mansion.
Thank you, Director Ma.
Rice paper is precious,
but soldiers are even more valuable.
Director Ma, you must have guessed
that I came here today
to request your help to bring
Huang Jie's corps back.
Sir, I wouldn't dare call it a request.
The Chief has already informed me.
I was planning
to go to your office later
to report to you personally.
Then I'll get straight to the point.
There are 30,000 men in Huang Jie's corps.
We need at least five transport ships.
You're really putting me
in a difficult position.
Even if you pushed me to the limit,
I still couldn't produce
five transport ships.
That's not right.
I know
that the military aid from the U.S. alone
included ten transport ships.
My request isn't unreasonable.
Sir,
I'm just in charge of logistics.
There are too many transport requests now.
I really can't spare any
to allocate to you.
Then what should we do?
We just let
the 30,000 soldiers of Huang Jie's corps
wait in that internment camp in Vietnam?
Every few days, more than ten bodies
are carried out.
This involves
diplomatic affairs
and the image
of the Nationalist Government.
Director Ma,
can you bear the consequences?
Sir,
how about this?
I'll allocate three ships to you first.
Would that work?
Director Ma, since this is so difficult
for you,
then just take back the rice paper
and other things you sent to my residence.
If I can't bring back
General Huang's troops,
I won't have many chances
to use such fine paper and ink anymore.
Sir,
please don't leave.
Let me be honest.
I just can't make bricks without straw.
Commander-in-Chief Xue Yue
borrowed the ships
to march forward into Hainan Island
and hasn't returned them yet.
Chief Gu sent a fleet to Guangxi
to pick up Bai Chongxi's troops.
And Chief Zhou
dispatched many transport ships
to Zhoushan.
I don't even have enough ships
to send supplies to Kinmen.
I hope you can understand.
Please, have a seat.
General Hu Lian
has already urged me twice.
Sending supplies to Zhoushan
isn't that urgent, is it?
How about sending those ships
to Vietnam first?
You have no idea.
Of all the ships, those bound for Zhoushan
are the most needed and most urgent.
Everything must be transported
within two weeks.
Director Ma.
What can be more urgent
than my matter?
What can be more important
than the lives of 30,000 soldiers?
Sir,
you have a point.
But Chief Zhou also said
that this shipment of military supplies
is a top priority.