♪Wind♪
♪Incidentally blows away
fascinating whispers of love♪
♪Whispers of love♪
♪Sound the best
with loyalty to the only valentine♪
♪The prosperous life♪
♪Is when we are together all year round♪
♪For the rest of my life♪
♪All I want is a perfect love with you♪
♪I'll remain elegant for you all my life♪
♪Giving you my love little by little♪
♪I care for you with every piece of my heart♪
♪And I miss you every day and night♪
♪I'll be loyal to you
in the best years of my life♪
♪Melting love with gentle smiles♪
♪I won't be afraid of anything♪
♪And I won't change my heart for you♪
=Jade's Fateful Love=
=Episode 21=
Your Grace, taste the almond cake.
I made it personally.
Your Grace, if you want to talk,
just get to the point.
Actually,
I shouldn't have come.
But anyway,
I met you several times
and got you out of the abandoned palace.
I think I should come.
The abandoned palace?
You opened the door for me?
The North Prince asked me
to secretly protect you.
Without a high position,
that was all I could do for you.
Thank you for helping me out.
You flatter me, Your Grace.
I was just entrusted.
Your Grace, what are you
going to tell me?
These days,
you haven't seen the North Prince, right?
He's been very busy lately.
That is true.
But actually,
he's in some unspoken trouble.
What do you mean?
His Highness got
the letter of marriage from Dongyu.
First, he wanted to get you out.
Second, he wanted to show your father
his determination to marry you.
Third, he wanted peace in the world.
Your Grace, are you aware?
I am, of course.
He did a lot of things for me.
I will defend him.
That's not enough?
No.
You should leave him.
I know I shouldn't have said this.
Forgive me, Your Grace.
you must have the right reason
for saying this.
Please be clear.
The North Prince went to Dongyu twice,
risking his own life.
Who's actually behind this?
I'm sure you know.
In the marriage case,
the Prime Minister and his men were weakened.
But the political forces are struggling.
The Prime Minister is ambitious.
How will he just give up?
I'm afraid he'll take revenge hard.
Then how will His Majesty and His Highness
cope with that?
What's your opinion?
The political forces are divided.
His Majesty and the Prime Minister
nearly have the same power.
Now, the frontier commanders play a key role.
Among them,
the Lord of the South matters most.
The Lord of the South?
Princess Luoyi's brother?
Exactly.
His Majesty needs his help.
And he requested
to marry Princess Luoyi to the South Prince.
Our assassination in Dongyu failed.
Turns out Su Nian betrayed us.
Do you know
where she is now?
I don't know.
Since Su Nian took the mission,
she's been away
from the House of Romance.
Your mission is to supervise Su Nian.
But now you tell me
you don't know where she is!
I was negligent.
I thought without the antidote,
Su Nian would die of poison soon.
So, I stopped spying on her.
Bring her back,
dead or alive.
Yes.
I'm it.
(To Yueling)
(Yueling,)
(Su Nian is missing.)
(I'm so worried.)
(I'm going to find her. I'll be back soon.)
(Don't worry.)
Actually, I'm jealous of you.
For what?
Someone will steal my husband.
If a man cares so much for me
and does everything for me,
I'll die without regret.
Not at all, Your Grace.
In this case,
if the North Prince disapproves,
what will happen?
Something terrible.
His Majesty can't get back his power.
And his reign will be unstable.
The North Prince
will feel guilty all his life, too.
What storybook can be so attractive?
You didn't even notice me.
What are you doing here?
Are you saying
you don't want me to come?
Yueling.
You haven't been here for days.
Are you stuck in some trouble?
Trouble?
No.
But recently,
the West Market has been great in revenue.
I'm carefully making future plans.
These things are complicated.
So, I was held up for some time.
Nothing bothers you?
Nothing.
Why do you ask?
Has His Majesty had
our stamped engagement letter to Dongyu?
When will the wedding be held?
Yueling, you're eager to marry me, huh?
You remind me.
I should rush His Majesty.
I don't mean that.
Fine. You don't.
Does anything amuse you lately?
No, nothing.
The other day, I visited the West Market.
Xingyi has left,
looking for Su Nian.
Don't worry. I'll send my men to find him
and secretly protect him.
He'll be safe.
Yueling, is something bothering you?
No.
I'm done talking about me.
Let's talk about you.
In recent days,
has anything happened?
Just some political things.
You may get bored.
I want to listen.
What do you want to hear, then?
I'll tell you all that I know.
Let me think about it.
I hear the Lord of the South is powerful.
Is he very important in current politics?
He has commanded troops in the South for years.
His subordinates
were cultivated by his seniors.
When he was guarding the frontier,
in either an invasion case
or a provoking fight, he never failed.
He's indeed one of the best frontier generals.
He's also a great power we need
to fight the Prime Minister.
Which side is he on now?
He hasn't decided yet.
If his sister Princess Luoyi
marries someone on His Majesty's side,
this problem
will be readily solved, right?
Yueling,
did anyone tell you something?
Shiyu,
if you're stuck in a dilemma,
I want to share the burden with you.
If you don't want to tell me about it,
I believe you have your reason.
I just don't want you
to be restrained
by anyone or anything.
Anyone including me.
You can always choose what you want.
I'll support you and understand you.
All right.
Your Grace,
it's getting cold. Go to bed early.
Qianqian.
I haven't seen the full moon for a long time.
The fifteenth day is only a few days away.
By then, we can see the full moon.
Your Grace, I'll go make the bed.
(The moon still waxes or wanes.)
(If we can't end up together,)
(I'll only wish)
(for your safety.)
(Pleasant and Harmonious)
Recently, has Yueling
met someone?
Her Highness has been staying indoors.
The other day, she visited the West Market.
Anything suspicious?
On the West Market, Her Highness
ran into Lady Chen.
They talked for a while in her carriage.
Chen Susu?
(Nanfeng House)
We haven't met for days.
Mr. Perfect, your painting...
Fabulous.
Fabulous, indeed.
You flatter me, Your Grace.
It's modest of you, Mr. Perfect.
Your Grace, is something bothering you?
Tell me about it.
Maybe I can offer some help.
I do have one thing
to ask you.
Go ahead, please.
A good friend of mine
is engaged with the man she loves.
But because of family restrains,
that man
can't marry her.
Though my friend doesn't want to give up,
she won't make her man
get stuck in a dilemma.
What can she do
to make her beloved man give up
and leave her without worry?
You...
Your friend...
If she's worried about the engagement,
how about fighting fire with fire?
She can find another man
and get married before him
to make him give up.
In this case,
he won't hesitate for you.
Oh, no.
He won't...
He won't hesitate
for your friend.
Find another man?
It must be done very soon.
Better in a day or two.
What should I do?
In a day or two?
Such a hurry?
If you want a suitable man
in such a short time,
you'll have to inform everyone in town
and choose one from them.
Inform everyone?
We can't do that, can we?
Let's do this.
Since the decree isn't issued,
I'm not the North Princess Consort.
I'll inform everybody in town
and have all the regular-age men here
for me to review.
I'll recruit a husband in public.
(Benign and Benevolent)
Your Grace,
are you hesitating
for tomorrow's recruitment?
Your Grace, you always pretend
you don't care about anything.
Actually, you can't forget the North Prince.
In your heart,
you don't really want to recruit a husband,
do you?
Does that
even matter?
If I don't do something
to make people know he and I won't be together,
I guess he'll be further embarrassed.
Your Grace,
I understand.
But if someone really wins tomorrow,
what will we do?
You can't get a real husband, can you?
No one but him
can be my husband.
The North Prince is here.
Shiyu, you're just in time.
Here's a defective chess game
I don't know how to finish.
I don't think
I can play chess with you, Shan.
So, you're here
to tell me something, huh?
I'm here to explain about Luoyi and me.
You and Luoyi make a perfect couple.
If she can marry you,
I'll be relieved.
Luoyi and I have been cousins.
We were and we will be.
So, Shan, don't try so hard
to let Princess Yueling know about it.
Is this
what you're going to say?
I won't marry Luoyi.
But if I can keep you in the Capital City,
will I still get your support?
If you can do that,
I'll certainly support you.
Your Highness!
Good news, Your Highness. Good news.
Xu.
Look at my bottom.
What, Your Highness?
Rock solid, isn't it?
Rock solid, indeed.
What's the panic for?
Word came from Princess Yueling
of husband recruitment.
Recruit a husband?
Who will she get? Zhou Shiyu?
No.
Your Highness,
we don't know why,
but Princess Yueling suddenly claimed
she wouldn't marry him.
She's recruiting a husband.
Many young talents have gone there.
So, she just thought it all through.
Recruit a young talent?
Isn't it just a hint for me?
That's right.
Your Highness, you're marvelous.
In this recruitment,
you will be the winner.
Besides, the tests are designed
by Mr. Qin.
Your victory is a sure thing.
Siyuan?
Then I'm bound to win.
Get me dressed.
With the best appearance,
I will marry Princess Yueling
and piss Zhou Shiyu off!
Piss him off!
- Let's go.
- Let's go, Your Highness.
I'm exhausted.
Ping'er, look.
How do I look in this dress,
compared to the Princess of Dongyu?
You're born elegant.
You look a hundred times better than her.
You're honey-tongued. You'll be rewarded.
Thank you, Your Grace. Oh, no.
Thank you, the North Princess Consort.
I'll take this one. And I'll pick some more.
All right.
So many dresses.
- What about this one?
- It's good, too.
When I reach the Princess's,
I'll do the best I can.
By then, don't blame me for winning.
You've never seen the Princess of Dongyu.
Isn't it too soon to tell?
If she's extremely hideous,
you'll have no time to regret it.
Ping'er,
what are they saying about the Princess?
Go ask around.
Yes.
The Princess of Dongyu?
Your Grace, I've got the information.
Are you saying
the Princess of Dongyu is recruiting a husband?
Yes, Your Grace.
When she knows you'll marry the North Prince,
she's getting cold feet, I think.
Your Grace.
Shall we go have a look?
All right.
If she gets a good husband,
as the North Princess Consort,
I should congratulate her.
Let's go.
We've been waiting for a while.
Why has nobody come?
Qianqian,
did you get this around?
Yes.
Other servants and I
spread it this early this morning.
This is weird.
In this case,
why has nobody come?
Your Grace, let's just wait.
They don't come because they have poor taste.
But here I am.
Your Grace, he...
Gentlemen.
Gentlemen,
Her Grace has picked a husband.
Thank you for coming.
Here's some lucky money for you.
Take it and leave.
There you go.
So soon?
The recruitment is indeed competitive.
Her Grace looks fabulous.
It has to be fiercely competitive.
Here.
What a pity!
I had wanted to see Her Grace.
Take this.
Umm...
Sorry, sorry.
Sorry about that.
You're here for the recruitment?
Of course.
We... We want a young talent.
But Your Highness, you...
Talent?
That's just me, isn't it?
(Talent)
You're here alone.
Who can you compete with?
I think you fear I'd win, huh?
Let's get started, then.
There you go, Mr. Perfect.
In this case,
Your Highness will be
the first candidate.
Come with me.
Wait for me.
(Arena)
Your Highness,
there are three parts of the recruitment,
the literary test, the martial test,
and the final test by Her Grace.
I have a talent of literary and martial arts.
Mr. Siyuan, test me now.
The mountain remains towering,
but snow covers it.
The water remains still,
but the wind ruffles it.
Nice!
Great.
He answered so smoothly?
Since when was His Highness so knowledgeable?
Mr. Perfect,
is that a good answer?
Mountain to water,
towering to still, snow to water,
and cover to ruffle.
Perfect match.
More than that.
It has an artistic conception, too.
Your Grace, what is she doing here?
This recruitment
isn't something shameful.
Why can't I be here?
Gao Luoyi,
it's the first time
I think you have good taste.
I also start to think
you're civilized.
Come on.
Your Highness.
Your Highness, you're finally out.
The anxiety is nearly killing me.
What happened?
Her Highness is recruiting a husband at home.
What did you say?
Recruiting a husband?
Your Highness, you passed
the literary test.
Prepare for the following martial test.
Yang Xu.
Come on, Your Highness.
Come on.
Your Highness,
you'd better give up.
If he hurts you by accident,
I won't be responsible.
He doesn't look strong.
I'd fear I would hurt him.
Yang Xu, do something.
Your Highness,
pick a weapon you want.
Come on.
Bring it on.
No offense.
You have some strength.
Your Highness.
Make a move, Your Highness.
Go ahead, Your Highness.
I just let him get me.
- Beat him, Your Highness.
- Again.
Your Highness, give it up.
Don't try to be strong or get hurt.
Zhixuan, try harder.
Come on.
I can continue!
How dare you punch me!
My eyes...
- Come on!
- My eyes.
Punch me, huh?
Oh, my eyes!
How dare you!
I said you were no match for me, huh?
The South Prince won!
His Highness won.
Brilliant, Your Highness.
In this case,
I'll let you win.
He used a dirty trick. How could he win?
(Talent)
Why are you here?
You should be in the palace.
I didn't dare to linger in the palace.
If I came later,
my wife would be stolen.
She's recruiting a husband.
Shiyu, don't see her as your wife.
What dirty trick did I use?
You must be jealous of me.
Not really.
(Talent)
You're awesome, Zhixuan.
But without a rival,
you're kind of lonely.
Do you dare to compete with me?
Shiyu.
All right.
Let's compete, then.
No way.
This is a public recruitment.
Everybody should be equal.
Will you only stop me?
Your Highness, come this way.
Her Grace set the last test by herself.
Here it goes.
I love the most beautiful place in the world.
What is this place?
Beishuo is beautiful everywhere.
But I guess
your favorite place
is the grassland of Dongyu.
It's the pond under a cliff.
(Pond)
The North Prince is correct.
Shiyu.
He gave the right answer.
But that's merely one question.
He won't win unless he passes three questions.
Your Grace, go on, please.
What's the most expensive pastry in the world?
I know.
The Snowflake Pastry in the palace.
It's the tea cake.
Am I wrong again?
(Tea Cake)
Your Grace,
you have the last question.
Zhixuan, you...
There's something I treasure most
and it sticks even when I'm dying.
What is it?
In a life-threatening situation,
what can be more important than money?
The jade you wear.
(Jade)
Since the North Prince
has all the correct answers,
the winner will be...
Wait a minute.
I won two rounds while he won only one.
How does it count? It doesn't count.
Yeah. I'm the witness.
The South Prince won.
The North Prince won, actually.
He's exactly the man
who knows Her Grace perfectly.
Siyuan.
Siyuan, say something.
Well...
Her Grace is the one to choose.
You answered all the questions correctly.
It's indeed...
Here is the Royal Decree.
Oh, you're all here.
I'm just in time.
North Prince and Princess Yueling, listen.
Here is the decree of His Majesty.
"I hear Ashina Yueling, the Princess of Dongyu,
is virtuous, gentle, kind,
(Royal Decree)
and gorgeous.
She makes a perfect couple
with the North Prince.
I'd like to make peace
with the Emperor of Dongyu for generations.
So, I hereby get them engaged.
Their wedding will be done
by the Ministry of Rites
and the Bureau of Astronomy.
On the fifteenth day of next month."
Respect this.
With pleasure, Your Majesty.
You may rise, Your Highness.
Congratulations, Your Highnesses.
Everybody,
I'll take my leave.
♪Ceaseless, love lingers and lingers♪
♪You and I both know it♪
♪In this world, we stay side by side♪
♪Watching the stars rise and fall♪
♪My eyes are red from missing you♪
♪Tonight, I hope the moonlight will♪
♪Kiss your eyebrows♪
Why don't you just stay
and be my wife?
♪I'll always be in love with you♪
♪Promising it'll last forever♪
♪As the breeze blows, the flower fades♪
♪Leaving a wish to be fulfilled♪
♪To have joy for the rest of its life♪
How did this happen?
I should be the North Princess Consort!
Your Grace, Your Grace.
♪As the breeze blows, the flower fades♪
♪When I look back, you whisper♪
♪Then I wake up from the dream♪
♪Like how we met for the first time♪
♪Clouds slowly float across the sky♪
♪Telling what is awfully bothering♪
♪Ceaseless, love lingers and lingers♪
♪You and I both know it♪
♪In this world, we stay side by side♪
♪Watching the stars rise and fall♪
♪My eyes are red from missing you♪
♪Tonight, I hope the moonlight will♪
♪Kiss your eyebrows♪
♪I'll always be in love with you♪
♪Promising it'll last forever♪
♪As the breeze blows, the flower fades♪
♪Leaving a wish to be fulfilled♪
♪To have joy for the rest of its life♪
♪I'll stay with you for thousands of years♪
♪Until we grow old together♪
♪As the breeze blows, the flower fades♪
♪When I look back, you whisper♪
♪Then I wake up from the dream♪
♪Like how we met for the first time♪