[The Snow Moon]
[Episode 9]
Lord Qingchuan.
Who is he?
We call him Gui.
They are numerous.
Neither human
nor demon.
They hold deep resentment in their hearts
and inflict harm upon both races.
Then why did he kill me?
Perhaps to protect the Fox Demon.
What happened to your head?
I accidentally got cut by a knife.
Don't move.
Why are you so careless?
Thank you.
Did you make a move on the Fox Demon?
No, I didn't.
I'm no match for him at all.
How could I act recklessly?
Why did you lie to me?
Don't take any more risks like that.
Just find the key to the Earth Scroll.
Then, I'll go back first.
Otherwise,
that bad fox will suspect me again.
Where have you been?
Lord Fox Demon.
I went to rinse my mouth.
It took so long.
Did you secretly meet
with someone outside?
How could I?
Secret meetings take a long time.
It takes me a long time to rinse my mouth.
I deeply reflected on my own actions
while rinsing my mouth just now.
I think you've misunderstood me.
I'm just a lowly nobody.
How could I dare to kill you?
Besides,
I don't have the power to do that, do I?
Mainly, I wanted to test your strength.
But I found
that you're really unpredictable.
I admire you even more.
Your Lordship, don't kill me!
What have you done to me?
Nothing.
Just infused some bugs on you.
If they don't smell my scent,
they'll have a fit
and bite you in the gut.
If you don't behave and run around,
even deities can't save you.
You!
Me?
Lord Fox Demon.
How could you show me such care
without my consent?
Are you the Lord Fox Demon I admired?
It depends on your behavior.
Your Lordship.
Can you lend me your cloak for a moment?
I want to sleep while smelling your scent.
Otherwise, I can't fall asleep.
(Fine.)
You d*mn fox.
Gentle bugs.
This is the attire of Lord Fox Demon.
It's full of a strong fox scent.
Now you can enjoy smelling it.
But please, don't bite me anymore,
and don't bite my organs either.
Where do you think the Earth Scroll is?
Su Xiaohuan has been
in the Emperor's bedchamber for many days.
How come she's still alive?
I guess,
she must have been bedded by the Emperor.
That's right.
I believe Su Xiaohuan is a vixen.
She knows how to seduce the Emperor.
I think so, too.
What are you gossiping about?
There is nothing between me
and the Lord Fox Demon.
You're alone in a room together,
like a spark in dry firewood.
If nothing happened,
unless you're a barren woman.
Nonsense!
You call me a barren woman?
Why don't you say he's impotent?
No need to kneel.
Alright. I know you're wrong.
You may rise.
You said I'm impotent?
Lord Fox Demon.
My stomach hurts.
Help me!
Lord Fox Demon.
Put me down!
What are you doing?
Lord Fox Demon, what are you doing?
Nothing.
I just want to prove myself
to avoid being gossiped about.
No!
You don't need to prove yourself.
You're so strong and powerful.
How can you be impotent?
I was talking nonsense.
Everyone should take responsibility
for their words and actions.
You mustn't lower your taste
because of me, Your Lordship.
Besides, how can a maid become a royal?
Yes, you should be matched with a royal.
I, a humble maid like a chicken,
am not good enough for you.
Foxes have a natural affinity
for chickens.
I love little girls like you.
Hold on!
Lord Fox Demon is so mighty!
Lord Fox Demon is so powerful!
Lord Fox Demon is amazing!
Lord Fox Demon is formidable!
Lord Fox Demon is great!
Lord Fox Demon is really amazing!
Lord Fox Demon is fantastic!
Get out!
Okay.
Lord Fox Demon is so powerful!
What's going on?
Have you become possessed
by the Fox Demon?
Why are you wearing the clothes and cut
of the Fox Demon?
If it weren't for the d*mn bugs.
Who would want to wear his clothes?
Oh, I mean,
I'm afraid of the cold lately.
That's why I borrowed his clothes.
Oh, no.
I'm already warm enough in this.
Thank you.
Oh, by the way.
I've searched his bedchamber thoroughly.
but I didn't find the secret scroll.
Could it be the Fox Demon has...
It can't be wrong.
You must have missed something.
We're here
to prepare for the operation
on the night of tomorrow's lunar eclipse.
Operation?
What operation?
On the night of the lunar eclipse,
the Fox Demon is at his weakest,
and it's our best chance to kill him.
Every lunar eclipse, he hides away.
If we can find his hiding place,
we'll have a chance to kill him.
I understand.
Xiaohuan.
Don't do anything rash.
Send me a signal immediately
once you find his hideout.
Alright.
Lord Fox Demon.
Lord Fox Demon?
Your Lordship?
He's so vicious usually.
He knew he'd lose his power
during the lunar eclipse,
so he's hiding so early.
What a coward!
Where is he hiding?
(The lunar eclipse has begun.)
(Where is the bad Fox Demon hiding?)
♪A leaf boat in the misty haze,
your silhouette♪
♪Whose past does the distant fog hide?♪
♪Time flows on, after so many years,
where to find that cliff of solitude?♪
♪Affairs of rising and falling,
entering whose dreams?♪
♪That wilderness in the North,
so picturesque♪
♪I stand alone,
admiring the rain of falling petals♪
♪Like flowers are not of yesterday.
The sky filled with your image♪
♪You drift through my dreams♪
♪I've walked several ten million li♪
♪Chasing your footsteps♪
♪I've passed several ten million li♪
♪Searching for your memories♪
♪I've walked several ten million li♪
♪Passing darkness and cliffs steep♪
♪Looking back for a glimpse of scenery♪
♪That wilderness in the North,
so picturesque♪
♪I stand alone,
admiring the rain of falling petals♪
♪Like flowers are not of yesterday.
The sky filled with your image♪
♪You drift through my dreams♪
♪I've walked several ten million li♪
♪Chasing your footsteps♪
♪I've passed several ten million li♪
♪Searching for your memories♪
♪I've walked several ten million li♪
♪Passing darkness and cliffs steep♪
♪Looking back for a glimpse of scenery♪
[Exclusive information
network broadcasting rights]
[belong to YOUKU.]