♫  Misty dawn and tender dusk, the whole world seems gentle  ♫
♫  A young boy in uniform gallops under the blinking stars  ♫
♫  His eyes are so loving, determined, and happy  ♫
♫  Looking back, what transient beauty  ♫
♫  Winter, the season when snow falls  ♫
♫  But you have spring in your arms  ♫
♫  The fragrance of sweet flowers fills the world  ♫
♫  During the sunny summer days  ♫
♫  Our feelings grow stronger  ♫
♫  I'm so in love with you in autumn  ♫
♫  Every falling leaf speaks of my love  ♫
♫  Dancing and swirling in the air  ♫
[Fall in Love]
[Episode 32]
Supervisor Xu, since you don't consider this to be something a noble should do,
you don't have to attend this interrogation.
Executive Director Fay and I can go in together.
Officer Zuo, you don't trust me?
This isn't something you should do.
Executive Director, please.
- Hello, Sir.
- Yes, yes.
Brother Zuo, sit down.
Executive Director Fay.
Commander Tan, we've brought back Miss Mu already.
The evidence is solid. Is there anything else you want to say?
Where is Supervisor Xu?
Supervisor Xu is not feeling well, so I asked him to go back and rest.
But I just saw him when you got out of the car,
and there was nothing wrong with him.
Commander Tan, you were really waiting for us to come back.
Why? You're feeling guilty?
Guilty?
Anyway, I'm innocent. You didn't find the arms and ammunition.
So, you'll have to let me go.
We didn't find the arms and ammunition?
If we didn't, why would we bring Miss Mu back?
Miss Mu told us everything in detail.
Commander Tan, your only way out is to tell the truth.
No wonder something felt wrong.
That woman wasn't Wanqing.
Brother Zuo, what truth do you want me to tell you?
I know nothing about any arms or ammunition.
I was clearly framed. What do you want me to say?
Would you be satisfied if I just framed myself?
Then, why were you nervous?
How could I not be nervous?
As you all know, Mu Wanqing and I had a falling-out not too long ago.
Who knows if she'll shift the blame onto me?
If she says anything to you, don't believe it.
She can't wait to see me fall.
You're afraid of that?
I won't blame you if you laugh at me.
If you had to deal with such an unreasonable woman,
you'd be afraid too.
Now, I'm rather curious. What exactly did she say?
About that...
we can't tell you.
How about this?
You ask Mu Wanqing to come here,
and I'll confront her face-to-face. Okay?
You're still doubting me? Right?
Fine, you can call her over right now.
I'll prove everything one by one. Okay?
Commander Tan, we didn't find any arms and ammunition at the pier.
As for Miss Mu's testimony, it's only a reference.
We won't believe it.
How about I submit the closing report to Beijing first thing tomorrow morning.
We'll wait for Governor Pei's approval.
And then, you'll be cleared of suspicion.
Fine, Brother Zuo, I'll believe in you.
But there is one thing.
If that Mu Wanqing dares to accuse me again,
lock her up for a few more days.
Wait, no. Just keep her locked up so she won't try to harm me.
What is she?
Officer Zuo, you should now be able to rest assured.
I... I told you.
Those who are clear, are clear.
There's no harm in being cautious though.
Gentlemen, how did it go?
Did you reach a conclusion?
Once Commander Tan heard Miss Mu testified against him,
he became anxious right away.
He even asked us to lock up Miss Mu for a few days
in order to protect himself.
We always say a woman's heart is like a needle at bottom of the ocean.
(T/N: Hard to find; to understand)
I never thought that when a man is cruel, it's no less impressive.
[Yamato Trading Corporation]
Move!
Get in!
What's going on?
Hurry up!
Adjutant Xu,
I've made an inquiry. Officer Zuo submitted his closing report this morning.
He concluded that Tan Xuanlin isn't guilty.
They're waiting for approval from Beijing to release him.
How about Junichi Yamashita?
I heard that they searched Mr. Yamashita's place last night.
Many Japanese people were arrested too.
Even Secretary Hasegawa was taken away.
This Junichi Yamashita,
his plan was a pain in his own foot.
Such solid evidence, but Tan totally got away with it.
We nearly made it.
We still have a chance
before the approval from Beijing arrives.
The investigation team found the arms and ammunition already.
Tan Xuanlin will be convicted very soon.
Even if you continue keeping your mouth shut, it will be futile.
Since he's getting convicted either way,
then is what I say still important?
I'm afraid it's you whose efforts are going to be futile.
Looks like you won't give up until you see your coffin.
Xu Bojun must really be at an impasse,
sending you pieces of trash here.
You can't even handle a woman like me, and you want to go after my young uncle?
Since it's all...
a stupid daydream.
I know Miss Gu has a strong body.
She's not afraid of getting beat up.
So, let's...
try something more exciting.
Rickshaw!
Go to the Chinese General Chamber of Commerce.
Stop! Stop.
This isn't the direction to the Chamber of Commerce.
Mr. Yamashita?
Mu Wanqing set us up.
All my men were arrested.
I need your cooperation
to make Mu Wanqing pay the price.
Let go of me! Let me go!
Let go of me! What are you going to do?
Xu Yuan, what are you up to this time?
Don't be scared.
The first morphine injection is always like this.
It'll be fine once you get used to it.
Oh right.
After the injection, you'll feel like you're floating in Heaven.
- Let's go.
- Morphine?
You! You!
Yes. It's a bit more addictive compared to opium.
But you can relax.
The dose I'll give you today is a little bit lower
compared to a lethal dose.
Don't you dare!
- Hold her.
- Stay away!
You bastard!
How could you do such a thing
to a cornered beast, you bastard!
You'd better start worrying about yourself.
The investigation team will be here soon.
As long as you say you saw Tan Xuanlin collude with the Revolutionary Army,
I'll give you the cure right away.
You! In your dreams!
Still playing tough?
Half an hour from now,
I'll let you feel something worse than death.
Eldest Miss.
Good news!
Mr. Xu just called. He said that the approval from Beijing has arrived.
Commander Tan is fine!
Have they arrested those Japanese men?
Last night, Officer Zuo's men took out that Japanese stronghold.
They arrested many people
including Junichi Yamashita's Secretary, Hasegawa.
Unfortunately, they didn't catch Junichi Yamashita.
He probably ran away.
Junichi Yamashita escaped. How about Mu Wanting?
I've asked the Chamber of Commerce to keep an eye on the situation.
If they see Mu Wanting, they'll report it immediately.
Coming!
Governor Pei's approval has arrived.
You're clear of suspicion now.
You can now go out.
This time, it's all thanks to you.
You're welcome.
Anyway, I wasn't helping you.
Where is Zuo?
Is he afraid to see me?
- About Zuo...
- Report!
Report.
Officer Zuo's orders. A new witness has been found
and needs to be questioned.
Officer Zuo has already rushed over.
Commander Tan, please stay here for now.
A new witness?
- Who?
- It's Miss Gu Yueshuang.
Where is she?
How many trips have you made today?
Have you seen her?
Yes, I remember. I saw her enter the Zhabei Hotel.
- Let's go!
- What's going on?
Hurry! We have no time left.
How about it?
Please… Please… I'm begging you. I'm begging you.
The investigation team will arrive soon.
As long as you admit that Tan Xuanlin colluded with the Revolutionary Party,
I'll give you the cure.
Okay, okay, okay. Okay.
I'll promise you anything. I'll agree to anything.
I'm begging you.
To see the investigation team,
I need to fix up my hair and makeup.
If you had said it earlier,
you wouldn't have suffered so much.
Shuang'er.
What happened?
What happened to you?
You came.
You're here.
I...
Now, I'll...
give you my answer.
I...
I... I...
I... I promise you.
♫  Tears turn into heavy rain  ♫
♫  We went back to when we first met  ♫
♫  I immediately saw your charming face  ♫
Shuang'er!
♫  To the endless sky and ocean  ♫
Wake up, Shuang'er!
Open your eyes and look at me. I'm begging you,
open your eyes and look at me again!
♫ fall down with us ♫
♫  If I forget your profile  ♫
♫  How would I put back together  ♫
♫  The memories that revived me  ♫
♫  Let’s embrace either during the sunrise of sunset  ♫
Shuang'er!
Shuang'er.
♫  I have exhausted myself in this life  ♫
Shuang'er! Shuang'er!
Who did this?
I want to know who did it, too!
Why... Why didn't you protect her?
Why?
Who did it? Who did it?
Who did it?
This Miss...
I don't know why, but she just fell from our guest room upstairs.
Who brought her here? Speak!
A couple of officers.
What did they look like?
What was their dialect?
An officer and two soldiers.
They sounded like they're from Yue City.
♫  If I forget your profile  ♫
♫  How would I put back together  ♫
♫  The memories that revived me  ♫
♫  Let’s embrace either during the sunrise of sunset  ♫
It was your father who did it.
Why did he do this to her?
What did she do to you?
♫  My whole life  ♫
I've been looking for her all night.
I was about to find her. I was just one step away.
Just one step!
♫  If I forget your profile  ♫
♫  How would I put back together  ♫
♫  The memories that revived me  ♫
♫  Let’s embrace either during the sunrise of sunset  ♫
♫  I have exhausted myself in this life  ♫
♫  My whole life has become lonely  ♫
♫  Even if my vision is blurred and I can’t clearly see  ♫
♫  I’ll still sing with you on horseback  ♫
It's okay now.
We'll go home.
Your young uncle will take you home.
You don't have to be afraid anymore.
Come on. Let's go home.
- How is it going?
- Let us take her.
Scram! All of you, scram!
[Zhabei Hotel]
Supervisor Xu, we arrested twelve criminals in total,
and only Junichi Yamashita absconded.
We need to send these criminals to the Consulate to repatriate them.
Please confirm.
The archivist said Mu Wanting only looked up one file.
In the time they called us, Mu Wanting had already left.
She stayed for less than five minutes.
In such a short time, she must have came prepared.
Which file did Mu Wanting just look at?
- Bring it to me immediately.
- Yes.
[Municipal Public Lighting]
[Electric Rate Regulating Circuit Unit]
[10]
- Are there any more copies?
- Yes.
- Get them for me.
[Shanghai Street Gas Lamp Distribution and Pipeline, Hankou Power Plant Detail]
[Hankou]
Notify the police immediately.
Someone wants to sabotage the power plants on Hankou Road.
Yes.
[The Sincere Co. Ltd]
Mister, please drive faster.
Yes.
- Commander Tan.
- Where's Wanqing?
Miss Mu went to the power plants on Hankou Road.
- Faster.
- Okay.
Mr. Yamashita, why are you looking for the pipelines?
Don't you want Tan Xuanlin and Mu Wanqing dead?
I'll help you fulfill that wish now.
[Hankou Power Plants]
Look.
The mark on the drawing is right here.
What's going on?
Why is there a power outage?
Hold this for me. I'll go check the distribution board.
Since you're here to die, you can't blame me for this!
I didn't expect you to get away with it.
Admit your defeat.
You're still helping this woman?
Back then, her father killed your father.
If you're a real man, you should kill her right now!
The one I should kill is you.
Did you think that by bribing Sergey, everything would be perfect?
Is it him?
Who is he?
He says he doesn't know him.
Are you lying to me?
I found Sergey and the former associates of the Foreign Gun Brigade.
They told me they once encountered a gang of Japanese bandits
who used explosive bullets in Jiangpu.
And their leader
was a Japanese veteran who fought against Sergey on the battlefield.
That veteran was you, Junichi Yamashita.
I never thought that you were acting all along.
That's right. I decided to follow along until the moment was right.
I intended to keep you alive for a few more days.
But you came to me yourself.
Old scores or new, let's settle them all today.
Now that you know all about it,
I want to see what you've got
to take my life.
You better not use your gun.
If you use a gun, none of us can live.
I don't need a gun to kill you.
Mu Wanting!
Wanting, give me that.
Don't you know that the Japanese guy is using you?
He wants to throw fire into the pipes and ignite all the gas lamps in Shanghai.
Of course I know.
I know that if that happens, the Mu family will be finished.
You and Tan Xuanlin will be doomed as well.
Are you still that self-centered?
Are you going to bury the entire city of Shanghai because of your personal grudges?
Personal grudges?
If it weren't for you, I wouldn't have lost everything.
If it weren't for you, my mother wouldn't have died.
Just for these personal grudges, I'll let Shanghai be buried! Is that a problem?
- You're insane. Come with me!
- I won't!
Come with me!
Don't move!
- Go!
- Let go!
- Don't move!
- Let go of me!
- Let me go! Let go of me!
- Wanting!
- I won't go with you!
- Let's go!
I want you to know what it's like to lose everything.
Let go of me!
Open the pipe!
Wanqing, let's go! Come on!
Let me down!
Let go of me! Didn't you want to abandon me?
Don't come near me!
I'm sorry. Sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Don't keep me in the dark again.
Never leave me alone anymore.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
This silver pendant, although it isn't worth much,
but it is the most precious thing I have.
My most precious things are both here.
I will definitely be back soon.
Don't remove it.
Keep it for the rest of your life.
All right?
This silver pendant…
I won't remove it.
Let it stay with you forever, all right?
I…
I... I promise you.
- Hurry.
- Here.
- Come on.
- Let's go.
Go!
Shuang'er is dead.
Xu Bojun did it.
It was all my fault.
It was all my fault that I didn't take care of her well.
Did you know?
When I was on my way here,
I was so scared.
I had never been this scared my entire life.
I was afraid...
I was afraid that if I was late for one second...
what if you too...
We had foreseen everything already.
We just never predicted that Xu Bojun would go after Miss Gu.
I thought I hid it well.
How did you see through it?
Actually, when I came home and saw the photo that day,
I already knew you were lying to me.
The Foreign Gun Brigade?
Were they involved in a crossfire in Jiangpu?
Yes.
They encountered a gang of bandits,
but it was more to scare them off.
Bandits?
They didn't encounter soldiers?
The Foreign Gun Brigade was Master's escort.
Why would they shoot soldiers?
I'm sorry.
Earlier,
I said those awful words.
I know you kept it from me because you were worried.
But I'm really glad that it was a lie.
I lied to you.
How did you switch the goods?
After you saw the photo at my house that day,
you suddenly left without saying goodbye.
I assumed Mu Wanting tampered with the photo album.
So recently, I had been keeping an eye on her.
I found out...
that she had contacted Hasegawa, Yamashita's Secretary.
[Yamato Trading Corporation]
So I thought they would be going after me soon.
Just as expected,
they moved shipments of Western medicine into the warehouse.
I was afraid that they were going after you.
But I didn't know what was going on over on your side.
It was only until Mr. Liao called me,
when I found out that things had reached a critical point.
I figured out a way to get rid of Yamashita's spies,
by going to the dock in disguise.
When I got to the dock,
I happened to see the arms and ammunition arrive at the pier.
Hold it steady.
To stall for time,
I switched the numbers of Warehouses Six and Nine.
But I was still worried when the steward came to open the door with the key,
the lie would be exposed.
But we were lucky.
One of the stewards happened to be drunk,
so I made a call and sent the other steward away.
I switched the positions of keys six and nine.
Sir, there is a package for you at the door.
What?
When I just finished switching the keys, Officer Zuo's men were there.
The drunk steward took them to Warehouse Nine.
Open the door to Warehouse Six.
Just like that,
when you were inspecting Warehouse Nine,
I moved the arms and ammunition from Warehouse Six.
Then I returned the key.
And I wrote down the name Junichi Yamashita
and registered the Japanese Chamber of Commerce on the shipping form.
Please fill out the form.
[Yamato Trading Corporation]
[Shanghai Bund Pier]
At last,
I asked Steward Mu to put the form with the shipment of Western medicine
and let their plan backfire.
Wanqing, did you know,
that was very dangerous for you to do?
What if the steward hadn't been drunk?
What would you have done then?
But collaboration is a capital offense.
I had to take the gamble no matter what.
I couldn't just stand by and watch you die.
Weren't you afraid?
For you, what am I afraid of?
♫  Tears turn into heavy rain  ♫
♫  We went back to when we first met  ♫
♫  I immediately saw your charming face  ♫
♫  To the endless sky and ocean  ♫
♫  I made a promise  ♫
♫  Let’s let the mortals fall down with us  ♫
♫  If I forget your profile  ♫
♫  How would I put back together  ♫
♫  The memories that revived me  ♫
♫  Let’s embrace either during the sunrise of sunset  ♫
♫  I have exhausted myself in this life  ♫
♫  My whole life has become lonely  ♫
♫  Even if my vision is blurred and I can’t clearly see  ♫
♫  I’ll still sing with you on horseback  ♫
♫  Tears turn into heavy rain  ♫
♫  We went back to when we first met  ♫
♫  I immediately saw your charming face  ♫
♫  To the endless sky and ocean  ♫
♫  I made a promise  ♫
♫  Let’s let the mortals fall down with us  ♫
♫  If I forget your profile  ♫
♫  How would I put back together  ♫
♫  The memories that revived me  ♫
♫  Let’s embrace either during the sunrise of sunset  ♫
♫  I have exhausted myself in this life  ♫
♫  My whole life has become lonely  ♫
♫  Even if my vision is blurred and I can’t clearly see  ♫
♫  I’ll still sing with you on horseback  ♫