♫  Misty dawn and tender dusk, the whole world seems gentle  ♫
♫  A young boy in uniform gallops under the blinking stars  ♫
♫ His eyes are so loving, determined, and happy ♫
♫ Looking back, what transient beauty ♫
♫  Winter, the season when snow falls  ♫
♫  But you have spring in your arms  ♫
♫  The fragrance of sweet flowers fills the world  ♫
♫  During the sunny summer days  ♫
♫  Our feelings grow stronger  ♫
♫  I'm so in love with you in autumn  ♫
♫  Every falling leaf speaks of my love  ♫
♫ Dancing and swirling in the air ♫
[Fall in Love]
[Episode 9]
Guangyao, your arm is wounded. Go back and rest.
I'll wait for you.
Thanks to Brother Guangyao, your name was cleared.
Don't you want to know why I wasn't afraid of the accusations?
I had checked the assassin's purse long before them.
Your Brother Guangyao was not the only one
who was very thorough.
[Military Government of Guangzhou in the Republic of China, General Check]
You must know one thing.
Whether it's reasoning skills or attentiveness,
I'm as good as he is.
Why are you laughing?
Why must I know?
Why do you have to compete with him in front of me?
I wasn't. I just noticed that you were worried about me.
Why would I worry about you? You're thinking too much.
Shouldn't you be worried about me?
If anything happens to me, you'll have no one to help you.
You're the one who thinks too much.
You rogue!
And you tended to the wounds of the rogue.
I'm leaving.
It's late. Let me drive you back.
You're rather unlucky these days. I don't want you to get kidnapped again.
I've been having bad luck ever since I met you.
Knowing me will make you lucky.
Guangyao,
if Uncle Xu finds out
you wasted a great opportunity to take down Tan Xuanlin,
he will surely punish you.
No matter.
Framing someone and hiding evidence aren't things I do.
No one asked you to frame him.
It's the Southern government that wanted to frame him.
You could have just played along
and taken Tan Xuanlin down, completing your mission.
I don't understand why you didn't do that.
Do you think the Southern government would be so kind
as to help us get rid of him?
They have their motives.
Our fathers are busy mobilizing allied forces of the five provinces.
At that moment, the South sent an assassin to kill Guangyao and frame Tan Xuanlin for it.
Shanghai would have been in turmoil had they succeeded.
And mobilizing an army would naturally be difficult.
Now you understand.
Guangyao.
From the very beginning, you requested to deal with the case yourself.
Were you trying to prevent Uncle Xu from creating trouble?
Since you had seen to this case yourself,
Uncle Xu won't be able to take advantage of the situation.
Hongchen,
some words you should keep to yourself.
There's no need to say them out loud.
It's a corrupt world, but you still want to be righteous.
It's not worth it.
It isn't about whether it is worth it or not,
only if it is right to do.
[Defense Command of Shanghai]
Tan Si,
take this off.
Does it still hurt?
It's gotten better.
Commander, do you believe the assassin was sent by the South?
What do you think?
I don't think so.
Look.
The Tan Army has no conflict with the Revolutionary Army.
Why would they target us?
Besides, if they are looking for enemies,
Provincial Military Governor Xu and Provincial Military Governor Pei both killed members of the Revolutionary Party.
If they're looking for trouble, they should target them first.
Why us?
It's not that simple.
Now that the assassin is dead,
we can only take him as someone sent by the Revolutionary Party.
[Fragrant Orchid Room]
Brother Guangyao, your arm is wounded.
I made chicken soup for you. Have some.
It's fine. It's late. I'm not hungry.
But I took a long time making it for you. It's good. Just try some, please.
Thank you very much, but I'm really not hungry.
You should have it.
[Fragrant Orchid Room]
Wanqing, you're back.
Brother Guangyao, why are you still awake?
Are you feeling better?
I'm fine.
I hope you weren't startled tonight.
Did Commander Tan give you a ride home?
An aide drove me home.
And don't worry. I'm not that easily scared.
With Commander Tan there, of course you wouldn't be afraid.
Brother Guangyao, you don't need to worry.
Hello, Wanting.
I just made a late night snack
and was about to eat it with Brother Guangyao.
Miss Wanting, I told you I wasn't hungry. You should just have it.
I'm going upstairs. Have some good rest, your wound isn't fully healed yet.
[Make every effort for national prosperity]
[Attempted murder in Shanghai committed by Revolutionary Party]
- Report!
- Come in!
Commander, a Mr. Liao wishes to see you.
No. Tell him I'm not here.
Mr. Liao says that ten years ago he was your father's doctor in the army.
Give him some porridge.
Hey! What happened?
Hurry.
The commander and his eldest son were attacked by horse bandits in the valley ahead.
Go help them.
- Xuanlin!
Brother! Brother! Brother!
Xuanlin!
Dad!
Dad…
Commander.
Xuanlin.
Uncle Liao.
Come on. Let me take a good look at you.
You've grown into a man.
I read the news about you earlier.
The second young master of the Tan Family
has become the charismatic King of Shanghai.
Uncle Liao, I haven't seen you in ten years.
These past few years, I've been trying to reach you, but I failed every time.
How's everything going?
I'm doing some small business to make a living.
Come, Uncle Liao. Have a seat, please.
Here.
Thank you.
Uncle Liao, I know.
Back then, because you argued fiercely with Provincial Military Governor Luo
on his revoking the designation of the Tan Army,
he had you expelled.
Back then, they ran into horse bandits who stole our supplies.
And your father died on the battlefield. Not only did Provincial Military Governor Luo not care,
he also blamed your father entirely for losing the battle
and even revoked the designation of the army.
That was so cold-blooded.
That battle...
has shamed us for so many years.
I lead my men to countless victories.
But still, someone will sneer at us,
and tell us that we couldn't even beat horse bandits.
Gossip is a terrible thing.
Your father was a decorated officer.
But after losing his final battle, his great reputation was all but forgotten.
Uncle Liao, actually, there's something I want to ask you.
You saw how brutal the defeat was.
Have you ever had any doubts?
Actually, I've always suspected
that your father didn't run into horse bandits.
Uncle Liao, you also think they weren't horse bandits?
Horse bandits usually just want money.
They don't simply slaughter people.
But back then, they detonated rocks in the mountains to block the path.
Your father, older brother, and every single soldier were killed.
I can't imagine horse bandits having such combat effectiveness.
For the past ten years, I searched everywhere,
but I never heard of those bandits again.
If they were truly horse bandits,
they wouldn't simply abandon their life as outlaws after just one fight.
Unfortunately, there were no survivors.
Every time I dream of my father,
I want to ask him what actually happened back then.
But I eventually wake up.
This is a bullet I removed from your father's body.
I've kept it all these years.
Maybe it can help.
An expanding bullet.
The wounds in all the bodies were large.
Many had half of their chest blown up.
This kind of bullet is prohibited in regular armies around the world.
Mr. Liao, so what you're saying is
if regular armies wouldn't use it, then horse bandits wouldn't ever use it.
Xuanlin, I also want to tell you that
many things are not what they seem.
The injustice that the Tan Family suffered years ago should not be inflicted on others now.
Uncle Liao, what are you implying?
That year, the horse bandits your father confronted might not be horse bandits.
And last night's Revolutionary Party member in the Far East Hotel,
might not have been a Revolutionary Party member.
Uncle Liao, what new business are you in?
Don't make others do what you yourself don't want to do.
What happened in the past and what happened today…
I just hope that Little Commander Tan can find the truth.
Yes.
The case has been closed already. The Revolutionary Party was indeed behind it.
Father, I simply couldn't ignore the truth.
The truth is not important.
You are too soft-hearted to beat that Mr. Tan.
You let such a good chance slip.
Yes… Father.
It's my fault. I deserve to be punished.
Never mind that. You are a righteous man.
If you actually did something against your heart,
I'm afraid you wouldn't be able to live with it.
Thank you for your understanding.
Politics is like playing chess.
Once you lose your opportunity, you can never get it back.
Luckily, you don't win or lose in just one round.
According to the first article of the covenant signed by Tan Xuanlin,
the deadline to dismiss the Tan Army is approaching.
This round, we must win.
Yes.
Uncle Liao, since the assassination attempt last night,
the military governor's mansion has ordered me to hunt down every Revolutionary Army member in the city.
It'll be chaotic out there for quite some time.
Doing business isn't easy. Please take care.
Of course.
But I'm just a businessman. No one will look for trouble with me.
Uncle Liao, don't make it difficult for me.
I understand.
Commander Tan,
until next time.
Mr. Liao, until next time.
Where did you get the bullet? Is it really from Old Commander Tan's body?
Old Fu, do you remember Dr. Liao?
I remember him. The doctor beside Old Commander Tan.
He was very gentle. An educated person.
I met him. He gave it to me.
He kept it for all these years.
He also believes the people who killed my father
might not have been horse bandits.
I knew it!
Commander Tan could never be defeated by a bunch of horse bandits.
However, all of the soldiers who followed Commander Tan died with him.
No one knows what happened in the valley.
Unacceptable!
How dare they rank Tan higher than us!
[Tan Xuanlin ,Top of The Four Junior Marshals]
Calling him the Top of the Four?
Are they out of their mind? Him?
It's just a tabloid. Don't take it so seriously.
Tan Xuanlin is simply a horse bandit.
[Junior Marshal Su Hongchen, Junior Marshal Pei Shaojun, Junior Marshal Xu Guangyao]
How can he be on the same level as us?
But in terms of title, we are indeed lower than him.
He's just a puppet commander. That's nothing to be proud of.
I just hate seeing him looking so proud.
He is reluctant to dismiss the Tan Army.
Maybe he wants to be more than a puppet.
That's not up to him.
Mr. Executive Director, it's been a long time.
- Please have a seat.
- Thank you.
You invited me over several times before,
but I was too busy filming to meet you.
So be my guest today, and accept my apology.
Miss Gu, don't apologize.
Whenever you want to see me, I…
I'm always available.
Thank you, Mr. Executive Director.
Mr. Executive Director! What a coincidence!
Commander Tan.
- Tan Xuanlin?
- Your secretary said you have an appointment tonight.
- Anton Fay?
- It turns out you're with Miss Gu.
What…
Why are they two together?
I don't think we are meeting here by coincidence.
No one can fool you.
I tried to make an appointment several times but was always rejected by your secretary.
That's why I had to ask Miss Gu for this favor. Please don't blame me.
Mr. Joseph is my friend.
You captured him, calling him an assassin.
You, Commander Tan, just took office.
Are you flexing your strength?
Mr. Executive Director, you are very well versed in the Chinese language, you even know this idiom.
But, really, the idiom is not very suitable.
In front of you, I'm actually a follower.
[Supervisor's Office]
Guangyao,
- I was at the cigar bar...
- Wait.
How did you get in?
I'm Junior Marshal Su.
Can't I enter?
I want to tell you something serious.
I was selecting cigars at the bar.
Guess who I saw?
Gu Yueshuang.
Yes, I saw her indeed.
But she was with Tan Xuanlin.
They're a couple.
There's nothing weird about them being together.
But the other person with them is
someone you can never guess.
Big deal. Who was it?
Anton Fay.
You want to build…
You want to build a Chamber of Commerce militia?
Yes.
My men are all veterans who fought in real battles.
They can surely maintain law and order well.
Now the Municipal Council only has patrolmen and military police,
and it's not appropriate for them to intervene
in disputes between Chinese people.
If we can build this militia, things can be much easier.
Well…
If I remember it correctly, Commander Tan,
as soon as you took office,
you signed an agreement with the military governor's mansion.
The first article was to dismiss your army.
And the deadline is approaching.
Mr. Executive Director, you have a great memory.
The thing is, my soldiers' only skill is fighting.
But the military governor's mansion insists that they be sent to factories.
It's a waste of their fighting skills.
Besides, the current situation is very uncertain.
The Revolutionary Army may enter the city at any time.
The military governor's mansion obviously has its hands full.
Mr. Executive Director, don't you want a private militia
that truly belongs to Shanghai?
Depending on the sky and the earth
is no better than depending on ourselves.
I think it is you who wants an armed force
without any interference from others.
Great minds think alike.
Your proposal is quite interesting.
I think...
I... I can consider it.
It's just that…
It's just that I need to see
your sincerity.
Rest assured, Mr. President.
I'll arrange a romantic night for you.
Tan Xuanlin went to find Anton Fay.
What exactly does he want to do?
No matter what he wants,
it can't be a good thing for us.
I remember you and Anton Fay's female secretary are pretty close.
She's just one of my many admirers.
You could say we are close.
Anyway, that foreign girl does like me.
Say it. What do you want me to do?
I want you to ask her what they talked about.
[The Dancing Hall]
Oh dear, we've been married for so many years.
I didn't even know you were so romantic.
I'm so happy with this anniversary.
Anything you want, darling.
Young Uncle, you are so bad.
You had everything arranged but didn't tell me. I was so nervous.
You shouldn't have been. I'm here.
No one can take advantage of you.
That's true.
I only need my Young Uncle in my life. I don't have to marry.
All right, all right. Go back home.
- Drive slowly.
- I'm off then.
- Take care.
- Bye.
Don't drive too fast.
Commander, Miss Shuang'er is just like before.
- She's so close to you.
- Of course, she is close to me.
I saved her life. It would be impossible if we didn't have a bond.
Commander,
do you think Anton Fay will help us for Miss Shuang'er's sake?
Of course, he won't. He's shrewd.
It won't be easy to win him over.
And you are not worried?
The deadline to dismiss our army is approaching.
Food should be eaten one bite at a time.
A journey should be taken one step at a time.
Great!
If I were you, I'd be in no mood to eat or sleep.
You know, that phrase...
that describes when the sky collapses suddenly in front of your face,
yet you remain completely calm.
The sky fell when I was fifteen.
Don't worry. The sky of the Tan Family won't fall.
- Open the door.
- Okay, okay.
[Supervisor's Office]
I got the information, Guangyao.
Tan Xuanlin wants to reform his army
into a militia for the Chamber of Commerce.
What do you think…
All right, I got it.
Junior Marshal?
Tan Xuanlin is scheming to persuade Anton Fay,
so he can reform his army
into a militia for the Chamber of Commerce.
He's just a nominal commander of Shanghai.
Anton Fay won't risk offending the military governor's mansion to help him, right?
It's hard to say.
From Anton Fay's perspective,
the current situation is uncertain.
Having more guns in his hands means more certainty.
Tan Xuanlin's proposal is exactly what he wants.
There's no guarantee he won't be tempted.
If we had known it,
we should have framed him for the assassination.
And the military governor would have been satisfied.
I know, I know. One shouldn't only follow the ways of the world
but also righteousness.
It seems that I need to visit this Mr. Executive Director.
Come in.
Why are you here?
The door was open, so I just entered.
Well, Tan Si forgot to keep the door closed.
Should I not be here?
No.
Give them to me.
Thank you.
Why did you want to see me?
No reason. I just wanted to see how your wound was.
Don't worry. It's just a small wound.
It's almost fully recovered.
You're in a bad mood today.
Am I?
Are you worried about the reorganization of the Tan Army?
You said that it'll happen by the end of this year.
I heard the military governor's mansion has been pushing you.
If you find it difficult, maybe I can ask my father
if he can move your men onto Mu property.
I'm not pushing you for Brother Guangyao.
I really just want to help you.
After all, my family can offer the highest salaries for your men.
You... might not be able to help me on this issue.
Don't worry. A self-interested man like me…
I'll surely ask for your help if it's needed.
I won't be passive about it. You can go.
- All right.
- Bye.
Brother Guangyao.
Brother Guangyao?
What's going on?
I made an appointment with Anton Fay.
I'll discuss with him the reorganization of the Tan Army.
You can go back and rest today.
You don't need to prepare my dinner.
Shall I go with you?
The Mu Family is influential in Shanghai.
With me speaking in your favor, you can get the task done quicker
and go back to Yue City.
I just think it's not very proper for you, a girl,
to attend such an occasion.
I'm your secretary.
It's part of my job to accompany you.
Besides, you are the esteemed Supervisor.
How can you go without an assistant?
Fine. As you wish, Miss Secretary.
[Shanghai Movie Set]
Young Uncle, you're always busy.
How did you find the time to have dinner with me?
I met with Anton Fay thanks to you.
Of course, I should show you my gratitude.
Well then, dinner won't be enough.
In order to see you, I even turned down Anton Fay's invitation.
Why does he want to see you?
Is he giving you trouble, because you tricked him into seeing me?
No. You underestimate me.
I am the Queen of Shanghai in the film circle.
All he can ever do is fawn on me.
He's meeting Junior Marshal Xu
so he asked if I can go keep Xu's female companion entertained.
I turned him down, saying I have scenes to shoot.
Isn't Junior Marshal Xu the supervisor in your Command?
Since when did the two get into contact?
Besides, isn't he unmarried?
Since when did he have a female companion?
Shuang'er, I'll take you out for dinner another day.
Tan Si, let's go.
I'm done. I'm coming.
Just leaving like that…
Who cares about dinner?
[Far East Hotel]
Please.
Executive Director Fay.
Supervisor Xu. Nice to meet you.
Executive Director Fay, I've been in Shanghai for a couple of months,
but I've been too busy to visit you.
My father has blamed me for this.
He asked me to entertain you well tonight.
And… is this young lady
Mr. Mu's daughter who came back from Japan? Right?
Let me introduce you. This is Miss Mu Wanqing.
She is my foreign language secretary now.
Miss Mu, I've seen you at some parties before but it was only a glimpse of such beauty.
Now I see you do have an outstanding disposition.
Truly, the First Daughter of Shanghai.
I'm flattered, Mr. Executive Director.
I hope in the future you will be able to advise me during my work in Shanghai.
Then it will be my pleasure to serve Miss Mu.
Mr. Executive Director, let's sit down and talk while we have dinner.
All right.
[Far East Hotel]
Commander, Miss Mu is with Supervisor Xu.
Do you still have to look out for her?
You have no idea. Anton Fay is a pervert.
Xu Guangyao can't handle him.
Executive Director Fay,
Today, the Municipal Council sent the Command a copy of a report
on the Ministry of Economy, Trade, and Industry of Japan.
The report says that Japanese cotton yarn factories are
willing to provide low-interest loans for Chinese cotton yarn factories.
Have you seen it?
Yes, I have.
But I think Miss Mu knows best
about issues about the cotton yarn industry.
After all, almost half of the cotton yarn factories here in Shanghai
belong to the Mu Family.
What's your opinion, Miss Mu?
The loans from the Japanese Chamber of Commerce. Should we take it?
Executive Director Fay, a shrewd man like you must know the pros and cons of this issue.
The Japanese cotton yarn businessmen want to take over the Chinese market using this method.
They would then dominate the market and inflate the prices.
They've already ruined the cotton yarn market in Tianjin and Qingdao.
Now they want to do it again with Shanghai's market.
If Executive Director Fay allows them, Shanghai would be in turmoil sooner or later.
Look at her. She's not only a foreign language secretary,
but an economy secretary as well.
But your family have their own cotton suppliers
and warehouses on the pier.
You also have established sales channels.
I guess you won't be affected.
But the cotton yarn industry is critical to the people's well-being.
It affects the common people.
If it falls into Japanese hands, we'd be under their control.
Just imagine, Executive Director Fay, if we'd have to get our coats for the army,
quilts for civilians, or medical gauze for hospitals from the Japanese.
I don't believe you would be at ease.
That's Mr. Mu's daughter.
You have great long-term thinking.
The Mu Family is willing to offer loans
to the cotton yarn factories so they can get through the hard times.
Also, without interest.
Aren't you openly confronting the Japanese then?
So… if I choose your side and turn the Japanese down,
then… I would seem unfair.
You don't have to worry about that, Executive Director Fay.
I have an idea where you can please both sides.
Tell me about it.
Executive Director Fay, the Tan Army is awaiting reorganization.
If they can be put into the cotton yarn factories,
the Mu Family can give the factories money in the name of their resettlement fees.
With the money to overcome their hardship,
the factories naturally won't have to take loans from the Japanese.
And the Japanese can't blame you
for preventing the factories from taking their loans.
And more importantly, by resettling the Tan Army into cotton yarn factories,
Commander Tan can't build his Chamber of Commerce militia.
So he wants to turn the army into a militia.
No wonder he doesn't want my help.
Junior Marshal Xu, look at you, beating around the bush for so long.
You simply wish to remove this militia idea.
Right?
Executive Director Fay, let me put my cards on the table.
Shanghai is under the jurisdiction of the military governor's mansion.
And the military governor's mansion won't allow any militia to exist.
So the best solution is to put them into industries, making them workers.
Miss Mu, it's a matter of your family's interest.
You are asking me to offend the Japanese and Commander Tan.
Shouldn't you have a couple of drinks with me first to show your sincerity?
Come on.
Executive Director Fay, Miss Mu can't drink.
I'll drink for her.
Miss Mu, you ask for my help, but you won't drink with me.
Well… you are not sincere enough.
Executive Director Fay, I really can't stand foreign wine.
No problem. Then…
we can drink Chinese Moutai.
[Moutai]
Right?
Hurry up. Let's drink this.
Here.
Be careful.
Executive Director Fay, Miss Mu really can't drink.
Allow me to drink with you.
Hold on, Junior Marshal Xu.
Well, if it's Miss Mu with whom I drink,
naturally, I drink one for her,
and she drinks one for me.
But if it's with you, it's inappropriate.
Well then, how does Mr. Executive Director Fay want to drink with me?
Six.
I like six. It's a good number.
Let's do this.
She drinks one,
then you drink six for her. Okay?
♫ Tears turn into heavy rain ♫
♫  We went back to when we first met  ♫
♫  I immediately saw your charming face  ♫
♫  To the endless sky and ocean  ♫
♫ I made a promise ♫
♫  Let’s let the mortals fall down with us  ♫
♫  If I forget your profile  ♫
♫  How would I put back together  ♫
♫  The memories that revived me  ♫
♫  Let’s embrace either during the sunrise of sunset  ♫
♫  I have exhausted myself in this life  ♫
♫  My whole life has become lonely  ♫
♫  Even if my vision is blurred and I can’t clearly see  ♫
♫  I’ll still sing with you on horseback  ♫
♫ Tears turn into heavy rain ♫
♫  We went back to when we first met  ♫
♫  I immediately saw your charming face  ♫
♫  To the endless sky and ocean  ♫
♫ I made a promise ♫
♫  Let’s let the mortals fall down with us  ♫
♫  If I forget your profile  ♫
♫  How would I put back together  ♫
♫  The memories that revived me  ♫
♫  Let’s embrace either during the sunrise of sunset  ♫
♫  I have exhausted myself in this life  ♫
♫  My whole life has become lonely  ♫
♫  Even if my vision is blurred and I can’t clearly see  ♫
♫  I’ll still sing with you on horseback  ♫